♪In the stormy night♪
♪The dark hair of a charming woman
is reflected in the flame of a candle♪
♪Shrouded by year after year
of memories♪
♪I can do nothing
but feign indifference♪
♪Outlining your cheeks♪
♪Together and apart,
just like quicksand♪
♪I'm meant to make peace with myself♪
♪Rebuild or crumble♪
♪Drift away in the clouds♪
♪Driving away♪
♪Your dashing pretense♪
♪A drunken dream♪
♪A person I miss♪
♪Of course I know if it's real♪
♪Even if you're just by my side♪
♪I want to hold on to you
but I can only play dumb♪
[In Blossom]
[Episode 29]
[Northwestern Military Annals]
Sir, are all the name lists here?
Yes.
This is the complete
Northwestern Military Annals.
It is updated every two years
during recruitments.
Each update has been
carefully checked for accuracy.
Sir, could you please
think about it again?
If someone wants to change
their household registration,
are there any other methods?
Unless...
What is it?
Unless it was changed
before the twelfth year
of Jingchang reign.
The late Emperor
ordered the Ministry of War
to reorganize the name lists that year.
Since then, every update has been
strictly regulated and monitored
with no loopholes.
Let's say, before the twelfth year
of Jingchang reign,
the supervision wasn't that strict,
so soldiers could register themselves
without being monitored.
You can try to find
the original register from that time.
[Shuyu Abode]
I've just brewed this ginseng soup.
Drink it while it's hot.
Look,
I'm almost recovered now.
Can I stop drinking this ginseng soup?
I've been drinking it for so many days.
I'm sick of it.
My soup
isn't as tasty as
that from the Grand Commandant's Residence.
You can ignore it.
No, it's good!
I must drink it.
It's great.
Is it tasty?
Of course.
I will brew more for you tomorrow.
Sure.
Mr. Pan. Miss Yang.
How was your investigation
at the Ministry of War?
According to the Deputy Minister of War,
if we want to investigate who changed
their household registration,
we need to dive
into the original register
before the twelfth year
of Jingchang reign.
The twelfth year of Jingchang reign?
Yes. One more thing.
Earlier in the street,
I just encountered a soldier
urgently delivering a message.
It seems there's trouble at the border.
The border?
[Grand Commandant's Residence]
[Guest List]
Darling.
Here's the guest list you wanted
for Jing's wedding.
You may check if there's anyone missing.
There's no need to check.
I will let you decide.
One more thing.
I was thinking
of the assassin
who tried to kill Mr. Pan.
Although he didn't succeed this time,
will he make another attempt?
Jing's wedding is next month.
There'll be many guests around.
If anything happens...
Rest assured.
We've learned from past mistakes.
During Jing's wedding,
I will definitely monitor
the wedding myself
to ensure everything goes smoothly.
We have a message!
Sir!
Northwestern's soldiers rebelled,
and the Jiang clan is invading.
His Majesty ordered you
to head to the palace
for an audience immediately.
Prepare the carriage now.
Yes.
Come on.
Don't stop drinking.
If I don't get you drunk today,
I won't use the name Pan anymore.
Let's see.
Let's agree first.
If you drink too much
and get scolded by your father later,
don't blame me for that.
My father is only concerned
about that illegitimate son now.
He doesn't care about me anymore.
Here, drink up.
Mr. Pan.
It's been a long time since we last met.
Mr. Sun.
Why aren't you preparing
for my brother's wedding?
Why are you drinking in the restaurant?
Don't even bring that up.
This is an order from the authorities.
Mr. Pan, you seem to be in a good mood.
Mr. Pan,
I have something to say
that might offend you.
Your elder brother
is really hard to please.
If you were the one
marrying the Princess,
I wouldn't be busy till now.
And I wouldn't have to worry much.
Who does Pan Yue think he is?
He is only good-looking.
If it weren't due to him,
I should be the one
who became the Prince Consort.
We both have noses and eyes.
Do I look ugly compared to him?
You're right...
Indeed. Since you're the legitimate son,
you should be
the one marrying the Princess.
Does your father love your brother more?
Has he secretly helped him?
This must be the reason
for the change in this marriage.
Recently, I heard
that the Prince Consort has been
hunting for assassins in the whole city.
He even raided an underground brothel.
He is well-known now.
Is your father
helping him secretly?
My father doesn't even have time
to deal with that mess.
But he, an illegitimate son,
will bring trouble to our whole family.
How could that be?
With the support of the Prince Consort,
the Pan Mansion
will definitely rise to power.
That's right.
Let me tell you a secret.
Why do you think
he chose that kind of brothel?
Why is that?
Shangguan Zhi
is actually the daughter
of the traitor Yang Ji'an.
She's Yang Caiwei.
Are you sure?
Such a bizarre thing
happened in this world.
How could Shangguan Zhi be Yang Caiwei?
Investigate
what Shangguan Zhi has done in Heyang.
If she really is the daughter
of the Yang family,
this time,
we must let her and Pan Yue
die together.
Your Highness.
Your injuries are not healed yet,
so please sit down.
Alright.
Your Highness.
Yesterday, there
was an urgent message to the capital.
Has anything serious happened?
Soldiers stationed in the northwest
mutinied over the non-payment of wages.
The Jiang clan invaded,
causing an urgency at the border.
General Lu, who is in charge
of military affairs in the northwest
finally repelled the enemy
after several hard-fought battles.
After a thorough investigation
by the court,
it was found that General Lu turned out
to be part of the Jiang clan from Luoxi.
He changed his military status
when he was still a lieutenant.
His Majesty suspects
that General Lu is a spy
from the Jiang clan
and immediately summoned my brother-in-law
and other important ministers
to discuss this matter.
As a result,
General Lu was removed
from his position as Grand Marshal
and detained in the prison
of the Law Enforcement Office.
The Grand Marshal?
He is one of the three
highest-ranking officials.
How could he be a spy of the Jiang clan?
I am also very surprised.
General Lu has a good reputation.
If he really were the mastermind
who has been planning for years,
it should have been easy for him
to take action.
Why bother
repelling the Jiang clan several times?
I think this matter
is not that simple.
By the way,
are there any discoveries
for the investigation
of Luoxi officials?
Yes, there are.
We need the Jingchang's military records
from twelve years ago.
Can Your Highness find a way
to get them?
My brother-in-law
is in charge of the military documents.
I'll go back and look for them.
Thank you.
Caiwei and I will go
and see General Lu later.
We'll find a place to meet later.
Let's meet at the Fengya Garden.
Sure.
The prison is crowded and chaotic.
Wait for me in the carriage later.
I will.
[Law Enforcement Office]
Prince Consort?
Aren't you busy
preparing for the wedding?
How come you're in this filthy prison?
The Princess asked me to see General Lu.
There's a private matter
to ask him about.
This way, Prince Consort.
Hold on.
You look good.
I thought that cut
would stop you for a few days.
Father, what is it?
It's about General Lu.
Don't get involved in this matter.
Father, rest assured.
I got the order from the Princess.
It won't bring trouble
to the Pan family.
[Healing Powder]
General Lu,
I've prepared some wine and food.
Would you like to drink with me?
Please leave.
I don't want to see anyone.
Don't you want to clear your name?
Or, are you planning to plead guilty?
The rebellion in the Northwest
has nothing to do with me.
However,
in the Emperor's eyes, I am the culprit.
What right do you have
to talk about clearing my name?
I know the person who framed you
is just like you.
He was a member of Jiang clan from Luoxi
who changed his nationality.
I am Pan Yue.
It's nice meeting you.
Are you Pan Yue? The son of Pan Jin
who's going to marry the princess.
Yes, I am.
What did you mean just now?
What do you know exactly?
A spy from the Jiang clan
has infiltrated the court.
Over a decade ago,
he made his fortune in Heyang
using money as his tool.
He gradually got a high position
within the court.
The reason why I'm here
is to get you to explain
and uncover the truth.
Your Highness.
Quan.
Why are you here in my study?
I have a friend
who asked me to find a long-lost friend
in the military.
This person changed his name.
This is why I want to look through
the past military registers
and see if I can find any clues.
You've come to the right person
for that.
I'm still keeping the military rosters
of over a decade ago.
Mine are even more complete
than what the Ministry of War has.
Let me get them for you.
Thank you, Quan.
Take your time.
[Northwestern Military Annals]
What do you want from me?
I want to ask you
about how military funds
could have gone missing.
Let me tell you something.
The military funds
for the Northwestern soldiers
are supplied from local salt taxes.
However, in recent years,
illegal salt from the Jiang clan
has been flooding the market.
Illegal salt is cheap,
leading to low prices for official salt
and difficulties
in collecting salt taxes.
The soldiers in the Northwest
are living in hardship.
Someone in the military camp
took the opportunity to cause trouble,
accusing the commanding officer
of embezzlement.
The commanding officer then sent troops
to suppress the chaos.
The chaos
resulted in the death of a soldier.
The matter led to this rebellion.
I once found a place where they hid
the smuggled salt in Heyang.
Looks like
this batch of salt likely originated
from Heyang.
If you are removed from the office,
the court will definitely appoint
a new Grand Marshal.
May I know
if you were to be removed from office,
who would be the most qualified
to take your place?
The General, Xun Jian.
Apart from him,
the other candidates
have similar qualifications.
Seems like he will get the most benefit.
Is it him?
No.
Xun Jian is from Hanzhong,
not from Luoxi.
Moreover, he is already old
and unable to work hard anymore.
Even if the Emperor appoints him,
he will most likely decline
the position.
Since you're aware of this matter,
the spy might also be aware of it.
You're right.
In that case, can you try to recall it?
Are there any other high-ranking
officials in the Ministry of War
just like you
who changed
their nationalities a decade ago?
It's hard to remember events
from over a decade ago.
Do you know if there are any
high-ranking officials
in the Ministry of War
who dealt with Heyang?
Or, perhaps
any henchman of a senior official
whose right eye is slightly yellowish?
I can't really recall.
I've heard that since you
were imprisoned,
you've been on a hunger strike
as a form of protest.
You should eat something first.
Let's think while eating.
General Lu, why are you
rolling up your sleeves like that?
We Luoxi people have been riding horses
since we were young.
We're not used to
the attire of the Central Plains.
Especially
these inconvenient wide sleeves.
So I've developed the habit
of rolling up my sleeves when eating.
Darling, can we eat now?
Look,
this freshly steamed sea bass
with osmanthus is good.
It's him.
[Northwestern Military Annals]
Your Highness.
Have you found it?
Not yet.
I have another one here.
Let's see if it's in here.
[Jia Quan,
native of Zhuo County, Youzhou]
[Yuchi Changqing,
native of Jiang clan, Luoxi]
It seems that Your Highness found it.
The mastermind
is actually Grand Commandant Jia.
Zhuo Lanjiang tried to assassinate me
in the Grand Commandant's Residence.
Now that I think about it,
it was Jia Quan who led me
step by step
towards Zhuo Lanjiang's hideout.
Moreover,
with his official position and records,
he's one of the successors.
With the Empress' favor
for the Princesses,
and a few good words from her
in front of the Emperor,
he will definitely stand out.
Grand Commandant Jia
must have used Mrs. Jia
in pushing the wedding forward.
The Princess went to look for the records
at the Grand Commandant's Residence.
If Grand Commandant Jia catches her,
she will be in danger.
It's almost time to meet her.
I wonder if she's still
at the Grand Commandant's Residence.
You go to Fengya Garden first. I'll go
to the Grand Commandant's Residence.
Let's split up and find her.
Okay.
No... No.
I didn't find the name.
I'll think of another way.
Thank you, Quan.
Are you sure you want to go?
Look,
how gentle and beautiful she is.
I must have done something great
in my past life
to have been able to marry her.
If you don't want your sister
to end up like your parents,
you'd better behave and listen to me.
From the beginning,
was it a conspiracy
that you married my sister?
Twelve years ago,
I killed your parents with my own hands.
But
I spared both of you.
Although your sister
has had a leg problem since then,
she married me.
Consider this as repaying my mercy
for not killing her.
This is such a wonderful thing.
How could you call it a conspiracy?
If you dare harm me and my sister,
Her Majesty will never let you off!
I have thousands of ways
to explain to the Empress.
As long as I make it
look like an accident,
nobody will suspect me
since I have always been
a loving husband.
My sister knows nothing.
I beg you to spare her.
I will do anything you tell me to.
You're a smart person.
Don't worry.
I don't want to be so ruthless.
As long as you promise me one thing,
I will keep
your sister safe.
What is it?
Kill a person for me.
[Fengya Garden]
Is the Princess here yet?
She has just arrived,
and she is now waiting in the room.
Miss Shangguan,
you still have the cheek
to come to the Princess?
Your Highness.
Your Highness, what's happened?
I'm sorry.
Miss, where is the Princess?
I don't know.
I haven't seen Her Highness in a while.
I'm going to look for her now.
Mr. Pan?
You seem to be in a hurry.
Has something happened?
It's nothing important
but some trivial matter
regarding the wedding.
I want to discuss it with the Princess.
Since she's not around,
I'm leaving now.
Her Highness must be
teaching Shangguan Zhi a lesson.
I'll go take a look.
Murder!
Shangguan Zhi,
the daughter of a merchant,
was caught murdering Princess Changle
out of jealousy, with solid evidence.
Three days later,
a trial will be held
- at Law Enforcement Office
- Nice!
- to be shown as an exemplar.
- Great!
[Notice]
How dare the daughter of a merchant
act treacherously
and murder the Princess.
- Exactly!
- She's really audacious!
If there were nothing between Mr. Pan
and Shangguan Zhi,
this tragedy wouldn't have happened.
Exactly. In just four months,
two wives of Mr. Pan died.
Nobody would believe he's innocent.
I've also heard
that his mother committed suicide
because of him.
A person like him
is still a disaster
even if he looks good.
I agree.
Why would such a person exist?
A perfect person like Mr. Pan...
- How disappointing!
- Yes!
Let's leave...
- Let's leave.
- Let's go.
- It's none of our business.
- Let's leave.
- Let's go.
This is unbelievable.
[Biography of Mr. Pan]
What a fair, young lady.
It's a pity
that you'll be executed
because of a man.
I like your strong personality.
- Forget it.
- No...
This case involves the imperial family.
Let's not get ourselves into trouble.
Let's starve her for a few days
and see her suffer.
- Let's leave.
- Wait...
- Leave.
- Look at this girl.
- Fair and young. What a waste.
- Let's go now!
Your Highness.
Your Highness, what's happened?
I'm sorry.
Your Highness!
Jia Quan
is using my sister's life
to make me do this.
I'm sorry
for all that I put you through!
Please don't blame me.
Your Highness...
Tell my sister this.
The incident of Qixia Ridge
due to spouse.
Your Highness!
Sir.
What's going on?
Mr. Pan is begging Master
to let him see Shangguan Zhi
at the Law Enforcement Office.
Master rejected the request.
He's been kneeling all day.
Isn't this my arrogant eldest brother?
Why are you looking so embarrassed now?
I almost didn't recognize you just now.
Seeing your pitiful look
makes me feel truly sorry for you.
Our father is unbelievable.
Not only did he reject your request,
but he also doesn't let you eat.
I've got something hot here for you.
Eat it while it's still warm.
Here.
Yue.
Why are you doing this to yourself?
At least have a bit of it.
Hui, that's enough!
Father.
♪I wish upon you all that is well♪
The case has been handed over
to the Grand Commandant Jia.
There's no use for you to be begging me.
I know.
I just want to see her.
You should leave.
Even if you kneel here until you die,
I won't let you see her.
If so, I will kneel until I die.
♪Longing turns to ashes,
ashes scatter to thin air♪
♪Wait for a chance to start anew
after the past life ends♪
♪Despite countless thoughts♪
♪What should I do with my aching body?♪
♪Attracted by the setting moon
and refuse to leave♪
♪Don't forget the way you came♪
♪Even with great tact♪
♪How do you plan for love and revenge?♪
♪Longing turns to ashes,
ashes scatter to thin air♪
♪Wait for a chance to start anew
after the past life ends♪
♪Despite countless thoughts♪
♪What should I do
with my aching body♪
Let's see how long you can endure this.
♪Embracing the night breeze,
holding a jade hairpin in my hand♪
♪A bright heart worn by tragedies♪
This child is so fair and tender.
He is sure blessed.
Of course I must give him a nice name.
Let's name him
Pan Yue.
What do you think?
He is my firstborn.
I hope our ancestors
will give him their blessings
and grant him a lifetime
of peace and joy.
Yue.
- Yue.
Master,
the teacher told me earlier
that Young Master's essay
is very well written.
He complimented it well.
He called him
a child with splendid future prospects
who will grow up to be
a brilliant young man.
Young Master has been waiting here
for you to read his essay.
When I was at the Pan Mansion
delivering things today,
I saw Mr. Pan's son.
He is really handsome.
He looks nothing like his father.
I heard from the servants
at the Pan Mansion.
They don't even know
if he is really Mr. Pan's son.
Got it.
Master!
Something bad happened! Madam is...
Madam!
Madam.
Madam...
Mother!
The rumors hurt,
and only death can prove my innocence.
Our child is innocent.
Please take good care of him.
If I won't let you see her,
are you really planning to kneel
until you die?
This is the only thing I can do.
If the father and the son fight,
the family is not harmonious.
What is the meaning of me being prudent?
If your deceased mother knew about this,
she would blame me.
Get up.
Yue!
♪Like the dew, we wait for the glimmer
of light to greet the morning♪
♪How many looks do we need
to affirm each other?♪
♪It's sincerity that fools me♪
♪But it's seriousness that traps you♪
♪The depth of the past
is best left unexplored♪
♪How many more falls
do I have to experience♪
♪Before I can face love
and hatred with grace?♪
♪Don't ask if it's a moment♪
♪Of liberation or cowardice to let go♪
♪Perhaps it's a misstep into your heart,
it's a hasty feeling♪
♪It's an unwillingness
to be just a passer-by with you♪
♪Even if I were to die
after a few intense struggles♪
♪I would have lived a life worth living♪
♪If grasses and trees are sharp blades,
if mountains and waters are temples♪
♪It's good to be alive
even for a short moment♪
♪I wish I could be worthy
of the thoughts♪
♪And I wish I could be worthy
of the love♪
♪Perhaps it's a misstep into your heart,
it's a hasty feeling♪
♪It's an unwillingness
to be just a passer-by with you♪
♪Even if I were to die
after a few intense struggles♪
♪I would have lived a life worth living♪
♪If grasses and trees are sharp blades,
if mountains and waters are temples♪
♪It's good to be alive
even for a short moment♪
♪I wish I could be worthy
of the thoughts♪
♪And I wish I could be worthy
of the love♪
♪Be worthy of this love♪