♪In the stormy night♪
♪The dark hair of a charming woman
is reflected in the flame of a candle♪
♪Shrouded by year
after year of memories♪
♪I can do nothing
but feign indifference♪
♪Outlining your cheeks♪
♪Together and apart,
just like quicksand♪
♪I'm meant to make peace with myself♪
♪Rebuild or crumble♪
♪Drift away in the clouds♪
♪Driving away♪
♪Your dashing pretense♪
♪A drunken dream♪
♪A person I miss♪
♪Of course I know if it's real♪
♪Even if you're just by my side♪
♪I want to hold on to you
but I can only play dumb♪
[In Blossom]
[Episode 27]
What is your name?
Zhi.
You know Dancing Among the Clouds?
I have been practicing with Miss Yun,
so I know it.
Okay, you are selected.
Take the girls away.
[Luoyi]
Have we arrived so soon?
It was left behind by Miss Shangguan.
They went this way.
No personal belongings
are allowed in Shiluo Garden.
Girls,
your purses,
sachets, handkerchiefs
- must be removed
- So that place is Shiluo Garden.
- and left here.
- This should be the place.
I'm so sorry.
Sir, there is no trace
of fragrant powder ahead there.
I don't find any on my side either.
That's strange.
Is there something wrong, sir?
This house is small.
It doesn't look like a place
used to entertain dignitaries.
Moreover,
they have always acted
mysteriously and inconspicuously.
This house is close
to the downtown area.
The sound of musical instruments
would be easily heard by passers-by.
Ze,
go and see
if this house has a back door.
Miss Yun, ask around
about this house.
Okay.
Yes, sir.
Fill it.
Beauty.
Have a drink with me.
Drink up, sir.
Come on.
Shiluo Garden.
Sir, my clothes are new.
This should be it.
Keep drinking, keep pouring.
Pour it for me.
Come on.
Come on, beauty.
Drink.
Girls,
starting today,
you are part of Shiluo Garden.
This Shiluo Garden
is not a usual place of entertainment.
As long as all of you are obedient,
in the future,
you will enjoy endless glory and wealth.
That's a lot.
Look.
How nice.
Shower and get changed.
After that, wait to be summoned.
Yes, madam.
Hurry up.
How lovely.
Indeed.
Mr. Pan, this house has no back door.
Sir,
I just asked the neighbor next door.
They said no one lives here.
- How about at night?
- I asked several families.
They all say this is an abandoned house.
No one has lived here for a long time.
This is bad.
There must be a secret passage here.
Search.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Found it!
Well, look! I've never
worn such beautiful clothes in my life!
Yeah, look at this hairpin ring.
I bit it just now. It really is gold!
Just as the legends say, Shiluo Garden
is full of gold and jewels.
We will surely have a good life
in the future.
Yes.
When Yunchang first came here,
she must have thought that she would be
wearing gold and jade in the future,
leading a life of wealth and honor.
Little did she know
that this magnificent Shiluo Garden
is actually a devil's cave
that devours people whole.
Stop there.
Madam Wan.
What are you doing here?
I... I want to relieve myself.
Shiluo Garden has its rules.
See what you should,
and don't see what you shouldn't.
Otherwise, you will be like her.
Not only deaf,
but also mute.
She looks pathetic now, right?
Ten years ago,
she was also the most popular girl
in Shiluo Garden.
Because she slapped the lead dancer,
she was punished by Mr. Zuo.
Finally,
she ended up like this.
Take a look at this sachet.
Embroidered sachet.
Come and take a look.
- Come and take a look at this sachet.
- Take a look at this paper umbrella.
Embroidered sachet.
Sachet, embroidered sachet.
Greetings, sir.
Fill it already.
- Come on, sir. Let's drink.
- Come on.
I'll fill it for you.
Here.
Come on.
Beauty, come and have a drink.
Come on, drink.
This place is securely guarded.
Looks like there is no way
to send a message to Pan Yue.
I hope he can see the clues
I left behind
and find this place as soon as possible.
The guests in this room
are the most exalted
among our distinguished guests.
Perform well.
If something goes wrong,
even I can't protect you girls.
Yes, madam.
Mr. Zuo, Mr. He,
the girls are ready.
So he is the owner of Shiluo Garden.
Could he be the mastermind
behind the Ripple Organization?
Mr. Zuo,
we'll talk about those matters later.
Let's enjoy the dance now.
Sure.
Let's get started, girls.
Yes.
Good.
I heard that this dance
is Shiluo Garden's unique skill.
Sure enough, seeing it once is better
than hearing it a hundred times.
Thank you, Mr. Zuo.
Mr. He,
Shiluo Garden's sincerity to you
is not merely this dance.
You are asking me for a favor.
But until now,
I haven't even met your master
in person.
I don't know
who he is.
If an accident happens…
Don't worry, Mr. He.
The reason our master never showed up
is all for your safety.
If something happens in the future,
the investigations won't
find their way to you, Mr. He.
It seems like Mr. Zuo
is just the steward of Shiluo Garden.
There is another mastermind behind him.
Since you have said so, Mr. Zuo,
if I am to refuse again,
I might come off as disagreeable.
The thing you requested is here.
Thank you, Mr. He.
Madam Wan, serve Mr. He well.
Make sure Mr. He is satisfied.
Rest assured, Mr. Zuo.
It seems that the real purpose
of Shiluo Garden
is to collude with imperial officials
and do some shady businesses.
What exactly did Mr. He give to Mr. Zuo?
Zhi.
Madam.
Mr. He wanted you to serve him alone.
Hurry up and go in.
Come on.
A hat with seven pearl beads
inlaid on the top.
What? Do you want the guards
to search the streets now?
That's right.
If you search the streets now,
you will definitely alert the enemy.
The later we find her,
the more danger she would be in.
Okay, if your mind is set,
then do it.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Three pairs of pearl earrings,
a total of 12 beads.
A pair of gold bracelets.
A string of agate beads.
Two strings of amber beads.
Mr. Sun.
The number of pearls on the gift list
seems to be wrong.
Who is there?
Your Highness!
Are you okay, Your Highness?
I'm fine. Quickly, lead your men
to chase the assassin.
Mr. Sun, take care of Her Highness.
I will lead the imperial guards
to capture the assassin.
Yes.
Beauty, that dance you did just now
really took away my soul.
Sir, please have something to eat.
Mr. He.
The night is still young.
Why should you rush?
Why don't I play a drinking game
with you?
What kind of drinking game
do you want to play?
Why don't we play
guessing the hidden coin?
Sure.
Guess, which one?
Beauty, you guessed it right.
Mr. He, please drink.
It's your turn to drink this time.
Guess again.
Left side.
Impressive, beauty.
I'm just lucky. Drink up, Mr. He.
It's obvious
that whenever you are about to win,
you will slightly raise your eyebrow.
Come on, let's continue.
Mr. He, let me warm you
a few more pots of good wine.
How can I get in?
Go and warm some pots of good wine
for Mr. He.
Also,
Mr. He said he wanted something
to spice things up.
Yes.
Search every house!
Yes, sir!
Sir, let's continue.
Beauty, are you trying to get me drunk?
If you are afraid of losing
and don't want to play, just say so.
Why bother acting like a sore loser?
So what if I lose to a beauty?
Then let's have one game
to determine the outcome.
The loser has to down this pot.
Mr. He.
I want to ride a horse!
Sir! Are you okay, sir?
Go away!
Help!
- Sir!
- Somebody, help!
- Come quickly.
- Hurry, something happened to Mr. He.
- Hurry up, he is an important guest!
- Sir!
If something goes wrong with him,
we can't afford it!
Be careful, Mr. He.
Mr. He!
It turns out that the pattern
painted on the token
is not a water ripple at all.
It's just a part
of this ram horn totem.
Water... Water ripples are...
Yang...
Yang.
So, the "Yang" mentioned by Gu Yong
before he died
is not the surname Yang,
but referring to the rams.
[Custom Clearance Document]
[Salt Distribution Commandant,
He Hongyi, to govern the prisons.]
Customs clearance document?
Salt Distribution Commandant?
Could this be related to the salt
in the back mountains
of Xinzheng Academy?
Yang Caiwei, please be safe.
It is such
a huge underground pleasure house.
If it is really hidden
among the streets,
there must be some differences.
I can definitely find it.
I can find it for sure.
Keep searching.
Yes, sir.
May my god hear my call.
Darkness, cover me.
Darkness, give me godly power.
May the shadow of darkness
spread throughout the world.
May your lives
be swallowed up by darkness.
Master.
What is it?
Mr. He went crazy after drinking.
He is awake now.
Mr. He said
it was a new courtesan
who secretly put
excessive five minerals powder
in his wine.
I'm afraid an outsider
might have sneaked in.
Kill her.
Yes.
I have to find a way to escape quickly.
You, go over there.
Even if you have to turn
the place upside down,
find her.
Yes, sir!
What's going on?
I'm sorry, sir.
There's a thief in Shiluo Garden today.
Hurry up.
How disappointing.
- Sir, please don't be angry.
- We'll send you back.
You go and search over there.
I'll take this side.
We must find her!
Yes!
Hold on.
So much swill. Is this all yours?
Yes.
[Zhu's Textiles]
Everyone, search.
Let's go.
Search every corner.
Any clues over there?
No.
- Go there and have a look.
- Yes, sir.
Nothing here either.
Nothing. Go there and have a look.
Quiet.
Yes.
Goodbye, sir.
Let's go.
I'm expecting your next visit.
Goodbye, sir.
Take care.
Sir, goodbye.
It was all okay.
Be careful.
I'll help you.
Madam Wan, we couldn't find her
in the backyard.
Where did she go?
Madam Wan, bad news.
Some imperial guards broke in.
What? Imperial guards?
What are you doing?
This is a private residence.
Even imperial guards have no right
to break in here.
An assassination attempt on Her Highness.
We are searching for the culprit.
What does that have to do with us?
The owner of this house
is not someone you can afford to offend.
Where is that girl named Zhi?
I have no idea.
I'm looking for her too.
Search the place.
Follow me.
Over here, catch him.
Young Master.
How is it? Did you find her?
I've searched the place.
I couldn't find her.
But a carriage just left
from the back door.
However,
the carriage belongs to us,
the Pan Family.
[Pan Mansion]
Where is she?
How dare you?
Hand over Shangguan Zhi.
Otherwise, don't blame me
for ignoring our blood ties.
Shangguan Zhi.
Think it over before you speak.
Do you want Shangguan Zhi
or Yang Ji'an's daughter,
Yang Caiwei?
How did you know?
Put down your sword
before talking to your father.
That day, I went to see you
to talk about the marriage.
However, I saw
you with her.
Caiwei.
It's good to have you here.
You kept calling her Caiwei
and talking about your childhood.
Recalling all the various incidents,
you never liked Shangguan Zhi.
How could you suddenly
fall in love with her?
Although I don't know what happened,
I guess
Yang Caiwei didn't die.
She's disguised
as Shangguan Zhi instead.
Moreover,
she's even investigating
Yang Ji'an's old case with you.
Am I right?
Yang Ji'an's family
was murdered back then.
As his friend,
you watched from the sidelines
without doing anything about it.
To this day,
do you still want
to be their accomplice?
Not sparing even Yang Ji'an's daughter?
Am I so despicable in your eyes?
If I were an accomplice,
Yang Caiwei would have died
a hundred times.
Then, why did you show up
at the Shiluo Garden?
I was invited there by my colleagues.
I have no intention
of joining any party,
but I have to do things accordingly.
I took Yang Caiwei away
because I was afraid
that this would implicate the Pan family.
I can return her to you now,
but
you have to answer my question first.
You and Her Highness
are getting married soon.
Why do you still want to be with her?
This matter has progressed this far.
You're setting yourself on fire,
did you know that?
Do you want to end up like Yang Ji'an?
I only live once.
So what if I die?
You are deceiving the Emperor!
I know.
That's why, a few months ago,
I promised you
to sever my ties with the Pan family.
So what if you could find her?
That's my own business.
I won't bother you anymore.
Fine.
I'll tell you where she is,
but starting from today,
your ties with the Pan family
will be severed.
It's a deal.
Sever your ties?
Fine.
It's my fault.
I tried to become associated
with the imperial families
but ended up
getting into this muddy water.
But I don't understand.
Why is Her Highness willing
to destroy her reputation
to act in this show with you?
Not everyone is like you, Father.
You only care about yourself.
Men,
bring her out.
Caiwei.
How are you? Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Leave.
Remember.
I've never seen you two tonight.
Let's go.
Anyway,
we have to thank your father
for helping me this time.
I know.
I'm very grateful to him.
But it seems like I can never
talk properly with him.
What are you laughing at?
Thank you for your good luck.
Oh, right.
Did you find anything inside?
I entered a secluded room
in Shiluo Garden.
There was a tapestry inside.
The pattern on it
was exactly the same as the ripples.
When put together,
it looks like a ram horn.
So the pattern we have been searching for
was not ripples,
but ram horns.
Ram horns pattern.
Does their organization
worship rams?
Oh, right.
I saw a middle-aged man
who was worshiping.
I guess
he might be the mastermind
behind the Ripple Organization.
Did you see his face clearly?
The room was too dark,
so I couldn't see it clearly.
Middle-aged man.
Is it the one
with the slightly yellowish right eye?
That is the master of Shiluo Garden,
Mr. Zuo.
Shiluo Garden has secret ties
with the imperial officials.
He is the one handling everything
personally.
I saw him hosting
the Salt Distribution Commandant.
The official gave him
a customs clearance document.
Salt Distribution Commandant?
That batch of illegal salt
in the back hill of Xinzheng Academy
might have something to do with them.
I think so too.
The Salt Distribution Commandant's
customs clearance document
allows the bearer access anywhere.
But where is he going to ship
this batch of illegal salt to?
How long has Pan Yue been back
in the capital?
How did he find the Shiluo Garden?
Master, I checked
the guest list for Shiluo Garden today.
I found that Pan Jin was also on it.
Could Pan Jin
be working from within?
Pan Jin?
He has been pretending to be a coward
all his life.
Does he even have the balls to do so?
Master, what should we do now?
Send someone to investigate
and find out if Pan Jin
is involved in this matter.
Yes.
By the way,
the traitor has been eliminated.
This is the token I found at his house.
Zhuo Lanjiang
is more direct than his father.
I really need to think about
how to use him.
♪Like the dew, we wait for the glimmer
of light to greet the morning♪
♪How many looks do we need
to affirm each other?♪
♪It's sincerity that fools me♪
♪But it's seriousness that traps you♪
♪The depth of the past
is best left unexplored♪
♪How many more falls
do I have to experience♪
♪Before I can face love
and hatred with grace?♪
♪Don't ask if it's a moment♪
♪Of liberation or cowardice to let go♪
♪Perhaps it's a misstep into your heart,
it's a hasty feeling♪
♪It's an unwillingness
to be just a passer-by with you♪
♪Even if I were to die
after a few intense struggles♪
♪I would have lived a life worth living♪
♪If grasses and trees are sharp blades,
if mountains and waters are temples♪
♪It's good to be alive
even for a short moment♪
♪I wish I could be worthy
of the thoughts♪
♪And I wish I could be worthy
of the love♪
♪Perhaps it's a misstep into your heart,
it's a hasty feeling♪
♪It's an unwillingness
to be just a passer-by with you♪
♪Even if I were to die
after a few intense struggles♪
♪I would have lived a life worth living♪
♪If grasses and trees are sharp blades,
if mountains and waters are temples♪
♪It's good to be alive
even for a short moment♪
♪I wish I could be worthy
of the thoughts♪
♪And I wish I could be worthy
of the love♪
♪Be worthy of this love♪