♪In the stormy night♪
♪The dark hair of a charming woman
is reflected in the flame of a candle♪
♪Shrouded by year
after year of memories♪
♪I can do nothing but feign indifference♪
♪Outlining your cheeks♪
♪Together and apart,
just like quicksand♪
♪I'm meant to make peace with myself♪
♪Rebuild or crumble♪
♪Drift away in the clouds♪
♪Driving away♪
♪Your dashing pretense♪
♪A drunken dream♪
♪A person I miss♪
♪Of course I know if it's real♪
♪Even if you're just by my side♪
♪I want to hold on to you
but I can only play dumb♪
[In Blossom]
[Episode 4]
[Peace and prosperity]
Ling.
Young Lady.
Where is my brother?
Mr. Shangguan had to go back
to the capital to take care of business
and left early in the morning.
He didn't want
to disturb your sleep.
This is the money he left for you.
And there's more.
Come in.
Greetings, Young Lady.
They're the maids
Mr. Shangguan hired overnight.
Mr. Shangguan said
your life here must be
the same as in the capital
and you mustn't suffer a bit.
In the future,
how should I explain everything
to Shangguan Lan?
Do you need anything else?
No.
Send them back and clear out the house.
Let's move.
Move?
[Heyang Magistrate's Office]
Mr. Pan.
Are you sure you want Miss Shangguan
to go to the county yamen?
It's going to be a real mess.
It's all right.
It won't take long
for her to back off.
[Heyang Magistrate's Office]
Yue.
Shangguan Zhi.
The county yamen is an office.
Yes, Mr. Pan.
What does this mean?
Mr. Pan, my brother's gone back
to the capital,
and Sunrise Garden has been cleared out.
If you refuse to let me stay
at the county yamen,
I'll have to live outside.
Mr. Pan, please take me in.
You said yesterday
that you'd do anything,
even serving tea and water, right?
Yes.
That's good.
Come on.
Come on, place your bets!
Put in more money.
Bet more and you'll win more!
Quick!
Place your bet!
Let's see if I can beat you.
It's got to be small.
- Listen to me.
- Alright.
Small.
Liu, what are you doing?
Pick it up. Come on.
Yeah.
Come on, go on!
Quick.
Come on.
Seriously.
- Come on.
- Go on.
- I've been unlucky lately.
Come on, again.
Bet on big.
Pan...
Mr. Pan.
Aren't you taking office tomorrow?
Every evil person has had his day.
It's your worst day.
I know you.
Yes.
I was there when you broke
into the courtroom last time.
You were at the Ghost Market, too.
He's the Imperial Censor,
Pan Yue.
Mr. Pan,
I'm very impressed
with your grace.
To be under your command this time
is a fulfillment of my wish.
You're quick-witted.
I'm new here
and I need a lot of advice
from you in the future.
Mr. Pan, you flatter me.
I have just been staying in Heyang
for a little longer.
If you've come across things important,
I can still give you advice.
Tell me what's the important things
for an official in Heyang.
Sir,
have you heard
that Heyang has a magisterial talisman?
Go ahead.
Sir, please take a look.
[Silver Rain Terrace]
Silver Rain shrouds Heyang,
[Hundred Flowers Court]
brothel away from Hundred Flowers Court,
[Life and Death House]
gambling on life and death for money,
[Relief Hall]
Relief Hall helps countless households.
To secure your position,
remember the Four Greats.
In Heyang,
the county yamen is just a display.
The Four Greats
are the real masters of Heyang.
Don't offend them.
This is really very beneficial.
What's your name?
Liu.
Liu,
what should I do
if the Four Greats
are involved in future cases?
The case doesn't matter at all.
Sir, the first thing to investigate
is the identity
of the plaintiff and the defendant.
That which is favorable
to the four clans is the truth.
Or else, it's an offense.
If we handle the case this way,
you'll be in peace in Heyang.
Ze,
did you hear everything?
What's the punishment
for being such an official?
Officials who embezzle, accept,
and pay bribes
are treated the same as those who steal
and are sentenced to death, exile,
whipping, caning,
and no amnesty shall be given.
I've been ordered
by the Emperor to govern Heyang.
On my first day in office,
you taught me
how to be a corrupt official.
Such intentions are inexcusable.
Take him down.
Give him 20 strokes of the cane
and a three-month
suspension of his salary
as a warning to others.
Sir.
Go.
Sir, I won't do it again. Sir.
Sir.
Sir, I won't do it again.
Shangguan Zhi.
Young Lady.
Get him caned.
Me?
You want me to be the bad guy?
So you won't be the one who gets hated.
Yes, Mr. Pan.
It's so heavy.
You said you wanted to punish the evil
and uphold the good.
But are you condoning
these corrupt officials?
You'd better go back home
and live in comfort.
Although Pan Yue
is to build up his authority,
he gives me a chance to vent my anger.
These enablers of evil like this one
must be taught a stern lesson.
Sir, I'm done.
What about you guys?
No.
Sir, don't blame me.
I'm new here.
I'm sick
of the way Liu works.
Am I right, guys?
Yes.
Although I'm a registrar,
I never forget
that I'm a disciple of the sage.
I've advised
the former magistrate and Liu,
but they won't budge.
Fortunately, you're here, Mr. Pan,
so I can fulfill my ambition.
Good.
In two hours,
I want to see this place
look like a real county yamen.
Hurry up.
Let's go. Come on.
Hang in there.
Sir,
did I do a good job?
Is there anything else I can do?
Not bad.
It would be a shame for you
to be a handyman with your intelligence.
You need to be put to good use.
You flatter me.
I'll do anything
to help the magistracy.
Go and settle down
and meet me in the second hall tomorrow.
Put it over there.
Be careful.
Close the curtain later.
Okay.
Put this pot of flowers in.
It's Young Lady's favorite.
Be careful.
Women have also to go
all out chasing after men.
She even came
to the county yamen for him.
How bold of her.
Come on.
She's not to be messed with.
Be careful.
Young Lady, look.
I've tidied up a bit.
Are you satisfied?
You call that a little tidying up?
I haven't done it yet.
I'm getting to it now.
No.
I'm a lowly clerk at the county yamen,
not the young lady
in the Shangguan family.
You don't have to be so extravagant.
Yue didn't like me in the past, right?
It's all because I've been spoiled.
So,
I'm going to show him some
of my new hard-working self now.
Maybe
he'll grow to accept me.
It's like those plays
where the prince
doesn't like the princess at all
and prefers the poor girls.
You could interpret it that way.
I got it.
That's Yue's room?
Yes.
I can't believe it went so smoothly.
Pan Yue, you're not that hard
to deal with.
Wait and see.
Sooner or later,
I'm going to make you
pay for what you owe me.
Young Lady,
I've prepared a set of maid's clothes
as you ordered yesterday.
You... You're overdoing it.
Isn't this too conspicuously poor?
If it's not conspicuous,
how can you attract Mr. Pan's attention?
That's true.
I'm a woman
who wants to achieve something great.
Why should I be afraid
of being conspicuous?
I just wonder
what kind of job Mr. Pan
will assign you.
Based on his vindictive nature,
I'm sure he'll get back at me.
I can only play it by ear.
Sir.
What do you want me to do?
You don't look like
your usual self today.
I've just changed into a plain outfit.
It's not just the outfit.
It's like you're a new person.
I survived a catastrophe,
so I'm trying to make a fresh start.
Survived a catastrophe?
I haven't asked you
where you went after you made a scene
in my bridal chamber that night
and how the accident happened.
Shangguan Zhi
was in Sunrise Garden that night?
What was she doing there?
Why don't you say something?
That day,
when I saw you marry another woman,
I was so upset that I left
after writing a suicide note.
I wanted to find a place
to be alone for a few days,
but I didn't expect
to be robbed by bandits.
I jumped out of the carriage,
fell down the hill, and fainted.
They probably thought I was dead
and that's why I survived.
It's quite thrilling, wasn't it?
It's almost like a play.
Yes.
Life is like a play.
There are many more
dramatic stories than this.
This is just nothing.
Sir,
why do you suddenly care about me?
Nothing.
These days,
when I think of all the things
that have happened between you and me,
I've indeed let you down,
and that's what brought us
to this situation.
What does he want?
I shouldn't bother you
with this kind of thing.
No matter what happened in the past,
I'm in the county yamen now.
I'll keep my manners and work hard.
It seems
I'm the one who's stuck in my ways.
In the past few days,
I've been trying to think
of a job for you.
I've finally come up
with something suitable.
But I don't know
if you're willing to do it.
I am.
Sir, I'm at your disposal.
The registrar is old,
so you'll assist him
by taking notes of the trial
and making announcements.
You mustn't leave my side
without any exceptional reason.
I'm the one who's investigating him,
but now it's like he's watching me.
Sir,
this is the last month's case files
that have been inventoried.
Put them in the archive.
Yes, Sir.
I have to take a chance
to find the case file
of Shangguan Zhi's fall in the archive.
Sir,
the carriage is ready.
It's time for you to go to the monument.
What's wrong?
Are you not going?
Useless official!
Get out of the carriage,
you useless official!
What's going on?
What's this about?
Is she trying to make a scene?
Who is that?
- I have no idea.
- Let's go and take a look.
It's Mr. Pan.
It's him.
What's going on?
It's Mr. Pan.
- Yes.
- What's it about?
Who are you? Do you have any complaints?
I don't have any complaints.
I just don't like the way
you officials act and show off.
You're shameless!
You're a disgrace!
Nice curse.
Do you know
that insulting an official in public
is punishable by 30 strokes
of the cane and half a year in jail?
That's right.
Any other magistrate
would have arrested you.
Only Mr. Pan has the decency
not to bother with a shrew like you.
Leave now.
Darling.
Why is he here?
Mr. Pan, I'm Sun Wancai.
I'm sorry for the rudeness
of my wife.
Thank you, Mr. Pan, for forgiving us.
Darling,
come home with me.
What a useless official!
Take me to jail if you can.
Otherwise, I'll curse you day and night.
I'll make your infamy
spread all over Heyang!
She's doing it on purpose.
Don't be so hard-headed.
Sir,
I think you should
punish this woman severely
as a warning to others.
You want to help her?
I...
How could I have wanted to help her?
I think she's just too rude
and is too much of a troublemaker.
She must be punished severely.
You want to take your wife home?
Of course I do.
Your wife
looks disoriented and incoherent.
Is she ill?
According to the law,
a disoriented person is exempt
from punishment.
Yes.
My wife
is disoriented.
Please forgive her.
But I need to make it clear to you
that if you take her back,
you will be solely responsible
for her behavior.
Can you do that?
I'll keep a close eye on her at home.
If it happens again,
I'll take full responsibility.
Okay, you can take her back now.
Thank you. Sir.
Send her home now.
Useless official!
Darling.
Your eyes have been gnawed by pigs
and your conscience eaten by dogs!
Do you know how many wives
were beaten to death by Sun Wancai?
You look so upright,
but you're an enabler!
You're just like them!
She's acting up again.
Wait.
Shangguan Zhi,
as I mentioned,
what's the punishment
for cursing an official
in public?
30 strokes of the cane
and half a year in jail.
The offender, Mrs. Sun, is disoriented,
so her behavior is
the sole responsibility of her husband,
Sun Wancai.
Sir,
he's a member of the Four Greats.
Arrest him.
Come on, arrest him.
How dare you?
You set me up, huh?
Do you know who I am?
Threatening an official
is an additional offense.
Fine.
Wait and see.
Good!
Mr. Justice,
I'm sorry for my offense.
Please don't punish me.
Get up.
My jail
is not for good people.
What a hypocrite.
I wonder what Mr. Pan is going to say.
Yeah.
What's going on?
Pan Yue, the new magistrate of Heyang,
I hereby inform the people
of this place with all sincerity.
I will devote myself
to the concerns and welfare of you all
in return for the Emperor's favor.
It sounds sincere.
Mr. Pan is a good official.
Yes.
Mr. Pan,
my name is Gan Juncai,
a native of Heyang.
I'd like to gift
two Night-luminescent Pearls to you.
Two Night-luminescent Pearls?
Ze, jot it down.
My name is Huang Yanbin.
Congratulations on your promotion.
Two boxes of books have been
delivered to your residence.
Two boxes of books?
Books are full of wonders.
Please check it out.
Ze, jot it down.
My name is Song Mingxuan,
and my courtesy name is Rui'ang.
It's my honor to meet you, Sir.
What's your gift?
A jade scepter.
A jade scepter?
Okay. Jot it down.
Sir, I've prepared a feast for you.
Please do come.
[Heyang Magistrate's Office]
Young Lady,
When I passed by the main hall,
I saw Mr. Pan hosting a banquet.
I wonder who the guests are.
It's so lively.
It's a bunch of rich new friends.
Mr. Pan has only just arrived in Heyang.
He's made a bunch of rich new friends?
All that glitters is not gold.
Keep an eye on the main hall.
Yes.
I have to find the evidence
as soon as possible
to bring Pan Yue to justice.
Sir,
these are the unsolved cases
accumulated in Heyang over the years.
Please send someone to investigate, sir.
Is there any unsolved case here?
Can you see it?
No.
Sir, all of these are unsolved.
Including this.
Well...
Sir,
these aren't just pieces of paper
with no feelings.
They're lives.
Master.
Mr. Jiang, you're old.
You're mentally disturbed
and a little crazy.
You should retire as soon as possible.
Sir!
I'm not crazy!
Master.
Sir!
I'm not crazy, Sir!
[The third month of the 11th year
of Yongning's reign, not archived]
Even if Shangguan Zhi's death
was a suicide,
there should be the case file here.
Where have you been?
Mr. Pan ordered me to get the case file
on Miss Yang's fall a month ago,
but I can't find it.
Miss Shangguan,
well...
Rumors of Miss Yang's death
are spreading,
damaging Mr. Pan's reputation.
Mr. Pan would like to review the case file
to clear up the suspicions
and explain it to the public.
But Mr. Pan
took it away that day.
We were like birds in a pair,
but you've suddenly left me all alone.
We were like two roaming fish,
but you left me halfway.
He's really in love with the princess
with all these love words.
If I didn't know your background,
I'd think you were a lovesick man.
How did he get so badly injured?
It looks like it's only been a month.
Come on, go home now.
Masters,
my young master has not returned.
The three of you should make the call
on this clan meeting.
Silver Rain Terrace has no objections.
[Gu Yong, the Head of Relief Hall]
[Cai Sheng,
the Head of Life and Death House]
[Qing Di,
the Head of Hundred Flowers Court]
Young Master Zhuo
should preside over this.
Together we are known
as the Four Greats,
but the Silver Rain Terrace
safeguards Heyang.
Silver Rain Terrace
is the greatest in Heyang.
Right?
Mr. Gu,
I didn't come here today
to listen to your flattery.
Get to the point.
I've got a game going on later.
You're still in the mood to gamble?
Sun Wancai was arrested by Pan Yue.
His men came to me for help.
As a man who beats his wife,
he deserves it.
You can't say that.
Sun Wancai
pays us tens of thousands of taels
every year.
Pan Yue arresting him
makes us lose face.
He's just a nobody.
Get rid of him if you have to.
Do you think
he is just like those
you used to get rid of as you wished?
He's the Emperor's future son-in-law.
If this becomes a big deal,
I'm afraid we won't be able
to stay in Heyang anymore.
There is nothing to fear.
No, I think he came to Heyang
just for appearances.
The Emperor's future son-in-law
in your mouth
has received a lot
of congratulatory gifts today.
In a few days,
he'll return to the capital
to marry the princess.
Want to bet?
I admire your confidence, Mr. Cai.
You deal with him, I'll pay you.
Do I need your money?
Mr. Gu,
Don't use others to your advantage.
No, Qing Di.
What is your plan, then?
Diplomacy before violence.
How can I get the key?
[Heyang Magistrate's Office]
Come and take a look.
Freshly unearthed old royal artifacts
from ancient tombs.
You're not buying jewelry
but the same old royal...
Yang...
Come and take a look.
[Beauty Parlor]
Miss, what do you think of this?
Let me see.
It's him.
Yeah, it's the latest style.
Come on, try it.
Let me see.
It's nice. It suits you perfectly.
You want to get this?
Okay?
Have a look around and see
if there's anything else you like.
Miss, look over there.
That man is my friend.
Because it's his first time
in a place like this
and he's not comfortable with it.
Please help him to trim his face.
Okay.
All right, I want these two.
I'll wrap them up for you later.
Mister, this is your first time here,
isn't it?
Let me trim your face.
It's very effective.
No, thanks.
Come on.
Come and have a try.
Miss Yang. You're being tailed.
It's Pan Yue's man.
Is he suspicious of you?
I'm not sure.
He could simply be watching me
to find an excuse to kick me out
of the county yamen.
Let's not worry about him.
I came to ask you to do me a favor.
Go ahead.
I remember you used
to sell a jar of something called...
Hundred Miles Fragrance.
Hundred Paces Fragrance.
It's a strong drink.
After drinking it,
everyone will collapse
within a hundred steps.
Yes, that's it.
Get me a jar.
Why do you need it?
You can't drink that.
I won't drink it.
Get me a jar.
Okay.
I've got news about Master Jiang.
Really?
I heard about a medical center
selling medicines to an old man.
From the description,
age, appearance, and so on,
it must be Master Jiang.
I'll check it out.
If there's any news,
I'll come back and tell you.
That means Master is still alive.
That's great.
[Heyang Magistrate's Office]
Young Lady, where have you been?
I was bored,
so I went out to buy some food.
Who's here to present gifts again?
Liu said
the guest was
from the Four Greats in Heyang.
The Four Greats?
Mr. Pan,
how
have you considered my request?
This isn't easy.
Please tell me
what you're worried about.
Look,
I arrested Sun Wancai
in front of the public,
in front of everyone decisively.
Now you're asking me to let him go,
isn't that eating my words?
We're willing to pay some money
to compensate for your loss of face.
Sir, name your price.
Four thousand taels?
Forty thousand?
Four hundred thousand?
Forty...
He was so upright when he was a kid,
but how did he grow up to be so bad?
You like drinking so much,
I'll let you have a good drink.
[Du Kang]
[Antidote to alcohol]
Nice.
Liu, don't go.
I've prepared some food and wine.
I'm new here,
so I'm grateful for all your kindness.
I'd like to express my gratitude.
Firstly, as a token of my appreciation,
and secondly,
to mark Mr. Pan's first arrest
on the streets.
Please sit down.
Sit down.
Okay.
Come on, don't keep standing there.
Quick.
Thank you.
Thank you, Miss Shangguan.
There are so many delicious dishes.
Yes.
Actually, Mr. Pan would like
to get close to everyone.
It's just
that he's cold on the outside
but warm on the inside.
He's embarrassed to take the initiative,
so you guys should be more proactive.
Okay.
That's true.
If we don't accommodate him,
do we want him
to accommodate us?
That's right.
Of course.
Don't just talk about it.
He's coming.
Go.
Go now.
Tell him to come and have a drink.
Mr. Pan,
we're celebrating the first arrest
on the streets.
Would you like
to join us for a drink?
Sure.
Come on, a toast to Mr. Pan.
Come on, Sir.
Flattery always works.
I know people
like you love flattery.
I don't believe
I can't get you drunk today.
Shangguan Zhi,
aren't you going to give me a toast?
Of course. I am.
I wish you fame and fortune
in Heyang.
I hope it'll be as you wish.
I hope you lose your reputation
and reap what you sow.
It's rare for the masters
to be so happy today.
I'll give you a toast too.
I don't drink.
Why don't you drink?
You're looking down on me
because I'm a girl, aren't you?
I didn't mean that.
If so, drink it.
Sir.
Miss Shangguan, Mr. Pan is...
He's drunk.
I'll help him back.
You guys clean up this place.
Mr. Pan is drunk.
I'll send him back.
Sir, be careful.
Don't bump into anything.
Don't get injured.
There are too many mosquitoes.
I'll kill them for you.
[The Case of Miss Yang's Fall]
No one was in the room when she fell.
The autopsy showed no poison
and no trauma.
There's no sign of burglary
or damage to the bridal chamber,
except for a water stain from who knows
where next to the body.
Water stain?
Why is there a water stain
next to the body?
Mr. Pan,
get some rest.
I'll go back first.
The candle in the room went out once.
Before relighting the candle,
Pan Yue should
have knocked out Shangguan Zhi.
He used mechanism
to make Shangguan Zhi delay the fall
to create an alibi.
Why was there a water stain
next to the body?
Water?
Could it be...
If Shangguan Zhi had been knocked out
before she fell,
there must have been trauma on her body.
It's been a month.
Her body may have decomposed.
But it's also the only clue
I've got so far.
But where would
Pan Yue bury Shangguan Zhi?
Young Lady.
Mr. Pan asked you to go out with him.
What?
That's great. Young Lady.
All your hard work
is finally coming to fruition.
I heard you sent me back
to my room last night.
Yes.
I didn't know that wine was so strong
that even Ze got drunk.
I didn't expect you
to be the best drinker.
I remember
you drank a lot last night, too.
Maybe I didn't feel drunk
when I met my soulmate.
But why do I remember in a trance
that you seem to treat me...
What?
What did I do to you?
I didn't do anything to you.
What is this?
A mosquito bite.
You know
that there are a lot of mosquitoes
at the county yamen.
In fact, I killed them
for a while yesterday
so as not to disturb your rest.
Well, that's very kind of you.
Don't mention it.
Sir,
where are you taking me?
I've searched everywhere
and finally found a bandit
who injured you a month ago.
Now I take you to identify him.
Let's go.
Lai Laosan.
Who are you?
Who let you in?
Get out.
This is the new magistrate, Mr. Pan.
Pan...
Mr. Pan.
Look at him.
Is he the bandit who
hurt you the other day?
I'm not sure.
The bandits were masked.
Masked?
Why didn't I think of that?
Looks like we'll need
physical evidence.
Lai Laosan,
you pawned this
at the pawnshop the other day.
You're a poor man.
Where did you get this?
This...
I picked it up somewhere.
You picked it up somewhere?
Where did you pick it up?
This jewelry is unique
to the Shangguan family's carriages.
Shangguan Zhi, am I right?
Is that so?
Tell me.
How did you get this?
You're the one who killed someone
and stole the carriage, aren't you?
No, I didn't.
Sir,
I didn't hurt anyone
and I wasn't a bandit.
Did the carriage come
to your house by itself?
Well...
I...
I stole it.
That was the day
you got married.
I lost all my money again.
I passed the mansion
where you were married on my way home.
I thought
that a nobleman from the capital
must have a lot of valuable things
and would be too careless
to take precautions on the wedding day.
So
I thought I'd break into the backyard
and steal something valuable.
I shouldn't have stolen things.
But I definitely didn't rob
and kill anyone.
Please see to it, Sir.
Where's the carriage now?
Sir.
You said you ran into bandits
on your way out,
but why was the carriage in Sunrise Garden?
Yes.
Why was my carriage in Sunrise Garden?
♪Like the dew, we wait for the glimmer
of light to greet the morning♪
♪How many looks do we need
to affirm each other?♪
♪It's sincerity that fools me♪
♪But it's seriousness that traps you♪
♪The depth of the past
is best left unexplored♪
♪How many more falls
do I have to experience♪
♪Before I can face love
and hatred with grace?♪
♪Don't ask if it's a moment♪
♪Of liberation or cowardice to let go♪
♪Perhaps it's a misstep into your heart,
it's a hasty feeling♪
♪It's an unwillingness
to be just a passer-by with you♪
♪Even if I were to die
after a few intense struggles♪
♪I would have lived a life worth living♪
♪If grasses and trees are sharp blades,
if mountains and waters are temples♪
♪It's good to be alive
even for a short moment♪
♪I wish I could be worthy
of the thoughts♪
♪And I wish I could be worthy
of the love♪
♪Perhaps it's a misstep into your heart,
it's a hasty feeling♪
♪It's an unwillingness
to be just a passer-by with you♪
♪Even if I were to die
after a few intense struggles♪
♪I would have lived a life worth living♪
♪If grasses and trees are sharp blades,
if mountains and waters are temples♪
♪It's good to be alive
even for a short moment♪
♪I wish I could be worthy
of the thoughts♪
♪And I wish I could be worthy
of the love♪
♪Be worthy of this love♪