It's finally settled.
Su Manyun and Lu Jingxi
both lost their shares in the Lu family.
They will never make waves in the Lu family again.
This way, your position in Lu Group is secure.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to keep it from you.
The reason I didn't tell you about these plans
is because I didn't want
to drag you into my family's mess.
Taking down Su Manyun
and helping you secure the Lu family
is the only thing I could think of doing for you.
If you feel
that I was just using you from the beginning,
you can choose to end this at any time.
I have no objections.
Do you think what I care about
is being used by you?
You can get a good night's sleep now.
Shen Jingyao finally got the punishment he deserved.
The revenge for the original host's murdered mother
and the suffering from his abuse
have finally been settled.
As for those who aided him,
Su Manyun and her son didn't end up well either.
But,
why?
Why haven't I returned to my original timeline?
Young Madam.
Come in.
Young Madam,
the master wants you to go to his study.
Well,
the master doesn't look well today.
You must be careful when you go there later.
Dad, you called me here today
because of my family's affairs, right?
It seems you still have some self-awareness.
Shen Zhixia,
what our Lu family needs is a daughter-in-law with a clean background
who can help the family,
not a trouble tied to a murderer.
Jingheng.
Zhixia.
Read this carefully, you two.
The lawyer has drafted this agreement.
From now on,
you go your separate ways.
Alright.
The agreement is fine. I can sign it.
You...
I don't agree to the divorce agreement.
You don't agree?
Are you blind or stupid?
Don't you know
what her situation is right now?
Her father, Shen Jingyao, is a murderer.
You still want to be tied to her family.
Do you think our Lu family doesn't have enough trouble?
Dad.
When Zhixia and I got married,
it was your idea.
Now it's your idea for us to get divorced.
I won't listen to you this time.
I won't divorce Zhixia.
Are you still a member of the Lu family?
Have you considered the Lu family's reputation?
The Lu family's reputation?
I will fight for it on my own,
instead of sacrificing my marriage
or Zhixia for it.
I have made my decision and I won't change it.
If you don't accept it,
I can leave the Lu Group and start my own business.
I will never leave Zhixia again in my life.
You are going to piss me off.
For this woman,
you don't even want the inheritance rights of the Lu Group?
I think you're crazy too.
I am not crazy.
I know very well
what the most important thing is.
You guys...
Why did you say such harsh words?
Leaving the Lu family
and giving up the inheritance rights.
You've worked so hard in the Lu family for so long.
For me,
is it worth it?
Then tell me, what makes it worth it?
I just feel that
I'm not worth it.
Whether you are worth it,
is up to me.
Where are you taking me?
Why did you bring me here?
We've known each other for so long,
but we've never
sat quietly together like this.
What do you think of this place?
It's beautiful.
This is my favorite place.
Whenever I'm in a bad mood,
coming here,
even if I do nothing,
can quickly calm me down.
I don't think I've ever seen you like this.
Like what?
Before.
You always wear such a hard shell,
making you so hard to figure out.
I thought in your eyes,
my heart was already laid bare.
My mom gave me this beach.
When I was little,
she often brought me here to pick up seashells.
You are the first person I brought here.
And the only one.
Do you know what I mean?
I don't quite understand.
Then I'll make it clearer.
Shen Zhixia.
I love you.
As long as you're willing,
we can be together forever.
What about our rules?
Can I unilaterally break the contract?
No.
But,
we can break it together.
I'm doomed.
I got carried away by the mood and lust.
Oh, Shen Zhixia.
You don't even know if you have a future.
How can you give one to someone else?
I'm so done.
There's no turning back now.
He's already like this.
If I say last night was just an accident,
wouldn't I be a total jerk?
Did you sleep well yesterday, young madam?
How can sleep be good or bad?
Just slept normally.
Shen Zhixia, are you crazy?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Are you not feeling well?
I'm not.
I'm perfectly fine.
What are you doing?
Buckling your seatbelt.
What else could I be doing?
Seatbelt.
I'll do it myself.
Okay.
Stop the car.
The weather is quite nice.
I'll go for a run.
Zhixia.
Mr. Lu,
do you want to get out and exercise too?
Why would I need to exercise?
Drive and catch up with her.
Run faster.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
What? What?
Come on! Come on!
Why are you slowing down?
Are you crazy?
I'll wait for you at home.
Bye.
Drive.
People talk about long-distance relationships.
Long-distance relationship?
Mrs. Wang has to take a cab to see Mr. Li.
Cast
Shen Zhixia / Liao Huijia
Lu Jingheng / Deng Chaoyuan
Lu Jingxi / Liu Yufeng
Wen Shuyi / Zheng Nanxi
Wen Zhuocheng / Wang Ye
Su Yuran / Ma Jie
Lu Zhenye / Xu Jian
Shen Jingyao / Niu Piao
Assistant / Cai Changyuan
Servant / Zhang Zhiying
Bodyguard A / Wen Yunting
Driver / Jiang Sen
Student's Parent / Zheng Xiaoling
Student's Parent / Xue Qi'an
Waiter / Geng Jiaqi
Strong Man A / Li Yang
Servant B / Zhao Xuelian
Female Companion / Zhou Yixin
Guest B / Xue Qi'an
Mrs. Zhang / Zhao Bin
Coach A / Wang Xiangkun
Coach B / Niu Liang
Curator / Wang Ying
Servant A / Zhao Hui
Servant B / Xu Huiying
Reporter A / Zhu Yuanjie
Reporter B / Wang Yue
Reporter C / Zheng Jiangbing
Gardener / Wu Yuhang
Rich Lady A / Wu Fan
Stall Owner / Cao Linghong
Employee B / Zhang Yuxuan
Employee C / Wang Weiliang
Guest A / Peng Sisi
Li Gang / Song Qing
Nurse A / Wang Furong
Nurse B / Huang Xinyuan
Lin Hui / Liu Longxia
Boxer / Wei Xiuqiong
Boxing Double / Zhao Zihan
Female Lead Double / Huang Jingping
Cast Members
Xie Yizhao / Peng Jinhan / Zhang Qi / Wu Qiuyue / Huang Fuwei / Liu Jieyu / Tang Lin / Zeng Chen
Chen Nanhui / Ye Nanxin / Hong Yun / Zheng Qinghui / Jiang Yingjie / Zhang Qian / Chen Weixin / Guo Qinlian
Zhuang Hongyong / Hu Luoluo / Li Binbin / Chen Hongkun / Wang Siya / Li Fengjie / Mai Xiaoqi / Huang Jinping
You Yanlian / Wu Zhijia / Wang Yanzhang / Rao Xiancui / Wang Yikai / Zhuang Xiaoling / Long Jiali / Zhan Tiansheng
Lin Zhenhua / Wu Rongxin / Dong Ronghuang / Li Xuan / Li Aoyu / Huang Yutong / Zhou Shiqing / Xin Sihan
Huang Xinyun / Cai Xiangpeng / Lu Yan / Lai Shiyu / Yang Kunkun / Hao Yang / Su Yanhong / Wu Xiaohui
Huang Chaopeng / Zhang Yue / Cai Shaohong / Li Yongxiu / Wu Jiaxin / Zhang Meiqi / Lai Duoqing / Xiang Hanmei
Lv Meixue / Xu Yanxin / Chen Zhiyuan / Wu Jiabang / Peng Jiayi / Wang Wenchao / Zhuang Qingqing / Lv Tingting
Hong Yushun / Wu Donghua / Guo Jiajie / Yi Huilin / Fu Weiquan / Lin Xinru / Luo Qiaoying / Lai Xuwei
Yang Qiao / Xiao Qing / Zhuang Binting / Zi Yu / Lin Jingwen / Xiao Fangming / Fu Zihan / Hu Manling
Zhang Jun / Wu Jingjing / Chen Xu / Lin Longhui / Huang Yongcheng / Jiang Jingmei / Zhang Baoting / Chen Xuanrong
Chen Yixin / Xiao Yuzhen / Huang Yashan / Lin Yingying / Wu Shouyan / Qiu Junda / Zheng Lili / Wu Mingyuan
Xu Jiangbin / Song Yufeng / Ke Peirong / Xin Mingming / Chen Zhuoya / Tan Yanyu / Wang Dan / Huang Yinhui
Zeng Jinglin / Chen Jiajia / Gui Xiaolian / Lei Xiaoying / Wei Shixuan / Yu Xin / Zheng Wenrong / Yu Xinyuan
Zhang Junwei / Wu Ruofan / Shi Hanbin / Guan Yongyao / Han Yingying / Wang Qinghua / Liu Jingkun / Fang Jiaying
Zeng Wenjie / Lin Shishi / Li Jingshuang / Peng Wanmin / Li Wenjie / Guo Xiangyu / Yang Yinghong / Liu Xinyu
Casting Director
Kai Xuan
Yu Sen
Production Manager / Zhao Lianjun
Coordinator / Li Dong
Executive Director / Zhao Tingting
On-site Assistant Director / Jiang Zhihui
Casting Assistant Director / Wang Xiangkun / Liu Yu
Script Supervisor Liu Lei
Director's Assistant Xu Ruiping
Location
Location Manager Dai Hongwei
On-set Producers Wang Chao, Yuan Yongchun
Executive Art Director Geng Yishun
Set Decorator Wang Ruining
DIT Liu Yang
Still Photographers Song Antao, Li Taiyu
Boom Operators Guo Hongwei, Shi Yanli
Wang Zhenzhong
Makeup Artist Zhang Jiawei
Key Hair & Makeup Wang Kexin
Assistant Makeup Mo Haidan
Hair Stylist Liu Donglai
Assistant Hair Zou Cuiyin
Props Cheng Zhongdian, Zhang Wei
Post-Production Video
Haoyuan Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing Jingyu Shijie Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Post-Production Producer Bai Zijun
Colorists Rong Zhanqing, Guo Hui
Subtitles Wang Wei, Song Pan
Post-Production Audio
Beijing Mingchen Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Sound Director He Bochen
Sound Effects Editor Niu Haichao
Dialogue Editor Wang Lifeng
Foley Artist Wang Xianwei
Sound Coordinator Ma Zining
Post-Production VFX
Beijing Mingyang Lianmeng Film & TV Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Director Ma Mingjun
VFX Supervisor Rao Xianjun
Lighting & Rendering Artists Zhang Wenxuan, Fu Xuanwei
VFX Lead Rao Xianjun
VFX Artist Zhang Yun
Compositing Leads Sun Jiawei, Li Guixiang
Opening & Ending Sequences
Beijing Mingyang Lianmeng Film & TV Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Package Design Liu Encheng
Voice Actors
Lu Jingheng: Gu Li
Narrator Li Xiaohong
Music Provided By
"Warm Corner"
Lyricist R2
Singer Zhang Fan
"The You Given to Me"
Lyricist Xu Yuteng
Singer Xu Yuteng
"Night Breeze Blowing Towards You"
Lyricist Zhang Zhiyu
Composer Guo Chao
Singer Wu Yuxi
"I Thought"
Composers Cheng Huan, An Xu
Publicity and Marketing
Hainan Jiaying Film & Television Culture Co., Ltd.
Project Coordinator Ren Meiyu
Project Operations Yao Can
Special Thanks
Fujian Quanzhou Ruixing Automobile Sales & Service Co., Ltd.
Acknowledgments
CR Land Quanzhou Yuefu
Fujian Quanzhou Quanzhou Bay Skyline No. 1
Fujian Jinjiang Lilanz Creative Park Hongxuan Restaurant
Fujian Quanzhou Modern Service Industry Association
Fujian Jinjiang No. 3 Experimental Kindergarten
Xuzhou Yushuiyu Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Musician Xu Yuteng
Beijing Lehuowanyin Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Fujian Shishi Zhongjun Gold Coast Zhongjun Huamanhaishu
Fujian Quanzhou Molesi World Restaurant
Fujian Quanzhou Yujian Sports Complex
Fujian Quanzhou Yihe Hospital
Fuzhou Taihe Property Management Co., Ltd. Quanzhou Branch
Quanzhou Development Jiangnan Tianjing
Fujian Quanzhou Yijia Hotel
Fujian Quanzhou Baohui Jewelry Co., Ltd.
Fujian Quanzhou Film and Television Service Center
Presented by
Fujian Quanzhou Ruiquan Film and Television Culture Media Co., Ltd.