Now, please hold the hand of the man
you'd like to go on
a one-on-one date with.
This is the hardest decision.
Please choose in three seconds.
We're nervous too.
"IT'S THE MOST DIFFICULT
DECISION"
In a sense, it's a match of pride
-between the twins.
-I don't know what to do.
"A MATCH OF PRIDE
BETWEEN THE TWINS"
You're the woman who makes me nervous.
I'm serious.
"OLDER TWIN, KIM SUNGJUN"
You're my ideal type.
I came to like you.
"YOUNGER TWIN, KIM SUNGHUN"
Seriously.
-What?
-Seriously.
-I don't know.
-I'll show my charms during the next date.
-Why am I so nervous?
-Ji Yeeun,
please choose in three seconds.
Three,
two,
one. Please choose one.
That startled me!
Kim Sunghun is out.
Hold… Hold on.
Ji Yeeun!
I think I got outshined.
I didn't get eliminated
because of my long hair, right?
Ji Yeeun chose Kim Sungjun.
"JI YEEUN CHOSE KIM SUNGJUN"
Now… Hold on.
My goodness.
-Chewy candy played a big role.
-Chewy candy?
-Don't throw it away, okay?
-Okay.
I can't stand awkward situations.
He smoothed out the situation
in a witty way.
He made things very entertaining for me,
so I chose him.
60 MINUTES TO LOVE
60 Minutes to Love,
New Face Every 30 Minutes!
One-on-one date begins now!
You don't need to put it on.
I brought it to show different charms.
-It's okay.
-This is how I look in a shirt.
You're making me feel warm.
Really? It's okay.
Please.
-I saw it.
-This is how I look in a shirt.
-I'll take it off if I get warm.
-You look too warm.
Now, you're right in front of me.
Thanks to the two of you,
time passed so quickly.
I wanted to show my fun side
as well as my serious side.
I thought I wouldn't get to show them,
so I was disappointed.
Despite being an identical twin,
I'm different from Sunghun in some ways.
I think you've chosen me
because of those differences.
-That's right.
-Yes.
You're quite different
from the image I had in mind.
Why do you say that?
You have a very small face.
You're tall.
Your personality too.
You aren't overly cheerful.
-There's seriousness about you.
-Yes.
You saw correctly.
It's nice.
When I look at a person,
I pay attention to his or her energy
or vibes.
-You have incredible energy.
-Can you feel it?
You're full of positive energy.
I don't like awkwardness.
When there's silence,
I constantly try to break it.
I'm the same.
-I see.
-I'm the same.
We have many similarities.
"WE HAVE MANY SIMILARITIES"
You said earlier
that you couldn't ask many questions.
-Do you have questions?
-Well,
I have many questions.
Do you like hot weather?
-I prefer winter.
-Winter.
Do you like cold weather?
I enjoy the scenery of cold weather.
I enjoy watching the snow fall.
But I'm actually
too sensitive to cold weather.
-But…
-You're sensitive to heat too.
I'm a bit sensitive to heat too.
You can take it off.
Shall I take it off?
It's too hot. I'll need to take it off.
This won't do.
"HE GOES BACK TO THE TANK TOP"
I don't know where to look.
It's okay. My body is covered anyway.
What are you looking at?
Your eyes are very clear.
You look a bit like a quokka.
That's right. Many people told me
that I resembled a quokka.
Hamsters and quokkas.
Animals in that category.
Cuteness is the strongest quality.
You can't help but fall for cuteness.
-Many people were on the show.
-Yes.
-There must be men you've chosen.
Yes.
What do you look for in those men?
Which quality do you hope
that they'd possess?
Me? I want our conversations
to flow easily.
I want our conversations to be fun.
Right.
-People who put you at ease are the best.
-That's right.
Do you have a hobby?
I like to walk.
Do you walk alone or with other people?
I walk alone.
Do you go to the Han River?
Cheonggyecheon.
-Really?
-Yes.
I might see you at Cheonggyecheon.
"I MIGHT SEE YOU
AT CHEONGGYECHEON"
Even if we don't go on a date…
Right? That might happen.
Where do you live?
I currently live in Oksu.
It's close to Cheonggyecheon.
That's right. That's what I think.
Ten minutes remain.
I'm someone who likes the pull.
When I do something…
When I set my mind to do something,
I think it through.
That's good.
"I'll meet Yeeun today.
I'll go on a date with her today."
Then it comes true.
It's the law of the pull.
-The law of the pull?
-Yes.
I'm sure you didn't realize this,
but I've been pulling you in.
The weather is very nice today.
It's pretty outside.
I want to go outside with you
and enjoy a date.
That sounds good.
Is there a male actor you like?
It depends on the drama.
When I watch this drama,
I like this actor.
When I watch that drama,
I like that actor.
Then your ideal type must change.
That's right.
It changes.
That's why I don't know myself.
-You know…
-Three minutes remain.
Women's ideal type changes a lot.
-It actually changes.
-Exactly.
Is it the same for men?
-Does your ideal type change over time?
-Mine did.
It went from sexiness to cuteness.
That was why I asked.
It changed today.
-Why are you lying?
-I'm not lying.
I love cute characters so much.
I mentioned a quokka earlier
because it was my absolute favorite.
That was why I mentioned it.
On my way here,
I had many thoughts.
"I'll show this side to Yeeun."
"I'll make this comment."
-Such thoughts…
-Which side did you want to show?
I wanted to show my sincere side.
That's nice.
Within that side,
I wanted to show my sense of humor.
You've done a good job
of showing your charms.
You've been very charming.
There's more to show.
-Right.
-Yes.
Is there more to show?
Of course.
Hold on. After 1 minute and 30 seconds,
-will another man come?
-Yes, I think so.
Who will come?
"NERVOUS"
Seriously.
It's my first time having a blind date
alongside a man, except my brother.
Right.
It's all about my confidence.
-Your confidence.
-Yes, my confidence is key.
-I need to build up my confidence.
I'll need to control my mind.
I see. Do it now.
Hold on. I'm getting a bit nervous.
-Another man will come in 30 seconds.
-Seriously.
Hold on. Let me put on some lip balm.
-Lip balm.
-Yes.
It's over.
60 Minutes to Love,
New Face Every 30 Minutes!
Two-on-one date begins now.
Kim Kwangtae from EXchange has entered.
-Hello.
-It's nice to meet you.
Hello.
-Hello.
-It's nice to meet you.
KIM KWANGTAE, EXCHANGE 3
INTERNATIONAL FOOD SALES MANAGER,
THREE YEARS YOUNGER, ENFJ
You're more petite than you appear on TV.
I guess I looked huge on TV.
No.
You just look very pretty
in person.
Thank you.
-I watched EXchange.
-Did you watch it?
Does it mean that you know who I am?
I know who you are, Kwangtae.
You know who he is.
-I know you.
-That's good, I guess.
How old are you?
I was born in 1997.
-He's young.
-You're young.
I'm younger than you.
You're the same age as my brother.
You were born in 1997.
Do you have a brother?
-Do you have a brother?
-Yes.
I have two younger brothers.
Have you dated someone
who was your younger brother's age?
…your younger brother's age?
I bet she has.
-No, I haven't.
-No?
So, what do you think?
Do you prefer a man
who is your younger brother's age
or a man who is one year older than you?
As for me,
"FULL OF HOPE"
I prefer older men.
My younger brother's age…
"A CEREMONY OF VICTORY"
That's right.
You'll change your mind today.
Kwangtae, how did you join
this blind date?
Me? To be honest,
this is my very first blind date.
So…
I was simply invited
to a blind date with you.
I thought, "I should do it."
"A BLIND DATE WITH YEEUN"
I'm here to show you
my natural side.
What's your natural side?
My strength is
that I can put you at ease
even though we've just met.
You have a great personality,
so you'll probably feel at ease
no matter who you're with.
You're right about that.
Am I right about that?
I have a great personality,
so no matter who I'm with…
You're right about that.
-Since this is my first time meeting you,
-Okay.
may I ask you what kind of men you like?
I was surprised to see a man in a tank top
upon entering.
She likes a man in a tank top.
-No.
-I was wearing this shirt earlier,
but she told me to take it off.
So, I took it off.
I wanted to keep it on,
but I took it off.
Yes.
He looked too warm in it.
He was sweating a lot.
-I like someone who is kind
-Okay.
and considerate.
It has nothing to do with tank tops.
Five minutes have passed.
What do you do for a living?
I haven't introduced myself properly.
I currently work at a company.
Caviar and truffles
are some of the luxury food items
my company deals with.
I'm their sales manager.
Do you enjoy eating?
I really enjoy eating.
Do you go to famous restaurants?
-I don't go to famous restaurants.
-I see.
In that case, what's your favorite food?
-Tteokbokki.
"YEEUN'S FAVORITE FOOD"
I like tteokbokki.
There are many famous tteokbokki places.
-But tteokbokki is
-Okay.
usually tasty.
There's tteokbokki at the Seokgwan Market
near the school you attended.
-I've tried it.
-It's famous.
-It's so tasty.
-My school was nearby.
-Which school?
-Kyunghee University.
It's quite near.
I've been to Kyunghee University.
-People visit for cherry blossoms.
-Yes.
I asked about famous restaurants
because I run a social media account
on that topic.
I'd say that I have a talent
in finding good restaurants.
I love taking people to such restaurants.
-So…
-There's a line, right?
No, these places don't have a line.
These places are hidden gems.
Otherwise, I'll make the reservation.
That's really nice.
I work at a company
that deals with food items, right?
I really like truffles.
-Really?
-Yes.
I'd like to give them as a gift.
If he gives you truffles,
I'll give you tteokbokki.
-I'll give you truffle tteokbokki.
-Truffle tteokbokki.
Truffle tteokbokki.
I haven't thought of truffle tteokbokki.
I'll cook for you myself.
Are you good at cooking?
I enjoy cooking. Also,
I make the best tteokbokki.
Have you had a meal?
No, I haven't.
-You must be hungry. I'm hungry too.
-My stomach is empty.
I heard that this place was famous
for its afternoon tea set.
I absolutely love desserts.
The desserts here are well-known
among foodies.
I want to eat them right away.
My blood sugar is low.
-Please bring them in.
-It's low.
Seriously, that's…
"KWANGTAE PREPARED DESSERTS
FOR YEEUN"
This is insane!
Can I eat them?
Thank you for the food.
How is it?
It's so tasty.
There's a variety,
so please try a bit of each.
Perhaps because they're hotel desserts,
they're luxurious.
They're luxurious.
-I love this.
-Here.
-What is it?
Thank you.
You're a sweet guy.
-It's too big.
-I want to try this one.
-This one?
-Yes.
-You should…
-Yeeun wants to try this one.
I'll cut it for you.
-It's…
-Thank you.
Do you like small bites or big bites?
Today, I'll go for small bites.
Small bites.
The size that'll fit in your mouth.
There you go.
-This piece has the most cream.
-Okay.
Thank you.
It looks so tasty.
I love brown cheese waffles.
This place must be famous for desserts.
Where do you recommend…
Which dessert do you like?
It depends on which dessert you like.
-I'll give you one recommendation.
-You're good.
You're good.
-He's good.
-You're good.
Where did you learn such techniques?
When a guy is too smooth,
it's a turn-off, isn't it?
I'm not like that. I've never been here.
I've never had such desserts.
I can see that.
You're right.
Although I'm younger than you,
I'm not a young man.
Time passes so quickly.
What?
-While eating…
-I know.
Seriously.
-This is like a mealtime.
-I finished it.
"TIME PASSED QUICKLY
WHILE THEY WERE EATING"
It's good to see you eat well.
When I take a woman somewhere
to eat something,
I don't want her to go,
"Why would you pay so much for this?"
When I say, "Let's go
to this nice restaurant I found,"
I want her to follow me
and enjoy the food. That's all I want.
Let's say you go to a good restaurant
-and see a long line.
-Okay.
Do you tend to wait or not?
I don't wait.
Me neither.
I make sure we don't need to wait.
That's nice.
How do you do that?
I wait in line alone
and get close to the owners.
What's your ideal type?
I like someone
who does her work diligently.
That's totally me.
I agree.
-I also like someone with definite charms.
-That's me.
That's totally me.
You're doing a very good job
of eating right now.
It's nice to see.
It made me happy just watching you.
I like someone who eats with gusto.
Your face is turning red.
While I enjoy eating,
I'm only eating right now
to raise my blood sugar level.
I mean…
I didn't mean it that way.
It was really nice
to see you eat comfortably. Seriously.
Five minutes remain.
Do you have any questions you want to ask?
-Me?
-Yes.
That's right. I want to know
what your MBTI is.
I'm a firm believer,
so I'm curious.
What do you think it is?
ENFP?
ISFP?
Am I right?
-Didn't you hear it earlier?
-No.
I really didn't.
-It's ISFP.
-ISFP?
Do you know a lot about MBTI?
-I know which personality types suit mine.
-What are they?
-Which ones suit yours?
-As for me,
I like the personality type that has
either S or T.
In that sense,
your personality type is very nice.
I thought you were an extrovert
because you were cheerful on TV.
You make us feel at ease,
so I took you for an extrovert.
I guess that on the inside…
-I'm different.
-You're soft-hearted.
I'm definitely not an extrovert.
I have to be alone when I rest.
You're the type to listen to music,
read a book, and go on a stroll.
What kind of date do you enjoy?
-The thing is,
-Okay.
I haven't been on many dates.
-It depends on who you're with.
-That's right.
-That's right. It depends on who I'm with.
-It's different.
I like simple dates.
I enjoy taking a stroll together.
Some people like outdoor activities.
I'm not a big fan of outdoor activities.
For example…
How should I put it?
-Something like rock climbing.
-Rock climbing.
I don't like that. It makes you sweaty.
I enjoy going on a stroll too.
I like simple dates.
I enjoy eating tteokbokki
and listening to music together.
I'm serious.
But your outfit is perfect
for outdoor activities.
Right now, I'm feeling warm again.
-I cooled down earlier.
-You cooled down earlier.
But I'm sweating again.
Yes.
One minute remains.
-Time passes so quickly.
-So quickly.
Only one minute remains.
-I thought 30 minutes were long.
-I know.
Seriously,
it was nice to get to know you.
You speak as if you won't see him again.
Do you have any more questions for me?
-Me?
-It's okay if you don't have any.
-I do have questions, but…
-I have so many questions.
Time passed so quickly.
Since you've had something to eat,
it'll be nice if you can relax
and continue on with the conversation.
What should I do?
It's hard.
It's really hard.
-Of course, it's hard.
-It must be hard to choose one.
-It's hard.
-Five seconds remain.
Five, four,
three, two,
-one.
-Think of the chewy candy.
-The chewy candy.
-The blind date has ended.
"BLIND DATE ENDS"
Ji Yeeun, you must now choose one
of the two dates.
Gentlemen, please get up from your seats,
-close your eyes,
-Time passed so quickly.
and stretch out both hands.
Like this?
I'm not a big fan of outdoor activities.
I don't like that. It makes you sweaty.
I have to be alone when I rest.
You're the type to listen to music,
read a book, and go on a stroll.
I'll cut it for you.
You're a sweet guy.
"THE SWEET OLDER MAN,
KIM SUNGJUN"
I prefer older men.
You'll change your mind today.
Although I'm younger than you,
I'm not a young man.
It depends on which dessert you like.
I make sure we don't need to wait.
"THE YOUNGER MAN WHO TAKES
THE LEAD, KIM KWANGTAE"
Ji Yeeun, please put a rose
on the hand of the man
you'd like to go on
a one-on-one date with.
Gentlemen, please keep your eyes closed
until the end.
Please choose in three seconds.
Three,
-two,
-Chewy candy!
one.
Please choose one.
60 MINUTES TO LOVE
Translated by Dongjoo Park