THE 2ND ROMANTIC INTEREST, KIM SUNGJUN'S
30-MINUTE AMUSEMENT PARK DATE
THE 3RD ROMANTIC INTEREST, SUK HYUNJUN'S
30-MINUTE GYM DATE
KIM SUNGJUN VERSUS SUK HYUNJUN
WHO WILL GO ON A ONE-ON-ONE DATE?
Yeeun, you must now choose one
of the two romantic interests.
Kim Sungjun, please look Yeeun in the eye
and say your last words.
Yeeun.
I wanted to see you laugh a lot.
"SUNGJUN PREPARED AN AMUSEMENT PARK DATE"
This is so funny.
"TO MAKE YEEUN LAUGH"
It's hot, right?
-Thank you.
-To make sure you don't get overheated,
I packed everything.
-Sit here.
-Thank you.
-What's that?
-I brought gimbap.
"KIM SUNGJUN MOVED YEEUN"
There are many things I haven't shown.
I'd like to have another date with you
somewhere cool.
Okay.
Suk Hyunjun, please look Yeeun in the eye
and say your last words.
One…
I want Yeeun to feel more at ease
at the gym
and enjoy exercising with me.
I think it's a healthy date.
-A heart shape for men.
-All right.
What's wrong with you?
-I can't sit on your shirt.
-Yeeun.
-You can use my shirt as a picnic mat.
-No.
Milkshake
When we first met, you said
that you wanted to go for a drive.
Do you remember that?
I want to remiss that memory and…
Is it "reminisce"?
Is it "remiss" or "reminisce"?
-Reminisce.
-Let me start over.
I'm sorry. In any case,
I suggested going for a drive together
back then.
I want to go for a drive with you.
Gentlemen, please go into your car
and close your eyes.
Now, Yeeun, please get in the car
of the man you'd like to go on
a one-on-one date with.
"KIM SUNGJUN VERSUS SUK HYUNJUN"
Please choose in three seconds.
Three…
Three.
Two…
One.
"WHO WILL YEEUN CHOOSE?"
Please choose one.
Can I open my eyes?
Suk Hyunjun is out.
…two, one.
Please open the door. Knock, knock.
Open the door.
What?
Thank you.
-What? Are you getting in?
-Yes.
Yeeun!
-Hello.
-I waited for you.
-I waited for you, Yeeun.
He brought a sun umbrella and gimbap
in a pretty wooden container.
He also brought a picnic mat.
His sincerity won my heart.
-I did my best.
-Right.
I did my best, right?
Why do you think you got eliminated?
Me?
I guess I'm not Yeeun's type.
Where did it go wrong?
I was confused.
Where did it go wrong? What went wrong?
Perhaps it was
a mistake to make her do
a triceps exercise.
I don't know where it went wrong.
YEEUN CHOSE SUNGJUN FOR A ONE-ON-ONE DATE
SUNGJUN'S OPPONENT
IN A ONE-ON-ONE DATE WILL BE CHOSEN
THROUGH THE NEXT TWO-ON-ONE DATE
This will be my last two-on-one date.
I'm in Hongdae.
I haven't walked
around this area in a while.
I'm looking forward to today as well.
My last decision is coming up,
so I'm nervous.
60 Minutes to Love,
New Face Every 30 Minutes!
The two-on-one date planned
by Romantic Interest Cho Yeongseok
begins now.
The fourth romantic interest,
Cho Yeongseok, has entered.
May I call you nuna?
-Nuna.
-Okay, Yeongseok.
I also have a rapper name.
Let's get it!
Skrrt!
"THE FOURTH ROMANTIC INTEREST,
CHO YEONGSEOK"
Hello.
Nuna, hello.
Yeongseok, hello.
I forgot that we decided to talk casually.
-Nuna, hello.
-Hi, Yeongseok.
-Hello.
-It has been a while.
It has been a while. Did you lose weight?
-I gained weight.
-Did you gain weight? I'm sorry.
I ate a lot.
-Now, Yeongseok and…
-Yes.
Isn't there one more romantic interest?
The first romantic interest,
Park Changsun, has entered.
Korea National University of Arts
and Jungang Girls' High.
"HE WAS ALWAYS PREPARED"
He brought something today as well.
I decided to make you milkshake.
HE SURPRISED HER EVERY TIME
THE FIRST ROMANTIC INTEREST, PARK CHANGSUN
He brought a bouquet of flowers.
"CHANGSUN PREPARED
A BOUQUET OF FLOWERS TODAY"
It has been a while.
Oh, geez.
-Hello.
-Oh, goodness.
Oh, geez. Please don't do this.
Please don't do this.
Women hate this the most.
Thank you.
I thought the vibe was too depressing.
It came apart.
Oh, no.
-It's wet.
-It rained.
-Shall I hold them like this?
-Sounds good.
-Shall I hold the flowers only?
Thank you.
I brought a present as well.
Why did you do that? I didn't…
Today,
I don't want you to get exhausted.
-So… Yes.
-It's an energy drink.
-It's an ampoule. Press the top.
-You brought one for me as well.
-Press it.
-Did you know
-that he was a pharmacist?
-Yes.
I know because I watched Couple Palace.
-Really?
-Yes.
Open it and drink it later.
I also brought multivitamins.
This is the date Yeongseok has prepared.
Last time we met,
we mentioned a video arcade.
A video arcade.
So I prepared a video arcade date.
The weather is still hot, so…
…video arcade…
Those were the places I thought of.
I thought about what we could do
to have an active date
indoors.
I decided to take her to a video arcade.
Then we'll capture today's good memories
at a photo booth.
-I haven't been there in a long while.
-Me neither.
Let's go today.
The date has begun.
Twenty-seven minutes remain.
I see that you've met many men.
That's right. Many men.
I'm the first romantic interest.
I haven't been to a video arcade often.
But it's fun
even if you're bad at the games.
Even if you're bad at the games,
time will pass quickly.
I agree. Time will pass quickly.
-I…
-Hongdae has changed so much.
I haven't been here in a while.
Same here. Seriously.
-Rain…
-Thank goodness it stopped.
I know.
"YEEUN AND YEONGSEOK CONTINUE TALKING"
Thankfully, the rain stopped.
-The two of you became very close.
-Well…
-We decided to talk casually.
-Yes.
-Okay.
-Yeongseok…
-"Yeongseok."
-He's younger than me.
-Okay.
I feel comfortable around younger men.
Talking to her casually
puts me more at ease.
-Why don't the two of you talk casually?
-Well, we…
-We…
-There's a bit of an age gap.
-I see.
-I make sure to respect the elder.
I see.
Yes.
This is the place.
Let's get it. Let's go.
It's nice.
-It's cool in here.
-It's cool.
ACTIVITY 1: VIDEO ARCADE
There's a basketball game.
-Shall we play basketball?
-Basketball?
-Shall we do that?
-Go ahead.
-Basketball. Let's get it.
-Are you good at it?
-I'm bad at it. I prefer soccer.
-Same here.
-This is…
-Do you want to have a match?
-Well…
-How about a match?
"A BASKETBALL MATCH
BETWEEN YEONGSEOK AND CHANGSUN?"
-Let's give it a go.
-Shall we?
Okay. In that case…
-Rock-paper-scissors.
"SCISSORS VERSUS PAPER"
-Go first.
-Shall I go first? Okay.
-The elder should go first.
-May I play with you, Yeeun?
There's only one hoop,
but let's do it together.
Okay.
-A couple's mode?
-There's a couple's mode.
Let's go.
Come on! Why is there a couple's mode?
"YEONGSEOK WAS THE ONE
WHO SUGGESTED A BASKETBALL MATCH"
I'm good at this!
"HE ENDED UP GIVING THEM
A COUPLE'S BASKETBALL SESSION"
-Use this ball.
-Okay.
-Does it work better?
-Yes.
I'm good at this.
It says, "Together forever."
"TOGETHER FOREVER"
It says, "Forever with you."
"FOREVER WITH YOU"
That's so funny.
What's wrong with that machine?
"Everlasting love."
Come on.
What the heck?
What kind of a basketball game…
-What's the score?
-The last one is, "I love you."
-It's 40 percent.
-Is it 40 percent?
-Now, let me try with Yeongseok.
-Okay.
It's a couple versus a couple.
COUPLE'S TEAMWORK MATCH
40 POINTS, ?? POINTS
Game over.
One more time. Let's get it.
-Focus.
-Ready?
Go!
You're good at this.
The balls aren't coming down.
Bring it on.
Come on!
"I LOVE YOU"
Come on. Bring it on.
"THAT'S HOT"
-We can do it.
-Three points.
We can do it.
Not much time remains.
-Go on in. That's good.
-Three points.
No!
-Time's up.
-You guys did so well.
Really?
It was my second try, so…
"WHAT'S THE COUPLE'S SCORE?"
The score's higher.
"61 POINTS, 40 POINTS"
I lost.
-Sixty-one percent.
-Congratulations.
-That equals 74 points.
-Yes, 74 points.
How much time remains?
-Fifteen minutes remain.
-Shall we go to the third floor then?
What else is fun?
Shall we go to the third floor?
A boxing machine.
There's a boxing machine.
-There are many games.
-All right.
-A boxing machine.
-Here it is.
-Shall we do the boxing machine last?
-Seriously, the boxing machine…
Let's make a bet with the boxing machine.
-That's a good idea.
-Okay.
The two of you should do it.
"WILL HE MAKE UP FOR HIS LOSS?"
What will be the penalty?
The penalty?
What's the next date?
We're going to karaoke.
-Karaoke?
-Yes.
-I prepared a karaoke date.
-Then the penalty should be singing first.
-Okay. Sounds good.
-The loser sings first.
-The loser?
-This is bad.
-Okay.
-The loser should sing first.
-Okay. Let's go.
-Okay.
-Do you want to go first?
-My pride will be hurt if I lose.
-Rock-paper-scissors.
-Shall we? The loser goes first.
"PAPER VERSUS SCISSORS"
Okay. Press "Start"
-and punch.
-Okay.
Seriously, I haven't done this
since elementary school.
This is…
I'm excited.
Here comes a punch.
It's 8,448 points.
I did better than I expected.
-Is that a good score?
-Now…
I have no idea
if it's a good score or not.
Here I go.
"YEONGSEOK WINS"
It's the highest score.
"CHANGSUN LOSES TWICE IN A ROW"
Wasn't it the same?
-You'll sing first.
-That's good.
Yeeun, try it.
-Shall I?
-Yeeun, it's your turn.
I have weak punches.
-Let's go.
-Hold on.
"HANDKERCHIEF"
-Give me your right hand.
-Okay.
Thank you.
What's this?
Are you her coach or something?
It can be unsafe for the wrist.
Thank you.
Grab your wrist.
-Do it like this.
-Like this?
What?
-You can't push it with your palm.
-I used my palm.
-I still got over 2,000 points.
-Okay.
-You're good.
-Hurrah. In that case…
-He'll go first because…
-I'm in trouble.
-Let's go outside.
-Okay.
-We're done checking out the place.
-We need to go to a photo booth.
All right. It was fun.
-It was fun.
-Seriously.
Let's go.
-It must be cool inside.
YEONGSEOK'S 30-MINUTE DATE
ACTIVITY 2: PHOTO BOOTH
-No props?
-Shall we use the props?
-There are props.
-You're right.
Let's pick one for each other.
-A cute one.
-We'll each pick a headband.
-Okay.
-Then Yeeun can choose one.
I love that idea. I won't look.
Let's see which one Yeeun would like.
Place it over there so that I don't know
who chose which.
-Okay.
"ROUND 3
FINDING YEEUN'S HEADBAND MATCH"
A headband that suits her?
I think this one is the cutest.
And it resembles her.
"YEONGSEOK PICKS A HEADBAND
THAT RESEMBLES YEEUN"
-That's a good one.
-Yes. This one.
I'll choose this one.
This one.
"CHANGSUN'S CHOICE"
-Shall we put them here? She'll pick one.
-Let's put them here.
-Okay. All right.
-Here.
Now comes her choice.
I'll turn around.
They look similar.
-These two?
-Yes.
"WHOSE HEADBAND WILL YEEUN CHOOSE?"
-These two?
-Yes.
"IF CHANGSUN LOSES AGAIN,
IT'LL BE HIS THIRD LOSS"
"YEONGSEOK HAS TAKEN TWO CONSECUTIVE WINS"
"CHANGSUN'S PICK, YEONGSEOK'S PICK"
I'll choose this one.
Yes!
-Did you pick this one?
-Yes.
-Congratulations. I see.
-Wear these with me.
-I'll wear this one…
-Okay.
…and feel lonely. Okay.
-I'll wear this one.
-It's cute.
It's cute.
Shall we get our photos taken?
Your hair will get ruined
since it's too thick.
I prefer a thin one.
Which frame shall we choose?
The basic one?
The basic one? The original one?
-Five minutes remain.
-So many options.
-All done.
-You're the heroine.
-The center?
-Yes, come to the center.
-Come to the center.
-I'll step back.
-How…
"YEONGSEOK MOVES FORWARD,
CHANGSUN MOVES BACKWARD"
-All right.
-We should be gentlemen
and move forward.
Really? I'm sorry.
One, two, three.
-It's cute.
-One, two, three.
-Yes. Here.
"HALF OF A HAND HEART?"
-It'll be hard for her to use both hands.
-I…
-Shall we do this?
-What's this?
One, two, three.
-The last one.
-Strike your own pose.
My own pose? Okay.
One, two, three.
-We need to choose.
-Yes.
-Okay.
-It looks adorable.
-Good.
-Yes.
-It's cute.
-Good.
Nice pictures!
Yes, they look good.
I'll sign the photos
and give them to the two of you.
-That's incredible.
-Sounds good.
-Make sure you keep them.
-Okay.
-Hold this. Really?
-I keep the photos in a container.
Five seconds remain.
Five, four,
three, two,
one.
The date has ended.
Okay. It has ended.
Yeeun, please proceed
to the next date planned
by Park Changsun,
the first romantic interest.
-Okay. Let's go to karaoke.
-Karaoke.
YEONGSEOK'S 30-MINUTE DATE ENDS
CHANGSUN'S 30-MINUTE DATE BEGINS
-Good.
-Let's go to the cool karaoke.
-Yes.
-Karaoke.
"TJ MEDIA HAS GRANTED PERMISSION
TO USE THE KARAOKE SONGS"
I absolutely love karaoke,
but I haven't been to one in a long while.
This room is nice. It's so spacious.
60 Minutes to Love,
New Face Every 30 Minutes!
The two-on-one date planned
by Romantic Interest Park Changsun
begins now.
Firstly, I prepared a karaoke date.
Whenever Yeeun is stressed out,
she goes to karaoke.
-When you're angry about something…
-Okay.
…how do you relieve stress? I'm curious.
-I go to the karaoke alone.
-What?
"CHANGSUN REMEMBERED
YEEUN'S STRESS-RELIEF METHOD"
Yeeun likes to go to karaoke
when she's stressed.
So I prepared a date
that Yeeun would like.
I can sing at karaoke alone for two hours.
But I haven't been able
to visit one lately.
So I haven't sung "Milk Shake" at karaoke.
I must've sung it more often…
-I know.
-…than you.
-Is "Milk Shake" available at karaoke?
-Yes. it is. It's 88043.
"THE SONG NUMBER IS 88043"
-Changsun.
-It's 88043.
Right. I can sing "Milk Shake"
from the beginning to the end.
I went to coin karaoke every day
for two weeks.
Really?
I sang for two hours.
"CHANGSUN PRACTICED SINGING
TWO HOURS A DAY FOR TWO WEEKS"
I haven't sung it.
"Milk Shake" is available!
It's 88043, right?
-It's 88043.
-Yes.
-It's a really good song.
-I'll lower the key by one step.
I won't lower it.
It's my first time singing it at karaoke.
When I was little,
I liked it more than candies
The sweet taste was like
A cool cloud on a summer day
I felt like I was floating
Above the blue sky
More than the cocktail colors
"CHANGSUN SINGS THE MALE PART"
The white color charmed me
I fell in love
The cool feeling that washes over me
Under the scorching sun
"HARMONIZING"
Come on!
I want it so much
-Drink a milkshake in a cheerful way
-Drink a milkshake in a special way
Flavors burst and bloom in my mouth
-Like
-Like a balloon
"YEONGSEOK STEALS THE MALE PART"
-I'm happy when I have you
-When I have you
-Milkshake
"ZERO STONE TAKES THE RAP PART"
What you drink, wear, and where you live
Since when were they so important?
They say, "Have a sweet drink
And take a break"
Now, I'm less afraid of making decisions
People's smiles matter the most to me
I might get childish, I might get drunk
Sleeping hours, causes
There are so many things to think about
Whenever something depressing happens
It's the only taste that excites me
The taste
"YEONGSEOK STEALS THE MALE PART AGAIN"
Of ice cream with fragrant syrup
The taste of my happiness
The precious memories
Came to me in the middle of summer
I was happy because you were the gift
That stayed by my side
-Like a balloon on a summer day
-Like
I fly up into the sky
-I'm happy when I have you
-Milkshake
"IT ENDS AS YEEUN AND YEONGSEOK'S DUET"
Just how much did you practice singing?
He practiced a lot.
You practiced the rap part so hard.
Yeeun, you're a good singer.
Changsun, you can sing with emotion.
I sang it 100 times,
but I couldn't sing well today.
I sang it the worst today.
You did well.
-Who is your favorite singer?
-Do you know "The Man, The Woman"?
The man who wants to leave
I'll sing it.
-Can you sing it?
-Yes.
If you're bad at being "The Man,"
he'll be "The Man."
Okay.
I think I'll be bad at it. Shall we begin?
Let's go.
I'll lower the key by one step.
-How about two steps?
-Two steps.
"THE MAN, THE WOMAN"
You know this song, right?
You need to sing in tune, okay?
Okay.
Get into the emotion.
Because you might come back to me
To me
That's cute.
I can never love someone else
-We loved each other like crazy
"YEONGSEOK PICKS UP HIS MICROPHONE
IN THE END"
-Let's sing together.
-Are we singing together?
-We loved each other like crazy
"A DUET SONG BECAME A GROUP SONG"
The man who wants to leave
Back then, I didn't know
That love was a farewell
I didn't know
It's disconnected.
"I BELIEVED EVERYTHING"
We sing "The two of us" together.
-The two of us
That was funny.
You know…
-You were well-suited.
-Yeeun, 10 minutes remain.
-Ten minutes?
-What should we sing?
-Then…
-I wonder which song you'll choose.
Do you know "Thank you for Goodbye"?
I've listened to it.
-Really?
-Yes.
I want to be sentimental.
May I sit alone in a corner?
-Okay.
-I want to sit alone.
-You do this when you go to karaoke alone.
-Yes.
I need to lower the key. It's too high.
You want to be sentimental. How pitiful.
-The light should be dimmer.
-I…
-It should be dimmer.
-Yes.
"'THANK YOU FOR GOODBYE'
JI YEEUN"
I'll lower the key by four steps.
Don't make me repeat myself
Don't make me hate you more
I won't change
Let's stop hating each other
Let's save ourselves from more regrets
Let's just go crazy and break up
You and I act like it's love
"CHANGSUN GOES SOMEWHERE"
What's the point
Of ending things in words only?
Let's stop dragging it out and break up
-How about…
-Where did he go?
"CHANGSUN COMES BACK"
"CHANGSUN IS BACK WITH ICE CREAM"
I only brought two
because I have two hands.
"ONE IS OBVIOUSLY FOR YEEUN"
-Oh, no. You'll share it with me, right?
-Thank you.
Is it for me? Thank you.
Oh, no. Eat this.
I wanted to give it to the younger one.
Thank you.
Yeeun, stop being sentimental.
Come here.
-Really?
-Three minutes remain.
-It's time for the last song!
-Three minutes.
-Let's go.
-You don't know it.
"THEY PARTY HARD UNTIL THE END"
The date has ended.
That was so funny.
Seriously, your singing was so…
-It was funny, right?
-Yes.
I'm glad you relieved your stress.
-It was so funny.
-I had fun.
"THE TWO-ON-ONE DATES HAVE ENDED"
Yeeun, you must now choose one
of the two romantic interests.
Park Changsun,
please look Yeeun in the eye
-and say your last words.
-Seriously.
I hate this part the most.
I prepared a date that Yeeun would like.
She enjoyed my terrible singing.
I prepared the date in hopes
of moving her heart.
Pink hydrangea symbolizes
a fluttering heart.
Hold on.
It can be unsafe for the wrist.
"SWEETNESS PERSONIFIED, PARK CHANGSUN"
Despite being a terrible singer,
I tried my best to prepare a date
that'd make you happy.
If you choose me by any chance,
I'll prepare something you'd like
for the second date as well.
Yes.
Cho Yeongseok,
please look Yeeun in the eye
and say your last words.
I brought a present as well.
I thought you looked a bit tired.
This is…
Since it was hot,
I thought about what we could do
to have an active date
indoors.
Yeeun is cute, so…
I wanted to record the day with photos.
One, two, three.
The way she was so focused on singing
was very cute.
"THE MAN WHO PUTS YOU AT EASE
LIKE A FRIEND, CHO YEONGSEOK"
I prepared a second date as well.
It'd be a shame to part ways now.
Once more, I want us to go,
"Let's get it."
That's funny.
Gentlemen, please go into
your respective room
and stand by.
I'm in trouble.
"CHO YEONGSEOK'S ROOM,
PARK CHANGSUN'S ROOM"
It'd be a shame to leave now.
Yeeun, please open the door
and enter the room of the man
you'd like to go on
a one-on-one date with.
Please choose in three seconds.
Three…
In three seconds?
-That's insane.
-Two…
one.
Please choose one.
60 MINUTES TO LOVE
Translated by Dongjoo Park