You are such a despicable guy.
Why are you always provoking me?
Why did my mother want to raise someone like you?
In the future, don't provoke me if you don't have the confidence.
I thought you two reconciled.
Friends shouldn't be fighting.
Why should I reconcile with that kind of guy?
Are you alright?
What are you doing?
Why do you always provoke Hyeon Seok?
If you do not provoke him first...
Son.
Between family members..
No matter what happens,
we cannot give up on each other.
Honey!!
Mother said
that no matter what happens,
we cannot give up on our family members.
But at that moment, I realized that
sometimes we need to let go
so we can hold tighter.
Year 1995
The sound really resonates.
This is the result from drinking this medicine.
Granny, I kept a specially good one.
Give this drink to grandpa.
Yes, that's right.
We have to work in order to live.
It is good. Everyone please buy.
The medicine is unequally good.
A person's talent is a person's talent.
If not, how can he sing so well like this?!
Yes, that's right.
Everyone come and buy.
You don't have to fetch him personally.
He is my father.
If you can't handle it anymore, come look for me.
I have no problem feeding the three of us.
I really don't know how my father
can have such a good friend like you.
This kid.
You really can talk well.
The train will leave.
Hurry.
How many times do you want to eat tofu?
When will you come to your senses?
You should feed me properly.
It's embarrassing.
What did you do right that I should feed you properly?
If I have to feed you tofu again
that will be the end of our relationship.
This kid.
How can you talk like that to your father?
When you become a good father..
Say hello.
She will be your mother from now on.
This kid.
He might have thought you're a goddess.
I am Jin Sun Hye.
I'll be your mother from now on.
How is it?
Are you satisfied?
Are you not satisfied? She's asking you.
He is still flustered.
Don't yell at him.
We should get along now.
That day.
I saw an angel for the first time.
This.
He will now be your father.
He will be your brother.
Isn't he handsome?
Omma, aren't you too much?
We already disagreed.
Yet you still do this.
I can choose who I want to be as my husband.
But that's too much.
But isn't this too much? Our father is much more handsome.
Look at them!
They look like beggars!
They will look good if they wash up.
Washing up is not enough.
He is not a doctor.
Who said that my husband has to be a doctor?
At one look, we know that they are not good.
Why are you still marrying him?
Because I love him. Will it do?
Go. Take a shower.
You should wash up and get cleaned.
Tomorrow, we are going to register our marriage and have a photo as well.
How? How did you
find that kind of woman even though you were in prison?
You must have a secret.
You marry because of love.
I'm asking you
how did you made her fall in love when you were in prison?
There is this one word.
One word?
You say we are important
If we really are
you shouldn't be marrying that kind of man.
Soon you will understand
why I married him.
He will surely treat you like he is your real father.
So I married him.
I do not want to be a son to that kind of man.
I only want you to be happy.
I think that in this way we will become happier.
Please trust me, okay?
Go on. What one word is it?
What is the reason why that woman agreed to marry you?
It is fate.
Ah really. You.
What fate?
Father.
Did you lie again?
Are you going to cheat her?
Telling her that after selling a 1O billion land
we will be able to enjoy life?
Am I right?
Right?
You think she is so foolish she will let me cheat her?!
I don't think so.
And what you said also doesn't make sense.
I still can't believe that that woman will marry someone like you.
It's because of that word.
Love knows no boundaries.
Then you just overboard it.
I still can understand it.
What is it?
What happened?
Did you lie again?
Don't you think it's magic?
You have a mother plus a younger brother and sister.
It's a miracle. Isn't it?
My son who came from south to north.
The dialect has progressed.
How should we describe it?
Isn't this the most basic?
You and I still have the local accent.
So here. We must try to speak normally.
So this will be the price.
Don't you bathe in prison?
Look. It's all grey.
Look at this.
You also have some.
It hurts. It hurts.
Drink this.
Ah. This kid.
Father said something.
Having a family is a miracle.
So I am determined
not to be chased out by them.
Who would have thought that our life would be like this?
We are staying in a house with a swing in the courtyard.
What are you two doing?
Hurry. Get off.
Our father made the swing.
Why are you playing with it?
Why are you playing in my dad's swing?
Sorry.
We will not do it again.
Don't touch anything that belongs to our dad.
Don't touch.
Do you understand?
Yes, yes. We won't.
We promise not to touch anything.
Come on let's go eat with mum.
That..
If you do not want to call me uncle,
Then, you just can call me "Hey!"
Hey.
I don't care what I call you.
That is also fine.
Calling me "Hey" will do.
Then call me mugwort or wormwood.
Call me anything.
Why are you still not coming in?
The soup is turning cold.
Let's go.
Why are you checking it? Go inside. Quick.
I know
There are a lot of things I can't do in this house.
But I should not be chased out.
Therefore I must try to keep the promise of not touching anything to stay in this house.
What are you doing?
The wood is not properly placed.
I'm afraid it might hurt the kids.
What about you, Jeon su?
I feel like washing the window curtains.
I will do that.
I have nothing to do anyway.
You have night shift today?
Yeah.
I'll be back tomorrow morning.
This family has two reliable man.
My heart is at ease.
Omma! Omma!
Why? What's wrong? Cockroach?
The bathroom's drain got clogged.
It's because of Hey and this wormwood.
Hey and wormwood?
He bathed a while ago. Now it's clogged.
I thought I already cleared it up.
It's all mud.
You didn't rinse it with water.
I washed the window curtains that time. I'll give you a good dredge.
I'm sorry.
I'll go to work.
You all settle this.
How can you be like this?
Hope you can call us Hey and wormwood.
Mmm...
Why does mum work at night?
She already works 24 hours in the restaurant.
Your mother is a nurse.
What did you say to fool her?
She is a nurse.
How can a nurse marry a man like you?
A man with previous criminal records of fraud
Previous criminal records of fraud?!!
Our mother isn't crazy.
I'm really going insane.
This kid.
Be careful with your words.
They still have no good opinion of us.
Sorry.
Father.
Now I know
I must be careful with my mouth at home.
You need help?
Father
Please check if there's anything in need of repair.
I'll take care of it.
Alright.
There are so many things to be repaired.
Is it because this home lacks a man to take care of it?
Hey Gong Joon su
Why?
How come you are shy in front of your mother?
You didn't even dare to raise your head even once.
How can I?
Like father, like son.
You also steal a glance at your mother.
Talking nonsense?
When did I?
Excuse me, may I ask?
Do you know where Nurse Jin Sun Hye is working?
At the emergency room.
Thank you!
Mum doesn't just look like an angel.
She really is an angel.
Who are you?
That beautiful woman is my mother.
What? I don't care what's your relationship with her.
Hey! Go to your mother.
Tell her to give me pain reliever.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
What is this?
Where did you get this much?
The uncle I worked with gave that to me.
What did you do?
Sell medicine.
At every market fair.
What kind of medicine?
Every kind
There is also this medicine which enhances men's ability.
Where did you get them?
Uncle makes them.
That's not good.
Cheating rural people.
Is it bad?
Uncle said he puts things in that are good for the body.
No harm is done.
It's bad.
Is it?
But why are you giving me the money you earned?
I just want to give it to you.
I am grateful since you let us live together with you.
I do not know what I should give you.
So I'll just give you this.
Keep the money. Buy books and things you need in school.
For the wedding photoshoot tomorrow
Please use this money to buy father a nice suit.
This is the first time I've received money from a son.
It feels good.
I'll be going.
Gong Joon Su.
I'm very satisfied.
For giving me the money you earned.
See you tomorrow morning.
Be careful.
And that...
Why don't you ever call me mother?
Ahm. That.
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid that if I call you mother
This miracle will disappear.
So I don't dare call you mother.
Because I feel that only
when I stop selling those drugs,
that's when I'll deserve to call you mother.
Kids at the back, look at camera lens and smile.
Kids look at the camera.
They are just like that. Please go ahead.
Is that so?
Ok then. 1, 2
It doesn't taste good?
Let's get something else.
You want to eat sweet and sour pork?
Don't act like it's your money.
We're spending mum's money.
I'm just tolerating you.
We know this uncle has a criminal record.
So?
What so?
He has a previous criminal record.
If he is a doctor like our father,
then we will not be against it.
Our father earned a lot.
He also received an honor.
Your father was really very influential.
I chose him as your new father.
He saved me when we were young.
But that's not the reason why I love him.
And you listen properly.
My husband is your new dad.
Joon Su is also my son.
In the future, when you get married
I will not bother you.
I will unconditionally support you and you can marry whomever you love.
So you should also accept my choice.
This is not a request. This is an order.
Eat.
Eat like it's delicious.
That time I promised
that I will also find someone like mum.
I will love a woman with courage.
He's tall.
Introduce yourself.
Due to personal reasons, I am in 4th grade even though
I am already 13 years old.
I will study hard and be a good friend to everyone.
Do you have a poor eyesight?
No ma'am.
Then you just sit right next to Jin Joo.
In school, pretend that you don't know me, huh?
I will.
But the fact the we know each other
was soon discovered.
Your mother probably wouldn't hurt you.
Gong Joon Su!
You come here.
You are the biggest here yet you are the one who wants to escape.
My son, are you afraid that you want to escape?
At first, mum thought you to be brave. So it's not it.
You married again?
Yes, that's right teacher.
He is my eldest son. Please look after him.
Jin Joo!
Are you ashamed that mother remarried?
Mum, why do you only care about them?
You made a 13 year-old kid in 4th grade your son.
Is that something to be proud of?
I know you are hurt.
But how can I make you accept them?
Don't think that way.
Soon you have to rely to your father and older brother.
Do you know? He has a criminal record.
And that 13 year-old in 4th grade is his son.
How can I not be ashamed?
He is your husband.
You love him.
So you do not feel what I feel.
But everything matters to me.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I also have no way out.
When I grow up, I won't fall in love with a person like him.
I will not get married nor have children.
I became aware that
maybe having a family is a miracle to us
but for JinJoo and Hyeon Seok,
it's hard for them to accept it.
That's why I understand
why they treat us like insects.
It's expected.
I already said I cannot.
Teacher.
I will never forget this favor.
So, please!
Teacher, please.
You have been arranged to attend my class.
How can I change it?
I am being cast out.
You are the biggest in your class.
Who will dare to provoke you?
Teacher, I only have a big frame.
But I am actually weak.
If you do not believe me, try hitting me.
Must you really be like this?
You see. I am weak.
I really am.
Teacher Kim
Is anything the matter?
This kid. He wants to change class.
He says he's being cast out.
But the truth is he is not.
Is that it?
Let's get rid of the formality.
Let's have a man to man talk.
If you don't want to say anything,
just return to your class now.
I feel sorry for JinJoo.
Who is JinJoo?
My sister.
Are you twins?
No, we're not.
I am 13 years old.
My sister is 11 years old.
Then how can you be in the same grade?
Because I quit school midway and came here.
I feel like you have a lot to say to me.
Your brother will transfer to another class?
Doesn't he want to be in this class?
You're not Kim Jin Joo anymore.
You're Gong Jin Joo now.
Classmates, from now on
we will not call her Kim Jin Joo.
Instead we will now call her Gong Jin Joo.
The x-ray showed nothing serious.
But if his head aches or if he feels dizzy,
immediately come to the hospital.
Ne.
We are really sorry.
My child also had done wrong.
Things like this cannot be avoided between children.
Thank you for your understanding.
But this is really a problem.
My friend also plans to remarry.
Right now she is looking for guys with the same surname as her former husband.
Yes, right.
JinJoo's mum
You should also consider the kids.
Is that right?
How could she consider that a problem?
Sorry.
I didn't find a husband with Kim as his surname.
Mum, you really feel sorry?
In fact, I really think there is nothing to be sorry about.
Honey.
Omo! Doesn't this take a few days to prepare?
You opened earlier.
Although this is the first time to do it, it's not that bad.
You. Is that how you evaluate your father, huh?
Delicious.
Try one. It's delicious.
You really are something.
Eat first before you go.
Don't worry about her.
She will meet people like her.
She has to experience hardship to understand.
You have strong words.
You think so?
As a mother, I am not too emotional.
That's why she's with someone like me.
Bingo!
You just should have hit his head softly.
I also felt very wronged.
A lot of people also call me Gong Hyeon Seok.
Gong Hyeon Seok.
Might as well die and forget it.
Like this, mum will regret it.
You should not let trash be brought home.
Noona, if you die, what will I do?
I'll die with you. I'm scared.
You sit down. I'll push.
I will certainly not become like mum.
I will surely become like dad.
Don't laugh.
He sure can act.
I want to watch, noona.
You wanna die?
He laughed. My younger brother laughed.
He laughed.
My younger brother laughed because of me.
Here it is.
Thank you.
Please come again.
This the first day. Business is not bad.
You go inside and rest.
You still have night shift.
Don't you know?
I'm like the other people.
I don't feel tired if I have to earn.
And you married an average man.
We are destined.
My stomach.
Stomach.
Save me.
I have to live.
I have a son. He can't live without me.
My stomach.
That's why we came here.
Doctor save me!
I'm not doctor.
Doctor, save me!
I have a son.
I am nurse. The doctor will be here any moment from now.
Save me.
I have a son.
I ask you to please calm down.
The doctor will be here.
Someone please save me.
Sang Man oppa?!
Save me.
Doctor!
I am ashamed to meet you like this.
What have you done that you're in prison?
I committed something.
Fraud.
You always blush when you lie.
My face thickened through the years.
Is it because of me?
What are you saying?
It is not because of you that I live this way.
That time..
If you did not come..
Even if it didn't happen, you and I,
we still can't be married.
I am an orphan. I wander anywhere.
Your parents cannot let you marry me.
Right. And I also have to look after their health.
Several years ago, dad passed away due to cerebral hemorrhage.
Not one year after, mum also passed away because of heart paralysis.
Is that it?
You should have gotten married, right?
We parted.
What happened?
He is an upright doctor.
We were to open a clinic in a village without doctors.
We found happiness there.
But a typhoon came
He died saving the people of the village.
Oppa
Huh?
If not because of me,
perhaps you wouldn't become like this, right?
If you didn't
try to stop those thugs, I couldn't have escaped.
I am tired.
I am going in to sleep now.
Oppa, do you know?
You are my first love.
Next Episode Preview.
My first love will become my final spouse.
Isn't this fate too?
Why did you marry a man like me?
Son, you know mum loves you very much right?
I don't need it at all.
I don't expect them to accept me as their brother.
I only hope that they will not hate me.
Hyeon Seok.
Hyung!
If you again dare to threaten my younger brother, you'll be doomed.
Get it?