♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪Hello♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2=
=Episode 21=
Yun Xiangxiang!
I...
I never thought you could get
the seal engraving by Mr. Guo.
This is great.
Everybody thinks
that Mr. Guo is best at his painting.
But actually, he's
most skilled at seal engraving.
Unfortunately,
he never sells any of his seals.
That's the reason
why I had to buy his paintings
for the seal prints on them.
Xiangxiang.
I never thought
you could get this from him.
The name of the daughter
of the family Yun
is worthier than mine.
You are embarrassing me, grandpa.
This present.
I like it very much.
I'm glad that you like it, grandpa.
Mr. Guo and I had a special encounter.
I asked him
to engrave the word
"longevity" in Chinese.
I wish grandpa
a wealthy and healthy life,
and many many offspring to come.
I already have wealth.
I'll have to count on Sihan and you
for the offspring.
Mr. Fu.
The Chu Group sent someone here
for the Chairman's birthday.
Should we go greet him?
He's so handsome!
Is this the young master
of Chu Group, Chu Beiye?
He looks so handsome!
Chu Beiye...
Mr. Chairman.
Do you remember me?
I'm Chu Beiye.
You are a big man now, Chu.
I wish you health and longevity
on behalf of the Chu Group.
This Sayings of the Confucian School
is hand-copied by my father.
It's a gift for your birthday.
Chu Beiye should know
Yun Xiangxiang's real identity.
My favorite saying is,
words must be honest,
and deeds must be faithful.
Yes.
It's also our family motto.
Yun Xiangxiang is from the family Yun.
But you have to keep it
in your heart too
after you join our family.
You have to be an honest person,
and do honest things.
I understand, auntie.
This must be Mr. Fu's fiancee,
the daughter of Yun Group, Miss Yun.
Yes, she is.
Mr. Chu.
Nice to meet you.
Let's have fun, everyone.
Enjoy yourselves.
No restraints.
Miss Yun.
May I dance with you?
Xiangxiang.
Mr. Chu is our guest.
You should dance with him.
Mr. Fu.
I'll borrow your fiancee for a while.
I just made this drink for you.
Please have a taste.
Mr. Fu.
The Chairman has something
to tell you in private.
He wants to meet you in the guest room.
I see.
Okay.
You didn't expect
to see me here, did you?
I didn't expect
that you are the successor of Chu Group.
There's a lot you didn't expect.
Do you regret now?
Anyway,
I have my reasons to do this.
I hope
you won't ruin it for me.
You are so terrified?
Don't worry.
I won't tell the Chairman or your mom.
No matter why you pretend
to be someone else,
I believe you have your reasons.
I also believe
you won't use it to hurt others.
Thank you, Chu Beiye.
Xiangxiang.
Let's have another dance.
I'm sorry.
I have to go now.
Xiangxiang.
Mr. Chu.
Have a drink with us.
I've heard so much about you.
Let's have a drink.
Let's go.
Why are you here?
Why can't I be here?
Sihan.
We've known each other for so long.
Don't you think
you are a bit too cruel to me?
Qin Zhirou.
You drugged me.