♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪Hello♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2=
=Episode 32=
How is grandpa?
Thankfully, he is blessed.
Otherwise,
he would've been dead
because of you two.
I'll go see him.
Wait.
He said
he doesn't want to see you.
Yun Xiangxiang,
he asked for you.
Fu Sihan,
why would you do that?
If you didn't like the girls
I introduced to you,
you could just tell me frankly.
There's no need to get a fake fiancee.
Now you've made a mess.
I feel so sorry for you.
Feel sorry for me?
That's right.
I wound up in this wheelchair
because you felt sorry for me.
I don't know what you mean.
There's no one else here.
Why bother pretending?
Fu Sihan.
You are not trying to get me
to say something, are you?
You think I'll fall into your trap?
It's been years since the accident.
But believe me,
the evidence hasn't all gone yet.
Stop trying to sound tough.
What for?
You can hardly save yourself now.
Xiangxiang.
What did grandpa say to you?
Sihan.
Let's break up.
What do you mean?
I'll explain everything to grandpa now.
Don't.
I already told him
that I lied to you.
I think
it's time for me to leave.
I won't let you leave.
I'll go tell him everything right now.
This is my own choice.
You...
Are you sure you want to leave me?
Sihan.
During the time I've spent with you,
I was really happy.
But grandpa needs you.
This family needs you.
You have your responsibility.
Forget me.
You'll meet someone
who's much better.
Miss.
Are you looking for anyone?
No, no.
I'm just...
Enjoying the view.
Is it her?
You are the last woman
I'll fall in love with.
Don't you worry.
Even if you were the only man
left on this planet,
I wouldn't fancy you.
What are you doing?
Put me down!
There are eight rules you need to obey
while living with me.
I have rules too for living with me.
Just one rule.
Don't try to change who I am.
The dress is nice.
But you lack some elegance.
You...
What are you doing?
You had a few drops there.
(This is the first time I've seen)
(Mr. Fu cares so much about a girl.)
Well, miss.
What's your relationship with Mr. Fu?
She's my fiancee.
Let me have a look.
No.
Let me see.
You said,
Sihan,
I'm falling in love with you.
Yun Xiangxiang.
He's your boss.
You are his employee.
You can't like him.
Call me Han.
Whatever you like,
that is the rule.
All the dreams you had in your comic,
I'll realize them for you one by one.
Why would a real couple
need a relationship contract?