♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪Hello♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2=
=Episode 14=
(Obstetrics)
Wow! Isn't this the big star Qin Zhirou?
Everybody, come and look!
She's so beautiful!
Run! Run!
No one is healing you!
I'm dead!
Again.
Mom.
I lost!
Ugh! I lost!
Mom.
Xiangxiang.
I just talked to the doctor
about your new treatment.
We have settled it.
Good.
Let me introduce you.
This is my daughter, Xiangxiang.
This is Chu, Chu Beiye.
So you were the "mummy" I met before.
Yeah.
But I'm a friend of your mom now.
You can call me uncle.
Chu.
Let's have another round.
Sis.
Do you know how many times we've lost?
Please spare me.
I really can't bring you to win.
You are a bad gamer. Don't blame others.
What did you say?
Who are you to call me bad?
Yeah, I said that.
You are a bad gamer.
Come, my girl.
Help me restore my dignity.
You play with him this time.
Let's do it and see who's a bad gamer.
I'm totally in.
Let's do it.
First blood!
Double kill!
Triple kill!
Wow.
Victory!
Who's the bad gamer?
Great!
My daughter is amazing.
No way.
Dignity restored!
Okay, mom.
I should go now.
Work's waiting.
Please be good.
Eat on time, take your pills,
and listen to the doctors.
Got it?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay. I'm leaving now.
And mister.
Don't always ask my mom
to play games with you.
Thank you.
Miss. That's a wildly unfair accusation.
It's your mom
who always asks me to play with her.
Okay, stop nagging.
Back to your work.
Just go.
Chu.
Where's my phone?
Grandpa! Are you okay?
Doctor! Nurse!
Come! Quick!
Get him up first.
Be careful. Easy.
Take it easy.
Are you okay, grandpa?
Here.
Slow down.
Your phone.
Thanks.
Can I have your WeChat?
We can play together next time.
I don't play with a bad gamer.
Bye.
(Fu Sihan)
Hello.
How come she knows Fu Sihan?