♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪Hello♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2=
=Episode 16=
So,
there isn't anything
between you
and that girl, Qin Zhirou.
No.
And you have been
faithful to Xiangxiang.
Yes, grandpa.
Grandpa.
Sihan and I are so happy together.
He would never do anything like that.
Right, Sihan?
Yeah.
Ah.
(If you don't feed me,)
(I'll have to
eat something much tastier.)
(Sounds so familiar.)
(Isn't that the line from my comic?)
Ah.
Does it taste good?
Yes.
Don't call me Sihan from now on.
What should I call you?
Call me Han.
Okay.
Han.
Ay.
Seeing that everything is good
between you two,
I can rest assured now.
Chairman,
I've already contacted the press.
There won't be any comments
like those in this morning anymore.
They will only report the engagement
of Mr. Fu and Miss Yun.
That girl called Qin Zhirou.
She looks like a fine person.
I never thought she'd
use our family for popularity.
You know her quite well, right?
Go give her a warning.
Don't do that anymore.
Oh.
Okay.
Xiangxiang.
Yeah.
My birthday party is in a few days.
You and Sihan
must come on time.
Yes, grandpa, we will.
Right?
Goodbye, grandpa!
Who was it
that disdained my romance comic so much?
"Feed me". "Call me Han".
What about now?
You still need my comic
at the critical moment.
That's why I regret it now.
Your plot and lines
are really difficult to bring out.
And you are not much of
an actress yourself.
You...
Listen.
I'm not done with the time
when you kissed me.
I only played along because of grandpa.
That's why I signed
the contract with you.
This is your obligation.
Okay, boss.
I'm so sorry.
Okay?
They were so sweet just a minute ago.
Why are they arguing again now?
Ugh.
Why do I always mope for other's love?
I really don't know
how it became like this.
I see.
It's all because of Yun Xiangxiang.
She led me to the Obstetrics on purpose.
Yun Xiangxiang.
She really has some tricks.
My dad holds
some grudge against you now.
What do I do now?
Don't worry. I'm here.
Take his birthday party
as an opportunity.
Use your head.
Yeah.
Fu Sihan has made his engagement public.
Now it won't work to make a scandal
between Qin Zhirou and him.
You can stop those fake accounts now.
Fu Sihan.
My good nephew.
Tell me.
How can I ruin you completely?