♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪Hello♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2=
=Episode 13=
Let her take more rest
and she'll be fine.
Okay.
I'm leaving then.
Okay. Thank you, doctor.
Mr. Fu.
The doctor said it's not serious.
She'll be fine after taking some pills
and having some rest.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's late now.
Perhaps you can go to rest.
I'll take care of Miss Yun for you.
It's fine. You can go now.
Do you want to
look after her by yourself?
I don't care about her that much.
I just don't want her illness
to get in the way of our act.
(This is the first time I've seen)
(Mr. Fu cares so much about a girl.)
I understand.
I'm a professional private assistant.
I know when to be there,
and when to disappear.
I'll leave now.
Mom.
I'm so cold.
Chu He.
What happened?
What's wrong with him?
The doctors are still discussing.
We are waiting for their diagnosis.
After our examination and discussion,
we are sure that Mr. Fu Sihan has got...
He has got...
Viral influenza.
A cold?
What?
You gave me quite a scare.
What kind of sickly boss are you?
It's not a big deal.
Just give him some ginger tea.
Is this what rich people do?
I'll get berated to death
if I put this in my comic.
Ungrateful little...
She is ungrateful indeed.
Why doesn't she think about
whom our boss got the virus from?
All because of taking care of her.
Not grateful at all.
Hello, Dr. Zhang.
You called me earlier.
What's the matter?
(The new therapeutic scheme
for your mother is available.)
(We need to talk about it in person.)
Really?
Can I come over on this Saturday?
(I'm going on a business trip
on Saturday.)
(I won't be back until next week.)
(You should come as soon as possible.)
Now...