Hand over the antidote.
Otherwise, I'll send you to hell right now.
This poison is called Liangxinmian.
The antidote must be taken
with Lingzhi within an incense stick's time
to survive.
If anything happens to Qingshu,
I will make your entire Xie family pay with their lives.
Guards!
Someone is breaking out of prison!
Qingshu.
I didn't expect
you would be willing to die for Xiao Jingyan.
Over there.
Qingshu.
Search carefully.
Not here.
Search over there.
Okay, nothing.
Qingshu! Qingshu!
I've been able to cure this minor poison
since I was ten.
You scared me to death.
But you still shouldn't drink just any poison.
Do you really think you are immune to all poisons?
If I didn't do this,
how could I trick you out of prison?
Alright, I still have to rely on our Divine Doctor Yan.
Of course.
You...
Didn't you already take the antidote pill?
How could the poison still flare up?
Let me see.
Your pulse...
doesn't seem like...
I...
I'm actually fine.
Your Highness,
we've shaken off the pursuers outside.
I got it.
You've shaken off the pursuers?
Yes, we did.
All of them.
You already took the antidote,
yet you faked a poison attack.
You have ulterior motives, Your Highness.
If I didn't do this,
how would I know her true feelings for me?
Miss Yan is incredibly smart,
and you are quite the schemer, Your Highness.
This marriage,
I'm afraid the Matchmaker carefully calculated it
with an abacus.
Go back today and take the military flogging.
Who told you to bring her here?
I am willing to take the punishment.
Your Highness, it's getting late.
I'll go escort Miss Yan.
Go.
While I still have some patience,
let's finish
talking it out once and for all.
Do you really not have
the Record of Officials?
You are turning the tables on me.
I was the one asking you what the Record of Officials is,
and why the Empress Dowager insists it is in my father's hands.
As for the Record of Officials,
I only vaguely heard my father
mention it when I was a child.
It is a secret royal record
documenting the hidden affairs of all officials.
Palace secrets.
As for what the Empress Dowager said,
I'm afraid it's just a guess.
Since it's so important,
why didn't the late Emperor keep it himself
instead of giving it to my father?
Only after finding your father
will the truth come to light.
Any news on
my father's whereabouts?
We have a few clues.
But very soon,
we'll find his exact location.
According to the gossip Xiaowu heard,
these past few days,
what Prince Ling's Mansion transported to the northern suburbs
were not herbs,
but weapons.
Cui Tingru finally couldn't hold back anymore.
However,
the Xuanjia Army only has 800 cavalry.
Cui Tingru secretly raised 3,000 suicide soldiers
and 2,000 Black Armored Guards.
800 against 5,000.
If we fight head-on,
I'm afraid the odds are against us.
800 against 5,000 is a guaranteed loss.
Luckily, I have a good plan.
What is your plan?
You will know when the time comes.
Before that,
promise me one condition.
Okay.
I agree to all your conditions.
Cui Tingru knows my father's whereabouts.
Get the truth out of him before you kill him.
Okay.
Alright.
Business is over.
Let's talk about personal matters.
Personal matters.
Let's talk another day.
Stop.
From now on,
without my permission,
you cannot
kiss me recklessly.
Okay.
Next time before I kiss you,
I will report to you first.
You.
Report.
Your Highness,
the Empress Dowager has noticed something.
The Western Regions wine bestowed by the Emperor yesterday
was poisoned, wasn't it?
I have found out
that someone from Zichen Hall sneaked into the mansion.
This person is the Emperor's confidant,
always staying in Zichen Hall.
He wants to eliminate me silently.
The damn Emperor
wants to kick me to the curb when I'm no longer useful.
Fine.
Since the Emperor has no regard for our old ties,
don't blame me
for being ruthless.
This empire
is ready for a new ruler.
Notify the Black Armor Guards.
In three days at midnight,
we strike.
Who is it?
Father, you're back.
Linlang.
I accidentally fell asleep.
What time is it now?
It's already late.
Why are you
sleeping in my study?
I wanted to wait for you to finish your work,
and greet you before leaving.
Who knew
I'd accidentally fall asleep.
Look how filial my daughter is.
You've seen me now.
But I have something
to discuss with Mr. Jin.
Go get some rest first, okay?
Father,
you've changed.
You don't love me anymore.
Never mind.
Affections in this world all fade away.
Brother Jingyan did,
and so do you.
Your Highness,
the Princess probably heard it just now.
A little bird just heard the wind and rain.
There's no need to disturb her peace.
But she once had a relationship with Heir Xiao.
She is still my daughter.
Do not mention this matter again.
I respectfully obey your command.
Lord Xie, do you mean
that what is forged in the Heishui Valley furnaces
are Prince Ling's battle blades?
Prince Ling intends to purge the Emperor's entourage.
Every word I heard is true.
Prince Ling plans to, in three days,
raise an army and rebel.
What is the Empress Dowager's will?
By the Empress Dowager's decree,
you are ordered to personally lead 800 Jinlin Guards.
In three days,
bring back Prince Ling's head.
Since I am already meat on the chopping block,
beheading my former master would actually be a relief.
I, Xie Yuheng, accept the Empress Dowager's decree.
The Azure Sky is dead.
The Yellow Sky will rise.
In the year of Jiazi,
prosperity to the world.
Xuanjia Army, hear my orders.
Defend the imperial city to the death.
Attack the city!
Kill!
Cover your mouth.
Your Majesty.
At all key routes in the imperial city,
we have tripled the Imperial Guards.
The traitor Cui Tingru
will never step a single foot inside the city.
Absolutely impossible.
Where is Xiao Jingyan?
Prince Xiao is leading 800 Xuanjia soldiers
to engage the enemy outside the city,
facing Cui Tingru's 5,000 rebels.
Damn Prince Ling.
against 5,000?
5,000.
This parrot's ability to mimic speech
is far superior to the myna
I previously kept.
I think so too.
Just now,
it even squawked,
'Prince Ling deserves death.'
Kill them!
Cuimei.
Huachao.
Weikun, Huachao.
Long, Cong, Biao, Hao.
Shuang, Bin.
Shuang.
Ningzheng.
Hao, Chun, Kang, Shuai, Hua.
Weichao.
Wei, Chao.
Qiang, Yuan, Liang, Bo.
Xi.
Tao, Qiang.
Hui, Yue, Yun, Qing.
Yiyi.
Sisi.