Your Majesty.
The envoy of Northern Di requests an urgent audience.
He says it is a matter of great importance.
Granted.
The envoy of Northern Di pays respects to His Majesty, the Emperor of Great Feng.
You may rise.
I take the liberty of requesting an audience with Your Majesty.
It is truly a matter of grave importance.
Please dismiss your attendants.
Speak.
You were in such a hurry to see me
just for a landscape painting?
Please examine this painting carefully, Your Majesty.
Yan Qingshu.
Xiao Jingyan.
This painting is known as the map of the Heishui Valley iron mine.
Just based on this painting,
you call this a secret map of an ore vein?
Whether it is true or false,
Your Majesty will know once you send someone to investigate.
This gift comes at the perfect time.
Northern Di is indeed my good ally.
The Khan entrusted me to say,
since the Emperor of Great Feng gave us ten cities,
it is only proper to reciprocate.
Heaven helps me.
I was just worrying about having no excuse to punish him,
and now I have this ironclad proof of treason.
Guards.
Imprison Xiao Jingyan immediately.
He will be charged with treason.
He will be executed on a chosen day.
Summon Yan Qingshu to the palace to see me immediately.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Lord Xiao.
I am ordered by His Majesty
to escort you to the imperial prison for interrogation.
If you surrender,
your family will be spared.
My lord.
The Xiao Army is always on standby.
We will never let you fall into anyone else's hands.
Mo Yu.
I am here.
From now on,
everyone in the Xiao Army
is at the Princess's disposal.
Yes.
Protect yourself.
Wait for my return.
Wait.
Heir Xiao,
I trust you've been well.
Pardon my offense again.
Then I will trouble you, Commander Qin.
The Heir...
He just left like that?
Summon Yan Qingshu to the palace for an audience immediately.
Mo Yu,
deliver this letter quickly.
Understood.
Princess, please be careful.
The Xiao Army is always on standby.
Yan Qingshu, take a good look.
This is the evidence of you and Xiao Jingyan
colluding with Beidi.
What else do you have to say?
We did not draw this map.
This attempt to frame us is too clumsy.
The evidence is solid.
How dare you argue?
My signature
and Prince Xiao's red private seal are fake.
Are you saying
that I am framing you two?
The map of Heishui Valley that I drew,
I personally gave to the Right Worthy Prince of Beidi.
How did it end up in Your Majesty's hands?
Could it be
that the Right Worthy Prince gave my map
to Your Majesty?
Yan Qingshu, Yan Qingshu.
How dare you bite back
and slander me?
I wouldn't dare.
I just looked at the drawing carefully again.
It indeed looks like the one I gave to Prince Youxian.
However, I am confused
why this drawing is in Your Majesty's hands.
Please enlighten me, Your Majesty.
Yan Qingshu,
don't even think about getting what you want from me.
Hand over the Records of Officials immediately.
Otherwise,
I will make the eight hundred soldiers of the Xiao Army
be buried with Xiao Jingyan.
Fine, play dead.
Guards!
Summon the royal physician.
Your Majesty.
Lady Yan's pulse is erratic.
She seems to have been poisoned by a rare toxin and her vitality is dissipating.
I am afraid she only has a few months left to live.
Yan Qingshu, listen to me.
Hand over the records of the officials,
and I will spare Xiao Jingyan's life.
Otherwise, I will immediately order
him to be executed by a thousand cuts.
I am a dying person.
I can't even save my own life,
so how can I care about the lives of others?
Kill me or torture me,
do as you please.
Good.
Guards,
take her away and guard her strictly.
Use every means possible to keep her alive.
I will not allow her to die.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The game has reached its end.
The real contest
starts now.
I am the Son of Heaven.
My will
is the will of Heaven.
My choice
is the law.
No one can judge me.
No one.
I, Yan Qingshu, pay my respects to Your Majesty.
Yan Qingshu.
It's been a few days. Have you thought it through?
Exchanging the officials' records for Xiao Jingyan
and the lives of the 800 Xiao family troops.
My patience is limited.
Your Majesty need not repeat yourself.
I only have a few days left to live
and have no more attachments to this world.
Now, I only act for my own peace of mind.
Your Majesty's relentless pressure
annoys me.
Why not speak your mind to me?
If I am at ease,
perhaps
I might remember something.
Rest assured, Your Majesty.
My days are numbered.
Your Majesty's words
will be buried with me.
Alright.
I will speak my mind to you today.
The Duke and the Marquis of Zhenbei
were pillars of the state.
It's a pity
they were ignorant of the times and inflexible,
which ultimately brought disaster upon them.
By the times and flexibility, Your Majesty means
Your Majesty
conspiring to illegally forge weapons
and selling them to the Northern Di?
Insolent!
Even if I did it,
so what?
The borders have been at war for years.
The treasury is empty.
Without money and grain, how can we support the army?
Trading with the Northern Di was a matter of expediency
to solve an urgent problem.
Even if I did it,
it was all for the country.
What a way to be all for the country.
Then,
ceding the northern borders and Tong Pass,
dozens of military strongholds, to the Northern Di
was also Your Majesty's expedient measure
to enrich the treasury?
That was to end the war.
You are just a woman.
How could you know the cruelty of war?
I couldn't bear to see the people displaced
and the land engulfed in war again.
Exchanging a few cities for a century of peace,
what's wrong with that?
Should we end up like the neighboring country,
trampled by the iron hooves of the Northern Di,
with corpses littering the fields, to be considered wise?
What noble intentions.
Then,
colluding with the Khan of Beidi,
having shadow guards disguise as Beidi imperial guards,
and hunting down the Heir of Zhenbei who investigated the weapons case...
For what reason?
Was that also for peace?
Also for the people?
I could not let anyone else know
the truth behind those inferior weapons.
It was you, Your Majesty.
Three years ago,
the weapons that caused the tragic defeat of the Zhenbei Army
and the wrongful deaths of the Marquis of Zhenbei and 3,000 soldiers,
were ordered by you through Prince Ling.
Why would you ruin your own defenses?
Only by letting the Late Emperor see his flawed decisions
could I implement my national policies.
I did this all for the grand vision of Dafeng.
How could ordinary people like you understand?
What a grand vision.
For your grand vision,
you poisoned the Late Emperor?
Shut up!
He forced me.
He never cared about me.
Only that reckless Crown Prince...
A few days ago,
what Yan Qingshu said in his letter,
I
could hardly believe it.
Now,
hearing it with my own ears,
I am truly
burning with grief.
Poisoning the late Emperor,
violating human relations,
it's intolerable to heaven.
I am the mandate of heaven.
Everything I did was for the Dafeng Empire.
The process is not important.
The result trumps everything.
I have not let my ancestors down.
Dafeng is still here, and the people are safe.
That is enough.
Colluding with the enemy and betraying the country,
ceding territory to survive,
and even
killing the father to usurp the throne.
A foolish ruler,
a wicked ruler.
How can we let him continue to
taint the throne
and mess up the court?
Yes.
The laws are archaic.
The current laws
are not worthy of judging my merits and faults.
I want to amend the laws.
I will tell future generations
that everything I have done
was to protect the state.
I am not wrong.
Your Majesty is wrong.
Why are you here?
Your Majesty,
we old ministers
heard everything.
Poisoning the late Emperor,
framing loyal subjects,
colluding with the enemy,
ceding territory for peace,
hunting down the descendants of the loyal.
Now you even want to tamper with the law
to cover up your wrongdoings.
Your Majesty,
your sins are so grave
that both man and God are outraged.
Your Majesty,
you have lost your virtue before the world.
I have no face to see our ancestors.
We, your loyal subjects, tearfully beg you,
for the sake of the state,
and the people,
Your Majesty,
to abdicate.
Cuimei
Yong
Weikun Huachao
Longcong Biaohao
Bin
Shuang Bin
Shuangbin
Ningzheng
Haochun Kangshuaihua
Weichao
Qiangyuan Liangbo
Xi
Taoqiang
Huiyue Yunqing
Yiyi
Si Si