Young Master.
Father,
I
have returned.
You wretch.
The Xie family's
century-old reputation
is ruined overnight.
Xiao Jingyan.
We cannot exist under the same sky.
Boss.
What is it?
These are the newly made osmanthus pastries from the kitchen.
The steward specially ordered them to be sent for you to try.
They must have added double the osmanthus
to have such an overwhelming fragrance.
Sweet but not cloying.
Xi'er, you try some too.
You are kind, Boss.
But I dare not break the rules.
Try it.
Boss.
There's a distinguished guest outside.
They say they're from the palace.
People from the palace?
I, Xiao Jingyan,
risk my life to report to Your Majesty.
Prince Ling, Cui Tingru,
Minister of Works, Xie Wanshu,
and his son, Xie Yuheng,
colluded with Northern Di,
committed treason,
and massacred loyal subjects.
The evidence is conclusive.
Xiao Jingyan,
how dare you slander a prince in the Hall of Supreme Harmony
without any proof?
If I didn't have ironclad evidence,
why would I alarm Your Majesty?
Your Majesty.
The witness is waiting outside the hall.
Please examine this, Your Majesty.
Bring in the witness.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Prince Ling.
Do you still recognize the word 'Treason'?
It is the merit branded
by your Black Armor Guard.
This flag
was taken back from the Beidi royal tent,
wrapping the Marquis's last remains.
Where is your conscience?
What you sent
were hollow swords and spears.
Three thousand brothers,
three thousand loyal souls,
were hacked to pieces by the Beidi people.
Their intestines
were hanging on the barbarians' saddles.
In the bloody battle at the border,
we protected the country with our lives,
but you supplied defective weapons,
causing our army's great defeat.
Three thousand heroic spirits
were buried in the sand.
May I ask Prince Ling,
these past three years,
at midnight,
have you ever heard
the crying of my three thousand brothers demanding your life?
When my father's head
was made into a wine vessel,
where were you?
You were in the dark,
forging swords and arrows for the Beidi.
Your Majesty.
This letter
is the ironclad proof of Prince Ling's collusion
with the Right Wise King of Beidi.
I beg Your Majesty to seek justice for my father
and the three thousand Zhenbei Army soldiers who died unjustly
for the country.
I pay my respects to the Empress Dowager.
Yan Qingshu,
it's been a long time.
I am humbled.
May I ask why you summoned me
and what decree you have?
Just a casual chat.
Offer her a seat.
Thank you, Empress Dowager.
I have heard...
The Duke possesses a record of hundred officials.
Have you ever heard of it?
To Empress Dowager,
I have never heard of it.
The record of hundred officials belongs to the royal family.
Three years ago,
the late emperor secretly entrusted it to the Duke for safekeeping.
Now the new emperor is enthroned,
and the court situation is newly settled.
It is time to return it to its rightful owner.
I am ignorant.
Since it belongs to the royal family,
why did the late emperor entrust it to my father?
The Empress Dowager is asking you a question.
How dare you question her?
I misspoke.
But my father has been missing for three years,
with no news at all.
I will return it when he comes back.
Very well.
I have one more thing
that I hope Miss Yan can part with.
You are too polite, Empress Dowager.
I would not dare refuse to give you anything I possess.
The Heishui Valley iron mine map.
Please understand, Empress Dowager.
I know nothing of this item.
Hand over what the Empress Dowager wants,
and you may still leave in one piece.
If you disobey again,
there will no longer be the legitimate eldest daughter of the Duke in this world,
Yan Qingshu.
Qingshu.
Hurry and hand over the records and mine map to the Empress Dowager.
Do you really want to get yourself killed?
Hand over the things,
and I can still beg the Empress Dowager to spare your life.
At this moment,
other than me,
who else can protect you?
Are you counting on Xiao Jingyan?
Your Majesty.
I have important matters.
I shall take my leave.
I'll leave your head
on your neck for now.
Next time,
I will take your life.
Prince Xiao
is truly a young hero.
Truly, like father, like son.
Let's see who dares touch her.
I will tear him to pieces
and scatter his ashes.
Your Majesty.
I am tired.
You may all leave.
I'm fine.
Are you all deaf?
Her Majesty is unwell.
Leave Zichen Palace at once.
Let's go.
Lord Xie,
you messed up this act
again.
What exactly is this Record of Officials?
You are indeed hiding something from me.
We'll talk after we leave the palace.
Prince Xiao,
today at the Hall of Supreme Harmony,
you drew your sword and alarmed His Majesty.
and trespassed in Zichen Palace again.
I will obey the decree.
You will be escorted to the Ministry of Justice prison to await trial.
Okay.
I'll go with you.
However,
I did this alone,
and it has nothing to do with anyone else.
Commander Qin, please let them pass.
Men,
escort the Duke's daughter out of the palace immediately.
Lord Xiao, excuse me.
I can't just leave him behind.
The Ministry of Justice prison is heavily guarded.
We can't force our way in.
I am under orders from the Heir
to escort Eldest Miss Yan home safely
without fail.
Home?
Where do I have a home anymore?
Escort Eldest Miss Yan back to Zhuque Tower.
I am going to save him.
Are you coming or not?
Disobeying military orders is punishable by death.
I won't go.
The Prince
might die.
Then what are we waiting for?
Knowing you like wine,
I prepared this fine wine.
You should savor it.
Such good wine,
you'd better save it for yourself.
On the way to the underworld,
Mengpo soup will accompany you.
Stop.
Qingshu.
Xie Yuheng, how dare you poison him?
Give me the antidote.
If you want the antidote,
trade it for the Baiguan Xingshu and the Heishui Valley iron mine map.
Qingshu,
don't listen to him.
I don't have those things.
Yan Mingli said
you have the Heishui Valley iron mine map on you.
What if I say I don't?
Would you dare to poison the heir in this prison?
Why wouldn't I dare?
He destroyed the Xie family and stole my love.
He deserves to die.
Stole your love?
You are not worthy.
Qingshu.
I changed my mind.
You drink this poison,
and I'll give him the antidote.
How about it?
A life for a life.
You die,
he lives.
A life for a life.
You die,
and he lives.
Xie Yuheng.
Remember what you said,
a life for a life.
Qingshu.
If you dare break your oath,
my soul will fall into the infinite hell
and turn into an Asura.
For all eternity,
I will seek your life.
Qingshu.
Cuimei.
Yong.
Huachao.
Weikun Huachao.
Long Cong Biao Hao.
Shuang Bin.
Ningzheng.
Hao Chun Kang Shuai Hua.
Wei Chao.
Weichao.
Qiang Yuan Liang Bo.
Xi.
Taoqiang.
Hui Yue Yun Qing.
Yiyi.
Yi Yi.
Sisi.