♫ The dark green sea is hazy ♫
♫ dissipating in a flash. ♫
♫ Rivers and lakes divide the world. ♫
♫ Ten thousands arrows are firing at once. ♫
♫ Who has time to worry? Who loves the color of blood? ♫
♫ At that time, spirits are high. ♫
♫ Who calls the world his home? Who dares let his horse freely run? ♫
♫ Silently, tears form in the death of night. ♫
♫ Heroes are cutting all ties, ♫
♫ giving up whether it's life or death, ♫
♫ never asking what the cost is. ♫
♫ Good and evil must be distinguished. ♫
♫ The wind blows off the snow. ♫
♫ On the body, etch multiple scars, ♫
♫ wandering all over the world, ♫
♫ only wish to ask for answers from this world. ♫
♫ A teenager doesn't have to be a hero. ♫
♫ There is no need for flowers in the dream. ♫
♫ Destiny need not be afraid. ♫
♫ Because you have him all the way, ♫
♫ experienced a handful of conquests, ♫
♫ overcame a number of challenges. ♫
♫ From now on, happy and free! ♫
♫ The only wish is, with the world, ♫
♫ would come along the willing of change. ♫
[Legend of Awakening]
[Episode 6]
Miss Qin, the Qin family is from an aristocratic clan.
Instead of enjoying a luxurious life,
you're in pursuit of Mountain and Sea Gang, and having a hard time here.
I still remember the scene where all the Phoenix Ridge Gang were killed.
After my parents passed away, I wouldn't listen to my brother.
So I've been wandering around the world.
As people always say, "Pay your own debts."
If I hadn't been so arrogant,
Phoenix Ridge Gang would never have been destroyed.
Thus, I have to get to the bottom of this.
I owe them that.
Miss Qin certainly do have noble aspirations.
But aspiration doesn't work on dead people.
I won't be deceived by you again this time.
In the martial arts tower, the mechanisms are specifically designed.
There will be no casualties.
You saw what Wei Tianqi did to us.
Can you be certain that he won't rig the mechanisms?
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Don't worry, Miss Qin!
My life is far more critical than yours.
I don't have much time.
Lu Ping, you have to get out of there.
After one joss stick is burned, not even God can save you.
I think this mechanism is controlled by its engine.
As long as we destroy that part, we can get out of here.
I can use my Pneuma of Strength.
Doesn't your family's sword skills include the Pneuma of Vision?
See if you can see through how it works and try to stop it.
I can't! I'm not as good as my brother, I can't see through it.
You can't?
Forget it then.
What do you mean forget it?
What are you doing?
There's only you and me in the last moments of our lives.
What else can we do?
Now that I look at you, you're actually quite pretty.
If we couldn't sleep together, isn't it astonishing if we could die together?
You... Bully!
I'm taking my clothes off.
Even if I had to die, I would never die with someone like you.
I see it!
Miss!
Miss, are you wounded?
Oh no!
The Pneuma Confinement is unleashed.
I have merely one joss stick of time to use the Pneuma of Strength.
If I keep this on with Qin Sang, it would be too late.
I have to come up with a plan to force her to protect me.
Young Master Lu...Your clothes...
Don't look at me like that!
If I didn't do this, you wouldn't unleash your power,
and we would've been buried underground.
You have a sly nature.
Who knows what else goes on inside your brain?
Fine!
How about this? Let's make a deal.
I wish to obtain the Tianying Stone in order to be accepted in the Pneuma Combat Convention.
You may stay and watch over me.
If someone from Mountain and Sea Gang tries to contact me, I will be at your mercy.
But in order to obtain the Tianying Stone, I need you to help me.
Are you setting me up?
If I wished to do that, you would've been dead.
Why would I put myself through so much?
Ziyan, keep an eye on Wei Tianqi.
Make sure he doesn't cause any more trouble.
And I will be watching this delinquent.
- Who knows what he is up to?
- Yes, Miss.
Please take care!
And you too, Young Master Lu.
Listen to me carefully!
From this very moment, you are not allowed to leave my sight, nor talk to me.
You and I are suspect and supervisor.
If you truly are from Mountain and Sea Gang,
I shall use my Kuiying Sword on you.
Sure, Lady Qin.
Did you get his identity?
Master, his name is Lu Ping and he's from the Wind Taker Institute.
I have been watching him inside the tower.
That man is more than what he seems.
Besides, he is the one Young Master Wei is looking for.
If he is the mysterious man who met with Miss Qin at Ruyu House that day,
everything would makes sense.
Who would've known this man is right under our noses...
Lu Ping is now at the top of the tower.
Our men have been stationed around the martial arts tower.
We can make a move once the other disciples are out.
- But there's one thing... I don't know if I should tell you.
- Say it!
Don't you have to keep him alive for His Lord?
This man killed Xing Luo.
We're out of his league.
We can only take his life by using the mechanisms in the martial arts tower.
Sacrifice him to avenge for His Lord.
Only then, would His Lord spare our lives.
Give the order! Do it.
I appoint you as the commander, no mistake is allowed.
Yes.
The smell inside the tower is not normal.
Some of them went in and some of them head out.
Don't take me back!
- Let's go, Young Master.
- We have to, Young Master.
- I'm not done yet.
- Young Master.
Master ordered that, when the time is right, we must leave.
- I want my revenge!
- Let's just go, Young Master.
Wei Tianqi?
Why is he taken away by his own men?
This is not right. It's a trap!
Eldest Senior!
Mo Lin? Why are you here?
Did you guys defeat Wei Tianqi?
We defeated others from downstairs.
But the Wei Guards seem to have been ordered to take Wei Tianqi away.
The exam isn't complete, how could they throw their honor away?
Unless their lives are at stake.
I smelled some men with an unknown identity outside the tower.
They had weapons in their hands, so this can't be good!
Chun, take everyone with you.
And, get the Master of Chan State Academy over here as fast as you can.
Yes.
Su Tang, Mo Lin and I will go up to find Lu Ping.
I'm afraid he is the target at the exam.
Maybe your judgment is wrong.
Wind Taker Institute isn't a popular organization.
Maybe, it's that the Chan State Academy is coming for you.
This exam concerns the qualifications of Pneuma Combat Convention.
It's the goal of every martial arts disciple.
But the guys at the academy have all dropped out.
It shows how powerful the man behind the scene is.
I'm afraid they're scared of what Lu Ping can do.
So they deliberately lured him here, to finish him using the terrain and the mechanisms in the tower.
The closer you are to the top, the fewer people there will be and the higher their chances are.
So to speak, the biggest trap is at the rooftop.
I'm going with you!
You're Miss Qin's maid, what are you doing here?
Miss Qin is with Young Master Lu at the moment.
I heard everything you said.
She will also be in danger if something happens to him. Just follow me!
Wait, wait, wait! Wait for me!
- Tianqi!
- Master.
- What happened?
- Father!
Why did you have them bring me back?
I haven't finished the test yet! I didn't lose to Lu Ping and I still want to put Wind Takers in their place!
Get Young Master back to his room and lock the door!
He will not leave his room until the exam is over!
- Yes.
Father, what is going on?
My boy, behave and stay home!
Don't you go out and mess around.
Your life, my life, and the lives of our entire family are depending on it.
I thought you were good at what you do.
But why do I feel like you've weakened?
If Lady Qin is here, how can my poor technique even be noticed?
Miss Qin.
I don't know who you really are but a girl has to have her leverage.
I will give it back to you once I find out your identity.
Why is there another mechanism? Lu Ping, what is happening?
This isn't the exam! Someone is coming for us.
This cage is made by meteoric iron, not even my Kuiying Sword can cut it loose!
How can his Pneuma of Strength suddenly be so strong?
I've seen that chain before.
What is it? Who are you?
No matter who I am, I cannot die here.
I'll hold it myself! You guys go get them out!
- Big Brother!
- Miss!
- Su Tang.
- Ziyan.
Su Tang, this is meteoric iron.
Even Pneuma of Strength cannot break it, let me think of something else.
Get out of here with Eldest Senior.
Without me, I don't think the guys at Mountain and Sea Gang will go after you.
- Big Brother!
- Listen to me, shut up!
I brought you all in here and I am bringing everyone out! No one from Wind Taker's will be left behind!
Here it is! I think this remedy can burn the meteoric iron.
- Step back.
- Step aside.
Big Brother.
Assassin boy, your time management is spot on.
One joss stick of time! Not one second more, not one second less.
There is something wrong with your tower! Eldest Senior might be in danger!
You have to open that tower now!
You uneducated kid... It's true that you don't know how this works.
Listen to me! This is the exam, we will never open the tower in advance.
Eldest Senior and Senior Sister Su Tang are both in there.
Even the stubborn Lu Ping is one of our brothers.
If you don't open the tower now, the Wind Takers will never let this go!
We won't let this go!
- Open the tower!
- Open it now!
- Open it!
- We won't leave you alone!
Your skin is slit open. It's as if you don't feel anything at all.
Is everyone in Wind Taker Institute a lunatic who doesn't feel pain?
Brother, why didn't you leave?
Why did you have to drag Eldest Senior in here with us?
I was probably infected by the guy who only knows how to carry rocks.
Don't worry! Even if I become crippled, I won't blame it on you.
Shouldn't you clearly explain to me what exactly the chain on Lu Ping's body is?
Miss Qin, I don't have the answer to your question.
The most important thing is leaving together.
I'm sure the reason why he didn't leave is because he believes that,
if we do this together, it will be better than fighting alone.
Miss, I hear noises outside.
Perhaps, Chun brought the Master Wei here.
Wind Taker's disciples are in there, too, Lu Ping is not the only one inside.
Don't worry! Since the Killing Dragon Stone was dropped, no one can escape.
Once we set out the Hypnotic Smoke, we can then go inside.
As Master said, we only keep Lu Ping alive, the rest are doomed to die.
Set the smoke!
Oh no! I smell Hypnotic Smoke.
This place doesn't even have rat holes.
How much more unlucky can I be with you guys at my side?
What about the top of the tower? That is the weakest spot of the entire tower.
Mo Lin, can you use your silver needle on me again to gain me one more joss stick of time?
It's useless! You're used to the pain.
My needle can't stimulate your veins anymore.
Don't come close!
Disturbances in the three realms are like a burning mansion.
Only the invincible Mountain and Sea Gang can tide you over.
Miss Qin, you should just give in.
You really are one of them...
Big Brother!
Don't go! Trust your brother.
Then why did you save me?
His Lord was interested in your abilities.
He knows the only way to have you, is to lure you in.
Do you know how Mountain and Sea Gang deal with prisoners?
They drain every single drop of blood
and scrape every single bone of your body.
They'll show you the only thing you'll ever feel in this world is pain.
You should be happy that your guys at Phoenix Ridge Gang are all dead.
No more suffering!
If it was you, how long can you hold on?
Shut up!
Brother!
Thanks, Silly!
He's crazy! He's using Qin Sang's sword to stimulate his veins.
He's fighting against the Pneuma Confinement.
I think there's one Pneuma Confinement missing in his body.
- They're out!
- They're here!
Eldest Senior is out!
- Eldest Senior!
Are you okay?
My tower!
Senior Brother, what happened? Are you hurt?
Move!
What on earth did you do?
Didn't Headmaster make it clear?
The person who obtains the Tianying Stone and gets out the tower first wins the exam.
I, Lu Ping of the Wind Taker Institute,
retrieved it!
Headmaster, I wonder how many disciples of Chan State Academy passed this time?
- Yes!
- Tell us!
- None, right?
Although the tower is expensive, but it doesn't seem firm at all.
Now, Chan State Academy's disciples don't even have a chance to retake the exam.
- You...
- He's right.
- None!
What the devil did you do?
I was generous to let you inside the tower, and now...
You deliberately destroyed it, didn't you?
Fine! This is a capital offense.
Wind Takers, stay in Chenqiao Town for the rest of your lives.
You shall never participate in the Pneuma Combat Convention again!
He took off!
All right now!
Let me introduce to you once again, your senior, God of Bandits.
- He's God of Bandits?
- Lu Ping is God of Bandits?
I'm not dreaming, am I?
- Does it hurt?
- Doesn't it hurt?
He even acquired the Tianying Stone.
You don't believe my words, the words of your Eldest Senior, any longer?
It's true then!
So Lu Ping was the one who saved us from Mountain and Sea Gang!
- God of Bandits!
- Lu Ping!
Miss, why don't we sit down and rest?
God of Bandits! Lu Ping!
Let's go!
Thank you for the Tianying Stone.
A delinquent will always be a delinquent.
You just can't control your hands.
Stealing means taking without asking.
I traded it with something of the same value.
This is belong to the Mountain and Sea Gang!
When did you give it to me?
That is more useful to you than it is to me.
I hope you get what you want one day.
Don't touch my brother!
He needs to heal.
Miss Qin, all the troubles along the way are brought by you chasing my brother.
We don't know if the Mountain and Sea Gang is planning an ambush around here.
We should go.
Everyone has their own path, I wish you would stop chasing after my brother.
Brother, let's go!
Miss, are you really letting Young Master Lu go?
We still have work to do.
Don't you think what happened in the tower is a bit suspicious?
You mean... The Wei Family?
Lu Ping got away?
Who on earth is Lu Ping?
How could you fail with so many men and mechanisms in the tower?
He brought the tower to the ground, many of our men died in there.
Fortunately, I already told them to not wear our signature clothes.
At the moment, we haven't been exposed.
He broke the tower?
Even damaging the tower is a crime.
Gather all of our men to look for them.
Head to the governmental office if you have to, I don't care how much money we have to spend.
Have them guard the gate.
Lu Ping can never leave Chan State!
Master, one more thing!
There was another person in the tower.
Miss Qin! I thought you set off for Kaifeng?
Master Wei, did you know that someone from Mountain and Sea Gang entered the tower and tried to kill me?
Well...
Why were you in the tower?
Mountain and Sea Gang?
Even if they ought to commit crimes, they wouldn't do it in the tower.
They wouldn't dare offend your family.
They are thousands of mechanisms in the tower.
Perhaps someone of Wind Takers accidentally activated it
and hurt you unintentionally.
The machines in the tower are for the purpose of the exam.
But the ones I bumped into are all fatal and dangerous.
My Kuiying Sword couldn't even cut its iron cage.
This is clearly plotted!
Since you're willing to cooperate,
then I shall stay and find out the truth with you.
Okay... Okay.
I'll give out the orders.
Father! Help me, Father!
Father! Help me!
Do you have any idea who my father is?
Brother, what are you doing here?
Miss, please forgive the Agile Dragon Army for not arriving on time to save you.
General Qin, I...
It was impolite of me to receive you like this.
Please forgive me, General.
Big Brother!
After all the days you've been gone, so am I still a brother to you now?
Actually, I would've come home after a few days.
You wouldn't have to bring so many men to get me.
Even the Agile Dragon Army is here.
Outsiders would think you're fighting a war again.
If something did happen to you, even if the General was on a battlefield,
he would still come back for you.
Big Brother... I was wrong.
I shouldn't worry you.
I've been out in the world for so many years.
I don't need you to protect me like this.
You don't need protection?
Then take good care of yourself!
Are those the people who hurt you?
General! I treated Miss Qin like my guest!
I would never dare!
Please clearly investigate, General!
Sangsang, help! Sangsang!
How dare you! You don't get to call Miss Qin by her name!
Big Brother, this is just a misunderstanding.
I hurt myself accidentally.
Thank you, General!
I'm scared, Father.
Sang'er,
it's time to go home.
It's almost time for the Pneuma Combat Convention.
You should stay focused.
[Wei Residence]
Big Brother, about Mountain and Sea Gang...
The world will take care of the world's business.
But the Wei Family didn't help much with rescuing the Phoenix Ridge Gang
and now with the thing of the tower, they truly are suspicious.
Should you really not look into them?
Think about it! If what you said sounds like such a comprehensive plan,
how could the Mountain and Sea Gang allow someone like Wei Tianqi be a part of it?
Sangsang!
That sort of makes sense!
But how did you know I'm here?
Did Ziyan tell you?
You wrote the letter yourself, saying that they imprisoned you here.
Did you forget?
A letter?
Sang'er, is there anything else that's left unsolved?
Did anyone else pick on you?
General! Actually, in Chenqiao Town—
Nothing happened.
Big Brother, I promise you I will behave this time.
No more troubles! I just need you to promise me something.
Tell me!
I want him to send me off.
Me?
Sangsang thinks so highly of me! I, Wei Tianqi, will do whatever it takes!
- You...
- I—
Sang'er, are you really interested in that loser?
He's not like you, only scolding me all the time.
He, at least, will have a chat with me.
Sangsang! Wait for me in Kaifeng! I will go and find you.
Sangsang! Wait for me!
Wait for me! Sangsang!
Watch your step!
Our family conquers the world sitting on horses, what a joke would it be if you fall?
Miss, breaking the tower is a capital offense.
Are you not worried for Young Master Lu?
After all, he did he save me...
I mean, he saved your life, Miss.
If I didn't make the Wei Family escort us,
they would be in the hands of Wei Zhong by now.
Whether to live or die, it is up to him now.
I cannot help him.
If my brother gets word of this, it will be even harder for them.
Miss, so you intentionally stop the Wei family,
so that they can escape Chan State.
In order to protect Young Master Lu, you even admitted to the letter you didn't write!
Are you done?
You think Young Master Lu is a good person as well, don't you?
I don't think he's a bad person, since he is up against the Mountain and Sea Gang.
It must have been his idea to send a letter to my brother.
He saved me once and I returned the favor, and that's that!
If we ever meet again, I shall give no mercy.
Stop looking at it! I know what I'm doing.
It smells amazing!
I was too indiscreet to not have brought salt with me.
A little bit of paprika and cumin would have been better!
Eldest Senior.
I'm back from scouting, no one is chasing us.
Chun and Shitou have gone to let them know we're coming.
Let's rest here for a while.
If we travel for the night, we'll make it back in Wind Taker Institute tomorrow morning.
I never expected the arrival of Qin Qi; he made the Wei Family too occupied to notice us.
We got lucky!
Luck? I traded my life for that luck.
Is Lu Ping awake yet?
Serving him is draining me out.
Are you injured?
Your elbows are still attached and so are your limbs. So cut the crap!
Men don't fight with girls.
Eldest Senior, was it really not you who called the Agile Dragon Army?
I even thought your brother called them.
Su Tang, who exactly are you two? Tell me!
Perhaps, I can help.
Maybe I can help you save some trouble.
You can't help us.
Brother!
Have some water!
Brother, you were nice in the tower.
Why are you acting up?
That was in the tower.
What happens in the tower, stays in the tower.
Besides, the Wei Family and the Mountain and Sea Gang won't let us go so easily.
Are you trying to lose another leg by following us?
Wind Takers never lets anyone stay behind.
This is our rule.
Whether you want it or not, I'll obey it.
As you wish!
- Master!
- What did you say?
Lu Ping is the God of Bandits?
- Yes.
- And he even broke their tower?
- Yes, Master!
- Yes!
If you ask me, I don't think Lu Ping is a fool.
He's keeping all the skills hidden.
Yes! Eldest Senior said he and Lu Ping are both wounded, so they walk slower.
They want us to bring the good news to you first, they'll be here very soon.
Master, should we get ready to welcome them?
Welcome my head!
Come here, all of you!
Do you have any idea how costly that tower is?
Which part went out of our control?
Never mind Qin Sang's causing some troubles.
Now, Qin Qi, too?
Lu Ping sneaked out of Chan State right under our noses.
Master, he can't run forever.
No matter how far he goes, he still have to go back to Wind Takers.
Before His Lord starts blaming us, we have to get him back!
In order to keep everyone's mouth shut, wipe out Wind Taker Institute.
Yes.
Senior Wei, do we really have to find Lu Ping? He brings bad luck.
If it weren't for him, why would Sangsang be so far away from me?
And how could Chan State Academy be completely humiliated?
If we do not revenge, how can you call yourselves men of the martial arts?
My father is a coward.
But I, Wei Tianqi, will not tolerate this!
But Lu Ping is capable of breaking the tower to ruins.
Our men, including you, might not be his rival.
- He has a point.
- Yes.
Don't worry, my friends!
Everything is under my control.
Make it tighter.
Tuck it in.
Hurry up!
Carry ten kilos with you every day!
I don't want to see anyone lacking one step.
Get moving!
Master! It's daytime already.
Eldest Senior and Lu Ping still haven't come back.
Did anything happen to them?
- Yes, Master!
- Would anything have happened?
Did anything happen?
It's a good thing they haven't come back.
Who knows how much money he is going to cost me?
Sorry!
I let you down again, Master!
Eldest Senior ! Eldest Senior is back.
- Eldest Senior!
- You're back!
- Lu Ping! Eldest Brother!
- Are you alright?
You're finally home.
- Eldest Senior!
- I got you.
Be careful!
What took you so long?
Here, I got you.
Slower.
- Good to have you back.
- All right!
- I was so worried.
Stop!
Master, Chan State's exam...
We won!
- Rong.
- Master.
Head to town!
See if they have any followers.
Yes, Master.
Followers? What followers?
How could there be followers? What does he mean?
- How can this be?
- Didn't we win?
Surround Wind Taker Institute immediately! Don't let anyone out!
Master! Master!
The Wei family is here, in Chenqiao Town! They're coming for us!
- See?
- Coming for us?
I told you so!
They're coming for us, what should we do?
The Wei Family got to us before the Mountain and Sea Gang could.
With us here, we'll never allow them to touch Lu Ping!
- That's right.
- That's what I'm talking about! We won't allow it!
Although I don't like this Wind Taker Institute,
I hate Wei Tianqi even more.
So, I've decided to help you once more for free.
- Yes!
- Thank you, Young Lord Mo! Thank you, Young Lord.
Shut up!
You brat...
Ever since the day I took you in,
I knew you'd be a big trouble to me.
Get out now!
I said get out!
Master...
- Master...
- Why is this happening?
Now is not the time to scold him.
We can't let the Wei Family take Lu Ping away.
What's the matter?
That family has power and money.
Do you know that?
This guy?
He's a rat's poop, destroying the entire porridge.
There's no place for him here.
You clearly don't want to offend the Wei Family.
- Yes!
- Exactly!
- What a coward!
- What's up?
How embarrassing?
Today, I will not change my decision.
Who disagrees? Go with him!
Master.
Stay away from me! Don't call me master.
With everything that's happening, it's either his departure,
or the end of Wind Takers.
From now on,
you have nothing to do with Wind Taker Institute.
I'm sick and tired of that shabby little cabin.
Leaving is just a matter of time! The earlier, the better.
Su Tang?
I'll go where my brother goes.
Lu Ping!
Don't let your temper get in the way.
Rest, cripple! Don't break both of your legs.
Otherwise, you'll be taking your loser master's place.
Master.
- Don't push Lu Ping away!
- Don't let him go!
Master, don't do this!
Please! Please don't do it, Master!
Lu Ping... You acted like you were so sure.
So now where are you going? The Wei Family are almost here.
Come with me...
Master, we've searched the entire Wind Taker Institute.
Lu Ping is nowhere to be found.
You're a bunch of losers!
Spit it out! Where's Lu Ping?
Don't abuse your status!
Wind Taker Institute is small
but it's not just any place where you can trample over!
Don't, don't, don't! Calm down, calm down!
Don't, don't, don't! Don't fight.
Who said you get to do that?
Master Wei, sorry about that.
It's true that Lu Ping is not here any more, I fired him already.
Besides, once he heard your name, he fled with a tail between his legs.
Master, we can't talk to this stubborn, old man.
- Why don't we set this place on fire?
- Do it!
Don't! Sir! Please don't! Don't!
Master Wei.
I got it! That brat must have fled to the back of the hillside.
I'll take you there.
- Hurry up.
- After you.
- Let's go!
- Over here.
This way, please!
- Eldest Senior.
- What should we do?
Follow them! Make sure Master doesn't do anything stupid.
- Okay.
- Let's move.
[Ending OST: "The Paper Boat"]
[by Zhiqian Xue — Singers: Zhiqian Xue and Kewei Yu]
♫ Waiting to be buried by the lake in the town, ♫
♫ the White Paper Boat drifting with sorrow. ♫
♫ Lights on the other side of the sea ♫
♫ punched fingertips in the red water tower. ♫
♫ Watch the little boat churning, laughing at the ordinariness. ♫
♫ Like a kite being pulled into a low altitude, ♫
♫ I smiled to the leaving person. ♫
♫ The more spotlight, the more vivid the story. ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue. ♫
♫ Like a moat built under the sea, ♫
♫ waiting for the words on the paper boat to disappear, ♫
♫ there must always be someone who doesn’t remember listening to the other. ♫
♫ Anyone who is correctly guessed will end in disfavor. ♫
♫ You are particularly touched but others consider it ordinary. ♫
♫ Like the author, roughly put down with a weak stroke, ♫
♫ the writing boat on the lake was just like a paper crane in the air. ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue ♫
♫ Can a moat be built on the seabed?  ♫
♫ Wipe all the words on the paper boat! ♫
♫ Please let someone not remember and don't tell another! ♫
♫ Hide the reluctance between words ♫
♫ Unfortunately, I (you) are an average author ♫
♫ No matter how you (I) describe the rest, it's unnecessary! ♫
♫ Don't describe my unfulfilled promise! ♫
♫ Don't interpret my hidden fire-smoke! ♫
♫ Don't let the paper boat in the rough wave chasing me! ♫
♫ Don't wait until it over to know there are you and me! ♫