[Opening OST: "Young Warriors"]
[By Wang Sulong — Lyrics by Wang Sulong and Zuo Muxiu]
♫ The dark green sea is hazy ♫
♫ dissipating in a flash ♫
♫ Rivers and lakes divide the world ♫
♫ Ten thousands arrows are firing at once ♫
♫ Who has time to worry? Who loves the color of blood? ♫
♫ At that time, spirits are high ♫
♫ Who calls the world his home?
Who dares let his horse freely run? ♫
♫ Silently, tears form in the death of night ♫
♫ Heroes are cutting all ties, ♫
♫ giving up whether it's life or death, ♫
♫ never asking what the cost is ♫
♫ Good and evil must be distinguished ♫
♫ The wind blows off the snow ♫
♫ On the body, etch multiple scars, ♫
♫ wandering all over the world, ♫
♫ only wish to ask for answers from this world ♫
♫ A teenager doesn't have to be a hero ♫
♫ There is no need for flowers in the dream ♫
♫ Destiny need not be afraid ♫
♫ Because you have him all the way, ♫
♫ experienced a handful of conquests, ♫
♫ overcame a number of challenges ♫
♫ From now on, happy and free! ♫
♫ The only wish is, with the world, ♫
♫ would come along the willing of change ♫
[Legend of Awakening]
[Episode 35]
This is Old White.
He's also a poor guy imprisoned here.
- Unfortunately, he is insane.
- Snowy weed.
This drug... is not fatal.
The weed would be given to those who know the secret in the army.
They will lose their mind if taken over a long period of time.
They will forget their past and even forget who they are.
If I am right,
he is Lu Chenfeng.
What did you say?
He is Lu Chenfeng, Tianquan's Peak Master.
He is also the reason why I came to Wuji Manor.
How about Lu Ping and Qin Sang?
Don't worry.
I've settled them at the same place as your Uncle Lu.
They're safe.
I hope you can understand that
it's necessary for me to do that.
Father,
this is my fault.
I wronged you. I am sorry.
Now we've gotten the Thousand Pine Ruler back.
The Mountain and Sea Gang will surely come for it.
We must be more cautious in the future.
I am handing over the care of Wuji Manor
and the entire pugilist world to you.
I understand.
Go with your brothers and take the Thousand Pine Ruler to Wuji Manor.
Keep it under close supervision.
I will take care of the rest.
Yes.
No wonder he called me "Older Brother."
He was probably calling my father.
Lu Ping.
We met an old friend by chance.
Isn't that good?
It's just a pity that he doesn't remember anything.
Otherwise, I could ask
what my father looked like
and what my mother looked like.
You don't have parents,
but you still have me.
I will definitely find a way out
just because of your words.
We'll bring Old White with us.
This drug was for him.
Someone has a secret and doesn't want him to remember it.
What do you mean?
There's something that I think you must know.
Wen Rui had fought against the attackers before.
It doesn't seem like he's from the Mountain and Sea Gang,
but from Wuji Manor.
Recently, Master Yan has done a lot secretly behind our backs.
It seems that he was purposely trying to stop the Agile Dragon Army from eliminating the Mountain and Sea Gang.
- I even suspect that—
- It can't be.
Uncle Yan is a good friend of my father's. He also despises Liu Song.
He was injured last time trying to help the Big Dipper with their problems.
He does his best to protect me and the Big Dipper.
If you say he's colluding with the Mountain and Sea Gang, I absolutely don't believe it.
I don't get it either.
If he really did,
what's his purpose?
If Old White could wake up, that'd be great.
You shared some of his meal.
The effects of the drugs should have been weakened by now.
Let's ask him if there are any clues.
Maybe we can get out of here and find out who the mastermind is.
How should we ask him?
Let's stimulate him.
Qin Sang, he is just a pitiful person.
Move.
Who exactly are you? Speak.
It's you.
We've found a way out.
Old White is not crazy.
It's not a normal sword either.
It's a treasured sword.
With this sword,
I can find a way out.
Qin Sang,
do you know?
Actually, I'm the same as him.
I've been locked in a hellish place like this
for nearly ten years.
I almost forgot who I was before.
I thought I was the only one who the gods would bestow such a miserable fate.
I never thought someone else would suffer the same fate as me.
Old White,
you don't want to give up either, right?
So in order for us to survive,
we have to fight together.
Sister-in-Law.
Who are you calling sister-in-law? Your sister-in-law is here.
Forge the sword.
Sister-in-Law.
What did you say?
This sword was forged for your sister-in-law?
You…
Your sister-in-law is my mother.
Sister-in-Law. Return!
No one is allowed to go near the master's study these next few days, understand?
Yes, Young Master.
Hero Xifan, have you seen the princess?
What happened to her?
She has been looking for Lu Ping since last night and hasn't been back all night. So far,
we can't find her anywhere. I am extremely worried about her.
Don't worry. I've arranged them to be in the same place as your Senior Lu.
They're safe.
I had no choice but to do this.
She—
Xifan, do you know something?
The princess went looking for Lu Ping every night.
After all, she is young and cannot help thinking about romance.
I think... the attack was just an act they put on.
It's possible that they both eloped.
That's impossible. The princess is extremely righteous.
The Mountain and Sea Gang has not been destroyed yet.
How could she ignore His Majesty's edict and the Qin Family's reputation?
If she completes her mission and accomplishes what she wanted, will the result be different?
What do you mean by that?
I have to inform you of some news.
Wuji Manor has successfully retrieved the Thousand Pine Ruler as of the day before yesterday.
You retrieved the Thousand Pine Ruler? Then, why didn't you tell us?
Princess is not in the mood to discuss serious matters. You are indulging her as well.
Should I have still relied on the Agile Dragon Army? Matters of the pugilist world should be settled by the pugilist world.
I could only solve this by myself.
Young Hero Xifan, is this true?
General Wen, a few days ago,
my father and I besieged a team from the Mountain and Sea Gang. We indeed retrieved the Thousand Pine Ruler.
What about Liu Song?
He escaped.
However, we've solved the problem of the commander's seal.
I have invited people from different martial arts circles to Wuji Manor for the wedding.
This... wedding must be held.
Now the princess is missing.
If you send soldiers to look for her, then aren't you telling the world that the princess ran away from the marriage?
Who will bear the guilt
of going against the edict and resisting the marriage in the Qin Family?
Please provide me with a solution.
I have a method that will satisfy both sides.
The marriage can be held as planned. The Qin Family can keep their reputation.
The plan to exterminate the Mountain and Sea Gang remains the same.
The marriage will be held as planned?
The princess is missing. How are we going to hold this wedding?
Don't we still have an old friend of the Qin Family at Wuji Manor?
Father, do you mean Ziyan?
No. Ling Ziyan is a servant of the Qin Family. How could she—
General Wen, I will help you send people to look for the princess.
However, we still have to take care of serious matters. Think it over carefully.
Are you part of the Qin Family or a soldier of the emperor?
Father, do we really have to deceive General Wen like this?
Don't say anymore. Matters of the pugilist world should be settled by the pugilist world.
There are too many rules in Agile Dragon Army. I am annoyed about them.
Moreover, haven't you always wanted to protect your brother?
After this matter is settled, Lu Ping and Qin Sang can run away together to a faraway place.
As for the matter of having Ziyan marry in the place of the princess, I will report this matter to His Majesty myself.
Father, can I go see them?
No. We must eliminate the Mountain and Sea Gang once and for all.
Wen Rui believes in our words for now.
Don't cause trouble and make him suspicious.
Fan'er, you can't hesitate when trying to do something important.
We have found the Thousand Pine Ruler.
This marriage... treat it like Dad is fulfilling your desire.
Everything will be as you wish.
You just need to go with the flow.
Yes.
Young Manor Master!
Young Manor Master, Miss Ling is here. She said she's here to prepare the wedding clothes for you.
I see.
Ziyan, my father's decision was abrupt.
I am sorry about this.
I begged Manor Master for this marriage.
Manor Master, I am willing to marry on behalf of Miss.
I am willing to cooperate with you to complete the arrangement of His Majesty. Don't worry.
I grew up with Miss. I am very familiar with her actions and demeanor. There will be no flaws.
You have no relationship with Wuji Manor.
Why are you willing to sacrifice your reputation?
Young Master saved my life.
I am willing to share his worries and serve him all my life.
I hope you can fulfill my wish.
Xifan asked me multiple times to take you in.
This shows the importance you hold in his heart.
Since that's the case, then it's settled.
Thank you.
Why are you doing this?
I am a nobody. I've also received a great favor from Wuji Manor.
This marriage also affects the fate of Wuji Manor and your future.
I'll do what Miss can't do and doesn't want to do for her.
Ziyan, you don't have to force yourself.
I'm not forcing myself. I'm willing to.
Ziyan.
I want to marry Yan Xifan. Others may think it's an act.
You and I know clearly.
Xifan,
you don't want to marry me?
In this world, there is only one person whom
I would like to get married with and live with.
This person...
is you.
General.
You still haven't found her yet?
No.
Go check again over there.
Yes.
You, follow me.
Lu Ping, are we going to get out soon?
Are you in such a hurry to go out and get married?
I remember when you and I first met.
You kept hiding your identity from me. You didn't want to tell me.
It caused me to mistake you for being a member of the Mountain and Sea Gang.
Are you still blaming me?
I understand now.
You always kept it a secret because you didn't want me to get involved and get into trouble.
Why are you talking about this?
I was so cruel to you at that time because I wanted to protect you.
You grew up from much suffering, yet you are still so tenacious.
I come from a noble family, but I can do nothing for you.
I will lose the Qin Family's reputation.
I am a man. How can I have a girl protecting me?
Isn't that even more humiliating?
Lu Ping, if this time Yan Qiuci's really has bad intentions,
what are you going to do?
I will ask him personally.
I will accompany you.
Those heroic words Miss Qin said before,
still can't withstand my masculinity.
You brat. I hate people who don't say what they mean the most in my life.
I've been sitting for too long. It's uncomfortable.
Elder Brother, it's done.
Done?
Good, Old White. You're good.
We haven't put the first edge on it.
There's no time. We need to get out of here first.
Lu Ping. Miss Qin.
We are facing the Mountain and Sea Gang right now.
For Wuji Manor and Shuo State,
the truth can only be hidden along with Junior Lu.
Everyone will think that you two are a couple living a sequestered life.
They won't search for you anymore.
Liu Song, I won't let you escape from me again this time.
We've almost succeeded.
Go on.
What's wrong?
Hurt.
I have a headache.
This is bad. It's toxic smoke.
Someone wants to kill us. We have to hurry out of here.
Old White, hurry and run. Let's go.
- Qin Sang.
- Elder Brother.
Let's go. Hurry. Let's go.
Old White, you're a good person.
You should know that I can't leave my wife behind.
If we can't get out, you should live your life well. Do you hear me?
Go. Go.
Qin Sang, can you hear me?
Silly, why did you come back?
Qin Sang, I always say you're a fool,
but I am the biggest fool myself.
No. The four pneumas are not enough.
I need to break another lock. If I can break another, then I can save you.
Lu Ping, don't do that anymore. You'll die.
I don't believe I can't save you.
Lu Ping. Lu Ping.
Lu Ping.
Chenfeng,
forge a sword for my wife.
Weapons are divided into Yin and Yang. Yin and Yang coexist.
They will never be separated.
Okay.
I will forge it will cold iron, and finish the edge with blood. It will definitely be a good sword.
Elder Brother, what do you want to name this sword?
Wifey, do you have a good name for it?
Let's call it... Dream.
D-Dream.
Finish the edge with blood. Finish the edge with blood.
You need to finish the edge with blood. Finish the edge with blood! Finish the edge with blood!
Elder Brother, I remember! You need to finish the edge of the sword with blood.
Yes. Dream. We still have Dream.
Qin Sang!
Is it because of the toxic smoke or because she bled too much?
Qin Sang! Qin Sang.
It's the Cold toxin. Cold toxin in her body.
Is there something wrong with your sword? Did you poison it?!
No. No.
It's the cold iron from the bottom of the lake.
I need to find Wen Rui. He should have a way. Old White!
Why are you staring blankly?
Father.
I've sent invitations. Uncles from all sects are here.
This a big opportunity. I will introduce them to you later.
Father, when will we eliminate the Mountain and Sea Gang?
We eat one bite at a time. We do things one step at a time.
Eliminating the Mountain and Sea Gang will be the first big thing you do in the pugilist world.
Then, can I meet Lu Ping after I've accomplished that?
It is your wedding today. You are marrying the girl you love.
Cheer up.
If you can't find her, then keep looking! If she's alive, I want to see her. If she's dead, I want to see her corpse!
- Yes!
- Wen Rui.
Princess!
Hurry and find a doctor.
Look at what you did to the princess.
You couldn't protect her with an army.
How about you?
General, Princess has cold toxin in her body. This—
Hurry and make some ginger soup. Then get a fire to warm up the princess.
Yes. I am on it.
Lu Ping. Lu Ping.
I am here. Do you feel better?
Where am I?
Princess, you're in the mansion at Wuji Manor.
It's my fault that you got hurt.
Yes. It is your fault.
A question for you. We went to Wuji Manor just now. Why is there red everywhere?
What's going on?
Master Yan insists on the wedding despite the disappearance of the princess.
It's a marriage bestowed by His Majesty. There's nothing I can do.
Wedding? Qin Sang wasn't here. Who will Xifan marry?
What's wrong with Wuji Manor?
Wuji Manor.
Elder Brother! Sister-in-Law!
W-Wuji Manor.
Old White, what's wrong? What's wrong, Old White. Old White, what's wrong?
Elder Brother. Sister-in-Law. I saw them again.
- Everything's okay.
- I saw them again.
Miss, who is he?
He is Lu Chenfeng.
Old White, don't be scared.
- He is out of his mind.
- You're okay.
You're okay.
He only trusts Lu Ping. Don't disturb him.
Old White.
I remember.
What do you remember?
The reason why I have painstakingly stayed here for 19 years.
Elder Brother is here. You can tell me.
You're a liar! My elder brother is already dead.
Old White, do you remember?
I need you to kill him for me.
Kill my foe for me.
I want to avenge my elder brother!
Why don't you kill him by yourself?
Who is he?
I don't know martial arts.
My elder brother, sister-in-law, and other seniors and juniors,
they all know martial arts except for me.
I only know how to forge weapons.
I thought with my elder brother around,
he would be able to protect me my whole life.
Because of this, I couldn't protect him the day he was killed.
Even though I don't know who you are,
but I can only rely on you now.
What is his name?
He…
I don't know. I remembered just now.
I only know he is at Wuji Manor.
Wuji Manor. Wuji Manor.
Wuji Manor.
Come out with me. I have something to ask.
Why?
- Let go of me.
- Tell me the truth.
What happened at Wuji Manor these past few days when Qin Sang and I were trapped?
Yan Qiuci has already gotten the Thousand Pine Ruler back from the Mountain and Sea Gang.
Today's wedding is for Xifan and Ling Ziyan.
He used Qin's reputation
and frontier military defense as excuses.
I... couldn't stop him.
He is good to his own son.
How about the son of his friend?
To the son of his brother?
What do you mean by that? What are you going to do?
What can I do?
We are old friends.
We can talk about the past.
Master, wait for me. Master.
- What's wrong with you again?
- Master.
The Pneuma of Energy is for moving light on your feet.
It's for you to move quickly.
It's not for running forward day and night.
We have been running for a whole day. Horses would die running like this.
I am the next to die from exhaustion.
I am afraid that my elder brother won't make it if we don't get there in time.
Master, why don't you carry me?
What did you say?!
Wait.
Master, the smell of Boss.
Something is wrong.
Old White.
I am taking him to Wuji Manor.
Lu Ping, it is Xifan's wedding.
Although Yan Qiuci is unpredictable,
he is determined to destroy the Mountain and Sea Gang.
In case someone is controlling Wuji Manor from behind
or there are secrets,
we have to wait until we find out the truth.
Don't be impulsive.
Don't worry.
Xifan's wedding... I know what to do.
I have come to an agreement with Wen Rui.
He will attend the wedding tonight and bring Old White and me into the manor.
I'm just checking.
Whatever the outcome is, I will discuss it with you.
You should rest here.
Wait for me to return.
Take care of yourself.
Let's go, Old White.
[Wuji]
Master Liu. Nice to meet you.
Old White.
It is a big event today. You need to listen to me.
Yes, Elder Brother.
Why do you still call me "Elder Brother"?
Don't worry. Today, you only need to identify the enemy.
I will take care of the rest.
Manor Master Yan, congratulations!
Everyone, please have a seat.
I am indebted to everyone here, being the master of
the martial arts circle for years.
Recently, the Mountain and Sea Gang is causing trouble in the pugilist world.
I will have to fight against the gang with you.
Today, my son and Princess Xining are getting married on behalf of His Majesty's wishes.
After the wedding, they will work together with Wuji Manor and you
to eliminate the scum in the pugilist world
and maintain justice.
Great!
It's time. Please welcome the bride!
[Wuji]
You don't even wait for me to drink with you on your wedding day.
Do you remember our brotherhood?
Old White.
Look carefully. Is your enemy here?
The Yan Family is skilled in using the sword.
Today, I will pass on the family's treasure, this sword, to my son.
This means that I also pass on the Yan Family to Xifan.
I hope you all can take care of my son in the future.
Xifan, take this.
Thank you, Father.
Congratulations, Young Manor Master!
Old White, what's wrong?
The sword.
The man with the sword.
It's him.
He was the one who killed my elder brother.
[Ending OST: "The Paper Boat"]
[by Zhiqian Xue — Singers: Zhiqian Xue and Kewei Yu]
♫ Waiting to be buried by the lake in the town, ♫
♫ the White Paper Boat drifting with sorrow ♫
♫ Lights on the other side of the sea ♫
♫ punched fingertips in the red water tower ♫
♫ Watch the little boat churning, laughing at the ordinariness ♫
♫ Like a kite being pulled into a low altitude, ♫
♫ I smiled to the leaving person ♫
♫ The more spotlight, the more vivid the story ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue ♫
♫ Like a moat built under the sea, ♫
♫ waiting for the words on the paper boat to disappear, ♫
♫ there must always be someone who doesn’t
remember listening to the other ♫
♫ Anyone who is correctly guessed will end in disfavor ♫
♫ You are particularly touched but others consider it ordinary ♫
♫ Like the author, roughly put down with a weak stroke, ♫
♫ the writing boat on the lake was just like
a paper crane in the air ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue ♫
♫ Can a moat be built on the seabed? ♫
♫ Wipe all the words on the paper boat! ♫
♫ Please let someone not remember and don't tell another! ♫
♫ Hide the reluctance between words ♫
♫ Unfortunately, I (you) am (are) an average author ♫
♫ No matter how you (I) describe the rest, it's unnecessary! ♫
♫ Don't describe my unfulfilled promise! ♫
♫ Don't interpret my hidden fire-smoke! ♫
♫ Don't let the paper boat in the rough wave chasing me! ♫
♫ Don't wait until it's over to know there are you and me! ♫