[Opening OST: "Young Warriors"]
[By Wang Sulong — Lyrics by Wang Sulong and Zuo Muxiu]
♫ The dark green sea is hazy ♫
♫ dissipating in a flash ♫
♫ Rivers and lakes divide the world ♫
♫ Ten thousands arrows are firing at once ♫
♫ Who has time to worry? Who loves the color of blood? ♫
♫ At that time, spirits are high ♫
♫ Who calls the world his home?
Who dares let his horse freely run? ♫
♫ Silently, tears form in the death of night ♫
♫ Heroes are cutting all ties, ♫
♫ giving up whether it's life or death, ♫
♫ never asking what the cost is ♫
♫ Good and evil must be distinguished ♫
♫ The wind blows off the snow ♫
♫ On the body, etch multiple scars, ♫
♫ wandering all over the world, ♫
♫ only wish to ask for answers from this world ♫
♫ A teenager doesn't have to be a hero ♫
♫ There is no need for flowers in the dream ♫
♫ Destiny need not be afraid ♫
♫ Because you have him all the way, ♫
♫ experienced a handful of conquests, ♫
♫ overcame a number of challenges ♫
♫ From now on, happy and free! ♫
♫ The only wish is, with the world, ♫
♫ would come along the willing of change ♫
[Legend of Awakening]
[Episode 41]
I brought you here
because I wanted to see you in your wedding outfit.
As long as I know in my heart
that you're here waiting for me, I will definitely come back.
Father.
You are getting married. Why are you here all by yourself?
I am nervous. I wanted to sit here for a bit alone.
Father, why don't you keep me company?
You brat.
Your marriage was decided in such a hurry.
There's still a lot of matters to take care of in the valley.
I've been out there for so long, how long has it been since I spent time with you?
Right? Come, come.
Come here. Have a seat. Sit!
Fine. Fine. Fine!
You're about to get married but you're still acting like a kid.
You only know how to idle around.
Aren't you used to it by now?
Besides, don't you think your son is dressed particularly nice and looks really handsome today?
You brat.
You're about to be married. You're an adult now.
I think that girl you chose really is pretty great.
You're like me. You know how to pick them.
Then form today onward, I'm entrusting the Carefree Valley to you.
Just in time. This year's herbs are almost ready for harvesting.
You have to pay attention to it. Understand?
Father, why do you have so little ambition?
I used to praise you before as a great hero.
Great hero? Is it so easy to be a great hero?
A great hero... Leng Xiutang was a great hero.
Didn't he still die in the end?
I don't expect much from you.
All you have to do is guard Carefree Valley well
and live a safe life. Got it?!
Yes.
I know my limitations.
Compared to Lu Ping and Xifan, I may be nothing.
At least I've always thought so.
In this life, all I can do is follow them.
Father, you said before that when a man gets married, it means he's grown up.
He should learn to take responsibility for things.
So I have one more thing to do.
Wait. wait.
Silly kid.
Are you about to do something silly?
Father.
My Pneuma of Pivot has been stronger than yours for a while now.
Don't worry.
I will be a great hero for you.
I am not good at Pneuma of Pivot,
but I have to try.
What are you thinking about?
Why are you here?
The assassin and Su Tang are getting married today.
Su Tang said that you are still a Wind Taker senior.
You have to be there.
She asked me to invite you.
I thought... we wouldn't have the chance to drink together ever again.
I owe you an apology for the matter from before.
I almost killed you at Wuji Manor last time.
Consider us even.
Lu Ping, thank you.
Hey, don't worry about it.
Brothers aren't particular about these things.
I just hope you won't hide anything from me from now on.
All right. Let's have a good time tonight.
Let's drink instead of talk.
- What's wrong?
- It's bad.
Ziyan took the token Mo Lin gave me before.
She must've gone to find Mo Lin.
You're finally here.
Did anyone notice?
Don't worry.
They're all busy preparing my wedding.
No one will pay attention to the back mountain.
I will keep watch for you.
Be careful.
It's my fault I can't help you.
I'm not doing this because you begged me to.
I am willing to do it.
Besides, my death isn't necessarily certain.
Wait for me to get this done. I still have to head back and get married.
Young Master Mo, you have to succeed.
That's the only way we can all live.
Never mind. I will take the gamble.
Seeing as I'm lucky enough to be able to marry Master,
I'm sure I can get back safely.
As long as the flower blooms, then get rid of the poison, then it's done.
I can bear this pain.
Master. Master?
Where is Mo Lin? That brat. Did he go do stupid things again?
Master. Young Master Lu Ping and Young Master Xifan entered the valley just now.
They said… They said younger master might have hastened to bloom the Two Form Flower.
Disciples in the valley have already gone with them to the Forbidden House.
What? How? What?
Why are you still standing here?!
Go. Hurry, let's go!
Ziyan, why did you do this?
I know I acted on my own.
But at least if Mo Lin tries to bloom the Two Form Flower,
he has a higher chance of survival than you.
You asked Mo Lin to risk his life on his wedding night.
Did you think about Su Tang?
I said before, a hero shows up at the last moment.
You brat!
You...
You brat.
You did it. You got the flower to bloom.
Father, I have told you.
This is a piece of cake for the World's No.1 Assassin.
You brat. You even lied to me.
Let me tell you. The next time you try this, see how I handle you!
Why didn't you discuss such a big matter with me? What if something happened, what would happen to Su Tang?
Ziyan put forward such an unreasonable request and you still had to join in the mess with her?
Don't be mad. Look, I haven't been poisoned to death, right?
Besides, this time I did something right.
Boss, there's something related to Qin Sang that I can finally say now.
- Brat.
- Mo Lin.
Brat.
Brat, were you poisoned before?
Younger Master said it was just a little poison.
Master Mo, what's wrong with Mo Lin?
He had already succeeded.
But he was poisoned by something else and his last injury wasn't completely cured yet.
The two poisons have been added together. It's penetrated the viscera from the wound.
Boss,
don't feel sorry for me. I not only did this for you.
But for Qin Sang,
she asked me to keep it from you.
In fact, she has been poisoned by the cold toxin.
Her whole body's meridians
are completely out of order.
She is in extreme danger.
Boss,
I thought if the Two Form Flower could save you,
it could save her as well.
I could bloom this one for you and then plant another for her.
I didn't expect that I wouldn't have enough time.
Mo Lin, you can't die.
Su Tang is waiting for you to get married.
Father, I am sorry.
In this life, I've spent all the luck I had
being able to marry Su Tang.
Mo Lin. Mo Lin!
Mo Lin.
Mo Lin!
Mo Lin! Mo Lin!
Don't you want to get married?
You sent Mo Lin to die!
It's not Xifan's fault. He wanted to bloom the Two Form Flower by himself.
I'm the one that didn't want him to do it so I went to beg Mo Lin.
If you want to find someone to relieve your anger on, kill me then.
Xifan doesn't want you to die and he wants to protect Wuji Manor as well.
He just wanted to balance loyalty and friendship. He's already suffered enough.
Mr. Lu Ping, it's bad. The Agile Dragon Army has surrounded Carefree Valley. They want to break in.
They said unless we turn you over, they won't leave.
Why is the Agile Dragon Army here?
Ziyan, did you ask them to surround the Carefree Valley?
Before I entered the valley I gave Wen Rui the order.
If I didn't come out of the valley tonight, he'll lead the troops to surround the valley.
Xifan, now that the Two Form Flower has bloomed, Lu Ping can go back to Kaifeng.
This is your hardship?
You still only want to complete the emperor's order.
The younger master of Wuji Manor...
has become a dog for the imperial court.
Yan Xifan,
you killed your brother.
Xifan, if we don't take Lu Ping now, there won't be any time left.
Get out, all of you!
This is Mo territory. If the Agile Dragon Army wants to enter,
let's see if they're capable of it!
Chuangu,
- throw them out.
- Yes!
Master Mo, I…
I won't kill you two only because you were Mo Lin's brothers once.
All of you, get out now!
Get out!
Su Tang is still waiting for you.
So fragrant.
Osmanthus forest. There are more trees than the last time I saw it!
Master, do you know?
Assassins have a rule when working.
As long as there's someone we care about in our heart, then death won't take us.
Mo Lin!
Brother, where is Mo Lin?
Su Tang,
stop waiting.
I won't go. Mo Lin promised he would come back for me.
I have to wait for him.
Su Tang...
He won't be coming back.
Impossible.
He is the World's No.1 Assassin.
He has the best luck.
He always says, the great hero shows up at the last moment.
I have to wait for him to come back.
If I leave, he won't be able to find me.
I am sorry, Su Tang.
I am sorry.
Master, I'm entrusting Su Tang to you.
You're leaving?
You are right. The Power of Awakening is strong.
Wherever I go, there's going to be strife.
Maybe my leaving is the best way to protect you.
If you leave, then what about your Pneuma Confinement?
Master,
I don't want much.
I only want to be a common man.
But the talent of the Power of Awakening hasn't given me the chance.
What it brings is one pair of shackles after another.
With my ability,
I should be able to control it better.
Right?
Sleep well.
Don't think about anything.
I will take care of
everything else.
Xifan, I know you hate me.
But I can't just watch you die.
You said you ordered Wen Rui to surround Carefree Valley last night.
If you were only a maid, why would Wen Rui obey your orders?
Ling Ziyan, when did you start working for His Majesty?
I thought you were innocent and pure before and needed me to protect you.
But it's only now that I understand.
My methods can't compare with yours or even more so, His Majesty's.
What did His Majesty promise you? Money or the future?
That had you deliberately plotting ways you could stay by my side!
I didn't do it for the future.
Xifan,
you are the only one who treats me equally and with your whole heart.
His Majesty said if Lu Ping didn't die, you would die.
Between the two of you, I could only protect the one I care about the most.
Some things you are not hardhearted enough to do, or you can't do.
I will do them for you.
Whatever I've done, it's all been to help you.
Ling Ziyan,
I would never do anything to hurt my brothers.
If you can't even understand that, then it means I was blind before and misjudged you!
Miss Ling, what happened in the valley? Should we attack?
General Wen, please go back to Kaifeng. Don't worry about the Carefree Valley.
Xifan.
- But His Majesty's edict…
- The Force Eater matter,
I will report to His Majesty later.
If you step in and cause more trouble, which one of you will bear the responsibility?
You're on your own then.
You brat.
You're finally willing to stay in Carefree Valley.
It's all my fault. I shouldn't have let you bring others into Carefree Valley.
Don't worry. Starting from today,
no outsiders will be allowed to come into the valley and bother you anymore.
I will leave a safe and peaceful Carefree Valley to you. Okay, son?
You'd better leave. No matter how long you stand there, it's no use.
Master won't see you.
Mo Chuangu, no outsider is allowed in the valley. Get rid of all of them!
Master, the boy rushed into the mist forest recklessly.
He choked several times and refuses to leave.
He's... still a living person after all.
I am Yan Xifan. I'm asking to see Master Mo.
You dare come here?
Carefree Valley is a place where we live sequestered lives.
If you hadn't come, none of these tragic events would've happened.
All of these tragedies were brought by you outsiders!
Under the circumstances,
do you not want to let Mo Lin rest in peace?
I know. It's all because of me.
I'm here today to let you deal with me.
Before that, I want to show you something.
Mo Lin left a letter to Ziyan.
Yesterday's incident happened suddenly. We haven't had time to give it to you.
Father, granted, I am always lucky;
but just in case, if you're reading this letter,
then I must be dead. Don't be too upset.
Don't blame Senior Brother either.
The Mountain and Sea Gang are fierce. He and Lu Ping have their responsibilities.
I'm the most useless disciple in Wind Taker.
The only thing I can do is to try my best to help them.
I want you to sincerely praise me from the bottom of your heart,
I am indeed your son.
I want my friends to sincerely praise that
I am indeed their brother.
This time, it's my turn to protect you.
Your unfilial son, Mo Lin.
Foolish child. He really is a foolish child.
Mo Lin isn't a fool. He really is the World's No.1 Assassin
and my most responsible brother.
The chaos of the Mountain and Sea Gang endangers the world.
Master Mo, please help and develop an antidote to eliminate the Force Eaters.
In regards to the antidote, I will find a way.
Not to help you, but for my son.
As a father, I want to finish this for my son.
Do this. You go and capture some more people who've been cleansed of it.
Maybe through them, I can find a way to stop this.
My sincerest thanks to you. Master, I have another presumptuous request.
I want to see Lu Ping.
Lu Ping's long gone.
Did he say where he was going?
Before Lu Ping went, he left a message for you.
He said that the grudge between you two,
those three moves that day, have already been repaid.
Someone else needs to pay the rest.
This is bad. Lu Ping is going to seek revenge against His Majesty.
Reporting!
Master, Miss Ling is in a hurry to send a letter to Young Master Xifan.
[Letter of warning]
Oh no. I'm afraid Liu Song is going to test them on the people in Jin City.
You can't be everywhere at once, don't you still have that extraordinary father of yours?
I'm going to Jin City to help. Please help me send a message to Wuji Manor.
Ask my father to stop Lu Ping at all costs. Please don't let him do something foolish.
As Master expected,
Xifan caused Carefree Valley's accident because of the master of the Windchimes Gang.
Lu Ping has already left Carefree Valley and is headed towards Kaifeng.
The secret letters to all sects are already prepared.
As Master ordered, it clearly states that 19 years ago,
Yan Qiuci and Zhai Rong joined forces to invade Big Dipper
to assassinate Leng Xiutan.
That he detained Lu Chenfeng in Wuji Manor and killed him,
I advise all heroes to never be blinded by traitors.
Yan Qiuci will be defeated.
Older Brother!
It has been 19 years.
You were too soft-hearted back then.
You thought the best way was to stop the war.
Now I will start a blood feud,
let those who destroyed my home
repay me with their blood.
Coming next should be a good show.
Xifan, you came.
If you don't have the skills, don't push yourself.
Thank you, Young Master Yan, for your help.
What's the situation?
Everything is fine now. But we don't know if there will be more Force Eaters.
I'm guessing Liu Song is just testing it.
Strengthen the defense, protect the people and avoid fighting against them.
We don't need to fight recklessly.
Send these bodies to Carefree Valley, please. Master Mo is working on potential solutions.
Yes.
Xifan, these Force Eaters are very strange.
It was a sneak attack. But the moment we started fighting back, they ran.
I chased them here to try and capture one to ask why.
Wait.
The defense troops received this letter a few days ago.
The general believes in Master Yan so he ignored this.
It's bad. These Force Eaters who snuck into Jin City are just disturbing our line of sight.
The real purpose of Mountain and Sea Gang is to sow discord
and ruin my father's prestige, then no one will help.
Master Yan is in danger now.
We have to get back as soon as possible. Let's go.
[Wuji Manor]
Tell Yan Qiuci to come out here!
Today, he has no choice but to give us a statement.
- That's right!
- Tell him to get out here!
Tell him to come out here!
Hypocritical villain, what right does he have to lead the martial-arts circles?
Today we're here to get justice for Master Leng, aren't we?!
- Aren't we? For Master Leng.
- That's right!
- Tell Yan Qiuci to come out.
- Tell him to come out!
I am here.
Everyone, what is it that you want?
This letter says that 19 years ago, you colluded with Zhai Rong
to kill the former master of Big Dipper, Leng Xiutan. Is that true?
- Speak out.
- Speak.
How do you explain this?
Since the letter is clear, why do you need to ask again?
Master Yan, this is all too shocking.
Please give us an explanation.
Even if it's true, what can you do to me?
- You-!
- For the past ten years, I have led the martial arts circles.
I mediate all disputes among sects so that you can still grow strong in this troubling time.
This was something that that great hero in Big Dipper would have never done.
Is there anyone here who could've done it?
This....
Wuji Manor has been a strategic defensive position on the border for a long time.
Protecting people, giving them peace, with the armies garrisoned here.
Now the Mountain and Sea Gang are colluding with the country of Dan. The border is in danger.
Who dares to stand up and
say that he can rise up to the current situation?
If there is one, I will give my position to him immediately and plead guilty with death.
Anyone?
Leng Xiutan's death
brought prosperity in Jianghu for more than ten years.
I don't think I need to give anyone an explanation.
Everyone here had better think more about how to deal with the Mountain and Sea Gang.
Master!
Master, there's a letter from Young Master.
Lu Ping knows the truth of the Event of the Seven Stars.
I hope you can stop him. I will be there soon.
Wait a moment, Master Yan. You can't convince us, so now you want to escape?
You—
[Wuji Manor]
Master, do you really plan to go?
You still don't understand?
Lu Ping is Liu Song's sharpest sword right now. He's sent out his right hand to commit an assassination.
The sects were the left hand, here to seek revenge. Liu Song planned all of this.
He's trying to stretch me thin, make it difficult on both sides.
If Shuo is in chaos, how can Jianghu be preserved?
Master, Lu Ping can use five forces now, he's quite strong.
He won't be easy to deal with. Let me go with you.
Don't bother. You stay with the steward and take care of Wuji Manor for me.
Don't let those mobs make trouble again.
The Yan Family's Sword has had a reputation in Jianghu for many years.
If it doesn't get pulled out of its sheath at this time, how can it still be called the fastest sword in the world?
Yan Qiuci, I haven't come looking for you to pay your debts yet.
Yet you had the gall to come looking for me first?
I know others can't stop you, so I didn't waste any time and personally came.
Xifan has already paid for your sins.
Be good and get out of my way; go back to repent. I won't kill you.
That year Eldest Brother used to ignore the chaos in the world, only concerning himself with his corner in Big Dipper.
How could he be considered a hero?
After the Event of the Seven Stars, I brought the Wuji Manor to great heights and became the master of all martial arts circles.
I did everything on my own, defending the border.
Only because of that could the martial arts circles be as great as they are today.
Even if my eldest brother were alive today, he may not have had such achievements.
It's all worth the sacrifice that your parents made so we could have what we have now.
I have nothing to regret.
So even until today, you are still just one of Zhai Rong's dogs.
What I do now, was never because of loyalty to another.
After you go, you will only become Liu Song's sharp sword.
If I don't stop you today, the moment Zhai Rong dies, the world will be in chaos.
Then where will Jianghu, that I've been in charge of my entire life, go?
After everything you said, you still did this for your own selfish reasons and slaughtered the innocent.
Life and death are decreed by fate. You need to recognize that.
If you must go today,
then you'll have to die in my hands.
Well said.
I hope that if Uncle Yan dies under my sword today, you'll learn to recognize that life and death are decreed by fate.
These words of having no regrets, you can save them for my parents and Uncle Lyu.
Kill me if you can. Leave no chance for my revival.
(T/N: lit translation is to cut out the stem and the root)
Because if I live even just one day, I won't let Zhai Rong go,
and I also won't let anyone stand in my way.
Fine. I will do as you wish.
[Ending OST: "The Paper Boat"]
[by Zhiqian Xue — Singers: Zhiqian Xue and Kewei Yu]
♫ Waiting to be buried by the lake in the town, ♫
♫ the White Paper Boat drifting with sorrow ♫
♫ Lights on the other side of the sea ♫
♫ punched fingertips in the red water tower ♫
♫ Watch the little boat churning, laughing at the ordinariness ♫
♫ Like a kite being pulled into a low altitude, ♫
♫ I smiled to the leaving person ♫
♫ The more spotlight, the more vivid the story ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue ♫
♫ Like a moat built under the sea, ♫
♫ waiting for the words on the paper boat to disappear, ♫
♫ there must always be someone who doesn’t
remember listening to the other ♫
♫ Anyone who is correctly guessed will end in disfavor ♫
♫ You are particularly touched but others consider it ordinary ♫
♫ Like the author, roughly put down with a weak stroke, ♫
♫ the writing boat on the lake was just like
a paper crane in the air ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue ♫
♫ Can a moat be built on the seabed? ♫
♫ Wipe all the words on the paper boat! ♫
♫ Please let someone not remember and don't tell another! ♫
♫ Hide the reluctance between words ♫
♫ Unfortunately, I (you) am (are) an average author ♫
♫ No matter how you (I) describe the rest, it's unnecessary! ♫
♫ Don't describe my unfulfilled promise! ♫
♫ Don't interpret my hidden fire-smoke! ♫
♫ Don't let the paper boat in the rough wave chasing me! ♫
♫ Don't wait until it's over to know there are you and me! ♫