[Opening OST: "Young Warriors"]
[By Wang Sulong — Lyrics by Wang Sulong and Zuo Muxiu]
♫ The dark green sea is hazy ♫
♫ dissipating in a flash ♫
♫ Rivers and lakes divide the world ♫
♫ Ten thousands arrows are firing at once ♫
♫ Who has time to worry? Who loves the color of blood? ♫
♫ At that time, spirits are high ♫
♫ Who calls the world his home?
Who dares let his horse freely run? ♫
♫ Silently, tears form in the death of night ♫
♫ Heroes are cutting all ties, ♫
♫ giving up whether it's life or death, ♫
♫ never asking what the cost is ♫
♫ Good and evil must be distinguished ♫
♫ The wind blows off the snow ♫
♫ On the body, etch multiple scars, ♫
♫ wandering all over the world, ♫
♫ only wish to ask for answers from this world ♫
♫ A teenager doesn't have to be a hero ♫
♫ There is no need for flowers in the dream ♫
♫ Destiny need not be afraid ♫
♫ Because you have him all the way, ♫
♫ experienced a handful of conquests, ♫
♫ overcame a number of challenges ♫
♫ From now on, happy and free! ♫
♫ The only wish is, with the world, ♫
♫ would come along the willing of change ♫
[Legend of Awakening]
[Episode 45]
Everyone has their own fate.
If they can't deal with their own hardships,
what can others do?
Unless Leng Xiutan were still alive; otherwise,
Lu Ping can only wait for his death.
Not necessarily.
Su Tang, why are you here?
I escorted Master Chu Min to Big Dipper. I heard from Master that my brother and Qin Sang were here.
Elder Guo, I have a way to save my brother.
[Big Dipper]
Sister Qin, I have a way to save my brother.
Su Tang, when did you get to Big Dipper?
Yesterday. Master Chu Min has lost her memory.
I came especially to entrust her to Master in Big Dipper.
Lost her memory?
According to Master and Elder Guo, Master Chu Min's memory may be hard to recover in a short amount of time.
Fortunately, she still remembers that she had taught at Big Dipper.
Master asked her to continue teaching at Yaoguang Peak when she is better.
Hopefully, it will help her recover her memory.
That's good. Lu Ping can feel at ease then, too.
Sister Qin.
About the news of Master Chu Min, can you tell my brother after he's been healed?
So he doesn't have to worry as much.
Lu Ping can be cured? How?
I've already talked to Elder Guo about how to do it. If we find the Two Form Flower, my brother can be cured.
Two Form Flower?
The Two Form Flower can protect his meridians and make them bear the power of six pneumas.
It was very hard but my father managed to plant one. My brother took it when he left the valley.
Do you know where it is?
Sister Qin, are you all right?
Su Tang.
Let's talk about the Two Form Flower later.
Lu Ping has already suffered a lot.
Let him live a few more days for himself.
But you are the one who cares about him the most. Don't you want to save him?
It hasn't been easy for Lu Ping to gain a few days of peace.
If he regains the six pneumas, who can guarantee he won't get pulled into the chaos again?
I married Lu Ping last night. I don't want much.
I just want to live a peaceful life for a few days.
I hope you can help me.
God, why do you always have to play tricks on people?
There's only one Two Form Flower.
In order to save me, Lu Ping made me take it.
Now I am afraid all I can do is use my blood, a life for a life.
Why?!
Why out of the two of us can only one survive?
Why can't you let us be selfish for once?
I really don't want to leave him.
Bandit, you said you would cook. Have you been well behaved?
Lu Ping... Lu Ping!
You can choose one pneuma to practice. Then reach two.
Until you can use several pneuma.
Your fists are not straight enough. How could you use pneumatic powers?
Keep your wrists relaxed and your knees straight. Try one more time.
Why are you here?
I've learned the pneumatic powers.
- You're so great!
I want to join the army, too!
I have to serve my country.
One by one. Don't rush.
Why didn't you stay at home? What are you doing here?
Came out to relax. I can't stay at home all day.
How was Big Dipper?
Looking at these children,
I think of the days when I lived and practiced with my seniors and juniors.
I felt like I should go to see Big Dipper.
I can go with you right now. Good timing, as Su Tang just got back, too.
Su Tang. Sangsang came in the morning for a short time.
What did you say to her? Why did she ignore everyone and run off?
Has she seen the Two Form Flower? Can your brother survive?
Wei Tianqi, are you looking for a beating?
Are you looking forward to my brother's recovery or death?
I'm telling you. Even if my brother is gone today, there is no room for you.
Who says I am gone?
Brother!
I am sorry. I shouldn't have left you alone in Carefree Valley.
It's good to see you back. As long as you're alive.
Sangsang, let's not disturb their sibling reunion.
I don't want to hear the name of Sangsang anymore.
Today, you can call her sister-in-law.
You. Shameless.
Master Chu Min.
You all can learn from Master Chu of Yaoguang Peak from now on.
Yes.
New? Your foundations aren't even solid.
First run 50 laps before entering Yaoguang Peak.
Master.
Brother, our Master—
Master Chu Min.
Don't call me "Master" if you aren't one of Yaoguang Peak.
When did Big Dipper have such weak disciples?
Senior, there's no harm in saying what you want to say.
You've always been very frank anyway.
Your internal breathing is disordered.
Before, you could have lived for more than a month.
But now…
How many days does he have left?
Three days, at most.
I used to hate the pneuma confinement.
But now that I don't have it,
I can't protect my own life.
This is probably retribution, isn't it?
What if there was another chance for you?
No one has a second chance.
Just say it. What would you do?
The times when I went down the wrong path,
I would do differently.
Unfortunately, there is no turning back when it comes to time.
I will try cooking the porridge again. I'll ask Su Tang to help this time.
Su Tang, I didn't tell you before.
Now I've decided, I'm going to save your brother.
I need your help.
Sister Qin, don't joke.
I found out about all of it. You'll die.
If the Two Form Flower was in your blood, would you give it to Lu Ping?
You and my brother just got married.
If something happens to you, my brother would rather die.
I know he will be very sad. So I want you to accompany him.
You're the one that's closest to him.
For you, he'll continue to live his life well.
There are some things that
no matter how hard it is, you still have to do.
I want him to live well.
Live according to his heart's wishes.
No. Qin Sang, are you insane?
You're going to die for Lu Ping? I don't agree. Come with me.
Tianqi.
What did you call me?
Tianqi, Shuo is also your hometown.
You have your brothers and friends here.
Now the war has begun. You don't want to lose them either. Do you?
As one person, I can't do anything about it. But Lu Ping can.
But I don't want to watch you die.
Tianqi.
Don't come over here. No matter what, I won't agree to it.
Ever since you came to Big Dipper, you've changed a lot.
You know we should focus on the bigger picture.
I believe you will become a formidable and brave man in the future.
This is my last wish.
You will help me. Won't you?
Sangsang, You know I won't turn you down.
You know that whatever you say, I'll say yes to.
How is everything?
The disciple guarding him has been transferred by me. I just gave Lu Ping silver needles.
It'll be half a day before he wakes up.
Su Tang, watch the gate.
No matter who comes, don't let them disturb us.
Take care of yourself. I'm entrusting Lu Ping to you.
My master taught me medical skills. Don't worry.
It won't hurt at all. It'll feel like you're asleep.
Tianqi.
Thank you.
♫ Anyone who is correctly guessed will end in disfavor ♫
♫ You are particularly touched but others consider it ordinary ♫
♫ Like the author, roughly put down with a weak stroke, ♫
♫ the writing boat on the lake was just like
a paper crane in the air ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue ♫
♫ Can a moat be built on the seabed? ♫
♫ Wipe all the words on the paper boat! ♫
♫ Please let someone not remember and don't tell another! ♫
♫ Hide the reluctance between words ♫
♫ Unfortunately, I (you) am (are) an average author ♫
[Wind Taker]
♫ No matter how you (I) describe the rest, it's unnecessary! ♫
[Surpass Big Dipper]
[Wind Taker Academy]
Do you miss it?
Now when I think back, that was the happiest time.
Although anything could've happened at any time and I was running for my life each day,
it wasn't as empty as it is now.
That's good. This way I won't regret my decision now.
Bandit, I can't go with you this time.
But remember I will always be with you.
Where are you going?
Brother, you're awake. How do you feel?
Where is Qin Sang?
Qin Sang.
He's regained the six pneumas and his meridians have been reshaped.
This brat, he's got both his life and his martial arts back.
Brother, be careful. Be careful.
Su Tang, what happened? Where is Qin Sang?
Where is Qin Sang? Su Tang.
Tell me what happened. Su Tang.
Your injury could only be saved by the Two Form Flower.
Sister Qin took the Two Form Flower before. In order to save you,
she switched your blood with hers.
Brother. Brother.
- Lu Ping!
- Brother.
Bandit, I acted on my own this time.
Do you blame me?
I had wanted to blame you.
But I get it now.
The ladies of the Qin Family
are like a raging fire.
Strong and vigorous.
No one can persuade you to do differently.
Do you regret marrying me?
I regret...
not marrying you earlier.
Will you promise me anything I ask for?
The heavens or the earth, whatever you want.
I want to go up and have a look at the highest place in Big Dipper.
Lu Ping, the night is so quiet here.
It's like the night we got married.
It gives me the feeling that
there are only two of us in this world.
As long as you're willing,
I'll always be by your side.
Watching for as long as you wish.
I won't let anyone disturb us.
♫ Wait for a gust of wind to blow through
the youngster's sleeves ♫
♫ Time drifts by  ♫
I was a kid when my parents died in battle.
I didn't understand why my brother had to inherit the Qin Family.
I didn't understand what family and country meant.
Now it feels like I finally understand it a bit.
You've always understood things more than I did.
♫ float above the clouds, walk into my heart,
and stay there for a while ♫
Could you stay with me longer?
Teach me more.
♫ Passing through the world, we meet by chance,
dreading the parting time ♫
Do you remember what you said that day?
You said that people have life and death, and countries rise and fall.
You can't manage them all.
It was all nonsense.
I know that fate has been unfair to you, making you suffer a lot.
But you and I met under this sky.
Our entire past is here.
Just for me, please protect this place.
Is that reason enough?
♫ You are like a firework of the world and
also a passing dream traveler, ♫
It's enough. I will.
♫ forever stay in my heart ♫
Bandit,
you can't lie to me this time.
Frivolous bandit.
What? Do you want to stay here with me for the rest of your life?
Here.
I am the honor of the Qin Family.
Of course, I have to help when I see how useless you are.
Damn it! He left so fast.
His clothes left even faster. He didn't even leave me anything to remember him by.
Who are you yelling at?
You.
Compared with being a lady of the house, it's better to be a couple of chivalrous and righteous heroes in Jianghu.
What did you wish for on the river light?
I forgot while I was busy letting go of the light.
What? Stupid.
Lu Ping, no matter what you want to do, I will accompany you.
Even if it's dark at night, with stars and someone by your side,
the road will always be easier to walk.
Lu Ping, I am sorry.
♫ Once again speechless, the sunset falls silently ♫
♫ This world is too noisy ♫
Someone loves you.
Life or death, right or wrong,
I will always be by your side.
After the war subsides,
let's go somewhere beautiful
and live the life of ordinary people.
Isn't that what you've always wanted?
♫ you are standing right in front of me ♫
♫ Who is reflected in your eyes? ♫
♫ Pretending to be indifferent like a drizzle, ♫
♫ when the mirror in the bottom of the pupil has been lifted out, ♫
♫ my affection is deciphered a longing ♫
♫ Who is reflected in my eyes? ♫
♫ It’s a lifetime of foreshadowing you ♫
♫ The candle wants to extinguish, the lamp wants to dim,
don’t want to say it’s the end ♫
♫ In a fleeting moment, you said a place faraway, ♫
♫ I want to see what the future is like,
even if I’m called a wanderer ♫
Wei Tianqi, leave him alone.
Sangsang!
♫ Who is reflected in your eyes? ♫
♫ Pretending to be indifferent like a drizzle, ♫
Sangsang.
♫ when the mirror in the bottom of the pupil has been lifted out, ♫
♫ my affection is deciphered a longing ♫
Master, did I do something wrong again?
Everyone has his fate.
Reunion is fate. Separation is also fate.
You don't have to blame yourself.
♫ Who is reflected in your eyes? ♫
♫ Pretending to be indifferent like a drizzle, ♫
♫ when the mirror in the bottom of the pupil has been lifted out, ♫
♫ my affection is deciphered as a longing ♫
♫ Who is reflected in my eyes? ♫
♫ It’s a lifetime of foreshadowing you ♫
♫ The candle wants to extinguish, the lamp wants to dim,
don’t want to say it’s the end ♫
♫ No matter if the sky is clear or not ♫
Master, Big Dipper has never been so bright. What's...?
Maybe someone's untied the knot in his heart. The stars have returned to their place.
The Awakener has finally truly awakened.
[Tomb of Qin Sang]
[Qin Sang]
I know you've always wanted to be free
and unfettered in Jianghu.
This place has the most beautiful scenery during the day and the brightest stars at night.
There are seniors and juniors practicing martial arts,
making it lively every day.
You'll definitely like it here.
After I've finished what I have to do,
I will come back to keep you company. Okay?
Big Dipper is not a place where anyone can just bury bones.
You've broken the rules again.
Since you're speaking of it now, does that mean you've acquiesced?
I can use the six pneumas now.
Even if you disagree, you're no match for me.
After last night,
how does your body feel?
At the time, my entire body felt hot.
I thought I was going to die.
But after I woke up, I realized I was okay.
I know... she wouldn't let me die.
Then, what plans do you have now?
I have to do what I promised her.
No more pursuing hatred and resentment?
Didn't you want to drag my brother out of the grave and ask what happened?
If I did that, Uncle, could you let me go?
It depends on whether you understand him or not.
Now I really understand why Master kept hiding the truth from me.
He was afraid that I would be deceived by hatred... become another Liu Song.
I don't practice martial arts so that I can address the resentment or hatred in my family.
Then, who do you do it for?
[Ending OST: "The Paper Boat"]
[by Zhiqian Xue — Singers: Zhiqian Xue and Kewei Yu]
♫ Waiting to be buried by the lake in the town, ♫
♫ the White Paper Boat drifting with sorrow ♫
♫ Lights on the other side of the sea ♫
♫ punched fingertips in the red water tower ♫
♫ Watch the little boat churning, laughing at the ordinariness ♫
♫ Like a kite being pulled into a low altitude, ♫
♫ I smiled to the leaving person ♫
♫ The more spotlight, the more vivid the story ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue ♫
♫ Like a moat built under the sea, ♫
♫ waiting for the words on the paper boat to disappear, ♫
♫ there must always be someone who doesn’t
remember listening to the other ♫
♫ Anyone who is correctly guessed will end in disfavor ♫
♫ You are particularly touched but others consider it ordinary ♫
♫ Like the author, roughly put down with a weak stroke, ♫
♫ the writing boat on the lake was just like
a paper crane in the air ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue ♫
♫ Can a moat be built on the seabed? ♫
♫ Wipe all the words on the paper boat! ♫
♫ Please let someone not remember and don't tell another! ♫
♫ Hide the reluctance between words ♫
♫ Unfortunately, I (you) am (are) an average author ♫
♫ No matter how you (I) describe the rest, it's unnecessary! ♫
♫ Don't describe my unfulfilled promise! ♫
♫ Don't interpret my hidden fire-smoke! ♫
♫ Don't let the paper boat in the rough wave chasing me! ♫
♫ Don't wait until it's over to know there are you and me! ♫