[Opening OST: "Young Warriors"]
[By Wang Sulong — Lyrics by Wang Sulong and Zuo Muxiu]
♫ The dark green sea is hazy ♫
♫ dissipating in a flash ♫
♫ Rivers and lakes divide the world ♫
♫ Ten thousands arrows are firing at once ♫
♫ Who has time to worry? Who loves the color of blood? ♫
♫ At that time, spirits are high ♫
♫ Who calls the world his home?
Who dares let his horse freely run? ♫
♫ Silently, tears form in the death of night ♫
♫ Heroes are cutting all ties, ♫
♫ giving up whether it's life or death, ♫
♫ never asking what the cost is ♫
♫ Good and evil must be distinguished ♫
♫ The wind blows off the snow ♫
♫ On the body, etch multiple scars, ♫
♫ wandering all over the world, ♫
♫ only wish to ask for answers from this world ♫
♫ A teenager doesn't have to be a hero ♫
♫ There is no need for flowers in the dream ♫
♫ Destiny need not be afraid ♫
♫ Because you have him all the way, ♫
♫ experienced a handful of conquests, ♫
♫ overcame a number of challenges ♫
♫ From now on, happy and free! ♫
♫ The only wish is, with the world, ♫
♫ would come along the willing of change ♫
[Legend of Awakening]
[Episode 38]
[Seven Martyr Court]
Do you know why it is called the Mountain and Sea Gang?
It's because I want to tell those people from then
that their guilt will never go away.
Don't you want to go back to the gang to meet your parents?
What did you say?
Your parents loved you and cared about you.
It's too bad that they died at the hands of the Mountain and Sea Gang.
You saved me.
Why do that to me?
Back then, if it weren't to save you,
Your parents wouldn't have lost their power.
And if it weren't to protect me, they wouldn't have been cheated by Yan Qiuci.
Zhai wouldn't have invaded the land of Dan.
Do you think Guo Youdao and Chu Min haven't noticed?
They were lying to you in order to protect Yan Qiuci.
You and I are the same.
Men!
Take him back.
No need to lock him up.
He already has nowhere to go.
- Yes.
Lu Ping.
Can't you tell?
He wants to be alone.
You are too inconsiderate.
Lu Ping, you are a disciple of Guo Youdao and Big Dipper.
In this world, there's no prison that can hold you.
When Master was alive,
as clever as he was,
you both never went to avenge my parents.
Is it because you didn't know?
Or because you didn't want me to know?
- Lu Ping.
- Don't say anything more.
Old Guo sacrificed his life for me,
just so I could continue living a lie
and even end up working for the enemy.
He didn't want you to give up.
He wanted you to live.
One doesn't give up
because they have a reason to live.
Or at least had a reason.
Chief, the commander's seal has been sent to Liu Yange.
His mission will be finished soon.
We will discuss the war against Shuo.
Master, how about I find some medicine to remove your scars?
When we rebuild Dan again,
with your noble blood, you will be back on the throne.
Teacher,
you have helped me for 19 years.
All these years, every day I only thought about avenging my brother.
But just then, when I was talking with Lu Ping,
I realized I couldn't remember what my brother used to look like.
The only thing I can remember...
is this scar.
Perhaps it's my motivation to keep going.
It's right of you to think like that.
Although Lu Ping was captured,
but Wuji Manor isn't a mess right now.
Instead, they are contacting other people in Jianghu.
Yan Qiuci and his men can hold on for a bit longer.
It's the rabbit fighting the eagle.
He isn't fighting for his life but kicking as he's dying.
Now that Lu Ping has come back, Lin Tianyi should move faster.
I will be back in the south when we have enough Force Eaters.
I will go now to start preparing.
[Older Brother - Leng Xiutan]
Brother, you were kind and merciful,
but you and your wife lost your lives.
I had originally wanted Lu Ping to live in peace.
But Zhai destroyed my country.
A day doesn't go by where I don't remind myself that I can't be soft-hearted.
That I can't make the same mistakes you did.
Now your son has come back.
It's time to get our revenge.
[Wuji Manor]
With the seal with the Mountain and Sea Gang, Jin will be attractive in the eyes of
a general, since it's located on the border.
Send messages to all the sects.
Ask them to share their skills generously and send disciples to Jin.
Yes.
Miss Qin, are you here to take me to Kaifeng for punishment?
Have you already prepared yourself?
Lu Chenfeng died because of me.
His Majesty's plan was ruined by me.
How could His Majesty not kill me?
Do you think you deserve to die?
I have made contributions and mistakes in my life.
Since it's already done, I'm not afraid of the consequences.
I would just like to ask you for more time,
to arrange the alliance against the gang.
I entered Jianghu when I was young.
Before I leave, the last thing I want to do is leave with a clear conscience.
Since we are facing a powerful enemy.
I will set off for Kaifeng tomorrow.
I will plead to His Majesty to pardon you from death.
You have to protect the border
and make no mistakes.
I never thought you would be so generous.
I haven't forgiven you.
You killed people for your own lust and destroyed Lu Ping's life.
You can't make up for all your mistakes with your death.
But you indeed have made contributions to the country.
Your mistakes don't cover your contributions.
I have said what I wanted to say.
Please take care of yourself.
Qin Sang, I heard that you're getting ready to set off for Kaifeng.
You want to go even with the cold toxin in your body? Do you want to die?
Didn't you say that the poison cannot be removed?
Every day you continue to live is a blessing. I will find a way to save you.
Moreover, if Lu Ping returns and finds that you died because of me,
he'd kill me.
Qin Sang,
do you think the Mountain and Sea Gang had a plan when they imprisoned Lu Ping.
So they won't kill him.
Then he.... Can he still be saved?
Mo Lin,
has Su Tang not eaten anything since Lu Ping was captured?
No matter how much I urge her, she won't listen. Women are troublesome.
Cook her a good meal and bring her to me.
I have found a way to save Lu Ping.
Really?
Master, why don't you say anything? Don't you want to save your brother the most?
One moment you don't care about my brother, the next, you want to save him.
What do you mean exactly?
When I stopped you before, it wasn't the right time yet.
Now is a good time to finish all this in one move.
The Mountain and Sea Gang is in the north. It is hard for the army to fight.
Even if I take the army, I can't win easily.
Now that the gang has the commander's seal, it will cooperate with Dan. They will hold a meeting.
Do you mean that we can sneak in to save him?
I already had Wen Rui searching for information. The mission from Dan has already set out.
They must pass through the mountains here.
If we secretly hide the army here and attack them at the right time,
you two can sneak into the mission and into the Mountain and Sea Gang.
So, this whole time you have been waiting was for this opportunity?
Master, I even said you wronged her. I have a powerful intuition.
You won't go with us to save him?
Who knows? My brother could be waiting for you.
You're not the only one with a brother, I had one too.
The responsibilities he left, I have to shoulder.
Therefore, Su Tang, I entrust Lu Ping to you.
Then I'll definitely bring him to see you. He'll figure out the misunderstanding at Wuji Manor. Just wait for me.
Qin Sang.
Then I'll beg another favor from you.
After you save Lu Ping, take him as far away as possible.
After the war is over, I'll come and look for you and your brother.
Okay. You promise?
Qin Sang, if we do this, then there must be someone who can lead the Agile Dragon Army.
I can fight sometimes, but I can't lead an army.
Be at ease. We have a more suitable person.
But it depends on whether he's finally understood everything.
Since the Mountain and Sea Gang left, you have been hiding in your room.
Do you plan to not say anything or see anyone for the rest of your life?
The war will begin. I will go back to Kaifeng tomorrow.
Su Tang and Mo Lin will take the Agile Dragon Army to rescue Lu Ping.
The Mountain and Sea Gang will cooperate with Dan.
You want to use the Dan mission.
You were able to think of a solution so quickly.
The one who leads the army has to be you.
Qin Sang, it is a severe crime to use the Agile Dragon Army without informing His Majesty.
Do you want to die?
That's why I need you.
His Majesty wants young officials to connect the court and Jianghu.
Without Lu Ping,
you are the best choice.
When I get back to Kaifeng, I will buy more time for you.
At the same time, if you can save Lu Ping with the Agile Dragon Army
and serve the court ever after, then we are using the Agile Dragon Army appropriately.
Do you mean for me to serve in the court?
I know you don't want to.
You entered Jianghu to live a free and happy life.
But in this world, there is something more important than happiness.
I know you've always missed the days in Zhaifeng.
But... we have to grow up some day.
You have to find your own way.
Attendent!
Young Master.
I want to have a bath.
Yes. I will go prepare it right now.
Father.
How's the recovery of your injury going?
I am fine.
Father, Lu Ping can use five pneumas and he has The Horn.
If he wanted to kill you, I couldn't have withstood even one move.
Lu Ping thinks of the country. I can't give up on him.
I've come to bid you farewell.
I promised Qin Sang to take the Agile Dragon Army to save Lu Ping.
I will go to Kaifeng after that and work for His Majesty.
In the future, I won't be with you anymore.
Are you doing this because you think I wronged Lu Ping? I don't need you to make up for the mistakes I made.
If you hadn't done what you did back then, his parents wouldn't have died.
Wuji Manor, which united the martial arts circles and protects the country, wouldn't exist either.
It's already hard to tell right from wrong. I am not qualified to evaluate this.
But I know the reason why this tragedy happened back then.
His Majesty was right. We need a bridge between the court and Jianghu.
We are facing the enemy, Lu Ping is missing, and I'm the only suitable candidate.
You've only ever wanted to be a man in Jianghu since you were young.
It is not something glorious for people from Jianghu to become officials. It's a yoke.
You've taken on too many responsibilities upon yourself.
Everyone has things they want to do.
But growing up is about doing things that should be done.
I have already made my decision. Please help me accomplish it.
Young Master, I heard that you're going to Kaifeng with the lady to work for His Majesty.
I'm sorry, Ziyan.
I promised you to take you traveling in the central plains and to live in seclusion.
I've broken this promise.
There's no need to say that. I'm completely willing to go with you.
Only when I'm with you do I feel the happiness humans feel; the happiness that I'm meant to feel.
Wherever you go, I'm willing to go too.
From now on, don't call me Young Master, call me Xifan.
You have to stay at Wuji Manor.
After saving Lu Ping, I'll come for you.
Don't you need me to come and serve you?
It is dangerous. I can deal with it by myself.
Princess. Young Master Yan. Our men have been prepared. We can set off at any time.
Be careful on your way. I will talk to His Majesty in Kaifeng.
There's one more thing I don't understand. I think it's better if I discuss it with you.
Dan's military power is not better than Shuo.
Even if it is powerful, the Mountain and Sea Gang is still just a sect in Jianghu.
With Lu Ping, they just have one more with the power of awakening.
Can they conquer the army and change the situation with just one man?
Or have they made other preparations? And they're more confident because of Lu Ping.
If possible, please check in the Mountain and Sea Gang.
We are in the light while the enemies are in the dark. It's not good for us.
You all have to be careful.
After we leave today, we won't know when we'll see each other again.
Please take care.
Let's go.
Xifan!
Xifan.
From now on, you can only rely on yourself.
Father, protecting the border is important. There's no need for you to send us off.
Let's go.
Yan Qiuci cheated me. Yan Xifan leads the army without orders.
Qin Sang, you still want me to forgive such large crimes?
Are you trying to revolt?
Qin Sang, you are too self-indulgent.
Are you not afraid of ruining the reputation of Qin Qi and the Qin Family?
I know it's a crime to act on my own and I deserve to die.
But in the face of war, we can't afford to lose our power.
I can guarantee with my life that Yan Xifan will return with the army,
to serve under Your Majesty.
I have no choice but to punish you. Your marriage to Xifan will be canceled.
I will take away all the rewards and imprison you in your home.
If he'll be able to serve under me,
while all depend on his abilities.
Protect His Highness! Attack. Protect His Highness.
Help!
Greetings Your Highness.
What did you even do as the Mountain and Sea Gang?! You let bandits rob others?!
If without the safety guard to save me,
[Liu Yange, Prince of the Country of Dan]
who knows how much worse it would have been!
Where is your chief? Have him personally come and apologize to me!
It is not convenient for the chief to come. I invite Your Majesty to please have a rest here.
What? You actually want me to stay here and wait?!
Do you want to die?
Your Highness.
Your Highness, when you're in the Mountain and Sea Gang, you should obey the rules here.
And moreover, according to your relation, you should be addressing our chief and royal uncle.
Fine, we'll wait then.
There can't be bandits here,
unless someone has snuck in.
Go take a look.
Yes, Sir.
Someone's coming.
Clearly, there was someone just here.
Strange.
Where are they?
They may be in the front.
Go. Follow me.
Master.
Have you found anything strange?
- No.
- Continue the search.
Yes!
You two, go check up there.
- Yes.
Tell Liu Song that I don't want such tasteless wine.
You think you're at Yaoguang Peak in Big Dipper?
You are just a prisoner.
Even if Chief saved you from death, don't think so highly of yourself!
Chief is ambitious.
Your romantic relationship was only something from the past.
After a time, what needs to be buried will eventually be buried.
What are you doing?
Liu Song ordered that no one here can hurt me.
Now I've been hurt.
Could this be considered as you disobeying your chief?
You hurt yourself! Don't think you can frame me!
You insane woman! Do you think that I can't hurt you even if you're under the protection of the chief?
Thank you, Master. Mo Lin, take Master out first. I will go find my brother.
Find Lu Ping first. He doesn't have much time left.
If we keep going, do you think he can withstand it?
The chief already said that we're only keeping him for his blood. Who cares if he's alive or not?
Greetings, Royal Uncle.
I hope you are keeping well these days.
I'm on my last legs. Is His Majesty satisfied with the seal?
You've been recuperating in the North for some time,
you may not know what's going on right now.
We may have the seal now, but we're still not very powerful.
Shuo is still much more powerful.
Where does your confidence in all this come from?
You don't believe me.
Can you give me your men to try something?
Teacher.
Royal Uncle, is it your weapon against Zhai?
Please wait patiently.
Five pneumas!
The beggar is a martial artist skilled in five pneumas?!
We infused Xi Sui with the blood of a rare awakened individual.
This is our secret weapon which is more powerful than the power of awakening.
We call them Force Eaters.
Uncle! Uncle, help! Uncle!
Don't worry. I've already drugged him.
He will be asleep for awhile now.
Chief, a little Force Eater was able to frighten His Highness into this state.
After we finish the plan, no one can stop us.
Are you satisfied now?
I was wrong.
Please forgive me for my rudeness from before.
May I boldly ask to take a man like him back to Dan,
to cheer people up and put my father at ease?
What you want, I can give.
Go back and tell His Majesty that however many he wants, I can make that many.
Thank you, Royal Uncle.
Help us!
- Please, we beg you.
- Help.
Let us out!
Master Chu Min, Are these all the sects which disappeared from Jianghu?
Why are they all here?
Most of them are skilled people who can use several pneumas.
The Mountain and Sea Gang captured them to impose Xi Sui and make themselves powerful.
They are making killing machines for the Mountain and Sea Gang.
Then, don't they need to use my brother's blood?
Chu Min, I said before that you had too many opinions on things.
Go. Poison the two mice first.
As for this old woman, leave her alive for now.
Since the Chief said we can't hurt her, give her what she wants.
I want her peacefully alive, so she can watch
her own disciples die.
Wen Rui, how long have they been in there?
For an entire day. They haven't signaled us at all.
I'm not sure what's going on.
Wait one more day, if there's no news, attack immediately.
Reporting! Young Master Yan. General Wen.
We just discovered a group of people on horses secretly leaving the Mountain and Sea Gang with a big box.
We haven't figured out what it is.
It can't be Lu Ping can it?
Send a troop of our men to follow them and try to investigate if possible.
Yes, Sir. Let's go.
Lin Tianyi, let us out. Otherwise, I will…
What are you going to do?
I will ask my master to fight you.
What did you do to my brother?!
Mind your own business first.
This is our gang's poisonous smoke.
The longer it takes you to die, the more painful it'll feel.
I really want to know how long it'll take you to die.
Lin Tianyi, you…
I want her peacefully alive, so she can watch
her disciples die.
See how good these children are! They're just like us when we were young.
We prepared some crab porridge for you. Please come taste it.
Master, please accept our respects.
Thank you, Master Chu Min.
You will regret it later if you lie to your heart.
Master Chu Min, have you seen Qin Sang?
I am sleeping. Stop yelling! Get back to your training!
All right, then I'm off.
Wait. He really just left like that?
We have wasted
so much time.
♫ Wait for a gust of wind to blow through  ♫
♫  the youngster's sleeves ♫
♫ Time drifts by, ♫
♫  stopping at the dock ♫
♫ If there hadn't been an encounter, ♫
♫  there wouldn't evoke a sense of nostalgia ♫
See that star? That's Yaoguang Star of the Big Dipper.
♫ A streamer is chasing after the moonlight ♫
♫ Those eyes that move me, ♫
♫ float above the clouds, walk into my heart, ♫
♫  and stay there for a while ♫
♫ The sky, the land, the flowers, the birds, and the pavilion,  ♫
♫  they are always waiting on their own ♫
♫ Passing through the world, we meet by chance,
dreading the parting time ♫
Is this a gift for me?
Don't you have anything to tell me?
Are you leaving tomorrow?
I can use four pneumas already.
I will be able to use five after my training down the mountain.
You and Chenfeng, just wait for me on the mountain.
After I am back, I will let you finish what you want to say.
♫ You are like a firework of the world  ♫
♫  and also a passing dream traveler, ♫
♫ forever stay in my heart ♫
Go. Tell your chief that I want to see him.
Go.
Tell your chief that Yaoguang Peak's Chu Min wants to see him.
[Ending OST: "The Paper Boat"]
[by Zhiqian Xue — Singers: Zhiqian Xue and Kewei Yu]
♫ Waiting to be buried by the lake in the town, ♫
♫ the White Paper Boat drifting with sorrow ♫
♫ Lights on the other side of the sea ♫
♫ punched fingertips in the red water tower ♫
♫ Watch the little boat churning, laughing at the ordinariness ♫
♫ Like a kite being pulled into a low altitude, ♫
♫ I smiled to the leaving person ♫
♫ The more spotlight, the more vivid the story ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue ♫
♫ Like a moat built under the sea, ♫
♫ waiting for the words on the paper boat to disappear, ♫
♫ there must always be someone who doesn’t
remember listening to the other ♫
♫ Anyone who is correctly guessed will end in disfavor ♫
♫ You are particularly touched but others consider it ordinary ♫
♫ Like the author, roughly put down with a weak stroke, ♫
♫ the writing boat on the lake was just like
a paper crane in the air ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue ♫
♫ Can a moat be built on the seabed? ♫
♫ Wipe all the words on the paper boat! ♫
♫ Please let someone not remember and don't tell another! ♫
♫ Hide the reluctance between words ♫
♫ Unfortunately, I (you) am (are) an average author ♫
♫ No matter how you (I) describe the rest, it's unnecessary! ♫
♫ Don't describe my unfulfilled promise! ♫
♫ Don't interpret my hidden fire-smoke! ♫
♫ Don't let the paper boat in the rough wave chasing me! ♫
♫ Don't wait until it's over to know there are you and me! ♫