[Opening OST: "Young Warriors"]
[By Wang Sulong — Lyrics by Wang Sulong and Zuo Muxiu]
♫ The dark green sea is hazy ♫
♫ dissipating in a flash. ♫
♫ Rivers and lakes divide the world. ♫
♫ Ten thousands arrows are firing at once. ♫
♫ Who has time to worry? Who loves the color of blood? ♫
♫ At that time, spirits are high. ♫
♫ Who calls the world his home? Who dares let his horse freely run? ♫
♫ Silently, tears form in the death of night. ♫
♫ Heroes are cutting all ties, ♫
♫ giving up whether it's life or death, ♫
♫ never asking what the cost is. ♫
♫ Good and evil must be distinguished. ♫
♫ The wind blows off the snow. ♫
♫ On the body, etch multiple scars, ♫
♫ wandering all over the world, ♫
♫ only wish to ask for answers from this world. ♫
♫ A teenager doesn't have to be a hero. ♫
♫ There is no need for flowers in the dream. ♫
♫ Destiny need not be afraid. ♫
♫ Because you have him all the way, ♫
♫ experienced a handful of conquests, ♫
♫ overcame a number of challenges. ♫
♫ From now on, happy and free! ♫
♫ The only wish is, with the world, ♫
♫ would come along the willing of change. ♫
[Legend of Awakening]
[Episode 11]
These past three years, Su Tang and I have been staying at the Wind Taker Institute.
Our master might be reckless,
lazy, greedy, and a drunk,
but he is very kind to us.
I'll take you to meet him if possible.
All right!
Ping'er.
Ping'er?
Ping'er!
- Ping'er.
- Uncle Wen...
The Pneuma Confinement... is getting more powerful.
It's strangling me even more tightly.
Have you undergone Soul Splitting? Who helped you with it?
I begged my master for it.
- I did it to attend the convention in order to see you.
- This is foolish!
The Pneuma Confinement is used by the Mountain and Sea Gang as a barrier to control your pneumatic power.
You've suppressed it all these years, so it had been gradually calmed down.
But now that you've taken the liberty to apply the Soul Splitting,
the pneumatic power within you has turned into provoking the Pneuma Confinement.
If we don't break it soon, it will only get worse.
Uncle Wen,
can you break it?
I can't.
I've been stripped of my martial arts skills.
If we are to break the confinement,
I have to seek help from my academy.
But tomorrow...
is the second round of the convention.
Eldest Senior will need me to get through the second round with him.
Ping'er.
I know of your camaraderie.
But the longer you stall, the worse you will get.
I'll be sure to send my master a letter tonight.
I'll also handover the military affairs.
Tomorrow, I'll go with you.
This is the final timeline.
If we don't break the confinement,
there's no chance in doing so again.
- But...
- No buts, Ping'er.
All these years,
haven't you fought hard to survive and to live like a human?
If they truly regard you as a friend, they will understand.
Tomorrow, at noon, I'll be waiting for you at Xinghua House.
Hey!
You rascal, what are you standing there for?
Do you know how long I've been waiting for you?
You only got to meet Uncle Wen because of me.
Shouldn't you thank me?
Sure!
We'll go to the best eating house in Kaifeng.
[Laiyue Wine Store]
This is the best eating house in Kaifeng?
Not really!
But it has the best wine in Kaifeng.
But I only have... Let's see!
Ten taels.
We'll buy as much as we can with this.
Shop keeper! I want ten taels worth of wine.
Young Lord, please come in.
[Laiyue Wine Store]
This ten taels worth of wine wasn't bought by putting on the Qin family's tab through the golden badge.
Look! There's a shooting star.
When I was with the Mountain and Sea Gang,
all I ever had was endless torture and pain.
Only when I saw the stars at night from my cell,
could I feel a moment of peace.
Even when I fled,
they guided my path.
Su Tang once told me,
if you want to give someone a gift, you have to be sincere.
So I am sharing my most precious starry sky with you.
Aren't we supposed to be looking at stars?
Why are you looking at me?
I...
Thank you.
Don't mention it!
It's not just because of Wen Gecheng.
It's also for everything that has happened
after I met you.
Qin Sang,
I witnessed all sorts of wickedness in the Mountain and Sea Tower.
You are the one who showed me
that in this world,
there are still wonderful things, just like the starry sky.
Sometimes, I think to myself,
why did I escape from the Mountain and Sea Gang?
Perhaps,
it's so that I can be with you,
to gaze upon a sky at night like this.
Lu Ping, you're really crafty.
You only spent ten taels and you managed to buy the most beautiful starry sky in Kaifeng.
Tonight, there is wine; there are stars;
there is also you by my side.
I'll accept your gift of gratitude.
Qin Sang,
I still wish to break the confinement.
I want to live like an ordinary man.
This is a wish that I've had for ten years.
Is that too much to ask for?
Let's treat this as a farewell.
Young Lords, these are the four training outfits that you told us to make.
They are made in the latest style with the newest fabric.
Once you put them on, you'll surely look gorgeous at the Pneuma Combat Convention.
Take a look! How is it?
Eldest Senior, are you in your right mind?
You, usually, can't even bear to have a good meal, where did you get enough money to buy such nice clothes?
Store keeper, I'll pay the remaining of the cost with this jade pendant.
- Do you think it's all right?
- Let me take a look!
Normally, we only accept taels, not pawns.
However, since you both are so sincere,
I'll reluctantly accept it.
Give it back!
Eldest Senior, I think this jade pendant is quite old.
You've always carried it on you, can this be your heirloom?
I really don't know what you're thinking, but it's not worth pawning your heirloom for a few training outfits.
They are not some dragon armor; moreover, it will be a tough fight tomorrow.
Who knows? The outfits might get torn quickly. Let's go!
I have yet fully recovered.
I've only managed to come this far because of the help from you guys.
Tomorrow, we're going against Luo Ting, it will be a tough fight.
I just want to do something within my power to boost everyone's morale.
Don't hold me back!
Gentlemen, take care!
[ Li Ji's Tailor Shop]
[Cloth]
If the Pneuma Combat Convention awards the most obstinate person, you would win with your eyes closed.
But don't you worry! We might not be as skilled as Miss Qin.
Her opponent didn't even get to attack and we have Lu Ping.
Even if a great martial artist like me doesn't take the stage, he can defeat Luo Ting anyway. Don't worry!
As for the jade pendant, don't mention it to them.
All right! I'll let you be the unsung hero.
Let's hurry back to show them.
Let's see if these training outfits can bring out the valiance in me.
- Let's go.
Brother, are you really leaving? What can we do in the second round tomorrow?
The reason we came to the convention, in the first place, was to look for Wen Gecheng.
Now that the purpose has been served, we don't have to go through with it.
Brother, Eldest Senior hasn't fully recovered yet and Luo Ting hates the Wind Taker Institute to the core.
He won't go easy on us in this combat.
If we both leave, Mo Lin is all that Eldest Senior has.
They will definitely lose to Luo Ting.
They can surrender if they can't defeat him.
Brother, you know what Eldest Senior is like.
This concerns the honor of the Wind Take institute, I'm afraid that by that time,
he won't surrender and he might even get himself killed.
If it ends up like that,
we'll get Assassin Boy to poison him senseless and drag him off-stage.
Brother!
Lu Ping, are you in your right mind?
We've come this far but you're going to abandon us?
So what if I abandon you?
You're a useless bum without any strength, I found you a nuisance ages ago.
Lu Ping!
Lu Ping! Lu Ping.
After all that we've been through, I thought you've regarded yourself as a disciple of Wind Taker Institute.
I don't!
Wind Taker Institute has always been just camouflage for me.
What if I ask you to stay?
These are the training outfits that were custom made.
Haven't you been complaining that we didn't have a decent uniform?
I've told you! We can't lose anyone in the Wind Taker Institute.
As long as we fight alongside each other, we can surely win the convention and make our institute proud.
Zhao Xifan, why should I care if you can make the institute proud?
I finally figured it out! You're just a hypocrite through and through.
Lu Ping, what do you mean by that?
You want me to stay because you are no match for them.
You needed me as God of Bandits to help with your tasks.
Now, you need me on the team in order to win the convention.
Don't keep up false appearances if you're incompetent.
Didn't you always want to give up the badge of eldest disciple?
Sure! Give it to me now!
I'm going to tell the judges now, that the Wind Taker Institute is disbanded.
We're quitting the contest.
Fine! Lu Ping, you may leave.
Leave now!
Wind Taker Institute is no longer your concern.
Even if I'm the last one standing, I'll keep fighting until the end.
Sure! Then you better pray a few more times tonight.
You're on your own now.
Brother, you truly broke Eldest Senior's heart this time.
Just as well! He'll stop pestering me.
Brother, I know what you have in mind.
You deliberately spoke harshly, so that Eldest Senior would make you leave.
Then you won't feel so bad, am I right?
Brother, you actually care about the Wind Taker Institute, right?
Not at all! I'm not like him.
He wants to be a hero.
He wants to carry the Wind Taker Institute forward.
But all I've ever wanted is to be an ordinary person.
If I keep competing, my identity might be revealed.
By then, the Mountain and Sea Gang will come after me again.
Who will be able to protect me then?
Su Tang,
can you let me act selfishly for once?
I've thought of a way! You can leave, I'll stay.
- Su Tang.
- As a child, I lost my family.
All this while, I knew you had been protecting me from the Mountain and Sea Gang.
You are my brother.
Whatever decision you make,
as your sister, I'll always support you.
You'll go with Mr. Wen to break your confinement, I'll watch over Eldest Senior for you, isn't that a good idea?
- But...
- Don't worry!
I won't let Eldest Senior take any risk.
Just as well! My future is uncertain.
If you stay with him, at least you'll have someone to depend on.
Eldest Senior, don't be so harsh on yourself.
If you're angry, I'll go drug Lu Ping.
It will definitely keep him from leaving, what do you think?
Eldest Senior?
Is he meditating?
He just had a fight with Lu Ping for Lu Ping is leaving with Wen Gecheng.
He'll not compete in the convention tomorrow; Eldest Senior has been meditating since.
He said he is going to recover quickly and he won't talk to anyone.
Eldest Senior!
You rascal, you are making me worried.
Master, I have some medicine to dispel blood stasis.
Good! Give it to him quickly.
How are you feeling?
He is feeling better.
Xifan, the process comes first, the results come second.
It's the participation that matters and your health is the most important.
Master, I know you're just saying that to make me feel better.
But I failed to keep Lu Ping with us.
As the eldest disciple, that was a dereliction of my duty.
I can't embarrass Wind Taker Institute again.
Mo Lin, you need to leave us.
I have to speak with my disciple in private.
You're new here so you have no right to listen in. Step outside!
As your Master, I'll be honest with you.
I've sent you here to protect Lu Ping.
I don't care if you win or not.
- Master, what did you say?
- Protect Lu Ping!
Didn't he tell you?
He is not here to take part in the convention, either.
Then... What about surpassing Big Dipper?
The crazier we seem, the safer we are.
This is a strategy! Do you get it?
Lu Ping, Lu Ping, it's always about Lu Ping!
You taught us to punish evil, promote the good, get rid of bullies, and help the weak. Is all that a lie?
You have nothing to do anyway.
You might as well make some money.
Xifan.
I know that I'm also not a competent Master.
So you don't have to go all out for Wind Taker Institute, either.
- It's not worth it!
- Worth it!
Xifan!
I don't mean to disobey you.
Ever since I joined the Wind Taker Institute and was mentored by you,
it has been my ambition to protect the Wind Taker Institute.
Even if no one is truly devoted to the Wind Taker Institute now,
I will still choose to protect it.
- Master, please agree to it.
- As if I would!
I am your Master, you have to obey my decision.
I won't.
You're such a stubborn mule. This is so annoying!
Must you compete?
- I definitely must.
- Fine! I'll make you a wager.
If you win, I'll let you compete.
If you lose, you must return to Chenqiao immediately.
Why are you sneaking around?
Mo Lin! What is going on?
It's complicated.
They seemed to have had an argument; moreover, they seem to be parting ways.
Say something nice!
Xifan, tomorrow, you'll be in grave danger.
Just like this hand, you'll be alone without any help.
If you can lift this table up with the strength of your palm, I will let you compete.
Go ahead!
Master, this table is made of stone.
Not to mention that Eldest Senior doesn't have any pneumatic power now, but even if he did, he might not be able to lift it.
I have an idea.
But if I succeed,
Su Tang and Mo Lin, will you be willing to compete with me tomorrow?
My coming back here, exactly is to help you.
Since my disciple is staying, as the greatest assassin in the world, how can I get cold feet?
Later, the two of you...
Great idea! Eldest Senior, you're really something.
You're too crafty.
Master, you said we can't replace him but you didn't say we can't work together.
You said one palm but you didn't say we can't use five fingers.
Eldest Senior used two fingers, I used two, and Mo Lin used one.
That makes five fingers.
We've helped Eldest Senior form one hand today.
We'll also fight alongside him tomorrow.
All right, whatever!
You've all grown up.
- Bear this in mind! Make sure to return alive tomorrow.
- Yes.
Master, you still haven't seen the new outfit we made.
- I'll show them to you.
- Sure!
Su Tang, thank you for staying.
My staying behind, firstly, is to help you;
secondly, is to give my brother a sense of longing.
I hope he can return to the Wind Taker Institute for my sake.
Let's hope so!
The second round is tomorrow, can you help me enhance my pneumatic power a bit more?
Young Master, Master gave orders that you can't use the Marrow Washing skill in public.
I really can't help you again.
I don't care! Anyway, for tomorrow's second round, I must not be defeated.
Otherwise, how am I to propose to Sangsang?
Young Lord Wei.
Luo Ting? Why did you ask to see me?
I'm here to congratulate you for making it past the first round.
But I heard that you lost to Lu Ping and his gang in Chan State.
Yet now, your pneumatic power suddenly improved.
You made it past the first round with ease.
I would really like to ask you for some tips, what's your secret?
Why should I tell you?
This is what you don't understand: The aristocrats in the capital have their own social circles;
it's also the same for Qin Sang.
Although you're young and talented,
without a few local friends, I'm afraid you'll still be shunned.
If you're willing to share your tips with me, I'll be your sworn brother.
By then, you'll have lots of chances to approach Qin Sang.
Really?
Is there such a skill? You can borrow power from others?
Senior, I think the champion of this Pneuma Combat Convention is definitely ours.
- Qiao Ying.
- Yes.
Go to one of the examiners to rat out Wei Tianqi.
Just say that he has brought his personal guards with him to the exam
and he even cheated, in order to get him to scram sooner.
No one else must know about the Marrow Washing technique.
This person mustn't remain in the convention.
I understand, Senior.
A countryside parvenu dares to dream of being friends with us?
What a fool!
Why are you short of one member?
One of us is injured and decided to quit, so the three of us can keep going.
Miss, Shining Sky Academy's male team is in the East Group.
That saves us the trouble of going against our peers.
But this year, the West Group is also very competitive, we'll have to be more careful later.
That's odd! Why isn't Lu Ping here?
Today is the second round of Pneuma Combat Convention.
This round, it tests you on strategy and teamwork.
The venue is the woods below you.
The woods are divided into half by a red rope for the East and the West groups.
Not only are you up against complex terrains,
but also the attacks from other teams.
The last team standing in each group is the winning team.
You'll go straight into the finals.
Although lives are taken on battlefields, His Majesty is too kind.
Every team leader will receive an emergency smoke signal.
When your lives are in danger, you can use it to seek aid.
Once it is lit, it's deemed that the team has surrendered.
There are four hours in this round.
Now, every team will enter the venue according to the order of the lots were drawn.
You have time until half a joss stick burns out to select a spot that is the best for you.
The competition will commence at the sound of the drum.
We're in the same group as that bum. How unlucky!
You're still short one person right before the competition starts.
After hearing that you guys are up against the Shining Sky Academy,
was he too scared to get up from his bed?
Tackling some weasels like you?
I, the greatest assassin in the world, alone is enough.
So, you are the Eldest Senior?
You might as well gloat now when you can.
I'm afraid you won't get another chance later.
Eldest Senior, they seem so arrogant, they must have some dirty tricks up their sleeves.
It will be a tough fight today.
I already guessed that Luo Ting will resort to some dirty tricks.
Later, just follow me.
How about here?
Mo Lin, before the drum is sounded,
set a trap here as our defense.
Eldest Senior, instead of acting like cowards, why don't we just rush out and fight?
This is unlike you.
Little Disciple, you don't get it, do you? This is called a strategy!
Su Tang, we're outnumbered and my Pneuma of Sound is damaged.
It's hard to distinguish directions, that's why we can't have a face off.
But, it's very foggy in here today! This will play to our advantage.
We just need to hold down our fort here and wait for them to fight each other first,
then we'll find an opportunity.
- Very well, Eldest Senior.
- Sure, Eldest Senior!
Who knew although you're injured, your brains are still sharp, appropriate for leading an army.
As long as Wind Taker Institute can win, I don't care if they call me a coward.
Disciple, come and help me!
We'll show them what I can do. Come along!
Hold on!
Su Tang, you still have another task.
Time's up! Sound the drum!
Senior, it's foggy in the woods today.
It's harder to search for opponents.
Don't worry! I've already talked to the other teams.
No one will interfere with the fight between Shining Sky's team and Wind Taker's team.
Therefore, if anyone is moving around, it has to be the Wind Taker team.
Senior, you're so smart! Let's see where those weasels from the Wind Taker Institute can run off to.
We just have to keep waiting in here.
Someone is coming!
Let's go!
Over here!
What is this?
Gentlemen, how are you?
Zhao Xifan, how dare you play such tricks?
When we're up against villains, who cares about being just and righteous?
Here is a word of advice! Don't waste your strength.
Here in the worm grass, the more you struggle, the deeper you sink.
Unless you've mastered two pneumatic powers, it'll be difficult to get out of it.
Why don't you light up your smoke signal to surrender?
I'll let you out if you do, how about that?
Surrender? The game has just started.
Has he already mastered two pneumatic powers? How is that possible in such a short time?
I've concealed my pneumatic power just to see what you weasels have up your sleeves.
Enough nonsense, let's fight! Stop whining like a sissy.
Sure! Today, I'll show you countryside people
that the foundation of a century-old prestigious family can't be shaken by a few minions.
Beat them to death!
You had better light your smoke signal.
If not, no one can survive under the Sun Streamer Swordplay.
Since we're here in the convention, we have no fear of death.
Miss Qin, are you going to bully us with your standing?
I'm overpowering you with my swordplay.
You...
Don't get me wrong! As for the competition, I have to win.
Martial arts practitioners should act more righteously
instead of pitting your lives against mine here.
Don't worry! Even if you lose the competition,
I'll still refer you to my brother.
Thank you, miss.
- Let's go.
Ziyan, we're almost done here.
Let's check out the East Group.
But according to the rules, we can't leave our own venue.
Miss Qin has been fighting alongside us.
She has never left the West Group.
See? That's how you should abuse authority.
Miss, it's the Wind Taker Institute.
Look! How did Luo Ting improve so much overnight?
He must have used some dirty tricks.
What a bully!
That's odd! Why isn't Lu Ping here yet?
Xifan and the others obviously aren't a match for Luo Ting.
Could Young Master Lu be injured elsewhere?
Qin Sang, I still wish to break the confinement.
I want to live like an ordinary man.
This is a wish that I've had for ten years.
Is it too much to ask for?
This is bad! I'm afraid he is never coming back.
That rascal! He has gone back on his word.
He said he would compete against me.
Ziyan, stay here!
I'll be away for a while.
Miss, what about the competition?
We have plenty of time and we don't have any more opponents anyway.
I'll be right back! You keep an eye on the Wind Taker Institute's people.
Xifan might not last much longer.
If anything goes wrong, light a cloud of smoke to alert me.
I wonder which rascal dared to rat me out?
Doesn't he know who my father is?
Pneuma Combat Convention?
How dare they disqualify a talent like me? They are mere flies on the wall.
Young Master, Master said that if you lose,
you should return to Chan State as soon as possible.
Wei Ying, just because Wei Ming isn't here, it doesn't mean you get to play boss to preach me.
How can there be so many accidents?
Listen! When the examiner get to see how gifted I am,
I'll definitely rise from desperation.
Isn't Sangsang competing in the second round?
What is she doing here?
Stop right there!
Miss Qin, instead of competing in the venue this morning,
why are you here to see me?
Lu Ping, do you know what happens to deserters in my brother's army?
[Xinghua House]
According to the martial law of Shuo State, deserters will be executed.
It's because those who flee from danger,
are deemed unrighteous for deserting their comrades.
But Lu Ping, I know you're not that kind of person.
- But today, why did you—
- Qin San.
Have you forgotten?
I only attended Pneuma Combat Convention in order to find Uncle Wen.
I don't care at all about winning or losing.
He is now waiting for me at Xinghua House.
He is going to get my confinement unleashed.
I've been waiting for this day for ten years.
Others might not understand it, do you not understand it, either?
Coward!
What did you say?
I said you're a coward.
We made a deal to compete fair and square for once.
Yet now, you're running away at the last moment.
You clearly are worried about the safety of Xifan and others
but you insist on saying you're not.
I despise you.
I actually...
[Ending OST: "The Paper Boat"]
[by Zhiqian Xue — Singers: Zhiqian Xue and Kewei Yu]
♫ Waiting to be buried by the lake in the town, ♫
♫ the White Paper Boat drifting with sorrow. ♫
♫ Lights on the other side of the sea ♫
♫ punched fingertips in the red water tower. ♫
♫ Watch the little boat churning, laughing at the ordinariness. ♫
♫ Like a kite being pulled into a low altitude, ♫
♫ I smiled to the leaving person. ♫
♫ The more spotlight, the more vivid the story. ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue. ♫
♫ Like a moat built under the sea, ♫
♫ waiting for the words on the paper boat to disappear, ♫
♫ there must always be someone who doesn’t remember listening to the other. ♫
♫ Anyone who is correctly guessed will end in disfavor. ♫
♫ You are particularly touched but others consider it ordinary. ♫
♫ Like the author, roughly put down with a weak stroke, ♫
♫ the writing boat on the lake was just like a paper crane in the air. ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue. ♫
♫ Can a moat be built on the seabed? ♫
♫ Wipe all the words on the paper boat! ♫
♫ Please let someone not remember and don't tell another! ♫
♫ Hide the reluctance between words ♫
♫ Unfortunately, I (you) are an average author ♫
♫ No matter how you (I) describe the rest, it's unnecessary! ♫
♫ Don't describe my unfulfilled promise! ♫
♫ Don't interpret my hidden fire-smoke! ♫
♫ Don't let the paper boat in the rough wave chasing me! ♫
♫ Don't wait until it's over to know there are you and me! ♫