[Opening OST: "Young Warriors"]
[By Wang Sulong — Lyrics by Wang Sulong and Zuo Muxiu]
♫ The dark green sea is hazy ♫
♫ dissipating in a flash. ♫
♫ Rivers and lakes divide the world. ♫
♫ Ten thousands arrows are firing at once. ♫
♫ Who has time to worry? Who loves the color of blood? ♫
♫ At that time, spirits are high. ♫
♫ Everywhere is home, who can dare let his horse freely run? ♫
♫ Silently, tears form in the death of night. ♫
♫ Heroes are cutting all ties, ♫
♫ giving up whether it's life or death, ♫
♫ never asking what the cost is. ♫
♫ Good and evil must be distinguished. ♫
♫ The wind blows off the snow. ♫
♫ On the body, etch multiple scars, ♫
♫ wandering all over the world, ♫
♫ only wish to ask for answers from this world. ♫
♫ A teenager doesn't have to be a hero. ♫
♫ There is no need for flowers in the dream. ♫
♫ Destiny need not be afraid. ♫
♫ Because you have him all the way, ♫
♫ experienced a handful of conquests, ♫
♫ overcame a number of challenges. ♫
♫ From now on, happy and free! ♫
♫ The only wish is, with the world, ♫
♫ would come along the willing of change. ♫
[Legend of Awakening]
[Episode 14]
The storyteller told a very ridiculous story.
A hunter's home got caught on fire.
A fox who was to be killed and skinned
seized the opportunity to escape.
It was saved by a farmer.
Just as when the fox was recovered
and was about to bid farewell to the farmer,
it discovered that the farmer was sharpening his knife.
It turned out that he was the same as the hunter.
I just couldn't understand.
The farmer disguised himself for so long, just for the fur of the fox.
Master, what are you in disguise for then?
You said you cared for Wind Taker Institute.
But you didn't stop me
from giving up the convention.
You even followed me to Xinghua House
and tasted the Apricot Blossom Wine.
Why did you do these?
Let's end it here!
You are drunk, I'll escort you to your room.
That day at Xinghua House, Uncle Wen hurt a man from the Mountain and Sea Gang.
Why do you have the same scar on your body?
Just give me an explanation,
I'll believe you.
It's been three years.
I can finally see
the result.
Impossible! Master can't be from the Mountain and Sea Gang!
Zhao Xifan, the scar doesn't tell lie.
Sangsang, you've come to see me.
I know you care about me.
Wei Tianqi, how did you hurt yourself?
- Sangsang…
- Say!
Xinghua House! I got hurt there!
[Lu Ping]
- That day, I was in the restaurant.
- Minister Wen.
I met Minister Wen under the name of Lu Ping.
He looked strange.
At that time, all the customers stood up and came at once.
They said I was to blame.
I was to be killed.
Look what you do to my plan!
I didn't guess that the whole thing was ordered by Wen Gecheng.
Don't leave anyone alive!
Mountain and Sea Gang Seal!
Young Master! It is important.
Give it to your father!
I have no idea what it is.
Wei Ying gave it to me desperately and told me to keep it well.
You...
I thought I would die that day.
Suddenly a man in black came.
I was saved.
Later on, I can't remember what happened next.
It's Wen Gecheng's seal.
Didn't he take Lu Ping to break the the Lock?
Why did he plan to kill you?
What Wei Tianqi got into was the trap that had been prepared for Lu Ping.
The person behind all of this
is the real superior of the Mountain and Sea Gang.
It's Wen Gecheng!
Why did he incite Lu Ping to fight against Guo Youdao?
I'm afraid that the person who saved Wei Tianqi is our Master.
Wen Gecheng thought him as a hindrance so he did that.
Qin Sang, go back to the inn and stop Lu Ping.
Congratulations, Wind Division Leader!
Miss Qin, please excuse me.
Sure enough! The Wei Family have colluded with the Mountain and Sea Gang.
Wei Ming, since we have been discovered, no one can live.
Indeed,
you are the Leader of the Wind Division!
Awakener,
it's time to go back.
Eldest Senior!
Master Chu Min.
You all have been secretive,
also let her trick me into going back to the Tripitaka Sutra Pavilion, and even wanted to lock me in.
Say! What are you doing?
Master Chu Min, we have to return to the inn to help Master.
Congratulations, Wind Division Leader Wen!
It's been three years since you ruined your martial arts.
It was all for making such a success today.
If I wouldn't have done that, how could Qin Qi believe me?
I could only gain his trust if I can't protect myself.
Wind Division Leader Wen were once so glorious
but now, just a Bone-piercing Needle can hurt you like this.
Is it worth such sacrifice?
I will not hesitate to sacrifice my life for the Master.
I already asked my people to dispose Guo Youdao's body.
Please send more people for I have to take Lu Ping back myself.
Wen Gecheng.
Wen Gecheng!
Wind Division takes charge of intelligent information.
Fire Division is for catching people.
Do you think that kid is down on luck every time?
This time, it won't be your turn.
If Situ Chong of the Fire Division didn't lose the Mountain and Sea token,
how can there be those mistakes these days?
Master has waited for three years, are you going to extend his waiting?
Let's see whether you can use what Master gave or not.
Su Tang has been crying.
I've comforted her but don't expect me to do that for you.
I can't protect the people around me every time.
I'll ask my brother for help.
One is the subordinate who followed him for three years.
The other is a stranger defeating you in the Pneuma Combat Convention.
Whom do you think he'll help without evidence?
Since you have guessed as such, why don't you go searching?
Weak, irresolute, and always complaining,
I, Chumin, don't have such a student like you.
Eldest Senior, you said that
you wouldn't leave anyone from Wind Takers behind.
Yes, I said that.
I will definitely keep my word.
Miss Qin, please help!
Call me Qin Sang.
I will find evidence in the Zhiwei Study.
Wait for me! Agile Dragon Army will surely come.
Did Mo Lin wake up?
You are asking me to smell all around Kaifeng for Lu ping?
- Eldest Senior, you must be crazy!
- He once escaped from the Mountain and Sea Gang.
He must have been desperate to think of a way.
Mo Lin!
Su Tang, your brother isn't like you, he is crafty.
He is now very healthy and waiting for us to get to him.
It's cold in the north, take care of yourself!
Are you caring about me?
Or, are you addicted to the acting of Minister Wen?
If you had left with me that day in the Xinghua House,
you would have been better.
I have been trapped by you
since the Pneumatic Combat Convention,
right?
I am going to die.
Still don't want to let me know?
In as big of a city as Kaifeng,
a sloppy action only alarms the enemy as well as General Qin Qi.
The only thing I could do is to let you come to me.
So, the outbreak of my the Pneuma Confinement that day...
It was because of the drugs lit in the Zhiwei Study.
Your pneumatic powers were intensified and the Pneuma Confinement would be tightened.
Lu Ping, remember what I said
no one can leave the Mountain and Sea Gang.
Let's go!
Master. Lu Ping?
Guo Youdao.
- It's good that you are alive.
- See it?
I've told you that Minmin pretended to be cold but in her heart,
- she actually missed me—
- Shut up!
Wen Gecheng, you don't know me,
let alone my Master.
I found out for all these years that the only way to live
is to take the initiative.
As for my Master,
you still have a lot to learn from his acting.
He is the little fox in the story.
The old one returned it to life, the young one must send him a present
to make Wen Gecheng understand his death.
Master, the moon is so beautiful.
Drink with me!
No way! I got drunk last night. No more drink!
Okay! You refused the invitation and chose the threat.
What with your attitude? I will not drink.
What will you do?
Master, without treating your injury, your arm will be ruined.
It doesn't matter with such a little injury.
You already knew that I was hurt by that Wei Zhong's beating.
Master, don't tell a lie that could be easily destroyed
by simply looking at your scar.
Uncle Wen hinted several times that we has had a spy from the Mountain and Sea Gang.
The person who followed me to Xinghua House, except Xifan, Su Tang and Mo Lin,
was only you.
All the evidence shows that you lied to me.
Since you don't believe me,
why do you still come and find me for a confrontation?
You said that you are not willing to let me die before I pay off my debt.
So I've placed a bet
on your bit of kindness.
What are you doing? Can't you be gentler?
- It hurts...
- So can you tell me the truth now?
The reason I came to Xinghua House was all to protect you.
Who knew that Wen Gecheng had set a trap there for you?
Initially, I even thought that he wouldn't easily reveal himself
but I didn't expect that he killed all three guards from the Wei Family.
Wei Tianqi was also almost died by his hands.
Then, he said with certainty that the Mountain and Sea Gang was to blame.
I have suspected him since then.
Tonight, I planned to check on the situation in Wen's mansion.
Don't bother!
He, first, hurt himself and then he blamed you for all these things.
He wanted me to kill you in his place.
No one can do such a thing except the Mountain and Sea Gang.
I'll send you off to hide for a while.
Slow down!
Master, I discovered someone is monitoring us outside.
If I didn't fight with you, they would definitely suspect us.
Since you love acting so much, why not accompany me for another show?
People from the Mountain and Sea Gang are prudent.
They would always suspect others.
However, no one would suspect someone whom they thought was already dead.
People who were to handle Master's body were all handled by Master.
Wen Gecheng, it's your turn to come with me.
Lu Ping, you even learned to plot now.
However, the Mountain and Sea Gang was not like the gang in the past.
Why me?
I am just a poor boy from the countryside.
You guys from the Mountain and Sea Gang are going to rule the world.
What does that have to do with me?
Why are you fixated on me?
You underestimated yourself.
- What do you mean?
- What do I mean?
I'll tell you after returning to the Mountain and Sea Gang.
There is a bamboo forest at the end of the river.
Wen Gecheng must go ashore there and wait for help.
We can save Lu Ping there.
But he seems to be leveled up by using Marrow Washing technique.
- Now this—
- If we are to save Lu Ping, we need a sword.
A sword which sees through the disguise and defeats all.
Master, I forget how to use such a sword.
Xifan, to atone is not to suffer.
It is for you to be able to
recapture the things you lost in the past.
Do you still remember why you first used a sword?
Master, I understand.
No one from Wind Takers will be left behind.
The Mountain and Sea Gang might have an alternative plan.
Lu Ping has to face all these.
I can't hide him anymore.
It is his fate.
To fight against it or to obey it.
He has no other way.
- Master Chu Min!
Can you see him?
Of course!
Old Guo! Old Guo, you are alive!
You are alive! He is not dead.
Let go of me!
Go after Lu Ping to save him.
Master Chu Min, please take care of Master, we are going to save my brother.
- Go.
Minmin,
we also have a place to go.
Mountain and Sea Gang,
we can't let them succeed so easily.
Let's go!
[Zhiwei Study]
You just gave me such things to cheat me.
Are there any secret rooms?
I really have no idea.
No idea?
Impossible!
Evidence of Wen Gecheng's identity must be here.
I must find it!
- Sang'er, what are you doing?
- Brother.
Wen's family members said you barged in after Sir Wen left.
Time is tight! I'll make it simple.
We found that Wen Gecheng was from the Mountain and Sea Gang.
This is their Mountain and Sea Gang Token.
Sang'er, do you know what you are talking about?
Brother, trust me!
Wen Gecheng planned to capture Lu Ping at the Pneumatic Combat Convention.
They already have captured Lu Ping.
There must be secret about the Mountain and Sea Gang Token.
I still need time to figure it out.
But Lu Ping doesn't have time.
Can you send Agile Dragon Army to save him?
Wen Rui,
Miss doesn't feel well, send her back home!
What's wrong with Miss?
Brother, do you not believe me
or do you not dare to believe me?
Send Miss back home!
Sang'er, you are crazy!
Who is there?
This is it!
[Official Directory]
[Names of Officials]
These are the names of officials Wen Gecheng have recommended these years.
They are likely to be from the Mountain and Sea Gang.
Wen Rui, send her back home.
She cannot go out without my order.
Yes.
Brother!
I'll capture Wen Gecheng.
Tonight, no one from the Mountain and Sea Gang can escape.
We have done what we can.
The remaining should be left to fate.
Don't drag me any longer!
I'm dying.
Just tell me...
if you have any secret.
Stop playing me!
Our people will come to us after going through the forest.
Microscopy is, indeed, powerful.
Can you see your own end?
I told you.
Stop playing me!
Lu Ping.
Break Mark!
A kind of Pneuma of Pivot that is rarely seen in a century!
You can use it just by the eyes of your enemy.
Sadly, you have met Microscopy.
You can't play me for the second time with the same trick!
Lu Ping, do you really think you know yourself?
Do you really think an Awakener like you can be born in the countryside?
Don't you want to see your parents back in the Mountain and Sea Gang?
What did you say?
Your parents loved you.
They miss you.
But they both died
in the Mountain and Sea Gang.
Xifan, to atone is not to suffer.
It is for you to be able to
recapture the things you lost in the past.
Sword of Yan Family.
Brother!
Let me see! Where is your wound?
It looks like I, the world's number 1 assassin, seem to become better.
What about you? Are you okay? We are late.
A mysterious man saved us.
Brother.
I am so lucky! He was killed just by one arrow.
Yes! Fortunately, you've arrived in time, so I'm okay.
But I want to ask him how to break the Pneuma Confinement for Lu Ping.
- Master, we have searched around but we can't find Master Wen.
- Search again!
Bring him if he's alive and his body if he's dead!
My little disciple, let's play a game.
Guess the number of peanuts in my hands is odd or even?
If you are wrong, you have to formally acknowledge me as your master, what do you think?
If you lose, stop following me all day.
Sure.
Odd!
Thanks Master Chu Min! Thanks.
- Master Chu Min.
- Say no and mean yes.
You'll regret later.
Then, let's find a nice day for our acknowledgement.
Good! Pupil, eat more. Eat more!
Come, come, come! Here!
Pneuma of Vision and Pneuma of Strength mutually promote Wild Sword in Northwest.
I heard a young master from Wuji Manor was lost.
Yan Xifan.
I've been rude for what I saw today. Pardon me!
It's just a family name.
It's not bad to be called Zhao Xifan for four years.
Toast!
I hid my name for my life.
What about you?
I couldn't save my friend before.
I felt sorry for the name, the Sword of Yan Family.
Now it's different.
I am happy to help you.
How can you, a Young Master, be so melancholy?
You don't want to go home when you have one.
Look at me! I don't even know where my home is.
I come to tell you,
what Wen Gecheng said was just to irritate you.
You don't have to bear it in mind.
I have been searching for three years,
and I've found the fake one.
I thought initially that I
was from an ordinary family.
But Wen Gecheng told me
my parents were killed by the Mountain and Sea Gang.
I thought I would be free once
I entered Pneuma Combat Convention.
In the end,
I found only mysteries
and a blood feud.
All in all,
I still found nothing.
At least you have Wind Takers and us as your brothers-in-arms.
Lu Ping, if your parents were alive,
they would surely be proud of you.
I didn't know that
you usually don't talk much but, now, you are good at comforting.
Stop the nonsense! Let's just drink.
Lu Ping,
do you remember what I said?
It was taught by my father.
We learn martial arts to stand out from others
and to protect the country and our people.
After winning at the convention, you don't have to hide.
You can use your pneumatic powers in the right way.
Eldest Senior,
what is the right way?
Qin Qi wiped out the Mountain and Sea Gang by using Agile Dragon Army the right way.
But the Agile Dragon Army aimed to kill Ling Ziyan,
is that because she's on the evil path?
Eldest Senior, you told me to choose the right way, but what is it?
Ling Ziyan defected Sun Streamer Swordplay and was forced to this point.
Wen Gecheng said that I was important.
If one day
I break the the lock,
yet the Power of Awakening is used by them,
will I have a same end as her?
Not necessarily! The tradition of the Wind Takers is that no one is left behind.
As long as I am alive, it will never happen.
Trust me!
Don't worry, Eldest Senior!
As long as there are Wind Taker Institute and our brothers,
I will not give in,
no matter what the Mountain and Sea Gang wants.
I will never be afraid.
Although you forget your parents,
they must have heard the words you just said.
[Ending OST: "The Paper Boat"]
[by Zhiqian Xue — Singers: Zhiqian Xue and Kewei Yu]
♫ Waiting to be buried by the lake in the town, ♫
♫ the White Paper Boat drifting with sorrow. ♫
♫ Lights on the other side of the sea ♫
♫ punched fingertips in the red water tower. ♫
♫ Watch the little boat churning, laughing at the ordinariness. ♫
♫ Like a kite being pulled into a low altitude, ♫
♫ I smiled to the leaving person. ♫
♫ The more spotlight, the more vivid the story. ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue. ♫
♫ Like a moat built under the sea, ♫
♫ waiting for the words on the paper boat to disappear, ♫
♫ there must always be someone who doesn’t remember listening to the other. ♫
♫ Anyone who is correctly guessed will end in disfavor. ♫
♫ You are particularly touched but others consider it ordinary. ♫
♫ Like the author, roughly put down with a weak stroke, ♫
♫ the writing boat on the lake was just like a paper crane in the air. ♫
♫ Laughing like the moon, ♫
♫ regretting the lighthouse broke in the waves, ♫
♫ I call the Milky Way that isolates us all, blue. ♫
♫ Can a moat be built on the seabed? ♫
♫ Wipe all the words on the paper boat! ♫
♫ Please let someone not remember and don't tell another! ♫
♫ Hide the reluctance between words ♫
♫ Unfortunately, I (you) are an average author ♫
♫ No matter how you (I) describe the rest, it's unnecessary! ♫
♫ Don't describe my unfulfilled promise! ♫
♫ Don't interpret my hidden fire-smoke! ♫
♫ Don't let the paper boat in the rough wave chasing me! ♫
♫ Don't wait until it's over to know there are you and me! ♫