(Lee Eun Saem as Kim Hye In)
(Yeri as Baek Je Na, Lee Jong Hyuk as Seo Do Eon)
(Yoo Jung Hoo as Lee So Mang, Han Da Sol as Oh Si Eun)
(Jang Sung Yoon as Kim Hae In)
(Park Si Woo as Min Yul Hee, Jang Duk Soo as Park Woo Jin)
(Bitch x Rich)
(Production sponsors)
(Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, KOCCA)
(All characters, locations, organizations, events...)
(in this drama are fictional.)
(From school exams to CSAT, Double Study)
Who do you find...
as the most influential teen in Korea?
(Hot Topic)
(I'm the legendary one for even bringing this up.)
Jang Won Young of IVE?
Celebrities aside.
Then, it's her.
The only daughter of Hanmyung Group's CEO.
Oh, Baek Je Na?
I hear she's gorgeous as well.
That's what I call a gifted life.
I see. Her name is Baek Je Na?
What could someone like her...
lack in her life?
(Bitch x Rich)
Would you like to dine here for dinner?
Whatever.
It's so pretty.
Je Na.
Gosh. Talk about rotten luck.
I don't spend all that money here...
just to share the space with a riff-raff.
We apologize.
And now I've lost my appetite.
Bring the car around to take me home.
I'll also be walking out in these shoes.
Je Na, just a second.
What the... Who said you could acknowledge me?
Do you have a death wish?
I understand your hatred for me,
but the last thing I want is to be on the outs with you.
Am I supposed to be best friends with the broad who seduced my dad?
Who let the crazy cat out?
I feel bad about how this affected you,
but I don't feel any guilt toward your mother.
Let's be honest. I'm not the reason...
your parents drifted apart.
I have no interest in your dad's company or his money.
Him being the CEO of Hanmyung Group doesn't mean much to me.
I love him for the man he is, and that's all.
I don't see how that makes me the villain.
You're buying a dress that costs more than your teacher's salary,
so cut this crap about your love being innocent.
Do you know why I see people like you as vermin?
I would've at least pitied you if you honestly said...
you were after his money.
You still have pride despite having nothing to your name.
I knew it. She told on me already.
(Dad)
Yes?
Ms. Je Na, he wants you to pick up.
Just say I'm not with you.
But he'll know that you're heading home.
Then, I'll just go somewhere else.
Don't you dare look for me.
Where did they go?
Hey.
- What's your issue? - What's your problem?
You're from my school?
And you dare act like this to me?
Don't people usually feign ignorance in this situation?
What are you talking about?
Are you a transfer student?
Do you know who I am?
I'm letting you off today since I had a terrible day.
Don't let me see you in school.
What an uncultured freak.
That's rich coming from a thief!
Who said you could leave?
What are you doing? Have you lost it?
Jail is a luxury for people like you.
I'll teach you a lesson myself,
so bark on if you dare.
- Why you... - Let go of me, darn it!
You...
Darn.
- What do you think you're doing? - Stay still!
- Hey! - You thief!
Why isn't it coming off?
You thief. Just stay put.
- I paid a fortune for these. - Have you lost it?
(Kim Hye In)
Kim Hye In?
What...
Why were you in there?
I was looking for a book to read.
You're here early.
Judging by how worried the pastor was...
tells me that So Mang is acting up again.
Do you mean Lee So Mang in 12th grade?
Trouble caused on school grounds can be swept under the rug.
But he always...
gets into trouble somewhere other than on campus...
making it hard for us to do damage control.
Unbelievable.
You two aren't close, right?
Not really.
You should be wise about who you hang out with.
Not everyone can be considered as a friend.
Of course. Don't worry.
Lee So Mang?
I thought your dad would've grounded you.
I cashed that in for a punch to the face.
Who knew the pastor packed a mean punch?
My dad will go to the fiery pit. I'm sure of it.
All I'm asking is that you wrap it up for me like before.
How is that not possible?
I even have the receipt which says I bought it today.
With designer items, even shopping bags have price tags.
There are people online who sell the boxes and dust bags.
But I don't want to sell it for money.
I lost the bag and box because someone stole them.
I'm afraid we haven't come across this type of situation before.
This was the first designer item I bought,
but because of that crazy cow...
Ms. Je Na, what on earth...
Don't say another word.
How dare she?
That crazy cow will get what's coming.
They say...
that decent shoes lead people to good places.
Do you know what shocked me the most...
when I first stepped foot...
on that school's campus?
What did you see?
A new world.
The school harboured a new world...
I was once oblivious of.
(Cheongdam International High School)
And I was enlightened.
I believed...
that my life was somewhat adequate...
only because...
I hadn't seen...
or experienced such things...
during the 18 years of my life.
I didn't know what I had to be jealous of.
Wait. I think I know this shop.
They sell an afternoon tea set, right?
That's right. Let's go eat.
I was a loser whose world was tiny compared to theirs.
Ta-Da. Pretty, isn't it?
No way.
The clerk said it'd take a while to find the exact same stone.
I had it upgraded to replace the one you lost.
Oh, my.
- Let me put it on you. - Sure.
There.
It's pretty. I love it.
- Are you sure it's pretty? - Yes.
You can't see it properly.
This is torture.
You're being a gentleman, though.
Do you want some help?
Babe, why don't we just speed up the wedding?
It's not like we'll get to marry someone else.
Seriously, Je Na? Don't you know how to knock?
Hey, what happened to your face?
Did you injure yourself?
Babe, I'm hurting too. Can you relieve my pain?
What?
- Baek Je Na, you... - Darn it!
I'm fuming.
What is this about?
There's someone I must find.
You wait and see.
I'll make sure attending school is a living nightmare for you.
Welcome to Cheongdam International High.
I'll work hard until I graduate.
- As in how? - In every way.
I like how passionate you are.
This is the key to your locker.
Ask the student volunteer...
if you have any more questions.
- Right. I'll see you later, then. - Sure.
Bucket?
You...
Meeting like this again should be considered as destiny.
As if.
Come on, Bucket. Who knew we'd meet again like this?
Can you stop calling me Bucket?
Why? It's a nickname only we know about.
If I'm Bucket, that'll make you Sick Pervert.
Wait. That doesn't sound so bad.
I was bored at school anyway.
Enough with the nonsense.
Making a good impression on the first day is everything.
Anyway, I've seen most of the school myself,
so I don't need a tour.
This is where we should part ways.
Take care.
Wait, you can't leave like this.
What's your problem?
I'm not done telling you about the real juicy parts of the school.
I don't smoke,
so I don't need to know about the juicy spots.
I wasn't talking about the places to smoke.
If only you knew of the hierarchy within the school...
You should let go.
Seo Do Eon?
She's not interested.
Why are you grabbing on to her when she isn't interested?
How does this concern you?
Do you know her?
You're the one who's grabbing her without a cause.
Hey, Bucket. You don't know him, do you?
I can get to know her starting today.
Just because you are...
the heir apparent to CI Foundation...
doesn't make you her Prince Charming.
You're a diamond.
So act like one and be with your queen.
Bucket here lives in a different world.
Go off on your own.
But that makes me look like the bad guy.
You're a fun one,
Bucket.
Sorry about that.
My grip was too strong.
It wasn't that bad.
Anyway,
I'm Seo Do Eon in 11th grade.
If school life gets hard for you,
call me anytime.
If that's what you suggest...
I got it.
- I'll get going, then. - Sure.
Wait. I didn't tell him my name.
Seo Do Eon, my name is Kim Hye In.
H, Y, E. Hye In.
What he enjoys doing are costly activities.
Maybe his dad owns a super big company.
He has a girlfriend?
Sorry about that.
If you have eyes, use them.
Hold on.
Why does this feel familiar?
What the...
Is it their first time seeing a transfer student?
What? Why is this...
What was that?
I just tripped. Are you all just going to stare at me?
What are you doing?
I think it's her.
She said she'd be a transfer student...
who looks feisty and poor.
What?
Do you know how curious I was?
I was dying to know...
what you did to make our school's queen so furious...
and why she couldn't find any information about you.
I thought maybe the president had your back or something.
What the heck are you talking about?
But you're...
an equal education parasite, aren't you?
What?
I thought...
good shoes took you to good places.
But...
the shoes that I mistook as mine...
She's over here!
took me to the fiery pit.
Kim Hye In?
Did you admit me after knowing everything?
What do you mean?
They're treating me like trash for being an equal education candidate.
You acted as if you cared by mentioning scholarships.
How are you going to take responsibility?
“Responsibility?”
You're the reason I came to this school.
You should take responsibility.
Right.
The annual tuition costs 100,000 dollars,
and others can't attend this school even if they want to.
Who should you thank for being here?
Hello?
I have an offer to make.
An offer that can change...
your miserable life.
I looked into it, and there was no evidence found at the scene...
or anything that could be of harm to the school.
It seems as though Kim Hye In was cooperative.
That's what she stated?
Yes, sir.
Kim Hye In said she didn't see the culprit's face.
All right. You may head home now.
(Cheongdam International High School Application for Enrolment)
The choice is yours, Hye In.
(Seo Hee Soo)
If you want, I can transfer you back to your old school.
Is that what you want?
That's not my point right now.
I was just saying you should do something about...
I see.
So, on top of your admission and scholarship benefits,
you want me to be responsible for your peer relationships?
You're still a child.
There's only one thing I can do for you.
Letting you in...
and out.
The rest is up to you.
So make a choice.
Will you grab the chance that's been given to you...
or will you return to your miserable past?
I can see that you enjoyed my special welcoming ceremony.
You...
Do you think you have an idea of who I am now?
That crazy girl from yesterday?
You were from this school?
How dare you?
Can't you tell after seeing all that's happened?
How are you so slow?
Don't tell me...
Did you incite all of the students to go berserk...
on my first day of school?
Just because of what happened yesterday?
What? "Incite?"
Me?
Just because of you?
Who on earth are you?
I'm Baek Je Na, and since you got on my bad side,
you can consider your school life to be doomed.
(Who do you think is the most influential teen in Korea?)
(Baek Je Na)
I see. Her name is Baek Je Na?
I'm curious too.
What could someone like her lack in her life?
(Write a comment.)
I'm doomed.
You must be insane.
Seriously...
Hey. Get her.
- Je Na, are you okay? - Are you okay?
She's bleeding.