[All the characters, groups, businesses, incidents, agencies, and locales in this drama are fiction]
[Episode 10]
You knew already.
I told you I would become... a swordsman.
(T/N: Same spelling/sound as prosecutor in Korean)
Then why didn't you tell me so?
You didn't tell me anything, either.
You see, I'm a shy person.
Seo Hyeon Gyu is the one looking for this, isn't it?
The CEO of Law Firm Kangsan.
I expected that much.
Everything that has happened so far since the Seocho-dong case...
there's no way for the Kangsan's Knife-cutter to have operated on her own accord.
Tell me now
everything you know, Mister.
It'll be a long story.
I'll listen to you clearheaded.
Although the defendant was well aware that
the product manufactured at his company
could cause critical side effects on the human body,
he hid this fact in the organization systematically and distributed his products to the market.
Therefore, endangering the lives of many, which led to death.
Additionally, to cover up this incident, the defendant
destroyed the evidence, bribed, and threatened the victims.
Which only shows the heinous nature of his crime.
Hence, this court hereby sentences
the defendant, Jo Byeong Soo, imprisonment for life.
[Prosecution]
Mr. Seo Hyeon Gyu!
What the hell are you doing right now?
What do you think you're doing?
Let go of me.
Stop saying nonsense.
Don't you think I know that he's a substitute?
I don't think it matters that
much whether he's the real one or not.
What?
Most people in this country can't distinguish between real and fake anyway.
I create the truth my client wants and just received a payment for that.
Truth isn't something you look for.
It's something you create, Prosecutor Park.
Don't you have...
even the minimum amount of conscience?
Don't you?
Prosecutor Park, you're a very naive one.
What kind of attorney cares for a conscience?
We just work for money.
The job of an attorney, you see...
isn't to find justice or conscience.
It's about protecting the client.
That's why we get paid big money.
You want us to care for our consciences in the middle of that?
That behavior certainly lacks a sense of conscience.
I'm going to...
do whatever it takes to expose you.
Good luck.
Hey, Park Jae Kyung.
Are you out of your mind?
Why are you digging into Kangsan without my permission?
Slush Fund Creation and
Stock Price Manipulation Case of Daejung Group from three years ago.
[Daejung Group Slush Fund and Stock Price Manipulation Case]
Taesung Motors' Sudden Acceleration Case.
Joojung Construction's Department Store Collapse Case.
- And this is—
- Hey, you.
the most recent one.
[Humidifier Sterilizer Case]
Humidifier Sterilizer Case. They're all...
cases that Kangsan defended.
These are cases ruled as guilty by the Supreme Court.
They did get ruled for sure.
The problem is that the core suspects of each case are still having a feast
while the innocent substitutes are behind bars.
Okay. Sure.
Let's say your claims are true.
Even though you have no evidence to back that up, let's just say that you're right.
However, what will you do about cases whose trials are already over?
I'll catch the architect first.
CEO Seo Hyeon Gyu of Law Firm Kangsan.
Appoint me to investigate him officially.
You—
Do you even know who he is to say something like this?
That guy isn't just an attorney.
Every authority in this country is dying to befriend him.
People from the Blue House and hotshot politicians
are dying to have a meal with him.
That's who he is!
I don't understand what you mean.
If he did something bad, we should catch him.
Isn't that the purpose of our existence?
The presidential election is coming up soon.
Now isn't the right time, at least. Take your foot off the gas.
Well...
I'm saying I'll do my job. Why are you telling me to take my foot off the gas?
I refuse.
[Civil Service Division Establishment Proposal]
We're going to create a place called the Civil Service Division.
Where you only have a title of a prosecutor,
but you won't be able to do any real work.
It's not a place of exile.
It's a disposal room where you dispose of the defects.
We also have one here in the Criminal Division, right?
A prosecutor who's called a defect.
This is an organization.
If you keep up this act, I'll have no choice but to send you there.
Understood.
Send me there, then.
- Hey, Jae Kyung!
- Instead,
I'll be there after getting Seo Hyeon Gyu.
Please appoint me to investigate him officially.
Hey—
I heard stuff went down between you and the Deputy Chief.
Did rumors spread already?
I know your character, but...
you should be conscious of the higher-ups sometimes.
You've got to sit in one of those executive positions as well, no?
Hey...
A country bumpkin from Sapgyo passed the bar exam and became a prosecutor.
If I want anything more than that from here, then I'm being greedy.
You do you, Mr. Righteous..
There's no point in worrying about you ever.
- Thank you.
So? Did you get anything?
Why are you asking all of a sudden?
What?
I'm just curious.
He passed the bar before us, you know.
You stay out of this.
Don't become a defect along with me.
A defect?
There's something like that.
[Reporter Jin]
Anyway, you stay out of it. Okay?
Yes, Reporter Jin.
Yes, yes. Go ahead.
Seo Hyeon Gyu?
Okay, I understand. One second, please.
What's up?
I'll have to go first.
He said he had something to give me.
He said he found evidence to catch Seo Hyeon Gyu, however...
I couldn't get it at that time.
That reporter got into an accident, you see.
So I thought this was lost.
But...
I got it from the Chief one day before he passed away.
Do you know how he ended up with this?
I'm not sure.
Kim Tae Ho might be the one to know, though.
That reporter who called you.
By chance was that person someone I know—
Who is it?
- Are you expecting someone?
- No, wait here.
Who is it?
Long time no see.
Do you have a guest?
I'll come back later—
[Bad Prosecutor]
We meet again, Prosecutor Jin.
Gosh, I kept saying I'll pay a visit...
but I only got to come now.
Who has the item I'm looking for?
How unfortunate.
It's a useless item anyway.
Neither of you was able to break the code yet.
Hand it over to me, Prosecutor.
It's a request.
Your ass must be on fire
for you to be coming all the way here to get a useless item.
What's inside must surely be frightening for you.
Wow...
He would've been about 30 by now...
if Joon Soo was still alive, right?
- This son of a—
- Prosecutor Jin!
Just go back.
You're soiling the taste of liquor.
Prosecutor Jin...
could you please excuse us for a moment?
You're not the obedient type, huh?
Your mother must've had a hard time.
[Jung's Barbecue]
Do you... call your mom often?
[Mother]
Answer.
Please answer.
Answer!
Mom, answer, please!
Mom!
Yes, Son!
The car behind you. The car!
- Oh, gosh...
- Are you okay, Mom?
That damn bastard! How dare you drive like that?
- Come on, get up.
- Goodness, seriously.
- I-It hurts, it hurts.
- Why?
- Where? Do you think you got injured?
- Yes.
I only told them to say hi...
for the sake of our old times.
Enough is enough.
I could just kill you here.
Then you would've done it already.
If you're really capable of doing it,
you would've done it when you lost your wife and kid.
What?
Couldn't you just forget everything and live on?
I understand your desire to pay me back for what you got.
But Jae Kyung... it's not like your family will come back if you avenge them.
Let's just forgive.
Let's just forgive and forget everything and move on.
Bring me the item.
You tell Prosecutor Jin to give it to me.
There's no need for him to experience what you went through.
I said I'm okay. Why bother getting hospitalized?
They said you sprained your ligament, and your bone is fractured.
You're not okay at all, so just stay here.
I can just get outpatient treatment at home.
I have a group reservation tomorrow.
No, you can't go.
You have to take the day off. You need absolute rest.
Also, since you're here, get your checkup while you're at it and
take a break from the store for a few days. Is in it nice?
You need to live long to see your son get married.
I don't want to become an orphan.
Let's live long together, Mrs. Lim.
I'm going to live until the 22nd century.
Let's do that.
I'm off now.
Get better soon. I'll call you.
Seo Hyeon Gyu?
The CEO of Law Firm Kangsan?
What about your mother?
Is your mother okay?
Fortunately, she's okay.
The problem is that I'm not okay.
- Where are you right now?
- On my way to meet Prosecutor Oh Do Hwan.
I need to secure the black box.
Seocho-dong murder case happened because of the MP3.
Whoever the real culprit is... he must also be connected to Seo Hyeon Gyu.
You're going to catch the culprit first to get to Seo Hyeon Gyu?
I'll put them in jail myself.
Seo Hyeon Gyu messed with the wrong guy.
Jung, I understand how you feel but let's calm down a bit.
Even so, you can't just go to him without a plan—
♫ You can't bring me down ♫
Jin Jung...
Next up is...
K-Co Labs' Additional Collection of Taxes by the National Tax Service.
It's being investigated by the joint task force at the Northern District Prosecutors' Office, isn't it?
What do you think, Attorney Lee?
You're a former prosecutor general.
You must know a lot of people in the joint task force.
I think it'd be better to pass on this case.
Attorney Oh... this isn't the Prosecutors' Office. Get yourself together.
The joint task force on Financial and Securities Crimes was formed ambitiously.
However, in contrast to its beginning,
it still hasn't produced any meaningful results
according to popular opinion.
The joint task force must be dead set on this case, right?
Exactly.
As you can see on the last page of the report,
the joint task force is currently doing an additional internal investigation
on the officers' embezzlement allegations of tens of billions of won.
Under the circumstances,
shall we protect the client while going as far as to make an enemy of the regime?
Please keep in mind that...
we might fall into the curse of the victor...
as well if things go wrong.
Attorney Oh.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
The thing just now.
You didn't even share the information beforehand.
Are you messing with me on purpose?
Gosh. I apologize.
I'll be careful next time.
Hey!
You're laughing when I'm talking to you?
I heard you made a deal with my father using me.
You're making quite the scene thinking he's got your back.
Is it because you were born as a low-life?
You must've had a hard time...
being raised...
under a mother who's not quite a mother.
- Please cut it out.
- From the way I see it...
you take after your mom, Attorney.
- I heard your mom was the same. Sticking to this man and the other—
- I said to stop.
You should be the one to stop it.
Do you know... the difference between you and me?
Is that I'm allowed to do this.
Hey...
I got smacked in the face because of you.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Because of a low-life jurk like you...
the son of a bar hostess,
I was smacked by Father, you punk!
Well...
what brings you here, Prosecutor?
I had something to say.
Please take your leave...
or you can come with me to the Prosecution right now.
Gosh, it must hurt.
Are you okay?
Just tell me what you want.
Memory card.
I know you have it. That's why I'm here.
Let's keep things easy.
Why do you want that all of a sudden?
I'm going to catch him.
Do I need a different reason?
I could just arrest you for allegations of destruction of evidence, Oh Do Hwan.
Bring it to me before that.
If you need it that badly...
The proof was filmed very well.
What?
Am I handing it over too easily?
It's simple.
Don't think too hard about it.
I don't need it anymore and
you need it now.
Cut the crap and say the real reason.
Because he crossed the line.
This is the end of what I can do for you.
Good luck with the rest.
There was one more guy on that day who came to Ye Young's house.
A fidget spinner?
Yes! T-The thing that kids spin on their hands.
A fidget spinner.
You didn't see the culprit's face?
What about his voice?
He had a mid-to-low tone and a soft voice.
Why did Oh Do Hwan willingly hand this over?
He never moves without a purpose.
I got smacked in the face because of you.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
We'll know when we catch the culprit.
Do you have an idea as to who?
- Yes, Prosecutor.
- Yes.
Attorney Seo Ji Han of Law Firm Kangsan...
Find out everything about him as soon as possible.
Okay, got it.
[3139]
[Men's Locker Room]
Hurry up. We don't have time.
Stay put for a second.
Stuff like this get harder the more
you rush me.
I'm not even a locksmith.
What the hell am I doing?
He's coming.
Damn it, what do we do?
What do you mean?
What else? Go stop him.
Make some time for me, all right?
How?
Gosh, you're driving me nuts.
Just stop him!
Hey...
use your honey trap.
Just go at him.
Honey trap...
What's the matter?
I must've gotten the wrong person...
[Men's Locker Room]
Killing a person by beating her on the head with a knife rack...
It's not easy to kill with just one blow.
Just as the autopsy report said,
he beat the victim at least a few times...
even after the victim died.
While committing murder, he must also...
[Seha University Hospital]
have injured his hand.
Check the list of all the ER patients
on the day of the incident from all the hospitals
within a 5km radius of the scene.
I'm Prosecutor Shin Ah Ra from the Central District Prosecutors' Office.
Please cooperate with us regarding an investigation.
Collect all the patient lists with a hand injury.
I'm sure Seo Ji Han will be among them for sure.
Okay.
Gosh, what's wrong with me?
My head... What's wrong with me?
- Are you okay?
- I'm sorry...
I have sickle cell anemia.
Thank you so much.
- Please look at me.
- You're so kind.
Could I be hospitalized?
[ER Patient List]
[Seo Ji Han]
Seo Ji Han!
Wait a minute.
The guy in the dashcam footage was wearing the same clothes.
If all of this is a coincidence, we can't do our job.
I'll ask for the arrest warrant for Seo Ji Han.
We got this bastard.
The prosecutor is acting cute.
Yes, it's me. CEO Seo.
♫ The sound of children playing ♫
♫ The school grounds around dinnertime ♫
♫ Tinged by the sunlight that is regretfully left behind ♫
I'm sick of this.
It's always the same song.
Can't we listen to something else?
You don't know how to appreciate good music.
Listen carefully to the lyrics. They're so touching.
I like cartoon songs more.
You said you could put a lot of songs in here.
Can't you also put the songs I like in here?
I can't. It's daddy's.
Whoa, you're so petty.
Okay then.
If you win first place at the dictation test this time—
[Where are you?]
Where are you?
Mommy seems to be mad.
She becomes King Kong when she's mad.
- Hey... let's go before she becomes King Kong.
- Let's hurry.
Gosh...
♫ Do you think of me sometimes? ♫
♫ The shy fluttering that I had felt for the first time ♫
♫ Even now... ♫
I used to come here often with my father.
We came to slack off, so we didn't have to help Mom out.
Your mom must've had it rough.
Mister...
the reporter you mentioned last time...
The owner of this thing...
It was my father, wasn't it?
A defect?
There's something like that.
[Reporter Jin]
Yes, Reporter Jin.
It's me, Prosecutor.
Seo Hyeon Gyu?
Jung...
you should stop here now.
You're at it again.
You might experience what I went through.
Then you'll regret it for life.
You owe me one life, you know?
Couldn't you just stay out and call it even with that?
About what happened to your mother...
It won't end with a warning next time.
Do you plan not to listen—
- I'm a dog barking at a deaf tree.
- What did you say?
- What?
Nothing. It's my bad.
You can only choose between these two options.
You can do it with me or leave everything to me.
Also, I'm not going to lose anyone this time.
I'm going to catch him before I do.
What?
"Based on the collected evidence and the record of evidence collecting status,
factual evidence is lacking to admit the cause and need for the arrest warrant
[Dismissed]
as per requested by the Prosecution."
That's what it says.
What kind of crap is this?
[Seoul Central District Court]
Exactly why can't you issue the warrant—
It's a hearty harvest.
A hearty harvest of bullshit, both of you—
Hey, Prosecutor Jin.
How dare you talk that way? How rude!
Cut the nonsense.
Was this the reason for rejecting warrant issuance?
Let's grab some food next time.
Please take care.
Mr. Seo Hyeon Gyu.
Your gift was well received.
I'm glad.
Did your mother like it?
I'll pay you back soon...
because I can't stand owing someone.
Sure.
I'll be off then.
I'm not done talking.
I promise you.
I'm going to get you locked up, no matter what.
You can't even get a mere warrant issued.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
If I get serious about stopping you, Prosecutor...
you'll really die.
It's so weird.
It's not the case in other countries, but Lady Justice's eyes are blindfolded only in Korea.
Do you know why that is?
It's saying they should give sentences according to the person.
Also, the thing at the bottom. Do you know what that is?
People think it's the book of the law, but it isn't.
It's the list of names of powerful people.
That's funny.
What number are you on the list?
I'm the one who writes the list.
Attorney Oh...
Yes, CEO.
Is there something you know?
About how Prosecutor Jin was able to apply for a warrant.
If he did indeed apply for a warrant,
then it means he has a card up his sleeve.
But I just can't figure out what it is.
A person named Yoo Jin Chul gave me the memory card.
I think that person must've had a copy.
Oh, my.
Why didn't you check when you were getting it from him?
I apologize.
Please be more careful from now on.
Yes, Sir.
I can't even fathom how deeply rotten this is.
It'll never end...
unless we remove the root itself.
We need the herbicide, but there's no way.
Wouldn't something fall from the sky at a time like this?
There must be a way, whether it's a hoe or a pesticide.
Let's not give up and keep looking.
Who said I'm giving up?
I'm just saying that's how things are.
Yes, Investigator.
No.
Just photosynthesizing.
Yes, please go ahead.
What?
Yes, Judge.
I mean, we just met. So what's up?
I'm sorry, Sir.
I'm so ashamed.
He said the arrest warrant for Seo Ji Han was issued.
What?
♫ You forget your true feelings and chase after the traces ♫
Are you satisfied now?
Thank you for the help.
The thing you promised?
♫ I like it as it is ♫
♫ Show me who you are now shining brightly ♫
Good going.
A so-called judge having an affair.
Love... isn't a sin, is it?
Bullshit.
Your existence itself is a sin.
♫ Beautifully shining little star ♫
Thank you for helping out.
Jae Kyung...
I trust you.
Don't worry.
I won't make the same mistake and, this time...
there's a failproof card to catch that guy.
MP3?
Would it be enough with just that?
You know full well what kind of person Seo Hyeon Gyu is.
It'll be hard with just that alone.
It sounds to me...
like there's more stuff.
Something more substantial than the MP3?
[Law Firm Kangsan]
What is this about?
Gosh, these punks...
The audacity of these guys...
Do you even know who we are?
We're the Prosecution, you punks!
Hey, Eun Ji.
Make them quiet.
I'm here to meet Seo Ji Han.
[Arrest Warrant]
This is the arrest warrant for Seo Ji Han.
Please cooperate.
One moment, please.
- Contact Attorney Seo.
- I got it.
Wait. One second. What are you going to do?
Contact him?
You think we're here to escort him?
If you guys keep this up, it's an—
It's an...
Move out!
I told you to wait here.
We're the Prosecution. The Prosecution!
- Move out!
- This guy, seriously...
I said to move—
Hey, let's break through.
Stop him!
Move out, move out!
E-Everyone, we have an arrest warrant!
We have an arrest warrant!
- Move aside!
- Wait, wait.
Hold them off!
Come on now! Let go!
What do we do, Father?
They're right below, on the first floor.
So why did you... do something stupid like that?
If you were going to do it, then don't get caught.
Go and suffer just a little bit.
Father...
No father in this world abandons his son.
You're my son and...
the next CEO of Kangsan.
Don't worry and trust me.
What the heck? You didn't run away yet.
You should've run away.
I wanted to beat you up while catching you.
Is that something a prosecutor should say?
Let's go. You need to serve some time.
Let go.
I'll go on my own feet.
What is this jurk saying?
Take him.
You're next in line.
[Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office]
He won't talk.
It's not going to be easy.
To apply for the restriction warrant, we need one more thing whether it be evidence or a confession.
Our goal is Seo Hyeon Gyu, anyway.
If we just unlock the MP3, Seo Hyeon Gyu and Seo Ji Han...
We'll be able to put them away for sure.
That was his reason for committing murder in the first place.
We don't have time.
We need to hurry up and unlock it. Any luck with the password?
Dad's password?
Yes. I thought you might know something.
Maybe a number he used often?
I don't know exactly, but... this is for sure.
- Our family members' birthdays.
- Birthdays?
He was such a busy guy, you know.
One time, he kept forgetting our birthdays, so
I told him to use our birthdays for passwords from then on.
He didn't forget again after that.
But why do you ask?
No, I just got curious suddenly.
I'll see you later.
[Interview]
[Please enter password]
My birthday...
[920112]
[You have two more attempts remaining]
Mom's birthday?
[You have one more attempt remaining]
Gosh... damn it!
Coco...what are you biting on now?
I told you not to eat random things.
Why are you chewing the motorcycle key?
Will it be okay?
What?
You're buying... this without letting Mom know.
Sometimes, asking for forgiveness
is easier than asking for permission.
Remember today, my son.
Today... marks the day men's dreams came true and
the day of accepting a new member into our family.
The birthday of Elly.
It's a foreign name.
Yes, she's from Germany.
Guten Tag. Dokgo Tak.
(T/N "Good day" in German, Name of a Korean cartoon character)
Madong Tak.
(T/N: Name of a Korean comic character)
- Dad...
- Yes?
Don't say that stuff in front of Mom.
Okay.
Well... everything works out if you're handsome.
[Please enter password]
It worked.
It worked!
Father... this is a bit...
Hey, aren't you going home?
You won't get paid for overtime even if you do that.
Mister...
I unlocked my dad's password.
Take a look.
Do you come to the theater often?
Not often.
But I do come with my wife and son sometimes.
What about you, Executive Director?
Why did you call us here?
You're quite impatient, Executive Director.
About your company's humidifier disinfectant...
I think you two will have to take the blame for it.
I noticed that you two did a great job raising your children.
Do your children know that, though?
How you two merrily failed in a futures contract and
your houses are about to be levied now.
How do you know that, Attorney?
What do you mean, how do I know that?
Because the one who gave me this job...
your chairman, told me. That's how I know.
This is a good opportunity for you two, so
please make a good decision.
And what if we refuse?
Well... I didn't think that far.
I guess...
I'll find someone else.
We do need someone to take responsibility.
Honestly, though, that's too much of a hassle for me.
Why don't you just say yes?
I'm sorry, but I don't think this is right.
I can't be imprisoned for something I didn't do.
I'd rather be an incompetent father
than to be a cowardly one.
Okay then.
If that's how you feel...
Please don't come to me to talk about things like this ever again.
I'll be off now.
What the heck? Let go.
Let go! Let me go!
I said, let me go!
What is this?
Let me go, I said!
Let go!
Well, Manager Jo. So...
have you made up your mind?
Y-Yes. Yes, I did.
[Play again]
There was a reason Seo Hyeon Gyu was dying to find this.
Prosecutor Jin.
Yes?
Stay out of this.
This was my case from the beginning.
Hand over the MP3 to me and take your hands off of it.
We already said we'd do this together.
- This is enough to handcuff him—
- Listen to my order.
I'm your superior.
This isn't that kind of a matter.
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
Did you get scared after watching the video or something?
Yes. I got scared.
Leave.
What's the matter? Really!
Do you think this is a joke?
You told me that... you don't want to lose anyone.
I feel the same way.
I can't stand to see that happen again.
So, Jung, trust me and
you stay out of this. Okay?
I'm glad... that we're on the same page.
I also can't stand by
and watch something terrible happen to you.
So let's do this together.
They say to carry a burden together.
Why are you trying to keep carrying it alone?
Don't ever say you'll do it alone.
Just say it one more time.
I'm going to take you out of the case.
He thinks he's the boss around here.
What's that?
It's my mom's birthday.
Go to your mom.
Go where? We've got so much work to do.
You said it's her birthday. It only comes around once a year.
She's not feeling well. How sad would she be if you didn't celebrate her birthday?
The world won't end just because you take a break for a day.
Also... tell her you love her...
while you help her recover from her injuries.
I regret that the most.
I'll be going, then.
It's really a promise, okay?
Don't try to do anything alone.
Okay, okay.
You're taking the MP3, too. What can I do?
Hurry up and go. Your mom must be waiting.
Okay. Oh, right...
Thank you for the arrest warrant on Seo Ji Han.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Never mind, then. I'll be going.
Hey, Prosecutor Jin.
We've got tons of work to do starting tomorrow. Don't be late.
Don't be late yourself.
It looks like Son Heung Min has a game tonight.
I'll only watch the first half.
Call me if he makes a goal.
I'm going.
Yes, CEO Seo?
The item you were looking for...
I have it.
Come and get it.
♪ Happy Birthday to you. Happy Birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy Birthday dear Mrs. Lim ♪
♪ Happy Birthday to you ♪
- You saw that, right?
- Congratulations!
Why ask me to sing a song? Hurry up and blow it out.
You're getting the checkup tomorrow, okay?
Okay. Thank you, Son.
How is it that your son is such a good singer?
- Thank you.
- Is he a singer?
Gosh, he's not just good at singing.
He's also good at studying and sports.
My son is a prosecutor.
- Oh, my gosh!
- A prosecutor? My goodness!
- He's a prosecutor?
- I'm so envious!
- He's so handsome.
- Also a good singer...
I'd love a son-in-law like him.
I have to answer this call. I'll be right back.
Hello?
♫ It feels like my blurry vision has become a little more blurred ♫
♫ After all, the world is always unkind ♫
♫ It was a huge illusion, it hurts quite a bit ♫
♫ It's miserable, miserable ♫
♫ I believed that something would be
a little different from yesterday ♫
♫ Mistake, mistake, my bad ♫
♫ I just close my eyes indifferently ♫
♫ I want you to be quiet, but it's not easy this time ♫
♫ Look carefully, look at me ♫
♫ All I need is one bite, one bite ♫
♫ The more you swallow, the stronger you become ♫
♫ I need just one bite, yeah, just one bite ♫
♫ Now you gotta know, yeah you gotta know ♫
♫ Somewhere in the dark corner ♫
♫ Take a bite before the dawn right now ♫
♫ One bite, need just one bite ♫
♫ Now you gotta know, yeah you gotta know ♫
♫ I'm going to rip the night apart and dig deeper ♫
♫ And swallow the bitterness like a poison ♫
♫ All I need is my reckless judgment ♫
♫ I'm alone howling ♫
♫ The standards are all different ♫
♫ You talk a lot ♫
♫ Reasonable, reasonable ♫
♫ Whatever the answer is, because I can never avoid it ♫
♫ No way, no way, give up ♫
♫ I just close my eyes indifferently ♫
♫ I want you to be quiet, but it's not easy this time ♫
♫ Look carefully, look at me ♫
♫ Take out or break out ♫
♫ It doesn't matter what it is ♫
♫ Be careful this night ♫
[Bad Prosecutor]
I couldn't keep any of the promises I made to you, Mister.
You did well. We're now accomplices.
How dare you come here?
May the deceased rest in peace.
I'll never forgive you.
Prosecutor Jin seems to have found a clue on the case.
He has a helper?
Tell this to your father clearly.
I have the evidence of him committing murder.
Your needless arbitrary actions and pride drove Jae Kyung to death.
I'm getting curious at this point.
What drove you to this point, Prosecutor Jin?
My family upbringing.
♫ Now you gotta know, yeah you gotta know ♫