[All the characters, groups, businesses, incidents, agencies, and locales in this drama are fiction]
Senior!
Are you hurt anywhere? Are you okay?
Yes, I'm all right.
Please do me a favor.
This is a ledger with the list of drug buyers.
They're all usernames.
The culprit is in there.
The one who killed Chief Prosecutor.
From two weeks before Chief Prosecutor's death until the day of the incident,
there were a total of five drug buyers.
Please confirm their identities.
All right. I'll look into it.
It's important, so please get this done as—
I think someone was on your tail.
Hey, you bastard!
- Get him!
- He's over there!
Hey, go block the exit!
The rest of you, come up!
Since when have you been tailing me?
Since you left the office.
Your lack of shame knows no bounds.
How can you be this brazen?
I should be the one saying this.
I heard Prosecutor General said that you...
should put all your effort into capturing Prosecutor Jin with me.
This is the end of your solo act, Shin Ah Ra.
We're a family, you know.
Family?
Us?
Don't even say that as a joke.
I'm disgusted just listening to it.
We'll see about that.
I'm sorry, Prosecutor.
I think we lost him.
That's interesting.
Hey!
Hey, come this way!
Where did he go?
Where the heck did he go?
Jung!
J-Jung...
Jung, get yourself together!
Jung!
Get yourself together.
Can you get up?
Let's go to the hospital.
Hang in there a bit longer. We're almost at the hospital.
We can't go to the hospital.
The hospital will report me.
- We definitely can't—
- Is getting reported the issue here?
You're going to die!
Who is it?
Who's there?
He's bleeding too much.
Careful, careful now.
Luckily, he missed his organs.
The problem is that he lost too much blood.
His blood type is B.
What's your blood type?
- Hey.
- Yes?
- She's asking about your blood type.
- O-Oh, okay.
I-I'm t-type A.
Sitting around here won't solve anything.
- We should contact the hospital right away and—
- It's fine.
No need to do that.
[Bad Prosecutor]
[Episode 6]
You already know even if I don't tell you, right?
He needs to be at complete rest for a while.
Thank you.
Buy me a drink later if you're thankful.
Relationships are really a funny thing.
My law school student is working with you now.
It's ill-fated, you know.
You don't know what happened to him?
Thanks for your work. Get home safely now.
Hey, Park Jae Kyung!
It's not like I don't know what happened to you, but
isn't it about time for you to get back into things?
You didn't become a prosecutor to live like this forever, did you?
Wake up and pull yourself together.
Bye now.
What happened?
I'm not sure...
When I found him, he was already...
You must be tired. Get some sleep.
I'll look after that guy.
N-No, I'll keep nursing him.
You're Shin Ah Ra, right?
44th class of the training institute.
How do you know about me, Director?
How could I not know when you're next to Prosecutor General Kim Tae Ho?
Let's take our time with the talks later.
Get some sleep for now.
I'll bring you a blanket and a pillow.
Prosecutor Jin escaped the scene?
How?
I think Prosecutor Shin Ah Ra helped him.
Traces of blood were found at the scene,
but I think they were Prosecutor Jin's.
Looking at the shape and the amount of traces,
it seemed that somebody attacked Prosecutor Jin.
What?
Did you not know?
What about the attacker?
We're investigating right now.
Thank you.
I don't think your mom will stay quiet if she finds out you're the last in your class.
That's why... you need to go in and be my shield, Dad.
I'm scared of your mom, too.
Okay then.
I can sacrifice myself with no problem for my dear son.
What do we do, son?
I think I left my phone at the press.
Stop lying.
You're lying because you don't want to go in with me, huh?
Hey, don't you know that your daddy's a journalist?
Chasing only after the truth, Journalist Jin Kang Woo!
Can't I come with you?
I will be right back. Stay here and eat your ice cream.
No, I want to come with you and look!
- Stay put. I'll be right back.
- C-come on!
Prosecutor!
Prosecutor... Are you okay?
Prosecutor Jin!
How's your wound?
- Did you seal it?
- It's okay. Everything's done.
So why would you go there alone?
You can never act on your own from now on.
Never, never again.
- Why are there so many shoes?
- Did I make you all worry?
- You're here?
- I'm sorry.
Oh, I brought these.
All right...
What's this?
This is gunpowder and lighter.
Hey, why did you bring them?
- This is the best way to sear the wound.
- Sear where?
Don't do it! Do it when you get hurt.
- Who are those people?
- I'm okay.
- Look, it barely brushed against it.
- The three siblings.
I'm all better now.
Jin Jung and the three siblings.
Prosecutor... did you at least see...
the face of the one that stabbed you?
I couldn't see the face, but...
I saw sterile gloves on the hands.
It's probably the same person.
The one that left the syringe at my house.
Why would that bastard... keep trying to kill you?
There must be a reason for trying to stop the investigation.
Something that must stay hidden even by killing a person.
I haven't the slightest idea.
I'll just follow you.
It's easy. Don't make it too complicated.
We catch and beat the crap out of the stabber or the planner...
Either of them, for sure.
Even better if we catch both of them.
Let's move.
It's revenge from now on.
[Prosecution Service]
I heard you met Prosecutor Jin. Why did you do that?
I'm sorry.
Fine.
Instead... this will be the last time you don't listen to me.
It's a warning, Prosecutor Shin.
In fact...
I also don't have the face to meet that kid.
What kind of Prosecutor General can't even cover up for a family member?
Prosecutor Jin probably understands.
I would be glad if that was the case.
How's Prosecutor Jin's body recovering?
Pardon?
Weren't you taking care of him?
Where is he right now?
How did you... know that Prosecutor Jin was attacked?
I got the report from Prosecutor Oh.
He said there were traces of Prosecutor Jin's blood at the scene
and that you took him to get him treated.
It'll be bad if the wound doesn't get treated and develop complications.
Never mind. Let's take Prosecutor Jin to the hospital right now.
That would be better.
Yes, it's me. Bring out the car.
What's the address?
Senior!
Don't tell anyone at the office about me being here.
Not even the Prosecutor General?
I don't trust anyone, but you, Senior.
Prosecutor Shin.
I'm sorry, Prosecutor General.
I can't tell you.
What do you mean?
I clearly gave you an order.
I can get the punishment for disobeying your order later.
After arresting everyone involved in this case.
How did it go?
There's no suspicious character in the call history.
They're all investigators or office-related people.
What about the mobile carrier location tracking?
About where they have been.
We did all that a long time ago.
But the broadcasting station's radius is too wide.
I don't think I can pinpoint a location.
We placed one of Eun Ji's guys as a tail,
but Prosecutor Oh is also, you know...
quite the player as well.
We really can't kidnap him?
No, we can't. Put away that idea.
It seems certain that there's a location where Prosecutor Oh meets the one behind the scenes.
The problem is...
how to find out that location.
That's... with a location tracker.
Come on. What if things go wrong, and we end up at Incheon again?
Maybe we can put it on his car, but not on him.
We can't even put it on his car, actually.
Wasn't his car smashed and is being repaired?
Hey, Go Joong Do...
Good job. You did well.
What about me?
You, too, Eun Ji.
I think we can find a way.
The navigation.
In 2.7 km,
there's a tunnel ahead.
What? The navigation?
The navigation!
What about the navigation?
Look up the repair shop for Oh Do Hwan's wrecked car.
A black sedan. 1514.
- Whoa...
- Understood.
Wait...
Hey!
Aren't you guys going home?
We were going to go after breakfast tomorrow.
Breakfast tomorrow?
I'm going out right now.
Gosh...
Why are you leaving tomorrow morning?
I'll leave right after breakfast.
Hyeon Gyu,
you're putting me in a tough spot if you keep this up.
How could you do that to a prosecutor?
Let's say Lee Jang Won couldn't be helped because of the item, but
you went too far this time.
I beg of you, please, Hyeon Gyu.
Prosecutor Jin...
I'll also try my best to catch him as soon as possible.
So if you can wait a bit longer...
Trying your best...
it means nothing.
A person should do a good job to be useful.
Also, Tae Ho,
I shouldn't have to tiptoe around you to do my job. Don't you think?
Did you find the item?
Give me a new worm.
This one's not that good.
This is the identified list of the philopon buyer IDs.
[Background Check Results]
[Tae Hyeong Wook, Chief Secretary of Law Firm Kangsan]
What's this?
Law Firm Kangsan?
The name's Tae Hyeong Wook.
The CEO Seo Hyeon Gyu of Law Firm Kangsan's Chief Secretary.
Chief Secretary of the biggest law firm in our country?
There must've been some mistake.
Not at all. I checked many times already but it is correct.
Any past records related to drugs?
No criminal records.
This is the first time.
A person with no records bought drugs?
That's weird.
What's even weirder is
that the date of purchase is
one day before the Chief's death.
[Law Firm Kangsan]
I apologize. The meeting took longer than expected.
Nice to meet you. My name is Seo Ji Han.
I'm Prosecutor Shin Ah Ra of the Central District Prosecutors' Office.
My reason for today's visit is none other than...
None other than wanting to meet Tae Hyeong Wook.
Chief Secretary Tae?
I'm not sure.
Asking for that without even telling us the reason is a bit...
It's regarding an internal investigation, so
please understand that I can't tell you.
An internal investigation?
I understand. I'll cooperate.
Thank you.
Instead, just let me know what it's about.
If it's enough to bring you here, then it must be a pretty big deal.
Just unload a bit more, please.
I'll make sure to pay you handsomely for the details.
Is it just me, or are you actually interested
in this more than you need to be?
It seems that I came on a wrong day.
I'll visit again next time.
[Law Firm Kangsan]
Yes, Father. It's me, Ji Han.
Someone came from the Prosecution.
[Shin Ah Ra]
Shin Ah Ra of Central District Prosecutors' Office.
Bring me her background ceck.
Okay.
I thought he was a lone wolf but Jin Jung has a lot of friends.
It's a background check report on the philopon buyers.
Tae Hyeong Wook is the most likely suspect so far.
Kangsan?
The biggest law firm in our country?
It's not certain yet.
It's just a little too suspicious.
How are things for you?
I'm still digging into Oh Do Hwan.
- By tomorrow-
- Not that.
How are things for you?
Now that I think about it I haven't told you that yet, Sunbae.
Thank you.
Treat me well if you're. All right?
Now...
get ready for my special doenjang jjigae.
Ta-da!
You should feel honored.
Not anyone gets to taste my food.
Is that so?
Thanks for the food.
Okay, please enjoy.
Snowball, come here for a second.
Come here.
Right?
It's weird, right?
Here.
"Hell no?"
I didn't tell you that I'm allergic to bean paste, did I?
Let's go out to eat.
Come on, let's go.
Who has bean paste allergies?
[Ox blood hangover soup]
Thank you.
I heard you gave me your blood.
It's the same blood.
You share it and reuse it.
I'll save you next time.
That's fine.
If you're going to save me, save me now.
The ox blood.
You want me to give you mine?
Have all you want.
Come on, man. Just one isn't friendly enough.
One glass of soju as well?
A patient should...
be sterilized, at least, right?
Excuse me.
[Suspect in the Murder Case of Chief Prosecutor Lee Jang Won is on the Publicly Wanted List]
Hey.
Put your cap on.
Hurry.
[Suspect in the Murder Case of Chief Prosecutor Lee Jang Won is on the Publicly Wanted List]
[Jung's Butcher Shop]
Mr. Park.
What's wrong with my Jung suddenly?
Murder?
[Jung's Butcher Shop]
I mean—
Hang up. I'll call back.
[Mr. Park]
[Beloved Son]
Did you order the public arrest of Prosecutor Jin yourself?
Later.
It's a hasty decision.
If Prosecutor Jin is not the culprit—
Prosecutor Shin, later.
Please tell me right now!
The evidence that proves he is guilty isn't clear, and there's a possibility of him being framed.
Violating the presumption of innocence law and revealing his face means
- you're branding him as the culprit—
- Shin Ah Ra!
Don't ever raise your voice in front of me again.
This is your last warning.
Hello and welcome.
Yes.
I would like to change my engine oil.
Okay. One moment, please.
- Thank you.
- Sure thing.
A black sedan. The plate number is 1514.
[NAVI-83]
[Search and Route]
[Recent Destinations]
Same time...
same movement...
there's nothing suspicious.
[73 Euneun-dong, Deokyang-gu, Goyang-si]
A wine bar?
- Gosh, thanks for having us.
- Welcome.
- Gosh, hello.
- Hello.
We're... detectives from the Seoul Police, Violent Crime Division.
We're here to ask you...
if you've... seen this person.
I heard he came to this place a few days ago with someone else.
Oh, this person. I do remember.
He also came two days ago.
[29 Ro 1514]
[Recent Search]
[Recent Destinations]
[77-22 Seocho-dong, Seocho-gu, Seoul]
[73 Euneun-dong, Deokyang-gu, Goyang City]
Stop.
If you give us a call next time...
G-Give us a call.
Did anyone come here?
They were here just now.
They just left, though.
It doesn't seem like they're here.
Everyone, come up!
Spread out and check the rooms!
- Okay.
- Understood.
Hey, what do we do?
- Jump.
- What?
Shit!
Then hide!
- Hey, are you okay?
- You can't stay there!
I can't jump. Never.
Shit...
This is too high.
Hurry up and come down!
What was that sound?
Goodness...
There!
[Prosecution Service]
- Is that what happened?
- Yes.
Prosecutor Hwang, long time no see!
There's good food on the menu today.
Enjoy your meal, guys.
Enjoy your food.
The rumor did spread quite a bit.
That you're ignoring the Prosecutor General's orders...
and helping Prosecutor Jin.
Even so... what the heck are they doing?
Eat up now.
- Okay.
- Sure.
Gosh, Prosecutor!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, Senior.
You should've been more careful.
You're now expelled from the class order, Senior.
You know the reason why, right?
Higher-ups order and subordinates obey. Uniformity among prosecutors.
Let's pay respect where respect is due, all right?
People like you and Prosecutor Jin
are the reason why other prosecutors are also in trouble.
You guys are really crossing the line here.
Are you guys in high school or something?
What are you doing? Being so childish, like a kid!
Hey.
Investigator Park.
- Have you gone mad?
- Have you gone mad!
Are you crazy!
Hey.
Did you throw away your sense of reason in the waste bin?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay... but how about you?
I'm not okay.
- Dan it...
- Clench your teeth.
You'll bite your tongue.
Wait, Prosecutor! Calm down!
Calm down! Please!
Come over here!
- How dare you!
- Please stop!
- Hey, you!
- Hold her down!
Try then.
If it's suspicious, it's right to investigate until the end.
[Reaping the greatest benefit from the Chief's fall]
[Prosecutor General Kim Tae Ho]
The reason why you're telling me to wrap up the investigations in a hurry...
is it because of your Prosecutor General appointment?
♫ I can't stand it any longer ♫
Congratulations, Prosecutor General.
♫ Look forward to the big picture I've drawn so far ♫
♫ As you did, no more than that, I'll give it back ♫
♫ No, you can't bring me down ♫
[Seocho-dong murder case assignment was not a coincidence]
[Seocho-dong Assault and Murder of Park Ye Young]
Hey, Chul Ki, this is not a mistake, right?
I'm keenly aware of the ones who are trying to stab my back.
And the reason why you assigned the Seocho-dong murder case to Prosecutor Jin.
[People who were aware of Chief's autopsy]
[Me, Ah Ra sunbae, Prosecutor General Kim Tae Ho]
There's no time. Please request a warrant first, Senior.
[Warrant Request for a Second Autopsy]
♫ Why is it natural to be twisted? ♫
♫ Open your eyes and look, look properly ♫
♫ On top of my head ♫
♫ You'll think there is ♫
[Why? Why me?]
Why would that bastard...
keep trying to kill you?
♫ I'll turn you over ♫
♫ Deep in the dark ♫
♫ Burn myself out more ♫
Yes.
I just heard everything.
Prosecutor Oh and the Prosecutor General are...
Shouldn't we let Prosecutor Shin know?
Once it becomes more certain...
You all did a good job. I'll look into it now.
You'll do it in person, Prosecutor?
To catch a tiger... you need to step into its den.
[Oh Do Hwan]
♫ You can't bring me down ♫
[Administrator]
You're saying I can break through the login lock with this?
Of course. Who do you think I am?
What's the program password?
zh...
+i!...
I'm kidding. I changed it.
What is it? The password.
It's 1004,
which stands for "angel."
[1004]
[Administrador]
[Prosecutor General Kim Tae Ho]
[Prosecutor Oh: We had a guest at the wine bar.]
[Prosecutor General: Are they Prosecutor Jin's people?]
[Prosecutor General Kim: Catch them by all means. Before he realizes.]
[Prosecutor Oh: Okay.]
[Prosecutor General Kim: Don't make me regret taking you under my wings. Prove your worth, Prosecutor Oh.]
What's wrong with your face?
Did something bad happen?
Well, there are lots of bad news.
Never mind that.
Did you find something out?
Stop with the nonsense!
I saw it.
The conversation between Oh Do Hwan and the Prosecutor General.
[Prosecutor General Kim Tae Ho]
Please help me, Senior.
I need your help to capture the Prosecutor General.
I know that it's going to be very hard.
But let me still ask this of you.
What if I decide to turn a blind eye?
I know you wouldn't do that.
You already had some ideas as well.
If you're still going to turn a blind eye, though...
Never mind.
Just don't do that.
That's not why we get paid with tax money.
Think about it and give me a call, please.
I can't wait too long, though.
This is Shin Ah Ra, Prosecutor General.
I have something to tell you.
May I come and see you in front of your house, please?
What is it that you need to tell me?
My thoughts were too hasty, Prosecutor General.
I was wrong.
I'll never go against your orders.
How could I trust your words?
You already have a history.
Tell me.
Shin Ah Ra, try and tell me.
Tell me what you can do to let me trust you again.
Prosecutor Jin's location...
I'll tell you.
[Jin Jung]
Yes, Senior.
Where are you?
At the stadium, where we just met.
Wait there.
I'll be there in ten minutes.
[Recording]
Prosecutor Jin!
What do I need to do?
Prosecutor Jin thinks that you're the one who framed him.
So he suggested to you to capture me with him?
Yes.
I thought it was nonsense...
because you would never do that.
You didn't do that right, Prosecutor General?
What should I even tell you?
Before that, Prosecutor Shin,
let's have your phone turned off.
Would the Prosecutor General trust me?
He probably wouldn't.
He'll try to examine your phone, of course.
Then do you know what to do next?
This is too obvious, though...
Don't make me do a body search on you, please.
You haven't answered my question.
Please answer me, Prosecutor General.
The one who framed Prosecutor Jin...
was it really you, Prosecutor General?
Just do as it says here.
[Lee Jang Won Murder Case Report]
As my Father orders.
Keep that in mind.
Answer me, I said!
I've served you for eight years
because I respected you.
You were my role model, and I wanted to be like you!
Everything you told me and the actions you took on your junior prosecutors...
Were they all lies?
On top of framing Prosecutor Jin,
did you also send a person to kill him—
Don't be hasty to run your mouth.
Mind your manners in front of your superior!
Mind your manners for your subordinate first, please.
Please tell me.
Were they all parts of your plan?
Did you really try to kill Prosecutor Jin?
No, no, I didn't!
I didn't do that!
I didn't even know about such plans, and I—
You're saying you did...
frame Prosecutor Jin, then...
Even if you hear the truth from me,
there's nothing you can do.
I decide whether I can do it or not.
You just answer me, Prosecutor General.
I couldn't help it.
This is my answer.
You'll be sent to the disciplinary committee soon.
Allegations of aiding and abetting a murder suspect's escape.
After expelling, you'll be investigated with restraint.
Thank you for all your work, Prosecutor Shin.
I would like to thank you for everything.
I'll bill you for the slap separately later.
This is too obvious, though.
It's fine if he finds out. Even better if he doesn't.
The real one is elsewhere, anyway.
What is it?
The real one is this.
Plan C.
Excuse me for one moment.
Ta-da.
You didn't know about this, did you?
You just answer me, Prosecutor General.
I couldn't help it.
That's my answer.
I skip the honorifics to bad guys, Prosecutor General.
I don't treat them as human beings, you see.
You're done for.
[Bad Prosecutor]
Put your guard up tight. It's your turn now.
Is there a reason why Chief Lee Jang Won's death has to be a suicide?
Prosecutor Oh Do Hwan, don't cross the line.
This is the only card we have left.
The one that can capture Prosecutor General Kim Tae Ho.
Fabricating the autopsy of Chief Prosecutor Lee Jang Won...
I did it alone.
It doesn't look good to have multiple prosecutors stuck to one culprit.
The medical examiner disappeared in the middle of transport.
You can just speak comfortably.
I'll write the contents, so you just need to sign if you want to save the two.
- Let me go!
- If anything happens to them...
I'm going to kill you.