= Based on the famous cyber fiction "Addicted & Heroin" =
# A bike was cycling along the sidewalk. #
# And then it stopped at the corner store. #
# There was beautiful handwriting on the blackboard. #
# And I saw your smile of ardent love. #
# The sun was shining on the playground. #
# And you were running free... #
# Ice cream and sugar-coated haws, #
# The taste of sweetness. #
# Our promise of love is still echoing in the sea waves, #
# Even though nothing could ever compare to the hug. #
# Have you ever held fast to love in solitary #
# Because you believe it will never fade away... #
= Addicted&Heroin =
= Episode 11 =
Gu Hai. Gu Hai.
Where is Bai Luoyin?
I don't know.
He hasn't been to school for two days.
Don't you live near him?
You don't know?
No, I don't.
I haven't been to his home for a long time.
Then let's go to his home after school.
You're a boarder, teachers will come to check.
Maybe we should wait.
If he still doesn't show up tomorrow,
then we can go to visit him on Sunday.
Don't wait until Sunday, let's visit him today.
Why are you so worried?
He just took a two-day off.
If something really happened to him,
someone would have come to pick his stuff a long time ago.
You're too calm.
I thought you were sympathetic.
I never expect you are such a person.
Yang Meng, good for you.
What's wrong with you?
Yinzi, Yinzi.
Baby boy.
Sir, you're home.
You haven't come here for a while.
Why are you here?
If I hadn't followed you here,
how can I know your dad call you 'baby boy'?
He is not my father.
He's Bai Luoyin's father.
Nice to meet you, sir.
You're also Yinzi's classmate, right?
You look energetic.
Sir, where is Bai Luoyin?
He is sleeping.
He went to bed so early?
He went to bed this morning.
He should be awake by now.
Is, is he ill?
No. He's just sleepy.
He wants to sleep.
- Baby boy. Come over here. - Okay.
Help me trim the vegetables. come on.
Why are you here?
You haven't been to school for two days.
So I come here to see you.
You had quarrels with Gu Hai?
Why him?
Don't you think
your feelings for him are special?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just don't wanna go to that place.
Send me back.
Return the same way we came?
Or you just left your bag at home?
It's Gu Hai's homework.
I intended to give it to him myself.
Now that he didn't come to school,
I'll leave it with you.
Where is Gu Hai?
I don't know.
You don't know where he is?
Are you two trying to
go to school in turn?
You are here today, and he'll come tomorrow.
And then integrate the knowledge together.
Gu Hai was here yesterday?
Yeah.
He was here when you were absent for two days.
Dahai,
I'm glad you broke up with your girlfriend.
When you were together,
I felt embarrassed to tell you.
What's so good about Jin Lulu?
She may be beautiful and good-looking,
but there are lots of beautiful girls.
You're too good for her.
He's right.
She always gives herself airs and graces.
And she throws her weight around.
She pretends to be what she is not.
If it were not for you,
I would've quarreled with her for several times.
You should've broken up with her a long time ago.
Look at these waitresses here,
they are all prettier than her.
That's right.
You're handsome and rich.
Every girl would think about you.
You're right.
Waiter. Wa...
Dahai. What's the matter?
Am I...
Am I not being good enough to you?
I've never been so good to someone before.
Yeah, yeah.
You've never been so good to anyone.
Then why did you say those cruel words?
Because I'm lowly.
I'm so lowly.
Who is lowly?
Dahai, where did you lean to bite people?
What has Jin Lulu done to you?
Yinzi, I miss you.
Dahai.
Get up.
Let go of me.
I thought you didn't care.
Dahai, get up.
No, Dahai. Listen to me.
I must sleep with you today.
No, Dahai, Dahai.
I'll change my name
if I can't make you feel comfortable.
No.
Huzi, Huzi, help me.
Huzi.
I heard that Gu Hai is going to transfer, right?
How do you know that?
I went to your teachers' office just now
and I heard them talking about it.
Good day, Mr. Gu.
Someone is outside. He said he is your classmate.
Can he come in?
Yes.
Okay. Please wait a moment.
Why are you here?
To send something to you.
You think I still need those craps?
It's your business.
Our teacher asked me to do so.
You can throw them away
if you don't want them.
These are your stuffs.
I gotta go.
Bai Luoyin.
Come back.
So, now you can only treat me like this?
What kind of attitude do you want me to have towards you?
Bai Luoyin.
Except for the day my mom died.
I never cried for anyone else.
Just go.
Get out.
# If I never met you, #
# Where would I live now? #
# What the days would be? #
# Was the life worth cherishing? #
# Maybe I would meet someone, #
# living a common life. #
# I don't know #
# if I can have sweet love. #
# I only care about you as time going by. #
# I'm willingly to feel you breath. #
Dad.
You come back so late.
Where have you been?
I sent something to my classmate.
Yinzi.
Dahai hasn't been to our home for a while.
Tell me the truth.
Did you have quarrels with Dahai?
No.
No?
Then why doesn't he come to our home?
He has his own home.
He is rich.
Why does he have to live in our home everyday?
Yinzi, let me tell you.
Dahai is such a good lad.
How can you find another friend like him?
It's common for you guys
to have quarrels.
You're a grownup now.
You should be broad-minded.
You can't sever ties with such a good friend
just because of some trivial matters.
It's not worthy.
I can't be broad-minded about this.
He's just a child,
what could he has possibly done to you?
He stole your girlfriend?
No.
His dad stole your wife.
What, what do you mean?
His father has married my mom.
It's...
Did you know about it at first?
Or he just kept it from you
and approach you on purpose.
Wait.
What am I trying to say?
Wait. I mean...
Neither of us knew that at first.
Mom came to see me the other day
and ran into him.
That's how I know that.
So, you both didn't know at first?
What a coincidence.
What do you young people call this?
Destiny. It's destiny, right?
It's great.
Now you're doubly related.
You can drop in to see him
when you go to visit your mom in the future.
Dad.
Don't you care?
Why should I care?
You mom has gone for so many years.
No.
I mean, we got divorced many years ago.
It's reasonable for her to find a lover.
She is a woman,
it's great for her
to find someone to rely on.
I know. She has talked to you many times.
But you shouldn't hate her or resent her.
After all, she is one of the few people in this world
who really cares about you.
I think she is very selfish.
Who isn't?
If it happened to you,
you would choose to live all by yourself?
Then why didn't you tell me before?
You never let me.
What should we do now?
I've already severed ties with him.
Listen to me, apologize to him.
And then continue your life.
I won't apologize to him.
What?
Why are you so goofy?
Did he ask his dad to marry your mom?
He is also a victim of the broken marriage.
I still won't apologize to him.
What? What do you want me to say?
- Dad. - It's...
Dad. Don't worry.
I know what to do.
Here's the thing.
You have to bring Dahai back
within three days.
Alright.
Remember that.
I get it.
- I'm sorry. - How dare you hit me.
Bro, you need to come with us.
Let go of me.
- Don't move. - Let go of me.
Tie him up. Hurry up.
Let go of me.
Who are you?
- Let go of me. - Hold him.
Let go of me.
I've never been so stupid in my life.
Look at my hand.
You see? My finger is hurt.
Stop it.
When I was in the army,
no one dared to fight against me.
We suffered great losses today.
I told you that we should bring more people.
But you refused. Look at us.
How could I know that he is so fierce?
Alright, stop it. Start the car.
The buyer is waiting for us.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
You tell me.
Don't you wanna leave me?
Don't wanna make a clean break with me?
Then I'll imprison you here.
You have no where to go.
You... You...
Baby.
You have already known that
I have special feelings for you, right?
So, you shouldn't be surprised
that I kissed you.
Gu Hai, what is the hell wrong with you?
Don't scold me.
Just hear me out.
You can scold me after that.
I don't have a lofty image in your heart anyway.
I'll let it collapse today.
I'm telling you,
I never regard you as my buddy.
The reason why I am so nice to you
is because I like you.
The reason why I sleep on the same bed with you
is because I wanna sleep with you.
I even dream about that.
Why?
You think I'm nasty?
You think I'm sick, right?
I can tell you,
it's your responsibility.
You must've known
my nasty thoughts a long time ago.
And you still try to seduce me on purpose.
Bai Luoyin.
I don't regret at all
for what I said today.
Don't you wanna scold me?
Come on, do it.
I wanna know how you're gonna scold me.
I won't scold you.
You're desperate, right?
You must regretting know me, right?
You want me to piss off, right?
I'm telling you. It's impossible.
You made me fall for you and now you wanna walk away?
Gu Hai.
You're gonna pay for what you said.
I don't care.
As long as I can see you everyday,
I can take anything.
Well.
Listen carefully.
I actually came to apologize to you today.
I talked with my father for a long time yesterday.
He doesn't care about who you are at all.
He also wants me to bring you home.
And then, I got kidnapped this morning.
Being tied here.
And I'm also humiliated by a psychopath.
You tell me, what should I do?
Untie me.
You...
You're telling the truth?
Of course.
What if it's a trap?
Then I'm tricked by you again.
Sir.
Dahai.
Why don't you come to our home recently?
I miss you.
Sir, did Yinzi tell you everything?
Yeah.
Yinzi knows nothing. I sent him to you.
He should've arrived at your place by now.
Yeah, he should be here soon.
Sir, I gotta go. I'll go check on him.
Untie me.
What should I do if you run?
Don't worry, I won't run .
My Yin.
Baby.
You're still angry at me?
Who do you want to sleep with?
If I don't wanna sleep with you,
- then I can't be a good boyfriend. - You...
Where are you going?
It's none of your business.
We haven't done talking, where are you going?
We have nothing to talk about.
Just now I bared my heart to you,
shouldn't you also say something to me?
What do you want me to say?
I think I'm kind that I didn't kill you.
What do I want you to say?
I've already told you that I like you.
Don't you think that you should respond?
Gu Hai.
Would you stop behaving like a crazy person?
I'm not crazy.
I'm telling you the truth.
What's wrong with two males?
Don't you remember the other day
while we were walking a dog,
we saw a dog and a cat were together.
That's not the same.
What's the difference?
You don't need to worry about my gender,
you don't need to worry about
whether it's a male cat or a female dog.
Just tell me,
whether you like me or not.
No, I don't.
Get out of my way, I'm going home.
What exactly do you want?
So you don't like me?
Alright then. I'll lock you in this room.
I will not let you leave
until you fall in love with me.
Gu Hai.
Yinzi.
I really like you.
I know you've known that a long time ago.
You can ignore my nonsense.
But you have to believe that I like you.
It's okay if you don't like me.
I can wait for you.
I can woo you.
I will give you lots of love.
You will be moved.
Luoyin, have a piece of sea cucumber.
There are still many sea cucumbers in the plate.
Why are you taking Luoyin's?
He doesn't like this, he'll have loose bowels.
You...
Wow.
Look at them.
They are so close.
I never had the chance to ask Hai
when is your birthday.
You're at the same age.
Then what about the month?
Our Luoyin was born in May in lunar calendar.
Hai, in which month were you born?
He was also born in May.
And the date?
May the first in lunar calendar. How about you?
The same as you. At what time?
I...
Weren't you born on May the sixth in lunar calendar?
It seems that Hai wants to be the elder brother,
but it turns out that our Luoyin is elder.
I feel really happy
to see them so close.
Then how about moving back here? Both of you.
Then it would be easier for me to look after you.
We have a driver to send you off to school and pick you up.
You father will feel relieved.
I won't move in here.
Hai, how about you....
I have moved back to Guomao Bridge.
The living condition is nice.
You don't need to worry about me.
I see. It's good.
If you wanna stay there,
stay there.
Good.
Alright. Let's eat.
Let's eat.
Come on. Let's eat.
# You carried me on your back, recollecting the past, #
# And stalling for time on your own. #
# I was smiling while listening to you. #
# But a tear-blurred vision faded in. #
# You held my hand that had been wavering, #
# Slowly moving forward... #
# Slowly moving forward with me... #
# Don't say I'd never understand. #
# Don't say I'd never feel the pain. #
# As the wind was blowing over, #
# It left some warmth on my lips. #
# Don't tell me you'll be here with me. #
# I didn't say it because I was stuck in silence. #
# You held my hands too tightly to hear what I was saying. #
# Don't say I'd never understand. #
# Don't say I'd never feel the pain. #
# As the wind was blowing over, #
# It left some warmth on my lips. #
# Don't tell me you'll be here with me. #
# I didn't say it because I was stuck in silence. #
# You held my hands too tightly to hear what I was saying: #
# Please, don't go... #