= Based on the famous cyber fiction "Addicted & Heroin" =
# A bike was cycling along the sidewalk. #
# And then it stopped at the corner store. #
# There was beautiful handwriting on the blackboard. #
# And I saw your smile of ardent love. #
# The sun was shining on the playground. #
# And you were running free... #
# Ice cream and sugar-coated haws, #
# The taste of sweetness. #
# Our promise of love is still echoing in the sea waves, #
# Even though nothing could ever compare to the hug. #
# Have you ever held fast to love in solitary #
# Because you believe it will never fade away... #
= Addicted & Heroin =
= Episode Nine =
Yinzi,
Look, look,
there are some blisters on my mouth, right?
It is quite painful.
Wait a minute. I have an ointment.
No need for the ointment, OK?
A kiss will heal everything.
Where?
Here.
Here. Here.  Yes.
What ointment is it? It works so quickly.
The hemorrhoids ointment.
It's OK. It can be used everywhere.
Last time I had blisters on my mouth,
it cured me of them.
Don't worry.
Really? Is it safe?
If I don't have any blisters,
will it have some side effects on me?
Side effects?
You may have two haemorrhoids.
Oh my God. It smells.
Sleep now.
I need to wash it away.
No need for washing.
I have to...
It is OK. Don't wash it away.
It smells so much that I can't sleep.
It's unbearable.
Hold on and you will be cured tomorrow morning.
I need to wash it away. Let me go.
Let me go.
You really want to wash it away?
Yes!
Have a try.
That's awesome. You should fix this.
Those old phones like this are very sturdy.
Don't you bring those things with you?
You can take anything you need here.
Look, our handwritings are
kind of similar?
Why not telling me that you are practicing calligraphy ?
Due to the essay this time,
the Chinese teacher has ignored me now.
Then you ignore him as well.
I should ignore you.
Then try it.
Give it to me.
I haven't finished it.
That's my paper.
I will continue practicing calligraphy.
What calligraphy!
What do you want to do?
You want to have a fight, huh?
So what? Give it to me.
So what?
No.
What?
How come you should come here?
You tell me why I am here.
Today is weekend.
I am moving now.
And I don't have a mobile phone.
So I can't contact you.
No phone?
What is it?
This one,
it has been broken for long.
Broken?
it is broken.
Who tells you to throw it?
We have thrown so many phones when we had quarrels before.
You should be angry at me
just for this broken phone.
Yinzi has just fixed it for me.
He fixed it. So what?
I threw it and I stamped it.
Kill me if you can.
Just because of the phone...
Gu Hai, you are not a man.
Chase her now.
Gu Hai,
Why should I chase her?
Because she comes all the way to see you.
Because you have been with her for three years.
Because you slept with her.
Yinzi, you know that
I will only listen to you.
You really want me to chase her?
Sure. You have to.
When a girl goes bananas,
It will make her accident prone.
Move now.
Lulu, Lulu,
Gu Hai, this is the first time that
you chase me after we have quarrels.
It's OK. Stop being so capricious afterwards.
I won't be capricious.
I won't be capricious any more.
You are moving the house, right?
Let's go. I will help you.
My package...
That boy has moved all the things away,
Where are you gonna move?
Move into Yinzi's house.
I've lived in his home during this period.
Gu Hai,
What?
Don't you think
you are being too kind to Bai Luoyin?
Every man has his own buddies.
Why you always find fault with him?
I am telling you,
you don't understand him.
If you understand him,
you will definitely like him.
Although his family condition is not good,
his thoughts are very profound.
His taste is also unique.
He doesn't smile much.
But in his heart,
He is mild on the outside but wild on the inside.
If he wants to be kind to you,
he is too shy to say it out.
Always be furtive.
If you unmask it,
he will be angry at you.
His bark is much worse than his bite.
He is very kindhearted.
I've lived in his house for free for so long.
He pretended to kick me out every day,
but if I don't go back home for half a day,
he will be the first one who worries about me.
By the way,
he is very clever.
The lock of our classroom,
after his modification,
the classroom can be locked from the outside
just by pulling the string from the inside.
And my phone.
It has been in the river for a while.
He should fix it.
Don't tell me,
you will move here for real.
Gosh. It is so cold.
He uses the cold water to wash face.
Will they ask you to wash your face with cold water as well?
A Lang.
Gosh. Why there is such a big dog here?
What about going out for diner together?
OK. Let me change my clothes.
OK.
Gu Hai, he is kinder to you than to me.
How can you find it?
He always keeps a poker face in front of me.
But he always wears a smile in front of you.
You said that,
you would feel safe if I was being cold.
This is men.
They have two sides
in front of their girlfriend and buddies.
In front of his girlfriend,
he has to manage his charming image.
So he has to pretend and keep a poker face.
So that he could fascinate you.
But it's different in front of his buddy.
He doesn't need to care about his image.
He can be naughty and capricious as he wants.
So you will feel close.
You see,
he is better at persuasion than you.
You give Bai Luoyin a punch.
Why should I punch him?
No reason.
I just want to see it.
You guys
always have a fight for fun, huh?
Are you so bored?
Gu Hai, I am just kidding.
Why are you so angry at me?
Are you so reluctant?
He is a man.
A punch is nothing to him.
Just a little touch.
Is that unacceptable?
Yes.
Nobody can touch him, including me.
Gu Hai, you are so disgusting.
Then get out of here.
Don't regret.
How come you drive her off again.
Why you say I drive her off?
Don't you see her bloody behaviors.
I can't spoil her.
I don't know how you guys could
be together.
Clam down.
It can't t continue if the mess can't be solved.
What's this?
It's for me?
Of course. It has been given to you.
Otherwise, who else I am gonna give it to.
Yinzi, you are so kind.
Hug my dad if you want to,
He pays for it,
He insists to buy it for you.
I even can't stop him.
Sir, thank you.
You don't need to say thank you to me.
Without Yinzi today,
I don't even know
the difference between a good phone and bad phone.
I think,
as long as it is sturdy and can call others,
then that is a good phone.
Yinzi said that was not enough.
We had to buy a good one for Dahai.
A fully functional one.
Sir, don't listen to him. That's nonsense.
Don't swagger after gaining it, OK?
What about you? What do you use?
I don't need a phone.
I have no one to contact with.
It's a waste to buy a phone.
You can contact with me.
Come on.
You are staying with me all the time.
Phone is useless to me.
According to you,
I also don't have anyone to contact with.
I don't need it as well.
Come on. I still wish that
this phone can distract your attention.
Then you will hate this phone, huh?
But out of my face.
Sir,
What are you doing?
It rained a few days ago.
And the roof leaked.
The corn that was just sun dried,
has been wet again.
I am climbing up to fix the roof.
Sir, come down. Let me do it for you.
You don't know how to fix it.
I can. Give it to me.
Dad,
come down.
Let him climb to the roof.
Otherwise, he lived in our home for free every day.
How could you say this?
Let me do it.
Are you sure?
Yes. Don't worry.
Sir, hold the coat for me please.
- Be careful. - OK.
The cement has been ready. Just smear it on the hole.
OK.
Put the cement on the roof first.
Right. It's there.
Here?
Yes. The side.
OK.
Why don't your father open the restaurant with Mrs Zou?
Why should he open it with Mrs Zou?
That is a best location.
They don't need to pay the rent or tax.
And also have government supports.
That's definitely profitable.
Mrs Zou is too busy there.
If your dad goes to help her,
Then the restaurant is owned by them two.
Isn't that better than his salary.
Your thoughts are good.
My father, he won't be willing to do that.
Why not?
Come here,
What? Mrs Zou is not
a widow?
Mrs Zou has husband.
He is working outside.
You mean,
they are afraid of those gossips.
I feel that Mrs Zou is lying to my father.
I guess she has divorced her husband.
You see,
she has lived here for so many years.
But her husband never came back during the holidays.
Is that normal?
Do you listen to me?
I hear that.
Don't you say that Mrs Zou is not a widow?
Yes. But my father always denies that.
I guess,
Your dad knows it very well.
Your dad is so close to other woman.
Do you feel a bit of uncomfortable in your heart?
No.
I once persuaded my father to marry her.
As long as I have memory,
he has been a single dad.
I can't let him live lonely all his life.
Have you ever considered to
let your dad remarry your mom?
Never.
I prefer Mrs Zou.
I don't want to see my father experience any sufferings.
In fact, my father,
he doesn't want to open the restaurant with Mrs Zou
not completely because he is afraid of the gossip.
You see, the restaurant belongs to Mrs Zou.
my father definitely feels embarrassed to get involved in it.
We are both men.
We can understand that.
If that is another woman,
maybe there is possibilities.
Mrs Zou? Impossible.
Right.
Be carful, man.
Mr. Bai,
Factory director has something to tell you. Go to his office now.
Hurry up.
OK. OK.
Factory director,
- Bai, Bai. Come here. Have a seat. - OK.
- During some tea. - OK. Thank you.
Bai, our factory decides to fire you.
Sit down. Sit down.
Director, you know my situation.
My son just goes to high school.
We need money now.
I also have to look after the elder in my house.
I have to pay for the medicine every month.
If not so,
a veteran worker with over ten-year experience like you,
I am not willing to let you go.
Then why do you fire me?
You are driving our family
to the wall now.
How could you say that?
How could I drive you to the wall?
It seems that they haven't called you yet.
Who?
You indeed don't receive their message.
Then I give them a call now.
Come in please.
You finally come here. Have a seat.
I am about to call you,
No need to call me.
I am coming now.
Who is this?
This is Bai.
This is the one you are looking for,
Mr. Bai, nice to meet you.
Sorry. My hands are not clean.
Bai, this is
the HR manager of Tong Jie Refrigeration Equipment Company.
His name is Miao.
You can call him Manager Miao afterwards.
Then you two have a chat first.
I go out to handle some issues.
Please help yourself.
OK. OK.
Mr. Bai, here is the thing,
Our company wants to hire you
as the engineer in our technology department.
20000 yuan per month after tax.
Every month,
we will sponsor a trip
And five thousand housing benefits.
two thousand meal and transportation allowance respectively.
You would work eight hours a day.
As for the holidays and weekends,
Manager Miao,
does your company print fake money?
Mr. Bai, Mr. Bai, you are so humorous.
It's not because I am humorous.
The conditions your company offers are so unreliable.
Mr. Bai,
Mr. Bai, this is my card.
Please take it.
I guess you have worked here for over ten years.
You probably know
the business of this factory.
Half of the components that our company uses are
produced by your factory.
I also know your factory director.
You can trust me.
The point is I know nothing about the technology.
Don't worry.
We'll arrange someone to guide you.
If so,
you can directly hire an engineer.
That is very convenient.
Mr. Bai,
If you are still hesitant,
then,
you can come with me to visit our company now.
The studio,
we have prepared it for you.
What good events do you encounter today?
Dad, you have been drunken without drinking.
I got promoted.
Promoted?
Are there any different positions in that old factory?
Not in our factory.
It's another company.
They invite me to work there as an engineer.
Dad, are you cheated by them?
How could you say that?
I have signed the contract.
The treatment is very good there.
They are afraid that I don't believe them.
They have given me five thousand as the guarantee deposit.
If you are available tomorrow,
I'll take you to see my new studio.
Gu Hai, come here.
What?
You arrange my father's promotion, right?
Your father's what?
Stop pretending.
# You carried me on your back, recollecting the past, #
# And stalling for time on your own. #
# I was smiling while listening to you. #
# But a tear-blurred vision faded in. #
# You held my hand that had been wavering, #
# Slowly moving forward... #
# Slowly moving forward with me... #
# Don't say I'd never understand. #
# Don't say I'd never feel the pain. #
# As the wind was blowing over, #
# It left some warmth on my lips. #
# Don't tell me you'll be here with me. #
# I didn't say it because I was stuck in silence. #
# You held my hands too tightly to hear what I was saying. #
# Don't say I'd never understand. #
# Don't say I'd never feel the pain. #
# As the wind was blowing over, #
# It left some warmth on my lips. #
# Don't tell me you'll be here with me. #
# I didn't say it because I was stuck in silence. #
# You held my hands too tightly to hear what I was saying: #
# Please, don't go... #