= Based on the famous cyber fiction "Addicted & Heroin" =
# A bike was cycling along the sidewalk. #
# And then it stopped at the corner store. #
# There was beautiful handwriting on the blackboard. #
# And I saw your smile of ardent love. #
# The sun was shining on the playground. #
# And you were running free... #
# Ice cream and sugar-coated haws, #
# The taste of sweetness. #
# Our promise of love is still echoing in the sea waves. #
# Even though nothing could ever compare to the hug. #
# Have you ever held fast to love in solitary #
# Because you believe it will never fade away... #
= Addicted & Heroin =
= Episode 14 =
Take care.
Bye.
Sir.
Dahai.
I'll take Yinzi to my place.
It's getting late, just stay here.
I've already arranged the room for you.
How could I ruin your night?
This kid!
How could you joke with me?
Let's go, Yinzi.
- Could he do this? - It's ok.
I'll carry him, bye.
Here we go.
Let dad help you.
Well, be careful.
See you, Sir.
- Well, I'll walk you to the door. - Okay.
Be careful on the way home.
Okay.
Bye.
Take a cab!
- Sure. - Okay.
I...
I wanna
go to the rooftop.
Go to rooftop?
Okay.
# It really wants to be itself #
# It also wants to be happier #
# The cat by the window is asking me #
# Where are you #
# the one who had fed it? #
# Get extra clothes when it's cold #
# I... #
Don't cry, Yinzi.
Your father is still you father
regardless of how many times he's gotten married,
he loves you the most.
There will be no one
cooking such horrible meals for me.
Do you still want to eat the food he cooked?
There will be no one
throwing away my underwear into the gutter.
Yinzi.
Then I'll cook for you,
and I'm sure what I cook would be worse than him.
I'll wash your clothes, too.
Let's buy a whole box of underwear
and throw one of them each time we do the laundry.
Yinzi,
I promise, besides your dad,
no one will ever love you more than I do.
I have to go out for a while.
What are you doing?
I'm picking up my brother, he has just come back from abroad.
Your brother? Your sibling?
Not sibling, he's my cousin.
He's been living abroad most of the time,
actually we don't have many chances to meet.
He's just back for business
and take a time to meet me.
He'll just stay for a few days.
Then you better go now.
See you.
Bro.
Bro, this is Bai Luoyin.
This is my brother, Gu Yang.
Miss, would you mind bring the dishes?
Have some.
What's up? Not to your taste?
No.
Hai Luoyin.
Yes, blending our name together you'll get an addictive drug.
Come on.
Brother,
I wanna propose a toast.
= Photo World =
Do you want something to drink?
The TV is too small.
Replace it with a bigger one tomorrow.
The color of the carpet doesn't match the coffee table.
The wallpaper gives a sense of depression.
The fringe of the curtain is too conspicuous.
The decorative pattern of ceiling lamp
looks too simple and ancient.
In the end, you just put such an enjoyable dining table.
What kind of designer
could possibly decorate
the room inappropriate like that?
Yinzi, hand me a night gown.
Come out with your bath towel on.
Bro? How... Why are you here!
I'm coming here to see you.
You don't hide even from him,
why are you hiding from me?
How can the decent gentleman like you
possibly stand for my vulgar behavior?
Watch yourself next time.
Why didn't you tell me that my bro is here?
You are such a bad boy.
I'll give you a lesson after his leaving.
He won't left so soon.
How do you know?
Just wait and see.
Bro,
why are you not leaving yet?
Why do you want me to leave?
Am I bothering you two?
You can do whatever you want.
It's time for us to go to bed.
Do you guys go to bed so early?
Don't your young people
often stay up late?
It is only over 8 pm now,
and the old man and the old lady could be still energetic now.
Don't say "your young people".
You're two years older than me.
Now that you're going to have a rest,
I won't bother you anymore.
Putting on more blankets. Don't freeze yourself.
Sure.
Bro, take care.
You little brat, get out now!
We're not done yet!
Window is still open, you can get in if you can.
Fine! Just wait for me.
Did he really go downstairs?
Did you really go out?
Would he ambush at the door?
Come here, you want to run away again?
Damn!
Let me tell you, you can't cry out any grandpa for help now.
Gu Hai, let me down.
I told you that no one can help you today.
Put me down, Gu Hai.
Call me husband.
Call me husband and I'll let you down.
Let me down!
Call husband or not?
You put me down.
If I had known this, I wouldn't come with you.
Do you want me to climb the stair?
Gu Hai.
Do you find it exciting?
Call husband or not?
No, no way.
Would you tell me
how did you get the scar on your waist?
The one on the waist?
I was cut down by my brother when I was a kid.
Gu Yang?
Right.
Why did he cut you?
When we were kids, we compete for a slice of watermelon,
he couldn't win me,
and then he gave me a cut with the fruit knife.
So do you think
it is his obligation to give you money
and treat you well?
I didn't force him, he did of his own free will.
But I have to say fair words
your brother is more handsome than you.
"Man should lose with grace"
When we were little,
we went out to fly a kite together.
But the kite string was broken,
and we chased for the fallen kite.
I was crying while chasing
and my bro was laughing while chasing.
What do you mean by that?
Can't you see it from this little thing?
My nature is good.
My brother is evil.
But I'm just curious
that kite had fallen,
you could just chase and take it back,
why did you cry?
Aren't you stupid?
Forget it! Sleep.
Bro,
when will you leave?
I'm not sure yet.
Before returning home,
I had planned to deal with this matter in six or seven days.
But the speed of our people made me so...
I'm afraid it'll take another week.
You should leave
as soon as you finish your business.
What do you want me leave?
I remember you were the one
who called me to come back the last few times.
But this time, why do I feel like
you are being dislike towards me?
Actually I...
I think you're tired of jet lag all day.
Hai,
this time I come back here,
I feel that you have changed a lot
and you've even known how to care for other.
Please don't talk with sarcastic tone, okay?
What about your little brother?
Why are you asking about him?
Just curious.
What would you like to have?
How about two packs of rice crust?
What kind of flavor would you like?
Chicken flavor.
Okay.
Hello, could you get me
two packs of "pot meat flavored chicken cock"?
Come on, get me two packs of "pot meat flavored cock".
We really don't have such thing here.
Keep the change.
Is that really so funny?
Gu Hai, that was a retribution
for you not taking things seriously all the time.
Now you're slipping of your tongue!
I'm going to eat, I just want to eat it, what, is there a problem?
Tonight, I'll eat yours.
It's not over, is it? You're still laughing!
"Pot meat flavored cock" !
Did you forget to lock the door?
You two got back home!
Why are you here?
Your father asked me to come and have a look.
He's worried about you guys living here.
Where did you get the key?
Your father gave it to me.
He had made two sets of keys for this apartment.
One for you
and other was kept by him,
just in case
when you need somethings,
we could come and see you guys.
Even if you want to come here,
you should let us know first.
I don't have your phone number,
so I couldn't contact you.
I didn't move anything in this house,
I just did some cleaning and organizing.
Luoyin, come here.
Luoyin, sit on the couch.
Luoyin,
I heard your dad and that woman got married.
So what?
What do you think?
The woman had a child of her own.
Do you think she would get a place for you in her heart?
Look, you father just got married,
they had kicked you out.
I was willing to come here.
Would you stop slandering my dad
every time you see me?
All right, all right.
Could you improve yourself
by putting him down?
I just feel sorry for you.
You're so young
and you need to be loved and cared,
they can't just let you be free.
I had my own difficulties in the past
and couldn't take good care of you.
Now I have the opportunity and the ability,
so you got to come back to me.
Let me make up for it, okay?
It's too late.
Yinzi,
do you want to take a bath together?
Here we are.
Look at you boys,
how could you be so close?
I'm so happy to see this
and I feel so relieved now.
What take you two so long?
Shouldn't we take more hot baths during winter?
That's true.
Come on, come on.
You two just sit down.
I just peeled an apple
and how about having some fruit?
Forget it. I'm going back to my bedroom to do my homework.
You just sit down.
Come on.
It's not necessary to do your homework.
it is just for dealing with the exam-oriented education.
Now, you should let your brain
get relax and have a good rest.
And you really don't need to
do those totally-skill-lacking homework.
Just think about it, even if they get into a famous university
and learn for four years,
but those come from the bottom are still at the bottom.
Son, your hair is too wet.
I'll blow it dry for you.
No, I can dry it myself.
How can we do that?
If you don't get it dry, you will get headache in the morning.
I have been like this for more than a decade
and I never got a headache.
Yeah, it's been ten years.
You are such a big boy.
You've got many bad habits that have formed.
It's hard to change now even if you want to.
All right, I'll do it for him.
I've never blown dry. I'm not used to it.
Come on, just get you hair dry
and then and we can go to bed.
Your dad suggested you two to study abroad for two years.
Foreign education is not at the same level as here.
I've been enjoying my life now.
For me, going to a regular high school
is an essential part of life experience.
It's the same to go to the high school abroad.
You could make new friends
and could also get many interesting and wonderful life experiences.
Moreover, it will be more valuable and meaningful than here.
All right, my hair's dry.
Don't waste your time on me anymore.
I don't have the good habit of letting parents make decide for me.
Luoyin.
Our brains
need full relaxation and rest.
So, could you please just leave?
Well, then you have a good rest.
I'm leaving.
It's really annoying.
How could she have the key to here?
If she come here everyday, how can we live our lives?
We must change the lock quickly.
# You carried me on your back, recollecting the past, #
# And stalling for time on your own. #
# I was smiling while listening to you. #
# But a tear-blurred vision faded in. #
# You held my hand that had been wavering, #
# Slowly moving forward... #
# Slowly moving forward with me... #
# Don't say I'd never understand. #
# Don't say I'd never feel the pain. #
# As the wind was blowing over, #
# It left some warmth on my lips. #
# Don't tell me you'll be here with me. #
# I didn't say it because I was stuck in silence. #
# You held my hands too tightly to hear what I was saying. #
# Don't say I'd never understand. #
# Don't say I'd never feel the pain. #
# As the wind was blowing over, #
# It left some warmth on my lips. #
# Don't tell me you'll be here with me. #
# I didn't say it because I was stuck in silence. #
# You held my hands too tightly to hear what I was saying: #
# Please, don't go... #