♪ Lost memory of the past ♪
♪ Can’t change how we loved each other ♪
♪ My heart only beats for you ♪
♪ I’ll protect you from all the storms ♪
♪ Even if there’s no miracle ♪
♪ I’ll walk through fire to hug you ♪
♪ Cuz we’re meant to be ♪
♪ Till love finds us again ♪
= Forget You Remember Love =
= Episode 23 =
Congratulations on Qianyu’s first day to work!
My daughter looks
like an office lady in this suit.
Ye Qianyu,
this outfit covers your violent nature
successfully.
As long as you don’t speak,
you’re safe.
Don’t say that!
Qianyu,
we’re so proud of you
that you can
work in Senwell.
Indeed.
Qianyu, I made these dumplings for you.
After eating them,
you’ll have
no trouble at all in the future.
Qianyu, Qianyu, I made some, too.
These dumplings are delicious, Master.
Qianyu,
once you’re in Senwell,
remember to study hard.
The future of our inn depends on you,
Qianyu.
Taichu has arrived.
See you.
Take care. Be careful.
Have a nice day.
Slowly, slowly.
She looks sharp.
She looks good in the suit.
Taichu, do I look OK?
Confidence is the best armor.
Let’s go.
Taichu is driving her to work?
He’d never let her go there alone.
You’re right.
Bye, guys.
Uh...
Qianyu,
when you’re at work,
remember to eat properly.
I will.
Taichu.
Please take good care of her.
She’s never worked
so far away from home.
I will, Mama Jinzhi.
Alright, Chen.
Don’t be so dramatic.
Senwell
is only an hour’s drive.
It’s not like I’ll be gone forever.
OK.
We gotta go.
Qianyu, Qianyu. Take this.
Don’t forget the dumplings.
Thank you, Chef.
Bye.
Mr. Shan, we’ve received GQ’s funds,
but they still have doubts about the project.
Or, they wouldn’t have sent Taichu to oversee it.
They trust him.
What if he doesn’t disagree with us?
I’ll take care of that.
OK.
Welcome back, Mr. Zhang.
Like I said,
I’d never do anything harmful
to Senwell.
Mr. Qiu and Mr. Lin’s own doing
has nothing to do with me.
Hope we can make a good team.
Mr. Shan.
Welcome, Taichu.
This meeting is for Senwell and GQ
to discuss development details together.
What’s the member of Guanmei Inn
doing here?
Let me introduce to you,
my assistant, Ye Qianyu.
Hello, I’m Ye Qianyu.
I’m honored to be here.
Senwell has minimum requirements
for assistants.
Dawei.
I think you know the details.
Yes, boss.
First,
a master’s degree or above.
Overseas study experience is preferred.
Second,
at least three years of work experience,
preferably in listed companies.
Third,
CET 6 or above.
Sorry,
Ye Qianyu is my special assistant.
My standards are different
from Senwell’s.
First,
I don’t think diploma is the only standard
Check this one.
to assess a candidate
but his or her ability to learn.
Besides, isn’t this project
about the development of Guanmei Fishing Village?
It’s only natural
to have its representative to sit in.
More importantly,
I believe Miss Ye Qianyu
is more than capable for this job.
Thanks.
Let’s begin.
Guanmei Fishing Village is rich in natural
and ecological resources.
We’ll build a high-end resort
from east to west on the island.
There will be a theme park, a nature park,
a water world and a duty-free shopping mall.
Guanmei Fishing Village
will become a one-stop resort for tourists.
The village isn’t too big
but it’s conveniently located.
It’s only an hour’s drive
from the city center,
so it can attract both the locals
and those outside the city.
Hence,
we need to calculate the maximum capacity.
According to the estimation,
we expect
about 30,000 visitors per day.
Before the construction,
I suggest we design
the MI,
BI
and VI first for the village.
A slogan is also needed.
It’s essential
for the image-building.
Ye Qianyu,
you’re a local.
Do you have any suggestions?
Me?
Well... Uh...
What does VI mean?
VI means visual identification.
It’s an image or symbol
that makes one thing different from the others.
For example, when you see a yellow “M”,
you instantly know it’s McDonald’s.
I see.
We can use Chinese white dolphins
for this...
This visit...
Visual identification.
A cute white dolphin
must be appealing.
What about the slogan?
What do you mean?
Slogan can be a word or a phrase,
similar to an ad.
Just like McDonald’s “i’m lovin’ it”.
I understand.
I’ll tell tourists
come to Guanmei to see white dolphins.
If creating a slogan is that simple,
we can fire
all our copywriters.
Simplicity isn’t necessarily bad.
McDonald’s “i’m lovin’ it”,
Haagen-Dazs’s
“Lover her, treat her Haagen-Dazs”,
and Nike’s “Just do it” are all simple.
The key is to express the company’s vision
and the image of the village.
Mr. Zhang,
anything else you’d like to ask
about the development details?
I only care about the BEP.
I’ve done the calculation.
It’s 27.53%,
much lower than the 70% risk value,
which means development of Guanmei
is a typical low-risk project.
OK.
Let’s have a ten-minute recess.
I’ll buy coffee for you.
I’ll go.
I’m new here.
Drinks should be on me.
Uh... What would you like?
I’m not picky.
I’ll go with you.
No need. I can do it myself.
Thanks.
You can’t carry them all on your own.
Besides,
I’m familiar with everyone’s taste.
Thank you.
= The Minutes Presided by Shan Junhao =
Mr. Zhao.
May I ask you a question?
What does SWT mean?
You mean SWOT?
SWOT, S-W-O-T,
stands for Strengths, Weaknesses,
Opportunities, Threats.
It’s an abbreviation.
In another word, advantages and disadvantages,
chances and risks.
Analyzing every project
from those four aspects
can produce a relatively comprehensive,
systemic and accurate result.
What does “BEP” said by Mr. Zhang mean?
It stands for Break-Even Point,
where one earns matches what one spends.
Why did you
use so many fancy words during the meeting?
I was confused.
Senwell is a listed company
and most of our business is international.
The majority of the staff studied overseas,
so we use those jargon a lot.
I’ll make a list of the common jargon
and send it to you.
You can learn them yourself.
Thank you so much.
Thanks.
Here’s your coffee.
Ye Qianyu,
is this your minutes?
Yes.
See how other people did it.
That’s called professional.
Qianyu is new here
and doesn’t know much.
I’ll teach her bit by bit.
Consultant,
you’re surprisingly patient
with your assistant.
Of course.
Is that a problem?
Have some coffee.
Yes.
Take a coffee break.
Thanks.
You’re welcome.
I’m sorry, my bad.
I didn’t put it there on purpose.
Ye Qianyu,
when you’ll stop causing trouble?
I didn’t mean to do it.
Files I’m going to show
to our partner this afternoon
are on the laptop.
Do you have a backup?
No.
I just finished. Didn’t get to make a copy.
How come you’re a disaster
everywhere?
Junhao,
don’t blame her.
It’s my fault.
I’m familiar with the content.
I can rewrite it quickly.
Director Fan.
Let’s bring the computer to IT department
and see if it can be repaired.
OK. Let’s go.
Sure.
Ye Qianyu,
I believe
you’ll bring Senwell
endless surprises.
Good luck!
She’s such a troublemaker.
Yes.
So clumsy.
Indeed.
She can’t handle such a small matter.
It’s OK.
Don’t worry too much.
Qianyu.
I apologize
that I wasn’t considerate enough.
Taichu.
You’ve done too much for me.
I’m not good enough.
Qianyu.
Don’t be discouraged.
I’m always with you
in Senwell.
Director Fan.
Consultant.
Director Fan. Director Xu.
Director Fan. How’s your laptop?
Don’t worry. It’s under repair,
but I can’t use it for the meeting this afternoon.
I’m really sorry.
It’s OK. I can redo it.
Consultant, I apologize
that your assistant was blamed
because of me.
I should be the one to apologize.
I don’t know much about Ye Qianyu,
but I think
she’s a smart girl.
I believe after professional training,
she’ll become an excellent assistant.
So I suggest
that Ye Qianyu
be trained in our Administration Department
for a while.
I can assign the best manager
to train her.
Once she completes the training
and comes back to work for you,
she’ll be of more help.
That’s unnecessary.
I can train my assistant well.
I will go.
Director Fan.
I want to go to the Administration Department.
Qianyu...
Taichu,
right now,
I’m unqualified for the job.
So I should improve myself
to become a better person.
Then I’ll be able to assist you
and work in Senwell.
If you insist,
I’ll support you.
Thanks.
Director Fan.
Can you take me to the Administration Department?
Consultant,
we’re leaving then.
Let’s go.
How could you be late
for the airport pickup?
You were supposed to arrive 40 minutes early,
and what you did?
You were two minutes late.
Don’t you know
Mr. Chen is an important ally?
If we offended him,
it would seriously affect our company’s business.
I’m sorry, Ada.
The traffic was bad and it was raining,
so I arrived two minutes late.
I’m really sorry.
If saying sorry can solve everything,
why bother making rules?
No monthly bonus for you.
Reflect on yourself.
Yes, Ada.
Director Fan. What brings you here?
This is Ye Qianyu,
Consultant Taichu’s assistant.
She’s new here
and isn’t familiar with our business.
I’d like you to coach her for a while.
Consultant Taichu’s assistant?
Sure. Entrust her to me.
I’ll teach her everything.
Qianyu.
Ada is a senior member.
You can ask her if you have any questions.
Study hard.
Thanks, Director Fan.
See you.
Sure, see you.
Hello, Ahda. My name is Ye Qianyu.
It’s Ada.
Sure, Ahda.
Yunyi.
Ziqian.
Let’s go have lunch together.
Sure. I’ll call Junhao.
No need.
He went to Senwell Hotel,
for a unannounced inspect.
The revenue continues to decline.
I’m sure it bothers him.
Why did you send Ye Qianyu
to the Administration Department?
To give her a chance to learn.
What’s wrong?
I know
you were afraid
if she continued to participate in the project,
she’d be too close to Junhao.
You have copies
of the files ruined this morning, right?
I know your work habits.
Ziqian.
You’ve become blunter.
I’m concerned about you.
Come on. Let’s go have lunch.
= Resume =
= Education Guanmei Community College =
You graduated from Guanmei Community College?
Yes.
Is there such a college?
Of course.
It’s famous in our village.
You used to work
as a tour guide and you delivered goods,
packages and food?
Yes.
Can you speak foreign languages?
Does “Hola” count?
How did you get to know Mr.Taichu?
He went to our village to travel,
and I was his tour guide.
That’s how we met.
Aren’t you lucky?
I’m strict
with all my staff members.
Follow me.
Come.
You first.
You blocked me.
= Janitor’s Room =
Do you know what this department does?
Given your resume,
I can only allocate
basic work to you.
That is to start working as a cleaner.
Cleaner?
What’s wrong?
Unsatisfied?
I didn’t mean that.
Cleaning seems menial,
but it’s crucial to maintain the image of Senwell
as a 5A office building.
Don’t undervalue it
or slack off on the job.
A good learner
can gain experience
from seemingly irrelevant trifles.
Doing every easy work well
isn’t easy at all.
I understand, Ada.
I’ll work hard.
Alright. Go get changed.
Thank you, Ada.
Cleaner?
Ye Qianyu,
you can do it!
I’m sorry. So sorry.
I’m sorry.
Cleaner 119.
Yes, Ada.
Floor 21 was waterless for half an hour.
Now, the water supply has been restored.
Go clean all the bathrooms there.
Yes. Got it.
Hello, Shengzhe?
Chen wants to know if you had eaten.
Yes.
She asked what you ate.
I ate... A big burger.
Wow, sis,
you had a burger!
Was it yellow,
big and delicious?
Yeah.
Yellow, big and delicious.
Can you bring one back for me tonight?
Qianyu.
Burgers are junk food.
They’re unhealthy
and can make you fat.
Don’t eat too many.
Alright. I know.
What’s worse,
if you gain too much weight,
Taichu might lose interest in you.
He’s a rare catch.
You cannot lose him, got it?
Mom, I have a job now.
Maybe I’ll soon become rich.
Then I don’t need to marry a rich man.
What?
You really think you can make yourself rich?
There’s a wealthy man willing to marry you.
How could you let him go?
Don’t feel so good about yourself.
Hello? Chen, can you hear me?
I’m losing you.
Hello? Hello?
This is Senwell.
How come the signal is so bad?
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Gosh!
That girl really pissed me off!
= General Manager’s Office =
Only GM’s office
is left to be cleaned.
After that, I can get off work.
Shan Junhao
should’ve left at this hour.
Come in.
Mr. Shan.
I’m here to clean your office.
He’s frowning again
like an old man.
Mr. Shan,
will it disturb you
if I turn on the vacuum cleaner?
Hmm.
What does that mean?
So yes or no?
I'll just forget this.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
I accidentally turned on the shower.
Ye Qianyu?
What are you doing here
in this uniform?
I’m an intern in the Administration Department.
Taichu arranged it?
No.
I want to improve myself
to not hold Taichu back.
Put this on.
Thank you, Mr. Shan.
Clean it up and leave.
Don’t disturb me.
As Taichu’s assistant,
do you always call him by the name?
Oh.
No,
it’s Mr. Tai.
I said it wrong.
Shan Junhao,
can you be less serious?
Don’t always frown.
When you do that, people get scared
and run away from you.
Cheer up, OK?
Come in.
Junhao.
Yunyi.
Let’s go home.
Mom asked Mrs. Lin to cook the meal.
She’s waiting for us.
You can go home first.
I still have work to do.
I’ll leave after it’s done.
I’ll wait for you.
Yunyi.
Don’t wait for me.
It’s going to take a while.
It’s OK. I want to keep you company.
Forget it.
Let’s go back.
This is the first time
you’ve put family before work.
Really?
Let’s go.
Oh, my goodness!
This kind of cold tone
really matches him.
You good-for-nothing!
Pack up and leave.
No, no, no.
I can’t believe Senwell hired
such an irresponsible person.
You’re fired.
Sounds exactly like him.
Qianyu.
Taichu.
Why are you here?
To pick you up.
Pick me up?
Are you hungry?
Yeah!
I haven’t had anything for a day.
Really?
Not exactly.
Come on. I’ll treat you to a big meal.
What’s wrong with your foot?
Nothing.
Are you OK?
I’m fine.
What are we going to eat?
You’ll find out later.
This crab stick is so good.
Taste it.
Have a try.
Eat it.
Go ahead or it’ll get cold.
Come on.
So? Isn’t it delicious?
So spicy.
You can’t eat spicy food?
We can have a two-flavor hotpot.
No need.
I’m fine.
Are you sure?
I’ll help myself then.
Eat as much as you can.
Qianyu.
Whose shirt is it in your bag?
Shan Junhao’s.
I accidentally wet my blouse
in his office this afternoon,
so he lent it to me.
I’ll dry-clean it before giving it back.
Why were you in his office in the first place?
I was there to...
Ada told me
to do a few things there.
Forget it. Not important.
How was your first day at work?
Great.
Had a busy day.
Good.
Congratulations!
To your new start.
Thanks.
Now that you have a job,
shouldn’t you consider your personal life?
What do you mean?
The wish I made to the meteor shower.
Taichu,
I...
I’m not...
No worries. I can wait.
Because of you,
my wait is fun and joyous.
Let’s eat.
Mr. Shan glanced at me.
He’s so cool.
Super hot!
He only seems that way.
Don’t you know how bad his temper is?
The new guy Taichu is my favorite.
He’s handsome and kind.
He isn’t scary at all.
I agree. I like him, too.
You know what, he’s also Dadao.
I’ve been following him on Weibo for years.
I never thought I’d meet him in person.
Gosh!
Ye Qianyu!
Mr. Shan is hotter.
Taichu sent another post on Weibo.
Ye Qianyu!
Can’t you mop the floor well?
What’s wrong?
I slipped and almost fell in the bathroom.
If someone else fell and got injured,
could you take the responsibility?
Sorry, I didn’t do it well.
It’s my fault.
Ye Qianyu,
Can’t you even do a simple job like that?
I’m sorry.
I’ll mop it again.
This is
a 5A office building.
Like the five-star hotel,
- everything must be spotless.
- Look, she’s in trouble.
Yes, Ada.
By the way,
the conference room
is empty now.
Someone else will use it later.
Go clean the bathroom first.
Yes.
Collect data from all these companies...
I’m sorry. I’m so sorry.
It’s OK.
I’m sorry, my bad.
I’m really sorry.
No worries.
Ye Qianyu?
Mr. Zhao.
How come you’re doing the cleaning?
Right now,
I can only do the easiest work well.
But I’ll work hard.
You can do it, Qianyu.
Hey,
I’ve put together a list
of all common jargon.
Do you still need it?
Of course. Thanks.
OK. I’ll send it to you later.
Thank you, Mr. Zhao.
No big deal.
Wait!
There’s one more.
Thanks.
You’re welcome.
Junhao, look,
this Tuscan castle is amazing.
If we have the wedding there,
it’ll be so romantic.
Helena Bay is good, too.
What do you think?
Or, maybe...
Let’s hold the wedding
in Senwell.
It’s more convenient for the guests, too.
You have a point.
We’re too busy lately
to spend too much time on this.
Mr. Shan.
Here’s the monthly operation analysis
of all the branches and their plan reports.
Have a look.
Wedding in a castle.
Good idea.
Junhao said
to have the wedding in Senwell
is better.
Look at him.
He’s even using his own wedding
for brand promotion.
Given Senwell’s current performance,
no wonder Marv beat us to it.
If we execute quietly
according to the plan in the report,
we’ll crush Marv
before they notice it.
This is classified information.
Make sure it’s kept safe.
I’ll supervise all departments
to execute it.
If there’s nothing else,
I’ll go back to work.
I’m leaving, too.
He must’ve left at this hour.
I... I’m sorry, Mr. Shan.
I didn’t know you’d still be here.
I’ll come back later.
Wait.
You have 15 minutes only.
Director Fan.
Ye Qianyu?
What are you doing here?
I’m here to do the cleaning.
Cleaning?
Ada assigned it to you?
Yes.
If Taichu knows
you’re working as a cleaner,
he’ll be annoyed.
I’ll rearrange your job.
It’s OK.
I’m getting the hang of it
and I’ve learned a lot.
I’ve never intended to tell Taichu.
Where’s Mr. Shan?
I don’t know.
He only gave me 15 minutes to clean the room.
Why is his shirt here?
I brought it back to him.
Brought it back?
Well,
when I cleaned his office yesterday,
my blouse got wet by accident,
so he lent it to me.
It’s OK.
Junhao is always generous to his staff.
You don’t need to give it back
because he never wears clothes
that have been worn by others.
♪ Distance between us ♪
♪ Seems short yet long ♪
♪ Heartfelt words are exchanged in diaries ♪
♪ There are no secrets between us ♪
♪ Didn’t get to say I love you so much ♪
♪ You broke into my lonely heart ♪
♪ And lit the fire called love ♪
♪ You drove out all my loneliness ♪
♪ So that I can slowly adjust myself ♪
♪ You painted my life ♪
♪ With flowers ♪
♪ You raised me up ♪
♪ From that moment on ♪
♪ You’ve been singing for me ♪