♪ Lost memory of the past ♪
♪ Can’t change how we loved each other ♪
♪ My heart only beats for you ♪
♪ I’ll protect you from all the storms ♪
♪ Even if there’s no miracle ♪
♪ I’ll walk through fire to hug you ♪
♪ Cuz we’re meant to be ♪
♪ Till love finds us again ♪
= Forget You Remember Love =
= Episode 26 =
Look, I’ve revised these documents.
Hmm. OK. Give them to me.
Send to you later.
Is Mr. Shan back?
Mr. Taichu, Mr. Shan hasn’t come back yet.
Please review this document again.
- OK. - I’ll go fix the seal.
OK.
Mr. Shan,
lots of journalists are out there.
Let’s go to the underground garage.
There Shun Junhao is!
- Look. - There he is. He’s out.
Mr. Shan! Mr. Shan!
Mr. Shan!
You have to answer us.
What are you going to do next?
Can you explain the fight?
Please answer me.
Mr. Shan!
Mr. Shan! Mr. Shan!
Don’t go, Mr. Shan!
- Mr. Shan!
- Your comment, please, Mr. Shan!
Qianyu.
- Taichu. - He’s so handsome!
Have you handed the video to Shan Junhao?
He hasn’t shown up.
I can only give it to him tomorrow.
All right.
Come on. Let me drive you home.
There is no other way.
We have to apologize in public
to recover Senwell’s loss.
Yes, Junhao.
I know you never lowered your head to anyone.
But for the company,
you have to.
Mom,
don’t you say no work at home?
But this is different.
Do you know how bad it is?
You have to consider the greater good.
My department has initiated crisis management.
But it’s important that you have to show up.
Are you done with it?
I said I wouldn’t apologize.
Indeed, Junhao doesn’t need to apologize.
I believe those who have sharp eyes
must know it has to be something else.
To have made the aloof Shan Junhao lose control,
it mustn’t be something simple.
No one who has sense
would be fooled by the celebrity gossips.
But most people
believe what they saw and the result.
If Senwell’s image is damaged,
corporate management will be hard to maintain.
A public apology
is the best solution to reduce negative impact.
No gesture is kind of a gesture, too.
It stands for Senwell’s
and Shan Junhao’s
resolution to give no tolerance
to malicious slanders.
Leave the incident and the reason
for the PR Department to explain.
But this event…
Enough.
Let’s listen to Junhao.
He’ll make his decision.
You’re back!
- You’re back. - I’m back.
Chen, you picked up money?
What’s with the feast?
Thank you for the surprise lunch.
She wanted to be nicer to you.
Sit down and have dinner.
Mama Jinzhi,
your cooking is as good as usual.
Have more if you like it.
Do you know?
Shan Junhao hit the headline
due to the fight.
Lots of people cursed him.
An arrogant man like him
should feel people’s wrath.
Xie Quan stirred up the trouble.
Were it me,
I would give him hell of a lesson.
You…
Remember what he did to you?
Why speaking for him?
Ye Qianyu,
you can’t put a foot on two boats.
Two boats?
There’s only half a boat now.
What’s wrong with her?
Chief Xie, I’m sorry for you.
Mr. Qin,
look at my wound.
It’s too big a price to pay.
I won’t let you suffer for nothing.
Goddamned Shan Junhao!
I won’t let him get away from this.
Neither will I.
To the exposure of Shan Junhao’s brutality,
a toast.
OK.
Mr. Shan, come in please.
There’s stain on the glass.
Wipe it away.
OK, I’ll take care of it now.
This fragrance bottle doesn’t go
with the room.
Replace it.
OK, right away.
Mr. Shan,
our stock price hits the daily limit.
Development, Operation, and Publicity
are totally out of control.
Tell the directors to deal with it.
Don’t dump the problems to me.
Chen, don’t worry.
The food is good here.
I’ll take care of myself.
The workload is heavy.
But,
I’m a highly regarded
manager in Senwell.
With great power comes great responsibility.
I’ll take care of myself.
Silly girl.
When could you learn to be honest?
Are you a manager in Senwell?
Mr. Shan.
Cheating is your professional skill.
What’s wrong with it?
I never hurt anyone.
Unlike you,
you beat another up.
It isn’t new that dog bites people.
But the contrary is.
No wonder you hit the headline.
You can’t go.
Move!
Hold on.
I have an important thing to show you.
Mr. Shan!
Look,
now we have this video,
we can unveil Xie Quan
so everyone can see his evilness.
We?
I’ve shown you such an important video.
You should smile.
At least you look easy-going when you smile.
Senwell pays great attention to clients’ privacy.
Do not film in dark again.
You’re welcome.
I think you should apologize,
but in an unusual way.
Unusual like how?
Mr. Li,
what are you doing?
Um… Nothing.
Look,
the door is so dirty.
- What’s wrong with the cleaning? - Oh!
I remember no one
checks in this room.
I have the card key.
Let’s open it and check out.
Joey.
You, um… Go back to work.
Morning, Mr. Shan.
Mr. Shan, you can make it.
Ye Qianyu,
what were you doing in there with Mr. Shan?
Dawei,
tell the Publicity Department
to organize a press conference immediately.
OK.
Junhao, you sure you want to apologize in public?
What makes you change your mind?
The press conference isn’t for an apology.
Then what is it for?
Go get ready.
I have work to do.
= Press Conference =
If he didn’t come,
Senwell would be doomed.
If he apologizes,
it will hit the headline.
- It sure will. - I’m certain.
It’s gonna be a great show.
What is Junhao going to say?
You’ll know in a while.
- Go over the questions. - Hmm, OK.
Thank you for coming to this conference
on short notice.
My conflict with Mr. Xie Quan three days ago
has stirred up a confusion
to both the public and Senwell Group.
Therefore,
I’d like to give my sincere apology to you all.
But to Xie Quan,
I think the apology is unnecessary.
Why is the apology unnecessary?
Didn’t he just apologize?
Why telling us it’s unnecessary?
Let’s see what he’s going to say.
Shan Junhao,
what do you mean?
You injured me so bad.
Now you want to disclaim responsibility?
As a renowned media professional,
you blackmailed your interviewee
and harassed our female employee.
You deserve it.
So it’s a dirty deal.
It is a filthy deal.
= Xie Quan, =
= we paid 270,000 RMB
for the wine you ordered yesterday. =
= Now, you ask for 500,000? =
= You’re utterly unethical! =
How could he do that?
I believe
you’ve found out the details about the incident.
Either I’m right or wrong,
it’s your call.
Senwell always values honesty
and pursues perfection.
To serve you with all our hearts
is our mission.
However,
we won’t allow anyone
to slander and defame us maliciously.
You…
You made up the story!
As to why Xie Quan did that,
I believe he owes you an explanation.
Is what he said true?
Please explain it.
Don’t you think
it’s against your professional ethics?
Can you explain to us?
What are you going to say to your fans?
Did something similar happen in the past?
- Your explanation, please. - Explain to us.
Chief Xie, please give us an explanation.
Do you feel no guilt
about the beating incident?
Do you have any comment about the video?
What are you going to say to Senwell Group?
Please explain.
Chief Xie, do you want to make an explanation
about this incident?
Chief Xie.
You owe us an explanation.
What are you going to say to Senwell Group?
How long have you been doing this?
♪ I found a coin by the road ♪
♪ And gave it to the police ♪
♪ The police took the coin and nodded to me ♪
Ye Qianyu!
Ye Qianyu,
as an employee of Senwell Hotel,
you need to pay attention
to your image like I do all the time.
You know?
Yes, manager.
I’ll pay attention to it.
Mr. Li.
Ye Qianyu,
Mr. Shan asks you to go
to the headquarters after work.
Ye Qianyu.
What did you do wrong this time?
Nothing.
Ye Qianyu didn’t do anything wrong.
On the contrary, she made a great contribution.
The video on the press conference
is filmed by her.
Wait for you at the gate after work.
Qianyu.
Taichu.
Where are you going?
Mr. Shan asks Ye Qianyu to go to the headquarters.
I think he wants to express his gratitude.
Go ahead.
I’m gonna go now.
Bye-bye.
Come in.
Mr. Shan, you want to see me?
Why do you still wear the sad face?
Shouldn’t we celebrate it?
Celebrate?
Who wants to celebrate with you?
You’re very grateful to me now, aren’t you?
I can consider a salary raise.
Never mind a promotion.
I want to hone my skills
in my current position.
Gosh!
I didn’t know you could smile!
Why did you film that video?
I thought you were cute
when you fought.
Cute?
Yes.
People like you
don’t blink in front of a catastrophe.
You’re like a moving iceberg every day.
I couldn’t believe you would beat someone.
Kind of brutal,
but it’s something we would do.
It’s not just my opinion.
Whose else?
Didn’t you see the comments on the Internet?
You’re the idol of countless girls now.
Why do you always drink up?
You can’t drink it like that.
I just want to gulp
the expensive wine!
Yunyi,
I selected out a few invitation designs.
Which one do you like?
They’re all beautiful.
What’s up?
Mom, I’m fine.
What time is it now?
Why hasn’t Junhao come home?
Each time in a crisis,
I turn the tide.
Tell me.
Am I right?
Oh gosh!
You always wear the long face,
like I owe you something.
When you pass by,
the temperature drops so drastically
that air freezes, dude!
Ye Qianyu,
you’re drunk.
No, I’m not!
- Yes, you are. - Come on, let’s drink.
- No more. - Come on.
- Drink it! - No. No more.
Yes or no?
No.
No!
Yes or no?
What are you doing?
Hand off!
Yes or no?
No.
Yes.
Yes, I’ll drink.
OK?
Drink the bottle.
Good boy!
I did it.
You haven’t drunk yet.
Tonghao.
You’re finally back.
Smile, OK?
You look handsome when you smile.
Ye Qianyu,
do you often drink so much with strangers?
You’re not a stranger.
You’re Tonghao,
whom I like the most.
= Yunyi =
Maybe he’s busy.
Look at these.
Ye Qianyu.
= Junhao =
Hello, Junhao?
Are you still working?
I don’t know how long it might take.
Go to sleep.
Don’t wait up.
Don’t work too late.
Health matters the most.
Hmm. Got it.
When I finish the work,
I’ll go home.
Hmm.
Am I right?
It’s a good thing that a man devotes to work.
Work?
Am I your work?
Is drinking your work, too?
Ye Qianyu,
you’re so horrible.
Horrible?
I’m cute, all right?
Come on. Let me send you home.
No!
I haven’t spoken my mind.
What do you want to say?
Tonghao,
are you happy after you came back?
No one has ever asked me that question.
I wish I lose my memory, too.
Then I wouldn’t miss you so much,
nor feel sad bacause of you.
But I don’t want to forget you.
Ye Qianyu,
I’m not Tonghao.
Yes, you’re Tonghao.
Tonghao is here.
I see him.
Hey,
what is it that you want?
Why do you always intervene in my life?
I just want you to be happy.
Don’t worry.
Whatever happens,
I’ll be on your back.
I’m neither happy nor unhappy in my life.
Because everything is in my control.
I don’t like it to get out of track
or to fall apart.
But…
Thank you.
Ye Qianyu.
Hello, Mama Jinzhi?
Taichu, is Qianyu with you?
She didn’t answer my calls.
She isn’t at my place.
Strange! Where can she go?
She hasn’t come home at this hour.
She’s working overtime.
But, don’t worry, Mama Jinzhi.
I’m waiting for her down the office building.
Take care of her.
OK, bye-bye.
Qianyu.
Taichu.
It’s late.
Whom are you waiting for?
Who else except you?
You’ve been waiting for me?
What took you so long up there?
And you drank wine?
Shan Junhao invited me to a drink
to express his gratitude.
Oh.
I’m so sorry.
I don’t know you’re waiting for me.
It’s OK.
It’s late. Let me give you a lift.
Thank you.
Let’s go.
At a time like this, he needs us to squash it.
But Shan Junhao is so cold-blooded.
He never said thank you.
Taichu,
you’re taking the wrong way.
This isn’t the way to Guanmei Fishing Village.
We’re not going back to Guanmei.
Where are we going then?
My place.
Chen will be worried if I don’t go home.
It’s 2 in the morning.
And you have to go to work today.
Don’t worry.
I’ve talked to Mama Jinzhi.
All right.
There’s a woman in your home?
These are prepared for you, OK?
Oh.
Change your shoes.
Towel, pajamas.
These are prepared specially for you, too.
Thank you.
Go take a shower.
There’s a toothbrush for you.
It’s ugly.
Your office is so cold.
Let the frog be your company.
It used to be Tonghao’s best friend, too.
Mr. Shan,
you don’t need to work like a dog.
Junhao,
you’re about to get married with Yunyi.
I know.
Junhao.
You slept in the office last night?
I was too tired from work
and I fell asleep.
You drank wine?
With whom?
I…
With Dawei.
Dawei is unbelievable!
Ziqian,
what is it you want to say?
Comments about yesterday’s press conference
are positive.
I suggest we do more of such interviews.
It’s instrumental to improve our image.
Put the work aside.
Junhao,
go home and have some rest.
Let’s go.
Mr. Shan.
Dawei,
you failed to take good care of Mr. Shan
and you left his bad habit unchecked.
How could his body stand it
if it goes on like this?
I…
Director Fan, I’m sorry. It’s my fault.
Are you sober now?
Almost.
Send Mr. Shan home for some rest.
OK.
Mr. Shan.
It’s OK.
It’s already working time.
Go back to work.
I’m not going home.
I’ll leave you.
Why is there a stuffed frog?
I also want to know.
A gift from an employee.
An employee?
Who is it?
The one who filmed the video.
Oh, that one.
She must be your fan, Junhao.
But the frog doesn’t go with your air.
All right.
Go back to your work.
What’s wrong with Ziqian?
You, too. Back to work.
OK.
Crap! Crap! I’m late.
There she is.
Qianyu,
you saved Senwell from the crisis.
Right.
Thanks to the video you filmed,
many of those cancelled rooms
are rebooked.
Forgive me, manager.
I’m late because I was occupied.
Ye Qianyu!
All right.
For the sake of your devotion,
I won’t punish you for late coming.
Thank you, manager.
Is it true you filmed the video about Xie Quan?
Well, I didn’t know
you were so resourceful.
Thumb up for you.
♪ Distance between us ♪
♪ Seems short yet long ♪
♪ Heartfelt words are exchanged in diaries ♪
♪ There are no secrets between us ♪
♪ Didn’t get to say I love you so much ♪
♪ You broke into my lonely heart ♪
♪ And lit the fire called love ♪
♪ You drove out all my loneliness ♪
♪ So that I can slowly adjust myself ♪
♪ You painted my life ♪
♪ With flowers ♪
♪ You raised me up ♪
♪ From that moment on ♪
♪ You’ve been singing for me ♪