♪ Lost memory of the past ♪
♪ Can’t change how we loved each other ♪
♪ My heart only beats for you ♪
♪ I’ll protect you from all the storms ♪
♪ Even if there’s no miracle ♪
♪ I’ll walk through fire to hug you ♪
♪ Cuz we’re meant to be ♪
♪ Till love finds us again ♪
= Forget You Remember Love =
= Episode 7 =
Why are you looking at me that way?
Pretty!
I will charge you if you keep looking.
I agree.
Just keep it on credit
and I will make money and pay you gradually.
Mama Jinzhi.
Cabriolet guy.
I am coming to visit Qianyu.
OK.
What a beautiful bundle of flowers!
I don’t think there’s any flower shop at Guanmei.
Did you buy it in the downtown?
Yes.
Great!
Qianyu is in her room.
Go up and she is there.
OK, thanks.
OK.
What a good son-in-law!
Taichu, it is a surprise to see you here.
I think you may feel bored alone at home
so I hope to keep you company.
The flowers are for you.
Thanks.
Tonghao,
haven’t you gone to Indonesia?
Qianyu didn’t allow me to go
and asked me to come back.
It is an illegal agency
and Tonghao will just become
illegal laborers there.
Luckily I found it just in time.
Luckily that you returned safe and sound.
Were you playing the piano just now?
Go on!
Taichu, thank you!
For what?
I know you have kept it a secret intentionally.
But I will repay you
the money for the piano gradually.
What are you talking about, Qianyu?
I don’t understand.
Anyway,
thank you for the piano as a gift for me.
I didn’t give you a piano as a gift.
Yes, you have given me this piano as a gift.
It is really not a gift from me.
Isn’t this piano a gift from you?
No.
Who did this then?
Maybe somebody
wants to give you a pleasant surprise.
Continue to play the piano.
I can’t play the piano.
Taichu, will you play it?
OK.
I will play the favorite music of your mother.
Are you playing Canon in D Major?
Exactly!
How about this?
Chopin’s Fantasy-Impromptu in C-Sharp Minor
How do you know that, Tonghao?
You seem to be an expert in music.
Tonghao, go and deliver the goods.
Qianyu, let’s go together.
I don’t know the way.
Why are you so silly?
You just sit in front and be my guide
and go for a ride too.
I can carry you downstairs.
No. I can go downstairs by myself
with my one and a half legs.
Taichu, I am sorry.
I will practice the piano with you next time.
I will deliver goods with him today.
OK.
- Wait. - What’s up?
Don’t move.
What are you doing, Tonghao? Put me down.
Put me down.
Your leg is hurt and you can’t walk by yourself.
Slow down.
Tonghao!
Where are you taking Qianyu to?
I am going to deliver goods
and take Qianyu outside for a ride.
Mama Jinzhi, bye!
Tonghao!
Why are you grinning so silly?
Have you got a windfall?
I don’t know.
I just feel so happy,
even happier than getting a windfall.
Tonghao,
I didn’t expect you are an expert in music.
Maybe I usually attended a concert before.
I don’t think so.
You might be a waiter at a concert hall before.
A waiter?
But you can always bring me
many pleasant surprises.
I have lived in Guanmei Fishing Village
for a while.
In the beginning,
I thought it needed improvements
at this place indeed.
But later I found
many cultural elements
deserved preservation.
I will illustrate it in details
in my report.
Moreover, the story of white dolphins
is possibly true.
But I haven’t found the evidences.
If the story is true,
our plan will be
greatly affected.
I will try to prove it as soon as possible.
OK.
My foot has recovered.
Qianyu,
Tonghao, look!
My foot has recovered.
So we can deliver goods together, right?
Yes.
Mr. Tang,
you haven’t signed this agreement.
I won’t sign it.
I enjoy priority to buy back
Guanmei Hotel.
As I said before,
you might preferentially buy back
the shares mortgaged with Senwell.
But it has expired.
I very much understand that
Guanmei Hotel is your ancestral property
and you feel reluctant to sell it.
But you must
recognize the facts now.
Signing this contract
and all your arrears for Senwell
will be cancelled once and for all
and you will also get
an additional compensation of 2 million yuan.
Mr. Tang,
Although it is no big money,
it is enough for you.
According to the previous mortgage contract,
we can take over Guanmei unconditionally.
This is our second visit here.
Mr. Tang,
If you insist,
Senwell has to launch enforcement.
You shouldn’t do that.
Sales revenue 1,800 yuan.
Cost 1,400 yuan.
Profit 400 yuan.
Chen,
can I get some pocket money?
No.
You have too many pocket moneys.
How about me?
Not, either.
Mama Jinzhi,
can I check your account book?
Do you understand it?
Tonghao,
I have found a job for you through an agent.
A construction worker in Saudi Arabia.
They say you can make several
hundreds of thousands of yuan a year.
The salary and working environment
are both very good.
It is not illegal laborer this time.
My nephew confirmed it with me personally
because he is also working there.
Mama Jinzhi,
why do you feel so obliged to drive me away?
To Indonesia
and then Saudi Arabia.
Do you think I am a big trouble here?
I am not a liar at all,
right?
You are a liar of course.
You cheat our money
and also want to deceive Qianyu.
Mom.
Mama Jinzhi,
I think
you are wrong in the profit calculation
in your account book.
What?
I have always calculated it in this way
in the last couple of years.
The cost you mentioned just now
is only the purchase cost
but doesn’t include the labor,
water and electricity costs
and also house rental.
This house is our own house
and we run the grocery ourselves.
So there is no rental and labor cost.
Strictly speaking,
this house is valuable.
Although it doesn’t bring rentals,
it has depreciation.
You work for yourselves every day
and you deserve salaries
because you need to make a living.
The cost shall not be taken as profit.
Can you be more reasonable?
I can make a detailed adjustment plan
for Money Bag Grocery.
Tonghao is very talented.
Useful.
Can I stay here then?
It depends on your performances.
Qianyu! Qianyu!
Sheng.
Big trouble!
What’s up?
Senwell dispatched a group of people here.
They are forcing
Tang to sign a contract.
Just go and take a look.
What?
Let’s go.
Go.
Take care.
Mama Jinzhi’.
What happened to them?
Where?
Upstairs!
What have they done to Tang?
I don’t know. They are still discussing.
They said they would force Tang
to sign the contract at all costs.
I will go and see.
OK.
Take care.
Qianyu.
I didn’t expect to see you here.
I am your strong backup. Don’t worry.
Tang, whoever dares to force you
will have to face severe consequences.
Who are you?
I am Ye Qianyu,
guardian of Guanmei Hotel.
I see.
Let me go to Guanmei Hotel and see what I can do.
What is the use of your going there?
I just go and have a look.
As you like.
You are pushing Tang to the corner.
Don’t go ahead any further.
I think it is a misunderstanding, miss.
Misunderstanding?
Obviously, you are trying to
take away Tang’s hotel.
Qianyu, stop talking.
We didn’t force Mr. Tang.
Mr. Tang mortgaged his shares
with the financial company
under Senwell.
We are just performing the contract.
Don’t look for an excuse to justify yourself.
Guanmei Hotel is Tang’s home
and his life.
How can you be so ruthless
to dismantle it at your will?
Please be empathetic.
If we want to dismantle your home,
will you agree peacefully?
I am sorry, Mr. Tang,
can you explain to this lady first?
Forget it.
Don’t talk about it anymore.
Sorry.
Miss Fan.
Director Xu,
can I talk to you separately for a while?
You can talk about anything in public.
All the people here
are trustworthy representatives of Senwell.
I just want to talk to you separately.
OK.
Qianyu, just stay here.
No, I must protect you, Tang.
Take it easy, I will find a good solution.
What’s going on now?
Tang said he hoped to talk
to Director Xu separately.
Washroom?
What?
Director Xu!
What are they going to talk about?
Look!
Mr. Tang, what do you want to talk to me?
If you can help me to protect Guanmei Hotel,
I will do you a favor.
What favor?
As you know,
the news is fake.
Your general manager Shan Junhao
has never gone abroad at all.
Mr. Tang,
I wonder
what is the relation between
Mr. Shan’s going abroad and your hotel.
You don’t have to cover it up.
Frankly,
you know it better than me
what consequences there may be
if the media knows about
Mr. Shan’s traffic accident.
What?
If you return Guanmei Hotel to me,
we can make a deal
and I will continue to keep it a secret for you.
As you know,
the news about the traffic accident
and disappearance of Mr. Shan,
the general manager of Senwell Group,
will have great impacts
on your share price.
I guess you have many concerns
so you had to cover it up from the public
by claiming he has gone abroad.
Mr. Tang,
you can’t make up a story
just to protect your hotel.
It is not empty talk.
I know you need evidences
and I have such evidences.
Yunyi,
let’s go.
They are coming!
Go, go, go!
- Boss. - Boss.
What did you say to him?
What did you say?
Go.
= Guanmei Hotel =
Ziqian.
What’s up?
Director Xu, we will go to pick up the car.
What’s up, Yunyi?
Your expressions were different
when you came out just now.
What did Tang Shunming say to you?
Tang, what did you say to them?
What did you say, boss?
I got a grace period of one month.
Good news.
Qianyu!
Why are you here?
Shan Junhao!
It is me.
I am coming here for you.
Qianyu.
Hello, everybody.
Who is that?
He…
He is my cousin.
I don’t know
you have a cousin.
Yes, Qianyu.
I have seen all your relatives.
Ziqian,
do you know how important
the Guanmei Project is to us?
If we can’t get it,
we will be at a disadvantage in the future.
I know.
We have to get more time for Junhao.
Get in the car first.
Handsome guy, what’s your name?
My name is Tonghao.
Tonghao?
What a strange name.
Master, listen,
a handsome guy always has a good name
whatever it may be.
Keep yourself under control.
How are things getting along?
They agreed
to give Tang a grace period of one month.
Great!
= Guanmei Hotel =
What are you looking at?
Whose car is it?
Qianyu,
is he really your cousin?
Yes.
Come on,
come with me.
Handsome guy.
What?
This is what has happened.
So never tell others.
Listen, take Tonghao here.
OK.
Don’t tell others.
Now you can tell me
what Tang Shunming told you.
He knows about Junhao’s car accident.
How did he know that?
I know you need evidences
and I have such evidences.
What evidences?
I saw it.
You were there when the accident happened?
Yes.
Did you do it?
Do you think you can protect your hotel
in this way?
I didn’t do it.
I used to have such an idea
but I dismissed it at the last moment.
It is just an accident.
Why didn’t you
tell me right away?
I called the police immediately.
If I had told you then,
you would have suspected me like today.
But I remember the car.
Tang Shunming,
I thought you were an honest person.
I didn’t expect you would
threaten me with Junhao’s accident.
I didn’t wish to, Director Xu.
If you were
in the same situation as me,
you would understand my feelings.
OK.
I will give you a grace period of one month.
Tang Shunming shouldn’t have done that.
I didn’t expect that, either.
But he still has some conscience.
But he had the desire to hurt Junhao.
Why did you agree?
Because I believe Junhao is still alive.
Before he comes back,
we must protect Senwell.
But,
if he had told us earlier,
we may have found
Junhao now.
Yunyi,
don’t tell Aunt Jiang
and Uncle Shan about it.
Mr. Tang, are you looking for me?
Mr. Tang,
do you know me?
No.
I don’t know you.
Qianyu told me
that you had lost your memory.
I don’t remember my past.
But I think it is good now.
Qianyu and Mama Jinzhi
are very good to me.
If that is the case,
you just stay here.
If you are in trouble,
come to me for help at any time.
OK.
Thanks, Mr. Tang.
I have to go now.
Hey, wait a minute.
Anything I can help you?
Well…
Don’t you feel a little curious
about your past?
About this,
actually, I felt curious
and even at a loss in the beginning.
But then
I realized
it wasn’t important at all.
What is most important now
is that Guanmei Fishing Village is my home.
Qianyu, Mama Jinzhi
and Shengzhe
are all my family.
It is not easy for you
to be so open-minded at such a young age.
I learned it all from Guanmei Fishing Village.
Unfortunately,
Senwell
is determined to dismantle
our Guanmei Fishing Village.
I…
Well…
Just do your job if you are busy.
OK, I am leaving now.
What are you thinking about?
I am thinking how
I can make 8 million yuan a month.
So much money!
There is only one way out.
Just hand over the hotel
to such a management group as Senwell.
I have checked the data.
The hotels under its flagship
are top ones in the Asia-Pacific region.
So Senwell is absolutely a professional
hotel operator.
What are you talking about?
Tang’s hotel is going to be dismantled.
How can you speak for Senwell?
I am not speaking for Senwell.
I am just telling the truth.
Don’t you remember that
I checked the hotel all around
when I was looking for you then?
The equipment is too old and the service is poor.
Such a hotel won’t work well.
Refitting is necessary
if operation has to continue
and it will take a long time for such refitting.
Tang has a big debt to repay
and he can’t change the status quo
in just a month.
You don’t know it at all.
Guanmei Hotel is even more precious than his life.
It is the memory of
every one at Guanmei Fishing Village.
But it is the reality.
Without any better choice,
Tang has to give up.
Such a person who has lost his memory as you
will never understand
why we have to insist here.
Yes.
I have lost my memory.
But I can see the reality
and the increasing decline of the hotel.
The hotel has no time,
capital and talent
and it can’t continue operation in this condition.
Tang accumulated such a big debt payable
to Senwell in 5 years
and that is the proof.
It is none of your business.
You are not qualified to be our mentor.
Qianyu!
= Guanmei Hotel =
Mind your step!
Or you will damage the stairway
and pay for the repair.
Why is she so furious?
Tonghao, did you quarrel?
You must have found
who Ye Qianyu is like just in time.
Who offended Ye Qianyu on earth?
Me.
Man!
Shengzhe, are you still awake?
How can I fall asleep
when you keep rolling over on bed?
Sorry.
Do you know
what’s the most mysterious thing in the universe?
What is that?
The mind of a girl.
Shengzhe,
can you tell me
why Qianyu cares about Guanmei Hotel so much.
Since her mother died
and she came to this island with her father,
Guanmei Hotel has become her home
and where she has grown up.
Maybe people who have lost memories like me
can hardly know her feelings.
How about now?
What is most valuable
to you?
Most valuable?
Just imagine.
Will you agree if Taichu takes Ye Qianyu away
from you?
If you are reluctant to give up Ye Qianyu,
Ye Qianyu is also reluctant
to give up Guanmei Hotel.
I see.
A man’s intelligence will decline sharply
when he is in love.
I am really upset to see that.
Ye Qianyu, Ye Shengzhe,
come down for breakfast.
Hurry up!
Emergency!
Tonghao is gone!
He is gone？
Tonghao got up
one hour earlier than usual today.
I haven’t seen him since he got up.
He promised me he would stay here.
Breakfast time!
= Guanmei Hotel =
There must be good services and good environments
if you want to run a hotel well.
Do you have them?
Yes?
- Yes. - No. -
Yes or no?
No.
Service may be the most
or the least costly
in the world.
First of all,
appearance
is the most fundamental respect to customers.
Moreover,
a clean, neat and tidy environment
is also the most fundamental.
Do you want to save Guanmei Hotel?
Come on.
Get started.
What are you doing?
Qianyu, you are finally here!
Your cousin woke us up early in the morning
and requested us
to do one job after another.
Is he here to help us
or punish us?
Qianyu,
I am still dozing now.
Is it useful for us
to do so much?
It seems to be really different
and much brighter now!
It is marvelous
to have such great changes
after slight adjustments by Tonghao.
OK.
You can take a rest now.
We will continue ten minutes later.
What are you doing?
I am trying to rescue Guanmei Hotel.
Didn’t you recommend having
Senwell as operator of Guanmei Hotel?
It is the place where you have grown up.
It’s laden with many of your beautiful memories.
So
I hope to guard it with you.
Welcome.
What’s up?
Come in, please.
What are you doing?
Will people of the Ministry of Health
come for a check today?
I didn’t receive any notice.
Boss.
Tonghao asked us to do it.
Do you think our hotel is revitalized again?
Boss, I haven’t seen
such bright sunshine through the window for long.
Tonghao,
was it all done at your request?
Tonghao has done it for our good.
He said
he would guard Guanmei Hotel with us.
Mr. Tang,
I have checked the financial statements
of Guanmei Hotel for the past 3 years.
OK.
What?
Who gave you the financial statements?
Fengqiao,
you always lose your stance
whenever you see a handsome guy.
How dare you disclose
such trade secrets to others?
Everybody knows that
Guanmei Hotel loses more than
one hundred thousand yuan every month.
There hasn’t been any single customer
other than flies in the last few months.
Me.
But I am not a fly.
Mr. Tang,
if you want to refit Guanmei Hotel,
I think you should change
your management philosophy.
Guanmei Hotel’s loss keeps increasing now.
The fundamental reason
actually lies in
your failure to improve total quality management.
What?
Total what?
TQM. Total quality management.
Without total quality management,
guest satisfaction tracking system and
integrated business plan,
you will know nothing about
Guanmei Hotel’s market penetration index.
Guanmei Hotel
needs comprehensive and systematized management.
Mr. Tang, you can just check
the negative comment ratio
of Guanmei Hotel on MT website.
Customer experience is fundamental
of a hotel’s survival.
A hotel without good customer experiences
will only have poor customer comments.
If you want to change the hotel,
you need to firstly
change your philosophies.
Operated in the name of a hotel,
Guanmei Hotel actually doesn’t
have the base and capability to run a hotel.
I recommend
renaming Guanmei Hotel as Guanmei Inn
and turning it into a homestay facility.
I agree.
You may refer to the examples of
Antalya’s Citrus Garden Hotel
and Jakarta’s Sunshine Seaviews.
No.
I don’t think so.
Guests stay at Citrus Garden Hotel
simply to see the Kaleci City
and enjoy the feeling of roaming
in a seaside city.
And Sunshine Seaviews
is more like a five-star hotel.
But Citrus Garden Hotel
also advocates the scenes of sand ocean,
and the service concept of Sunshine Seaviews
is the most human-oriented one I’ve ever seen.
I believe the most valuable reference for us
is West Meadow.
Can you talk about something we know?
Yes.
Qianyu,
I didn’t expect
you had such a handsome and cool cousin.
Of course.
Tonghao, come with me.
Tonghao,
what did you do on earth before?
I don’t know.
I don’t know why.
I had many ideas just now
and I couldn’t help saying them.
You are so
well-educated!
It is just a hobby.
I think our hotel…
You are not a simple person
although I didn’t understand
what you were talking about.
Maybe my job
had something to do with hotel management.
Sorry.
I shouldn’t have been so angry
with you last night.
It doesn’t matter.
Because you make me understand
we should work hard
for the people and things we care about.
Taichu,
you have been to so many countries.
Why have you stayed at this small Guanmei Hotel
for so long
and helped us refit the hotel?
Because
it’s a place that deserves to be better.
♪ Distance between us ♪
♪ Seems short yet long ♪
♪ Heartfelt words are exchanged in diaries ♪
♪ There are no secrets between us ♪
♪ Didn’t get to say I love you so much ♪
♪ You broke into my lonely heart ♪
♪ And lit the fire called love ♪
♪ You drove out all my loneliness ♪
♪ So that I can slowly adjust myself ♪
♪ You painted my life ♪
♪ With flowers ♪
♪ You raised me up ♪
♪ From that moment on ♪
♪ You’ve been singing for me ♪