Come with me!
We're not going with you.
We won't trust anyone ever again!
Where are you taking us to?
It has nothing to do with us!
Let them go!
They're actors signed by our company.
Here's the contract.
I have a contract too.
I have the endorsement contract too.
You've been conned.
This is an exclusive contract.
Everything about them belongs to me.
Nonsense!
They signed my contract first!
They're mine!
I don't care! Get them!
Wait! Wait!
I have an idea!
Why don't you guys fight it out?
We'll go with whoever wins.
Trying to divide us?
Everyone, beat them until they agree!
We'll split the contracts!
Stop!
Lei Na.
Listen up.
They belong exclusively to Yao Inc.
=Love Crossed=
=Episode 28=
(The Colorist)
Kele.
Lu Xiao! Why are you here?
You're working
the night shift today, right?
I came to keep you company.
I missed you all day.
How's the interview?
It went well.
It went well?
Then... Should I be calling you
Mr. Lu from now on?
Actually, I'm still undecided.
Their offer wasn't that good.
So I thought I'd check out
what other jobs there might be
for me tomorrow.
Sounds good.
I'll support you
no matter what you do.
Then...
What else do you think I can do
besides becoming a piano teacher?
Besides a piano teacher...
What about a dance instructor?
I'll give it a try tomorrow.
You must be tired
from running around all day.
I'll treat you to something good.
Sure.
(Shizuren)
Hold on.
I am going
to teach you
the "Kele" way of eating this.
One bite of the croquette
and a bite of the Shizuren noodles.
Try it.
One bite of the croquette...
Is it good?
It's delicious.
Then... Do you want to try another way?
One bite of the croquette
and one bite of "Kele".
Take a bite of the croquette first.
Was it good?
What's that sound?
Qianya.
Why aren't you asleep yet?
I can't sleep.
You can't sleep again?
Do you want me to help?
Cross your hands and close your eyes.
Imagine
that you are in a completely dark room.
Lying on a soft, comfortable bed.
At this moment,
your face
is the center of your emotions.
It's peaceful. It's relaxed.
The muscles on your face
are slowly relaxing.
What is it?
Does that not work for you anymore?
That's not it.
I figured out
what I'm going to do next.
The news reported
that the four of you existed.
At that time,
I thought it'd be great
if I could meet you guys.
I never imagined
that one of them
could be sitting before me right now.
Do you play the game as well?
Yes.
But I chose Su Lie.
I had him work out with me.
Su Lie. He works out a lot.
What do you guys do
in that place
called the Bay House
for all these years?
We usually practice singing and dancing.
Sometimes, we work out too.
That doesn't sound much different
from what dancers do.
I heard
your parents passed away
a long time ago.
And you met Xu Guanghan
when you were in the streets.
Is that true?
Could you keep the questions
related to the interview?
I've already asked
what I needed to know.
You can sing and dance.
You're well-suited
to be a dance instructor at our studio.
Besides, you're so popular right now.
I'm sure
that you'll bring a new image
to our studio if you join us.
Does that mean I'm hired?
Do I have a reason not to hire you?
When can I start?
Right now.
(Falling Asleep In Seconds)
Xu Nian, look.
It's written here.
Over 38.2 percent
of the youth today
suffer from insomnia and anxiety.
The prevalence in the elderly
is as high as 60 percent.
Losing sleep has serious impacts
on one's health, work, and lifestyle.
There is no perfect cure
for it until today.
They can only rely
on long-term medication.
Just like I did back then.
Long-term medication
could also have serious side effects
on one's physical and mental health.
I may have failed
in running a social media platform,
but I gained a lot of experience.
And now,
we can create an application
targeting at people
who have trouble sleeping.
We can help relieve their suffering.
What do you think?
I think it's good.
The social media platform failed
because people
were addicted to the virtual world.
Since we can't wake those people up,
we can help those
with sleeping difficulties
to sleep better.
Okay.
Help me come up with a proposal then.
So soon?
Yes.
Two days ago,
I was still worried about you.
You are much stronger than I think.
Well, I'm an undefeatable bug.
Well, if you need any help,
let me know.
Help me look for information then.
Okay.
Give that to me.
(TR Dance Studio)
Everyone did great.
Take a break.
We'll come back to it later.
Thank you, Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu!
That move earlier was too difficult.
I can't get it right.
Could you personally
teach it to me again?
Sure.
Mr. Lu, I don't know
how to do that move too!
Like...
I can't do this part right.
Teach me, Mr. Lu!
Mr. Lu, I forgot all the moves.
Teach me, please?
Okay.
Mr. Lu!
I came first!
No, I was first!
Mr. Lu, teach me!
Okay! Stop!
Since everyone needs extra lessons,
why don't we practice it again together?
Together?
Let's get back and practice.
Never mind.
All right. Follow me.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four.
Buckle up. Show some spirit, okay?
If you aren't as popular,
then learn from him.
You can't have his looks,
but still you'd try to
pick up some of his charm.
There's no use sulking here.
Go get busy.
(TR Dance Studio)
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three.
Mr. Lu, can I invite you to dinner?
Mr. Lu, let's have a meal together!
No, that's all right.
Um... Wait.
Mr. Lu!
It's late. Let's meet again tomorrow.
All right.
You have to come tomorrow.
We'll have a meal together then!
Yes, tomorrow. Together.
- Okay.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
See you tomorrow.
I don't know a lot of the moves!
You have to teach me!
Bye.
Bye. See you tomorrow.
Why are you here?
I'm here to pick up my boyfriend
and accompany him home.
How's work today?
I see you're quite popular.
I didn't expect it too.
People in the outside world
are actually quite friendly.
The salary is good
and there's even a bonus.
The boss is nice too.
Wow.
It's great that you didn't choose
to become a piano teacher.
This job sounds amazing.
Yes.
And I noticed something.
What?
No matter if it's the virtual you
or the real you,
my Lu Xiao is amazing!
It was my first time
teaching someone to dance too.
I was quite nervous.
Don't worry. You did great!
It's not easy to face
all those women on your own.
All right.
It is your first day of work today.
I'll gather everyone
and let's have a hot pot feast
to celebrate!
Sounds great!
Hello, Granny. What is it?
What?
Okay. I got it.
What's wrong, Kele?
Granny said that Su Lie and Luo Ke
haven't gone back
to her place for two days.
They must've been off having fun.
Don't worry.
Why don't we go look for them?
Hello?
Ms. Guan, something big happened!
What is it now?
It's Mr. Cui.
Didn't you go to see your ex-wife?
I did.
We even...
No, I'm talking about something else.
What? Did they get caught
and brought back to the Bay House again?
That's exactly it.
It's about the Bay House.
I heard my ex-wife
said that it's been turned
into a tourist attraction.
And guess
who her friend saw there?
I found them.
This is the gift for you.
Thank you.
Why do you think
these people are so excited?
It's like they've never seen anything.
Maybe they've never
seen a house as big as this one.
This is the gift for you.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
Guan Qianya was a CEO as well.
But her house isn't that big either.
We even had to sleep on mattresses.
Grandma Fushun's place was worse.
Only a presidential suite
of a five-star hotel
could be better than this place.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Get over here.
Got it.
Stop! Stop!
Why are you guys here?
Are you coming back
or are you here to visit?
Neither.
We'll just get in and get out.
Get in and get out?
That means you're visiting.
Okay. Then we'll get the tickets.
Come visit tomorrow.
(Open to the public from 9 a.m. to late night)
We're closed for today.
Then,
get Su Lie and Luo Ke out here.
I have something to tell them.
No, no, no.
We're just security guards.
We're only here to guard the place.
We don't have the authority
to tell them to come out.
Hey, man.
Hello, bro.
Family.
We're a family.
I haven't seen you in a while.
You lost weight, didn't you?
Really?
Here.
Kele does know
how to do things, doesn't she?
Scan this.
You should eat something good.
Take a break. Have a late-night snack.
Well... Welcome to
the family of Yao Inc.!
Please.
Welcome.
A warm welcome.
Bro, did I do it well this time?
Those tourist ladies were so nice.
Even though
they've never lived in a big house,
they gave us a lot of gifts.
Yes. The women who came here
are different from those outside.
They're kind and generous.
Oh my gosh.
A woolen cap.
This fits my image in the game.
But I won't use this in the house.
What's this?
Sunscreen.
I can't even see the sun in here.
Why would they give me sunscreen?
Because
they're treating you
like the virtual character
in the game.
They think you've been
going surfing every day.
These people are hilarious.
They can't even differentiate
between virtual and real world.
Why are you guys back?
We've claimed the rooms
in the lower floor.
You have to sleep upstairs.
We're not here
to fight you guys for rooms.
Did Xu Guanghan catch you guys
and bring you guys back here?
No, it wasn't him. It was Lei Na.
We were conned
and almost got beaten up.
Lei Na appeared just in time
and brought us back here.
She even gave us this job.
What job?
Weren't you guys rehired?
How could you not know?
We're basically doing the same things.
All we have to do
is to eat, sing, and dance.
The only difference is that
there are tourists now.
They'll take photos with us
every now and then.
So you guys are actors
in a tourist attraction!
Xu Guanghan really
knows how to make money, huh?
We weren't rehired.
We're here to get you guys out of here.
We did all of that
to get out of this place.
Why did you come back?
Come on. Let's go back.
No.
We signed a contract.
What contract?
Another contract to imprison you guys?
No. It's different.
The contract didn't
say that we couldn't go out.
We asked for it to be added on.
The world outside is too scary.
We want to stay here.
We don't want to go anywhere else.
Why?
Because the world outside
isn't good at all.
We need to work
and earn money.
And there are many scammers.
We get all we need here
and we don't even have to do anything.
Why should we leave?
You guys
have already tried the food outside.
But you have to eat
healthy food here.
Don't you crave the food outside?
You guys don't know about this.
Even though we're still
eating healthy food,
it's
more of a performance now.
The tourists would bring us
lots of tasty food.
The more we eat, the happier they are.
Su Lie even dropped his banana.
They are all so excited about it.
Su Lie, weren't you afraid of women?
So many women come here every day.
Aren't you afraid?
But there are even more
women out there, aren't there?
In order to stay here and keep this job,
I'll do my best to overcome it.
Su Lie. Luo Ke.
You guys are helpless!
Why?
There's nothing wrong
with us trying to make a living.
Don't you guys have any pride as humans?
Xu Guanghan kept you guys here
as attractions for visitors
to see you and feed you.
How are you guys
any different from a monkey in a zoo?
Well, humans evolved from monkeys.
You guys might not even
be able to find a better job than we do.
Never mind.
I'm tired of this.
Let them do what they want.
This friendship is over!
Fine.
But remember,
you're not the ones
who ended this friendship.
We're the ones
who decided to leave you guys.
I'm so mad, Lu Xiao!
Beat them up for me!
That's enough. Let's go.
Let me know if you ever
want to come back.
I'll put in a good word
for you with Mr. Xu.
Don't be so upset, guys.
They've also seen the world outside.
So we should respect their choice
to stay in the Bay House.
I'm not upset with them.
It's hard enough to hold myself back
from how angry I am.
They made that decision
because that's their view
of the world.
We can't convince them.
And they can't possibly
be like Xu Nian and Lu Xiao.
I'm telling you.
I was so worried about them, you know.
I was worried
about how they'd survive in the outside world.
And now?
I have nothing to worry about anymore!
I'll just leave them to their demise.
Lu Xiao,
don't be mad.
After I gave him a punch,
I think I can let it go now.
All right.
Let's not talk about
such unhappy things anymore.
I have a good news to share with you!
Lu Xiao's great at work.
He became a celebrity instructor
at a dance studio!
I have a good news too.
Xu Nian and I
are going to create
an application together.
Specifically for people with insomnia.
Qianya, that's a great idea!
You're using your pain
to cure somebody's pain.
It'll be our win
if Xu Guanghan ever uses this app,
don't you think?
Thanks for the vote of confidence.
We'll be meeting the investors tomorrow.
That's great.
The first thing I'll do
is to invest in you guys
when I get my salary next month!
Okay.
Let's have a toast.
I hope you'll manage
to get the funds you need.
And for us
to get used to living
in the outside world soon.
Cheers!
What do you think about the project?
I think you don't need to ask for funds
for this project.
All you have to do is to make copies
of your proposal and sell them.
Reading it could cure insomnia.
You might not understand it as well
because you don't have
any issues with your sleep.
Maybe that's why you can't relate
to the pain of our target users.
Yes. That's right.
If I can't relate to it,
why would I want to invest in it?
We won't take up
any more of your time then.
We've set up a meeting
with another investor as well.
Great.
I can't stay here a moment longer.
I'd better go back and take a nap.
It's okay.
You must be Xu Nian.
I came because I saw your name
on the proposal.
I have a few questions for you.
Is your father
the famous Xu Guanghan?
Why didn't you stay and assist him?
But instead, you decided
to start your own business?
Does every wealthy kid
want to prove themselves
through hard work?
They would only go back to inherit
their parents' wealth
when they fail?
I have nothing to do with Xu Guanghan.
Please do not mention him and me
in the same sentence again.
You guys got into a fight?
Will you guys ever make up?
No.
What do you want?
I want to use him
to get connected to Xu Guanghan.
Did you really think
I was interested in this project?
Why don't you take a look
at the proposal?
No.
I have a clear goal
in mind when I do things.
Since you no longer
have anything to do with Xu Guanghan,
then let's not waste each other's time.
Don't mind him.
I've met tons of weird investors
like him.
There's another one.
I only have five minutes.
Let's get to the point.
Then
I'll brief you on our proposal.
No need.
I read it on my way here.
The project seems fine.
Then...
Are you willing
to be our angel investor?
I haven't finished yet.
The project is fine.
But Guan Qianya is not.
Why not?
I have many years of experience
in starting a business.
I built Crush On Love...
You're still bringing up
your company that went bankrupt?
It could have had a bright future.
But you ruined it.
Guan Qianya,
have you ever reflected
on how you got to where you are today?
It's because this world is too foolish.
This world?
There are so many
companies that run social software.
But why did yours fail
when theirs did not?
That's because Qianya stood up
against Xu Guanghan.
If it's not the world that's wrong,
it's your competitor.
You are as laughable as they say.
If someone who keeps failing,
just keeps finding excuses,
they won't succeed
no matter what they do.
Aren't you in a rush?
If you aren't interested,
you can leave.
Guan Qianya,
where does
all that pride of yours come from?
I did my research before I came.
Your company's done for.
You lost your house and your car.
You'd probably
have to sleep in the streets soon.
You want to start over
with these slides?
Not likely possible.
Stop wasting your time.
Let me tell you this.
You've long been
blacklisted among investors.
Of course,
I don't care how many
investors you've met before this,
but those who are still
willing to meet you
are either
ones with ulterior motives
or newbies in the investment business.
Then which one are you?
As a businesswoman,
I'm here to give you a piece of advice.
Stop embarrassing yourself.
That's all I have to say.
And that's five minutes. See you.
It's okay. We still have chances.
Goodbye.
Bye.
What is it, Lu Xiao?
Boss, I have something to tell you.
Speak.
I want to quit.
Why?
Is the pay not high enough?
Were you approached by other studios?
Now, I'm curious.
Why do you want to quit?
Because during the class today,
that girl...
Your move here was...
You want to quit
just because of that?
It's not a small matter.
It's harassment.
What sort of harassment?
You're the instructor,
and she's the student.
It's perfectly normal
to have physical contact
when you're teaching her to dance.
You're thinking too much into it.
Our female students
are all good students.
They wouldn't do something like this.
There's another thing as well.
Mr. Lu,
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
Come closer.
Closer.
Just tell me. I'm listening.
Come closer.
That's a small matter too.
You call that a small matter too?
All she did was give you
a peck on the cheek.
She's just kissing goodbye.
If you're not used to it,
I can help you practice it every day.
That way, you'll get used to it.
No need.
All right. Go back to work then.
What? Is there something else?
Mr. Lu,
are you free after class?
Let's have dinner together.
Sorry.
I have something to do after work.
What could be more important than work?
If you promise to have dinner with me,
I'll take care of your
KPI for this month.
If you go to a bar with me...
I'll have you covered
for the next six months.
Sorry. You came to the wrong person.
I have no obligation to go out with you.
What are you acting
all pure and noble for?
Who do you think you are?
If the people like you,
then you're a celebrity instructor.
But without them,
you're nothing.
I'm going to see your boss right now.
I'm going to cancel my membership!
Well, that's not funny.
You think she crossed the line, too,
don't you?
I think you're socially inept!
It's just dinner and a drink.
What's the big deal?
You've got nothing to lose.
Can't you treat a client as a friend?
But she...
What's with the "but"?
You need to understand
what it means to work with clients.
Understand?
If you get along with your clients,
your KPI will go up.
If your KPI goes up,
then your bonus increases as well.
Isn't that something good?
I won't be happy if that's
how my KPI goes up.
If you insist
on keeping your principles,
then I'm afraid this job isn't for you.
With that attitude of yours,
you won't last long
no matter where you work.
If you can't even stand
a little pressure like this,
then you should just go back
to your old life.
In this world,
no one is going
to give you something for nothing.
Oh, there is someone who would.
Xu Guanghan.
Qianya, why don't we leave first?
We still have another investor coming.
We've been waiting for two hours.
But I want to wait for them.
Why don't I take you to a place?
Where?
A place you know well.
Are you a student of ours?
Or are you interested
in having classes?
Oh, no. I'm here to pick up someone.
Pick up someone? Who?
Lu Xiao. I'm here to pick him up.
If he isn't finished yet,
I'll just wait over there.
Don't bother.
I fired him.
Fired?
Isn't he a celebrity instructor here?
His dancing is great.
Why would you fire him?
Because he doesn't love this job enough.
Because he doesn't know
how to deal with people.
He doesn't know
how to deal with clients.
He's not dedicated enough,
and neither is he crafty enough.
Someone like him
should just stay in the Bay House.
It's not that easy to survive
in the real world.
♪I'm sorry I admit♪
♪Every night I see you in my dreams♪
♪Dreams and reality become entangled♪
♪I can't tell them apart♪
♪You and I have different memories♪
♪As if we're searching
for the intersection♪
♪Piecing together
the secrets of the future♪
♪I'm falling hard♪
♪Draw a circle to encircle our hearts♪
♪A heart for a heart♪
♪Your favorite melody begins to play♪
♪In my mind♪
♪Beautiful memories
that belong only to us♪
♪Draw a circle to encircle our memories♪
♪Surrender our feelings to each other♪
♪Humming your favorite melody♪
♪Reminding you♪
♪Of the memories we shared♪