Kele, what's wrong?
Wash it!
Okay.
Do you want to wash it by machine
or dry-clean?
Hand wash.
Okay.
Why did you touch my teddy bear?
Didn't you ask me...
What?
Shut up and get out.
Kele.
Did you meet anything
unpleasant today?
You can tell me.
You knew it.
You annoyed me.
You touched my teddy bear.
How could I be happy?
Get out of here now.
If you don't,
I...
You see that?
I'd punch you to death!
Kele.
If this can make you happy,
go ahead and punch me.
Weren't you reckless just now?
Won't my hand be painful
if I punch you?
Your hand won't be painful.
You'd care about me.
Cheesy.
You're the best.
=Love Crossed=
=Episode 5=
Mr. Xu, I have something to report.
Throw the flowers away.
Isn't it blooming?
It bloomed in advance.
Do you know what it means?
It wants to bloom.
It wants to die.
Change them to artificial flowers.
Non-living things
are more reassuring than living things.
I'll get it done right away.
Hold on.
You haven't reported to me.
There are bad news and worse news.
Which one would you
like to listen to first?
The worse news.
Due to frequent server detection,
players are dissatisfied.
So we have to stop
catching the movement of G4
for the moment.
Carry out shutdown and
capacity expansion.
Why is it worse news?
IT department said it needs to
take two weeks.
Two weeks.
I've told IT department
to cut it to one week.
If they can't do that,
all of them have to resign.
It was handled well.
What should I tell Y4?
It's up to you.
As long as they're thankful for me.
Okay, I'll tell them
you give them one week of break.
All right.
What's the bad news?
The bad news is
someone
supports Guan Qianya.
Who?
Guess it.
Lei Na.
I think you might misunderstand.
We're not close enough that
we can flirt with each other.
I know.
Don't misunderstand me.
"Guess it" is the ID
of the supporter.
There are always rumors
on the internet.
You don't have to report everything.
Okay.
Guan Qianya, apologize!
Bad woman Guan Qianya.
Don't worry, Ms. Guan.
I've asked all our employees
to strike back on the internet.
I'm not worried at all.
There are many supporters online.
They are our employees.
(Netizens' comments)
Did you notice
the most active one
called "guess it"?
That's me.
What should we do next?
We can't depend on ourselves.
Next,
use the power of public media
to change this bad situation.
Well.
I think my ex-wife's best friend is
quite fit for it.
She's the top reporter of Follow News.
And we're pretty close to each other.
I can ask her to have an
exclusive interview with you.
If I'm not mistaken,
your ex-wife
is a loyal fan of Love Boys.
She is.
But her best friend isn't.
I still remember
after I've divorced
with my ex-wife,
I told her how
Love Boys made me depressed and sad.
She knew it all.
What are you waiting for?
Ask her out.
This isn't appropriate
to ask her out.
She's my ex-wife's best friend,
after all.
I've never thought of that.
I mean, the exclusive interview.
Right away.
Su Lie, I won't go easy on you today.
Go easy on me?
I'm the one who should say that.
Come on then.
Let's play this.
Okay.
Lu Xiao, open the door.
I took the teddy bear here.
Yesterday, you shouldn't...
Xu Nian.
What's wrong?
Didn't you realize?
The matter now is very serious.
I know.
Lu Xiao is still mad.
No.
That's not important.
He's always like that.
What's more important
and serious than that is
Jiang Kele may not come back again.
She's pretty scary.
But if she doesn't come here,
we won't have good food.
Right.
Don't worry.
Jiang Kele will come back.
We need her for the job.
You're right.
Lu Xiao made Jiang Kele mad.
It has nothing to do with us.
But only Xu Nian helped her.
Would she hold grudges against us?
You're right, too.
Jiang Kele is such a simple girl.
She won't hold grudges.
She'll come back once
she calms down.
I hope so.
(Facial Cleanser)
Go.
Don't go.
Why are you still here?
You should've left at this time.
The salary of the part-time job is high.
You should've worked hard.
I'm not going.
I want to resign.
Why?
Because I'm not happy with the job.
Let me tell you last night...
Stop. I know it all.
A great man once said that
if you're not happy with your job,
don't work then.
Don't make yourself suffer.
As you've decided to resign,
as your best friend,
I'll support you unconditionally.
Qiqi. Oh, dear.
I thought
we'll get far apart
after I got another job.
I didn't expect you'd still
care about me.
All right, cut it.
If you're touched,
how about you introduce the job to me?
Don't make our life difficult.
How much is it actually?
Five times of our salary.
Oh my god, five times!
Three thousand, four thousand,
five thousand.
How about this?
If you really
want to get the job,
I can introduce it to you.
But the salary
can only be twice as ours now.
Twice?
Jiang Kele!
It's been a few days. You became clever.
How smart.
Pass the job I gave to you to others?
No wonder I feel strange today.
My eyelid keeps on twitching.
It made me want to meet you.
It turns out that
I'm fated to expose you.
Granny.
We're all profiteers.
We don't have to expose each other.
Granny.
This lipstick is
the most popular one now.
It's a limited edition.
Only our store has it.
It's for you.
Thank you.
May I introduce myself?
Please go ahead.
You don't have to know my name
and my resume.
You just have to know that
Jiang Kele gets five times
of the salary for this job.
But I will do it for three times.
Your self-introduction
lets me get to know you again.
I want to announce two things now.
First,
I'm not going to resign.
I want to go back to work.
Second,
I don't want to befriend you anymore.
Please give me two dozen.
Okay.
I can give you this.
All right, we can start now.
As a responsible public figure...
As a person with a sense of
social responsibility,
awaken women blinded by the illusion
and promote the healthy
development of society
are part of my job.
Although I was
attacked and scolded by netizens,
I don't care.
Because I know that
there are no others
who would speak out if I don't do so.
Ms. Guan.
Since you realized
the danger of Love Boys,
why did you say it
only when
the company's performance fell?
It's hard not to guess that
your motive is for your own benefit.
It's true.
The department store is depressed.
The apparel market declines.
The marriage market is bleak.
If I didn't do this job,
I'd be like others looking on.
If you don't experience it,
you won't know the pain.
I felt the pain,
so I shouted.
But no one knows
if he or she will be the next
who suffers from it.
Trending of Love Boys
will bring great harm to reality.
Isn't it just a game?
Won't it exaggerate?
For you who don't play games,
it's just a game.
For those who are addicted to the game,
it's the whole world to them.
My friend
used to be confident and optimistic.
She was looking forward to the future.
But after she played Love Boys...
I really hope that
she won't be deluded by Y4 anymore
and becomes confident,
adorable and lively as she used to be.
Ms. Guan.
As a top reporter,
I've seen too many people
telling sad stories like that
to get sympathy.
Ms. Guan, did you ever play Love Boys?
To get to know our rival,
I've played it once.
To be honest, it's all trash.
So Ms. Guan,
your company was defeated by trash?
Yes.
Didn't your best friend
get divorced because of trash as well?
Ms. Guan, I knew it all.
Don't be mad.
She likes to pick on others.
But it wasn't aimed at you.
Did she act harshly when
you two talked
for the whole night?
When she talked with me,
she's pretty gentle.
Maybe she's
serious at work.
So you should trust me more.
Because of me,
she won't write anything negative.
I won't trust you anymore.
I'll figure it out myself.
What else could you think of?
If there's still another way,
would a top reporter interview you?
You and your ex-wife's best friend
get lost.
(Yao Inc.)
As long as I finished cleaning
before 4 o'clock,
I won't be seeing them.
Just be like usual.
Keep it up, Jiang Kele.
What are you doing?
We're having English afternoon tea
for four.
Now it's English afternoon tea
for three.
Why are you all here at this time?
Mr. Xu appreciated our hard work
and gave us one week break.
What are you holding?
Is it something delicious?
I brought you egg waffles.
Egg waffles
are the perfect match for afternoon tea.
Now it's English afternoon tea
for four.
Should we ask Lu Xiao to come
and eat as well?
No! He doesn't deserve to eat
my egg waffles.
If he's hungry,
go back to his room
and eat his teddy bear.
Don't worry.
Lu Xiao won't eat his teddy bear.
It means a lot to him.
It doesn't mean a lot to him.
The person who gave it to him
means a lot to him.
So he doesn't let others touch it.
No matter how important it is,
did he have to be that mad?
He even wanted to beat me.
That's how he's like.
We used to dance together.
I stepped on his foot accidentally.
He said he wanted to beat me to death.
Look at me now.
I'm still alive.
Did your wound recover yet?
Don't mention it.
It's still painful.
He punched you?
The blow was too fast.
I couldn't dodge.
I met Lu Xiao once while sleepwalking.
He threw me over his shoulder.
It was too fast.
I was awakened right away.
Does he usually act so to you too?
He won't act so to me.
I can still compete with him.
Because Xu Nian is the leader.
Lu Xian only bullies the weak.
We've been living in constant fear
of him for over ten years.
After hearing all these,
I feel much better.
But don't worry.
I won't forgive him.
It's fine.
As long as you bring us good food.
Not a problem.
I'll bring you good food every day.
From now on,
four of us are victims league.
Cheers!
I won't clean your room anymore.
Just stay in your dirty room.
I'm back.
My sunshine is back.
I need some positive energy
from you, quick.
Stop it.
Your sunshine is out of battery soon.
What I can do now is
not to deliver negative energy.
What's wrong with you?
I met some troubles at work.
Your cosmetic shop has
a few people only.
What troubles do you have?
No matter how many people,
either two or five,
there'll be wheeling and dealing.
Wheeling and dealing?
You should ask me that.
I'm good at wheeling and dealing.
No.
I mean, handle rivalry
inside the company.
Go ahead and tell me. I'm listening.
Nothing, actually.
Well, my colleague
has a dirty toy.
I saw it, so I washed it.
He didn't thank me
but scolded me and even
wanted to beat me.
I have one question for you.
Did he ask you to wash it?
No.
That's why!
He didn't ask you to wash it.
After you washed it,
you wanted him to thank you.
Weren't you making trouble?
So I did wrong.
No!
Women never do wrong.
Women are always right.
As your best friend,
I'm always by your side.
Just say it.
Should we scold, punch or ruin him?
Cut it out.
I scolded him.
I took revenge.
Great.
As women,
we should protect ourselves.
Since you took revenge,
forget about it.
Got it.
Women should be mean or generous
at the right time.
Right.
Since you've finished,
listen to me as well.
It's fine.
I won't understand too if you tell me.
If I said something wrong,
you'd scold me.
Don't say again. Let's drink.
Cheers.
You drink first?
(Zolpidem Tartrate Tablets)
You didn't sleep well again?
I've finished the medicines.
The medicines I prescribed last time
can be taken till the end of the month.
You must have increased
the dosage by yourself.
The medicines I prescribed
exceed the normal range.
I've told you before
if you continue to do so,
it's life-threatening.
If I die, just let it be.
It's more suffering that
I can't sleep well.
Qianya, I know you suffer a lot now.
But before
we have the new treatment,
you must try your best to
stay calm and relaxed.
And you ought to take the medicines
according to the doctor's advice.
Okay.
(Love Boys)
Qianya, you're great.
I remember everything you said.
Keep it up.
Guan Qianya, cheer up!
This morning,
an article
exposing Guan Qinya criticizing Yao Inc.
for her own benefit is trending.
It gains support
from the netizens,
especially male netizens.
In this article...
This article
used negative headline deliberately
to attract the public's attention.
But the content is
all about praise towards Guan Qianya.
Once the article is published,
it becomes the hot topic.
Many netizens share and comment on it.
Awaken women blinded by
the illusion
Death throes...
are part of my job.
Although I was attacked and
scolded by netizens,
I don't care.
Because I know that
there are no others...
Mr. Xu.
Should we take any action?
No need.
There are fans of Y4.
We just sit by and watch.
Guan Qianya, come out!
Guan Qianya, apologize!
Ms. Guan.
Did you see that?
Is that spectacular?
(Crush On Love)
I saw that.
Quickly chase the people we hired away.
How embarrassing.
I can't.
They're not hired. They're all real.
What?
Look.
After my ex-wife's best friend
published the article,
many people support you now.
Guan Qianya, we love you!
Support Guan Qianya!
Guan Qianya is the best!
Love ya, Guan Qianya.
We love you, Guan Qianya.
Who's that?
Come in.
You told me to come in.
Get out.
I've come in.
Don't chase me away.
You're reading?
Look what I brought.
Milk tea.
You must've never tried it before.
Listen, I've forgiven you.
If you drink this milk tea,
then let's wipe out the past.
No.
Give it a try! It tastes good.
Really.
Lu Xiao, if you don't want to drink,
can you give it to us?
As long as you move her out,
the milk tea is yours.
If you dare to drag me,
I won't bring good food
to you again.
Well, Lu Xiao.
It's a matter between you two.
We shouldn't get involved.
You two settle it.
Goodbye.
Enjoy your milk tea.
There are no others here.
Just tell me.
What should I do for you to forgive me?
Get out.
I don't want to go out!
Unless you make yourself clear.
Gentlemen won't beat others.
I...
Oh no.
All right, there's a matter of Qi Chuan.
Has he died?
No.
Didn't I say that
I don't want to
hear about him unless he is dead?
Okay, I won't say then.
You almost said it.
Just say it.
Qi Chuan also reposted the article
and asked all the fans
to support Guan Qianya.
Qi Chuan has lost popularity.
That's why he likes to show himself.
To be honest, it's all trash.
So Ms. Guan,
your company was defeated by trash?
Ms. Guan, did you ever play Love Boys?
To get to know our rival,
I've played once.
To be honest, it's all trash.
Mr. Xu, are you okay?
I'm all right.
But Guan Qianya is in trouble.
Good afternoon all.
The next song is the latest song
by Master Songwriter, Qi Chuan.
This song continues to explore
the inner world of a cool girl.
It's a song followed by the hit song
seven years ago called
see-through bangs.
Thank you for giving me inspiration.
Qi Chuan is the most talented person.
Guan Qianya, come out!
Guan Qianya, apologize!
So annoying.
Why are there so many people
waiting for me?
I think they're waiting for Guan Qianya.
Let's go.
He's really Qi Chuan.
I loved his songs when I was
in high school.
He's so handsome in that style.
Oh goodness, he's looking at me.
I think he's looking at me.
His new song
is produced for a girl like me.
Hello, Mr. Qi Chuan.
Hello.
This is Ms. Guan.
Mr. Qi Chuan.
I really admire you a lot.
Your songs are so nice.
You're good-looking too.
Mr. Cui.
Please close the door.
I opened it deliberately.
Let our employees see that
Mr. Qi Chuan is willing to work with us,
so as to gain their confidence.
Ms. Guan.
Don't feel embarrassed.
Everyone knows that your company
is going to be bankrupt.
I don't feel embarrassed.
I just want to help you,
a once famous artist to regain dignity.
Your buttons are messed up.
Ms. Guan has sharp eyes.
Bravo.
I'll close the door.
Stop looking. Back to work!
Go back quickly!
They closed the door.
They're going to discuss work.
If Ms. Guan and Qi Chuan can cooperate,
our company will gain hope.
Then I don't have to resign.
Qi Chuan is a savior.
Savior?
He's just an artist who
used to be famous.
Y4 are the most famous now.
Wake up please.
How impolite.
My manager told me that
your commerce department has long
contacted me, right?
For endorsement.
Right.
But that was
like last year or the past two years.
Did you think that I'm not
famous anymore?
Do you know how popular
my latest song is?
Come on. Play it for them.
No, you've always been famous.
But as you know,
our company went bankrupt.
My endorsement fee.
You can pay for sure.
I know my company.
I think we can't pay you.
What if I say
I just need one yuan.
I'm not cooperating with you for money.
Our company
won't be able to give you shares.
I don't want shares either.
I'm sorry, Mr. Qi Chuan.
I'm very curious and confused.
You don't want money
and shares.
What do you want exactly?
I want you to
beat Xu Guanghan together with me.
Mr. Xu, what's the matter?
Do you know who I trust the most
among you all?
Me?
What a narcissist.
But you're right.
You're intelligent.
I've never worried about you.
You also help me to take care of them.
You taught me well.
Luckily you knew it.
In this world,
you won't exist without me.
Yes, I bear it in mind.
Now I have a very important mission
for you.
You won't let me down, right?
What's it?
Bear in mind.
Remember everything I'm going
to tell you.
And never say it to anyone.
Okay.
♪I'm sorry I admit♪
♪Every night I see you in my dreams♪
♪Dreams and reality become entangled♪
♪I can't tell them apart♪
♪You and I have different memories♪
♪As if we're searching
for the intersection♪
♪Piecing together the secrets
of the future♪
♪I'm falling hard♪
♪Draw a circle to encircle our hearts♪
♪A heart for a heart♪
♪Your favorite melody begins to play♪
♪In my mind♪
♪Beautiful memories
that belong only to us♪
♪Draw a circle to encircle our memories♪
♪Surrender our feelings to each other♪
♪Humming your favorite melody♪
♪Reminding you♪
♪Of the memories we shared♪