It's so boring.
It's said to work is the happiest.
Indeed.
When are they coming back?
It's been only 30 minutes.
Kele.
Why are you back?
Aren't you at your training?
I have completed all the tasks
ahead of schedule today.
Here I am to keep you company.
It's so boring to watch the TV series
all by myself.
That's why I'm here.
Thank you.
Kele, you're awake.
I was just about to go and wake you up.
Did you make all these?
Yes.
I learned to make these
from the recipe.
Here.
Take a seat.
Today, I've prepared
something special for you.
Braised fish?
How did you know that I like it?
Xu Nian told me.
How did he know?
It must be Qianya who told him.
You could have just asked me.
There's no need to do it
in a roundabout way.
If I were to ask you,
there would be no surprise.
By the way,
this isn't any ordinary braised fish.
I called it
Kele Fish.
A dish named after me?
No.
That's because it's a braised fish
made specially for Kele with coke.
Give it a try.
If I were to say
what I'm about to say next,
my dad would be mad.
But I have to say.
This is really good
given it's your first attempt.
Really?
Have more.
Dig in. Come on.
Here's another one.
Wait.
We can't finish everything ourselves.
Why don't we ask them to join us?
We've been waiting for you
to say that!
We have the utensils ready!
Don't eat too much.
Save some for Kele.
Don't worry. We're not like Xu Nian.
He comes late and eats a lot.
Why do I feel like
someone's talking behind my back?
Speaking of the devil.
This is Kele Fish?
That's right.
I made it for Jiang Kele.
None of you can eat it.
♪You're in my embrace
when I open my eyes♪
♪You reassure me♪
♪Your care and attention
make me feel important♪
♪Every day I want your attention♪
♪I can't stop throwing tantrums♪
=Love Crossed=
=Episode 21=
Lu Xiao, why are you here?
I'm here to pick my girlfriend up
from work
and send her home.
Sure.
How do you usually go home?
I usually take the subway.
If we move now,
we should be able
to catch the last train.
Let's go then.
Hold on.
Let's go home.
Kele, you're home.
I should get going now.
So you meant it
when you said you just wanted
to send your girlfriend home?
If not?
Would you like to come in
and have a drink?
What drinks?
Jiang Kele.
Alright, I was just messing with you.
It's the boiled coke with ginger.
I'm afraid you might catch a cold
since you got wet in the rain.
Here. Coke with ginger.
I didn't know it tastes so good.
It's not.
The Kele Fish that you made is the best.
Lu Xiao.
Thank you.
Thank you
for all you've done today.
These are things
that I never dare to dream of.
Actually, I'm really happy today.
This is my first time
being in a relationship.
So it turns out
that it actually feels that great
being able to take care of a girl.
From now on,
I'll make you happy every day.
No.
Because if you have to work
and try to make me happy
at the same time,
it'll be really tough on you,
and you'll get distracted.
I just want you to focus on your work.
The sooner you complete the contract,
the sooner you can leave the Bay House.
That way,
we'll be able to date in public.
Whatever you say.
(Love Boys)
Do you think it looks like him?
I think it looks a lot like him.
Where did you get this picture?
Lisa took it.
Lisa?
Didn't Guan Qianya fire her?
Yes, that's why she's working
in the restaurant now.
She said Guan Qianya has lost her mind
and is addicted to the game.
She's even dating
a replacement
who looks a lot like Xu Nian.
Lisa thought
this picture would be of use to us.
So she wanted something in return.
From the day
Guan Qianya stood up against me,
she has already lost her mind.
Mr. Xu, what should we
give Lisa in return?
What else does she want?
We have given her a lifetime membership.
It's her job to do us favors.
Okay.
(Crush On Love)
I've seen this sweater
in Xu Nian's room.
He is Xu Nian!
I'm so blessed
to be able to have breakfast
with my Lu Xiao.
My goodness. I'm so happy
that I'm about to pass out.
That's a little exaggerating.
It's not like we haven't
had breakfast together before.
That's different.
We had it with the others,
but now, it's just the two of us.
Also, it's a couple set meal
that you made yourself.
All right. Eat up.
♪I still remember the first time we met♪
♪Even the skies turned pink♪
♪You control my mind and my body♪
♪I don't want this dream to end,
so I'll act on my love♪
♪Let love explode and bombard you
with sweetness♪
♪I'll take your entire world by storm♪
♪I'll follow you wherever you go♪
♪Like a tail you can't get rid of♪
Am I interrupting something?
No.
Do you want to join us for breakfast?
Do you want to have breakfast?
I'll pass.
I have a bigger fish to fry.
I want to discuss it with you two.
What is it?
Xu Nian.
Mr. Xu is here.
Let's go.
Hi, Mr. Xu.
Please give us the room.
I have something
to discuss with Xu Nian.
Get moving.
Lei Na, search Xu Nian's room.
All right.
Mr. Xu.
Jiang Kele took the sweater
the other day.
Well, let's see
if we find any contraband.
Okay.
Mr. Xu, I found a phone.
Who gave it to you?
It's a limited edition.
First, the sweater. Now, the phone.
I never expected such a big surprise
coming from you.
Xu Nian.
I have some questions for you.
Ask away.
I have questions for you too.
Let's see
who has more questions.
Why conceal the existence
of the four of us?
That's a good question.
Anything else?
Why did you lie?
Why tell everyone
that we are virtual characters in Love Boys?
Not bad. What else?
Why imprison the four of us?
So this is what Guan Qianya told you
after you sneaked out?
I didn't sneak out.
It has nothing to do with her.
I did some searching using my phone.
Tell me. Who gave you the phone?
You haven't answered my questions.
Fine.
If you really want to know,
I'll tell you slowly.
When I was young,
I was a celebrity manager
who started from scratch
and established Yao Entertainment
after a decade or so in the industry.
I've helped to bring fame
to many people.
One of them is Qi Chuan,
who became famous at a young age
and is all washed up now.
The other one was Ge Yilan,
the female star
who has once been popular
in Asia.
But she has withdrawn
from the show business.
My question is
why imprison us?
You have been living here
since you were kids
and you were happy all the time.
Now that you're all grown up,
you're asking me that?
Why did I specifically
mention these two people?
That's because
they have some moral flaws.
They were obedient
when they were nobody.
But they got out of control
once they gained fame
and betrayed me.
It broke my heart
and made me suffer setbacks
in my vision of building
an entertainment empire.
Because of them, I realized
that betrayal is human nature.
It's all in the blood.
So I thought
if the weakness of human nature
can be removed,
they'll be at my disposal.
So you used the four of us
as a bargaining chip
to create Love Boys?
That's right.
At first,
I wanted to create virtual characters
without humanity.
But then I realized
to make Love Boys a success,
humanity is imperative.
That put me in a dilemma.
But soon,
I found the solution.
That is to design Love Boys
using real humans as prototypes,
writing emotional responses
into data and codes.
That way, real human emotional reactions
can be presented
in the interaction with the players.
To achieve this great plan,
I set my sights
on my newly born son.
Since he was a kid,
I have him strictly trained
to learn etiquette, culture,
music, dance, et cetera,
to make him a perfect man.
I strived to get a
perfect virtual character in Love Boys.
Shortly after,
I discovered that women
have strange needs for men.
All kinds of different needs.
But it can basically
be divided into four types.
Gentle, wise, outgoing, and obedient.
My son is the wise type.
So I found three other kids
who were about his age.
Lu Xiao.
Luo Ke.
Su Lie.
That's how the Y4 that
takes the world by storm is formed.
I bet you get the hint now, don't you?
Xu Nian, your real name is Xu Jin.
I'm your biological father.
That's impossible.
How could you possibly be my father?
Didn't you tell me
that my biological parents
abandoned me in the hospital
when I was born?
I lied to you.
It's impossible.
You're so young.
How could you possibly be my father?
You've been lying to me
all the years.
How can I believe you?
Kid.
What he said is true.
He's your biological father.
He's still in good shape.
Forever young and good looking.
I told you to cut down
the aesthetic treatments.
Now your son wouldn't even accept you.
Grandma Fushun,
why don't you go back first?
Who are you?
If you're not a member of the Xu family,
stay out of our family business.
Grandma, is he telling the truth?
Yes.
To be specific,
you should call me Great Aunt.
Aunty.
This isn't the time
for a family reunion.
Grandma Fushun.
If he's my father,
who's my mother?
Do you remember
that during one Mid-Autumn Festival
I played a movie for all of you?
The name of the movie is
"The Making of Female Stars".
Do you remember the story?
That movie
actually tells the true story
of your biological parents.
What do you need?
Sirloin steak medium rare.
Actually, I know who you are.
I've read news about you
and seen your interview on TV.
You're Mr. Xu Guanghan,
the top celebrity manager
who can turn an ordinary person
into a super star.
Right?
I have a friend who looks up to you.
She has sent a resume
to Yao Entertainment before
but didn't receive any reply.
So I wonder
if you could spare one minute for her?
Sure.
Really?
Thank you, Mr. Xu.
How can you dress like this at work?
How inappropriate!
I'm receiving complaints
from the customers.
I...
What? You're fired!
Get lost!
Don't talk to her that way.
From now on,
she works for Yao Entertainment.
It was a beautiful encounter.
But who would have known
what would happen later on?
You know what?
In the end, that girl
really became a super star.
(Universal Gilded Film Festival)
Lanlan, the audiences
are curious
about your relationship status.
Are you still single now?
Lanlan.
I heard that you
and the British actor, Eric,
have been secretly dating
for two months because of the drama.
Is it true?
Of course not.
We're just colleagues.
Behind the scenes, we're good friends.
(Film Star World)
Besides, I already have someone
that I like.
(Ge Yilan)
Someone she likes?
-Who is it?
-I have no idea.
I'm so curious.
(Ge Yilan)
Of course.
It's not convenient to reveal it
to you right now.
Lanlan, you're so open
about your relationship.
I bet something good is going to happen.
What's your plan?
Share with us.
Indeed, we have plans in motion.
Sorry.
Thank you, everyone.
It's about time.
We have to go inside now.
Thank you.
-Lanlan!
-Bye!
Lanlan, look over here!
Lanlan.
If I hadn't stopped you,
were you planning
to make our relationship public?
Why not?
We've been together for so long.
It's just a matter of time.
When did I ever say
that we were going public
for our relationship?
But we can't hide it forever.
Guanghan, I want to be with you
out in the public like normal people do.
Since you have chosen this industry,
you should understand
the freedom sacrificed
is the price we should pay.
You're a public figure.
The fantasy of the people.
Most importantly,
do you think we'll get their blessings
by going public?
You're being too naive. It won't happen.
Once your reputation
is subject to uncontrollable changes,
your career will be at stake.
But...
No buts.
We have put in so much effort
to get to where we are today.
It's your dream to become
the most popular female star
and it's what I hope for.
If you do this,
it's as good
as destroying everything that we have?
But it's too late now.
Not at all.
I've asked someone
to take down the interview.
We'll make a new recording.
Just do as I say.
Tell them that your love life is bleak.
You yearn for love,
but you just haven't met the right guy.
Guanghan.
That's not what I meant.
I...
I'm pregnant.
It's the third month of pregnancy now.
I knew you would be surprised.
When I first found out,
I was really scared.
But the thought
of this baby
being the fruit of our love,
it made me so full of courage.
So I'm giving birth to this baby.
I can quit the showbiz.
Guanghan,
I know you lacked family warmth
since you were a kid.
So let's have this baby.
You, him and I
can become a warm family. All right?
This isn't the time for a relationship.
Your schedule for the next year
is all full now.
We can't afford any mistakes.
The golden career period of a female star
is very short-lived.
It'll be gone if you miss it.
Follow my plan.
Do as I say.
Let's take care of this discreetly.
I think we have a week.
One week.
When Xu Guanghan
had everything arranged,
Ge Yilan suddenly disappeared.
When Xu Guanghan
found her,
it was half a year later.
That's when Ge Yilan
was about to give birth,
and Xu Guanghan made his move.
As soon as the baby was born,
he told Ge Yilan
that the baby was dead.
♪I'm sorry I admit♪
♪Every night I see you in my dreams♪
♪Dreams and reality become entangled♪
♪I can't tell them apart♪
♪You and I have different memories♪
♪As if we're searching
for the intersection♪
♪Piecing together the secrets
of the future♪
♪I'm falling hard♪
♪Draw a circle to encircle our hearts♪
♪A heart for a heart♪
♪Your favorite melody begins to play♪
♪In my mind♪
♪Beautiful memories
that belong only to us♪
♪Draw a circle to encircle our memories♪
♪Surrender our feelings to each other♪
♪Humming your favorite melody♪
♪Reminding you♪
♪Of the memories we shared♪