(Year 2008)
I'm done here.
How's it going on your end?
Wait a minute.
There's a bad connection.
Why still waiting?
I've set up over 20 bulbs!
Why aren't you done yet?
Okay. It's almost done.
Why are you taking so much time?
Let me do it. Stop arguing.
Quiet! I'm memorizing the script!
Seriously.
Glow of the sea
and what? And...
Wait. Glow of the sea...
And then what?
Don't you two already
know each other's feelings?
Why are you making
such a big deal out of it?
Because I want to give her
a formal confession.
Remember,
girls are very particular about this.
Don't be perfunctory, okay?
Got it.
Wait. Glow of the sea...
And then what?
She's here. Let's get out of here.
A sky full of stars...
Move the stuff.
This one.
Move the ladder!
Ladder!
And that one over there.
The box, and the ladder!
Put the ladder away.
Help him out.
Slippers. My slippers!
Watch out for the lights!
My slippers!
Why did you ask me to come here?
I... I have something to tell you.
What's it?
The mermaids in the night time
will make the glow of the sea and...
And...
Shut up. You're too loud.
Did you tie the balloons?
Shut up.
A sky full of stars...
Forget it.
It's a failure. We... Let's go.
Let's go.
There are balloons, flowers
and colored lights.
You're not trying
to confess your love to me, are you?
N... No.
You're not trying to confess to me?
No, I didn't mean that.
Actually, I've been waiting a long time.
This time,
I'll take the initiative.
Liao Zhibai,
will you
be my boyfriend?
- Be together!
=The Embers=
=Episode 24=
I brought you some food.
What's wrong?
I thought they said
he was getting better.
Why isn't he waking up?
Li Zhi, be honest,
looking at Yuan like this,
with pale lips
and bloodless skin,
do you feel like
you can't resist him?
Are you sick?
I read online
that this kind of persona
is popular nowadays,
called a sickly man.
You're sick, aren't you?
You're awake.
Now that you're awake,
let's give a statement.
You're sick too, aren't you?
Think carefully. Is there anything else?
No.
Okay. Nothing wrong with your brain.
Sign here.
There are two documents.
One on Gai De's sexual assault,
and one on
the physical abuse he inflicted on you.
By the way,
how is he now?
You got him?
I can't disclose it yet.
Ask Shu He when you get back.
If there's nothing else,
we'll go back to the station.
Let's go.
I bought your share.
Have some before you go.
That's cool.
Let's dig in.
Come on.
What's going on?
Qi Xia told me
to call her as soon as you woke up.
But I can't get through.
I guess she's busy.
There was a case this morning.
What case?
How do I know?
I was here watching over you, wasn't I?
Early this morning,
a man's body was found at
the intersection of Yumanfeng Expressway
and Qianning Expressway.
The body was identified as the suspect
in the Liao family's fire
in Yong'an Village ten years ago,
who came back from the dead,
Liao Zhibai.
(One hour after Liao Zhibai's death)
Xia.
I know you're worried about me.
I'm fine.
Get the body out there.
Prepare for autopsy.
Let me do it.
Same as the preliminary,
there are water stains on the clothes,
residual soil and watercress.
Soak them for samples.
Okay.
Stab wounds,
gunshot wounds,
and strangulation marks...
What have you been through
in the last ten years?
Xia,
why don't we report this
to our superiors
and get another forensic pathologist
to do this?
No need.
I thought
he'd tell me
everything that's happened
over the years,
one by one, one day.
I just didn't expect it
to be this way.
Liao Zhibai...
I'll listen to every word...
you leave behind carefully.
The autopsy's over.
Call his family
to come and claim him.
Okay.
Zhibai,
you've kept me waiting again.
I really don't understand
why you chose this path.
But it's okay.
It's all coming to an end.
Let's go home.
(Three hours after Liao Zhibai's death)
Xia.
Why don't you sign it?
(Liao Zhibai's Death Certificate)
Can...
I sign it?
You're his family too.
Why not?
How did you convince them
to let me sign?
It's clearly against the rules.
I didn't say anything.
I told them
to let you sign it once,
and I'll sign it again later.
I knew it.
Anyway, thank you.
Siyuan,
my name
is finally
on a piece of paper
with a red seal, together with his.
It's not quite what I thought before
but
we're at least related,
right?
I think I've said goodbye to him
many times.
During the autopsy,
I wondered
if he would
suddenly jump out of nowhere
and tell me with a smile on his face,
"Look,
I fooled you again."
I think so too.
He's a
selfish,
bigoted man.
He's using human life
as a bargaining chip.
I can't believe
a man like that
just died.
He won't die for nothing.
As Shu He said,
he must have his own intentions.
He wanted his body
as the final piece of evidence.
Not only did he not take
other people's lives seriously,
but also his own.
I'm glad I didn't marry him.
He was just
so cruel.
(POLICE)
(Five hours after Liao Zhibai's death)
He turned himself voluntarily?
Yes.
Not only did he turn himself in,
he reported a crime,
and he gave evidence
that Na Wei was the real culprit
in the fire ten years ago.
And then what?
See for yourself.
He couldn't be wrong.
If he's turning himself in,
he must be certain of what he's doing.
Something must have gone wrong.
Where's Na Wei now?
There's no evidence.
He's released.
He's released?
Hello.
The autopsy report is out.
The murder took place
between 12 to 2 AM last night.
According to the physical evidence,
the first dump site
should be the river
next to Yong'an Village.
The body sank in the water.
It's a logical way
for a person to commit a crime.
However, the body
appeared at an intersection
with many people.
It's obvious
that it's not the murderer's work.
How did my brother
leave the police station?
At 9 PM last night,
we were working late at the office
when the power
in the station suddenly went out.
Liao Zhibai was taken away
at that time.
It's a serious incident
when a suspect
was taken away from a police station.
We immediately accessed
all the CCTV footage
and targeted this man.
He first tasered an office,
took the key,
and took Liao Zhibai away.
Does this man look familiar to you?
I don't know,
but he knows the inside
of the police station very well,
and cleverly avoided
many surveillance cameras,
leaving only this back figure.
There's a mole.
Director has ordered us
to investigate ourselves.
Everyone is a suspect.
Do you have a copy
of last night's shift log?
We've been working overtime
because of the Liao Zhibai's case,
and no one has taken leave.
There were backup lights
in the office last night
when the power went out.
I didn't see anyone leave.
Ni Ke wasn't here.
He's working out of the station.
Ni Ke?
I called him twice in between.
He's clear.
Two calls? What time?
One at 9:08 PM,
and the other at 9:25 PM.
9:08 PM...
9:25 PM...
Ni Ke, you're finally back.
What took you so long?
I'm starving.
They ran out of pineapple rice,
so they cooked it fresh.
I waited for a while.
(22:32 PM)
No, Ni Ke's lying.
He just got back at 10:30 PM,
so he must not have been
at the hospital at 9:30 PM.
Chief Shu, Director wants you to go
to his office when you have time.
Have you seen Ni Ke?
No. Hasn't he been out
of the station these days?
Okay, I'll be there later.
Shu He,
we need to find him as soon as possible.
If we don't, I'm afraid
he'll be silenced.
He's a veteran.
If he really wants to hide,
it's not that easy to find him.
I'll report to Director.
They're taking the open path.
We can't do nothing.
Do you have an idea?
(Good Luck Restaurant)
So this is where
your brother lived before?
Since Shen Congxin's incident,
they've moved out.
I'm here to look for clues,
to see if I can find Gan and Tai.
He lived in such a humid place,
so no wonder he's so sick
and couldn't get well.
Something's wrong.
I saw Bai Han withdraw money from here.
If they really moved out,
why leave a locked safe?
Hello, Mom.
Okay, we'll go back now.
(Qi's Pharmacy, Healing hands
as warm as the spring breeze)
Ms. Meihua,
you called to say something important
had happened at home.
What's going on?
You two
are hiding everything from me.
If I hadn't told you
there was an emergency at home,
would you have come back?
Mom, please don't be like this.
We've got work to do.
Jin,
what did you find out?
I got it.
Ni Ke's at the docks right now.
He's going
to follow the smugglers' boats
out of Buhe at night.
Ni Ke?
I've watched all the news.
Zhibai disappeared
from the police station.
Someone in the police force
must have a problem.
I got word
that the fat guy
had been selling houses and land,
and I felt something was wrong,
so I asked Jin to ask around.
I'll inform Shu He.
I'll come with you.
Siyuan.
I know
you've been through a lot lately.
You must be in a state of confusion.
As I said,
whatever troubles you're facing,
I'm here for you.
I'm your strong support.
Thanks, Mom.
Are you the one
who wants to take the boat?
The police have surrounded this place.
The whole force is out there.
You can't get away.
Shu He,
don't force me.
I didn't want to do this,
but I didn't have a choice.
Let me go and see my family.
Stop walking forward!
I'm unarmed.
Shu He,
I know I can't talk to you
about friendship right now.
But we've been partners
for a long time,
so it's kind of a bond.
Let me go to find my family.
They're abroad.
I haven't seen them for a long time.
Why do you smile?
I remember
that you received me on my first day
at the police station.
They told me you were a veteran
and that I should learn from you.
But I was so proud of myself
that I said yes,
but all I could think was,
"Who is he?
I'll make him my deputy one day."
Then you took me on cases and arrests
and I realized this veteran
was something.
You're my superior now.
Why are you still talking about this?
I've been wondering,
but now I know.
You're hiding your flaws
because you're afraid
and you don't dare to show them.
I don't dare?
Believe it or not,
I'll shoot you right now.
I don't believe it.
It's not that you don't dare.
You just wouldn't.
Come out with me now
and you'll be considered
to have turned yourself in.
You lied to me again.
I made a bet with Liao Siyuan and Qi Xia
that you wouldn't kill me.
If I win, they'll buy me a meal.
He can save money this time.
There's one less big eater.
I'm still not used to it.
We used to sit over there together.
When you first started your internship,
I sat on the left.
Then you became chief
and you sat on the left.
I never thought
one day...
One day, we'd sit face-to-face.
I'm not used to it either.
Don't waste time. Ask away.
How did you take Liao Zhibai away?
Around 8 PM that night,
I was at the hospital,
but I got a phone call out of the blue.
Na Wei called me.
(Six hours before Liao Zhibai's death)
I'm going to get a bite to eat
in the neighborhood.
Ni Ke,
when you come back,
can you bring me a pineapple rice?
Sure.
Are you crazy?
Liao Zhibai is in the police station,
and there are eyes everywhere.
I can't do this.
Don't worry.
I won't let him die in jail.
All you have to do is getting him out
of the police station
without anyone knowing.
I'll say it again.
I can't do this.
You can do this.
I know you want to live in peace.
All these years,
I haven't bothered you.
But something done can't be undone.
Do you really want
to pretend it didn't happen?
What do you mean?
Everyone wants to live in peace.
But Liao Zhibai is a time bomb.
He won't stop
until everyone is blown up.
If what happened ten years ago
really came to light,
you and I wouldn't be able
to live in peace.
It's only when it's finished
that no one will talk
about what happened back then.
I'll arrange for you to go abroad.
If I don't say yes,
I can't get out of this house?
You've got to be kidding me.
I'm a law-abiding citizen.
But what will happen
when you get out of here?
Do you think you can really live?
I don't need to go abroad.
I don't need you to arrange it.
But I only have one request.
Don't touch my family.
Your call,
officer.
Two hours later,
the street behind the police station.
One more thing,
the pen that Liao Zhibai used
to frame me
should be useless, right?
Can you bring it out for me?
After I left his place,
I snuck back to the station,
cut off the electricity
and found Liao Zhibai.
You're here.
In fact, I had prepared some drugs.
But he seemed
to know I was coming.
He didn't resist at all.
Then I handed Liao Zhibai
over to Tie Xin.
The police's emergency power system
has been activated.
They'll soon realize he's gone.
You're on your own.
Besides,
don't come to me anymore.
It's not up to me.
Thanks.
(Shu He)
(Simulate hospital
ambient sound to the voice call?)
(Shu He)
(Calling)
Hello, Chief.
The power's out at the police station?
I'm fine here.
Everything's fine.
Don't worry, I'm here.
Okay.
Ni Ke, you're finally back.
What took you so long?
I'm starving.
They ran out of pineapple rice,
so they cooked it fresh.
I waited for a while.
That's weird.
So many police cars
are running around at night.
Did something happen?
I'll know if anything happens.
Just eat. It's all right.
I got back to the hospital
after 10:30 PM.
I don't know anything
after that.
Do you regret it?
Yes, I do.
What else did you do for Na Wei?
The Liao family's fire
in Yong'an Village ten years ago,
Ti Yi's case and Lang Sang's case.
That's all.
Did you take the surveillance camera
that Liao Zhibai found in the bar?
It's me.
Why?
What else could it be?
Because I'm poor.
People like us
risk our lives out there all day long,
not spending any time at home.
Is it easy for a wife
to bring up a child
on her own?
My child is growing up,
and he likes more and more things.
How can I give him?
What can I give him?
That's when Na Wei approached me.
He knew I was short of money,
so he asked me to work with him.
He said I didn't have
to do anything unusual,
just to not investigate anything.
For ten years I've been reminding myself
not to think about those things,
to stop thinking about those things.
As long as I'm a good person
and do my job well,
no one will know about those things,
and I'll still be a good police.
But Na Wei is right.
Something done
can't be undone.
There's still a chance
if you turn state's evidence.
I'll plead for you in court.
It's no use.
Take my advice.
You can't fight him.
That's not something
a police should say.
Shu He,
I never begged you, did I?
Just one thing.
Can you not tell my son?
He bragged to his classmates at school
that his dad was a great police.
I thought so too.
(Eight hours after Liao Zhibai's death)
♪The night stretches long,
like an endless hallway♪
♪Without moonlight
or a god to guide the way♪
♪Memories drip
within the center of my heart♪
♪Burning you away,
leaving only emptiness♪
♪The distorted truth♪
♪Is tampered with,
buried, and forgotten♪
♪Beyond the embers,
the wound remains warm♪
♪It lights up again♪
♪Whose hands♪
♪Are pulling the strings?♪
♪Who stands at the end of the lie?♪
♪Behind the mask♪
♪Whose softness♪
♪Has decayed?♪
♪Lift the dust, feel it with your soul♪
♪The chains of destiny
have long bound us♪
♪To each other♪
♪If you don't die, I won't stop♪
♪Let's witness together♪
♪The end♪