♫ There's a mood I can't describe  ♫
♫ I can't face it or avoid it ♫
♫ I can only stand there and watch him leave ♫
♫ I can hear the sound of my heart breaking ♫
♫ Because he made us both fall in love ♫
♫ I'm willing to give up for the sake of our friendship ♫
♫ I don't want to see him hurt or suffer any more ♫
♫ His tears make my heart ache ♫
♫ Love makes us all fearless ♫
♫ Being able to protect him is my happiness ♫
♫ The realm of love only allows for two people ♫
♫ Please love him well for me ♫
Yan Yuewu, if you dare to do anything to Xiangshi, I will be after your whole family.
I'm late.
Not really. We were having ramen.
-Ramen after sex?
-No, just eating.
What's that on your neck?
Oh, I did that on accident.
Yan Yuewu, what did you do to Xiangshi?
She was just drunk. She was only playing.
Look how nervous you are. Other people would think you are here to catch him cheating on you.
Nothing happened between us.
Don't worry, Xiaoshi and I are into different things.
We are both tops.
My head hurts from rolling around. Didn't even get to do anything.
So you guys were half way there?
As long as I didn't get to enjoy it, it doesn't count.
Stop yelling.
We are leaving. Goodbye. Let's go.
Bye. See you next time.
Yang Xianghsi, be honest with me.
Were you guys really just did half of it?
Nothing. We were only playing.
What's with the hickie then?
She was drunk at first.
Then, she sobered up and we had food. That's it.
-You are lying to me.
-I smelled perfume on you last time.
You guys did go on a date,
but you were lying and said you were fixing her computer.
-I didn't.
-How many times are you going to lie to me?
Say it.
-What are you doing?
-What are you going to do?
I've always been the one backing down when you get angry.
Not this time.
-You pushed me.
-That's right. I pushed you.
Do you really think you can fight me?
-Let go of me.
-No! You are mine!
I'm not.
You eat here, and you sleep here. My family owns you.
That's right. I eat here and I sleep here.
But it doesn't mean that I'm a pet dog here.
Goodbye.
Yang Xiangshi.
What?
I'm sorry. Please don't leave, ok? Stay.
I said the wrong thing.
Thanks for reminding me of my status here.
I'm a grown-up now.
I should be gone.
Don't go. Come back.
I'm...I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have hurt you like that.
I'm sorry.
It was all because
that I need you so much.
I'm sorry.
Please move, Lord Yuan. I need to go to work.
Come home with me.
It's proven through my DNA that
I am not related to the Yuan family. Why are you asking me to go home with you?
My dad has agreed to adopt you.
Thanks, but I don't want to be adopted by you guys.
Why not? You get lots of money as my brother.
You don't have to go to work anymore.
I don't want money. I want my freedom.
Freedom?
That's right.
I can live freely and ride freely.
I get to love freely.
Love freely.
So you want to be in love.
With anyone?
Of course.
How can I love freely if I'm your brother?
Either a guy or a girl?
Anyone.
Even guys or girls.
If that so.
What if it's with me?
-Sure.
-Really?
No, I was saying that.
So you want to be in love with me, right?
What are you talking about?
Or else,
why don't you want to be my brother?
Eh.
I was
saying that
there are too many rules to be part of the Yuan family.
And it's not a lot of freedom.
Eh.
I just want to be myself.
Why are you taking a shower this early, Yan Yuerong?
What?
Tell you what.
I was so close to having sex with Yang Xiangshi yesterday.
But Yuan Jundao
treated him like a boy toy.
He looked like he was going to eat me alive if I touch Xiangshi.
I can't stand him.
Hey, lend me your shampoo.
Sister Yuewu.
The third son of, Yuan Junping.
Wow.
Your skin is so fair.
You are also in good shape
and good-looking.
No wonder you are so popular at school.
Sister Yuewu.
Could you not look at me like that?
I'm a little afraid.
What are you afraid of?
-Are you afraid that I'm going to eat you?
-Sister!
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Sister,
you scared Yuan Junping
-when you sneaked in like that.
-So what?
-At least knock.
-But I'm always like that.
However,
why is Yuan Junping taking a shower in our house?
We were playing basketball, so I let him shower here.
Hey, Junping.
I'm sorry.
Sister Yuewu, I'm sorry. I should've locked the door.
It's ok. It's nice to leave the door unlocked.
Sit. Sit.
Also,
I heard you mentioning my second brother when I was in the shower.
Even though I don't know what he did, I apologize for him to you.
He can be dumb sometimes.
I hope you don't mind.
It's ok. You apologized for him already. I will not mind.
It's ok. It's ok.
What?
I think Yuan Junping is quite nice.
You are good friends with him. Why don't you help your sister?
Hey, that's so sudden.
What's so sudden?
Love is very sudden.
It reminds me of a song.
♫ Love comes so fast, like wind. ♫
You shouldn't stay here for too long.
♫ There's no time to react.♫
Hey, Yan Yuerong.
Yan Yuerong, why are you running away so fast?
I'm so tired.
A bun.
It smells delicious.
No.
Why is there a feast here?
Stop eating buns.
Come on, have a good meal.
Mr. Yuancheng.
When are you going to stop stalking me?
Didn't I tell you that
I'm not going to be your family's adopted son?
I know.
You want freedom. The freedom to love.
-So you know.
-But you still have to eat.
Let's eat.
No.
If I eat this well, what am I going to do when I get used to it?
Don't worry.
I will feed you with good food every day,
as long as you work for me.
10,000 per hour.
-10,000?
-Yes. Ok?
No. No way.
No prey was ever
able to run away from me.
I'm standing right in front of you.
Why don't you just get it over with? I prefer it's just one shot.
Have you ever seen a prey making the hunter take the shot?
I don't want to die. I want you alive.
Why aren't you making sense?
Have you asked me if I want to be your prey?
Have you ever heard of a hunter asking for a prey's permission?
What do you want?
I have nothing valuable on me.
What, you want my body?
Do you like guys?
I don't know. I've never tried.
What...
what about you?
I never tried it either.
The first thing they taught me in the family is how to be immune to love.
What are you smiling about?
If you want to try it, I can do it with you.
I'm not afraid of any challenges in this world.
I didn't say yes to it.
Is it your Chinese sucks, or is it my Korean sucks?
You must be hungry.
Go have some dinner.
I will take you to eat something else tomorrow.
Wait a second.
I might not like what you think is delicious.
I have to find it delicious.
Really?
What do you like to eat?
Why are you asking it? Are you going to eat with me tomorrow?
-Yes.
Ok.
Then you eat whatever I eat.
Ok. I'm not afraid of it.
Ok.
There's a great street food joint next to my place.
Let's go try it tomorrow?
Street food?
Where are the keys?
Why are you touching me?
What are you doing?
Did something really happen last night?
Yuan Juncheng.
How do you know if two guys had sex or not?
♫
♫  In those times, be still ♫
♫  At this point, I cannot give up ♫
♫ It's not the end ♫
♫ We can start again ♫
♫ I'll have no regrets ♫
♫  I will tell my story again ♫
♫  I will run on this path ♫
♫  that I've chosen ♫