Episode 8
What's this?
We're the ones who are blinded. Why are you all so upset?
It's a huge sum of money.
If we go over there, it'll be even worse.
Let's turn the car around.
But where are we going if we don't go home?
We can't go to the hotel in the meantime.
Yes, Grace.
Madam, there's no one at the back door.
Come this way.
You're the only one here. Okay?
Turn the car around. Let's go to the back door.
What did she say? She's coming?
Make a work.
A rich family being chased away by beggars.
She's coming!
What are you doing? Why didn't you open the door?
Madam, you should get out for a bit.
What's wrong? I'm tired.
The will that Chairman Hong wrote to Madam Mo
is that she's threatening to take care of
her own family and Queen's Town.
So?
Is that what she's trying to do to drive us all out?
It's not that she's trying to drive us out.
She's already got reporters and the protestors.
So she's telling us to stay away until things calm down...
Does Madam Mo have the right to do that?
We're all living together.
Will you shut up?
Were you talking to the adults?
What did you just say, Grace?
My gosh.
You're so bad at understanding situations.
The car, driver, phone, and credit card.
That's all.
The company's security key and the security key
won't work either.
What are you talking about?
Why can't you go into my house?
Call the police right now.
Yes, I will.
The reporters must love you so much.
I've packed my things
thinking about Junghoo.
So let's go.
Darn it.
Get in! There's a camera on the other side.
Is this even possible, Baek Seob-ah?
You're locking up my father's house
and making us come in here.
Is it even possible for us to leave?
As a co-habitant, I can claim the right.
But we must sue the person who filed the lawsuit.
It will take time.
More importantly,
the chairman is using his power as a special agent
to support his family.
So all the assets of real estate, stocks,
and personal accounts are locked up.
Father.
Is that true, honey?
I just found out. My lips are burning.
The person with the lip balm...
Stop talking about lip balms.
It's not good to keep posting photos
to the press because of the reporters.
It's best to stay in a safe place
and find a way to do that.
Is Sucheol a real estate agent or what?
Hey, Sucheol! What did you say?
So your wife,
the one from the Seonda family, was also a co-habitant?
What did I say?
Geon-woo said Sucheol doesn't look like him at all!
Auntie.
But where is he going?
Oh...
What?
What is it?
Oh, no.
It's a private property.
What?
Hey, Hyeon-u!
What are you doing here at this hour?
Dad, I was in a rush.
Hey, Baek Hyeon-u!
Why aren't you answering your phone?
Hey, you...
You don't even have money to buy food.
What's with your face?
No, it's not that...
It's not that.
That crazy jerk's house is a success.
Look. The one you left behind is a failure.
It's a science to be a human.
Wait.
Of course.
I was so upset when I saw the news
that the house was ruined.
It was so sad.
Anyway, you just have to forget about that
crazy jerk and live your life comfortably.
You're here with me.
Crazy jerk.
Oh.
You're here.
You... You're here even more.
My goodness.
Oh, my.
Is that your ex-husband?
Anyway, how did you get here?
Oh, yes.
How have you been?
Yes, say hello.
Hello.
I'm sorry for the sudden visit, Father.
No, it's okay.
Thank you for coming.
Let's go inside.
I'm going to Seoul.
Call a cab.
Mom.
There's no cab in this neighborhood.
I'll go alone, so you guys can do whatever you want.
Honey.
Why did you come all the way here?
That's why I told you I wasn't coming.
Gosh, you!
Oh.
What's wrong with her?
I think she's having an affair.
Don't come near me.
Why is she coming after me?
Look at this.
Young Master.
I'm sorry.
It's going to get wet.
Hey, Yeon-woo.
It's warm.
We have to rely on this situation.
Why did you drag your family here?
I don't think so.
Even though the man's armor is split,
the Korean Peninsula is shaking in the Olympics.
What do you mean?
It's also a conglomerate.
Then we can put the re-unification in place.
The Korean Peninsula is shaking.
It's not that easy to reunite, Dad.
Let's get ready.
What?
Thank you for today.
I'll find out when I go.
I'm going tomorrow.
There's no way the situation will change tomorrow.
I know.
So you can't stay here anymore.
It'll take a while to get better.
This is the safest and most comfortable place right now.
I'm not comfortable.
How can a divorced husband's home be comfortable?
I'm comfortable with myself.
I'll just think about myself for now.
I have so much to do right now,
but I can't even worry about you.
Don't worry about me.
Divorced people don't do that.
Whether I'm ruined or not,
no matter what happens to my family,
it has nothing to do with you.
I don't care when you're doing well.
I can't do that right now.
So you can look at me.
Just stay in front of me.
This is ridiculous.
Would we be happy to be together?
I'm going to be less unhappy.
Let's not think about anything else today.
Let's try to be less unhappy.
I'm going to be less unhappy.
What's wrong?
You look good.
Put this on first.
What should I do with those two?
Just throw them away.
What?
You're going to throw them away?
You're going to keep them?
I think it's going to be expensive.
Isn't it over 50?
500.
I didn't come here because I wanted to.
No one can tell how fast your son is.
He's almost like a kidnapper.
My mother, who passed away, didn't say anything wrong.
She said she wasn't always sure about life.
Who knew that she'd meet him after working for a few days?
Why did my sister go there?
She's telling me to come to the villa right now.
She's going to leave me alone.
Yes, go.
But don't drink it.
Excuse me.
Are you Seosik?
Yes.
It's delicious.
Is it okay to eat?
Yes, it's really good.
Please eat a lot.
I told you to reduce the consumption.
If you know Dr. Yoon, it's going to be a mess.
Stop eating.
Don't worry.
Dr. Yoon didn't even answer my phone.
I think he's looking for me.
Why don't you eat like this?
I'm sorry.
I don't have an appetite.
Do you have water?
Water, water, water.
I don't drink water that's sealed.
Do you have water?
Hey, just eat it.
No, no.
I'll bring you the water.
Thank you.
I'd like mineral water from Alps.
What? Alps?
You're really...
I'm sorry.
My son is immature.
Oh, no, no.
That's possible.
You don't have to go to Alps.
Germany or Australia is fine.
Switzerland is good, too.
We really don't mind that.
I'd like some of that.
Just drink the water from the tap.
Give it to me.
You're not doing that to me.
My sister is beating me up, right?
It was so scary.
What are you talking about?
You beat me up like that, too.
Hey, my hands aren't that hot.
But Honghae is...
Shall I help you?
No, no.
You don't have to.
Go and rest.
But the all-you-can-eat...
I can call it all-you-can-eat.
I don't have a proper name.
Do whatever you want.
Don't like what I said earlier.
What did you say?
What about the bad guy?
I don't hate bad guys.
I was a bad guy in high school.
I'm a fox.
I'm sorry for saying that earlier.
You're not wrong.
You're screwed.
It's a careful thing to say,
but you two got divorced,
but you came all the way here.
Is it a heart signal?
No, we just came in a hurry.
That's all.
Right, you're a man now.
I can't do better than a man.
But is there something between you two?
There's nothing.
Oh, there's nothing.
If there was something,
we wouldn't have split up.
That's right.
You're right.
So I hope you don't misunderstand,
expect, or make any other mistakes.
I won't.
I told you last time.
Soyeong is the daughter of the principal's teacher.
She's a teacher now,
but she got a V-Met at Eumne Middle School.
You keep asking me for Hyunwoo's number.
It's not like I can tell you.
Please tell me.
Is that okay?
I don't need permission.
Then good-bye.
I knew it.
I shouldn't have brought her here.
Hey,
you're so rude.
You're so rude that you cut me off.
You're so rude.
Why did you come to my house?
This is my house.
Before my eldest son and daughter got married,
I lived here.
I'll keep the fire going.
You're paying for this?
Oh, my.
Don't say that.
I know the reason why you're here.
I know it's a problem,
but we were once family.
I heard from Hyunwoo
that you shouldn't tell anyone about this place.
I told the villagers not to work on the Internet.
I told them not to work.
There's no CCTV here.
The phone's battery is at its lowest level.
Don't worry about anything.
Have a good night's sleep.
Thank you so much.
Oh, my. You're so cold.
You can wash here.
Where's the bathtub?
There's no bathtub.
Here.
In the shower booth.
In the shower booth?
Where's the bath tub?
I don't use it.
Where's the bath bomb?
I'll use it as a towel.
Didn't you say your nephew's name was Ho Yeori?
That's right. Baek Ho Yeol.
No way.
The baby Ho Yeol isn't the baby Ho Yeol we saw earlier, right?
Yes, there were times like this.
He was so cute.
Yes, that's right. Baek Ho Yeol.
It's that Ho Yeol.
How many years has it been?
What's wrong?
Should I get you a new towel?
Hae Young.
What I don't believe more than this towel that's been eight years old is that
right now, Da Hae and Geon-woo aren't by my side.
That bastard, Yoon Eun-sung, is going to trick me and make fun of me.
What happened?
Where did you send the family members of this house?
You're here.
Where did Hae-in's family go?
I don't know.
They probably didn't go anywhere.
Why did you do that?
So you want to live here together?
You can live with people who took everything from you
and look at each other's faces in one house.
It's not over yet.
They're going to try to get this side of the drug somehow
and try to find a secret to attack.
You'd rather leave them...
You just want to leave Hae-in by your side, don't you?
Forget it.
There's no trace of her after it's over.
It's a waste of regret.
I've lived in this house for 25 years.
It's the first time I've chosen wine that I want to drink.
Let's enjoy life while enjoying the things we enjoy.
Okay?
You sent me to the orphanage, didn't you?
Don't forget.
I love you the most in the world.
That's why I'll endure it.
I'll endure it even if I want to see you
and even if I want to be with you.
I'll endure it because I love you.
You kept your promise well.
You endured it very well, didn't you?
I'm sure you know how a young son
lives after meeting someone in a faraway country.
You didn't even ask or contact me.
But after trying it,
you said you'd endure it because you love me.
That's all a lie.
You can't endure it...
if you really love me.
What do you want to say?
Do you want to come back and blame me?
No.
I'm saying I'll bring you home no matter what.
I'm different from you.
I'm going crazy just imagining
what you're doing with someone.
I...
can't stand it.
I came all the way here with so much difficulty.
Why did I come all the way here?
I have a different goal from you.
So just like how you abandoned me
and chose this family,
I can also abandon you
and choose something else.
I'm sorry.
Search the hotel and find a place to go.
This is hell.
What kind of hell would you go to to lay a bed?
The floor is warm.
Even if you abandon me,
will you still be able to deceive me?
What?
This is the first time
that Sucheol has slept on the floor.
If it wasn't for the Spanish royal bed,
I wouldn't have been able to lie down.
My blanket looks softer than that of Sucheol's.
Let's change this.
Honey.
Why?
This is my first time too.
This is my first time sleeping on the floor.
I'm also a second generation.
Hello?
Geumhui.
I saw the news.
What did everyone say?
It's a mess.
Geumhui, what do we do about my father?
Let's cut the talk about your father.
Why are you doing this to me?
Don't you remember what he said?
He told you not to come even if you die.
So don't call me even if he dies.
Geumhui, don't do this to me.
I hated him so much when he was a good father.
But now that things have turned out this way,
I'm getting into so many things.
What do you mean?
Geumhui.
If I had been nice to her,
I would've been able to live with her.
Maybe I was too mean to her
and she went crazy.
About 10 years ago,
I was so mad when my father got married to her.
So my father gave up.
He could've gotten so mad and done this.
I should've given this ring to Geumhui.
Should I just give it to her?
Should I just give it to her now?
Geumhui.
I'm sorry for everything that happened to my father.
Why are you crying?
Did your husband leave?
No?
Then are your parents sick?
Yes.
My father is sick.
When your parents are sick,
I think of all the things I did wrong.
Cry.
Cry and grow up well.
Everything will be fine.
Thank you.
Mom.
What is it?
There's a crazy guy in my neighborhood.
He keeps following me around saying I'm his mom.
Tell him he's my daughter.
Mom.
Why are you out here all night?
Excuse me.
This is my mom.
So you should go.
What did you say?
I'm his daughter.
Go.
Isn't she from Seoul?
She's my mom.
She's my mom!
Mom, aren't you going to watch a drama?
A drama?
I should watch it. I should watch a drama.
Let's go.
What is this?
Baekhyun's taste is pretty similar to mine.
Are you sleeping?
I'm going to sleep now. Why?
I have to leave early tomorrow.
I can't see my face.
I'm going to work early tomorrow.
When do you think you'll be off work?
I don't know.
Aren't you going on a day off tomorrow?
Can't I take a day off tomorrow?
Good night.
I'm going to sleep listening to music at the MPC.
Oh, that? Is it worth listening to?
It's all old songs.
It's just my taste.
I like all the songs.
But that's not mine.
Then?
I gave it to you before, but you didn't find the owner.
So I got it.
Where did you give it?
At the school playground in high school.
I gave it to you because you didn't find the owner.
At the school playground.
Didn't you say you came out of the sky?
I did.
I died on the first day of transfer.
What?
That was this?
Wait.
That was Baek Hyunho?
That's ridiculous.
Wait.
Is Baek Hyunho a guy who likes me?
He fell in love with me in that short moment
and kept this until now.
If he knew that I was the woman he fell in love with,
he would have fainted.
I'm sorry.
Why do you still have this?
I guess she was really pretty.
What?
I...
You don't have it?
Of course not.
It's from a long time ago.
I know.
But the fact that she still has it
means that the impact she gave was that strong.
She must have been really pretty.
What impact?
I don't remember if the owner was a man or a woman,
a teacher, a student, or a man in the water.
I don't remember anything.
Then why did you keep it?
I didn't keep it.
I just left it with the lock.
Okay.
Go.
Go and sleep.
What now?
I'll sleep with the curtains on.
It's a bit snowy in the morning
because it's the East.
Okay, so get out.
I'm sorry.
I guess I'm left with something that keeps coming to mind
I like you more
I like you
Do you need my help?
Sure.
I'm going to make japchae.
Cut some carrots.
Okay.
Baby, you need to cut carrots instead of fingers.
You need to cut them thinly.
How thin?
How exactly do you want me to cut them?
That's...
So...
Give it to me.
What?
Mother.
Yes?
You're really good.
What's so great about this?
What do you mean?
This is like modern art.
Really?
Oh, my.
I've never heard of this before.
You said you were going to make japchae.
What else do I need to do next?
Next, I need to make egg garnish.
How do you do that?
Garnish?
Do you want to see it in action?
I'm looking forward to it.
You're amazing.
You need to do it with both hands.
Oh, my.
Mother, you're so amazing.
Amazing?
Should I make you go crazy?
Crazy?
Do you really believe in your mother?
What's wrong with you?
You said you were going to make a fortune.
Why?
Do you hate your brother-in-law?
You're afraid he'll get in trouble if he finds out
that we're there?
That's funny.
Who helped you when you were in trouble?
I'm a woman too, but how could I do this to him?
Forget it.
You were here.
I looked everywhere for you.
Why me?
This is clean now.
It doesn't smell and it's fine.
Really?
If it's okay, I'll buy it.
It's expensive, but how can you buy it for free?
It's really okay.
Take it.
Then should I do your hair?
I'm good at it.
What style would you like?
What style can I do?
Anything.
I used to work at a hair salon in Cheongdam-dong.
Mi Seon, what's going on?
I've never been this upset since the sixth sense.
I'm sweating like crazy.
I heard you were there when I was cursing at you.
Is this a movie or a drama?
It's more fun than the ending of a drama.
So what happened?
You two can talk later.
I heard that crazy woman, Yein's mom, is here.
What are you talking about?
She didn't say anything.
Go away.
I don't want to go.
I heard everything from my husband.
He stepped on my poop, yelled, and cried.
He was so upset.
That's amazing.
How could he step on my poop?
I'm the one who stepped on your poop.
Right.
You're not my son-in-law, but my son-in-law.
I'm so embarrassed.
I was so embarrassed that I was going to take it.
I heard you were a total beggar.
Your mom is so talkative.
She's so kind.
Okay.
That woman is so mean.
She did something wrong.
How could she move here?
Right.
I really want to see her face.
Me, too.
What?
Did you get your lips stained?
Look.
Please join us.
AOMG New Peking Entertainment City 772772.
You said you wanted to see my face.
What?
My fortune is tied to the president for a while.
It's not a lie.
I'm not a wild slave.
It's night now.
And I'm going to go.
So I'm not a fool.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Seriously.
How could you eat me?
Excuse me.
Ko Sik.
You didn't have breakfast?
I'm going to the washroom at the department store.
The bean noodles are so savory and delicious.
Would you like some?
I didn't eat carbs this morning.
What a jerk.
When did he eat carbs this morning?
You're the president of the world's youngest group.
Please tell us how you feel.
How are you going to lead the group?
Is there any discrimination
or discrimination in the philosophy of the younger generation?
There's a saying that there will be
a global structure.
Is that true?
How is the health of the younger generation?
We're going to establish a Singaporean law firm
by 2025 to establish a national center
for the establishment of the country
by opening up the overseas market
and establishing a national center.
It's a plan to establish a Singaporean law firm
by 2025.
and use the money to run the law firm.
It's a plan to use about $1.4 billion.
I went to see Mr. Song and talked to him.
He didn't know about the non-funds.
He did the non-funds in Korea and overseas,
but he didn't know the final destination.
Does that make sense?
The non-funds were also written in the office
and sent to Mr. Hong.
The money laundering process
was a complicated process that took more than 10 countries.
The last one was in the Malaysian Laos.
But it wasn't there.
You called me, Mr. Song?
Isn't that sound too easy to hear?
There's no reason for it to be difficult.
The situation has changed.
I'm no longer the son-in-law of the King's,
and I'm no longer the husband of the CEO of the company.
I see.
But what can I do?
I'm uncomfortable with you being the department head.
You can do that. I understand.
Baek Hyeon-woo.
Stop acting.
I think you know everything,
so I won't lie to you anymore.
I'm waiting.
I've put Baek Hwa, Taepung, and Hwang Hyeon-kim
in three places.
I'm negotiating my salary,
but this is the case.
There's a big difference between when I'm working
and when I'm not.
As you know, I didn't get anything
from the negotiation between Hae-in and Lee Hyeon-woo,
so I have to do well this time.
I think it'll take about a month.
Can I ask for your understanding?
So you're preparing for a second term?
Yes.
But I'm not allowed to enter the confidential documents
of the legal team,
so you won't have to worry.
Go ahead.
Where are you?
Hae-in.
Isn't it Baek Hyeon-woo who took you out yesterday?
Where is he now?
I don't know.
You don't know where he went after taking him out?
That's right.
I don't know if he doesn't trust me,
but he just took the car and left.
He's not answering his phone.
If you know where he is,
please share it with me.
Okay.
Hae-in.
But this car is owned by my wife.
You look much better in it.
You look great in that outfit.
It's fancy, elegant, and not easy to lose.
This is why I didn't dress up.
It's too obvious if I touch it.
Please come before I clean up the shop.
I'll take care of it for you.
Grace, are you going to clean up the shop?
What?
I thought it was going well.
You have to clean up the shop, of course.
Right?
You've been doing it for a long time.
I know.
I thought I was getting a cold
after giving people a massage.
That's not possible.
Right?
I'm thinking of launching a cosmetic line
with the MD products from the department store.
What do you think?
If we can make the brand image
of the brand
look like the brand of France, Lafayette, or Harold in England...
Wait, wait.
Are you on a leave?
What?
Aren't I going to be the CEO?
Oh, I see.
You're not going to be the CEO from the start.
Then I'll move out.
What is it?
Close the shop
and get ready to move to the US as a former director.
If you get caught here,
there will be too many things for us to do.
If you want to start a cosmetic company,
you can start there.
I'll look for a investor.
Even if you quit your job, move out, and settle down,
you can never move to a Korean branch.
That's the academy.
Your daughter is in the third year of high school.
She's studying cello,
and she's taking a class in the entrance exam.
I filed a lawsuit against her
for fraudulent information and confidentiality,
but she couldn't be found.
It took me a long time to find her.
Wow, she had this.
It's not like she didn't have a copy.
She wouldn't have had a wife.
Who is this?
Hong Sucheol,
I'll tell you the truth about Cheon Dahye,
who was your wife for a while.
It might be a little scary.
You're not a good person
just because you're older and slender, right?
But I'm five years older than you.
My parents, my family, my education,
they're all fake.
I'll tell you one more thing.
Geonu isn't your child.
You can't tell, can you?
You're an Arab, but Geonu is a Tofu.
How can you not suspect him?
I'm sorry I broke up with you.
Where else would I meet someone like you?
Are you going to marry me or not?
I told you I wouldn't.
Fine, but give me those gloves.
You're a coward, but you're a coward.
What's my name?
Cheon Dahye.
You're rich, but you're a bad-mannered loser.
You don't have to marry me.
Fine.
But are you warm-hearted?
I'm sorry.
If you gave me everything I asked for,
I should've seen you when we met again.
To start the hope of the two of you,
please give them a round of applause.
You're a good man and a good woman.
Hey.
Don't be so sad.
That woman, Hong Yein,
got so upset because she got married
without listening to me.
You have to seduce Hong Sucheol
and get dressed right away.
I know.
But are you going to use your real name?
Make a name for yourself.
No, I'm going to use Cheon Dahye.
But where is Hong Sucheol?
He's over there.
Don't get married in the first place.
You're going to get in trouble.
Wow.
Did he grow up so well?
Don't be so cute. You're totally my type.
No.
After that...
You're not going to get married?
How can you not get married here?
You're going to get married?
No, no.
That fool.
He's still the same.
Since you're here,
eat something delicious.
Director, nice to meet you.
Where have you been?
I've been looking for you.
Welcome.
Please eat a lot.
You didn't even remember me.
Hello.
I'm Cheon Dahye.
Cheon Dahye?
Wow, what a pretty name.
Of course, your face...
Yes.
Since you didn't come to eat...
I'm here...
As if you didn't remember me,
I'm here to eat.
please forget about me.
And Geonu.
It won't be hard.
You're a bad person.
Hey.
Why are you crying?
Where did I find Dahye?
I can't find her.
She must've gone to the place where you caught her.
I didn't take her.
I left her there.
What is it?
Let go.
I left her here.
I told you that Dahye was the most precious person in the world.
I left her here,
so precious that I could never forget her.
Where did I leave her?
Dahye.
I'm awake.
Look at this, Geonu.
The girl that Dahye liked so much.
Hey, what's the point of doing this?
The case is already turned upside down.
We have to turn it upside down again.
How?
Yoon Eunsung didn't go there in a normal way.
I'm going to prove it.
Okay.
Let's say there was an illegal element and we're looking for all the evidence.
Claiming the criminal, trial, and lawsuit.
That's at least five years.
You're going to do that?
I'm going to do it in a shortcut.
What is it?
Investing.
Yoon Eunsung is going to trust a new business
and to steal the owner's shares with a quiz,
he planned to invest in Lee Joowon.
If that's proven,
it's easy to solve the family's family debt.
Above all, we can steal Yoon Eunsung's management rights.
The stolen shares are still the shares of the family debt.
I'm going to steal the way Yoon Eunsung did.
What is it?
We have time.
You should've given us the HR report.
It's uncomfortable to stay at the office.
I felt a bit uncomfortable.
It's my first time rejecting Mr. Hong's call.
There's no need to do that.
In this kind of situation,
a quick decision is the answer.
Wasn't Secretary Na close with Mr. Hong?
Who is that?
Wow.
Why are all friendship and loyalty
a abstract idea?
I'm sure you're not going to believe it.
Why are all friendship and loyalty
a abstract idea?
It's not in the world.
Secretary Na doesn't seem to be in touch
with Mr. Hong at all.
He said he'd be on vacation until he said goodbye.
He said he'd be taking his kids to a farm stay.
What about that?
He's not busy these days.
He keeps writing his resume during work hours
and goes to interviews.
I don't need all of that.
Tell the management to come out!
Yes!
What are we going to do?
He's being too much.
If he's the director,
he's going to be fired!
He's the son-in-law of Queen's!
No, you don't know.
He's fired.
At home and at work.
He's nothing now.
Anyway,
I'm here to hear your story.
You think we didn't tell you?
You promised to give me five times the market price.
You can't just sell it
and get double the price
for a resort or a house.
I think we have a double contract.
If you give me the contract...
What contract?
You can't answer the phone.
The number you have dialed is unavailable.
Oh, my!
What are you doing here?
You must be working on weekends too.
I don't sleep on weekends.
After work in the morning,
you can have a cold makgeolli and green onion pancake.
You'll be so jealous.
Yes.
You live like a human being.
I envy you.
People laugh when you say you envy me.
Have you tried makgeolli before?
I have.
I was curious when I was in college 30 years ago.
Then try it again when you're in this situation.
Thank you.
Here.
Then...
I should be drinking.
What should I say?
Well,
health is the best.
I know.
The chairman, who is the father of my son,
is sick.
I'm sorry.
The chairman, who is the father of my son,
is sick.
Then...
Nice to meet you.
But the situation is...
It's not good to be so clear.
Let's just drink.
But...
Oh, my.
Are you okay?
Yes.
One more glass.
What more?
You should go home.
No, I'm not going home.
Is it that uncomfortable?
It's not like you've lived here...
No, I'm not going home.
I'm not going home.
Are you sure?
I'm sure you're not going home.
But it's not like you've lived here...
No, no, it's not like that.
I'm the head of the family.
I should be able to tell my family.
They'll be okay and happy.
I'm going to my house in Seoul tomorrow.
But I can't say that.
I'm sorry to see my family.
I'm sure you're going home.
Oh, my.
I actually called my best friend.
I've never said this before.
I don't have money in my pocket.
Please send me 20 million instead of 10 million.
What about the money?
I can't.
There will be a prosecutor's investigation.
The reporters are looking for us.
I heard you don't think
it's right to put money in your pocket.
I was dumbfounded.
If your best friend did that,
you must be dumbfounded.
No, not my friend.
I don't have 20 million in my pocket.
The tax bill I signed a few days ago was 45.6 billion.
I'm so pathetic that I don't have 20 million
in my pocket.
Excuse me.
I don't know if I can comfort you,
but I don't have any money in my pocket.
You're lying to comfort me, aren't you?
I really don't have any money.
I've never had any.
Okay.
I'll call you back.
Director.
Hi.
I heard everything.
You're in a difficult situation.
It's nothing.
That's good.
I heard it's a secret that you're here.
Don't worry.
At least, we won't tell anyone.
We won't?
I'll get Yongdori's computer room.
I'm holding onto this place tight.
Okay.
I look forward to your kind cooperation.
Oh, my.
You're awake.
Geumhui.
Geumhui, are you okay?
Here.
Have some water.
Shouldn't you go to the hospital first?
I'm fine.
I didn't sleep well last night, so I'm dizzy.
Are you taking your meds?
What meds?
Are you taking something?
Just an anemia medicine.
Anemia?
I didn't hear that when I was testing it.
How much is anemia?
Don't be so overreacting.
I have anemia too.
I couldn't sleep last night, so I have an anemia.
Geumhui, are you doing this because you're fine?
It's all the same.
Geumhui, I'm fine.
But you're saying that you have a problem
with losing your mind.
You should go to a big hospital tomorrow
instead of following me to Seoul.
Okay, I will.
Why? I'm tired.
Why are you being like this to Hyein?
What about me?
She said she was sick.
She fainted.
You shouldn't be like this to the neighbor.
You should take care of your mother-in-law.
I mean, your mother-in-law takes good care of her.
Didn't you see her?
She was so quiet when she was listening.
Did you see Hyein answer to me so politely?
Geumhui, do you think you know everything about Hyein?
No. How would I know everything?
I don't know. I don't need to know everything.
Geumhui, why?
Oh, my gosh.
Geumhui!
What's wrong with you? Stop calling me.
Hyein...
What about Hyein?
Please listen to me.
Don't regret it later.
Be nice to Hyein. Please.
What's there to regret?
I don't regret anything from the start.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my goodness.
What's wrong with her?
Why don't I have a ex-husband like that?
I talked to the professor.
I made a medical appointment every day.
Sit down.
What are you doing?
Huh?
Well, you're just coming in one day.
Secretary Na?
Let's have a meeting in the office.
Okay.
I think you're meeting the protesters who are protesting.
Okay, I got it.
Call me again.
Were you talking to Secretary Na?
Tell me how much you found out about me.
I'm sorry.
What is it?
Tell me.
It's a typical real estate investment.
They put a businessman in the middle and collect the land owners
to buy five times the market price and contract the company at one-third of the price.
It's a double contract?
Then it's an intentional investment.
I have to prove that.
What about the businessman?
You said there was a middleman.
Is he in Korea?
Isn't he already abroad?
I did leave the office and disappear,
but he got married this weekend.
I thought he was going to go abroad as soon as he turned 17.
But he can't go.
He persuaded the land owners and sued them.
And he was suspended today.
Okay.
Then it'll be easier if we get him.
But I don't think he's going to go abroad.
I'm sure he's going to go abroad.
I'm sure it'll be easier if we get him.
Okay.
But you don't have to worry about this.
No, why should I?
Look at me.
I'm a husband-to-be.
The house is ruined.
It's not a normal house.
I sat on the street.
My grandfather is in a coma.
My sister went out of her mind.
The worst is that I'm at my ex-husband's hometown.
That's...
That's the worst...
But that's mine now, so I have to do something.
I came alone to do something about the high blood pressure index today.
Oh, that's good.
Yeah, if you do something like that, you'll be able to be good one day.
So you can leave without worrying about me.
Then we'll live without seeing each other like a divorced couple.
That's my goal.
To break up with you.
I'll share whatever it is in the future.
Let's do everything together as far as your health is concerned.
I'll have to achieve your goal as soon as possible.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'll park and go up.
Mr. Jang, what's your name?
I didn't know the hospital's name.
I'm glad to see you.
You used to have this kind of
I'm going to the clinic right now.
I got a call from the professor.
Yoon Eun-seo came to the clinic.
I don't know.
I don't know what you're doing with your family and guardian.
I have nothing to say to you.
Really?
Oh, my.
You don't like it, do you?
Please sit down.
You know what?
Yes.
I borrowed a handkerchief from a grandmother.
What grandmother?
So I had a son.
Oh, your name?
I don't know the name.
Howden is very fine.
He looks a little like Jang Gukyeong.
Is there such a person in our neighborhood?
No, that person.
Why?
Because he has a great voice.
That little...
I'm sorry.
That little voice.
The person with the voice of Jang Gukyeong is in our neighborhood.
If you didn't see a ghost, there's no such person in our neighborhood.
It's not.
You look alike.
Oh, my.
Oh, right.
Father-in-law.
Yes.
Let's eat.
Come here.
You guys are just right.
It's dinner time, so let's eat.
What's for dinner?
I made steamed ribs.
Steamed ribs?
I know.
I'm going to the police.
Mom, put the rice in.
Grace went to see you, right?
Did you organize it well?
Yes, I did.
Good.
You have to aim for what you want.
You don't even know the subject.
I'm going to be the representative of the department store.
Give me back the report.
No, that's Hyein's.
What are you talking about?
Hyein will come back.
I'm going to get rid of it by then.
Our chairman won't die easily.
I'll do my best to cure him.
I'll do my best to keep him alive.
I have the power to move 21% of the shares
that the chairman is in this state.
Do you understand?
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I told you.
I have different goals from my mother.
Where did you move the chairman?
You can't do that now.
You can't kill Jangji.
I can't help it.
My,
RIght now.
Right now.
Let's go.
Where are you going after dinner?
I'm just going to walk in front of this.
Huh?
I think Hyunwoo is coming soon.
Yeah, you think so?
Yeah, I'll wait a little bit.
I think we can eat together.
Let's go, then.
Don't go far away.
Yes.
Let's go.
What is it?
Are you Hyun Sungwook?
I've been looking for you.
Oh, yes.
I should have been in Boracay by now after the wedding.
I'm a little tired because of someone.
Did you get my text?
I replied, but I can't be drunk.
Let's get a judge.
I'm sorry.
I mean, I mean, it's been a while, but you're still keeping this.
Isn't that how strong the impact that the woman gave you was?
I guess it was really pretty.
What impact?
I don't remember if the owner was a woman or a man, a teacher, a student, or a security guard.
I don't remember anything.
I almost got in trouble.
As expected, the person who was the CEO of the company is very different.
How can you hit that in one shot?
You knew right away as soon as you saw the MP3.
This is a woman.
I was so close.
I almost got caught.
Hey, didn't you say you were like a prince looking for Cinderella with the MP3 in high school?
I did.
It was really pretty.
Do you remember?
It's unique.
It was my ideal type.
Do you recognize me when you look again?
I'll recognize you right away.
I don't have anything to say to you now, but maybe you were destined to that woman.
What am I doing somewhere?
What kind of a game is Baek Hyun-woo playing?
I'm going to kill you.
I think I would have done that if I knew.
Now you know.
I'm a bad guy who knows everything when I want to.
It's a bad experience to live with money.
You said you'd kill me.
Isn't that your class?
Is she going to come out of there?
Are you saying we should live in the same house?
Oh, my.
She's jealous right now.
I'm jealous.
Oh, my.
She's jealous right now.
I don't know.
I think I'm just picking it up.
It's my job to find out that.
It's something you have to go.
I'm holding it in a lot.
Dream on and get out of here.
I'm going to kill you.
Please subscribe and like.