slowly
count from one to ten.
Thank you.
Count from one to ten.
You know,
I'm not a bad guy.
I've been threatened many times.
So how do you live
against a truck?
We were both in the car.
I thought you were in the car.
I was trying to save you.
I was in a hurry.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
I just want to see you stop
suffering because of Baek Hyunwoo.
When Baek Hyunwoo tried to divorce you
because of another woman,
you even tried to die.
He tried to die because of a cheating guy?
You were pathetic.
I was pathetic.
You were too tender and kind.
You were married back then,
so I couldn't do anything for you.
But now you're different.
I'm going to protect you now.
No matter what you do.
This is the bus stop at Seonbang.
You're Baek Hyunwoo, right?
Why were you here
during the victim's trial?
I promised to meet him.
But I couldn't.
Why was Baek Hyunwoo's hair
found in the victim's car?
I think someone could have left it there.
Then what about this?
This knife was found near the crime scene.
Your fingerprints and victim's blood came out.
The victim's assets and knives were exactly in the same place.
Are you going to use them?
If the weapon was my fingerprints,
would I have left it near the crime scene?
That's not an attack.
This was an accident in Germany.
These are the wounds from breaking the glass.
If the hand that was holding the knife
had slipped and was attacked,
it would have been the back of the hand
or the bottom of the hand.
I don't know.
You're the one who's making the claim,
but the evidence is so clear.
It won't be easy to escape.
Confessing is better than your own imagination.
Isn't that what the lawyer knows best?
Baek Hyeon-woo, if this happens again,
don't save me.
Baek Hyeon-woo even tried to die
when he tried to divorce you
because of another woman.
Baek Hyeon-woo
Hye-in!
Mom!
Mom, can you recognize me?
Oh my god!
Are you okay?
Are you not sick anymore?
Sister, you must be tired.
Hello.
Father, mother, auntie...
I'm Hong Su-cheol.
I've heard a lot about you.
Let's have a meal later.
Hye-in!
Hye-in is a little tired
after the flight.
I think we should go and rest.
I don't think you're fit to be here.
Hong Su-cheol,
I hope you don't overreact to Yoon Eun-sung.
Who?
Hye-in, do you know what this person
did to my family?
I think I left all your family
and took over the Queen's.
But in fact,
the chairman who was tired of the
property dispute of his children died
and handed over the position to me.
He left the management of the property to his mother.
The chairman wanted to give it all to you,
but your parents and brother
couldn't leave it.
If it was not enough,
would the people in your family
like the news that you were going to die?
Of course.
I know about it.
I've read a lot of newspaper articles.
I don't think we were
so happy to see each other
while we were so happy.
Did you have any contact with your family?
No.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm a red pepper.
Can you give me your will?
I told you to get back together,
so you're being wary.
I stopped him from talking to you in person.
He asked me to do it before the surgery.
I can't imagine what kind of relationship
it was just because no one came with me
when I had such a big surgery.
Before, you must have been lonely.
I was lonely.
I was always alone.
But I was like that too.
That's why we were
the only ones for each other.
Don't believe your family.
I don't want to see you
being used anymore.
No, I don't know what he was talking about.
Don't believe him.
We're family.
Who are you listening to?
I heard that you put a charm
in your wallet that could break my ear.
Did you say that?
It's true.
My mom gave it to me.
I don't think that's important.
Ha-in.
Your mother was sued
for being a part of the department store.
She was immediately arrested.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Don't think that the bad past
will disappear
just because I lost my memory.
Ha-in, as you said,
our family had a lot of problems.
But it's a misunderstanding.
Right.
And that's not next to him.
It should be next to your husband.
Oh, my ex-husband?
He got caught writing a divorce paper
and got divorced without me knowing.
That's true.
But he's a bad guy
because he's so weak.
But that's not all.
You're in the detention center
for murder.
You're not going, are you?
You have to be there
when I open the door.
Why are you going home?
I've prepared a place
for you to live comfortably.
I used to live there,
so I'm going to live there.
I'm going to live there.
I used to live there,
so I'm going to live there.
You might think of something
at least a little bit.
I'll do that.
I'm worried that I'll be caught
by your family
and be a weak point.
It was so hard for your parents
to get you back to work.
The directors kept asking about
your health, so...
I know.
I'll make sure that doesn't happen.
Thank you for worrying about me.
Thank you is enough for me.
Now keep your promise.
We'll get married after the surgery.
We promised each other.
I'll take care of the wedding.
You're here.
It's been a while.
I have something to ask you.
Before Hyein got the surgery in Germany,
there was an accident.
Is that your mother?
Yes.
She's not dead.
What's the problem?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Didn't you know?
I told you everything.
As long as you're with Hyein,
you don't know what will happen again.
It's the same for the rest of your life.
Are you done threatening me?
Then I'll do it too.
This room.
Right?
Where Chairman Hong Man-do collapsed.
I saw everything you did
in front of this painting I gave you.
I left enough evidence.
So you're doing something to Hyein
just once again.
I can send you to jail like Baek Hyun-woo.
You dare to...
Yes.
I'm your nuisance now.
You can get rid of me.
What if I say I'm going to marry Yoon Eun-sung?
No way.
He was like that a hundred times earlier.
He's like a different person.
Hyein won't do that.
I've been following you.
You're from the Hong Gil-dong Detectives' Office?
Yes.
Gil-dong is our family's elder.
People have been asking me for help.
They're very talented.
I'm a detective.
They have been asking me for help.
They've been asking me for help.
They're very talented.
I'm still using that name.
What?
Take out $10 million.
Give me the rest of the $1 million.
Forget about the building.
I bought it to go out.
That's enough.
You're a detective too.
I'm a mistress.
Nam Yoon-won, get out.
They're friends like a self-proclaimed Wu Baek-goo.
I can't find any other place to look at these
Detective Hong is the brain of our office
He's the type who doesn't let go of his books
He used to run a book business
What kind of business?
He used to run a comic book store
Comic books are the database of all the cases in the world
It became the source of my detective life
Then what kind of case did you make as a detective?
Any case you know of?
You should find out yourself
If you're a good detective, you don't need to ask me
How much do you charge for the receipt?
Detective, I'll ask you that question
How much do you charge for the meal?
It's 8,000 won per meal, but it's a little hot
Jjajangmyeon is 12,000 won in my neighborhood
What?
The price is a big deal
We should be paying the price instead of catching the culprit
You have a heavy mouth
Who is that?
Oh, it's you
Wait a minute
Good job
Who are they?
They followed us when Hae-in was in Germany
We're the detective office that takes out one sheet
regardless of how much you've seen
We provide full package of information on the case
such as the case's details, the source of the case,
the psychological analysis, the solution, and the AS
We're a total human follow system
Oh, they're pretty good
So, what did you follow in Germany?
Listen to me
You can put down your worries in one go
What's so empty?
I wrote a new book
This is it, right?
You have the same taste in music
Yeah, we can have the same taste
What kind of person is he?
I mean, if he knows me, he's a 100% sure-to-be
But he doesn't know me
Then...
shouldn't he know at least him?
Yeah
If we have to meet, where else would it be as safe as this place?
He's such a vicious man
He stalked the ex-wife who cheated on him
and even killed someone to come here
How low-minded was Hae-in in his previous life?
Why would he do this to someone like this?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm sorry
Hae-in
Have a seat, Baek-hyun
What are you doing there?
I think it's because you're okay
How's the surgery going?
The treatment is going on, and where you're sick...
Are you worried about me now?
A lot
I was worried a lot
It's funny
You really think I don't know anything because I don't remember?
I wanted to see you
I knew everything
What your goal was to marry me
How you prepared for divorce
What you did to me after the divorce
I heard everything and checked everything
Hyein
Even if you don't know what you heard from Yoo Yoon-sung
That's not true
It's confusing now
But trust me
I only believe what I see
The divorce application you wrote without me
And you who is now a murderer
I saw it with my own eyes
Then why are you here today?
I checked everything
You said you knew everything
What do you want to know?
Didn't you come because you couldn't believe it?
The reason I came here
I came
Because
I don't want to
See you again
I don't want to see you again
I was curious
But I saw it
I won't see you again in my life
No
We will meet again
I won't get tired
I will be by your side
How can a person who has a dream say that?
When you woke up
I promised to be by your side
I'm sorry I kept talking alone
I'm sorry I made you come here
I'm really sorry
But
I'll be out soon
I'll keep this promise
So you
Jin-hwan, it's time
Eat well
Don't worry about anything else
I'm getting treated well
Jin-hwan, stay healthy
Stay healthy
Jin-hwan
I should have answered
This is
Not a normal person
He's got a number plate on his jacket
He knows why he was bullied
He knows
He's very sly
Not normal
Give me a pill
My heart is
My heart is pounding
I'm out of my mind
Wait
I'm getting dizzy
I'm going to cry
Thank you
Where have you been?
Why are you here?
Answer my question
Where have you been?
I don't want to answer
Can you leave?
And no matter what
It's unpleasant to be in the house without a owner
I'm sorry
But you're still being treated
I told you there were a few accidents that targeted you
Yeah
You said it was all Baek Hyun-woo's doing
He's in the detention center right now
Am I still in danger?
I'm just
I'm nervous
If you're not by my side
Something will happen
I'm sorry
For making you worry
Yeah
I'm sorry
Oh my god
I think the rumor is true
It's over with Mr. Baek
Be careful
We all wrote a secret note
Especially with Ms. Na
There's nothing to be careful about
He's not my boss anymore
What's the matter
Boss
Hello
I heard about it
Are you okay now?
Yes
I'm so glad
You paid for the surgery and the hospitalization
And Chul-young
Now I have a name
So-yul
So-yul is healthy now
That's good
Thank you so much
Did I do that?
Yes
It was before I came
Thank you for keeping your promise
Promise?
What?
You promised me that you would be back
Before the part
You were a secretary before?
Yes
You must know a lot about me
Right
You can think of me as a human's nephew
So
Oh, the boss...
Boss!
Boss, I was so happy to hear that you came back.
You're healthy now, right?
I'm an employee that you knew from the past.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks to you, I was able to get treated and go to my mother's last.
You sent me flowers at the funeral hall, and even supported the funeral fee.
I won't forget it even if you don't remember it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You sent flowers to the funeral hall of the employee's family.
I was a delicate person.
That was... Mr. Baek...
Huh?
No, you were a good person.
So, you came to the store once to buy the bugs that eat the sales.
You're warm.
Is this new? Where are you going? How?
I'm really curious.
Tell me.
Where are you going? How? Why?
You're kind.
Was I really like Mother Teresa?
Yes.
I knew it. I thought so.
I saw a stray cat on the way here today, and I wanted to feed it.
So I bought it for you.
I think you're the kind of person who doesn't want to do good deeds.
The memory has been erased, but the nature remains the same.
Let's do it well.
Huh?
You said it was a human external hard drive.
I'm like a reset main board, so I need an external hard drive with data saved, right?
But I'm in another department right now.
I'll take care of that.
First, contact the prosecutor's evidence record.
Why?
It's a murder case.
The prosecutor's going to have a lot of evidence.
But if there's a report that hasn't been reported as evidence, it's going to help us.
So the prosecutor's record was removed from the fine evidence found at the crime scene.
Yes, it's a green fiber piece.
So that's not the case of the prosecutor's record?
That's why it was taken away.
I'm sure Jinbeom fell off the bus.
We have to find that.
The kitchen knife used as a crime is the one I used in my house in Seoul.
But why is that there?
Did someone steal it?
I don't think I saw it for a few days before I went to Germany.
I didn't care much then.
Did you steal it?
I'll look at the building's CCTV.
One more thing.
Please investigate the black box of the bus that was driving near the crime scene.
There could have been a suspicious car.
Jinbeom could have been on that bus.
Hello, how many days do you get?
Sir, I'd like to ask you something.
Is there any CCTV on the fishing ground?
Father, I chased after the guy on the roof.
What are you chasing?
A crow cried early in the morning.
I chased him well in the trial today.
No, I believe that today's trial will go well.
I believe that, but the crow crying is a little...
Oh, my God, let's eat.
Honey, don't eat too much.
What's wrong?
It's a wrap.
Hey, don't do all the wrapping, rolling, and mixing today.
Don't drop anything.
I feel a little bad if I drop anything.
Hello, sir.
Daya said she's tired and she'll rest more.
Oh, no.
This is not a drop.
Our Sujin's master...
The floor is...
This is...
It's melted.
That's right.
It's melted here, right?
I dropped it.
But I can just eat it.
I'll wrap it up and eat it.
The meat is so good.
I'm full.
It's true, but the victim didn't show up.
Therefore, I have never met him.
Please start the defendant's argument.
I respect you, Mr. Judge.
The defendant claims that he has never committed murder.
If this is true, there must be a real culprit.
First, please pay attention to the crime tool, which is the most decisive evidence from the prosecution.
In the kitchen knife, the victim's fingerprints and blood were...
Green acrylic fiber.
As you can see, it's different from the defendant's clothes on the day of the incident.
But there is no evidence that it is the real culprit.
That's right.
But the person in that clothes...
He stole the crime tool from the defendant's house.
What if he was found near the crime scene on the day of the incident?
It's a knife.
It's the same knife as the crime tool.
The clothes he's wearing are green.
Next video.
The same person was burning shirts and gloves on the same day of the crime.
I tried to compare the fiber and the fiber on the crime tool.
The results of the comparison were the same.
The victim's blood and DNA were also detected.
It's just indirect evidence.
Only the defendant's fingerprints were detected on the crime tool.
What if there is more clear evidence than fingerprints?
Like the video and the picture of the crime scene that the real culprit took?
There must be a picture or video of this person.
We need to secure his cell phone.
You left evidence of the crime scene?
If he was a professional investigator, he would have done that.
You need to leave evidence to get money.
You just need to click this URL.
Done!
His cell phone is being copied here!
From the anonymous informant,
I received a picture and video of the crime scene in the real culprit's cell phone.
I submit it as evidence.
There is a reason.
This is evidence that was not corroborated before.
It could also have been collected illegally.
Please note.
This is decisive evidence that will have a huge impact on the trial.
I admit.
This is the real culprit.
The real culprit of the murder in the reservoir in Yeongjin-gun is arrested.
The Busan Coast Guard arrested the real culprit, Yoo Mo, who tried to escape from the Nambam Buyeori Beach last night.
It is known that Yoo is claiming to be the only criminal without accomplices.
Meanwhile, Baek Mo, who was arrested as the suspect of this case,
was acquitted in the first trial today and was released immediately.
Why isn't it coming out?
Isn't it wrong?
It will come out when it comes out.
But why are you here?
I can't do it myself.
The dangerous guy who stalked me was released.
Not the stalker?
Honestly, the boss is more like a stalker.
I'm scared.
Come down!
Our Mak Dong-ae!
What's going on?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You were worried, right?
I think there's a rule of the general.
I always made small mistakes, but I didn't make big ones.
What kind of mistake is that?
You're right.
Are you all right?
What is it?
I think there's a lot of misunderstanding.
Family relationships.
No, no.
It's okay.
But I don't think you two eat.
You don't eat tofu.
But do you hate tofu?
Why do you hate it? It's delicious.
What are you doing?
I'm going to eat it.
It's delicious.
What are you doing?
Did you see me?
I went.
Did you go?
It's good.
Let's follow him.
What?
Are you really going to stalk him?
What are you talking about?
I'm just going to follow him.
I'm not going to do anything weird.
I'm going to read it and see if he's going to do something weird.
That's exactly what stalking is.
No, I don't have time to talk about that.
Let's go.
You have to align the horizontal line.
I'm doing it.
You can go down if you're scared.
I have to help you.
Brother, are you okay?
It's okay.
Let me go because I want to.
The boss is crazy.
Please take this.
My sister likes dumplings.
I'll do it.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Have a nice day.
Yes, go in.
Do you understand my marketing philosophy?
It's not about getting money from customers, it's about getting love.
I'm sorry.
I'll also manage that philosophy when I make a comeback.
Fighting.
Director, is the hopang half the price?
Hopang?
Hey, how much is the half price?
It's free.
Take it all.
This is free too.
You'll regret it tomorrow, right?
Tomorrow?
You'll regret it tonight.
I think Bae Young-woo is coming.
Dad, I'm here.
Good job.
I'm sorry, dad.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I didn't do anything wrong.
What are you sorry about?
Brother, you did a great job.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Isn't that Hong Suk-cheol?
Yes, he's been avoiding us because of the
I guess he's comfortable.
They're really weird people.
Honey, it's Bong-hye.
Mom.
Hey, I made your favorite sweet red bean porridge.
You were worried, right?
Hey, I'm not worried at all.
Is it a life-saving rule?
No, no.
I was really worried.
Me too.
You did a great job.
Your parents have a good impression.
You don't like tofu, but you like sweet red bean porridge.
It's a child's taste.
Sweet red bean porridge?
I like it.
It's like seeing me in the past.
I did it before I became a fan of BTS.
The real person is...
I love him so much.
No, no.
What is it?
What is he?
He's starting here.
Secretary Na, did you always say everything you wanted to your boss?
Yes.
I was a cool boss.
I can't think of anything.
Then, give me 100 million won.
100 million won?
That's impossible.
You don't remember, but you have a clear judgment.
But why don't you know?
What?
Who your boss really likes.
Who?
I can't say more because I'm in a hurry.
I'll just talk about this.
You have a heart where your body goes.
What is this?
Mr. Ivan found it in the trash.
He thought we should give it back to his owner.
Does it say your name on it?
No, it's written in your foreign language.
That's why I can't understand the content.
Then we have to give it back?
Are you going to throw it away?
Could that be?
A lawyer from Korea called Mr. Baek's notebook.
He said if we find it, we have to give it back to him.
Then we have to give it back to him.
Boss, I'm going to pee.
Where are we going?
I'm going to get some rest.
I'll be back in a minute.
Aunt, do you live here?
We are here to congratulate Mr. Baek.
The catering company will arrive soon.
We can set up the food for the village, right?
Did you come, Ms. Han?
Oh, my God, you're here, too.
I'm in great mood, so I prepared a lot of gifts.
See you later.
I'm done. See you later.
What's so cool about it?
It's got all the health products and the massage machine.
The first prize is the latest drum washing machine.
Oh, the washing machine?
Oh my gosh! A washing machine?
I was going to change my washing machine.
Is this what you call a flex of the rich?
I want to live like a criminal when I'm born again.
Like me? Like what?
A pig. A pig.
I want to get married three times.
That's what I'm most jealous of.
Stop talking about that.
Why not? I need to be able to do that.
Of course.
What can a life without a washing machine change?
You're not going to say that in front of a guy who's never been there.
Are you really not going to get married?
The kindergarten teacher is really nice.
Yeah, he's the first one to make it hard for you.
Everyone, you should hurry up and get married.
How about next week?
Excuse me! Where is the village council?
Everyone, congratulations!
Everyone, thank you for spending your precious time with your younger brother Baek Hyunwoo.
Now, let's start the highlight of the day, the tofu cutting ceremony.
Let's go!
Together.
One, two, three.
Oh, that's neat.
Thank you!
Congratulations!
The next gift is a health product.
This is from my sister, Ms. Baek.
Please come out.
The number of the lucky person is...
Number 17!
It's a room!
Congratulations, sister.
Thank you, Hyunwoo. I'll be prettier.
Now, we're just about to start the first prize.
Today, we have a prize sponsor, Mr. Hong Beomja.
Applause!
The prize is...
Number 5! Congratulations!
Who is it?
It's Youngsuk!
It's yours!
What are you doing?
What?
Why?
I don't need it. I needed you guys.
Really?
Excuse me, Mr. Kim Youngsuk.
Yes, Ms. Beomja.
Don't you have any greed?
You got a washing machine. You should have it.
My washing machine is still usable.
It's been a long time. I've seen it all.
But it's still easy to wash.
This is the latest model.
It's AI, it can wash blankets and shoes.
Oh, okay.
Oh, okay?
If you get good things, you should get them.
Why don't you get it?
I won't come back here if I go to Seoul.
But you won't get me?
What if I go to Yeongnyeong?
I can't get married three times.
Are you getting married again?
That's not what I meant.
I'll tell you just once.
I like you.
I mean, I like you.
Are you going to let me leave like this?
I'm not going to come back here if I go.
Oh, auntie.
Oh, wait.
I have something to ask you about Kim Young-seo.
I'll be right there.
Oh, no.
Huh?
Why?
Yes, yes.
Yes, it's wireless.
It's connected to the speaker in there.
I'm going to get married.
Why don't you get it?
I won't come back here if I go to Seoul.
But you won't get me?
What if I go to Yeongnyeong?
I can't get married three times.
That's cool.
Are you getting married again?
Are you stupid?
That's not what I meant.
I'll tell you just once.
I like you.
I mean, I like you.
I'm not going to leave you.
I'm not going to come back here if I go.
Oh, my God.
It's a shame.
Hey, Young-seo, answer me.
It's okay.
Where are you going?
No, no, no.
No, no.
You have to push it.
Go, go, go.
Chairman, Baek Hyun-woo applied for a job at the board of directors.
He was found innocent in the first round,
so he cannot legally refuse a job.
He's not a zombie.
He's a little bit of a pain.
I know.
There's a bigger problem.
There's going to be an LP hearing in New York.
They're going to discuss the CEO's dissatisfaction.
What are you talking about?
If the CEO doesn't give the funds to investors,
the LPs can collect the documents and discuss the CEO.
No, no, no.
Who gave the documents to the LPs?
Baek Hyun-woo?
Is that right?
That's not it.
What do you think?
I'm going to wear it at the inauguration ceremony.
Oh, the inauguration ceremony.
What are you talking about?
It suits you so well.
It suits me, right?
I should have gone to a place that really suits me.
Call the bank.
Ask them to proceed with the CD transaction twice,
up to 4.2%.
At once?
We don't have time.
We need to secure as much shares as possible.
How dare they cut me off?
Oh, okay.
They bought 4.2% at once.
I guess they're in a hurry.
I guess so.
The debt is slowly being paid off.
Have you found the information that the CEO was going to give at the end?
Yes, but I got another piece of information.
It's evidence that the Yuen Sung family
was trying to steal the Queen's business card
and committed a fraud in the second half of the year.
Oh, my. Who did you get this from?
Did you bring it?
I got it from the US.
This is all I have.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
I gave you all the money I got from Osu-ri,
and now I don't have it.
You should have brought the money returned from that house.
That's the money from that house.
Where's the USB?
Did Dahee give you that?
Yes.
I told you.
That's my life's money.
I'm going to give it to you.
What?
I told you.
That's my life's money. I hid it.
Your life's money?
Oh, you idiot.
You're going to die because of that.
What?
Mrs. Mo doesn't want to see you anymore.
I let you go because you're pretty.
You know that Mrs. Mo hates pretty girls more.
Hey, stay still.
Stay still.
I said stay still.
You bastard.
Hey, hey.
Stay still.
Stop the car.
Put our arms on it.
Mr. Kito.
What are you doing?
Shit.
What's going on?
Did you see that?
I told you, I told you.
I told you.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
You bastard!
Let go of my daughter!
Stay still!
Mr. Su! Run!
Mr. Su! Mr. Su!
Oh, shit!
Sir, you should go when they let you go.
Huh?
Don't let go of me!
Why are you here?
Run!
Stay still!
Oh, shit!
Mr. Su!
You bastard!
Oh, shit!
Come out!
Dahye! Geon-woo!
I have to protect my people someday, but I can't do anything?
I can't even imagine.
Oh, shit!
An exaggerated reaction.
The opponent is like, oh, this is nothing.
Oh, this is the game I won.
Oh, my fist is no joke!
So that I can get a tight grip.
Let's go.
Oh, shit!
The opponent is waiting for the moment to let go.
And then he takes a decisive shot.
Hey, let's go.
Hey, put the bicycle away.
Oh, shit!
Hey, hey!
What are you doing?
Mr. Su!
Get up!
Oh, shit!
The dragon is going to eat Geon-woo!
Mr. Su!
Get a grip!
Are you going to die?
Mr. Su!
No, Mr. Su!
Geon-woo!
Geon-woo, I can't love you!
Me too.
Oh, shit!
What's wrong with me?
I'm sorry, mom and dad.
What?
Why am I the victim?
I'm the boss.
It's so funny.
Who is he?
I'm going to ask him.
I think we need to talk.
I have one, too.
You did a welfare?
Yes.
Why?
Because of me?
It's my job.
Don't you have a lot of places to go?
I think that's my choice, but...
I'm uncomfortable.
So please quit the company.
Go somewhere else.
I really...
I don't want to see you.
Why do you look at me like that?
I was the most difficult person in my life.
I'm the dumbest person in my life.
I'm going to be too much if I seduce you.
Did I?
I said I liked you.
I said I trusted you.
I said it out loud.
I thought you'd recognize me soon.
But...
But I'm fine.
I think it's natural.
You're more shameless than I've ever heard.
You're going to take a bite of my family and get something?
Why are you working so hard?
Don't call my name.
I don't know if it's because of the way you looked at me before.
It's not anymore.
Let's really stop seeing each other.
What are you doing?
Don't do this, Baek Hyunwoo.
No...
No, change.
I don't like this kind of thing.
Let go of me.
I'm sorry.
Haeng-ah!
It's me.
Grace.
Oh, my God.
You really forgot everything.
You're the one who liked and trusted me more than anyone in the world.
I'm sorry.
What?
I don't think we're the kind of relationship to talk and touch.
What's wrong with you?
It's me.
I'm sorry.
How did you know?
What?
How dare you?
Why are you being fooled by Yoon Eun-sung?
What is this?
It's me?
I sent you an invitation?
I'm sorry.
Please come in.
Okay.
Why is there no one inside this big place?
I'll help.
I'll take care of him.
My friends in Harvard are in your ride.
I hope my friends today are inmate.
Now, we will begin the wedding of bride Hong Hyein
and groom Baek Hyeonwoo.
Bride, enter.
How are you doing, Hyeonwoo?
You didn't get divorced, did you?
Do you have children?
One? Two?
It doesn't matter if you don't have children.
I only need Hyein to be by my side.
Don't make Hyein cry.
Make her happy.
10 years later, Hyein,
I know you won't be able to see this,
but if you are,
why would you?
Do what you have to do.
I won't ask you if you're doing well.
You'll still be pretty and healthy.
You'll be the most popular.
Of course, I'll try with Baek Hyeonwoo.
I'll come with Baek Hyeonwoo.
Are you Baek Hyeonwoo?
Yes.
As you were the whole family,
we made a reservation for the bouquet.
I left this place as a whole?
When?
About a month ago?
You left four years ago.
Then...
I saw it because it was the best date course.
Why isn't there anyone?
Ms. Hong,
I think the whole universe
is helping us these days.
I know.
I see.
It wasn't the universe that made us stay,
but you did.
I didn't know that.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'll go now.
Baek Hyeonwoo, don't think about living together
without getting married because you don't remember me.
I'll have to wear a wedding dress again.
I wouldn't have bought this.
I would've wanted to marry another man
who cheated on me and cheated on another woman.
I wouldn't have done that.
Yes, you wouldn't have.
If I were that kind of person,
you wouldn't have done this.
So, you should doubt me.
It's okay if you don't believe me,
but don't believe what Yoon Eunseong says.
Don't believe anything and doubt me.
Yoon Eunseong
hasn't been the one who's been protecting you.
He's been isolating you from your family and me.
Fortunately, we were both in the car.
But I thought you were in the car
and tried to save you.
What happened?
It's so nice.
You're asking me what happened.
I came because I had something to ask you.
Wait.
I'm going to have another drink.
Do you want to drink?
I'm fine.
What?
Haein,
let's go to the States together.
What?
You and I were abandoned by our families.
So, let's go together
with the people who were abandoned.
Let's go and live happily.
Are you sure I was abandoned too?
Why?
Do you think I'm lying?
It's not like that.
Let's talk about it later.
Let's talk about it when you're sober.
You said you had something to ask me.
I don't think I need to ask you.
I'll go.
Okay.
It's me, Navi.
I don't have my old phone.
You know, Baek Hyunwoo.
Tell me his phone number.
Send it to me.
I'll send it to you.
Baek Hyunwoo?
It's me, Haein.
I need to talk to you.
Where are you?
Okay.
I'll be there soon.
Hello?
I'm sorry.
thin
rides up and down.
I don't want you to be a bad person.
Instead,
you should miss me in spring, summer, fall, winter,
and even four seasons.
You should call my name after drinking.
But from then on,
forget everything and live happily.
Have a great relationship, get married,
and have a good family.
I won't play with you.
I'm already sick.
And write down the property of my life
in a good place.
I'm worried because I think I might die.
Can I go to heaven for good things?
That way, I'll see you again later.
I'm a little sad just thinking about this.
But if I live well and get surgery,
and forget you,
if I treat strangers,
if I lack that and make them ugly,
so you get tired of me,
what should I do?
But don't get tired of me.
Don't get tired and keep loving me.
I'm a pine tree anyway,
so I'll love you again.
I said I was a pine tree,
so I could trust you,
and I thought you'd recognize me soon.
Please hold on until then.
We'll never see each other again.
We'll meet again.
I won't get tired and I'll be by your side.
And when I recognize you,
come to me three times.
And Hong Hae-in.
The surgery was successful
because you were watching this.
You're saying you don't remember anything, right?
Then I'll introduce this man.
Baek Hyun-woo fixes things well.
It's a tray.
It just opens when you pull it.
But he's a bit nagging.
If you get a paper, take it out.
Why did you take out the copy machine?
I got a paper,
so I'm trying to get it out with some kind of a
Don't kick me.
Does it hurt?
It just hurts a little.
Should I go see if it hurts?
It's easy to fool.
Baek Hyun-woo, do you know?
There's a black knight in the basement of our company.
His name is Young-sook.
Young-sook.
There's a special move that makes people excited when they drink,
so you have to be careful.
I'm the black knight of Hong Hae-in.
Did you feel uncomfortable because of me earlier?
I'm so embarrassed.
Don't cry when you're crying.
If you get a sleeve, you'll hear a sound, so you should be careful not to get a
handkerchief.
If you still don't know, just memorize it.
That man is the reason I didn't want to lose my memory.
And even if I lose my memory, it's the only reason I wanted to live.
Baek Hyun-woo is a name I don't want to forget until the end.
I was happy to be with him in this life.
I'll pray that he's by your side in your life that will begin now.
I'm sorry, Baek Hyun-woo.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I followed Yoon Eun-sung and Hong Hae-in's German life.
First of all, Yoon Eun-sung was very dedicated to his liver disease.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'll do it.
You can do it alone.
Women never say to their favorite man, it's okay, I'll do it alone.
They try to turn it around somehow.
But Hong Hae-in was firm.
Even if you don't remember, you know your heart.
Oh, I'm not attracted to this guy.
I'm sorry.