Ultimate Note
Episode 31
You talked nonsense in front of
the human-faced tortoise.
The password you gave was wrong too.
Yes.
It seems that the model
is not delicate enough.
No.
The workmanship of the model
is exquisite.
In fact, I didn't see through your trick.
However,
I have made a minor mistake
and accidentally found out the truth.
Is it because
you didn't press the correct rivet?
The rivets drawn on the paper
aren't round in shape.
They are ovals.
It means that from my perspective,
it should be at the side of the poles.
However, I neglected the said fact.
I pressed the rivet
right in front of me instead.
You didn't find the right rivet,
but the passage opened automatically.
Therefore, I suspected
I was not the person
who opened the passage.
Someone controlled the passage in secret.
In order to examine it,
I pressed the wrong rivet on purpose.
Let's go.
As expected,
the passage opened nevertheless.
You also mentioned
the Imperial Readings of the Taiping Era,
Eight Trigrams and Five Elements.
What trick were you playing?
Mrs Huo,
it was just a distraction.
I will write it again
and you will get it.
"Gen" symbolises the mountain.
"Kun" symbolises the ground.
The first trigram in the Readings
of the Taiping Era was "Gen,"
followed by
"Kun" and "Kan."
"Kun" represents the earth.
"Kan" represents water.
I'm guessing it means
although the human-faced tortoise
is the God of Earth,
it can't live without water.
The human-faced tortoise
is a mystical beast.
"Zhen" represents thunder.
It can summon the God of Thunder
and Goddess of Lightning.
"Qian" represents heaven.
It means that the human-faced tortoise
can communicate with the gods.
CCTV.
T, A, O, T, U.
When I wrote it down, Fatty
immediately understood.
I wanted to say
we are spied.
The Huo family is trying to
get the drawing from me.
You looked as if you were
drawing trigrams,
when in fact it was Morse code.
You played the trick in front of me.
The Wu family always has something
up its sleeve.
Just one of my cheap tricks.
But sometimes,
cheap tricks work the best.
Thanks to your special arrangement,
I realised that the secret behind
the Yangshi Lei Archives
is Zhang family's Old Pavilion.
You are right.
Since you have the Yangshi Lei
and so much information,
and you want to enter
Zhang family's Old Pavilion,
then
let's work together.
Starting from Xin Yue Restaurant,
you have never planned to work with me.
I think it is a little too late
to talk about collaboration now.
If you don't agree with it,
don't blame me if I act mercilessly.
Hold on.
Are you looking for this?
Yes.
Wu Xie, what are you doing?
Eat it.
Eat slowly.
I may not have brought glory
to the Wu family,
but I still have spine.
I have memorised
the content on the paper.
I would be ripped open at the worst.
Rip him open.
Wu Xie, you will puke soon.
Don't move!
Wu Xie.
Is he the one
with the Qilin tattoo?
Leave.
Show me your hand.
Mrs Huo!
-Grandma.
-What are you doing?
Here.
Get up.
It's you.
I have no idea at all.
Mrs Huo.
What is going on?
You...
Do you still remember me?
That is right.
If you still remember me,
you wouldn't have come
to the Huo family.
If you come along,
we will succeed for sure.
Come.
This is your seat.
Is she getting muddle-headed
due to old age?
Forget it.
In that case,
I don't have to hide anything
from you anymore.
Bring it here.
These blueprints were drawn
in the 25th year of Daoguang's reign.
The designer was Lei Si Qi.
I have seven pieces in total.
In the past years,
based on these blueprints,
I built that model.
However, I realised
besides the blueprints that I own
there is one more blueprint.
Because of that,
I couldn't crack
the secret of the hidden passage.
Why do you need the blueprint?
My master likes it.
We have to find it out for her.
Mrs Huo,
they carved a bunch of characters.
We couldn't get a clear shot
of Wu Xie's Yangshi Lei drawing.
It's okay.
Whether he takes the long way,
or hand it directly to me,
it makes no difference.
I knew about the things
you've just said.
Then do you know
how I got these blueprints?
They were hidden inside
the video tapes
found by Xiu Xiu.
As for the content of the video tapes,
I guess you already know.
You don't have to stare at me that way.
Perhaps everyone
thought that I couldn't take the pressure
due to my age.
I would go crazy
after watching the videos.
Though I am old,
I am not muddle-headed.
Someone tried to threaten me
with my daughter's life.
They forced me to go inside
Zhang family's Old Pavilion.
Since they are eyeing something
in Zhang family's Old Pavilion,
I must get it before them
so that they are left with no choice
but to appear.
I don't know who they are.
I don't know their whereabouts.
I only know that
none of them are kind.
Some of them put
my daughter's life in danger.
Some of them
fooled me for many years.
For my daughter,
for the whole Huo family,
for the Mystic Nine,
I won't easily let go of them.
Therefore,
I must enter Zhang family's Old Pavilion.
Because the Huo family
always
gets its revenge.
Grandma.
I have shown you
all the blueprints.
Now, you know
how I obtained the blueprints.
The Ghost Seal that you stole
from Xin Yue Restaurant
is still with you, right?
It is returned to the original owner.
Yangshi Lei Archives.
Ghost Seal.
Qilin.
Wu Xie,
so you're already involved.
Mrs Huo.
What do you mean?
You have no choice now.
You must work with me.
In that case,
there is something
I need to figure out.
On the metal shelf in the old shop
belonged to the Huo family,
there was a photo taken
a few decades ago.
That person in the photo
who looks exactly the same as me
appeared at Golmud Sanatorium.
What is with that photo?
All the answers to the secret can be found
in Zhang family's Old Pavilion.
Why don't you see it for yourself?
You are just one step away
from the truth.
I don't trust you.
Take me home.
Let's go.
You don't have to chase.
Inform everyone that
we will depart three days later.
Yes.
Zhang Qi Ling has just turned us down.
Don't worry.
They will come.
You, on the other hand,
claim that you want to work with me,
when in fact you just want to
help Wu Xie out.
You want me to bring him along.
I'm not trying to help him.
As you said,
Wu Xie
is already deeply involved.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
It's 260 million?
Why isn't it a whole number?
Three of you
are still alive
because I became your guarantor.
You tricked me once.
Let's
call it even.
We've been over this.
I pretended to side with Mrs Huo
to get the information
from the Huo family.
I am helping you.
Master Hua'er.
Since you're eager to help,
you may as well double down.
Please settle our tab
at Xin Yue Restaurant.
Stop.
I am just your guarantor.
You have to
pay back the money on your own.
Unless
Wu Xie agrees to work with the Huo family.
Then, I shall consider helping you...
To clear the debt?
To buy more time for you.
Otherwise,
if Xin Yue Restaurant
comes after you again,
I won't interfere again.
You are talking rubbish.
Zhang
doesn't trust Mrs Huo.
His sixth sense is accurate.
Zhang said that she can't be trusted.
We will not join her.
She can't be trusted,
but we have to join her.
What?
You have to agree with him, right?
Where is the destination?
Like Mrs Huo said,
in the upcoming mission,
we'll be divided into two teams.
One team will go to Banai,
while another team
will go to the Four Ladies Mountain
in Sichuan.
Four Ladies Mountain?
Isn't Zhang family's Old Pavilion
located in Banai?
This mission
isn't a solo mission.
Both teams have to work together.
We will have to wait for
the instructions from Mrs Huo.
That is all.
By the way,
as for the equipment, expenses,
and relevant permits for this mission
will be borne by the Huo and Xie families.
I'll go get ready.
Call me if you need anything.
By the way,
since we've decided to go,
let's run an errand.
Sure.
Commoner's Hall
Take a look.
All the weapons that
can be found in the market
are already here.
Look at this Qinglong Yanyue Glaive.
Back in the day, Guan Yu
used it to vanquish his foes.
He was known for his loyalty
and worthiness.
You are not satisfied?
Look at this.
This was the dagger Jing Ke used
to assassinate Emperor Qin.
Is it too small?
It may be short,
but it's kind of like a sword.
This dagger
can only fool children.
Look at this.
What do you think?
It is not as practical as mine.
You two are so hard to please.
None of these weapons caught your fancies.
Mr Jin.
I have already shown you
the drawing of the sword.
You need to get me the sword
based on the drawing.
How dare you mention that drawing?
Have you seen the drawing
with your own eyes?
The drawing doesn't make sense.
Look at the handle.
It's so small the user would be
literally holding the blade.
You'd sooner cut off your
fingers than kill anyone.
It is not usable.
Why do you care if it is usable?
Just find it according to the drawing.
I am looking for a sword.
A sword!
I am not looking for antiques
or broken toys, okay?
Controlled weapons?
I can't help you out.
Listen, I don't do illegal things.
Fatty.
Do you remember Xiao Hua said,
the expenses and equipment
of this mission
will be borne by the Huo and Xie families?
Yeah.
So can the sword...
It can be considered as equipment.
I knew we could count on
Master Hua'er.
It's great to be from a rich family.
He gave us such a nice sword right away.
What are you doing?
I am leaving a mark for Zhang.
The first time I met Zhang,
my third uncle sent me a text message.
He said,
"Bring the Dragon's Back
and come quickly."
Dragon's Back?
Does it refer to Zhang?
It refers to the
Black Golden Ancient Sword.
We refer to the items we safekeep
as "Dragon's Back."
The sword is indeed quite nice.
However, the carving is unpolished.
Wu Xie.
Xiao Xie and you
will go to Four Ladies Mountain.
You
will go to Banai with Fatty Wang.
No.
You are separating us apart.
We have to act separately.
I can't act solo
while the three of you team up, can I?
I have my reasons
for such an arrangement.
Based on previous experience,
both teams
need to act simultaneously
at Four Ladies Mountain
and Banai.
As for the detailed arrangement,
I will explain to you guys
when we are there.
Both the teams
have to work closely
and stay seamlessly connected.
Therefore, both the teams
must work in perfect synchrony
despite the long distance.
She sounds like she is fooling us around.
If you want to enter
Zhang family's Old Pavilion alive,
we must do so.
Sure.
I have made myself clear.
We shall depart tomorrow.
Is the Dragon's Back ready?
Of course.
I kept it at Xiao Hua's house.
You are a reliable man.
Let's go.
Zhang.
I am good at writing,
but carving
is not my strong suit.
It is okay.
The name is great.
Little Black Goldie.
Zhang.
What do you think?
It is not bad.
The sword suits him perfectly.
It's just as good as
the Black Golden Ancient Sword.
Wu Xie.
It's time to think.
About what?
About my gift.
You two have been helping
each other all this time.
When you were in danger,
Zhang came to rescue.
When Zhang lost his memory,
you found it for him.
Now, you gave him a sword.
How about me?
You need to give me something.
What is wrong?
Are you hesitating?
Don't be so stingy.
No.
I suddenly recall Uncle Panma's words.
If you stay together with him,
you won't end well.
Soon or later,
one of you will kill another.
He said that either Zhang or I
will kill one another.
No.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
Zhang.
Now,
you are getting more and more humane.
Don't worry.
You will see him again.
By the way,
Mrs Huo said
someone is waiting for us in Sichuan.
Let's go inside.
Mrs Huo, we are almost there.
Look.
This is the eldest sister.
This is the second sister.
This is the third sister.
That is the youngest sister.
The youngest sister is the tallest and
the most beautiful mount among the four.
It is 6,000 m above sea level.
No wonder it's called
the Four Ladies Mountain.
It's the Alps of the east.
Xiao Hua,
your staff in Sichuan
is quite fond of his hometown.
Wu Xie.
You are not here for sightseeing.
Seize the chance to take a break.
We are heading to the village
to find the person entrusted by Mrs Huo.
Do you know who that person is?
No.
Is anyone there?
No one is here.
Is this the place?
Yes, this is the place.
The fire is burning.
I guess that person will be back soon.
Stay away from the fire.
You are being too cautious.
He's hired by Mrs Huo.
You think he'd set a trap for us?
This is no ordinary fire.
The locals
call it Ximi.
According to the legend, millennia ago,
the God of Fire gave it to the people.
The fire has been burning since.
If you do something disrespectful
in its presence,
bad things will happen to you.
That is so creepy.
The forever burning fire
is quite sacred it seems.
What if someone touches it?
Will that person be tied up
and grilled to death?
Grill him! Where are you going?
I didn't plan to run away.
Where are you going
if you are not trying to run away?
I just need to use the loo.
The loo is not in this direction.
Mr Black?
Get back.
I am a kind person.
No way I will run away.
Am I right?
Get back.
Fine, here, let me give you a massage.
Here, take a seat.
Here.
Let me show you
my skills.
Here.
It is called the Tianzong acupoint.
You work all year long.
Your back gets hurt easily.
Give it a massage.
You will feel relaxed immediately.
Harder.
No.
Your body is so strong.
You don't need a massage.
Let's try it on someone else.
It's my turn.
Here, take a seat.
This is the Shenyu acupoint.
Your forehead is dark
and bloated.
Your kidneys are weak.
I have to massage
this part.
How do you feel? Is it painful?
No, it is not painful.
It is not painful?
How about this?
Is it painful?
I still don't feel a thing.
They are rich.
Boss.
As you know,
the convoy is on the way.
I think it must be Mrs Huo.
They are coming.
Right on time. Get my gift ready
and deliver it to our acquaintance.
Grandma.
When are we going to the mountain?
Let's take a break first.
We shall do the scouting tomorrow.
You guys are going into the mountain?
It's been raining non-stop lately.
There could be a mudslide.
It is not safe
to enter the mountain.
We can't put it off.
Just wait for half a month.
Go inside the mountain
only when the rain dies down.
You don't want to
sacrifice your life for nothing, do you?
Besides,
look at
them.
Those are only young kids.
Some debts
have to be repaid even if it means
sacrificing your life.
He sold information about me,
and he still has the guts to come here.
I'm not seeing him.
I have transferred the money to them.
I knew it.
The price of a thousand goats
is peanuts for our kind Master Hua'er.
Thank you.
Thank you for the care.
May we
never meet again.
Mrs Huo.
Cox Hendry's people are here again.
They sent us something.
A message written in
Zhao Meng Fu's words.
"The long-lived tortoise..."
To think he was able to find this.
Such sincerity.
"The stabled old horse"
"yearns to travel a thousand li."
"Even the long-lived tortoise"
"has its end."
This Westerner is ambitious.
He thinks that even tortoises
don't live long enough.
Grandma.
Are you a friend of Cox Hendry?
When my third step-mum
headed the family,
the Huo family came into contact with him.
I was still young back then.
I met him once or twice.
Wu Xie said
he was working with Cox Hendry
to explore the mountain.
Who knew
he would surrender to you so soon.
I don't trust him.
Send it back.
Yes.
Boss.
She has rejected it
and sent it back to us.
Okay, send my second gift
and don't worry about it.
She will take it in.
But I don't understand,
why are we doing that?
I am telling you,
we have to cooperate with her.
From Tamutuo to the West Empress Palace,
we spent a lot of money and resources
looking for what we want,
and we lost a lot of men.
When we were just about
to reach the Palace,
Ah Ning was killed by the tiger snake.
Until now, we still get nothing.
After arriving in Banai,
I started to gain
the cooperation of Wu Xie.
Little did I expect that he didn't
find the Old Pavilion's location,
he nearly died in the water.
So I know
I can work with Mrs Huo.
So I passed all the information
to Wu Xie,
and aided him to lure her here.
What we should do next?
Give her the gift.
Okay.
Master Hua'er is indeed a loyal friend.
You are really generous
in helping your friend.
If something happens to you,
you can ask for my help anytime.
I will give you a discount.
No need.
Just pay me back the money.
If I could pay them back,
I wouldn't have to give massages.
Mr Black,
what did you do
to get yourself in such a huge debt?
Don't mention it.
It's because of the sacred fire.
I was thinking...
Forget it.
Let's not go into that.
You're the person Mrs Huo wants us
to find, aren't you?
Yes.
However, this transaction
is a big loss.
Transfer money to my bank account
to pay for the goats.
Are you serious, Master Hua'er?
You are such a kind person.
How could you be so heartless?
I suggest you keep working
on repaying that debt.
Let's go.
Allow me.
If I become your driver,
would it be worth ten goats?
Half a goat.