My Lady!
Daughter-in-law, are you keeping watch all night here?
Hurry!
No! No, no!
Is it all right if I come in for a moment?
W-What is the matter?
I beg your pardon, Father. There was a rat in the shrine.
I will light the candles again.
You must have been startled.
You did not get hurt anywhere?
I am fine.
By the way, what brings you here at this hour?
The light was still on inside the shrine,
so I came for a moment to check.
- Oh, my, Father!
- D-Daugther-in-law!
I am okay.
I got dizzy for a moment.
It must be because you sit inside the shrine all day.
Would you like to take a short walk and get some air?
Yes, Father.
[Knight Flower - Episode 6: While you were sleeping]
Is it not too hard on you?
Not at all.
How can I dare say it is hard on me?
You and Mother take care of me,
so I am always thankful.
Thank you for thinking that.
The days have gotten warmer,
but the coldness still rises from the ground at night.
So go down and sleep comfortably.
Father, I always feel bad toward you.
You took me in when I had no kin, and
you let me visit the temple for my brother when necessary.
One day, if my brother comes back,
everything would be thanks to your merciful grace.
Are you still waiting for your brother?
I am cautious, for this might be hurtful to you,
but should you not let go of him now?
Fifteen years have passed now.
I am sure...
Brother is alive.
If something had happened to my brother,
I will find out what it is for sure, whatever it is.
I apologize. I spoke needlessly about myself and
made you upset, Father.
Not at all.
I will also remember to look into your brother's whereabouts.
Find the man named Cho Seong Hoo by all means and
get rid of him without leaving any trace.
Yes.
Sir!
Did you find anything?
I looked at the flowers owned by pharmacies at Woonjong Street and Hwayeon Merchandising,
but none of them had the flower.
Really?
Did the corpse's mouth really smell like a flower?
It was the same scent, for sure.
Much like the scent of wisteria flowers.
Gosh.
Sir, they all died!
This is...
poison.
But the Finance Minister's cause of death was a head trauma. Right?
Since we found out this is a poison, we cannot rule out death by poison.
- Why was this dangerous poison inside the fillet?
- So this means
the man named Yong Deok was not the real culprit.
How on Earth would he have fed this to the Finance Minister?
I told you, right? I said there must be a heartbreaking story
behind this case of a man sacrificing his life for his love!
Did you not say someone saw him meeting a woman in a mourning dress?
I heard he fell in love with some family's widow.
That ring is mine.
Madam, please look at it closely!
Probably not.
You think so, too, Sir?
This must be a love—
Bi Chan, find out when and how the Finance Minister's drawing ended up in his house.
Yes!
If that man is not the culprit,
then who is?
Was Madam Baek sent off safely?
- She said she would not go.
- Wait, why?
Because of her servant, Yong Deok.
I was scolded by Mother, could not sleep, and almost got caught by Father.
I spent all night awake for her, but what is this now?
The heavenly maiden was given her wings, and now she wants to take the lumberjack, too.
(Reference to Korean folklore)
But the lumberjack is locked behind bars, so what do I do?
This is tiring, Yeon Seon.
For now, get some sleep until Madam summons you.
Young Madam, Madam wants to see you.
What do you plan to do?
Sorry?
The Minister of General Affairs' daughter-in-law stopped eating.
So you cannot be doing nothing. Right?
I intend to visit the Finance Minister's wife with some milk porridge.
The Finance Minister's wife?
No matter how small, good deeds cannot fail to produce good results.
Evil deeds, no matter how small, cannot fail to produce harmful results.
That is what you always told me, Mother.
So, doing good deeds instead of being attached to
such trivial matter seems better.
I will go and console Honorable Lady Jeonggyeong, who must be devastated.
I did not teach you in vain.
I will console her sincerely and keep her company.
After visiting the Finance Minister's home, I need to go see Madam Baek as well. Let us hurry.
Yes!
Are all these appeals requesting the immediate execution of the slave who killed the Finance Minister?
Since our country was founded, was there ever a case where an official was murdered by his slave?
If you do not take care of this case sternly,
in addition to the Royal Court's authority plummeting to the ground,
the Royal Family could be subject to danger as well.
I heard it was the result of a simple burglary.
So, would it really threaten the Royal Court and the Royal Family?
If children were to disrespect their parents, subjects the king,
and slaves their masters in this world,
what exactly do you consider dangerous, Your Majesty?
Oh, I did not think this was such a grave matter.
It looks like he must be beheaded, as you said, Left State Minister.
By the way, it would be difficult for now, would it not?
I reckon I can allow it only after one is tried three times by the court, regardless of his class.
What process are you referring to?
His crime is on the same level as treason.
Truly, there would be no difficulty.
It is only a slave getting beheaded.
Do as you say, Left State Minister.
In that case, he will be punished so, Your Majesty.
Who am I for you to visit, even bringing porridge?
I came because I was worried.
Even though you do not have an appetite, you need to eat.
How can a sinner who let her husband pass before her
have the right to put food in her mouth?
I am thankful for your consideration, but I have no appetite right now.
But you do have to eat it later. All right?
Are you really going to reside by his grave?
There are many eyes watching, so I cannot help but go.
You have affairs of your household to take care of and duties at the Peonies Club, so if you go like this—
I have done many things so far.
So, it would be okay to rest now. Right?
Were you exhausted?
I was indeed exhausted,
sometimes sorrowful,
and pitiful as well.
But it was also fun sometimes.
Could I dare to ask you a question?
Go ahead and ask.
Is it more unfortunate for you to have
the Finance Minister end up that way, Honorable Lady?
Please lower your voice.
What if someone hears you?
I knew you were an honest person from the beginning,
but I did not think you would ask me this quickly.
I apologize.
Am I supposed to be more unfortunate or
am I not supposed to be?
What is your opinion?
How can I dare think such a thing?
People talk about you and me as often as they eat their snacks.
The widow remaining faithful for life to a husband she has not even met
and Honorable Lady Jeonggyeong, who takes care of her crappy husband.
Who do you think has it better?
I would live on as myself by any means.
I should have been closer to you sooner.
I will visit and keep you company more often from now on.
Please do not come.
I am leaving to reside by the grave, so it will be hard to treat my guests properly.
That is...
what the traditions would say is proper.
Yes.
My Lady, you were seriously awkward just now.
I know it, too.
I must head to Myeongdogak after visiting the Finance Minister's home.
Why to Myeongdogak?
We must find substantial evidence that man Yong Deok is not the culprit!
Why go to Myeongdogak when the evidence is not like a pendant?
If you happen to find the evidence, he is not the culprit!
Who are you talking to right now?
- Let us hurry along.
- Yes.
I am going to go there, so make sure to be there!
Be where?
[Myeongdogak]
I will meet her and try to convince her.
Where is she right now?
It is the last room on the left side.
If she is doing that because of her lover,
it would be better not to tell her he was arrested.
I received word he was already sentenced to beheading.
Already?
Because it is a grave crime of murdering the Finance Minister,
he might be executed as soon as tomorrow.
I believe it will be difficult to get him out.
Yeon Seon, go buy the sticky rice cake Mother likes.
Yes.
What are you going to tell me, even making Yeon Seon leave?
That is not it.
The captain will be coming here.
I am going to meet him when he arrives, so please set up a room.
Yes.
I found a way for you to live, but I heard you refused to leave.
Do you know me?
I do not.
How did you know to save me, then?
I am only doing small deeds as I encounter them.
So, you do not need to place much meaning.
First of all,
find a way for you to live, Madam.
Is running away a way for me to live?
Hiding in a place where no one knows in order to prolong my life.
Is that really living?
If I leave my house, who can I live as?
Will I have a face?
Will I have a name?
It is not like I do not understand you,
but are you saying you will give up your life?
I was meant to die anyway.
A widow who devoured her husband
wanted to live on normally like other people, dreaming in vain.
So, I must accept the consequences.
How is anyone in this world meant to die?
What on Earth did we do wrong to deserve death?
Say, did we kill our husbands?
Are you also a widow?
So, what are you going to do?
I have a request.
If you would grant this request, I would not care even if I die right now.
There is a man called Yong Deok in the Finance Minister's household.
Please deliver this ring to him.
My mother-in-law is already aware of this matter anyway.
So, he might not be all right, either.
Please tell him I will live on.
So, tell him to live the rest of his life happily to its end, please.
If you show him that, he will understand, too.
The ring that the servant named Yong Deok held.
Are you sure it is the Finance Minister's?
You visited out of nowhere, and
now you are asking such a ridiculous question.
I am asking because I need substantial evidence to prove he is guilty.
So, please answer.
Was he not already determined the culprit by the Criminal Arresting Agency?
There is not much I, a woman, can say in addition.
But how can a servant do such a cruel thing to his master?
Are you not able to comprehend my feelings of
resentment and devastation, Sir Captain?
I apologize.
I trust you will resolve this matter wisely, Captain.
His Excellency's resentful spirit should be consoled,
even if it will be only a little bit, does it not?
I will do that.
Do you mind...
telling me the last thing His Excellency ate the night he passed away?
For example,
the tea he drank before going to bed.
I am not sure.
Just like any other days...
Your Excellency, I will leave you jariggi.
(Bedside water)
Who prepared his jariggi?
I prepared and gave it to him myself.
Understood. I will come to visit you again.
I won't see you off from here.
[The Cloud Dream of the Nine]
Say, by the way,
did Yeon Seon that girl not come today?
No, she has not come yet today.
But why are you looking for her?
Oh, it is nothing.
I was just going to ask her for a transcription.
Why did I hide just now?
Whoa!
Gosh, you surprised me.
Where is Young Master?
Is he inside?
No, I came alone.
Really?
Did you really come alone?
I absolutely cannot tell you.
So, please go about your business.
Look me in the eye and speak.
I hate men who lie the most in the world.
Follow me if you think I am lying!
Hey!
I see you often these days, Sir.
Oh, the thing is...
People would think you are frequenting Myeongdogak to meet your lover.
A lover? What a crude thing to say!
- I am not.
- It was a joke.
I was joking, but you are getting serious.
One might believe the joke to be true, after all.
Grand Merchant, do you not think you went too far? I am a captain of this country, after all.
I apologize.
Nevertheless, what business are you here for?
I came to meet her.
- Your lover?
- Grand Merchant!
Please come inside.
My, what on Earth are you here for?
Looks like you did not know I would be here.
I stay inside Myeongdogak all day.
How would I know what you do and where you are?
We will just let that go.
Please get straight to the point.
It is not a fitting question to ask someone who was in here all day.
But I hope you will answer me.
What is his problem? This is scary.
Could he have come to check who I am?
I thought you were coming to talk about the culprit!
Could you be...
Could you be Yong Deok's lover?
No, there is no way he would know.
You seem to know a man named Yong Deok.
Did you know that man has a lover?
Did you come, knowing everything already?
- So, that's—
- He was only trying to protect his secret lover.
He is not the culprit.
I can testify to that.
What in the world!
(He uses a word that describes a good world without any darkness or secrets)
How and why on Earth could such a thing happen?
I mean, it is against the customs, but getting this mad...
It is still not a crime punishable by death, is it?
Though against the customs, just wear the mask at night, why go to Seonghwangdang?
(Place where a village's patron is worshipped)
It was at the watermill.
What?
At the watermill?
I saw them together at the watermill.
Not at the Seonghwangdang.
What do you mean, "them"?
The night I was saving the children with you, I saw him meeting his lover.
His lover's circumstances do not allow her to identify herself—
I am glad.
What are you glad about?
It looks like my business here is a success, so I will leave now.
Wait! How can you just leave like this?
Instead of a lover who cannot identify herself,
are you going to take off your mask and be a witness?
At this point, there is nothing you can do.
If someone else is the real culprit, I will investigate and
look for the real culprit.
What if you fail to catch the real culprit?
Does that servant have to accept an unjust death?
I am asking if you can catch the real culprit by the end of tonight!
What in the world!
How and why on Earth could such a thing happen?
Here is your share for this month.
Even during the mourning period, you clearly remember each and every date,
which is seriously surprising.
Is there anything you heard from the elder?
About what?
The thing is...
Are you afraid the elder will find out how the Finance Minister died?
So, why did you do such a thing?
I obtained it to use it on His Excellency in the first place.
Did you forget that?
It was used for its intended purpose.
What did I do so wrong?
You used it for something much greater than killing the Finance Minister,
which is why you are living comfortably in wealth right now, is it not?
A captain of the Capital Garrison is taking an interest in this matter.
By chance,
is the captain's name Park Su Ho?
Is it someone you know as well?
If it was him, things would get quite troublesome.
A mere captain will not be able to catch me.
Even the one lying in his grave would not know what killed him.
The only thing is that he better not unnecessarily poke around and upset the elder.
I will take care of everything on my end.
However, you will have to be more careful from now on, Sister.
"Sister," you say?
They said lowly blood shows itself.
I treated you like a human a few times, and
now, do you really think you are my younger brother or something?
Would it not be problematic for you to treat me like this?
If I am to be troubled, do you reckon you will be unharmed?
I will take care of this matter neatly, so you will not have a thing
to worry about, Honorable Lady Jeonggyeong.
How could you come so late?
It is already almost time for supper.
Were you really at the Finance Minister's house all this time?
Please forgive me, Mother.
On the way back from consoling Honorable Lady Jeonggyeong...
I heard my husband always brought this snack for you whenever he visited Woonjong Street.
I could not just pass by since I was already there.
Have you no fear walking around Woonjong Street in broad daylight?
Go kneel at the shrine until I tell you to stop.
Yes, Mother.
My Jeong would buy and bring home for me...
his favorite sticky rice cake every time.
Oh, my. Sticky rice cakes!
How much is this?
They are 10 for five poon.
(1 nyang = 100 poon)
Good! Give me 20.
Never mind, give me 30.
Goodness, yes!
It has been a while since I had sticky rice cake.
Where do most women gather around here?
The place where most women gather would have to be
[Durae Rice Cake]
Myeongdogak at the end of Woonjong Street over there.
I said I was fine!
Do not be like that, now!
Myeongdogak?
Madam is so mean.
We bought it to give to her.
I am the one in the wrong, so how could I blame Mother?
I mean, it is not like anyone is listening, so why—
Yeon Seon.
At least my mother-in-law does not lock me up in the shed to die.
Also, if I really think about it,
nothing Mother said was wrong.
At this rate, you will really receive a memorial gate.
I will go down and bring back something.
I thought I should end my life when I lost my husband.
I heard that was the natural thing to do
and that was what she wanted.
One day, it was a silver dagger.
And another day, silk fabric was brought to me...
every morning.
However, it was difficult to end my life that easily.
So, you should find a way to live.
Should you not look for a way for you to live?
I will help you.
[Seok Jeong Ji]
I am asking only because I am really curious.
Do you not like me looking for a way to live, Husband?
By chance, will you be happy only if I follow you to death?
Living instead of dying.
For now, I will first save someone's life.
- Where were you—
- Sir, you really need to thank me.
I ran a full round around the city in your place, Sir.
How could you talk like that when you ran away in the middle of work!
Then, what could I do when Lady Yi Kyeong was searching for you fervently?
Good job.
Did I just get praised?
- Bi Chan.
- Yes?
Who do you think killed the Finance Minister?
It is probably faster to find people who have no grudges.
Then, who do you think had access to the Finance Minister's drawing and could kill him with that poison?
Honorable Lady Jeonggyeong?
Gosh, what did I just say?
How dare I say that about the relative of the Queen Dowager?
In any case, it does not seem like it will be easy to catch the real culprit.
Then, are you saying that servants should die unfairly if we cannot find the real culprit?
I am asking if you are able to catch the culprit by tonight!
If she is that impatient...
Bi Chan, go immediately to Myeongdogak and track their movement.
Why do you want me to watch Myeongdogak instead of Pil's Lodge?
- It is an urgent matter, so hurry!
- Yes, Sir!
Will it be all right?
It is not like we are breaking down the prison, so do not worry.
Still, it is the Criminal Arresting Agency.
The beheading has already been decided. We have no more time to waste.
And the drug?
It will work for sure. Right?
It is a drug with proven efficacy.
I also hired a physician.
But will you go dressed like that?
Sir!
The Grand Merchant of Myeongdogak just came out with a woman covering her face
and went toward the Criminal Arresting Agency.
- Are you sure they are headed to the Criminal Arresting Agency?
- Yes.
I will go to the Criminal Arresting Agency. Go back to Myeongdogak.
- Pardon?
- Let me know immediately if there are any other movements.
[Criminal Arresting Agency]
Grand Merchant.
Have you been well?
I came because I have a small favor to ask.
Like what?
Is there a man named Yong Deok who was brought in today?
Let me just talk with him for a moment.
His elderly mother is sick and is close to death.
Should I not at least let him know?
It is suspicious how she is covering her face.
Please understand, as she has a big scar on her face.
Gosh, I really should not...
- It is only for a brief moment.
- Of course.
Who are you?
Why are you giving me this?
What about My Lady?
She is safe.
You have to do what I tell you from now on in order to meet her again.
Take this right now.
And do not be shocked no matter what happens.
- Pardon?
- Are you still not done talking?
We are nearly done now.
You must take it right now, got it?
All right, hurry up and leave.
Who let the felon have visitors?
Well...
So what happened was...
My Lady, stay here for a moment.
It has been a while.
Are you not the Grand Merchant?
What brings you here?
I will tell you outside.
Let us go that way for a bit.
Wait.
- Take off your face covering.
- Pardon?
I must check your face before any issues arise.
I have a big scar on my face, so—
Show your face right now. Right now!
You little...
What are you all doing?
What is this discourteous behavior toward this woman?
Who are you?
I am a captain of the Capital Garrison.
She is someone I know, so just let her go.
Still, I must record who she is, at least.
She comes to pick up needlework at the Capital Garrison, so you do not have to worry about her.
Okay.
You should go now.
The night is late, so you head home straight.
Yes. Thank you.
Did Officer Kim go somewhere?
I think he went that way for a moment because he had business to tend to.
Then I guess it will take some time.
I will be leaving now, then. Let him know that I came by.
Okay.
What are you up to?
Gosh, the smell...
What is the problem?
Save me...
I feel like I will die like this...
He has been throwing up and having diarrhea like a waterfall since four hours ago.
Perhaps he has the plague!
Officer sir!
Officer sir! Officer sir!
Gosh, that was close.
I cannot believe he had the plague.
Gosh.
Goodness, seriously. Let us go quickly.
Look!
Are you all right?
My Lady! My Lady!
He did not die for real. Right?
Gosh, people do not die that easily.
Hey! Hey!
Wake up! Wake up!
You see? He is alive.
You should cross the line no further.
I have come this far. I cannot stop now.
I will distract him, so take this man to safety.
Yes, My Lady.
Chase the body.
Is she not our Midam?
Hurry up and chase it!
Have you all gone mad?
How could you get rid of a major felon's body like that?
I called for a physician when he collapsed after throwing up and having diarrhea all night,
and he said he already died from the plague.
We had no choice because we were afraid it might spread to other prisoners.
Are you sure you were not afraid to catch it?
I am sorry.
Both you and I are about to lose our heads right now! Is that the issue?
Geez!
Stop right there!
I told you to stop.
Stop your horse!
Stop right now!
Stop, Madam!
What did you just say?
I said you should stop.
After that.
I am sure I gave you multiple chances.
As someone who does all this, are you that unaware?
This man knows exactly who I am.
I use my sword better than my bow.
I do not know what you know, but all of it is a misunderstanding.
You know everything incorrectly.
Must I discuss this with the Left State Minister tomorrow?
What do you want?
Do you know what a serious crime you are committing?
Have you not thought about what would happen if this were to come to light?
Two innocent lives are on the line!
What about your own life, Madam?
Are you... worried about me right now?
It is because things have gotten complicated.
I was coming up with a plan, but you stole the body without a plan,
so my plan became useless.
And if that plan goes wrong...
All this is because you were so reckless, Madam!
You have been much help to me.
So, I ask you to take care of everything well according to the national law.
Gosh, seriously!
I will see you tomorrow night at Myeongdogak.
Hey! Hey!
♫ The sword you hold in your hand ♫
♫ The moment white moonlight shines ♫
♫ I threw all of me away, baby, I'm ready ♫
♫ I can't be reckless, come on ♫
♫ Come on ♫
Hurry up and bring the body!
It is not here!
What do we do now! The body is not here!
♫ Baby! ♫
♫ I don't know if the sun will come up tomorrow ♫
♫ But I will keep on walking ♫
Brother, is it all right if I come in?
Come in.
Why do you look like that from the morning?
I have something to discuss with you urgently.
Sit down for now.
Someone was arrested as the murderer of the Finance Minister.
I know. I heard he was a servant of his house.
I heard a testimony saying that he was not the culprit.
What do you mean?
If he is not the real culprit,
just tell the Criminal Arresting Agency and reinvestigate the case.
That witness cannot reveal her identity for personal reasons.
Who is she?
That is...
something I cannot tell you.
By chance, is it the one whose identity you were so curious about?
So? Did you come to me because you want me to pardon him?
Or to help you catch the real culprit?
It is not that.
The man who was in prison last night at the Criminal Arresting Agency suddenly died.
How did that happen?
More importantly, the body disappeared.
What are you saying right now?
And why are you talking about this—
I want you to help me so the missing body does not become a problem.
What did you say?
Your Excellency! Left State Minister!
What is the matter?
I have something I must tell you.
You know that slave who killed the Finance Minister?
Supposedly, he caught the plague and died last night.
A criminal who was facing beheading suddenly caught the plague?
But something more strange took place.
The body disappeared without a trace!
As a result, the Criminal Arresting Agency is frantic.
- Come inside.
- Yes.
You are paid by the government, yet you want to ignore the national law
and are trying to decide government matters,
because of that one person you are curious about?
That is not the only reason.
Though you are my family,
do you have a good reason for asking such a
ridiculous request of me, a servant of the court?
Brother, the Finance Minister's case is suspicious.
Suspicious?
Look at this autopsy chart.
His cause of death is trauma to the head,
but I saw purple spots on his gums and in his mouth.
Not only that, but I smelled a sweet floral scent coming from his mouth that I had never smelled before.
Did you just say a sweet scent?
This came out from the fillet of the Finance Minister's drawing.
When this melts in water, it gives off that scent.
- The flower petals melted?
- Yes.
Also, the water with the melted petals seems to be poisonous.
First, do not talk about this with anyone else.
I will try to come up with a plan, so wait.
Yes, Brother.
No matter how much they looked, there was not even a trace of him.
Someone took the body of the Finance Minister's murderer?
But why?
I will ask the chief to take responsibility,
and I will make sure to resolve this.
No, no.
Wrap this up with just a rebuke of the officers.
Pardon?
In any case, he was to be executed.
So what if something happened to him?
More importantly, if the Criminal Arresting Agency lost a body,
there will only be panic-stricken rumors spreading among the people.
Now that I think about it, you are right.
Then, I will wrap it up like that.
To think they would lay their hands on the body of someone to be executed...
I wonder who was so daring to do such a thing?
At this rate, everyone will find out except you!
I know I did wrong, too.
He is a captain!
Not just anyone, but a captain of the Capital Garrison.
Do not worry. I will come up with a plan to fix this and shut him up.
Will you eliminate him without a trace or something?
I already failed at that.
- Did you find out his weakness?
- It could not be worse than my weakness.
Then, how will you shut him up?
I plan to approach him with...
truth, faith, and pity.
Goodness. What quality of his can you trust?
He does not seem completely untrustworthy...
But something is weird.
What do you mean?
Why did he pretend not to know when he knew all along?
And he helped me hide my face...
Stop right there!
He also helped me, too.
Are you, by chance, taking his side?
"Eliminate him without a trace." It appears that the method will be the best.
So, what are you planning to do?
Do I look like I know what to do?
All I was trying to do was help someone in need.
But I got a strange feeling that something immense would come my way.
Did I mess with something I should not have?
Your Majesty!
It is this scent.
The scent that I smelled that day.
This came from the fillet of the Finance Minister's drawing?
Yes, Your Majesty.
It appears the Finance Minister died after drinking this.
Back then, nobody believed me.
Nobody listened to me.
You must stay strong.
Now that we finally found a clue,
we will soon be able to catch those who were linked to this.
Since you and your younger brother are the ones who have discovered all this,
now, I have no choice but to meet him in person.
Also, I have one thing to ask of you.
What is it?
The servant who was accused of being the culprit seems to be innocent,
so the fact that the body disappeared should be wrapped up without much noise.
You are right.
Would they not want things to get noisy, either?
I am sure they will move first to wrap this up with no issues.
From now on, we will have a lot to do.
Both you and me...
and your younger brother.
What is the matter now?
What did you do with our Midam?
Where did they take the body?
I asked what you did with Midam!
Your Midam used a cheap trick to escape.
There is no way our Midam used a cheap trick!
Because of your Midam...
I lost my horse and had to walk all the way here from there.
Do you know how tiring that was?
As long as our Midam is safe, I am relieved.
Did they take the body to Myeongdogak?
How did you know that?
Bi Chan.
No matter what I do from here on, if it is the right thing,
will you keep my secrets and follow me, despite whatever risk you may face?
Well, no matter how close friends I am with someone,
my mother always told me not to get involved with monetary or dangerous things.
- It is to help your Midam.
- I, Bi Chan,
will follow you to the end...
even to death.
Sir.
You still have not caught the masked man?
I am searching for him, but I have not yet—
Last night,
the body of the Finance Minister's murderer, who was taken to the Criminal Arresting Agency, disappeared.
- What?
- As a result, the Criminal Arresting Agency was in chaos.
Thankfully, the court said to wrap up the case because he was to be executed anyway.
What do you mean the body disappeared? This is ridiculous.
First, I should find out who took the body.
Yes, Sir. I will look into it.
The Commander of the Criminal Arresting Agency got called into the palace
and was greatly praised for resolving the murder case
of the Finance Minister with no issues.
I just cannot understand why the Criminal Arresting Agency received praise!
How is this any different from the culprit stupidly telling people where he is?
What exactly did the Criminal Arresting Agency do anyway?
What did they do that they went into the palace and received praise?
Did you hear the news?
The second daughter-in-law of the Minister of General Affairs who is in mourning.
Supposedly, she ran away in the middle of the night.
You mean, how in the watermill, they...
What about their hands? What?
In any case, the rumors say they were caught red-handed by the Minister of General Affairs' wife.
How could you talk of such vulgar things?
Gosh, it is just a rumor.
In any case, the Minister of General Affairs' family was in chaos because of that.
Goodness, I do not think she will be showing her face at the Peonies Meeting any time soon.
Do you know how modest my daughter-in-law is?
How could you make her listen to such dirty talk?
You should not listen to such things,
and go to the shrine and gather your feelings.
Yes, Mother.
Yes, I am coming.
[Myeongdogak]
Hurry.
I will see you next time.
Yes. What are you doing?
Is this what you want, Sir?
I have no intention to have you die.
But you are thinking of reporting me?
What is this? It did not work?
Since I will die anyway,
I will end my life cleanly in front of you...
You are not stopping me?
Seriously? Say something!
I will end my life...
Excuse me.
Dying is your choice,
but someone dying in front of me is a different matter.
Then, what how about this?
Do you think I will not be able to do it?
I had no intention to die today,
but it cannot be helped.
What is the reason?
Why are you going so far as this?
[In the end, it was her]
Cho Seong Hoo's only family was a younger sister.
After Cho Seong Hoo disappeared, she married
and became the eldest daughter-in-law of the Left State Minister Seok Ji Seong.
Her name is Cho Yeo Hwa.
I am the eldest daughter-in-law of the Left State Minister,
Cho Yeo Hwa.
[Knight Flower]
[Unfinished Story]
Thank you.
Be safe on your journey.
All right, let us go.
- Let us go.
- Yes.
It looks like you also have your own story.
Please survive and live the life you want to live.
Our next destination is over there.
All right, let us go.
There is a man and a woman who are spending a night together in a warm room for the first time.
I heard that all of Myeongdogak was quite hot.
Did you heat up their room in this weather?
Shall I tell you in detail?
How a man and a woman in love secretly come together—
No! S-Stop it!
I am sure they must be exhausted from such a fuss throughout the night.
I guess Madam Baek is just like you and is different in the day and at night.
"Confident at night, modest during the day," if you will.
[Confident at night, modest during the day]
Confident at night, modest during the day?
♫ Oh, I see the dead people drowning on my way ♫
♫ But there's only one left holding on the last bullet ♫
♫ when I breathe in, I smell the pungent smell of the earth ♫
♫ It digs through my veins, preventing me from breathing ♫
♫ But boy, you gotta wake up, stop the meaningless abstention ♫
♫ That nightmare turns to reality, there is nowhere to run ♫
♫ The parameter gets bigger the moment I realize I slipped ♫
♫ So where do we need to go, just put your chin up ♫
♫ Yeah, I keep runnin', runnin', no time to get low ♫
♫ Set aside the meaningless calculation ♫
Not too long ago at Myeongdogak,
a good-looking merchant with a silver tongue appeared.
He said there would be a major problem if you find out who he is!
I know you have helped me every time, Sir.
I got involved by coincidence.
All of it were things you helped me with.
My name is Joo Yo Seop.
Do not leave my sight, so you will not do anything reckless again.
How will he keep watch over me?
Will he barge into my house or what?
Oh, it so happens you are here!
I have also wanted to meet you.
Why did he come here?
♫ When I breathe in, I smell the pungent smell of the earth ♫