'Snowfall Street' - Chen Zhuoxuan
♫  The night is long, and the moonlight dances within my heart  ♫
♫  As I watch the passers-by wander the city  ♫
♫  Even bitter coffee can become sweet  ♫
♫  Just because you are by my side  ♫
♫  Take a look, even our youthful years spoke of destiny  ♫
♫  Let's continue our journey hand in hand and stand by each other  ♫
♫  Let's wait for our love to grow  ♫
♫  Snowflakes gently falls and rests on my shoulders  ♫
♫  One by one, filled with poems  ♫
♫  May the spring flowers bloom next year just as beautiful  ♫
Dad.
You're still up?
I'm going to bed.
Is the sofa too small? Sleep in the bedroom.
No. It's fine.
I got up for some water.
- Let me fetch it.
- No need.
Look.
I know you like this, so I got it for you.
But you got home late. I'm worried it may go bad in the fridge.
So I'm drinking it.
Is it nice?
Not bad. A bit too sweet.
Let me try it.
It's too sweet.
It's with full sugar. We get 30% sugar.
No wonder.
Sit and have a chat?
- Sure.
- Let's go.
Have it. It's too sweet for me.
Okay.
Xiao Tuo, I've always wanted to ask you something.
Did you sign up for a medical university as one of the options?
Yes, I did.
But I scored too low, so I lied and said I never applied.
But I would have gone to a medical university if I had...
scored high enough.
Y-You know what? Back then,
I went through so much to enter the medical university.
I had to bike for two hours to the cram school after class every day.
It was so cold in the winter I couldn't take it.
In the end, I set up a bed in the storage room
in my classmate's house in the county and slept there.
The winter nights were freezing.
I dared not take off my shoes or my hat.
It was so tough.
But I devoted myself to the medical university despite all that.
Because it had always been my dream.
My ambition.
Soon after I got enrolled, I met your mom.
We didn't meet at school. She was at the nursing school.
The medical university changed my life.
It offered me love, marriage,
a job, a family,
and two sons.
You've never mentioned it.
You've been way too busy.
It's not because of that,
but my negligence.
Over the years,
I neglected your mom, Xiao Ye, and you.
I've seen too much life and death at the hospital.
I really thought of myself as a savior.
Seeing the patients in agony,
I thought I could do more.
I wanted to be a chief physician, a head of the department,
a professor, and even a hospital director.
I was occupied and forgot that I was also a husband...
and a father to two kids.
Xiao Tuo,
I'm not a decent father.
I'm sorry.
Dad.
No.
Xiao Tuo.
I owe you an apology, too.
- Mom.
- I'm sorry. My son.
Mom.
I'm the one who should apologize.
Dad.
Mom.
I'm dying young and can't take care of you.
I should apologize.
Sorry.
We won't give up on you.
Son.
Don't give up on yourself, okay?
Let's hang in there, okay?
Let's not talk about...
my problem in the next few days.
Just stay with me for the week.
Just stay with me...
like in my childhood, okay?
Just like in your childhood.
Okay.
Senior, you're leaving?
Did you drive here?
- Yeah.
- Give me a ride.
But you just arrived.
I'm not here for something. And I don't have work today.
Where did you park?
- Are we heading the same way?
- Yeah.
Senior, are you going to play soccer this weekend?
Yeah, it's a friendly match.
I told Chen Guangpu that Xiao Que and I would go.
He said it would be awkward with Lin Tuo there.
I was trying to make them see each other.
They broke up for no reason. Both are stubborn.
Que can't let him go, but she doesn't admit it.
Neither of them backs down.
It's going to be the end of it unless we help them out.
What do you think?
Lin Tuo texted me that he wouldn't make it and asked for a week off from work.
- What happened?
- His parents came.
His parents came?
We have kitchen utensils, furniture, and everything you need at home.
- So pretty.
- Here.
Look.
My son is so handsome.
- I designed it. It's called "Let's have a meal together".
- Really?
And there's a heart.
Aren't you going to buy your son's design?
Yeah, thumbs up for you.
♫  The streetlights don't speak  ♫
♫  Ordinary leaves fall down in an ordinary manner  ♫
♫  Does anyone care?  ♫
♫  I guess the wind has regrets  ♫
♫  Listen, the years are passing by  ♫
♫  Seem to say there's still reluctance  ♫
♫  But one must grow up  ♫
Is it nice?
Smells great.
All right.
♫  "There's still time," what a beautiful phrase  ♫
How's it going?
Give it to me.
Let's put it all around the edges.
Okay, let's re-apply the glue later.
♫  I think the wind has been happy before  ♫
♫  Listen to the care it brought by  ♫
♫  "There's still time," what a beautiful phrase  ♫
♫  But can the years ever stop?  ♫
♫  Hold on and cherish this ordinary love  ♫
You're home so early? Why aren't you in the store?
Are you feeling unwell?
Let's not cook if you're tired. Let's eat out.
O-Otherwise, let me get a take-out for you, okay?
What'd you like?
River snails rice noodles, okay?
Okay, river snails rice noodles. I'm getting it now.
We got this.
Hello.
Senior.
I thought you weren't coming.
I had a plan, but I was done with it.
Would you like to play?
No, thanks. My arm is still injured.
And you? Are you playing?
No.
- Why not?
- I've gained too much weight.
So you can't play?
- Keep working out.
- Senior.
Senior, we're here.
Senior, I got a fruit tea to cheer for you.
There are lychee, passionfruit, and peaches. I got it just for you.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
No problem.
Lin Tuo, you're in the mood for a soccer match?
- What about your parents and fiance?
- Whose fiance?
- His fiance.
- Senior, don't listen to her.
Stay quiet or walk away. Don't spread rumors.
I'm not here for you.
- Shut up.
- Everyone's here.
I'm going to get ready.
- Wait for me.
- Go. Go for it.
All ready?
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Where are you going?
- Come on.
- Just stay. We're here for the senior.
Sit.
Go for it, Senior.
I thought he wouldn't come.
Senior told me he wouldn't come. Or I wouldn't get you here.
Who knew he'd come?
Isn't it awkward for me to be here?
My goodness. What? You have to avoid him forever?
Why don't you move to another planet?
You can't possibly avoid him.
Besides, you did nothing wrong.
Why are you awkward? Just sit tight.
He's the guilty one!
Come on.
Want to leave? We can leave. I'll text Senior.
Let's stay.
Go for it, Senior.
Nice!
I won't get to watch soccer...
Go for it, Senior.
Keep going!
...and see Xiao Que very often.
Nice!
- Go for it, Senior.
- Defend!
Nice, Senior!
- Nice!
- Pass it.
Go, Senior.
- Pass the ball.
- Defend!
Go for it, Senior!
This way.
Go forward. Defend!
Jiang Chucheng, go for it.
Pass the ball.
Run!
Back to defense!
Go for it, Senior.
Nice, Senior.
Pass the ball.
Shoot. Goal!
Nice!
After further systematic examination,
the possibility of immune-mediated pseudo-ALS can now be completely ruled out.
Meanwhile, the symptoms have gotten worse for Lin Tuo.
So, you should be prepared.
You always praise your job as a doctor.
What's so great about it?
Our son is ill.
Can you cure him?
Tell me.
Think of something.
It's not an ordinary disease with an easy cure.
What we should do...
right now...
is to get ready for the worst.
Like what?
What should I get ready for?
For the death of my son?
Do you hear yourself?
It's not something you can change.
You've worked in the hospital for years. You've seen life and death, too.
Do I have to explain to you how it works?
How is that the same? That's my son.
I gave birth to him and raised him.
- He's only 23.
- Isn't he also my son?
You're the only one in pain?
Am I the one to blame?
Aren't you, Lin Shouzheng?
Have you looked after them?
You only care about your job.
You call it a career.
You've forgotten that you have a wife and two sons.
You kept urging them to enter the medical university.
Have you smiled at them?
Have you hugged them?
Have you shown affection?
You're not a proper father.
We take countless tests, growing up.
We have to be good students at school
and good staff at work.
Tests are fair.
We get kicked out once we fail.
But there are no tests for potential parents.
Children do not get to choose their parents.
They're born to accept their fate.
This test is missing, so it's not fair.
How many parents have truly assessed themselves?
They may love their children, but there's no excuse to fail as parents.
Xiao Tuo, your mom and I love you so much.
But we've failed...
this test.
- Move.
- Hey.
What are you doing?
He Xindi.
It's taken. Sit in the back.
What's your problem? Get off.
What's your problem?
Well, someone has a problem and he knows it.
Watch your mouth, He Xindi.
Where is Xiao Que?
She went back.
Come on, Sister. It's a buddy's night. Leave us alone.
What?
We're no longer buddies because they broke up?
You're not my buddy.
It's not like I want to be.
Well, relax.
I just want to see what you guys do every day.
Senior, let's go.
Let's go.
What's this?
It's good. Let me get you some.
What's that? Mushroom? I don't know what it is.
Won't you let us eat?
There is nothing you like? Get something you like.
No, thanks. It's a lot. I don't have much appetite.
Why are you staying? Just leave.
I'm training myself to recognize cheaters.
- Who is a cheater?
- He.
Did you get something wrong?
Not at all.
He cheated.
Cheater.
Lin Tuo, do you swear that you've never cheated on Xiao Que?
Do you?
Let's make things clear today.
Lin Tuo, if I've wronged you, explain it!
There's nothing to explain.
So you admitted.
Lin Tuo, did you cheat on Xiao Que? Did you? Lin Tuo, say it!
- Let go.
- I need a word with you.
- What? I'm not done!
- Are you done? Come with me.
- Chen Guangpu, let go!
- Come.
- Guangpu.
- Stay. I'll talk to her.
- Let's go.
- Chen Guangpu, let go!
Let's talk out there.
Chen Guangpu, let go! You're hurting me!
I wasn't done! What are you doing? What's wrong with you?
- It hurts! What's your problem?
- Stop it!
He Xindi, I've been putting up with you. Listen.
Lin Tuo didn't cheat on An Zhique.
I won't let you off if you ever slander him again.
Get lost!
Was she telling the truth?
So why did you break up with Xiao Que?
Why did she say that?
And why are you asking for days off?
How did you get hurt?
What's going on?
Just stop, Senior.
- He is ill. His right hand is failing.
- Guangpu.
His right hand is failing. Like this.
- Like this.
- Chen Guangpu!
Why are you still trying to hide it?
Seriously? When are you going to tell them the truth?
When your left hand fails as well?
When you're in a wheelchair?
Do you enjoy being misunderstood?
Have some water.
Senior. Do you think...
there are gods in the world?
If...
If there are,
take me to worship them and ask them to save Lin Tuo.
Only a human can save Lin Tuo.
No matter how bad or difficult it is,
we have to help him.
You hear me?
Anybody?
Please!
Please save my buddy!
Save Lin Tuo!
I beg you.
I beg you...
Sister, what's wrong with them?
Isn't it obvious? They're fighting.
Are they in a relationship?
Do you think it's possible?
I think Guangpu kind of likes Xindi.
Xindi likes Senior. Senior likes you...
How did you figure it out, kiddo?
What's so hard about it? Isn't it obvious?
Don't say that it's dramatic. It's very common among friends.
You're attracted to each other.
Tell you what. We have a circle here. It's the same in that restaurant.
The chef likes the waitress, who likes the manager, who has a wife.
How do you know?
We talk when we take the trash out.
Who do you like?
Don't tell anyone else.
I kind of like the girl from the lemon tea place.
No wonder you always get things there.
You should have told me. I know her. Let me introduce you.
No rush. It has to happen naturally.
- Good luck.
- He Xindi!
Why did you delete my game account? How dare you?
Stand there. Explain it.
They'll end up together. You'll see.
Mom, Dad.
I know you're thinking about retiring early to look after me.
I totally understand.
But it's going to be a lengthy progress.
I don't want to live like a dying man when I'm still able to take care of myself.
I hope you can treat me as a normal person.
If I need someone to look after me one day,
you can take over from there.
Right?
I'd like to savor the rest of my healthy days.
I'd like to keep working.
It's not time to give up yet.
That's right.
You're a grown man, so act like one.
Do whatever you want.
Your mom and I will support you and respect you.
We are going back tomorrow.
Call us if you need something.
You go back first.
I'll stay a bit more.
He's a grown man. He's all right. He got this. Come with me tomorrow.
Are you serious? Don't you see his right arm? He can't even get dressed.
I won't disturb you. You can go to work.
I'll just cook for you.
Mom.
My left hand is still working. I won't starve.
Yeah, that's it.
We'll go home tomorrow morning.
Dig in, Mom.
- Isn't it the semi-finals of the Champions League? Dig in. Hurry up.
- Yeah.
Chen Guangpu. What's going on? You're leaving?
Listen. I signed the contract for a year.
Am I going to pay the rent by myself?
When did I say I was leaving?
But you... What's that for?
Why do you care? Who are you to me?
I'm your roommate and business partner.
How come you forgot that when you deleted my account?
Chen Guangpu.
You're turning against me for a stupid game?
Remember how you dragged me out in front of Senior?
How am I going to face him?
- You started it.
- He Xindi.
Let me be clear. He doesn't like you.
He likes An Zhique. It's pointless for you to be so sticky.
Wake up.
Who says I like him?
I just admire him, okay?
Who says I want to date him?
We're just friends.
Fine, move away.
Get all your stuff. Get out of here.
But you're still paying the rent.
I...
I'm going on a date.
You know I have many pursuers, right?
Yeah. No, I don't.
I didn't, but now I do.
Good.
I'm never in need of a boyfriend.
All my pursuers are either rich or handsome.
I'm single only because I'm too busy building my career.
That's why I'm not seeing anyone. You get it?
Y-Yeah. Good for you.
Xiao Que just broke up. She's not ready to see anyone.
Both of us are staying single for now.
We won't get married before 30.
O-Okay.
All right, I'm leaving.
Please step aside.
Okay.
Have a nice time.
Bye.
- What's wrong with her?
- I don't know what happened to her.
She came in and said she'd stay single with me forever.
All guys are untrustworthy.
She fought with Guangpu. That's a sign of them falling in love.
Ignore her. She's always like that.
What would you like?
An Iced Americano. Takeaway.
- Okay, just a second.
- Thanks.
Mom.
- Did you have breakfast?
-  Not yet.
I'll have breakfast with Senior.
All right. Thank him for me.
Got it.
I'll go wash up.
Wait, your dad is coming.
It's our son.
- All right, go ahead.
- Dad.
- How's it going?
- So far so good.
I-It's raining here.
How's the weather in Chongqing?
It's not raining. Just cloudy.
Get an umbrella with you.
Okay.
Morning.
Senior.
Let me.
You sure you won't tell Xiao Que?
Yeah, I'm sure.
It's only a matter of time.
The later, the better.
Maybe after she starts dating someone else.
Even if she finds out then, it'll be over.
How do you know she wouldn't accept your illness?
It's me who can't accept my illness.
And I hate to implicate her.
It's just dating after all.
Why should I force her, in her 20s, take care of a sick person like me?
But she deserves to know.
At least, she gets to choose, unlike what's happening now.
She thinks you've abandoned her.
How is she supposed to accept that?
Senior.
Think about it. What should Xiao Que do once she finds out?
If she chooses to stand by me,
she'll have to take care of a disabled man.
If she chooses to leave,
she'll be burdened with the guilt of abandoning me.
It's a disaster for her, no matter what.
I've thought about it carefully.
I've also considered finding an excuse to break up with her more naturally.
But she's going to get hurt anyway.
I'd rather keep it simple, like what I'm doing now.
Can you understand, Senior?
Yeah.
Sit tight. Let's go.
♫  They always ask me  ♫
♫  About what I love  ♫
♫  What exactly is happiness?  ♫
♫  What's worth a lifetime to pursue?  ♫
♫  I once gazed at the rainbow, wishing for happiness  ♫
I'm here.
♫  Cherishing a simple life, morning and night, with peace of mind  ♫
♫  The exception is you and I, the uniquely favored ones  ♫
- Be careful.
- Are you his family?
Here.
Help him.
- Thank you.
- Be careful.
Be careful.
♫  Who will tell our story?  ♫
- Hi.
- Hello, Uncle.
We're having grills together.
It's Australian beef, Uncle, Auntie.
Take a bite.
We're taking great care of him.
- Rest assured, Mom.
- Rest assured, Uncle, Auntie.
We can tell. Thank you.
Take another bite. Hurry.
Dig in, kids.
Go ahead. Dig in.
♫  They always ask me  ♫
Hungry?
Kind of. I got over it.
Didn't you eat?
Why didn't you tell me? You can eat some.
♫  The reason why we parted?  ♫
♫  Why do I remain silent my entire life?  ♫
♫   I've stared into the abyss and there's no longer happiness  ♫
♫  Love and parting are just a hair's breadth apart  ♫
♫  All promises become dazzling foam  ♫
♫  It's my fault to stay silent and not let go  ♫
♫  She brings color to the cloudy days  ♫
Lin Tuo!
♫  I must still record those memories of the past  ♫
♫  So many vows end up as wounds unhealed  ♫
♫  The shattering sound is my heart, my true self  ♫
Spread your legs.
Close them.
Your legs are fine.
But you have to gradually avoid walking alone,
just in case you fall again.
Safety measures are important.
Use the wheelchair if you want to go out.
It's time to adjust your lifestyle all around and accept that you're ill.
Senior, I'm done here.
Hurry back to work.
Okay, take care of him.
I'll head back. Stay in touch.
Bye, Senior.
Let's go.
Guangpu, I want to go to HW Cafe.
Okay, I'll take you there.
Let's go.
Visit us again.
Waitress.
Coming.
'It's Love' - Dong Shuhan
♫  The moment we met  ♫
♫  It feels like I'm being electrified  ♫
♫  Your face… Oh, my God  ♫
♫  That's what my Mr. Right looks like  ♫
♫  What do I do? I'm falling for you  ♫
♫  Happiness comes unexpectedly  ♫
♫  Cupid's arrow  ♫
♫  Makes everything indescribably wonderful  ♫
♫  The stars blink as if it's confessing love  ♫
♫  You seem to walk right out of the light  ♫
♫  My heart is beating so wildly  ♫
♫  I'm secretly rewinding my memories  ♫
♫  Oh my ~  ♫
♫  My heart is beating so wildly  ♫
♫  I'm secretly rewinding my memories  ♫
♫  Oh, my ~  ♫
♫  It's love, love  ♫
♫  Why do I feel like I'm on cloud nine?  ♫
♫  I'm so happy that even insomnia is all right
(So happy that even insomnia is all right)  ♫
♫  I'm walking with you all night long in my mind
(Walking with you all night long in my mind)  ♫
♫  So this is what love feels like  ♫