'Snowfall Street' - Chen Zhuoxuan
♫  The night is long, and the moonlight dances within my heart  ♫
♫  As I watch the passers-by wander the city  ♫
♫  Even bitter coffee can become sweet  ♫
♫  Just because you are by my side  ♫
♫  Take a look, even our youthful years spoke of destiny  ♫
♫  Let's continue our journey hand in hand and stand by each other  ♫
♫  Let's wait for our love to grow  ♫
♫  Snowflakes gently falls and rests on my shoulders  ♫
♫  One by one, filled with poems  ♫
♫  May the spring flowers bloom next year just as beautiful  ♫
Okay, this should be enough.
- Thank you.
- All right, take care.
- How much is this?
- Eight yuan.
Grandpa called me today,
asking when we would go back for the Spring Festival.
This is exactly what I'm worried about. What should we do about it?
If we don't even go back for the festival, Grandpa will definitely overthink.
But with the current situation, how can we get back?
Should we just tell Grandpa the truth? After all, we can avoid seeing him forever.
I've tried to persuade your brother, but he just doesn't agree
and says Grandpa mustn't know about it.
So what do we do?
Your brother lied to us before too, didn't he?
He said he had broken his arm,
and I didn't suspect him. I really thought he had broken it.
He and Chen Guangpu had broken their arms and legs when playing football before.
Are you suggesting we tell Grandpa my brother has broken his leg?
We have no other choice.
Okay.
Then let's just tell Grandpa my brother and I fell off bikes.
I'll pretend to be injured as well. That way, Grandpa won't doubt it.
Okay.
Will this work?
I've helped you put on the gauze and the splint already. There shouldn't be any problems.
Later on, I'll put this on my arm too.
Anyway, if it's a motorcycle fall, it's normal to see serious injuries.
I'll also fake some injuries on my face to make it more convincing.
You've put it on backwards. How can you not give it away?
No worries. No rush to put it on now.
I've informed your parents.
I said you fell and broke both your legs and arms when riding a motorcycle.
Okay.
As long as Grandpa can't tell. Just leave it like this.
Xiao Que,
Spring Festival is coming. Go home and have a look.
Still angry?
Why would I be angry?
Whom would I be mad at? I couldn't even see you. W-W-What would I be angry about?
Well, wasn't I busy?
Then why are you back?
I hurried back as soon as I was done. I need to mend our relationship.
Is a relationship so easily mended?
You left the home so decisively. H-H-How can it be mended?
I was waiting for you to calm down, okay?
So I could come back and apologize to you.
You... What did you do wrong?
I made you sad.
You know you made me sad. An Zhique.
I never thought you could be so heartless. I raised you with so much effort.
You fell in love and then left me. Isn't it true that you don't have your dad in your heart at all?
How could it be possible? You are my father, and I am your daughter.
No matter what, I should be filial to you.
Besides, I knew a long time ago that you weren't mad at me.
You had He Xindi send things to me many times without telling me they were from you,
but I could tell right away.
Isn't that so?
How can I be mad at you?
You're my daughter and my son-in-law. How could I be angry with you?
Dad, from my childhood to now, I haven't really done anything too crazy.
This matter might be the biggest thing in my life.
I hope you will still support me when I want to do something, just like before.
I promise I will not let myself be mistreated.
When I need you, could you still stay by my side?
Haven't I always been by your side?
Actually, when I first learned about Xiao Tuo's illness, I was stunned.
I'm quite regretful now. Haven't I added to your burden by arguing with you?
Taking care of a patient is quite exhausting.
I-I-I made you have to take it alone.
Don't worry, Xiao Que.
From now on, I will be with you. I won't ever let you suffer alone, okay?
I won't let you get tired.
I can manage on my own now.
You're my dad. Don't worry.
When I need you, I will go to you directly.
Well,
h-h-how is Xiao Tuo now?
He is not in a very good condition.
The doctor says it can be actually considered optimistic,
and that the time period is not short.
His left arm... His left arm is still quite functional.
His legs aren't very nimble, but his feet can still exert strength.
We plan to visit his grandpa this Spring Festival.
I-I-If the old man sees him like this now...
We will deceive him, saying he got injured riding a motorcycle.
All right then.
So you mean to say, you'll all celebrate at Xiao Tuo's home this year, right?
Am I not discussing it with you?
What's there to discuss? If you want to go, just go.
Besides, if I didn't let you go, could I stop you?
If you don't want me to go, I won't.
No.
Just go.
While Xiao Tuo's health is still okay,
have a good Chinese New Year.
Don't worry about me.
I have many friends.
I will play poker and "Fight the Landlord."
I-I-I'm telling you, without you, I can still have fun during the Spring Festival.
Thank you, Dad.
Grandpa.
Grandpa, we're back.
- Grandpa.
You got hurt so badly on a motorcycle?
What happened?
- Do you want me to make a dish?
- No need. Go take a rest.
Dad, don't busy yourself with it. We'll cook today's meal.
You guys go ahead.
I was saying I'd been feeling uneasy all along.
You can ask Xiao Ye how many calls I had him make.
Why was there no news from you?
I made a video call, and you didn't respond to me.
See, there was an accident, right? I figured something was up.
I told you all about it, but you didn't believe me.
W-W-Well, you see it now, don't you?
Riding a motorcycle in the winter?
You're dressed so warmly with a hat.
Your vision isn't clear, is it?
For sure, you were wearing earphones. How dangerous that is.
No, Grandpa.
It's just that I wasn't careful when turning and took a fall.
You took a fall.
And you, Xiao Ye! I've told you so many times. Don't walk with headphones.
What if you bump into things? How dangerous that is.
- Such a grown person, still making me worry.
- Grandpa.
We just got back. Scold them later. Don't be angry.
Xiao Que, I'm quite happy that you've come.
I wanted them to invite you here for Spring Festival.
But I felt it was inappropriate to let your dad be left alone at home.
No, my dad will spend the festival with his colleagues.
It's not easy for him to get a break this year.
He doesn't want me to be at home so that he can enjoy his drinks.
He should come here to drink. I've got plenty of good wine.
Any day during the holiday works. We have rooms for him.
All right.
Then, okay.
Your arm is injured like this, and so is your leg.
Xiao Ye, how come you injured your left face while he hurt his right arm and right leg?
How did you fall?
Come on, show me. You were sitting behind your brother.
He was in front and saw an obstacle. It fell to the right, right?
You hurt your right arm and leg. H-H-How did your left face get injured?
Grandpa, it happened so suddenly. Who would care about how we fell?
Yeah, I got panicked and I jumped off. I fell on that side when I jumped off.
No, no, when you jumped off, you see, the inertia would take you to the right.
But you scraped your left face. Was it a magic motorcycle?
Grandpa, you're reconstructing a crime scene now.
You've been watching too many crime dramas.
- I...
- Grandpa.
Have you ever guessed the murderer correctly?
You forgot the reason why you switched to watching idol dramas?
Exactly. Grandpa didn't even know who the killer was in the last episode.
I told him, but he kept insisting that there would be a twist.
I've never really guessed who the murderer was.
Grandpa, you see? They are looking down on us.
Let's watch a mystery film today and take a guess.
No, I'm not going to watch. I'll never be able to guess who the murderer is.
You're so badly injured.
Don't ride a motorcycle anymore.
- Got it.
- Sell it. Don't ride that thing.
All right, I won't ride it anymore.
Don't worry me.
What?
What is it?
You've been in trouble again?
How is that possible? I haven't. What's wrong?
The warehouse manager said you'd been unloading goods every day these past few days.
Some are missing?
I only unloaded the goods into the warehouse. I never touched them.
Who said you touched the goods?
- Do you need money?
- I don't need money. I'm making money.
Mom, this is for you.
For me?
It's even a gold necklace.
Is it really gold?
It's copper. Take it or leave it.
Who talks like that?
It was bought by our son. It must be real.
- And it's a golden ox.
- Why is it an ox?
My mom was born in the Year of Ox.
No, the Rabbit.
My dad was.
- I was born in the Year of Pig!
- I'm going to take a shower.
You were born in the Year of Ox. You take it.
No, the Pig!
♪  Don't break my heart  ♪
♪  Be gentle once again  ♪
♪  I don't want to see  ♪
A'Bao.
Uncle An, you're here.
What's up? Not going home for Spring Festival?
My home is too far away. No direct flights, and I couldn't snag a train ticket.
So I'm going back later.
You're here alone?
Yeah, Sister Xindi and Brother Guangpu have to do a livestream.
It's Spring Festival. Few customers. I can manage by myself.
I want to earn as much as possible for Xiao Que.
No wonder people say you have a good heart.
A'Bao, Xiao Que has gone to Xiao Tuo's home to celebrate Spring Festival.
I am also alone. If you don't mind, let's spend the festival together.
- All right.
- Come to my place to eat my dumplings then.
- I can make the wrappers.
- I'm pretty good at making the filling.
- What are you doing? I can help you.
- N-N-No need.
I'm just about to get the cake I just baked. Try it and see if it's different from Xiao Que's.
- All right. Just give me a little. Just some of it will do.
- Okay!
Xiao Tuo.
Xiao Que.
Can you take some pictures of me with Grandpa?
How about we go out for a walk with him?
All right.
Grandpa.
Grandpa, let's go out for a walk, shall we?
Good. I have a gateball match coming up. It's the last match of the year.
- We'll go with you.
- To cheer you on.
Where are you going? I want to go too.
Okay. Let's change our clothes and go together.
I'll go change my clothes.
No. 9. Gate 1.
I can't understand this little ball game.
Me neither. I know nothing related to ball games.
- My little grandson. My grandson.
- So handsome.
The beautiful girl in the back is my granddaughter-in-law.
- She's so pretty.
- There are three gates on the field.
One ball per person. Each goal scored is worth one point.
Hitting the middle pole scores two points. Five points per round.
At the end of the game, the one with the higher score wins.
How do you know it?
I often played with them as a kid.
Do you know my brother used to join Grandpa in dancing at the square?
It was not dancing. That was a senior choir.
You were dancing there with a fan. Have you forgotten?
You were dancing with a fan while singing?
- Yeah, in the center position. It was the Phoenix Dance.
- Really impressive.
Don't laugh at me. Didn't I do that to make him happy?
Hit No. 6.
Had I known it back then, I would have danced with him more.
Xiao Ye,
spend more time with him in the future.
He likes playing gateball, singing,
watching idol dramas, and grocery shopping.
He always says it's quite comfortable to be alone.
But look how happy he is when we're back.
He talks on and on, having endless words to say.
No. 1.
- It's them.
- No. 1.
Okay. It's my time.
It's Grandpa's turn.
- Grandpa, come on, Grandpa!
- Grandpa, you're cool!
No. 1. Three points.
- Come on. Come one, Grandpa.
- Grandpa.
Well, people spend their whole lives growing up,
getting married and having kids.
After their children grow up and start their own families,
they toil to raise their grandchildren.
Then their grandchildren go to school and fall in love.
And in the end, they're all alone again.
After I fell ill,
I just couldn't stop worrying about my grandpa.
Every time I think I might not see him again in the future,
I really can't get him off my mind.
Don't worry. Xiao Ye and I will take good care of Grandpa.
- Come on, Grandpa!
- Go for it, Grandpa!
Grandpa, you're amazing!
Grandpa, you're great!
- So cool.
- Grandpa, you're awesome.
♫  They always ask me  ♫
- Good!
- Bravo.
Old Xu, fantastic!
♫  About what I love  ♫
♫  What exactly is happiness?  ♫
♫  What's worth a lifetime to pursue?  ♫
♫  I once gazed at the rainbow, wishing for happiness  ♫
♫  Cherishing a simple life, morning and night, with peace of mind  ♫
♫  The exception is you and I, the uniquely favored ones  ♫
♫  Even the sheer innocence at the beginning  ♫
♫  Who will tell our story?  ♫
♫  Will we be portray through singing of melodies in perfect harmony?  ♫
♫  So many eager attempts, all encourage me not to shrink back  ♫
♫  My heart is what resonates, my true self  ♫
Grandpa, if you are tired, let's take a break.
You ran too fast just now. If it weren't for my regular exercise,
I couldn't have kept up with Xiao Ye.
Let's take a break.
Take a break.
Actually, I'm fine.
I'm in high spirits.
Now, I often drink my homemade health tea.
It works. My blood pressure has stabilized.
I also made some for your dad to cool down his temper.
He should drink more of it.
Haven't you noticed? It works. These past few days, your dad hasn't been angry.
He has a smile on his face. And he even does chores.
He gave me a big surprise this morning.
He was sweeping the yard.
You should have had him drink your tea earlier, so that I'd have got less scolding.
Yes. Your dad has gotten old.
Now he's too old to scold you guys...
and hit you.
After one gets old, they get less picky...
and less courageous.
They say when one gets old, there's not much time left.
Time is numbered.
Actually, I feel...
once a person gets old, time seems to stretch on especially long.
Guess what I'm thinking. I keep thinking about when Spring Festival will come,
when you get holidays and when you will come to see me.
Once a person gets old, they feel...
time just goes by slower and slower.
But don't worry about me.
I've lived a worthwhile life.
I married your grandmother, the woman I loved.
I also worked as a carpenter, a job I enjoyed.
I raised a daughter, who has never caused me any worry in my lifetime.
She's filial.
So are my grandsons.
And my granddaughter-in-law is filial too.
I've gotten old, but I have my house,
live a comfortable life and have a big family.
See? Others get old and suffer from dementia, but my mind isn't muddled at all.
Now, I often think of your grandmother when she was alive,
she would fill the yard with vegetables and flowers and such.
You were riding a little wooden horse
around the whole yard. "Grandpa!"
"When I grow up, I will take you to some grasslands to ride a big horse."
You even said that you'd buy me the grasslands.
In a flash, you've grown up.
Child,
I...
I don't need you to buy some grasslands,
nor do I need you to visit me every day.
I just want you to be healthy, safe and sound.
Let me know you are well every day.
That's enough.
I'm doing fine, Grandpa.
G-G-Good.
- I've been doing fine.
- That's good.
Good.
That's good.
- How come you're back?
- Where should I go?
Didn't you go back to your home?
I went back to fulfill my filial duties. I didn't hit the mark.
Isn't it not the Year of Ox?
I think at least one of them should be born in the Year of Ox.
When I was a kid, we had a bronze ox statue. Why did they buy it if it was not the Year of Ox?
What can you remember?
You don't even remember your parents' age. You messed it up, right?
At least it's gold. Oxen are seen as a good omen.
- Why did you buy these things?
- Isn't it Spring Festival? I need to get some festive things for our place.
- What does this mean?
- H-H-Hang this over there.
- What is this?
- Do you plan to get married during Spring Festival with these wedding decorations?
The seller must have sent the wrong item.
He Xindi, let me tell you. You have to cut this thing yourself.
Find a piece of red paper and a pair of scissors.
Sit by the window, looking outside, and cut out the sorrow of not getting married piece by piece.
This seller is crazy. I don't want it.
Don't do this. It's unlucky.
Keep it for now. You'll get married eventually. Hang it up later.
- Aren't you going home this year?
- Going home? I have no home.
I'll stay here. Where should I stick this? On the door?
This large "Fu" character. Hang it there, on that wall.
- There?
- Yes.
Move it to the center, to the right.
- Yes. A little higher.
- Is it okay?
- Coming.
- Try this. Add a little to it.
I can't beat him. I can't.
- How can they still run away? You're such a noob.
- Use less salt.
- Stop playing games. Eat something. Get him some food.
- Wait. I'll finish this round soon.
Have some water.
Coming!
Hello, your delivery. Wish you a pleasant meal.
- Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year, thank you.
- Why are you back?
- Give me. Go change your clothes.
- Change your shoes. I just mopped the floor.
- Change your clothes.
- Why should I do it?
- Go to my home.
- Why?
- To have dinner.
- I've just ordered some food.
- Come on. Eating takeout today?
Hurry up. Change your clothes.
- No need for that, right?
- Well, at least change your shoes.
- Your family...
- Cut the small talk.
How could I leave you alone at home to eat takeout for real?
Hurry up. My parents are waiting. Go.
- I need to put on some makeup.
- Why? It's not a blind date. Hurry up.
Wait a moment. I'll bring your mom some cosmetics.
Wait a moment.
Hurry up.
Change your shoes! I just mopped the floor.
What are they singing? Why can't I hear it clearly?
It's a live band. All about the atmosphere.
C-C-Can they be called a band? Without a touch of rock at all.
Uncle An, you even listen to rock?
What do you mean by "even"? I'm an old rocker, you know?
Rock. Like... Like this...
- Good.
- Irritable.
- Wait. I-I-I'm a bit giddy.
- What's wrong, Uncle An?
- Want some water?
- I got excited. It's nothing. Do your thing.
Come on.
This Spring Festival is meaningful because we have a new family member, Xiao Que.
And next year, there'll be one more, my great-grandchild.
Cheers. Let's wish everyone good health. Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year.
- You seem uncomfortable.
- Who's uncomfortable?
Guangpu says you're a Northeasterner and eat dumplings during Spring Festival.
Uncle Chen, you made this?
- Thank you.
- Where's your mom? Call her out for dinner.
Mom!
I'm coming!
Move aside.
Xiao He, Guangpu didn't even give a heads-up.
We didn't prepare anything.
Consider this a meeting gift.
Look, it has a diamond. A real diamond.
Mom, isn't it too valuable?
- Auntie Chen, this is too expensive. I can't accept it.
- What's so expensive about it?
It's his first time bringing a girlfriend home.
No, Mom.
Uncle Chen, Guangpu and I are not...
Just keep it for now. As long as you don't find it ugly.
Her taste has always been not so great.
What good taste is needed? Diamonds just need to look good.
Guangpu, put it on for her.
No, Auntie Chen, this is too expensive. I can't accept it. I really can't take it.
Just put it on as she said. It's pretty good.
Try it on.
It looks good.
It's like it was specially bought for you.
- Thank you, Uncle and Auntie.
- You're welcome.
Thank you.
We are a family. Let's not talk about money.
Chen Guangpu is unreliable.
If he argues with you, you teach him a lesson.
If you can't handle him, just tell me. I'll make him behave with beatings.
Okay, Uncle Chen.
Let's eat.
- Let's eat.
- Have a drink?
- Yes.
- Dad, you can't outdrink her.
- Hey.
- What?
- I said you can't outdrink her.
- I'll drink with you today.
- Uncle, Auntie, I toast to you.
- Cheers.
I'll finish this glass.
- See?
- Happy New Year.
Dumplings are here. Hurry, eat while it's hot.
Here you go, Uncle An.
- Drink.
- Okay.
- Okay, let's eat.
- L-L-Let's have a drink first.
- It's Spring Festival.
- A'Bao, Happy New Year.
Happy New Year. Wishing you good health,
- good luck and happiness.
- May you make a fortune.
Right, let's first give Que a video call to say "Happy New Year."
My dad is calling. Come on.
- Say "Happy New Year."
Dad, Happy New Year.
Xiao Que, Happy New Year. Lin Tuo, Happy New Year.
Drinking?
Mr. and Mrs. Lin, Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year, Mr. Lin.
- Happy New Year.
♫  How many flickers of light will it take to make a wish come true?  ♫
Don't drink too much. A'Bao, make sure he doesn't drink much.
Xiao Que's dad, I've saved some good wine for you here.
Come to my place during the festival to drink with me.
Sure, I'll come over and drink with you.
- Come on.
- Cheers.
- Happy New Year.
Don't drink too much, Uncle An.
♫  Take a look, even our youthful years spoke of destiny  ♫
♫  Let's continue our journey hand in hand and stand by each other  ♫
♫  Let's wait for our love to grow  ♫
♫  Let's continue the conversation we didn't finish  ♫
♫  Don't sigh over the slow passage of time  ♫
♫  Sending eternal wishes to the furthest corners of the world  ♫
♫  Let's wait for our love to grow  ♫
♫  Snowflakes gently falls and rests on my shoulders  ♫
♫  One by one, filled with poems  ♫
♫  May the spring flowers bloom next year just as beautiful  ♫
♫  Let's wait for our love to grow  ♫
♫  Snowflakes gently falls and rests on my shoulders  ♫
- Does it look nice?
- Yes.
♫  One by one, filled with poems  ♫
So amazing.
♫  May the spring flowers bloom next year just as beautiful  ♫
♫  One by one, filled with poems  ♫
- Happy New Year.
Look at my hand. Follow it.
Look up.
Puff your cheeks.
All right.
You don't choke on food, right?
This hand. Hold tight. Use some strength.
You know about this disease. It goes from one part to another part. It develops gradually over time,
from the upper limbs and then slowly to the lower limbs.
Slowly from the right side to the left. His strength will worsen.
His muscles will atrophy more and more.
Eventually, it may affect speaking, swallowing, breathing, and so on.
Even now, it's still difficult to fully control and reverse it.
We can only try to delay its progression as much as possible.
So in terms of nutritional support, respiratory management as well as mindset control,
one must do their best to potentially slow down the progression of this disease.
How is it? Is it strenuous?
- Am I heavy?
- No.
- Do you need help?
- No, thank you.
Xiao Tuo.
Don't come over.
Turn off the light.
Xiao Tuo, are you all right?
It's okay. Don't be scared.
I'll help you up.
All right. With this, you won't have to worry anymore.
You won't need to get up to go to the bathroom.
Let's go to sleep.
Xiao Que...
Send me to a nursing home.
'It's Love' - Dong Shuhan
♫  The moment we met  ♫
♫  It feels like I'm being electrified  ♫
♫  Your face… Oh, my God  ♫
♫  That's what my Mr. Right looks like  ♫
♫  What do I do? I'm falling for you  ♫
♫  Happiness comes unexpectedly  ♫
♫  Cupid's arrow  ♫
♫  Makes everything indescribably wonderful  ♫
♫  The stars blink as if it's confessing love  ♫
♫  You seem to walk right out of the light  ♫
♫  My heart is beating so wildly  ♫
♫  I'm secretly rewinding my memories  ♫
♫  Oh my ~  ♫
♫  My heart is beating so wildly  ♫
♫  I'm secretly rewinding my memories  ♫
♫  Oh, my ~  ♫
♫  It's love, love  ♫
♫  Why do I feel like I'm on cloud nine?  ♫
♫  I'm so happy that even insomnia is all right
(So happy that even insomnia is all right)  ♫
♫  I'm walking with you all night long in my mind
(Walking with you all night long in my mind)  ♫
♫  So this is what love feels like  ♫