Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
꧁Wings of Angels꧂Team @Viki.com
'Snowfall Street' - Chen Zhuoxuan
♫  The night is long, and the moonlight dances within my heart  ♫
♫  As I watch the passers-by wander the city  ♫
♫  Even bitter coffee can become sweet  ♫
♫  Just because you are by my side  ♫
♫  Take a look, even our youthful years spoke of destiny  ♫
♫  Let's continue our journey hand in hand and stand by each other  ♫
♫  Let's wait for our love to grow  ♫
♫  Snowflakes gently falls and rests on my shoulders  ♫
♫  One by one, filled with poems  ♫
♫  May the spring flowers bloom next year just as beautiful  ♫
I... I thought you would come over in the afternoon.
I got something later. So I came early.
- How about I... I'll leave.
- It's okay. I... I'm done here.
I'm sorry.
You broke up with me. So don't say sorry to me.
I've been thinking these days
about where I went wrong exactly.
Later on, I figured it out.
Actually, I didn't do anything wrong.
It's not that only a long-term relationship is a good kind of love.
Getting off halfway just means the journey has changed.
It's not like we are going to be in love just once in our lives.
Maybe there are many more breakups waiting for us.
I'm taking this away.
After all, our relationship was pretty good until it ended.
I'll walk you out.
Since we've already broken up, you should act like it.
I can face it. Goodbye.
Inside this suitcase are things that can be used regularly.
Like band-aids, cold medicine, and a set of sheets and quilt covers.
That suitcase is filled with clothes.
- You are like my mom now.
- It's good to be prepared, right?
Anyway, the items in that suitcase will all come in handy.
If your classmates need anything, give it directly to them and be nice.
By the way, the school usually provides bed sheets and quilt covers. But the quality of those is not good.
Just switch to your own. If you need anything, call me.
I don't lack anything. I don't need these things.
Take them.
Just listen to Xiao Que. She has the experience of college life.
- Once you're there, you'll know if you need them or not.
- That's right.
Grandpa, Xiao Ye will go to college tomorrow. Why not stay a few more days?
What's the rush to leave?
You make me sound utterly idle. I'm busy.
The gateball competition offers points and a bonus this year.
- A bonus? How much is it?
- No, it's a 380-yuan assorted grain gift pack.
- It's so expensive?
- It's a huge pack.
I just came to see you guys. I'm just glad you guys are doing well.
- I'll come when I have time.
- Okay.
Then, when you come, let me know, so I can pick you up.
No need. I can come by myself.
It's so late. Why isn't Xiao Tuo back yet?
He's been working overtime frequently. You should go to sleep.
You should go to sleep too. You need to get up early. Go wash up now.
- It's still early.
- Hurry up.
- Hurry up. Wash first.
- Let me finish this part.
- I'll be with you.
Go back. You still have work to do. Just stay.
We'll see you off.
I'm not senile. I don't need it.
Hurry back. Take care of yourself.
Take good care of Xiao Ye, okay?
Don't worry, Grandpa.
Goodbye, Grandpa. Let us know if you arrive.
Take care.
Let's go.
Did Xu Tianhai get married?
Did Xu Tianhai get married and then divorce?
Or did he never marry at all?
He said his mom was pressuring him to get married in Moments last week.
If you haven't seen that post, you can check your phone right now.
Lin Tuo, whose wedding ceremony did you go to attend?
Say something. What have you done on those days?
Why did you have to lie to me like this?
You came back and broke up with me.
Where on earth did you go?
- We have already broken up.
- Is this the reason for the breakup?
He Xindi is right.
No wonder you can't explain it to me.
No wonder you are so resolute.
I wondered if there was some misunderstanding between us,
if I didn't do well enough and I had neglected you,
and if I should try to win you back.
I now feel like I overthought.
Lin Tuo, you can break up with me.
But you lied to me, and let me down.
- Stop.
- What's up?
Come here and sit down.
What's up?
I have to ask you something. Sit down.
What's up with Lin Tuo?
What do you mean?
Chen Guangpu, tell me the truth. What exactly happened to Lin Tuo?
What are you talking about?
Fine, you're not telling, right?
Listen, Chen Guangpu. I've figured this thing out.
What do you mean?
You may fool Xiao Que, but you can't fool me.
I saw through the coldness and warmth of life in my teens.
My mom got married twice. My dad got married three times. I've been in so many relationships.
I understand men too well.
There's no such thing as breaking up for no reason.
I'm telling you, I have the evidence.
Evidence? What is it?
I told Xiao Que to think properly
if Lin Tuo has had any unusual behavior and if he's disappeared recently.
She told me Lin Tuo had been in his classmate's wedding ceremony for a few days.
I told her there's something fishy about it.
Guess what? That classmate is abroad.
He doesn't even have a girlfriend. So Lin Tuo got caught right away.
No secrets are safe in this world.
So what was Lin Tuo doing during those days?
He went home for a blind date, didn't he? And he found the match, right?
After that, he came back and broke up with Xiao Que.
He Xindi, you're really wasting your talent doing livestreaming.
You should write movie scripts.
My analysis is right, isn't it?
I'm truly impressed.
He Xindi, I underestimated you before.
You're not ordinary.
Hurry to the hospital. Get treatment early.
Alzheimer is now affects younger individuals.
What? Stop the gibberish. Chen Guangpu. I just got it correctly.
The situation is starting to get bad.
You need to be mentally prepared.
Mom.
What's wrong? I have to do ward rounds right away.
By the way, has Xiao Ye gone to college?
- Yes, he has.
-  That's good. You should visit Xiao Ye more on the weekends.
It's his first time leaving home.
Now he still has bad feelings towards me and your dad.
I wanted to take him to college, but he wouldn't let me.
-  I'll see him next month.
- Mom,
I'm sick.
It's ALS.
Mom, it's okay.
Look at me. Except for my right hand, other part is fine, right?
Look at my legs. I can stand and walk.
I'm fine. I can also lift my legs high.
Although a bit slower,
my left hand is quite skilled now. I can cook and write with it.
By the way, let me show you what I've written with my left hand.
Here. Take a look. Not bad, right?
Anyway, it's legible.
Why are you crying again, Mom?
It's okay.
You've always been like this.
You never talk about anything.
You won't tell us where you're going or what you're going to do.
Faced with such a big issue, you still wouldn't tell us.
Haven't I already told you?
Why didn't you say it earlier?
Why didn't you say it right away?
Are you a child without a family? Don't you have parents?
Are you silly?
I do have a family, Mom.
And that's why I couldn't tell you about it.
Mom.
If I didn't tell you,
I wouldn't be able to hug you again.
Xiao Tuo,
don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here. I'm right here.
Dad.
Weren't you on a business trip?
W-Where are your medical records?
Medical records?
They're in the box under the coffee table.
The password is 1105.
Wash your face and brush your teeth. I bought breakfast.
Have something first.
Lin Tuo, I bought you...
Guangpu, they are my parents.
Hello, Uncle, Auntie.
This is my classmate in college and my good friend, Chen Guangpu.
In case something happens to me...
He knows the password here.
I'm here to pick him up for work.
You shouldn't go to work now.
- Let's go to the hospital.
- Dad, I'm still doing okay now.
I can continue to work. There's no use going to the hospital. I'm taking the medicine.
Which hospital and which doctor?
Neurology Department of Baihui Hospital.
Dr. Zhou Fumeng. He is the chief physician.
Leave it to me.
- Is it too tight?
- It's fine.
Why is your dad still so harsh?
You're ill, and he still doesn't treat you kindly.
When my mom gave birth to me and Xiao Ye, my dad was on business trips.
My mom went to the hospital and went back home alone after giving birth.
Although my mom worked at the hospital,
she told me she felt particularly helpless,
and felt like she married the wrong guy.
When Xiao Ye and I were sick back then,
it was always my mom who held both of us, running up and down in the hospital.
In my memory, my dad hardly ever took care of us.
This is the first time I've seen my dad come back in the middle of a business trip.
His eyes are bloodshot.
He definitely didn't sleep all night.
Thankfully, both your parents are doctors. They know a lot.
If this happened to me, my parents would probably do nothing but cry.
Even the doctors
can't help with my illness.
Don't talk nonsense. Do you hear me?
Let's go to work.
Grab my hand tightly.
This side.
Tightly.
Not bad. There hasn't been much change. You need to adjust your condition.
Especially, get your eating and sleeping in order, okay?
Take the medicine.
- Okay, that's it.
- Thank you, Dr. Zhou.
Director Zhou, I am Lin Tuo's father.
Do you have time right now?
Please come in.
You weren't in your seat, so I thought you are here. What's wrong?
It's nothing. I just came out for fresh air.
Your arm hasn't healed?
Such an injury usually takes months to heal.
By the way, my friend's club has a soccer match this weekend.
They are friends I usually play with. If you're free, come along with Guangpu.
With my current condition, I can't play soccer.
Come as a substitute. I'll introduce you to some friends.
They are all designers and some business partners.
Get to know them. We can play soccer when your arm heals.
- You haven't played for a long time.
- That's right.
I've looked over Lin Tuo's medical records.
I've collected some other case studies.
Look, there are even some from abroad.
These are cases of ALS and some related papers.
I'm not sure if they are useful or not.
I can understand how you feel.
But as for Lin Tuo's diagnosis, it's been over half a year.
We've conducted all sorts of tests, including blood tests,
lumbar puncture, cerebrospinal fluid, MRI, and even CT scans.
We've also done EMG twice.
So there shouldn't be anything wrong with the diagnosis.
But I've heard that Guillain-Barre syndrome can be easily mistaken for ALS.
If it's Guillain-Barre, there's still a chance for a cure.
Yes, there are some similarities in the clinical presentation of them.
It's also a key point of attention in our diagnosis.
During our examination,
the phenomenon of protein cell separation in the cerebrospinal fluid was not present at all.
So the EMG's electrophysiological examination showed it is completely inconsistent with Guillain-Barre syndrome.
Therefore, it can be ruled out.
What about the case from abroad?
Are there any good treatment and diagnostic methods available abroad?
Under the current conditions, there is not much difference between overseas and domestic ones.
The internet information exchange is essentially synchronous.
We have some patients who went abroad for medical treatment.
But in the end, our peers abroad suggested they come back for treatment.
I have been practicing medicine for almost 30 years
and have seen too many incurable patients.
But when it comes to myself, I truly cannot accept my own child...
Then, Director Zhou, do you have any good advice?
Why is the senior sending you messages?
Why are you peeking at my phone?
I'm not peeking. I'm looking openly.
You could just get a privacy film.
I'd need to install an entire privacy screen.
Tell me. What does the senior want with you?
To play soccer on the weekend.
Play soccer? I'm going too.
- You know how to play?
- I know how to watch.
- Do I need you to watch?
- I'm not watching you.
He Xindi, when we play soccer, why do you always meddle?
I'm doing it for Xiao Que.
Isn't Lin Tuo also going to play soccer?
What are you up to this time?
Creating opportunities for them to get back together.
He Xindi, I'm begging you. Mind your own business.
They have broken up. And yet you want to force them together.
Why are you so malicious?
What?
Our friends have broken up. Are you just watching them for fun?
I get it.
Is Lin Tuo going to bring along a girl? Are you afraid we might get in the way?
- He Xindi.
- What?
If there was really a demon, it would only be you and no one else.
- You demon! Your family is a demon.
- Go away.
Xiao Que! Xiao Que!
They're playing soccer this weekend. Let's watch it.
I'm not going.
Why is that? Let's go together. It's no big deal.
You deserve it!
Your family is a demon.
Mom, why are you here?
I thought it is about time. So I came to pick you up to go home.
There's half an hour left. Come in. Take a look at where I work.
Is that okay?
- I'm almost off work. It's okay.
- Okay.
This floor is where I work.
It's the Design Department Team 3.
These are all my colleagues.
- This is my mom.
- Hello, Mrs. Lin.
- Hello.
- Mrs. Lin.
- Hello, everyone.
This is my seat.
- What would you like to drink? I'll get it for you.
- Don't mind me.
- Our pantry has everything.
- No need. Go about your business.
Hello, Mrs. Lin.
I'm Wei Haiyang, Lin Tuo's leader.
- Hello, Mr. Wei.
- Hello.
- Sorry to disturb your work.
- We're almost off work. It's fine.
- You're welcome to visit at any time.
- Thank you.
Is Lin Tuo working hard here?
He's not only working hard but also extraordinarily talented.
He's a rare talented designer.
Mrs. Lin, how about you come to my office for some tea?
Let's have a chat. Come this way, please.
Okay.
Come on, Mrs. Lin.
- Thanks. Thank you.
- Sorry for the delay.
Lin Tuo was originally going to be promoted to Designer.
He told me about his situation.
He wants to keep working. I support him.
Thank you.
Lin Tuo told you about this first.
It means that he really trusts you.
I only found out yesterday.
His father was on a business trip. He came over overnight after finding out.
Actually, we were not mentally prepared.
However, both his dad and I work at the hospital.
We do have some understanding of this disease.
I also brought him to meet pharmaceutical experts.
We learned about the current medical development for this disease.
They have done related research.
Lin Tuo has caused you quite a bit of trouble.
Not at all.
He has always been strong.
If he still wants to work, there will always be a position for him here.
Thank you, Director Wei.
His father went to the hospital today to see his chief physician.
We want to have him re-examined.
So I'm asking for a few days off on his behalf.
No problem. Go ahead and get the examination done.
And cooperate with the treatment. I'm waiting for your return.
You are back.
Hurry and wash your hands to eat.
You're on time.
- Change shoes and wash your hands.
- Okay.
I haven't cooked for a while. I'm not sure how it tastes. Try it.
- You try it too.
- Okay.
Is it a bit bland?
- No, it's not. It's tasty.
- It's good.
Dad, Mom.
Before we eat, I want to tell you something first.
I broke up with Xiao Que.
She doesn't know I have this disease.
I don't want to burden her.
Nor do I want Grandpa and Xiao Ye to know.
Grandpa is getting old. He has a weak heart. I fear he can't endure it.
Xiao Ye has just started college.
I want him to go to college happily.
Let's tell him when there's a chance later.
Is that okay?
Okay.
Let's skip it for now.
You all know how my illness will turn out.
But it won't become critical immediately.
I can still take care of myself now. Don't worry too much about me.
Once you're finished, go back to work.
I can take care of myself.
Your dad and I have discussed it. We want to take you back with us.
It's more convenient to seek treatment back home. And we can take care of you.
Mom, you know about my illness. There's not much to do about it.
It's not the kind that requires medication or hospitalization.
But how can you manage alone?
I'm not alone. Guangpu drives me to work and back every day.
He also looks after me. I got my leader at the company.
They've assigned me quite simple tasks.
I'm just be an assistant.
And my colleagues are very kind to me as well.
I want to spend more time at work while I still can,
and be with everyone a bit more.
There will be plenty of days ahead to be looked after by you.
I don't want
to stay at home like a useless one right now.
Before that day comes,
please treat me as a normal person.
Will you?
Okay.
Let's do as Xiao Tuo says.
That's all? Let's eat.
Eat more.
Sir.
- Could you give me a cigarette?
- Sure.
Thank you.
Are you all right?
- It's been a while since I last smoked. Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
Guangpu, thank you.
You're welcome. No thanks are needed between us.
I can take care of him. Please rest assured.
Then we'll go in first.
- Please go ahead.
- Okay.
♫  Chasing after the evening glow in traffic  ♫
♫  The streetlights don't speak  ♫
♫  Ordinary leaves fall down in an ordinary manner  ♫
♫  Does anyone care?  ♫
♫  I guess the wind has regrets  ♫
♫  Listen, the years are passing by  ♫
♫  Seem to say there's still reluctance  ♫
♫  But one must grow up  ♫
♫  Time is still kind, isn't it?  ♫
Bye.
How is it?
We need to await test results. They won't come out so quickly.
We don't have to wait here.
That's true. Then let's go home first.
Let's eat out today.
What would you like to eat? Your dad is treating.
- Hotpot.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Let's go.
You had been in bed for six hours. You must be tired.
♫  "There's still time," what a beautiful phrase  ♫
- What else?
- Crispy meat.
Okay, crispy meat.
Take a look at what you want to eat.
You two should order.
Then let's add... Add this one.
Miss. We are done ordering.
Okay. What would you like to drink? I'm placing the order.
- Beer.
- Okay.
Dad, you're drinking?
The two of us can drink some.
- All right, two bottles.
- Make it three.
Okay, just a moment.
- You are drinking too?
- Yes.
Dad, do you remember back when I was in high school?
It's the birthday of my classmate, and we sneaked out to drink.
We ended up getting really drunk.
The shop owner called an ambulance, which took us to your hospital.
You rushed into the room and kicked the bed over.
I sobered up instantly from fear.
You were a high school student. Sneaking out to drink behind your parents' backs was outrageous.
You ended up being hospitalized. How could I tolerate that?
After that time, I drank again in my sophomore year.
I didn't dare to take a sip at gatherings after the college entrance exam.
Xiao Que is good at drinking. She drinks a little with her dad every day.
I'm quite envious of her. I always think...
about the day when I can also drink with my dad.
Come on.
Mom.
Dad.
Thanks.
Look, isn't my left hand getting quite skilled?
It's pretty nimble.
You favored using your left hand to eat before.
I even thought you would become a left-hander.
They say left-handers are smarter. Is that true?
It's false.
There's no scientific basis for it. Left-handers and right-handers are the same.
It's merely a matter of habit.
They ordered a peach oolong smoothie.
I might have remembered it wrong.
Let me make another one. Send the customer a dessert as well.
It's okay. I'll do it. You should take a break.
You're here.
- Iced Americano?
- That's right.
Okay.
Where's Xiao Que?
She's upset. I'll call her for you.
There's no need. I'll take it to go.
Okay. Please wait a moment. It will be ready soon.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
꧁Wings of Angels꧂Team @Viki.com
'It's Love' - Dong Shuhan
♫  The moment we met  ♫
♫  It feels like I'm being electrified  ♫
♫  Your face… Oh, my God  ♫
♫  That's what my Mr. Right looks like  ♫
♫  What do I do? I'm falling for you  ♫
♫  Happiness comes unexpectedly  ♫
♫  Cupid's arrow  ♫
♫  Makes everything indescribably wonderful  ♫
♫  The stars blink as if it's confessing love  ♫
♫  You seem to walk right out of the light  ♫
♫  My heart is beating so wildly  ♫
♫  I'm secretly rewinding my memories  ♫
♫  Oh my ~  ♫
♫  My heart is beating so wildly  ♫
♫  I'm secretly rewinding my memories  ♫
♫  Oh, my ~  ♫
♫  It's love, love  ♫
♫  Why do I feel like I'm on cloud nine?  ♫
♫  I'm so happy that even insomnia is all right
(So happy that even insomnia is all right)  ♫
♫  I'm walking with you all night long in my mind
(Walking with you all night long in my mind)  ♫
♫  So this is what love feels like  ♫