'Snowfall Street' - Chen Zhuoxuan
♫  The night is long, and the moonlight dances within my heart  ♫
♫  As I watch the passers-by wander the city  ♫
♫  Even bitter coffee can become sweet  ♫
♫  Just because you are by my side  ♫
♫  Take a look, even our youthful years spoke of destiny  ♫
♫  Let's continue our journey hand in hand and stand by each other  ♫
♫  Let's wait for our love to grow  ♫
♫  Snowflakes gently falls and rests on my shoulders  ♫
♫  One by one, filled with poems  ♫
♫  May the spring flowers bloom next year just as beautiful  ♫
I've packed your bag.
You're awake now.
Then wash up and eat.
I'll go call Xiao Ye.
Didn't I tell you to wait for me while I went to get the wheelchair?
Can't you see how high the steps are? What if you fall again?
Doc said you should travel in a wheelchair from now on. In a wheelchair.
You get it?
Got it.
Sit.
Sit down.
Easy.
Is the height okay for you?
Let's go then.
That's enough.
Need something?
Leader, I have a favor to ask of you.
Sit.
Doesn't look like official business. Go ahead.
Lin Tuo needs to use a wheelchair now.
He can walk, but the doctor recommended minimal walking.
Can you make some adjustments to Lin Tuo's work if possible?
Can he work now?
He wants to. He doesn't want to bother you.
And it's not him who sent me to you.
I just wanted to ask if he could possibly keep his job?
I can help him with some things, or change my seat if necessary.
Then just join Team 3.
Okay.
Han Yuxi wouldn't let me get away with it if you did.
I can apply myself.
Don't.
You know how sensitive Han Yuxi is.
Moreover, you're the only ace in her group.
I don't want to cause trouble.
Is Lin Tuo doing okay right now?
He's clearly less spirited than before.
This fall has been quite a blow to him.
I'm afraid he won't be able to cope.
Understood.
Tell him to take care.
I'll take care of his job.
Thank you, Leader.
- See you later.
- Okay.
Don't ask Han Yuxi to change your group.
Stay there. Don't cause me trouble.
Got it.
Hello, here's your coffee.
- Thank you.
- No sweat.
I saw Chen Guangpu and Lin Tuo on my way to HW.
We need a car...
to get up this slope. Pushing is exhausting.
- Is this speed okay, boss?
- Sure, as long as you're not tired.
Need to go any faster?
Disabled, right? Is this the reason for the breakup?
You're quite the liar. Keep lying. You should find a decent reason.
- Xiao Que, it's not what you think.
- Then what is it?
Enjoying teaming up and deceiving me? Feeling good, aren't you?
- No, we can explain.
- No need for explanations.
Get up.
Lin Tuo, get up and say something!
What happened?
What happened to your arm?
You've seen it.
- Let's go home and talk.
- Xiao Que.
Leave us alone.
What's wrong with your arm?
It can't move.
Why?
Disease.
What disease?
ALS.
What will happen?
I'll die.
Can it be cured?
No.
That's why we broke up?
Right.
Okay, then I'll tell you now.
It doesn't count.
An Zhique...
You don't need to do this.
I have made it very clear. My illness is incurable.
- I am not joking with you.
- Do you think I am joking with you?
You heard me clearly, right?
This illness gives me only three years to live. Five years, tops.
Everyone will die, including me.
- It's not like that.
- Then you tell me what will happen. Your arm can't move now, can it?
Can it be treated or not?
It's not as simple as you think.
It's not about treating.
It's an incurable illness. There's no medicine for it.
It's the arm now. Soon, it will be the whole body.
I'll be paralyzed, worthless! You want to see me like this?
You should go.
You deserve better.
I mean it.
Please go. Go.
Just go!
Why are you yelling at me? Stop playing this tragic love with me.
Everyone will die one day!
Even if we make it to two hundred, we will still die.
Then let's separate after death. Why must we separate while we are alive?
Stop telling me this is an incurable illness. Get treatment if you are sick.
Aren't you just fine right now? Aren't you sitting here all well?
Your arm can still move, can't it?
I am asking you, yes or no?
You can still sleep well and go out.
You can still sit here properly.
Then why are you trying to drive me away?
Lin Tuo, if I leave, will your illness get better?
I don't even know what I did wrong. And you just don't want me anymore.
Lin Tuo, can you please stop pushing me away?
Can you please stop pushing me away?
I'm sorry.
He Xindi.
- He Xindi, open the door.
- Stop knocking. I won't open it.
Do you think I want to deceive you?
Do you think I feel good deceiving you?
I, Chen Guangpu, have deceived quite a few people. I've told quite a few lies.
I really wish it was a lie this time.
I wish it was all a lie.
It can be treated, but cannot be cured.
That's what the doctor said.
It means...
Lin Tuo's illness cannot be cured. It is a terminal illness. Lin Tuo is going to die.
Since that day, it's like I've been living a dream,
watching my buddy await death, but I can't help him!
Lin Tuo is my buddy.
He is my family.
I'm sorry and worried for him. I dare not tell him, for fear of making him feel bad.
Every day, I still have to pretend that nothing's happened in front of all of you.
But what about me?
When I am left alone every night, what should I do?
Does anyone know how much pain I'm in?
My buddy is going to die. There's nothing I can do.
Lin Tuo... Lin Tuo is such a good person.
Why does it have to be Lin Tuo?
That's how it is with this disease.
Is there really no other way?
Up to now, there has been no way to cure this disease.
I understand how you feel.
But I still hope you can understand ALS more fully and objectively,
not just from a loved one's perspective.
- Dad.
- What are you doing this late?
We need to talk.
Can't it wait till tomorrow?
Xiao Tuo is ill.
I know this disease.
When I was taking care of your mom, I've seen such patients.
It begins with limb immobility and eventually causes total paralysis.
- And after that...
- Xiao Tuo is not that severe.
It's just that he needs someone to take care of him now.
Who will do that? You want to do that?
But you don't have experience. How could you know how?
Well, I can do laundry, cook, and do household chores.
No, taking care of a patient is really different from doing laundry or cooking.
Dad, it's not about doing laundry or cooking. It's about Xiao Tuo.
Yes, I know it's about Xiao Tuo. That's why I feel bad about it.
How could such a good person end up with this disease?
He is already there. There's no point in saying anything now.
So, how sick is Xiao Tuo now?
He's in a wheelchair.
His legs can't move now?
They can. The doctor insists on no falls, so a wheelchair.
Then how is he supposed to live his life from now on?
That's why I'm thinking of moving in with Tuo to take care of him.
In case he falls again, or something. He now needs someone by his side.
You go to Xiao Tuo's place to take care of... No, Xiao Que, let me tell you.
Xiao Tuo's illness, you know, is nothing like a fracture or fever. It's not about lending a hand.
It leads to total paralysis and he'll be immobile, needing help with everything.
- He's so tall. Can you lift him? How can you...
- Dad.
So should I just leave him alone?
Didn't you take care of my mom the same way back then?
I didn't mean that.
You can help in other ways. And the person I cared for was your mom, right?
But Xiao Tuo is my boyfriend. He is also my family.
I love Xiao Tuo, just like you love Mom.
When you were taking care of my mom, did you think about these things?
No, it has nothing to do with that. Let me tell you.
An Zhique, you must stay calm now, do you understand?
You can't just do this in the heat of the moment.
Because I have taken care of your mom, I know how hard it is to take care of a sick person.
I won't let you do it. Don't try to be a hero, okay?
Dad, no, why would I?
Trying to be a hero for what? I'll be given a medal or something?
When I was not doing well, Xiao Tuo was by my side.
Now he's not doing well, and he needs someone, I need to be by his side. He needs me.
- Yes, Xiao Tuo needs you. I need you, too!
- Then what do you mean?
- I'm your dad. I also need you to take care of me. I'm sick too.
- What do you mean?
So now it's between boyfriend and Dad, and I can only choose one?
- I didn't make you choose, did I? I just want you...
- So what do you mean?
What you're saying now...
makes me think you're especially selfish.
No, I'm not.
An Zhique, h-how am I being selfish?
How am I being selfish, An Zhique?
I won't let my girl go down in flames. Shouldn't I do that?
S-Shouldn't I prevent my daughter from suffering?
I am your father, right? You are my daughter.
Fine. If I can stop you by being selfish...
Okay, then I'll be selfish.
I am selfish! I am selfish!
I'm selfish! I'm selfish!
- Don't go, okay? Okay?
- What are you doing?
Don't go, please?
Okay?
Just don't do it, okay?
Dad, I know you care about me. You don't want me to go.
And Xiao Tuo, he also doesn't want me to endure this hardship.
That's why he insists on breaking up with me.
But have you thought about me?
If I leave today, if anything happens to him,
do you think I could live with myself?
Dad,
I'm going to speak frankly to you now.
If his illness really can't be cured, he could only live for another three to five years.
Just let me endure these for three to five years.
If I run away today, I'd have to bear this guilt for a lifetime.
Is that okay?
Please, I'm begging you, okay? Let me go, Dad.
Please let me go, I beg you. Please let me go, okay, Dad?
Dad, I'm begging you.
Please, just let me go.
Xiao Tuo, I bought you breakfast. Remember to eat it.
Xiao Que, what are you doing?
I'm going to buy some food. What would you like for lunch and dinner?
Xiao Que, let's have a talk.
Let's talk when I get back. Or I'll just pick what's appealing.
- Eat it before it gets cold.
- Xiao Que.
Xiao Tuo.
Xiao Tuo, wake up, it's time to eat.
♫  The night is long, and the moonlight dances within my heart  ♫
♫  As I watch the passers-by wander the city  ♫
♫  Even bitter coffee can become sweet  ♫
♫  Just because you are by my side  ♫
♫  Take a look, in this world, love is ever-present  ♫
♫  The soft murmurs of time hold an added warmth  ♫
♫  Let's wait for our love to grow  ♫
♫  Let's continue the conversation we didn't finish  ♫
♫  Don't sigh over the slow passage of time  ♫
♫  Sending eternal wishes to the furthest corners of the world  ♫
♫  Let's wait for our love to grow  ♫
♫  Snowflakes gently falls and rests on my shoulders  ♫
♫  One by one, filled with poems  ♫
♫  May the spring flowers bloom next year just as beautiful  ♫
Generally, I don't cook. I can't just casually flex my skills.
These ingredients are quite expensive. I can't bear to see you waste food.
Shut your mouth.
Feel free to skip the meal.
Leave me alone. Go watch TV or something. Don't affect my performance.
We're doomed.
The ingredients will be wasted, and your kitchen could end up a mess too.
Food is served!
Here you go.
Well, Lin Tuo.
Give it a try.
How is it?
- Delicious.
- Isn't it?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Really?
- Eat more.
- Have some more.
- Did you make this?
Or what?
You... You ordered it in advance and hid it here, didn't you?
Come on, we came here together. Did you see me hide anything?
He Xindi, you can't even wash socks properly.
How did you pull off a feast like this? I don't believe it.
I've been independent since childhood. I couldn't even survive without my cooking skills.
These dishes are nothing special, I'll cook something fancier for you next time.
For this meal you made today,
I take back my words about you not being able to get married.
If you could make me dishes like this every day, I might marry you.
Forget it. I'd marry the tree downstairs before marrying you.
Also, I won't spend my days cooking like a maid, no matter who I marry.
Then you still won't be able to get married.
So you get married just to have someone cook for you?
For mutual benefits. She makes delicious food for me.
I earn money to support her. No problem, right?
Okay, Chen Guangpu,
if you give me one hundred thousand yuan a month, maybe I'll consider marrying you.
Then you might as well marry a tree.
Come on, Lin Tuo, eat some more.
Ma'am, someone wants to see you.
Let them in.
Auntie.
Xiao Tuo doesn't want you to know.
So at that time, he broke up with me quite decisively.
That's so Xiao Tuo.
He seems obedient but is very stubborn inside.
What I'm worrying about now is how to keep it from Grandpa and Xiao Ye.
Xiao Ye will be back on vacation. You can't hide it from him.
- But Grandpa...
- He is getting old.
His heart isn't good.
He raised Xiao Tuo on his own. We can't tell him.
I understand.
So I came here to discuss with you about taking care of Xiao Tuo.
I know.
You two love each other.
But it's not as simple as you think.
I'm planning to retire early or resign to take care of Xiao Tuo.
Auntie, what I'm thinking is...
Uncle Lin and you are professionals,
so of course, you know how to take care of him better than I do.
But to treat this illness, we need maybe years, not just a few months.
The cost of treatment and nursing care can be quite high.
We can't all just quit our jobs, can we?
What if we have to go to Beijing or Shanghai for treatment?
Or what if we have to go abroad? All of this requires money.
You two should just keep working and earning money.
I'll take care of Xiao Tuo.
My cafe isn't far from Tuo's home. I can bring him along when I go to work.
It's okay. It won't affect my work at all.
Xiao Tuo isn't that sick right now.
He can still work.
Right now, we just need to give him some confidence.
Tell him everything is fine, and that he just needs to take care.
Xiao Que,
you're only in your twenties.
This is too much for you.
It's not fair.
Auntie, Xiao Tuo being sick is fate.
I am his girlfriend.
That's also fate.
Since we've already accepted this fate,
we can't let it defeat us, can we?
You two love Xiao Tuo,
so do I.
We can't give up on him.
Thank you.
- What a coincidence! I just bought some plums, your favorite.
- Grandpa.
- Thank you, Grandpa.
- I could've prepped something nice if I knew.
I can get some fish from the market, and make you fish with pickled vegetables.
No need. I just came by to see you.
I have to go back soon. A'Bao is alone in the cafe. He can't manage it.
Now that you're here, at least have a meal with me.
We can eat together when Xiao Tuo returns from his business trip.
That would be better, wouldn't it? I just came back to see you.
Xiao Tuo's been traveling a lot recently, hasn't he?
He doesn't even reply to my video messages.
No kidding. He's been really busy recently,
working overtime every day, and traveling every week.
I can hardly see him.
The last time we watched a movie together was two months ago.
That won't do. How are you supposed to live like this?
If we don't strive now, life will be even harder later, right?
Rest assured, I support him, a hundred percent.
We are good.
Dad.
Why are you here? You should be at work.
Just finished a surgery.
Uncle.
Xiao Tuo's mom said you were here, so I came to see you.
Grandpa, could you please make me a cup of tea?
I'm craving for your herbal tea. With some ginseng, please.
No problem. I got a lot of good stuff.
One for Shouzheng as well. You'll sleep very soundly at night.
Thank you, Grandpa.
Xiao Tuo's mom has already told me.
- You...
- Don't worry.
Thank you.
Xiao Tuo is lucky to have you... as his girlfriend.
Then let's work hard together to make this luck last longer.
I'm getting on in years and feeling weaker now.
No way. You play gateball pretty well, don't you? You even won a trophy.
I cheated, kicking the last ball in with my foot.
That counts too.
I don't know if I can take part in next year's season.
I can't leave Xiao Tuo behind.
Xiao Tuo is doing well.
I'm by his side. You have nothing to worry about.
Of course, I feel much more at ease with you there.
I hope you two live a long and happy life together.
I promise you. We will definitely live a long and happy life together.
Okay.
Grandpa, the cab's here. I should go.
Call me anytime if you need anything.
All right.
You may go back.
- Text me when you get home.
- Sure thing.
Xiao Que,
remember to bring Xiao Tuo along next time.
We'll come to see you together next time. I'll tell him as I get back.
See you, Grandpa.
Take care.
It's cold here. Let's go inside.
Just a few more minutes.
Okay.
Do you know where I went today?
I went to your home. I met with your dad, mom, and grandpa.
Did you tell Grandpa?
How could I?
I told him you were on a business trip.
I came back to attend a wedding and to visit him.
Then what did you say to my parents?
Haven't you always wanted to talk to me?
So, shall we talk now?
Sure.
Auntie told me she's preparing to resign.
Uncle also plans to give up the race for director to look for a cure for you.
I said to Auntie that I hope they can continue working.
After all, treating this illness will cost a lot of money.
We can't just all stop working, can we?
So I'll take care of you.
I'll be a burden to you.
Hear me out.
When I first learned that you had this illness, I was indeed overwhelmed.
Later, I went to see Director Zhou,
visited the rehabilitation center, and saw those patients with ALS.
I now have a rough idea of what this disease is like.
Actually, I'm quite scared.
I don't know if I can handle it, or how long I can hold on.
I'm not a particularly great person.
I do this only because I love you.
I want to stay by your side.
So don't feel like a burden.
I can't make any promises.
When I can no longer hold on,
I might run away or give up.
So while I'm still here,
let me stay by your side.
Xiao Que.
- I...
- If one day I give up, could you not blame me?
I won't.
Never.
Okay.
Then in every weekend to come, your mom and dad will come to live with us.
I run my cafe, and you keep working.
None of us will give up.
You also have to cheer up. Let's all be a bit cooler, shall we?
Don't cry, shout, or feel helpless when things get tough.
I won't accept any suggestions made to me.
I demand that we face this together.
Don't ever think about driving me away.
It's pointless, so don't bother.
I'm not discussing this with you now.
I'm demanding you. Do you understand?
Okay.
Then let's go to bed. Tomorrow is a new day.
Let's begin with a good night's sleep.
Let's go.
Come on, stretch your arms.
That's good. Dress up sharply and go to work with me at HW.
Let's go.
Chen Guangpu...
did get you an advanced wheelchair.
Yeah, it's electric, moving on its own.
But I may not be able to operate it with my hands in the future.
Exactly, no matter how advanced it is, it still requires humans to operate it.
Could it possibly be voice-controlled?
- Brother. I'll do it.
- A'Bao.
- Take it easy.
- All right, one, two, three.
Be careful.
Welcome back. I have already prepared food for you.
We got iced Americano, ginseng lemon blossom tea,
and silky egg and shrimp sandwich.
Give it a try.
- Okay.
- Try it.
Is it tasty?
It is.
Brother, I am so happy to have you back.
Plus, I also can take care of you. I'm good at it. It's free!
And I don't know what else to say.
Anyway, just keep it up. We all love you.
Thank you, A'Bao.
Right, I baked a cake for you. I'll go get it.
Director Lin.
How is it? Not that bad, right?
Amazing, actually.
Come on, take a bite.
'It's Love' - Dong Shuhan
♫  The moment we met  ♫
♫  It feels like I'm being electrified  ♫
♫  Your face… Oh, my God  ♫
♫  That's what my Mr. Right looks like  ♫
♫  What do I do? I'm falling for you  ♫
♫  Happiness comes unexpectedly  ♫
♫  Cupid's arrow  ♫
♫  Makes everything indescribably wonderful  ♫
♫  The stars blink as if it's confessing love  ♫
♫  You seem to walk right out of the light  ♫
♫  My heart is beating so wildly  ♫
♫  I'm secretly rewinding my memories  ♫
♫  Oh my ~  ♫
♫  My heart is beating so wildly  ♫
♫  I'm secretly rewinding my memories  ♫
♫  Oh, my ~  ♫
♫  It's love, love  ♫
♫  Why do I feel like I'm on cloud nine?  ♫
♫  I'm so happy that even insomnia is all right
(So happy that even insomnia is all right)  ♫
♫  I'm walking with you all night long in my mind
(Walking with you all night long in my mind)  ♫
♫  So this is what love feels like  ♫