'Snowfall Street' - Chen Zhuoxuan
♫  The night is long, and the moonlight dances within my heart  ♫
♫  As I watch the passers-by wander the city  ♫
♫  Even bitter coffee can become sweet  ♫
♫  Just because you are by my side  ♫
♫  Take a look, even our youthful years spoke of destiny  ♫
♫  Let's continue our journey hand in hand and stand by each other  ♫
♫  Let's wait for our love to grow  ♫
♫  Snowflakes gently falls and rests on my shoulders  ♫
♫  One by one, filled with poems  ♫
♫  May the spring flowers bloom next year just as beautiful  ♫
Morning.
- Morning.
- Morning, Senior.
- Senior.
- You're so early.
- Lin Tuo, see you outside.
- See you.
Senior, I'm so glad you came.
If you didn't come, we'd feel doomed again.
Don't count on me. I haven't trained for two months.
I just came back from the exhibition in Guangzhou.
Still, you're a better player than us.
We're counting on you to win this annual contest.
And you know what? 80 percent of those girls are here for you.
How do I train to look like that?
Low-calorie meals. Work out every day. And there you go.
I haven't been working out. Want to join me?
No, I can't make it without hotpots.
Did the campus recruitment fair start?
We're still going through interviews.
Anything you like?
Not yet.
Our company is also recruiting, but it's not targeting graduates.
Send me your resume. I'll forward it to our HR.
Our line of work matches your major.
All right. Thanks, Senior.
No problem.
And you, Guangpu? Want to give it a try?
No, thanks. That's not my major.
I'm not much of a designer. I'll just stick to funds management.
I heard you had a family business to take over.
No, no.
Our wholesale business doesn't make money.
I'm just going to stay home and get allowances from my mom.
It's nothing like your family business.
My family business doesn't match my major. I prefer the job I'm doing.
Do they have a new media department where you work?
Yeah, they do.
Any vacancies?
I have no idea. I can ask them. Why?
All right. If there is a vacancy, can you hand in another resume?
All right, send it to me.
Okay, thank you. I'll treat you to dinner.
I won't let you pay. Do your best in the game.
Of course.
Let's go.
- Is the captain here? Come with me.
- Yeah.
- See you out there. Hurry.
- Let's go.
What? Don't you want them?
Let's go.
Here. Sit.
Sit there.
It's not even cold yet. Why are you wearing the scarf?
I wear it to create layers. This is fashion. You know?
The sports guys are super handsome.
I may find a few I like.
A few?
So that I have options.
Even if it doesn't work, we still have many seniors here.
Lin Tuo.
- Here.
- Thanks.
- Is Jiang Chucheng here?
- Yeah. There.
Senior.
I asked for a favor one year ago. You should have gotten me his WeChat.
He's here today. Get it done.
Oh, come on. Forget it.
He's way out of your league.
- What...
- I'm telling the truth.
Hilarious. Just be a quiet backup.
Excuse me. I'm a starter.
Ace defender. You can cheer for me once I score.
Trying to fool me? A defender is going to score? Just don't score any own goals.
Now, I swear I'll score two goals today. Applaud once I score.
All right, then.
Look how frail he is. He's going to score?
Senior said their company was also hiring designers and new media staff.
I told him to forward our resumes.
- All right, where does he work?
- Ji Jia Design. It's a leader in the industry.
- I'll send you my resume.
- Lin Tuo.
Good luck!
- Coming.
- Go for it.
- See you.
- Go ahead.
- You got this.
- Go for it, Senior.
- Go, Dong Yuan.
Go! Go!
Go for it!
- Lin Tuo.
- Go for it, Senior.
Go, Dong Yuan! Go, Senior!
♫  I want you to know that time waits for no one  ♫
♫  We must never give up  ♫
♫  Let's break, destroy, and burn empty promises  ♫
♫  Fearlessly, we keep marching forward  ♫
♫  I'm going against the tide  ♫
♫  Breakthrough! Break the shackles  ♫
♫  Setbacks can't bring us down  ♫
♫  We won't back down even if we're exhausted  ♫
Chen Guangpu, you loser!
You're a defender! Stop posing! Geez. What's his problem?
- What are you doing?
- Forget it.
- Let's go.
- It's in.
Go!
♫  In this vast world, there's nothing to be afraid of  ♫
♫  And nothing will stop me from going  ♫
Lin Tuo.
- Go, Lin Tuo!
- You got this!
Go, Dong Yuan.
♫  Even when I am lost and want to give up  ♫
♫  I'll reclaim what was once mine  ♫
♫  I'm flying against the current  ♫
Give it to me. You got this!
♫  Setbacks can't bring us down  ♫
♫ We don't back down
because we're warriors ♫
♫ Breakthrough! Don't stop me ♫
♫ Swiftly turn and avoid the attack ♫
♫ This is my constant pursuit ♫
♫ The old days have become my memories ♫
♫  I'll be even more persistent  ♫
♫  We're running out of time   ♫
♫  Breakthrough! Break the shackles  ♫
♫  Setbacks can't bring us down  ♫
♫  We won't back down even if we're exhausted  ♫
Lin Tuo!
- Lin Tuo!
Go!
♫  All the mean stares  ♫
♫  Fearless is the way I live  ♫
Lin Tuo scored!
Way to go, Lin Tuo!
- Lin Tuo!
- That was bad. Is he fine?
- What's going on?
Lin Tuo.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Are you hurt? Is it bad?
- Are you okay?
- Just a sprain. It's okay.
- Take a break.
- No need.
- Are you okay?
- Can you go on?
- Yeah. It's okay.
- Can you move?
- Okay.
- Can you get up?
- Go on.
- Be careful.
- I got rusty. I'm okay.
- You sure?
You sure?
Lin Tuo, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Oh, come on.
So sweet.
Here, let me toast you.
He Xindi, can you stop pulling a long face?
We tied with them today. You know what it means?
We wiped out the humiliation.
Stop bragging like you're the one who scored.
So ignorant. I passed the ball. That's the key, isn't it?
Yeah.
She's just upset because she didn't talk to the senior.
It took me two hours to put on the makeup.
He didn't even see me. What a waste.
Lin Tuo, it's been a year. I know I can't count on you.
How come I just can't get his WeChat?
I talked to him but he said no.
Just send me his WeChat name card.
T-That's inappropriate.
Don't give him a hard time. He's too good to be honest.
Let me make it clear. Our senior is really popular.
Thousands of girls want his WeChat. But they can't have it.
Why would he give it to you?
Forget it. He's way out of your league.
Chen Guangpu, if you didn't just say that, I wouldn't mind not having his WeChat.
But you did, so I have to make it happen now.
If I add him on WeChat and become his friend,
you'll buy me barbecue for a month. Fair deal, right?
Be friends? You made it even tougher. Okay. Deal.
Where is he working again? I'll send them my resume and be his colleague.
Ji Jia Design. It's a leader in the industry.
Xiao Que, Senior said that he'd forward our resumes.
- All right.
- Forward mine as well.
Yeah, forward hers. Make her sell beds and bedsheets.
What does it have to do with you? Shut up.
Rest assured. Once I get into Ji Jia, I'll introduce him to you.
That's my girl.
Have you told him that we're together?
No, he didn't ask.
Don't tell him.
- Why not?
- Office romance is not allowed. They won't hire a couple.
If we want to get hired, we have to keep it a secret.
- Is it necessary?
- Totally.
It's common sense. You have to keep it a secret.
We'll see.
Okay.
Senior.
- Senior.
Dinner is on me.
Senior, come and sit here.
- Thanks.
- Senior.
- Have some meat.
- He doesn't eat beef.
He doesn't?
I'll just have the green.
No, waiter. Take away all the meat dishes.
We want the meat. What's wrong with you?
Get lost if you have a problem.
Y-You don't have to bother. I'm fine with seafood and greens.
No, it's my treat. I decide what we're having.
- It's her call.
- Dinner is on me.
That was the deal. I just got delayed.
You're too polite.
Well, now that we've met, we're friends now, right?
Yeah.
Let me add you on WeChat.
Senior, your QR code, please.
Okay.
Done.
- Dinner is on you.
- Fine.
Waiter, two more servings of seafood.
You're so nice.
Senior, it's nothing. Just dig in. This one is so good.
It's a bit cold.
Why is it so bad? Should we go to the hospital?
No need. I just sprained my ankle. No big deal.
Does it hurt?
Not so much.
Seriously? Don't be so soft.
Soccer players fall all the time. I played half a game with broken bones.
No wonder you are kind of crippled. I bet it's from the injury.
He's injured here, not on the legs.
You're humiliating the host, huh?
- Don't I deserve some respect?
- Why would you say that?
He said...
What about him?
Whatever.
Senior texted me.
Lin Tuo, I sent to our HR the two resumes.
They want to interview both of you tomorrow. Wait for the messages.
Check your text messages.
I'm going to rent a huge apartment.
It's a job interview. You're not hired yet.
- Morning.
Morning, Big Monster.
Morning, Kiddo.
- All right.
- All right, let's go.
- Let's go.
Nice building.
Hello, we're here for the interview.
Come with me.
Please wait here. Someone will come and pick you up.
- Okay, thanks.
- Thank you.
It's quite pretty.
Senior.
- I got you coffee.
- Thank you.
Don't be nervous. Just be casual.
I have a meeting. Let's catch up later.
All right, see you.
Right, add me on WeChat just in case you need something.
Okay.
- I'll scan your QR code.
- Okay.
Okay, let's stay in touch.
- See you. Bye.
- Bye.
Thank you.
They're my juniors. Please look after them.
I know. You've said it many times.
- Afternoon tea is on me.
- Okay.
I'm leaving. Bye.
Bye, Senior.
Lin Tuo. Come with me.
- Okay.
- Wait. Wait.
- Go ahead. Go.
- See you.
I smell something amazing from the corridor.
Dad, wash your hands. Dinner is ready.
Hello, Uncle.
Xiao Lin, you cooked those?
I can tell from the smell. It can't be takeouts.
And it can't be from you.
- I'm still making the soup.
- Okay, thanks.
No problem.
We have a chef.
So happy.
The soup is ready.
Sit down.
Try and see if you like it.
I don't even have to try it. Check out the greens, the meat, the plating, and everything.
It's absolutely perfect.
- Try it, Dad.
- All right.
- It's amazing.
- Okay.
Is it good?
It's amazing. It's way better than the Mi...
- Michelin.
- Yeah, that's right.
Really, this is amazing.
Have you ever dined there?
No, I haven't. But I've heard about it.
- Uncle, try the soup.
- Okay, thanks.
Stay with us and I'll cook for you every day.
Xiao Lin, that's so sweet of you.
I'm deeply moved. Seriously.
Here.
Be careful.
My goodness. Come on.
Sis, what are these? Our place is tiny.
How are we going to move around?
Quit looking for a job. Join me and be a streamer.
How about it?
I'm talking to you. Why are you staring at your phone?
I'm waiting to see if there's a second interview.
What did you say?
I said you should forget about finding a job. Join me as a streamer.
You know how hard I tried to get into live commerce?
I don't have viewers.
The brands only gave me products thanks to the MCN staff.
I have everything set up.
This is a nice spot. Let's clean it up. And we'll livestream here.
No way.
Why? Let's start a business together.
You're starting your business alone. I can help you but that's it.
Besides, you have to pay me if I part-time for you. Otherwise, I get nothing.
That makes the difference. Don't try to trick me.
- What a fox.
- I'm just broke.
Let me unpack.
It's been two days. Why haven't they contacted me?
What's wrong?
- Good news.
- What is it?
Ji Jia informed me of the second interview.
Really? That's great!
I'm going to meet the director tomorrow.
That's great.
No message for you?
Check it again.
I did. There was nothing.
Let me ask Senior.
Let it be. He's not the boss.
I obviously failed the interview.
Not necessarily. We applied for different departments.
The procedure may be different.
Yeah, meet the director.
I can do a part-time job in the study room.
I can also help He Xindi with her live streaming.
I have many things to do. I'll look for another job.
But I want to go to work with you.
Me too. I can take you to work and pick you up.
At least one of us should have a decent job.
It's better to be you. Then I'm going to take advantage of you.
Good point.
Have the noodles. It's ready.
All right.
I added bamboo shoots with pickled pepper.
Let me try it.
This way.
Director Qian is having a meeting. Please wait here.
- Okay, thank you.
- Want some water?
It's okay. I got this. Thank you.
The pantry is just on the corner.
I'm from the Design Department Team 3. I sit by the window.
Call me if you need me.
Right, I'm Huang Xiaolu.
I'm Lin Tuo. Thank you.
- Have you prepared the material for Dahong?
- I'll dispatch it tomorrow.
Okay, the client doesn't like this.
The color is too dull. He wants us to offer more options.
Confirm it with him. This and that...
They're in different sizes.
Change it, okay?
Huang Xiaolu.
Lin Tuo, you know how to use this?
I haven't tried it before.
- Will the capsules do?
- Yeah.
- Let me help you.
- Thanks.
Let me. Put it down.
Where is the coffee?
Coming. Last one.
- Hurry. We're almost wrapping up.
- Okay.
Please take these to the conference room.
Here is our financial statement.
I always say that design and capital should be integrated.
We're no longer a workshop.
As our core designers, you can't simply focus on your artistic pursuit.
Study the market and look for capital to integrate design with capital, right?
Overall profits for the quarter retained a steady upward trend
but the increase slowed down compared to the previous quarter.
I assume you're aware of the key factor.
The current rise in commodity material prices led to a higher cost.
So we have to highlight our projects with a new design.
- Get me a latte.
- High-consumption design...
Extra sugar.
Okay.
Thank you.
Who made coffee here? Why don't they clean up?
There's water everywhere.
Sorry, Auntie. I did that. Let me clean it up.
- All right, I'll get the trash.
- Sorry,
- I was in a rush.
- Young people are pampered.
You never had a tough day in your life.
Back then, we wouldn't even dream of this.
Look at that. So much coffee left.
There's coffee left in every cup, all going to waste.
Let me clean up, Auntie.
- Sorry.
- You're new here?
Yeah, I made a mess here.
Go ahead. I'll clean the table.
Thank you.
Auntie, wait. Let me do it.
- It's too heavy for you.
- Thank you, kid.
- It's okay.
- What a nice kid.
You're one of a kind.
Thank you.
No problem.
You're new? Which department are you from?
No, I'm here for an interview.
Lin Tuo.
Yeah.
I'm Qian Hong.
Director Qian.
Good for you. You found work to do before you got hired.
Leave it. Come with me.
Time is tight. I have a dinner meeting. So let's cut to the chase.
We're starting a new design group. Sit.
So we're looking for an assistant for the designer.
Theoretically, we want someone with experience.
But I think you got this. Six-month probation, okay?
I got this.
I ran out of chocolate.
You'll work for him during the probation. Director Wei Haiyang from Design Department Team 3.
Hello, Director Wei.
He came for an interview. I'm assigning him to you.
Interview?
Yeah.
You got me coffee.
Yes.
Making coffee has become part of the interview?
I was in the meeting.
He worked in the pantry the whole afternoon.
So he should be a janitor. Why is he working for me?
Those words are not nice.
I can tell he's a hardworking one.
And that's our standard for designers now?
I find him handsome, okay?
I don't care. He's yours.
You'll decide whether to keep him.
Lin Tuo, you'll work for Director Wei Haiyang.
He's our best designer here.
Only he gets to decide if you can stay.
Understood.
I'm not going to the dinner. I have to visit the factory.
You're just anti-social.
That's right. Thanks for the chocolate.
So, Director Qian, am I hired?
It's a probation.
- Thank you.
- Save it.
It's just a probation. He can kick you out at any time.
All right, sign the contract with HR now.
Once you settle the wage, report to the guy you just met.
Wei Haiyang.
He's a very difficult person.
I hope you can hang in there.
Thank you, Director.
Director Wei.
Yes?
I'd like to introduce myself.
No need.
See you at work then.
Xiao Que.
- I got hired.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- That's great!
All right, put me down.
Let's have a feast tonight.
- It's on me.
- Of course. Let's go.
Is it here?
This is Ji Jia's store. Let's take a look.
Let's go.
Welcome to Ji Jia.
It's quite big.
They have everything. Furniture, kitchen stuff, you name it.
And they're running an e-commerce.
That's the amazing thing about Ji Jia Design. They don't just design things.
They've developed a whole industry chain from design to production to sales.
They started as a design workshop and became a tycoon in eight years.
- Amazing, huh?
- Yeah.
And you'll be an amazing designer in this amazing company.
I'm just an amazing designer-to-be on my probation period.
How long will it be?
- Six months.
So you'll be an amazing designer in this amazing company in six...
Enough. Since we're here,
let's get something and check their product quality.
- Let's go.
So cozy.
I wish I could sleep here.
♫  Oh, my ~  ♫
Let's buy it.
All right. Let's see.
- Get up. Don't get it dirty.
- How much is it?
Let's go.
Come here.
Try this.
- What's that?
- A hippo.
A hippo? What's this?
A dog?
Take a photo.
Let's go.
♫  Everything I like has come into my life  ♫
Looking cool, huh?
Kind of.
This mean-looking guy is my superior.
I'm assigned to him as his assistant.
♫  Turn every day into fireworks  ♫
Will they put up your poster one day?
Of course. And they'll post all the furniture I design here.
Each of them will be marked with the initials of my name.
This is so cool!
That's the honor of a designer.
So conceited.
Your posters will be from here to there
with the furniture you designed.
And it will write "Lin Tuo, Chief Designer."
You can have all my designed products.
Why are you so serious? Smile.
Should I? They told me to be formal.
Smile. Come on.
One, two, three, done.
♫  I'm so happy that even insomnia is all right
(So happy that even insomnia is all right)  ♫
What's so funny?
Check out the outfits.
- I look funny.
- The red scarf looks nice.
Let me be formal. It's like a grimace.
Not at all. You look adorable.
Smile more. One, two, three.
With this ID, you can access the whole building. Hold on to it.
You're seated at No. 5 of Design Team 3 on the fourth floor.
Pick up office supplies from the administration with your QR code.
Get Mr. Wei to sign on this. And bring it to me.
Okay, thank you.
There are pantries on every floor. They're pretty much the same.
Our team area is behind that big table.
The director is in the southern area. We're in the northern area.
The VP and chairman's offices are downstairs.
Our exclusive conference room is right ahead.
Director Wei's office is behind that glass office.
I sit over there.
How many team members are there?
Five, including you and Director Wei.
There are two assistant designers. We're their assistants.
I was an intern under Director Qian, and I just got transferred here.
We'll be teammates. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. I'll get Director Wei to sign this first.
All right, a word of advice. Don't be talkative.
Why?
He's got a temper. I got scolded last time.
I've had a taste of it.
- All right, I'll head over.
- Okay.
- Tell me if you need anything.
What's wrong?
Why so sneaky?
Sir, I'm here for your signature.
I'm...
Hello, Director Wei, I'm Lin Tuo. I'm an assistant on probation.
It's my first day here. Please sign on my registration form.
- You're the coffee guy?
- Yeah.
Hired just like that? You have connections?
No, I passed the interview.
I don't care how you got in. You're unlucky to be on my team.
I can kick you out at any time.
Got it, I will do my best.
Don't give me that. Here are the rules.
Don't call me Mr. Wei, Chief Designer Wei will do.
Never come later or leave earlier than me.
Always finish the job I assign you on time.
No exceptions. Stay on standby 24-7.
Don't call me if you can text me. Texts only. No voice messages.
Don't ever say you can't do something or you don't know something.
Don't talk to me unless it's necessary.
Got it.
Thank you, Chief Designer Wei.
Do you play games? King of Glory? PUBG?
- Yeah, I play both.
- How good are you?
PUBG KD 4.6. And 32-star Strongest King.
Not bad, kid.
No games during work hours.
Or I'll punch you.
Got it. Is there anything I can do for you now?
Get out of my office.
Think about what I just said. Get lost. Now.
See you, Chief Designer.
You don't have to pick me up.
It's your first day. It calls for celebration. How did it go?
Fine. It's not what I imagined.
I sat there all day and did nothing.
You just got there. Are the others busy?
Yeah, nobody talked to me at all.
Only the girl on probation period showed me around.
You already met a girl?
The one I met when I came for the interview.
I helped her with the coffee, remember?
You're so warm-hearted?
Just a small favor. I was thinking that maybe we'd be colleagues.
And look happened? She showed me around the office.
Is she pretty?
All right, you can be friends.
Why?
She looks kind.
Got any messages on the interview?
Not yet. It's been too long. I guess I failed.
I applied to some other companies.
I have an interview with the new media department of a real estate company tomorrow.
No rush. I found a job, anyway.
I can support you.
All right, thank you, Sir.
No problem.
- Hey, there.
- All set?
Yeah, done with the paperwork.
Director Qian signed the papers.
- Lunch is on me.
- Thanks, then.
Director Qian likes the kid. She even checked out his resume.
She won't regret it. Right, what about the girl?
I was about to tell you. New media only has one headcount.
Their leader has someone in mind.
So there's no vacancy.
I see.
Do you have any recommendations?
You're too sweet to your juniors.
You're assigning them jobs?
Not entirely.
All right, I'll forward her resume to some other companies.
All right, thanks.
Murder Mystery Games this weekend?
I-I have plans.
Rain check. It's on me. See you.
All right.
I'll send you a resume. Forward it to the headhunters.
'It's Love' - Dong Shuhan
♫  The moment we met  ♫
♫  It feels like I'm being electrified  ♫
♫  Your face… Oh, my God  ♫
♫  That's what my Mr. Right looks like  ♫
♫  What do I do? I'm falling for you  ♫
♫  Happiness comes unexpectedly  ♫
♫  Cupid's arrow  ♫
♫  Makes everything indescribably wonderful  ♫
♫  The stars blink as if it's confessing love  ♫
♫  You seem to walk right out of the light  ♫
♫  My heart is beating so wildly  ♫
♫  I'm secretly rewinding my memories  ♫
♫  Oh my ~  ♫
♫  My heart is beating so wildly  ♫
♫  I'm secretly rewinding my memories  ♫
♫  Oh, my ~  ♫
♫  It's love, love  ♫
♫  Why do I feel like I'm on cloud nine?  ♫
♫  I'm so happy that even insomnia is all right
(So happy that even insomnia is all right)  ♫
♫  I'm walking with you all night long in my mind
(Walking with you all night long in my mind)  ♫
♫  So this is what love feels like  ♫