What happened?
I feel so hot. This tyrant, he's so charming.
He should be the evil.
No.
What's wrong?
Smells not right,
it's the fragrance of intercourse.
Your Majesty, are you alright?
What are you doing?
Bloodletting. It can reduce the effect of the incense.
It's not that necessary.
It's not right, he is the king,
I'm his concubine,
we are legitimate husband and wife,
we should help each other in times of crisis.
Besides, he is the Ning An King,
throughout the ages,
no archaeologist can sleep with a real King,
I'm such a bad ass.
We,
how about we,
I've never heard that
people have a neck pain after sleeping.
Your Highness, you're awake.
Bitao, where's the King?
Your Majesty has left with your father
to go to the court early in the morning,
he specially asked me
to serve you well,
this is the letter your father left you,
he said that you have to read it
before you go back to the imperial palace.
He sent me to testify that
the princess and Yan Ming has an affair,
and he said that they will go to
catch these two after the court.
Catch who?
What's the matter with you,
Your Highness, what happened?
No, I have to report this to His Majesty.
Bitao, you go back to the palace.
Your Majesty, not only you're late for the court,
but you act so frivolous,
it's out of order.
I always like this,
you didn't know that until now?
My sister.
Your Highness, as the King's sister,
you talk so rude to the King,
I'm afraid no one will take your words seriously.
You give your advice everyday to the King,
what's wrong with me
giving some advice?
Do you dare to admit that
what I just said is not what's really in your mind?
You.
Enough, stop quarreling.
Your Highness.
Your excellency,
do you know who princess rushed to see?
Who?
Her new toyboy.
They said they're together every night.
This is,
Princess even has him in the palace.
They're about to meet now in the Ling Yu Palace.
This is the imperial place,
how can we tolerate such a thing.
That's ridiculous.
Though the princess could be domineering,
she will not break the royal law for just a toyboy.
Minister, it's not real, is it?
If you don't believe it,
let's all go to see.
Let's all go to Ling Yu Palace,
if it's not the truth,
we can make the princess a justice.
That's right.
All of you,
please.
Where's the princess?
Your Highness has ordered that,
she will not see the concubine.
Also she has left for the court,
if you really has something urgent,
you can just go the palace to see him.
Then where's the Mr. Yan Ming?
Is he in his residence?
Princess asked him,
he's already in the palace.
Shit,
whether I can change
the Princess's impression of me depends on this time.
God gives me this chance,
I will not miss it.
I'd like too.
We've got here in time,
I wonder what are you all doing here?
He is the famous imperial astronomer, Ling Shan.
Everyone said he's the No. one godlike ones,
he does seem quite immortal style.
This is where the princess lives in the palace,
why is Ling Shan here too?
Ling Shan is doing his duty,
comes here to watch the sky and do the divination.
In princess's house?
That's right.
But the stars appears at night,
now is in the day, and they closed the door.
When the imperial palaces were built,
the buildings were not like before,
which were all symmetry,
Ling Yu Palace corresponds to the position
of the sixth star of the Southern.
Since Your Highness returned victory,
the stars move in the track,
I come in here
to calculate that,
the princess has the Qi Sha star in her life fate,
which is actually the great blessing.
He's so good,
talking all the nonsense with such a dead earnest.
Ling Shan has the ability to tell the good fortune
and bad for great Ning,
and he never failed.
However, if the King didn't approve him of coming here,
it's really gonna get people talking.
What he said is all true.