[English subtitles are available]
Are you out of your mind?
A boss like him
will affect the morale
and lower the staff's willpower
and work efficiency.
If an enterprise
uses this overbearing and autocratic management method
for a long time,
it will cause brain drain.
Mr. Yang.
Go and
draft a proposal.
Take "I am more important than the company"
as this year's management slogan.
Let our company
become an enterprise
that does not press or force employees
and can let employees give full play to their subjective initiative.
That's a great company.
Okay.
Are you out of your mind?
You're still at work.
When you're work, you want to get off work.
We must execute the Chairman's order.
We must come up with the implementation details of
"I am more important than the company"
in the shortest time.
[In order to implement the chairman's request that "I am more important than the company",]
[all employees collectively work overtime to explain their importance over the company]
[in the roar of Vice Chairman Zheng.]
♫The subway will leave at 8:47♫
♫I only have three minutes♫
♫I run at the speed in the race♫
♫I make it at the last second♫
♫The team leader says you keep going♫
[Angry]
[Proposal]
♫I'm a great young man♫
[Planning]
[Future]
[Prospect]
♫I have my big dream♫
[Tianran]
[Well said]
♫How can I spend my life♫
♫Working for someone else♫
♫I'm a great young man♫
[0 yuan]
♫Though I'm empty-handed♫
[Expense List]
[Life]
♫Don't underestimate me♫
♫I was born in the Year of Dragon after all♫
♫Stand up and be a great young man♫
[A great young man]
♫Don't be a wimp, you guys♫
♫Only those who are tasteless will waste my talent♫
[Work]
[Never Give Up]
[Episode 38]
[Rice Cake Robbery]
[Cash Cheque]
[880,000 yuan]
[Cash check]
The Rice Cake system was successfully launched this time
thanks to Mr. Yu's leadership.
You are indispensable to the company's future.
Chairman,
I think
I can take on some
more important positions.
A vice chairman is nothing.
Mr. Yu,
are you ready
to take over Gaofa Group?
I was born ready.
No.
No. No.
Impossible.
It has been five years
since you were sent abroad
to study top hacking technologies.
Now it's time for you to step up.
At the summit, look down on the world with the wind.
[Planning Department 3]
At the edge of the wave, challenge the unknown.
Enjoy the present or keep moving forward.
Rice Cake Smart Technology System.
The future is now.
[Planning Department 3]
[Planning Department, Gaofa Technology]
I'm back.
You can force me to use my trump card.
Good for you.
Yu Qimiao.
Planning Department 3.
Within a month,
I will make all of you disappear!
Hello?
[Planning Department 3]
Ji, you're sleeping.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Again.
You're sleeping.
Your performance is gone.
I'll take a close-up shot for you.
Stop what you're doing now.
Sir.
[Planning Department 3]
Let me introduce
the new intern of our department.
Zheng Qiguai, welcome.
Welcome.
Qiguai is a top talent
specially introduced from abroad by the group
to better develop the Rice Cake system.
Why?
To add energy
to our department.
Let's learn from each other and improve together.
Li Tianran.
Stop
your work.
Get a set of office supplies
for the interns from the General Affairs Office.
Okay.
Come on, flip them over.
[Planning Department 3]
Qiguai, these are
your colleague.
Get close to them quickly
for work in the future.
You guys take the initiative.
Don't worry, sir.
Make her feel like home.
That's right.
Okay.
Ji, he...
Hello, my name is Jiang Mei.
There's a seat over there.
You can sit there.
If you need anything,
you can come to my seat here.
Okay.
Bye.
Bai.
That chair seems to be broken.
Go to the Logistics Department and get a new one.
Okay.
Let me do it.
No, how can I ask a girl to...
Just wait.
I'll get it for you later.
Thank you, Senior Bai Mashuai.
You're welcome.
Qiguai, right?
I'm the director here.
They all call me Mr. Yao.
Nice to meet you.
I'm sorry, Mr. Yao.
I don't know anything yet.
Thank you in advance for your care and help.
Thank you.
OK, you know me now.
Get to know everyone.
She's so strong.
Ms. Fan, what are you doing?
Nothing.
I've been slacking off for a long time.
Go on.
Sorry, I haven't saved my file. You...
Did I cause you trouble?
No.
I only typed a number this afternoon.
26. I got it.
You are really foresighted.
Let me get you a glass of water.
Call me if you need anything.
[Planning Department 3]
Why are you so careless?
Ms. Fan.
No matter how you look at her,
she is not like the top talents
introduced from abroad.
Interesting.
[Planning Department 3]
I've successfully merged in.
Good.
With your ability,
it's more than enough
to deal with those idiots of Planning Department 3.
We can't be careless.
I just tested them a few times.
I think
they are not
as simple as they look.
Remember,
you have two missions this time.
First
is to get all the parameters and codes
of the Rice Cake program.
Second
is to destroy the experimental data
in their hands.
This is a matter of success or failure.
You can't underestimate the enemy.
I won't let you down.
Father.
[Planning Department 3]
Here's the thing.
Our Rice Cake System
is a bold imagination.
Once it succeeds,
it will be
an all-round ecological
intelligent control system.
The purpose
is to create
an effortless
but ubiquitous sense of technology,
which seeps into every corner
of our clients' lives.
We are currently developing
the most important module.
You can take a look first.
See?
This is inheritance.
Bai can take a disciple now.
Bai.
[Planning Department 3]
Pass on the precious spiritual wealth
that I passed on to you
to  Zheng without reservation.
Have you ever taught Bai
how to differentiate a trap?
What trap?
The inheritance of the Li Bai family
is to be a hunter of traps
in the workplace.
I heard that high-level hunters
usually appear in the form of prey.
[Planning Department 3]
Hunter.
Take a look. This is it.
Senior Bai Mashuai.
Can I have a look at
the initial research data
and research parameters of the Rice Cake system?
Of course.
All our data
All our data is synchronized and stored
in the computer there.
You can check it anytime.
Okay.
It's so easy. Is it a trap?
But it doesn't seem like he's lying to me.
I'll take a look.
[Planning Department 3]
I'm sorry, everyone.
I suddenly remembered
when I synced the data yesterday,
I accidentally formatted the USB.
Everyone, please
upload
your data again.
Zheng,
you may have to check the data
in a few days.
Sure enough, I knew it wouldn't be that easy.
They're quite vigilant.
In order to get the data as soon as possible,
I guess I have to use extreme measures.
He told me the data is in this computer.
Since they wanted me to sit here,
then the documents must be here.
Who?
Give up.
Who is there?
Those are your inner demons.
Who are you?
Come out. I'm not afraid of you.
It's better to listen to music on the stereo.
It's good to be invisible.
How come I'm depressed after listening to music?
[Director's Office]
♫The subway will leave at 8:47♫
♫I only have three minutes♫
♫I run at the speed in the race♫
♫I make it at the last second♫
♫Down jacket and computer bag are a little heavy♫
♫The lady on the side wears too much perfume♫
[Planning Department 3]
This is not a good place.
It's haunted at night.
I must finish the mission as soon as possible.
How did my document get deleted automatically?
Why is my computer crashed?
It's not working.
What's going on?
Mine too.
Tianran.
Check your computer. Our computers are infected with a virus
Really? Your computers are all not working?
[Planning Team 3]
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Take a look.
If it's broken,
I'll get you a new one.
No need.
Mine is working now.
My computer is working.
Mine too. Mine too.
Is yours ready, Jiang Mei?
Mine too.
All working.
It's working. It's working. It's working.
[Planning Department 3]
Sorry, Zheng.
Tianran.
You did well.
Really?
In that case,
I'll treat her
in her own way.
[Planning Department 3]
Zheng.
Did you turn off my plug-in board?
No.
Please turn it on for me.
Okay, I'll turn it on for you.
It's okay now.
Thank you.
I'm steaming my face.
Rice Cake Protection can be tested.
Yay!
Did you send the hard disk here?
Okay, let me check the pickup code.
I didn't mean it.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, bro.
If I broke your phone,
I'll get you a new one later, okay?
Don't say that to me.
Are you delivering?
Bai Mashuai.
Who is Bai Mashuai?
Me. Me.
I'm Bai Mashuai.
No, master.
My pickup code...
It's okay. My phone is broken.
Forget about the pickup code.
Is this what you wanted?
Yes, it is.
Okay.
Please sign here.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's okay.
It's okay. I'll get a new one.
About getting a new phone,
I'll show you around
our company first.
You may not know much about our business.
Come on, bro.
I mistakenly shredded
the supplier's contract of the Rice Cake plan
on Mr. Yu's desk as waste paper.
Why is it shredded like this?
This contract was just signed.
It's troublesome to communicate with that company.
If your mistake delayed
the development progress of the Rice Cake Project,
what should we do?
I...
Mr. Yao.
I made a mistake.
What?
What I put on Mr. Yu's desk
was waste paper.
[Rice Cake Agreement]
Here's the contract.
Luckily, Tianran made a mistake
and saved it.
Don't panic when things happen.
Look how scared she is.
Sorry, Zheng.
Using magic against magic.
My Li Tianran
is very useful.
[Forecast Scenario in Operation and Maintenance Field]
Zheng.
Rice Cake Protection is going to be tested.
You have to pull yourself together!
Rice Cake?
I have nothing to do with Rice Cake.
I know nothing about its parameters or codes.
I know nothing.
This is really troublesome.
How about this? Get familiar with it as soon as possible.
We have many questions
to ask you.
[Shopping Mall]
They're making a key module
called "Rice Cake Protection".
This is
all the parameters of
Rice Cake Protection.
You're getting more creative.
You actually made a storage
into Bluetooth earphones
to deceive others.
You got it wrong.
Those are my Bluetooth earphones.
I misunderstood.
But... I still failed my missions.
I just stole
the parameters and codes of Rice Cake Protection,
but failed to destroy their experimental data
and stored data.
It doesn't matter.
It's enough having this.
As long as we make the first move and release it in advance,
those things in their hands
will become garbage.
Tell Planning Department 1 to stand by.
I have something important to announce.
Yes.
Is it completely restored according to the system?
According to your order,
We restored the ecological intelligent control system
of the whole house exactly
according to the system parameters
of Planning Department 3's Rice Cake.
They are exactly the same.
Good.
But I don't know
if I should say it.
Actually, if you want to
test it yourself,
I suggest you
check the one of Planning Department 1.
Our ecological system
is definitely a little better
than that of Planning Department 3.
We have the confidence.
Yes.
Go ahead.
Bai.
I'm Gao.
Gao, that's a good attitude.
We have to despise the enemy strategically,
but tactically,
we have to give weight to our enemies.
I...
What's the pros and cons
of this Rice Cake system?
We have to prove them
through the experiment.
Such an important matter
must be done by myself.
How about
you guys go out first?
Don't come in
without my order.
Okay, okay.
Be careful.
Don't disturb me.
Don't worry.
[Person not concerned is allowed to enter the experimental site.]
[Ergonomic test]
[Cardiac function test]
A human model is detected.
[Ergonomic test]
[Cardiac function test]
A cervical massage will be given to you automatically.
There is nothing special.
it's quite smart.
Isn't this just an ordinary massage chair?
[Ergonomic test]
[Cardiac function test]
AI intensity adjustment.
[Ergonomic test]
[Cardiac function test]
Be gentle.
[Ergonomic test]
[Cardiac function test]
Be gentle.
[Ergonomic test]
[Cardiac function test]
Done.
This fridge is quite magical.
Open the door.
Open the door now!
Open the door!
People outside, open the door! Do you hear me?
Who?
Who are you?
Let go now. Let go.
Blood pressure is dropping steadily.
He's out of danger.
The ambulance is 600 meters away.
The ambulance is 500 meters away.
The ambulance is 300 meters away.
[Person not concerned is allowed to enter the experimental site.]
Our beta test this time
is mainly to simulate
some simple family first aid scenes
such as
stiff neck,
cut
and fire.
Aiming at these situations,
we have developed
an ecological restoration emergency system
with strong matching-
Rice Cake Protection.
And this system
has been connected to
the internal ecological network of the group.
Of course, we should thank Mr. Zheng
for the fearless behavior of beta test.
He made outstanding contributions
for the successful beta test.
And our team
is very optimistic about
the prospect of Rice Cake Protection.
Zheng Qiguai
has learned some bad technologies abroad.
We should send her
to the southernmost part of the earth.
Let her reflect on herself.
[lucky day to step on eggs]
Yes.
Right.
I'll send you the analysis report
and testing data later.
Okay.
Thank you. Bye.
Why are you so busy every day?
Ms. Fan, don't you think
you don't even know what you're busy with?
Working is so boring every day.
That's how work is.
So after work,
we have to things we like
to enjoy our lives
and balance the pain of working.
What do you usually do, Sisi?
Reading Chinese comics, watching TV series, eating snacks,
buying blind boxes, merchandises, and figures.
There are many things to do.
So fulfilling.
Entertainment is important,
but
shouldn't we also
find some fun in work?
Mr. Yu is right.
Think about it.
The working time
is two thirds of our life time.
If you treat work as torture,
how can you feel happy in life?
Am I right, Ms. Fan?
Am I right, Jiang Mei?
Yes.
Mr. Yu is absolutely right.
Here's your chrysanthemum tea.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
I like to hear you talk.
In the current environment,
we have work and tea.
How happy!
You have to find and create your own sense of happiness.
You wrote it?
What kind of crap is this?
I used to think working is torture.
What the hell did you write?
[Planning Department 3]
But now,
I think working is getting interesting.
[Planning Team 3]
Cheers to our happiness.
Okay.
I'm happy to see you drink tea.
So sweet.
[Planning Department 3]