WELCOME BACK
ONE OF A KIND
ANIMAL TAMER
-I'll BE WHAT YOU WANT
-COOL LAWYER
YES! SHALL I TEXT YOU THE ADDRESS?
COMING SOON M. IÑAZU
MEDICAL EXAMINATION
COME ALONG! KARAOKE
WE'RE LAUNCHING FRIDAY NIGHT KARAOKE
You are breaking my heart
Maybe I really deserve it
For being
Just a girl in love
And always going round in circles
You are
Becoming my obsession
Now I need to realize it
That I'm just a ninja so in love
I'm your ally in this war
So tell me "yes"
That you love me
Say it once more
Now say it slowly
Say it to me, say it to him
Shout it out loud, so they hear it again
Take me away
I can't take anymore
It feels like the start
But it's nearly the end
Tell me it's not-
That it's not over
Tell me, "I love you"
I really do love you
I'm just beginning to lose my min-
19TH BUENOS AIRES TENNIS TOURNAMENT
WHAT A TEAM.
THANKS @MEIHUANG. WE'LL BE BACK.
GREAT TO BE AT WORK. #FRIENDS