Today's the last day.
My nerves are shot and I'm in a bad state.
I got a nosebleed
for the first time in a while.
I'm not in the best condition right now.
Let's still give it my best.
I slept so well.
I really did.
My shoulders are a bit stiff
but I think I'm the fittest person here.
Did you wash up?
-I did.
-You did?
They want us ready by 9:30 a.m.
-By 9:30 a.m.?
-The makeup team will be here.
Were you reading?
I wanted to calm my mind down.
-I got a nosebleed.
-Really?
Yeah, in the bathroom.
-Due to exhaustion?
-I'm not sure.
-Is it due to the dry air? Stress?
-Maybe.
We've been through a lot,
but today's the last day.
After this, we can go home.
There used to be a lot of food.
This is still a lot though.
-It's a lot for us two.
-Yeah.
I hope they get here soon.
Me too.
We can't leave any records of this.
We don't have our phones.
I don't think we would've been allowed
to take pictures anyway.
I really want to remember all of this.
Same.
We'll get started soon.
All right.
-Have a seat.
-Okay.
FIRST INTERVIEW
Hello.
-Hello.
With people like ORBIT,
I immediately realized
no one here can be underestimated.
I'm Ha Seok-jin.
Nice to meet you.
A player that caught my attention?
Well, personally...
I would have to say Seok-jin.
I'm the officer.
I'm the officer!
He's the most intimidating opponent.
He's a leader.
And he has his own style of playing.
For having the least Pieces,
Seok-jin and See-won
-will go to prison.
-What? That's how it is?
He tends to lead by action, not words.
He's also quite reserved.
In the same way
that I play by my principles,
he also did the same.
You have won.
...for 13 Pieces.
I'd personally like to see
skill-based eliminations.
Is this The Devil's Plan
or The Moocher's Plan?
It was a high-quality game.
If only we played individually.
I fear players like him.
Let me tell you the winning strategy.
ORBIT is amazing at playing games
he's never played before
as if he's familiar with them already.
He's adept at understanding games.
I'm the first player to go.
Then I should place my piece here.
The order is R, P, Y, B, then G.
He tends to create codes
and formulas beforehand.
And I expect him to display
such skills again today.
His weakness?
No!
When he makes a mistake,
he tends to react a bit sensitively.
-I thought you could save him.
-No, it's not possible.
It's like I'm watching
the fall of the welfare state.
This wasn't my intention.
I was able to maintain composure
due to all the lessons
my life has taught me.
I've learned that it's better
to hide my emotions in certain situations.
I wonder if I survived this long
because of that.
We're both on the older side
compared to the others
and we made it to the finals.
This could give hope
to people in their forties.
We can take on new challenges.
I'll do everything I can.
I want to see how far I can go.
I'll do whatever it takes to win.
Oh, boy.
ELIMINATED ON DAY 2
GUILLAUME
Wow. Seriously?
-Guillaume.
-Congratulations.
Hey, roommate!
My roommate!
I knew you'd make it.
-How have you been?
-I knew you would.
The two brains made it.
You didn't know it was us?
-I didn't.
-You had no idea?
-I had no idea.
-What?
You would've loved some of the games.
-I wish you were here yesterday.
-You would've dominated it.
-Really? I'm curious.
-We were amateurs.
-I'm curious.
-We played Hi-Lo.
Amongst amateurs.
-You did?
-Yeah.
You would've beaten us all.
It would've been child's play for you.
-Exactly.
-Yeah?
-That's great.
-Have a seat.
-You guys did great.
-You left your underwear, didn't you?
-When I got home, my socks were missing.
-Were they?
ELIMINATED ON DAY 3
LEE HYE-SUNG, KIM DONG-JAE
-Dong-jae and Hye-sung.
-Hello.
Dong-jae.
Hello.
-Who are the finalists?
-I'm sorry, Hye-sung.
It's me and Seok-jin.
-Really?
-Yeah.
You two are the finalists?
-Congratulations!
-I'm sorry.
I still feel so bad.
I really do.
-I'm going to make you feel bad forever.
-Exactly.
You did great.
One, two, three.
Someone's here.
Goodness.
ELIMINATED ON DAY 5
CHO YEON-WOO, LEE SEE-WON
-See-won.
-Hello, everyone.
-We're here.
-What happened to you?
-Hye-sung.
-Long time no see.
-It's been a while.
-Dong-jae.
I was so surprised.
See-won, Seok-jin made it to the finals.
-Did something good happen?
-Guillaume!
How did you get eliminated?
I had a glorious death.
I really needed you in prison.
-You did?
-You would've helped me a lot.
Why?
Seok-jin.
I made it.
You said you didn't get
why people cry during games.
After you left,
I sobbed my eyes out.
I'm proud of you. Thank you.
Thank you.
I cried so much alone.
I thought you couldn't understand.
No way. I don't get to say goodbye?
I thought I was a heartless bastard.
I broke you.
I guess you do have a heart in there.
-It was tough.
-So you made it to the finals?
-I made it here by sacrificing you.
-How could you...
-Seriously, Seok-jin. Did you hear?
-How could you?
It's time for our guest singer.
ELIMINATED ON DAY 6
PARK KYEONG-RIM, SEUNGKWAN
-Kyeong-rim!
-Welcome.
ELIMINATED ON DAY 6
SUH YU-MIN
-Yu-min!
-Seungkwan!
-Yeon-woo!
-Long time no see.
-You said you weren't going to the finals!
-Did you get Korean barbecue?
Why is it you two?
It should be Dong-joo and Seok-jin.
-Joon-bin.
-You did a great job.
Good job.
Why are you two the finalists?
What happened to Dong-joo?
How could you just leave us like that?
-Do you know how shocked I was?
-I still succeeded in a way.
-Dong-jae, I'm sorry.
-How was life without me?
I wanted to win for you.
You three should make up.
Hey, Seungkwan.
What happened?
Who are the finalists?
-Are you one of them?
-Yeah.
Are you serious?
-How could you?
-It's going to be intense.
-Curse me all you want.
-Who's the other one?
-I'm so excited.
-I'm not going to curse you.
Seok-jin, you can win this!
-Seok-jin, you got this!
-Wait a minute.
Is Dong-joo not here yet?
Wait.
Dong-joo's not here.
-She's the only one who's not here, right?
-Why isn't she here?
ELIMINATED ON DAY 6
SUH DONG-JOO
Dong-joo!
-Dong-joo.
-Dong-joo!
Why did you get eliminated?
You should've been
the first female winner.
Joon-bin was giving me a hard time.
-At the end...
-What happened at the end?
ORBIT made a big mistake.
-No, I'm sure he did it on purpose.
-So I got eliminated.
-Really? You're not joking?
-I'm serious.
There's no way he would've made a mistake.
-ORBIT.
Was it really a mistake?
-Watch the show later.
-So...
-I lost my mind.
-He bawled his eyes out.
See-won, I had no chance to say goodbye.
-I heard you had a tough time.
-Things were hectic.
-I heard you did.
-No, it was fine.
-Are you okay?
-Now that it has passed, I'm fine.
I'm excited for today.
Me too. We'll get to watch with no stress.
Did you bring the suit?
Yeah.
-I had them keep it for me.
-So you were set on making it here.
-I wasn't.
-Stop trying to fool us now.
-You were set on making the finals.
-Just be like Joon-bin.
-I wore this during the poster shoot.
-Be openly ambitious.
Just be honest.
You were set on making it to the finals.
-I swear I wasn't.
-You wanted to get rid of us.
You pretended to help.
Sure, you're right.
Go win then.
-Should we sit like we did on day one?
-Should we?
-Like we did on the first day?
-Yeah.
I remember where I was.
-Dong-jae knows how these shows work.
-Just like the first day.
It's such a shame
that you had to go home so quickly.
Should we introduce ourselves?
Shall we?
-We started from there.
-That's a good idea.
Hello, I'm Cho Yeon-woo
and I'm a pro Go player.
Did you say pro inmate?
-Pro inmate.
Hello, I'm Suh Dong-joo
and I'm a lawyer based in America.
I'm Guillaume
and I'm a pro gamer from Canada.
I'm ORBIT and I'm a science communicator.
The great strategist.
I united the weak.
There he goes again.
But I played for my own self-interest.
I'm sorry for having been
such a selfish person.
-Don't say that.
-Is that also science?
Hello, I'm Kwak Joon-bin
and I'm a travel YouTuber.
-You're handsome.
-Your voice sounds great.
-You look great.
-So cool.
Hello, I'm Seungkwan
and I'm a member of SEVENTEEN.
He's an idol.
-Seok-jin.
-Hello, everyone.
I'm Ha Seok-jin
and I'm an actor and YouTuber.
When I first came here,
my goal was to survive the first day.
It's hard to believe
that I survived this long.
Anyways, ORBIT and I
made it to the finals.
It will be the final battle
between the grand strategist
and the person who opposed him.
-I'll do my best.
-What a speech!
Dong-jae!
Hello.
I'm Kim Dong-jae.
I'm a college student and poker player.
Hello, I'm Lee See-won and I'm an actress.
I'm Park Kyeong-rim
and I'm a TV personality and MC.
I'm Lee Hye-sung
and I'm a freelance announcer.
Hello, I'm Suh Yu-min
and I'm an orthopedist.
It's like we're back on day one.
Do you feel better now?
There are countless things
I would do differently if I could go back.
-That's enough.
-Please just stop!
-What are you on about?
-There he goes again.
Stop thinking
that you have to do everything.
He feels bad
that his strategy went astray.
-And then...
-He's trying to lower Seok-jin's guard.
-If he wins...
-If that's the case,
-I have to support Seok-jin then.
-Okay.
Several people have fallen for his ploy.
It seems they've prepared
a last supper for us.
Let's all go and eat.
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you.
Eat up.
I'm excited about the finals.
It's the dramatic ending I wanted.
Seriously.
Most of all,
this is an exciting matchup.
You need to win this for us.
Even if you make a mistake,
try to keep your composure.
You've already played Nine Men's Morris.
You can win if you stay calm.
I want you to play confidently.
So many people support you,
so you have to win.
If you don't,
it would be embarrassing for me.
We have a love-hate relationship.
I know he pretends to be weak,
but he's the most complete player
in my opinion.
Yeon-woo was really weird.
I couldn't forget your glare.
Is that how I looked?
So I did an impression of you.
What is that?
Are you serious?
-That's hilarious.
-"What are you talking about?"
When you got eliminated,
your crying face
was just like your laughing face.
"Seungkwan."
That's hilarious.
"Why do you think it's always just me?"
Oh, that's what that is.
-See-won said that to Dong-joo.
-"Why..."
"So you can be
in an alliance but I can't?"
"That doesn't make sense."
"I don't think that's right."
Then Dong-joo went,
"You always say you want to team up,
but then you don't."
"You abandon me."
Are you imitating me?
-I think he is.
-Hey!
Is it all right to make light
of you two fighting?
I love it.
ORBIT.
-Good luck.
-Dong-joo.
-It's all right if you lose though.
-You know that, right?
-Is it okay to lose?
-Of course.
-I disagree.
-I want you to win.
-Don't pressure me.
Don't pressure him.
You don't have to play well.
-You really don't.
-You saw how I was yesterday.
-I did.
-Crush your enemy.
My goodness, Joon-bin.
-Don't pressure...
-Don't give Seok-jin room to breathe.
Don't pressure him.
There's an item of clothing
I wear for good luck.
It's this hoodie from the first day.
KIM DONG-JAE
COLLEGE STUDENT
Every time I wore this hoodie,
I won something or achieved good results.
I've never failed at anything
while wearing this.
I wanted to give Seok-jin all my luck.
-Seok-jin.
-Yeah?
For the first time ever,
I'm wearing this for someone else.
I want all my good luck to go to you.
I'm going to cheer you on.
ORBIT, it's all right to lose,
so take it easy.
I just hope I don't make
any more mistakes.
It's fine if you do.
You don't have to play well.
There's no need
to feel pressured, so take it easy.
I'll do my best and have fun.
-Yeah, enjoy it.
-I'm going to do my best
-It's your last game.
-to make it fun.
-It's time for them to go.
-Oh, dear.
Good luck.
-Good luck.
-The final match will begin soon.
Finalists, please gather in the game area.
Good luck.
-Good luck!
You got this!
I won't let you down.
You better not let science down.
-ORBIT, you can do it.
-I'll try my best.
You got this.
-I'll do my best.
-We're with you in spirit.
-Good luck.
-You got this, big brain bro.
-Make sure to win.
I'm so excited for this.
-Good luck.
Good luck!
-Good luck!
-You got this.
I'll go put on a show.
-Do your best, guys!
-Let's do this.
This is a scene to remember.
Good luck. Bye!
It's like a movie.
-I want to take a photo of this.
-Good luck!
I'm so jealous of them.
All of a sudden?
I forgot to bring my film camera again!
Were the lights always like this?
It feels a bit different.
Greetings.
Congratulations on coming this far.
The final match
of The Devil's Plan will begin now.
THE DEVIL'S PLAN
Dong-joo got eliminated
in yesterday's prize match.
As a result, ORBIT and Seok-jin
have advanced to the final match.
-This is so cool!
-It's like a movie!
They look so cool.
It's like we're at the movies.
The final prize accumulated
from all prize matches is...
250 million won.
I can't imagine how nervous they must be.
Three games
will be played for the final match.
Whichever player wins two games first
will be the final winner
and they will receive
the prize of 250 million won.
The final match will proceed as follows.
The first game of the final match
is Nine Men's Morris.
-I knew it.
-That's why they had that here.
I knew this would happen.
Nine Men's Morris
is a strategy board game
that has a long history
dating to the Roman Empire.
The second game is...
Hexagon.
-What?
-What's that?
This game requires memorization
and arithmetic skills.
The third game is dice poker.
This is a betting game
that involves mind games.
This is going to be tough.
-This is stressful.
-It's going to be a long day.
Here is the final Piece count
of the finalists.
ORBIT has 14.
And Seok-jin has 22.
-He has a lot.
-Twenty-two?
As Seok-jin has more Pieces,
he will be given a slight advantage
in the three games.
Here is the first game of the final match.
The first game is
Nine Men's Morris.
In this game,
players must place their markers
on three dots in a straight line
to remove an opponent's marker.
One player is given nine black markers
and the other is given nine white markers.
The player with more markers
will choose who goes first in each round.
Once the game begins,
the player going first
must place one marker
on one of the 24 empty dots
within 90 seconds.
The players will take turns
placing their markers
until all of them are on the board.
A player may not move a marker
that has already been placed
until all markers are on the board.
If a player ends up
with three markers in a straight line
while placing their markers on the board,
they may choose and remove
one of the opponent's markers.
However, if the opponent's markers
are in a row of three in a straight line,
those markers may not be removed.
The player must choose a different marker.
If all markers
have been placed on the board,
players must move
their markers during their turn.
When doing so,
players may move their markers
to a neighboring dot on the same line.
While taking turns doing this,
if a player's markers end up
in a row of three in a straight line,
they may remove an opponent's marker
from the board.
If a player only has
three markers left on the board,
they do not have to move their markers
to a connected dot.
They may move their markers
to any empty dot on the board.
-You're trying to survive at that point.
-As per the rule,
if a player's markers end up
in a row of three in a straight line,
they may remove an opponent's marker
from the board.
If a player is unable
to move their markers
or is left with only two markers,
the game ends in the said player's defeat.
If one player is left with three markers
and the stalemate continues
for more than ten turns,
the player with fewer markers
loses the game.
The game will last for three rounds.
The player who wins
two rounds first will win.
In a moment,
the first game of the final match
will begin.
I anticipated that we would
play this game.
We played it for a bit last night.
ORBIT is a much faster learner
in terms of understanding games,
so I can't take this lightly.
We both have to play to win.
So I'll try to avoid making mistakes
and give it my all.
I have several strategies in mind
to turn things in my favor.
But Seok-jin has survived hell
by winning a game of Gomoku,
so I'm not sure if I have the upper hand.
I have a headache.
-I threw up.
-You threw up?
I threw up in the bathroom.
This is exhausting.
The first game of the final match,
Nine Men's Morris,
will begin now.
-It's starting.
-Here they go.
Why am I nervous?
As Seok-jin has more Pieces,
he will get to decide who plays first.
Going first is a definite advantage.
If you go second, you have to
play defensively and wait for mistakes.
Unless they make a mistake,
the player to go first will always win.
I will go first.
Seok-jin will go first
and play with the black markers.
ORBIT will go second
and play with the white markers.
Round one begins now.
Seok-jin, please place one marker
within 90 seconds.
-Good luck!
-Good luck, ORBIT!
Please let me go first in round two.
I have no choice but to defend.
I don't know if I'm doing it right.
What?
I think he made a mistake.
Seok-jin is on the defensive now.
-ORBIT can attack now.
-That's right.
-He made a mistake.
-ORBIT is on the offensive now.
That would make three in a row.
ORBIT, please remove
one of your opponent's markers.
He can remove a black marker now.
And they can't remove markers
-that are in a row.
-Okay.
-He's going to get a row too.
-What?
That was a good move.
You have 30 seconds left.
Seok-jin, please remove
one of your opponent's markers.
They have to move their markers now.
This is so stressful.
-It's no joke.
-I can't calculate anymore.
Seok-jin, please remove
one of your opponent's markers.
This is amazing for Seok-jin.
-White is in a bad spot.
-That area is hell for white.
Black can just move
that marker up and down.
ORBIT, please remove
one of your opponent's markers.
That black marker is in the way.
But it's pointless
because Seok-jin can't attack right now.
That was good.
White can't do anything.
ORBIT, you have 30 seconds left.
Come on, ORBIT.
You have ten seconds left.
Seok-jin, please remove
one of your opponent's markers.
Seok-jin, you have 30 seconds left.
You have ten seconds left.
Five...
ORBIT, please remove
one of your opponent's markers.
That's good.
-He can go either way.
-Right.
Seok-jin's against a wall.
-He's on the defensive.
-Seok-jin's in trouble.
ORBIT got him.
It's all right.
Seok-jin is good under pressure.
You have 30 seconds left.
Five, four...
ORBIT, please remove
one of your opponent's markers.
You have 30 seconds left.
That was a deep sigh.
Please remove...
Seok-jin, you have 30 seconds left.
He's playing confidently.
This is tough.
It's difficult.
It really is.
This is hard.
Please remove a marker.
Seok-jin, you have three markers left.
You may now move your markers freely.
You have 30 seconds left.
-My head hurts.
-Five,
four...
What was that?
The reason why Seok-jin
isn't going on the offensive
when he can move his markers freely
is that if he gets his markers
in a row of three
and removes one of ORBIT's markers,
that means ORBIT
can also move his markers freely.
If ORBIT moves his markers as shown,
Seok-jin can't stop ORBIT from winning.
Let's end this round.
You need to remove this.
That's right.
I think white won.
If I do this, it's over regardless of
where you place yours.
I get three in a row.
Round one ends with ORBIT's victory.
He went second and won.
That was amazing.
-You're so good at this.
-This is tough.
I was waiting for him to make a mistake.
When it looked like he would,
I pounced just in time.
For the first round,
I was nervous about facing ORBIT.
But now I'm just exhausted.
My brain is fried.
This is an intense battle
right from the start.
Round two begins now.
-Good luck.
-Let's follow their moves.
-Okay.
ORBIT, please decide on the order.
I will go first.
You have an advantage if you go first.
-But he just won going second.
-That's ORBIT.
ORBIT, please place your marker.
I focused on placing my markers
in a rhombus shape in the middle area.
It makes moving my markers easier,
so I thought it would be an advantage.
-It's different from how Seok-jin played.
-Exactly.
ORBIT's using a new strategy.
What is that?
Round two is going to be quick.
Let's be quick. My head hurts.
Creating L shapes in the corners
is very advantageous.
Going first is too advantageous.
Is it?
ORBIT, please remove
one of your opponent's markers.
-What?
-Why didn't he form a row first?
You have 30 seconds left.
Okay.
The game just started.
-This is the real beginning.
-It is.
Wait.
Every option is blocked now.
-Black is...
-There's no option here.
And this area is completely blocked.
He can't attack here either.
-Whatever happens...
-Seok-jin has a slight advantage.
He's in a good position right now.
How did this happen?
You have 30 seconds left.
I think I made a mistake.
Please remove
one of your opponent's markers.
You have 30 seconds left.
I'm out of options.
I really am.
I realized how the game was progressing.
And I saw a way
to keep my opponent in check.
I trapped him in the middle
and saw that he couldn't move.
He'd have to take
several turns just to form a row.
So I decided to remove his markers
one by one
as he moved his markers
trying to form a row.
It was like choking his neck
while hitting him in the stomach.
Please remove
one of your opponent's markers.
This is...
a complete victory for Seok-jin.
It's over.
ORBIT, you are unable
to move your markers.
Round two ends with Seok-jin's victory.
He couldn't move anymore.
-He trapped him completely.
-That was great.
I got too confident
while forming my territory.
I should've looked at the big picture
but I made a mistake.
I didn't look at the bigger picture.
The first players have lost so far.
Exactly.
Maybe the pressure's too much
since the first player usually wins.
Going first is advantageous
but I let my guard down.
Did we have to drag this into round three?
I'm tired.
Round three begins now.
Usually, whoever wins
the second round has momentum.
It's fun watching
our most cautious players play.
It is.
Seok-jin, please decide on the order.
I will go first.
This isn't easy, is it?
Seok-jin, please place your marker.
I thought of it as Gomoku.
But it was more about
crowding my opponent out.
I'm not sure what to do.
I had to choose between taking over
the outer area or the middle area.
If Seok-jin was going to take the middle,
I was going to block him first
and take over the outer area.
And based on the
remaining number of markers,
I calculated which one I should remove.
You have 30 seconds left.
Five, four, three, two, one.
I have to block this.
It's still an open game.
This is playing out beautifully.
Their markers are more spread out
in this round.
They realized it's hard to move
when the markers are clumped up.
So they spread out.
I can't tell who has the upper hand.
I think they're pretty even so far.
They're both thinking clearly now.
I need to block this.
I'm out of options.
I have to place a new marker, right?
That's right.
I don't want to.
All right, here we go.
They've placed
all of their markers on the board.
-All their markers are on.
-The game begins now.
I hope Seok-jin wins.
Let's see.
I realized something in round two.
I was suddenly able to see
when and where to block him off
to be able to remove his markers.
I learned how to take control of the game.
You have 30 seconds left.
This is driving me crazy.
That was a good move.
Seok-jin will be able to
move his markers around more easily.
It seems so.
Darn it. What do I do?
I have nowhere to go.
Exactly.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Seok-jin, please remove
one of your opponent's markers.
Please remove
I knew that I had lost
as soon as the first marker was removed.
This game is over.
He can't turn the tides anymore.
I think ORBIT realizes that.
-Yeah.
-Whatever he does...
Seok-jin has it all figured out.
Please remove
one of your opponent's markers.
-It's over.
-Yeah.
It seems so.
I just felt for the pulse of the game
to understand how it would go.
And I realized
that it's actually quite simple.
But ORBIT overcomplicated his strategy.
He tried to calculate all of the outcomes.
I've lost completely.
I'm out of options.
There's nothing I can do.
This is a crushing defeat.
ORBIT has two markers left.
-It's over.
-Good job.
Well played.
Seok-jin played well.
Round three ends with Seok-jin's victory.
You're so good at this.
The first game of the final match
ends with Seok-jin's victory.
The second game
of the final match will begin soon.
It was a matter
of who made fewer mistakes.
I'm tired but I'll do my best again
in the second game.
I lost the first game.
But we still have
the second and third games.
I will give it my all.
-You're amazing.
-The second game involves numbers.
Here is the second game
of the final match.
The second game of the final match
is Hexagon.
In this game, players must remember
the combination of three numbers
that add up to the target number.
This is amazing.
Once the game begins, the number board
will be shown for 30 seconds.
The number board is made up
of 19 smaller hexagons with random numbers
that together form one large hexagon.
After 30 seconds,
the numbers will be replaced with letters
and the target number will be shown.
Players must recall
the combination of three hexagons
either in a horizontal or diagonal row
that add up to the target number.
How is that possible?
When giving their answers,
players must recite the letters,
not the numbers.
For example, if the target number is ten,
the answers would be ABC,
FJN,
GKO, or JNQ.
Players who wish to answer
may press the buzzer at any time
and answer within ten seconds.
If correct, the player
will earn one point.
If incorrect, they will lose one point.
The number of potential answers
for each round will not be revealed.
Once all answers have been found,
the next round will begin
and a new number board
and target number will be shown.
If no player presses their buzzer
within 90 seconds,
that round will end immediately,
and the next round will begin.
The game will last for ten rounds.
The player with more correct answers
wins the game.
The second game of the final match
will begin soon.
This is torture.
He's an intelligent person.
So I'm sure he's good at memorization.
And in that sense,
I feel that I'm at a big disadvantage.
I don't think I'm at a disadvantage.
It all comes down to
who keeps a cool head until the end.
I can't imagine
how stressful that must be.
Seungkwan, good thing we got eliminated.
-We can't handle that game.
-I agree.
If we were the finalists,
we'd be struggling the whole game.
We'd be like, "What's the target number?"
Apparently, Joon-bin has
a photographic memory.
Then why did he suck at Montage?
I couldn't press the buzzer on time.
What are you saying?
The same goes for me then.
You...
The time has expired.
Please return to the main hall.
-They look great!
-Good luck!
Seok-jin has a one-game lead on ORBIT.
If Seok-jin also wins this game,
he will become the final winner
of The Devil's Plan.
As Seok-jin has more Pieces,
he will begin the game with one point.
That's his advantage?
Yeah, he gets a point.
My focus was to try to
catch up as much as possible.
But his one-point lead did feel daunting.
Here is the number board for round one.
I feel like it'll be 11 or 12.
Maybe ten or nine?
Probably nine.
Maybe eight?
Here is the target number for round one.
I can't guess what it'll be.
-Five?
-Seriously?
Seok-jin.
How is that possible?
ADH.
Correct.
One, two, and two.
ADH.
ORBIT.
QRS.
Correct.
This is so nerve-racking.
-I wouldn't get a single answer.
-Me neither.
ORBIT.
Come on.
HIJ.
HIJ?
Incorrect.
Seok-jin.
IJK.
Incorrect.
I'm not sure.
I'm hesitant
because I don't trust my memory.
It might be better
to not say anything if unsure.
Yeah, that could be better.
As no one has pressed the buzzer
in 90 seconds,
this round ends here.
Here is the point tally of both players
after round one.
It's still one to zero.
The Pieces were so important.
It's such an advantage.
Here is the number board for round two.
622, 2115, 42744...
26426, 35312, 24...
I think it'll be seven.
I agree.
There are a lot of combinations
that make seven.
Here is the target number for round two.
She was right.
-You're psychic.
-All these combinations...
There were a lot of combinations.
ORBIT.
NOP.
Correct.
Seok-jin.
ROK.
Correct.
I think they both
memorized the bottom part.
That must be the part they memorized last.
-It's still fresh.
-Maybe they forgot the upper numbers.
Otherwise, someone would've said ABC.
-NOP.
-ROK.
How do you memorize this?
I wouldn't be able to.
It's completely different
when you're actually playing.
-I wouldn't be able to.
-I think a good strategy
would be to memorize three lines.
-Three lines?
-Don't try to memorize everything.
As no one has pressed the buzzer
in 90 seconds,
-this round ends here.
-Darn it.
Here is the point tally of both players
after round two.
ORBIT, you can do this.
Here is the number board for round three.
52351, 3522...
41532, 32253...
-Will it be ten this time?
-Yeah.
Either ten or nine.
I think it'd be better
to memorize the whole thing.
Here is the target number for round three.
Six?
-This is tough.
-It's risky to anticipate the number.
-You could be doomed.
-This is bad.
I keep thinking about
the previous target number.
ORBIT.
FGL.
Incorrect.
-Is that a possible combination?
-It is not.
It must be in a straight line.
I had no options just looking at
straight-line combinations.
So I assumed
crooked-line combinations would work.
FGL.
I was so focused on memorizing
and trying to get numbers in my head
under the condition that I was in.
So I forgot the rules.
I have to memorize again.
-I need to take a different approach.
-ORBIT.
CGL.
Incorrect.
Darn it.
Not being wrong
was just as important as being right
since you lose a point
for an incorrect answer.
He looks like he's being punished.
It's all right.
ORBIT, you can do it.
They've only played three rounds.
As no one has pressed the buzzer
in 90 seconds,
this round ends here.
Here is the point tally of both players
after round three.
I really need another strategy.
Here is the number board for round four.
This is tough.
They're really making it difficult
with bigger numbers now.
3562, 34315...
65333, 26326...
Here is the target number for round four.
Seok-jin.
On the hexagon,
I memorized
the three longest straight lines.
I personally thought doing that
would be a good way to reduce my mistakes
and memorize definite answers.
JOS.
Correct.
ORBIT took the wrong approach.
I think he's memorizing
the entire hexagon.
NOP.
-ORBIT.
-NOP.
ORBIT.
He got it right.
Correct.
Get your confidence back.
You can do it.
ORBIT.
JKL.
Correct.
ORBIT.
ROK.
Incorrect.
Oh, right.
ORBIT.
JOS.
Seok-jin already said that.
That combination has already been taken.
I'm sorry.
ORBIT is under so much stress.
I feel so bad for him.
As no one has pressed the buzzer
in 90 seconds,
this round ends here.
Here is the point tally of both players
after round four.
I keep getting the wrong answer
and losing points.
The difference is getting bigger.
Here is the number board for round five.
6372, 42236...
33241, 27235...
Here is the target number for round five.
Is it eight?
I feel like it'll be 11.
-I would've been doomed.
-Exactly.
Seok-jin.
AEJ.
Correct.
ORBIT.
HIJ.
Correct.
-They got answers already?
-They're amazing.
ORBIT.
LPS.
Correct.
-Good.
-Keep going.
How is he doing this?
ORBIT.
EIM.
-Incorrect.
-What?
ORBIT.
Come on.
Please get it.
CGL.
Incorrect.
Darn it.
Oh, no.
This is driving me crazy.
As no one has pressed the buzzer
in 90 seconds,
this round ends here.
Here is the point tally of both players
after round five.
Come on, ORBIT.
Here is the number board for round six.
All right.
I can't memorize this.
24371, 55358...
235, 4451, 28354, 4572...
This is difficult.
Here is the target number for round six.
28354...
ORBIT.
JKL.
Correct.
I can't remember
whether it was one or three.
As no one has pressed the buzzer
in 90 seconds,
this round ends here.
Here is the point tally of both players
after round six.
This is so hard.
Here is the number board for round seven.
652, 4342, 25536, 7514, 4342, 25536, 7514...
63512, 24551...
Here is the target number for round seven.
Ten?
I didn't anticipate that.
751...
-ORBIT.
-NOP.
Correct.
ORBIT.
HMQ.
Correct.
-He's amazing.
-Seriously?
-No way.
-This is it.
-This is thrilling.
-I can't sit down.
My brain's fried.
Here is the point tally of both players
after round seven.
He's catching up.
He's close.
Here is the number board for round eight.
Here is the target number for round eight.
-ORBIT.
-HMQ.
Correct.
Seok-jin.
IJK.
Correct.
Here is the point tally
of both players after round eight.
This is so fun.
-It's exciting.
-It's a great game.
-It's fun.
-It really is the finals.
Are there two rounds left?
Here is the number board for round nine.
4335, 2611, 63252...
43215, 13261, 63252...
Here is the target number for round nine.
63...
ORBIT.
-ORBIT.
-EFG.
Correct.
Seok-jin.
HIJ.
Correct.
432, 43215...
4335, 63252...
ORBIT, you got this.
Just get one answer right.
Cut the gap by one point.
ORBIT.
GKO.
Correct.
He's catching up.
-Is he one point behind?
-He is.
That's crazy.
Come on, Seok-jin.
43215...
433, 43...
26...
If you're unsure, don't answer.
ORBIT.
NJF.
Correct.
I should've gotten that one.
They're tied now, right?
They're tied.
So round ten begins with a tie?
I think I might faint.
As no one has pressed the buzzer
in 90 seconds,
this round ends here.
Here is the point tally of both players
after round nine.
Oh, boy.
This is crazy. He's really something.
Please, Seok-jin.
Here is the number board
for round ten, the last round.
565, 7816, 7816, 44233...
58268, 44233...
My brain isn't working.
-Me too.
-I'm nervous.
I just want to see them play
without knowing the numbers.
Here is the target number
for the last round.
Seok-jin.
Seok-jin buzzed.
AEJ.
Correct.
ORBIT.
-Please.
-You can do it.
DEF.
-Wait, no.
-Incorrect.
I made a mistake.
-Press the buzzer and go again.
-Oh, no.
I can't watch.
If you're unsure, just don't do anything.
You're right.
3398...
332697...
As no one has pressed the buzzer
in 90 seconds,
this round ends here.
Is it over already?
Based on the results,
Seok-jin is the final winner
of The Devil's Plan.
-Seok-jin!
Seok-jin.
Thank you.
I did my best in every game.
And I played without
expecting fortune to come my way.
I think having such a mindset
helped me in many ways.
-You did great.
-Good job.
-You were great.
-You did great.
-Congratulations.
This was a once-in-a-lifetime
experience for me.
I would like to thank everyone
for such a great experience.
That was amazing.
My goodness.
-That was a great match.
-You guys were amazing.
Seok-jin will receive
250 million won as the final prize.
-Congratulations.
-You guys were awesome.
I think we are all winners.
It's just that
ORBIT and I played
the last match as representatives.
But results are results,
so I'll enjoy this victory.
Thank you.
Congratulations! You're amazing!
The Devil's Plan has come to an end
with Seok-jin's victory.
Thank you to all of the players
who participated.
Great job, everyone.
-Great job, everyone.
Good job.
The Devil's Plan
was a miniature version of society.
It was like a village
made up of people with good hearts
and intelligent minds.
I realized you can meet
such diverse people in your life.
It triggered our instincts.
The show exposed our human nature.
We did make alliances,
but no one tore anyone else down
or isolated themselves.
I felt the warmth of humanity.
I had such a great time with good people.
I'm left with such valuable
and diverse experiences.
I made good memories with good people.
Even though the show is over,
I hope we can maintain our friendships.
This place was my home.
Where else would I be?
The show revealed
our competitive spirits so well.
I had fun and learned a lot.
It was an experience
that allowed me to grow as a person.
Thank you for giving me
this opportunity to grow.
Right now, I'm just so happy.
I had a great time.
This was the happiest I've ever been.
This week felt like a dream
and I don't know
how I could possibly forget it.
As a member of the cast,
I learned a lot about life.
One, two, three!
-Great job, everybody.
-Thank you.
Thank you, everyone!
Subtitle translation by: Ji-hun Lee