=Romance of a Twin Flower=
=Episode 30=
Ji Man!
Ji Man, are you all right?
How do you feel?
How long are you going to avoid me?
If I don't come to you,
are you going to hide from me
for the rest of your life?
It was you who left without
saying goodbye.
Shouldn't you give me an explanation?
I have nothing to explain.
Forget me.
How can I forget you?
In this life,
you will be the only one
in my heart.
My dad won't allow us
to be together.
He won't allow me
to be with someone
who lives in hatred all the time.
I...
So the best ending
for us
is to start over
on our own.
You still love me.
Right?
Why don't you believe me?
Believe me.
There is no future.
But why?
Because my biological father
is Cai Wenzheng.
What did you say?
Because my biological father
is Cai Wenzheng!
The Chief of the Tea Gang, Cai Wenzheng!
Even if you don't want to see me,
there's no need to make such a joke.
I'm not kidding you.
Nie Sangyu and I
are both Cai Wenzheng's
biological daughters.
It's just that we were
placed into foster care
by different people
as soon as we were born.
I was fostered by Ji Ming.
And she was sent
to Nie Xiangyuan.
So everything happened
after you met me
can be sorted out, right?
You are Cai Wenzheng's daughter.
♪How long have we been
looking at each other♪
♪To live up to the fate♪
Right!
So don't
come to me again!
♪Even breathing becomes lighter♪
♪Finally stop crying♪
♪As time goes by♪
♪Seeing you through♪
♪You are the reflected star♪
♪An unattainable shadow♪
♪Touching you broke the fate♪
♪I am the floating cloud♪
(Magistrate's Residence)
♪There will be sunshine after the storm♪
Your Lordship, you woke up.
How long have I been asleep?
Two days.
Two days?
So it's not a dream.
Your Lordship.
Your injury...
Never mind.
Her Ladyship went back
to Ship Guihai.
Do you want me to inform her?
No need.
She will never come back.
In the past, the quarrels
between the two of you
can be resolved soon.
But some things
are arranged by fate.
I don't quite understand.
Her father is Cai Wenzheng.
You get it?
It's impossible.
Your Lordship.
Is there any misunderstanding?
Remove
everything related to her
from the house.
And also
the cook.
Yes, sir.
Your Ladyship.
Miss Xue.
Why didn't you go back?
I just went back to the Magistrate's
Residence and you weren't there.
I'm here to take you home.
I haven't finished
sorting out the herbs here.
You should go back first.
Your Ladyship.
Did you quarrel with Yuxuan?
Why are you not even willing to
go back to the Magistrate's
Residence now?
No.
You think too much.
Do you treat me as an outsider,
so you don't want to
tell me anything?
I just want to do something
for Haoxue Cosmetics before leaving.
Are you leaving?
Why?
What happened?
Miss Xue.
There's something
I haven't had time to tell you.
Actually, I am not Nie Sangyu.
What are you talking about?
My name is Ji Man.
My real identity is the daughter
of Guihai Warrior.
Back then,
I entered the Marquis's Mansion
by mistake
because I lost my memory
after falling into the water.
Wait.
Are you kidding me?
It's true.
That is to say,
Guihai Warrior is not your godfather.
He's your...
So Ning Yuxuan and I
shouldn't be a couple,
and we shouldn't be together.
Due to my status as
the second-rank lady
with imperial mandate,
this matter
cannot be made public yet.
When the time comes,
I will completely be back to Ji Man,
someone
who has nothing to do
with Ning Yuxuan.
Your Ladyship.
Miss Ji.
We all know
how difficult it is
for you two to get to this point.
In my cousin's heart,
no one
can replace you.
In the past, he was always
serious in speech and manner.
But
from a certain moment,
as long as you are by his side,
he is sometimes as happy
as a child.
Because of you,
he became different from before.
the atmosphere in the whole mansion
is not as depressing as before.
Do you remember
when you fell into the water
before,
he was by your side
all day and all night?
He was afraid that
you would be in any danger.
I've never seen him
learn to cook
for anyone either,
even if what he cooked was a mess.
Your Ladyship.
Stop talking.
I'm really busy.
You'd better go back.
Miss Xue.
Thank you.
No matter who I am,
we will always be
the best partners,
whether it is before
or in the future.
♪If I can't let go of my delusions,
there's no use seeing the world♪
So many beautiful flowers.
So nice!
Who arranged this?
♪There is still a long way to go,
but our love and hate are at a loss♪
I'd better make another one for you.
Don't grab my noodles.
These are the best noodles
I have ever had.
So delicious.
♪My heart is breaking into pieces♪
It tastes so good. Take a try.
♪Even the tree that bears love-sickness♪
♪Can't bear how lovesick we are♪
When can I be with you
fair and square
as Ji Man?
Trust me.
I will definitely give you
a satisfactory answer.
♪Our fate has been decided in advance
because lovers always miss♪
(Ning Yuxuan.)
(Let the memories)
(be our treasure.)
(Perhaps not seeing each other)
(is the best choice.)
Master.
His Majesty is going to Haifang
to attend the Imperial Supplier Contest.
You are told to leave
for Haifang today
to deploy defenses
to protect His Majesty.
Pack up the luggage.
Let's set off immediately.
Yes, sir.
Hold on.
Send two letters for me,
to tell Qingyun and the others
my itinerary to Haifang.
Yes, sir.
(His Majesty is going to Haifang in person
to attend the Imperial Supplier Contest in these days.)
How long does it take?
Less than half a day.
Have you contacted
those merchants yet?
I have contacted most of them.
Most of them
are old friends of Lord Tan and you,
so they promised readily.
Only Haoxue Cosmetics
dominates the cosmetics industry.
Don't forget that
we have the ace in the hole.
It's a risky move.
The hit
will definitely defeat them.
And the game
will be quite interesting.
Sir, you do have foresight.
One more thing.
I heard that
Ning Yuxuan and Nie Sangyu
have been at odds with
each other recently.
Arrange a restaurant
when we arrive.
I'd like to meet
my old friend.
Yes.
Your Ladyship, why did you
ask me here today?
Is Ning Yuxuan feeling
better recently?
Thank you for saving His Lordship
that day.
Ning Yuxuan!
Hold on.
To be honest,
His Lordship's old illness relapsed.
He had soaked in ice water
for two hours
the night before.
How come?
Is his medicine enough?
If not,
I'll go get him some more.
There is still a lot of medicine left.
But after using it a few times,
it had little effect,
so he stopped using it.
Your Ladyship.
It shouldn't be up to me
to say something.
It's his secret trouble.
The way to save him
is not just medicine.
Although I'm just a bodyguard
with a humble status,
I can tell how much
His Lordship cares about you.
Please think about it twice.
I see.
There is one more thing
I don't understand.
Say it.
Since you saved him that day,
why didn't you let me tell him?
Perhaps it is the best choice
for us not to meet each other now.
It's good for him
and for me.
Put it here.
You should get to work.
Okay.
Qingqing.
How are you doing?
Qian Yiming?
No wonder.
So you're the one
following me these days, right?
I mean no offense.
(Qian Yiming)
Seeing that you are living well
and have your own business,
I am really happy for you.
Qingqing.
Let's talk privately.
No need.
Just say it here.
Qingqing.
Three years have passed
since our parting in the capital.
In the past few years,
I have been thinking that
if I hadn't been
so obedient
to my mother,
maybe I wouldn't have hurt you.
I've been in pain
all these years.
This time I came to Haifang
for another chance
from you
to prove that
I love you.
Qingqing.
Qian Yiming.
Stop acting.
Your acting skills have regressed,
and you didn't even shed tears.
I still have work to do.
Leave here yourself.
Qingqing, don't leave me.
Qingqing.
Don't call me
Qingqing anymore.
It makes me sick.
Qingqing.
I really love you.
You...
Do you like
someone else now?
Qingqing.
I love you, Qingqing.
I love you!
Mr. Ning.
I haven't seen you for a long time
since we parted in the capital.
Today I see you are
as elegant as ever.
Let me propose a toast
to you.
I'm on official business,
and I can't drink.
But I'm
curious
why Mr. Ling came to Haifang
to supervise me so early.
Look at what you said.
I'm here today
not to discuss business with you,
only to talk about our old days.
Then we have nothing to talk about.
Mr. Ning, you are so funny.
A moment like this
reminds me of
our days in the capital.
Stop.
Do not bring up memories.
Just get to the point.
Okay.
My visit to Haifang this time
is entrusted by His Majesty
to visit the lady with imperial mandate.
I also prepared her some gifts.
But
I also invited her.
Why didn't she
come with you?
She is busy with
the Imperial Supplier Contest.
How could she be so busy?
Yes.
She doesn't even have time
for a meal?
No.
Okay.
That being the case,
I have to pay her a visit in person
in your residence
as a show of courtesy.
Mr. Ning.
Don't make any excuses.
This is the entrustment of His Majesty.
Please.
(Magistrate's Residence)
Mr. Ling.
What's wrong, Mr. Ning?
We are already at the gate.
Won't you invite me in?
I'll at least
greet Her Ladyship.
What's wrong?
Could it be that
she won't go home tonight?
Mr. Ling.
Please.
Mr. Ling is here.
Mrs. Ning.
Darling.
What's up?
Isn't it enough to see me every day?
I invited Your Ladyship
to a banquet today.
Why didn't you come?
Mr. Ling.
I was so busy
with the business.
You...
You won't blame me, will you?
Never mind.
Fortunately, I have met Mrs. Ning.
His Majesty specifically entrusted me
to pay a visit to you
when I come to Haifang.
I also
prepared some presents.
Look.
Thanks to His Majesty for his concern.
But we won't accept
the presents.
Mr. Ling, you must have been
exhausted from a long travel.
Come in and have a cup of tea.
Yes, Mr. Ling.
Didn't you want to come in?
What about...
If you
don't want to,
we won't
force you.
I see.
Let's go, darling.
Wait.
The taste of food in Haifang
is different from that
in the capital.
Be careful not to
cause an upset stomach.
Darling.
Let's go.
Did you see Gui Bai just now?
No.
After coming out of the restaurant,
he left alone.
Keep an eye on Nie Sangyu.
Let's see what tricks they're up to.
Yes.
Thank you.
No need.
Your Ladyship.
Gui Bai.
His Lordship is in trouble.
Ling Jianxing has come to Haifang.
Right now he is rushing to
the Magistrate's Residence
with His Lordship,
saying that he wants to see you.
I was afraid...
I was afraid that if Ling Jianxing
found out that we were at odds,
he would take advantage of it.
It would be bad
if Haoxue Cosmetics was dragged down.
The play is over.
I am leaving.
Wait.
They may still be out there.
You'd better
not leave now.
I'll take you back
later.
No need.
I will leave myself.
Okay.
(Magistrate's Residence)
I already told you
I was immature at that time.
So childhood likes
don't count.
But are you
admitting that
you liked me
very early on?
I saw with my own eyes
that after leaving
the Magistrate's Residence,
Nie Sangyu went to Ship Guihai
and didn't return all night.
It appears
she had no intention of
spending the night at
the Magistrate's Residence at all.
Isn't it enough to see me every day?
Mr. Ling, you must have been
exhausted from a long travel.
Come in and have a cup of tea.
If you
don't want to,
we won't
force you.
Ning Yuxuan and this lady
with imperial mandate
are considered a perfect match
by His Majesty.
If they only have the name
of a couple,
but are actually at variance,
it's a serious crime
of deceiving the Emperor.
Zheng.
Continue to
keep an eye on Nie Sangyu
to see how far they are at odds,
and then report to me in time.
Yes.
Sir.
Princess Ruyue
should be here soon.
Right.
We've been waiting for a long time.
How long have we been waiting?
So long.
Mr. Ling.
It's time to begin.
Everyone, please be patient.
A distinguished guest hasn't come yet.
A distinguished guest?
Who's that?
So many people are waiting
for this one person.
That person must have a high status.
Why hasn't that person
come here for so long?
What distinguished guest?
The distinguished guest of Mr. Ling.
We'd better wait.
So arrogant.
The least etiquette...
Why hasn't that person come yet?
Coming. Look.
Look.
Really?
Coming.
What a scene.
She is dressed so grandly.
It's not as if she is here to
participate in a competition,
but to receive an award.
Everyone.
During this Imperial Supplier Contest,
in addition to local businessmen,
we have invited
businessmen from all corners
of the state.
Among them,
there is a distinguished guest.
Princess Ruyue.
Princess?
She's really a distinguished guest.
Yes.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hard work for you.
How could it be her?
Thank you, Mr. Ling, for your invitation.
As Mr. Ling said,
I came to Haifang this time
not only as a princess,
but also as a businesswoman
who participated in
the Imperial Supplier Contest.
I brought
a self-developed face cream,
and my goal
is to stand out
and win first prize.
Princess...
Mr. Ling.
This is a felon
of the imperial court.
How did she become
Princess Ruyue?
General Tao.
I'm afraid you misunderstood.
This is
Princess Ruyue,
Lord Tan's niece.
It's just that
she may have a slight resemblance
to that felon of the imperial court.
If she receives poor treatment,
I'm afraid we will offend Lord Tan
and the Emperor.
Everyone.
I came to Haifang in the order
of His Majesty.
His Majesty pays close attention
to public opinion.
And Haifang
is an important wharf of our country.
So His Majesty attaches
great importance to it.
As a result,
this year's Imperial Supplier Contest
is scheduled to be held in Haifang.
Mr. Ning.
I hereby announce
the official establishment
of the Shipping Department today.
The Imperial Supplier Contest
is officially starting.
It's on.
Great.
(Shipping Department)
Good!
- Great!
Awesome.
Nice.
Good.
Wen Wan!
Watch your manner!
Miss.
You got the wrong person.
Aren't you in the
Court of Judicial Review?
Miss.
What do you mean?
Stop acting.
You have done so many bad things.
How dare you come back?
How dare you disrespect the princess?
Take her down.
Wait.
Princess Ruyue.
One might cover up the past
if made any mistake.
But now you are the princess.
If you do
anything outrageous,
it will reach the Emperor's ears.
Think about it twice.
Reach the Emperor's ears?
My uncle Lord Tan
watched me grow up since childhood.
Even the Emperor
held me in his arms once.
What right do you have to remind me?
Someone.
Take them down.
- You!
Stop!
Princess.
I didn't have a chance
to introduce you just now.
This is
Mr. Ning Yuxuan,
Magistrate of Haifang,
also the current Left Consul.
This is
his wife,
also the lady with imperial mandate.
This is my first time to Haifang.
Please take care of me
from now on,
Mr. Ning
and Mrs. Ning.
Was there any misunderstanding
between the lady
with imperial mandate and Princess?
I just arrived at Haifang.
I don't know
when I offended Mrs. Ning.
She seems
quite hostile to me.
Princess, you just arrived at Haifang?
Haifang is rich in products.
You should walk around.
It's just since the Imperial
Supplier Contest is approaching,
Haifang has been quite a mixed bag.
But with Mr. Ling around,
there shouldn't be any problems.
I have long heard that the people of Haifang
are simple and honest,
and they are hospitable to guests.
Now I understand that
seeing is believing.
Alright, everyone.
Princess is exhausted
from the long journey
and has to go back to rest.
Princess.
Mr. Ning.
Mrs. Ning.
See you.
She's up to nothing good.
Be careful.
(Haoxue Cosmetics)
Wen Wan is back.
So weird.
Right.
Who is she exactly?
This vicious woman
has done so many shameful deeds.
How dare she come back?
We finally made Wen Wan
pay the price.
I don't know
what tricks she played again.
Now she turned into
Princess Ruyue.
And she has something to do
with Lord Tan.
So I guess
the story behind it
must be far more complicated
than we imagined.
Now that
she staged a comeback,
we have to be careful in the future.
Sangyu.
Don't care about the princess.
Since she dares to compete with us,
let's defeat her
and make her fall on her face.
Then let's tear off her mask.
Right, beat her hard.
Exactly.
Compete with her.
Beat her hard.
I'm going to convince my dad
to leave later.
In this situation,
I cannot leave the responsibility
of Haoxue Cosmetics
to you.
I will fight side by side
with you.
Really?
Then we have
a better chance of winning.
Yes.
Let's work together
to defeat that Ruyue.
- Defeat her!
Don't worry.
Well done.
You didn't show your slip.
How does it feel
to let Mrs. Ning suffer?
It's so satisfying to
watch them getting mad
but not being able to do anything to me.
I have never let
Nie Sangyu suffer before.
The more depressed she is now,
the happier I am.
I will definitely not let
her and Ning Yuxuan have an easy time.
I will make them repay me
for the pain
they have caused me.
♪Summer stars, autumn night♪
♪Who is wandering
under the moon in my heart♪
♪The deepest story
with the shallowest goodbye♪
♪After passing by,
I can only meet you in my dream♪
♪The wind can't breeze
the long street of time♪
♪The burning yearning will never cool♪
♪Two hearts meet again foreshadowing love♪
♪How can I describe it
when we look into each other's eyes♪
♪Take a life time to write the story♪
♪Together with you♪
♪Company you♪
♪Just for your glance and smile♪
♪The first promise means the forever love♪
♪Fireworks all over the sky
light up your night♪
♪Take a life time♪
♪To write the story with you gradually♪
♪Just like this♪
♪Our love goes on and on♪
♪The day we first met,
the year when we get old♪
♪My heart and my love will never vanish♪