=Romance of a Twin Flower=
=Episode 17=
Be careful. Careful.
Get up, Gui Bai.
Get up!
Come on.
Have some water.
How do you feel?
You seldom drink, do you?
I have to protect His Lordship.
I can't drink.
Then you shouldn't have drunk that much.
Do you
just give yourself to His Lordship?
His Lordship...
He's a good official.
He often says
we should contribute to life,
defend the people,
learn from the sages,
and maintain a peaceful world.
Peaceful world.
What a nerd!
I know
you've been stalking me
these days.
Your master
sent you for some investigations,
right?
But I also know
you're doing something else.
Protecting me.
Do you know
how I realized that?
Because wherever I went,
I could smell
the blood from you.
The man behind this
framed me with Lianxiang's death
and urgently forced me to plead guilty.
If I guess correctly,
since my jade pendant was lost,
I've been in his trap.
Haifang is far from the capital
but the news went back there
so quickly.
I'm afraid they want to suppress us
with this murder case.
His Majesty has been aware.
You'll be sent back to the capital
for the interrogation
of the Court of Judicial Review.
In case of unexpected trouble,
I guess they would kill you
before you return to the capital
and pretend you killed yourself.
I know.
I'm a titled lady
and now involved in a murder case.
If I'm really sent back to the capital,
I would be pretty much doomed.
I might even die.
So, this place
could be the safest for me
and the easiest to be monitored by you.
Ning Yuxuan,
I know you've been protecting me
from the beginning.
Thank you.
Boss.
Have you got anything?
Shen Liancheng has a minion Qiang,
a habitual thief.
He used to be stingy.
He spent all the money he stole
on the wine.
And in the casino,
he was heavily in debt.
But the other day,
he suddenly
got rich.
He not only paid off the debt,
but also became a wealthy man
in the casino.
My brother and I
sounded him out.
He confessed.
Shen Liancheng asked him
to steal the jade pendant.
Shen Liancheng?
Shen Liancheng isn't an enemy
of Ms. Nie.
He probably
framed her to trap Ning Yuxuan.
You two,
keep a close eye on Shen Liancheng.
His plan failed.
In a day or two,
he would do something else.
Got it.
Go.
The smell?
After you left that day,
I rethought
Lianxiang's case.
All the evidence
pointed to Mrs. Ning.
But one thing
was wrong.
The smell.
I wouldn't be wrong
about Mrs. Ning's smell of rouge.
But in Lianxiang's room,
I didn't smell
the same rouge.
Instead,
I smelt something
I seldom smelt before.
So, at that time,
I didn't realize
what smell it was.
But the other day,
I went to the wharf.
I smelt the same thing
from the boatmen
of the Dragon Gang.
The fishy smell
with the mildew smell
from the cabins.
This smell
would only exist on those
who always put out to the sea.
So, I'm sure
Mrs. Ning didn't
go to Lianxiang's room
that night.
The Dragon Gang?
It's quite a big thing.
What? How do I not know?
You know what?
It's not Mrs. Ning
who killed Lianxiang.
Not her?
Then who did?
No idea.
But I heard
Miss Shui of Shuiyan House
saw the murderer
and recognized him.
She did?
Yes.
The other day, she was jarred
and couldn't say anything.
Now, she has woken up.
Officers are waiting for her testimony.
Really?
Don't you see that more officers
are patrolling around Shuiyan House?
They're waiting for Miss Shui
to identify the murderer.
You're right, I guess.
Recently,
more officers are patrolling.
These years,
Shen Liancheng has been doing crimes
with the support of Lord Tan.
But now,
Lord Tan has abandoned him.
Few men
still want to follow him.
You're right.
After Shen Liancheng dies,
the original Dragon Gang
would no longer exist.
By then...
Lang,
we would have to
rely on you.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
Gentlemen,
you're my seniors.
You've been groveling
to Shen Liancheng for years.
Now we finally get a chance
to restore our gang.
I swear I'll do my best
to regain our status!
Good point.
Yeah. Good point.
- That's good.
- That's great.
Good point.
Chief, bad news.
Around Shuiyan House,
more officers are guarding.
They change shifts every two hours.
Our men can't get in.
Chief,
what do we do?
What time is it?
A quarter past six.
Let's stick to our plan.
Yes.
Shen Liancheng set out with his men?
It's quite lucky
for an idiot like him
to have lived to this day.
You screwed your mission
and still laughed at someone else?
If you fail your mission again,
Shen Liancheng
would be your example.
I understand.
I've arranged the best warriors
of Haifang
to stand by
and cooperate with Shen Liancheng.
This time,
they must do the mission perfectly.
It's best to kill them both.
Only in this way
can Master stop worrying.
Yes.
What are you waiting for?
Kill them!
Losers.
Go.
Miss Shui,
could you please do me a favor?
What is it?
I have a fair idea
of the man behind all this.
But with so little evidence,
I can't arrest
the murderer.
In this case,
Nie Sangyu would be sent to the capital
for the interrogation.
So, I need to set a trap.
And I need you
to cooperate with me.
I spread disinformation
that you saw
the face
of the murderer.
Are you saying
I should wait in my room
until the murderer comes?
I'll arrange
the best guards
to keep you safe.
Let me do it.
Your Lordship,
I want to stay here
and protect Miss Shui
without moving a step.
When I'm around,
I'll let no one hurt her.
Miss Shui.
If you trust me,
I'll protect you with my life.
I trust you.
Don't be afraid.
I promised to keep you safe.
Even at the cost of my life.
How touching!
Chief, some men are coming.
Our men saw
Shen Liancheng take his minions
to the Magistrate's Residence.
As soon as
they saw him,
they reported it.
Chief.
Oh, no.
Hey, where are you going?
Come on. Be seated.
Don't worry, Miss Shui.
Be seated.
Don't move.
Oh, I know.
What?
It may hurt.
Bear it.
I'm used to it.
To what?
Can anyone in this world
be used to getting hurt?
Since my childhood,
I've been fighting around
with His Lordship
and following his instructions,
to contribute to life...
Defend the people,
learn from the sages,
and maintain a peaceful world.
What a nerd!
Next time when you protect others,
could you first
take care of yourself?
The life doesn't hurt.
Neither does the world.
When you're wounded,
only you feel hurt.
Ning Yuxuan.
Why did you suddenly take me back?
You released me without permission.
Would this cause trouble?
Listen.
The murderer would do something tonight.
I must arrest him and his men.
The prison is no longer safe.
You should hide here.
You found the murderer?
Not yet.
But trust me.
Tonight,
everything would be clear.
Tonight?
What would...
Stop asking questions.
Later,
hide somewhere.
Whatever you hear,
don't come out.
Go.
Stay safe.
Just go.
(Magistrate's Residence)
Chief,
everything is ready
as you wanted.
Under such circumstances,
we have to fight desperately.
Tonight,
I must kill Ning Yuxuan!
Yes, sir.
(Be Diligent and Alert)
Shen Liancheng, Chief of the Dragon Gang,
broke out of prison, killed Lianxiang,
and tried to kill the witness Miss Shui.
Tonight, he even broke in
to assassinate me.
Shen Liancheng,
do you plead guilty?
You knew I would come?
The man behind you
tried so hard to get you out of prison
because he wanted you to do something.
But your murder came to light
and you failed to kill Miss Shui.
You have no way out now.
Unless you want to be abandoned,
you'd better confess.
Nice trap, Mr. Ning.
But so what?
You forced me
like this.
Even if I have to die,
I would fight it out with you!
Now that I dared to break in,
I didn't dream to leave alive!
Take him down!
(Will Ning Yuxuan be in danger?)
Ning Yuxuan!
Ning Yuxuan, are you all right?
Leave.
No, I won't!
I must stick with you!
Leave!
I'll stick with you, alive or dead!
I won't...
I won't leave.
No.
Ning Yuxuan!
♪Memories are always bitter
My heart is breaking into pieces♪
♪Even a true lover's knot
can't make us a true couple♪
- My wife
- Ning Yuxuan.
can't get hurt.
No.
Ning Yuxuan!
Ms. Nie, are you all right?
Ning Yuxuan.
Ning Yuxuan...
How do you feel?
Sorry.
It's my bad. Sorry.
It doesn't matter.
I'm not that fragile.
Ning Yuxuan...
Ning Yuxuan.
Ning Yuxuan!
Ning Yuxuan, don't scare me.
Wake up!
Ning Yuxuan!
Ning Yuxuan, don't scare me.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Hey,
be gentle.
Or let me do it.
You?
You want him to hurt more?
I...
It's all right.
I was wounded,
but I killed Shen Liancheng.
It's worth it.
Boss,
I don't agree.
Last night,
you could have
also killed Lackey Ning!
That was quite critical.
If I missed it,
I might hurt Ms. Nie.
I couldn't make a rash act.
So, you didn't want to hurt Ms. Nie.
We thought you...
I showed mercy to Lackey Ning?
The Nings are
our sworn foes.
I would never show any mercy
to Ning Yuxuan.
Shen Liancheng is dead.
We got rid of
our biggest trouble.
Now,
our plan to restore the Tea Gang
would officially start.
From this day on,
anyone who did bad things,
in collusion with Shen Liancheng,
would be eliminated.
Some men wanted
to go back to the right path
but were restrained by Shen Liancheng.
Let's present them
a totally new Dragon Gang.
Eliminating the bullies
and helping people in need
are the only codes of conduct
of our Tea Gang.
- Yes, sir.
Thank you
for protecting me all the time.
But it turns out...
It turns out
I'm not your wife.
You have to get better soon.
Don't scare me.
Do you hear?
(Magistrate's Residence)
- Your Lordship.
- Where's my wife?
Has she left?
Take it easy, Your Lordship.
Her Ladyship is still here.
In the past few days,
she was taking care of you.
Now, she's resting in her room.
Glad she has stayed.
Now that you woke up,
I'll have the doctor
check up on you.
Not now.
Have you interrogated the criminals?
Have they signed the testimonies?
My wife must be vindicated.
Rest assured, Your Lordship.
They were interrogated.
After Shen Liancheng died,
his men all confessed.
They not only admitted
how they framed Her Ladyship,
but also that they killed the beggars
in the temple of the capital.
Before I passed out,
I kind of saw the mark of the Tea Gang
on Shen Liancheng.
He was also from the Tea Gang?
Do some investigations
and see if the Dragon Gang
has more remnants from the Tea Gang.
Yes, sir.
Another thing.
Shen Liancheng made a sudden attack.
But Yuan Lang popped out unexpectedly.
How did he know about the attack?
I'm confused, too.
How could Yuan Lang
get here much faster than me?
He must have known
Shen Liancheng's plan.
Or he wouldn't have come
so fast.
Yuan Lang.
Shen Liancheng.
Dragon Gang.
Do a more careful investigation.
There must be something fishy.
Yes.
The problem in Haifang is
more complicated than I imagined.
No more thinking about this.
My wife must be tired these days.
Ask the cook to make something delicious
for her.
But Her Ladyship said,
after you woke up,
she would find Ship Guihai
and leave here.
What?
Your Ladyship.
You're awake?
Do you feel any better?
Does anything ail you?
I... I feel...
I feel numb all over.
I don't feel good at all.
What's the numb part?
Your arm?
Or the wound on your back?
Is it because of that wound?
How does it hurt?
It hurts here.
Your heart?
What's wrong with it?
It hurts?
Is it because of the wound?
But...
Are you all right or not?
I...
I'm so silly. You fooled me again.
The doctor said
you were all right
and would be better soon.
So...
So, I'm leaving.
Do you really wish to leave?
Yes.
Now, I know
who I am.
Shouldn't I go home?
And...
And I'm not Nie Sangyu.
Not your wife.
But I've never treated you
as Nie Sangyu.
So...
So, I'm Ji Man.
I should go back to my own home.
So much for this conversation.
I'll take Muxu away.
You stay for more rest.
The soup was just made.
It's still hot.
Have it before it gets cold.
Your Ladyship,
are we really leaving?
What about His Lordship?
Muxu,
I'm not Nie Sangyu.
I'm Ji Man.
So,
stop calling me Your Ladyship.
Call me My Lady instead.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
No.
My Lady, I mean.
Where are we going now?
Now...
We're going back to Ship Guihai.
Ship Guihai?
Here we go.
What's up?
Someone asked to see Miss Ji.
Miss Ji?
Yes.
Get him in.
Here he is.
Miss Ji Man,
someone's looking for Ship Guihai
on the wharf,
claiming to be you.
I guess
she must be a fraud.
You're always on the ship, aren't you?
What?
Someone pretends to be Miss...
Who dares to pretend to be me
and make trouble at my place?
Bring her to me.
I'd like to see
who this woman is.
- Yes.
- Done.
- All right.
Come on. Hurry up.
(Haifang Wharf)
Hurry.
Watch your step. Be careful.
What...
What a big ship!
So, this is Ship Guihai?
Ship Guihai.
Enjoying the sea breeze here
feels so good.
It's nothing.
After we embark on the ship,
we can enjoy the sea breeze every day.
Really?
Muxu.
Think about it.
If...
If I'm not
Guihai Warrior's daughter,
would...
Would we have
nowhere to go?
My... My Lady,
don't scare me.
It wouldn't happen.
I was just kidding.
Come on. Let's go over there.
All right.
Go.
Why hasn't she come yet?
My Lady, you're back.
You're really back.
We looked for you for a long time.
At last, you're back.
Yeah, My Lady.
You're finally back.
- Great.
- Wonderful.
Miss Ji?
This is terrific.
Make way!
Miss, you...
Oh, My Lady.
My Lady, you're finally back!
Where have you been?
- I miss you so much.
- Let go of her!
If you still didn't come back,
I would abandon the ship
and search for you on the land!
But Miss...
These days,
it's been so hard for me
to pretend to be you.
Miss.
Excuse me, but who are you?
I'm Sang Shen.
Sang...
Sang Shen?
My Lady, you don't recognize me?
Should I know you?
I... I grew up with you,
sticking together for a dozen years.
Yeah.
Yeah, My Lady.
Right, My Lady.
That's right, My Lady.
You grew up with me,
sticking together for a dozen years?
Do you remember that?
Her Ladyship...
She fell into the water and got hurt.
She forgot a lot of things.
Hurt?
Are you all right, My Lady?
- Much... Much better now.
- Are you all right?
And who are you?
Me?
Let go of her!
I'm Muxu,
Miss Ji's closest maid.
Shut up!
Go away!
This is my lady.
Who do you think you are?
She's my lady!
Wait, wait.
I have something to ask you.
Are you sure
I'm your lady
and Ji Ming's daughter?
Yes, of course.
You're my lady.
Forget about anything else.
The smell of cream
on you
can be unique in the world!
It's made of lily, cardamon,
rosin, almond, and glossy Ganoderma.
That explains.
No wonder when I embarked,
I felt very familiar.
Of course, you did.
This is your home!
Yeah.
This is your home, My Lady.
Why can't I
think of anything?
Come with me, My Lady.
Hurry.
Let me show you around.
Wait for me.
Hurry.
My Lady, come in.
Come in and look.
This is your room.
My room?
What a luxury room!
My Lady,
come this way.
Check your clothes.
These are the new clothes
for you.
Made of luxurious ramie fabric
we brought back from Yinzhou
before the turn of the year.
Just in fashion.
Ramie fabric?
The special fabric
for the Palace
in Yinzhou?
Yes, your favorite fabric.
Extremely expensive.
All the clothes are made of it?
There are a few more
wardrobes of clothes.
What are these?
My Lady, they're all yours.
Come and look.
Muxu,
look at this.
Put it on.
Come on.
Looks great.
Yes, yes.
A good jewel makes you look better.
Look at this bracelet.
Looks perfect.
- My Lady.
- Better than those in the capital.
But My Lady,
you never wore such jewels before.
These are your favorite.
The best pearls. Round and plump.
They're mine?
What a great pearl!
For my daily wear?
My Lady,
come here and see.
Something more?
Come and check.
What else?
Come on. Be seated.
You must be tired.
- All right.
- Be seated first.
My Lady.
- My Lady.
- You're so wealthy.
Books you've collected for years.
(Collection of Herbs)
Look.
Collection of Herbs?
Sheng Nong's Herbal Classic?
[*The Holy Farmer, a legendary ruler]
They're all out-of-print collections.
Classic of Cold Pathogenic Diseases.
Classic of Acupuncture.
Reference to Famous Herbs.
(My Lady, can you understand)
(these words?)
(Stop nagging.)
(We don't read the words,)
(but we can read the pictures.)
(Besides,)
(I can learn to read)
(from this day on.)
(Sang Shen,)
(you should learn, too.)
(Why am I)
(recalling...)
My Lady,
you must be thirsty. Have some water.
Thank you.
What a nice cup!
It's just your drinking cup.
Made of a whole piece of jade.
Jade?
A whole piece?
No flaws at all.
It feels warm and was perfectly carved.
Such a great cup
is even a rare treasure
for noble families in the capital.
It's true.
I can't drink with it.
Let's put it away.
If it's dropped or crashed,
there would be trouble.
Let me put it away.
No big deal, My Lady.
It's just a cup.
We've got some more in the warehouse.
Fine.
It's no big deal.
Besides this,
there are many more little things
you bought on impulse
but soon forgot.
Gold, silver,
jade, or glaze.
And everywhere, you bought houses,
shops, fields, and horse ranches.
Remember?
Here's the catalog.
Check it out.
Buy anything you want.
I make records for you.
When you want something,
you can find it immediately.
What a wealthy family!
My Lady,
you're the only daughter of Ji Ming,
Guihai Warrior.
Not to mention such little things,
you even own Ship Guihai.
That's right.
I own the whole ship.
You remember it?
Never mind, My Lady.
Let me show you this.
You will recall something.
Here, My Lady.
Formulations and experimental records
of the face creams
you've worked out for four years.
Check them out.
(The 12th formulation of face cream)
These are my formulations.
(The 13th formulation of face cream)
Five spoons of almond oil
and ten maces of beeswax.
Boiling for one hour.
All the processes
have been recorded.
Even the degree of boiling
and the most secret herb are recorded.
So, I knew how to make the cream before.
My Lady,
you invented the creams
just for us.
When you saw we have chapped skin
and bad appearances
because of the exposure to the sun,
you made up your mind
to make the best creams for us.
My Lady, you're the kindest girl
and you care about us most.
Think harder.
Have you recalled anything?
No, nothing.
It's... It's all right, My Lady.
Now that you're back,
you'll gradually get back your memories.
By the way, My Lady,
are you...
Are you still single?
What do you mean?
My Lady,
you ran away from home
to find the man you love
in the capital.
Did you find him?
The man I love?
The man she loves?
After a glance at him on the wharf,
you loved no one
but him.
After only a glance,
I fell in love with him?
Sounds like I used to be
very shallow.
Just a handsome man...
Can he be more handsome
than Ning Yuxuan?
Who's Ning Yuxuan, My Lady?
No... Nobody.
Sang Shen.
Where's my father?
I mean Guihai Warrior,
my very rich father.
Let's... Let's go find him.
Go.
My Lady,
you have no idea.
After you left a message
and ran away from home,
Mr. Ji got very angry.
He went to the capital for you.
But since he left,
we've heard nothing of him.
We can't help worrying.
You didn't hear of him?
Then why didn't you search for him?
Don't worry.
Mr. Ji is like a free loach.
Wherever he goes,
he'll be safe.
He ordered us
to wait in Haifang until he returned.
Oh, I see.
Ning Yuxuan.
What are you doing here so late?
For business.
For business?
Who are you?
How daring!
This is Mr. Ning Yuxuan,
the magistrate of Haifang
and the husband of Miss Ji.
What?
Gui Bai,
Ship Guihai
hasn't been repaired for years.
It shall be under repair from now on.
Everyone aboard
should disembark for settlement.
Off you go.
You came for the repair thing?
In this case,
we wouldn't bother you.
We can afford the repair, after all.
Yeah, we'll repair it personally.
You can't force us, can you?
Without charging,
I'm not forcing anyone.
If anything goes wrong with the ship,
people will die.
And no one can be responsible.
If you find it
very inconvenient,
I can offer my residence
for your settlement.
No, thanks.
How about this?
Tonight,
we'll set up
the fishing nets
and canvas
and spend the night simply
on the wharf.
By then,
we wouldn't disturb
the repair work.
What do you say, Your Lordship?
- Come on. Let's do it...
- Gui Bai,
any fishing nets or canvas,
once found damaged,
must be repaired.
Yes, sir.
None of them can be taken off the ship.
Ning Yuxuan!
I...
♪Summer stars, autumn night♪
♪Who is wandering
under the moon in my heart♪
♪The deepest story
with the shallowest goodbye♪
♪After passing by,
I can only meet you in my dream♪
♪The wind can't breeze
the long street of time♪
♪The burning yearning will never cool♪
♪Two hearts meet again foreshadowing love♪
♪How can I describe it
when we look into each other's eyes♪
♪Take a life time to write the story♪
♪Together with you♪
♪Company you♪
♪Just for your glance and smile♪
♪The first promise means the forever love♪
♪Fireworks all over the sky
light up your night♪
♪Take a life time♪
♪To write the story with you gradually♪
♪Just like this♪
♪Our love goes on and on♪
♪The day we first met,
the year when we get old♪
♪My heart and my love will never vanish♪