What is...
this?
I gave it to...
my first love to confess my love.
It doesn't mean anything else.
I didn't want to forget my wound then.
That's why I kept it.
But...
why do you ask...
You're Black Dragon, aren't you?
Strawberry?
Didn't you know it was me?
I suppose you didn't know.
That's why we're in this mess.
Leave. I can't talk right now.
What if they find out who the other person is?
I'm sure it'd be a huge shock.
Since they haven't found out, they might never know.
And Ju Yeon finally looks...
truly happy.
Ouch.
Ha Jin, are you busy at work?
Should I come and help you?
You know I'm not busy.
Ha Jin, should I come to entertain you, then?
You should just rest instead.
You must be tired, following my schedule.
I'm not tired at all.
Being at home is more tiring.
I have no energy because I can't see you.
I actually want to discuss something.
Huh?
Black Dragon and Su Jeong.
What about them?
Hey! Hey, beggar!
Hey!
♫  Baek Su Jeong is a beggar  ♫
♫  She's a beggar  ♫
Hey, how dare a beggar ignore me?
It's your fault!
Yong Jun.
Are you okay? Oh, no...
Did you two fight?
Can't you see he was injured?
What will you do
if his precious leg gets a scar?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You think sorry is enough?
You need to teach your child well.
I heard Su Jeong's mom is at a hospital.
I feel bad about it, too.
It must be hard on your own.
But still.
You shouldn't completely neglect your child.
- Pardon?
- It sounds like
she often doesn't bring supplies and interrupts classes.
I heard she can't pay for lunch on time either.
Did you know she didn't bring lunch
to the picnic and forced everyone to share?
- Ma'am.
- Other moms complain
about her ruining the class mood.
And she caused trouble like this, too.
I'm sorry.
Let's go, Yong Jun.
Dad.
Yes.
I...
didn't do it.
Yes.
I should care for you more.
No.
I'm okay.
I decided to become strong on my own.
Honey!
No...
I decided to care for Baek Su Bin, too.
Because Dad can't afford to
and Mom is...
gone now.
Maybe that's why I was even more angry.
That you were the first person I wanted to rely on.
But in the end,
I couldn't rely on you either.
And I have to be alone.
I hear the bagel sandwich is famous here.
We're here because they want to join our store.
Does it taste bad?
No, it's good.
Did something happen last night?
You look tired.
You don't seem to have an appetite either.
Was there an issue with the room you stayed in?
I didn't sleep very well.
I had a nightmare.
It was about things that weren't supposed to happen.
It still feels so vivid, as if it was real.
Gosh.
It must've been a terrible nightmare.
One moment, please.
I don't like fashion styles like that.
I don't want to be anywhere near it.
How about now?
I don't care.
Because I like you.
Your video game avatar isn't real.
You're actually this pathetic person.
Stop walking around looking like that
and stay sealed forever, you little nerd!
If the same person hurt me
and also made me smile,
what am I supposed to do?
Hey,
are you sick or something?
- Unni.
- Yes.
It's nothing. I'll let you start.
What did you want to say?
Huh?
The thing is...
Your director.
Are you still getting along with him?
Why do you ask?
So...
S-So, your director is...
The director is Black Dragon?
Huh? How did you—
How did you know?
Since when?
Last night.
You had to drag me out when I just got back from my business trip?
Brace yourself and listen.
We're going to my girlfriend's shop now.
Why would I go there?
The place is called "Sulo."
The owner there is your girlfriend?
Yes. When we get there,
your first love will be there.
Su Jeong?
Shit.
You knew?
S-Since when?
Last night.
Since last night.
Hey, a-are you okay?
Should we just not go? Huh?
Since when did you know?
The day you were bringing the director,
I saw you two together.
Yes, I knew it had to be then.
I thought about this a lot, too.
I thought finding out later would shock you more.
That's why I wanted to tell you today.
Are you okay, Su Jeong?
I'm not okay.
I'm totally not okay.
You dated Black Dragon, right?
That's the part that's not okay.
How could Black Dragon and I be an item...
Gosh, why didn't I know?
You should've told me sooner.
I wanted to.
But I didn't want it to affect your work.
And I didn't know you'd actually date.
Yes.
You did nothing wrong.
It's all my fault. My fault.
When I found out...
Black Dragon was an immature middle schooler.
What bothered me more than being deceived by a kid
was that I wasn't sure what I liked about him.
The person I liked and trusted was fake, you know.
I thought I knew him well this time.
If he's the Black Dragon who tricked me,
who did I like, exactly?
What will you do now, then?
I want to avoid him for now, but...
Hello.
Well...
I'm not sure what to say,
but I thought I should see you.
I wanted to see you. That's why I came.
So, you happened to meet at the shop
and found out we were Black Dragon and Strawberry who met in the game.
While trying to separate us,
you ended up together?
We ended up together by chance, too.
We didn't get together while trying to separate you.
That's not important here.
It means Chief Kim knew all about my past.
N-Not a lot. I learned a-a little.
A little.
- I'll go.
- Su Jeong!
Wait, calm down a bit.
Could you sit down for a moment?
Should we?
If y-you don't mind, may I say one thing?
Since this happened anyway, I want the four of us to get along.
Let's let bygones be bygones.
And it happened when you were little.
You two will keep seeing each other, right?
- Yes.
- No.
Gosh.
I should start prepping for today.
Gosh, I should h-help her, too.
Let's talk outside.
- Wait—
- Su Jeong—
- Ju Yeon—
- Black Dragon—
Do you think...
you can continue to like me?
What do you mean by that?
You found out who I am.
Would you still be able to like me?
Do you think...
you won't be able to?
I think it'd be difficult.
I don't think I could.
Can you decide that so easily?
It's not easy. It's obvious.
No matter how much I think,
my answer would be the same.
- Ms. Baek—
- So, let's stop now.
Stopping now...
would be best for both of us.
What do you think happened to them?
Ju Yeon wants to keep seeing her, but Su Jeong doesn't want to.
Maybe she's more hurt by the past than we thought.
Rather than that,
if you hit a wall frequently,
you become good at breaking through the wall,
but you get to know the wall too well.
It could make your fear grow.
Su Jeong hit many different walls
often on her own.
She might not want to deal with a certain wall.
She doesn't want to dredge up the pain, I suppose.
So, let's stop now.
Stopping now...
would be best for both of us.
It was easy for her.
Team Leader Baek.
Come to my office right now.
Please...
sit there and wait.
Team Leader Baek.
Yes.
The next branch for the renewal project should be the Daejeon branch.
The inspection result looks good, too.
I'll prepare so it doesn't affect the schedule.
I didn't tell you to leave yet.
Wait.
We're not done talking.
Director, why are you making me sit here all day?
I told you. I need to talk to you.
Talk to me now, then.
Just because we broke up—
That's what you think.
I can't break up.
Why should we break up?
Do you have to ask?
Did you forget what the first love means to us?
It's a bad memory.
We don't want to be reminded. How could we keep seeing each other?
Because I still like you.
You told me to keep liking what I like.
That's you.
How could I stop?
You said you liked me, too.
That was when I didn't know who you were.
Back then...
lying about my age...
I'm sorry.
It was my fault.
Could you...
Could you please forgive me?
Forget about everything...
and think of the Ban Ju Yeon now.
Why haven't you...
changed at all?
You were like this then, too.
You said you liked me.
But you left me behind as if everything was a lie.
See?
You haven't forgotten that I hurt you.
As you said,
I wish liking you was all a lie and a joke.
I wouldn't have gotten hurt
and wouldn't have said things that hurt a kid.
I could've comforted you
by saying we can meet when we're older.
I genuinely liked you.
That's how much I trusted you.
I was happy that I had someone to rely on.
But you were just a kid.
How could I like you again now?
I made it really spicy.
How is it?
I can't tell if it's spicy.
How strange. That can't be.
I broke up with him.
You don't open up easily.
You must've liked him a lot.
I know.
I guess I was very lonely.
After meeting Black Dragon...
at the offline meeting, I realized...
that I was really lonely.
That I was desperate.
I needed someone so much that...
I didn't realize he was a kid.
I think that's why I got tricked.
Like a fool.
I hate that so much.
You didn't just hate Black Dragon.
You hate yourself, too.
Yourself from back then.
Hyung,
have you been through a breakup?
What?
You must've had many since you dated a lot.
How did you repeat so many heartaches?
Ju Yeon, I think you're drunk.
When you start dating,
both people need to agree.
But why?
Why is it over when one person says,
"It's over" in the end?
I'm opposed to it.
I, Ban Ju Yeon,
will fight against this...
cruel breakup system.
No.
I actually can't.
Because I don't have the right.
What do you mean, the right?
I thought only I was hurting...
because only I was sincere.
I didn't know how disappointed she was in me...
and how hurt she was, thinking she was deceived.
I really was a clueless kid.
I'm the one who hurt her more.
Ju Yeon.
Leave.
The one I really hated...
wasn't you.
It was me.
An employee?
The rumor says a team leader.
- Look.
- Seriously...
Look.
Team Leader,
have you seen this, by chance?
What is this?
I saw the original photo, too.
I think this woman is Strategy Team's Baek Su Jeong.
There was a post
on an office worker site this morning.
I think it started there.
You were announced as a successor recently
and some employees even recognized
Team Leader Baek in the photo.
Even before the PR Team can handle it,
it spread on various social media and websites.
The rumor snowballed in the process.
I see.
Why did you meet Team Leader Baek's family?
I ran into them.
And I treated them to a meal to be nice.
I see.
That's what I thought.
You're in a tricky position over nothing.
I know.
How unfair to Ms. Baek.
Take care of it as soon as possible.
Team Leader Baek,
I heard you're marrying the director.
- Is that true?
- Pardon?
I hear your wedding is at the Yongsung Hotel.
The hotel employees know all about it.
But why would the director date Team Leader Baek?
And even marry her?
Why not? She's pretty.
Yes.
Being pretty is the best.
Gosh, I want to be pretty, too.
Excuse me, team leaders,
I thought Yongsung Department Store was No. 1 in the industry.
That's why I was proud to work here.
I gave my best, too.
But the team leaders of the No. 1 store
buys into an unconfirmed rumor and judges a female coworker's looks.
It's disappointing.
We were complimenting you.
Let's start the meeting.
And...
let's only talk about work at the office.
I know what you're thinking,
but the director and I aren't like that.
Yes. Of course not.
Pardon?
Na Na, what's wrong? Is something wrong?
It's not that.
No, it's just that...
I thought you might feel it's so unfair.
- Pardon?
- It makes no sense.
Why would you...
jump into hell at work with the director, even?
Seriously. They know nothing.
It's totally impossible.
But people are talking so mean.
It's because they haven't seen how much they hate each other.
They were so scary on the rooftop.
You must be frustrated by all this nonsense.
I'm okay.
- Don't cry, Na Na.
- Team Leader...
I know. They believe the way they want
just to entertain themselves. You know?
They know how to come up with sensational stuff.
They have no idea what Team Leader is like.
How long will this go on for?
I don't know.
It's a false rumor. They'll quiet down in a month.
Yes. They should.
I'll report them.
I took down all the articles.
We decided not to address it officially.
The PR team is handling the public opinions on the online communities.
That it's a baseless rumor.
Many didn't believe it, saying the successor
and an employee can't be dating.
I think things will quiet down in time.
You wanted to see me, Chairwoman.
Yes.
I don't mind your charade
but acknowledging their family events is enough.
Why do you create noise by not differentiating hierarchy?
You're giving people the wrong impression.
- Being excessive always causes trouble.
- I'm sorry.
Since you're known as the successor,
wherever you go and whomever you meet,
don't forget that the investors are watching you.
If you are to grow the company,
meet people who suit you in the proper places.
Yes, I'll keep that in mind.
So...
will you just let this go?
They started talking over nothing already.
You think it won't happen again?
Next time, they'll be noisy over even smaller things.
Baek Su Jeong...
Find the right moment
and dismiss her without people noticing.
You have to pull the weed from the get-go.
I think that'd be difficult.
It'd be difficult?
Team Leader Baek...
is a crucial staff to the renewal project.
Dismissing her over a false rumor
would be our loss facing an important project.
It'd be difficult to replace her, too.
Okay.
Just leave her, then.
If she gets on my radar again,
I'll take action myself.
I'll let you go.
You knew about...
their get-together, right, Chief Kwon?
Yes, I did.
But...
you've also cared for the employees' families in the past.
I didn't think it'd be such an issue.
So, I didn't report it to you.
I'm sorry.
If you're sorry,
you should take responsibility, Chief Kwon.
Are you okay?
Everyone is talking about you two all day.
Why should I not be okay?
It's not true, anyway.
I haven't seen...
Director in his office since earlier.
He was probably summoned by the chairwoman.
He'll be okay.
He's good at resolving anything.
You don't have to worry.
I'm not worried.
I think she is worried.
I'll do something about all the businesses with a below 10% sales record.
- All of them?
- Yes.
We'll cancel the contract or come up with a plan.
I'm planning to do something quickly.
The renewal project is underway, too.
I don't know how it'll be in the long run,
but fixing a few major stores won't be enough.
To double the sales and possibly more,
all branches need to improve the sales.
We'll get busy.
We should get busier.
That's a good idea.
We have to be extra careful right now.
Director.
What is it?
Well...
This isn't causing problems with the chairwoman, right?
I don't think it's any of your concern.
I'm directly involved. How can I not be concerned?
If she misunderstood, I'll explain myself.
I'll tell her there's nothing going on—
No. That's not necessary.
As you said, there's nothing going on.
It won't be an issue.
That's a relief, then.
Yes, it is.
So, let's not get personally involved from now on.
Okay.
Finally...
everything seems to be back to normal.
It's a relief.
♫  Stay  ♫
The song is innocent.
Start liking it again with me.
♫  Until I don't recognize myself, stay  ♫
♫  Wait just a moment  ♫
The payment went through.
Miss?
Oh, yes.
Thank you. Take care.
♫  I own my memories, stay  ♫
♫  Until I let you go, stay  ♫
♫  Even in my memories  ♫
♫  The small (the small) warmth (warmth)  ♫
♫  Let me (let me) cherish that, at least  ♫
♫  I think I'll freeze  ♫
♫  I feel endlessly cold  ♫
♫  If you leave (if you leave), too (too)  ♫
I don't need to ask to do this, right?
♫  The beauty is gone  ♫
♫  I think I'm already dying  ♫
♫  It makes me feel disgusted  ♫
♫  Stay, my dear  ♫
Are you home, my daughter?
Gosh, why is it raining so much?
Su Jeong.
Dad.
What's wrong, Su Jeong?
Su Jeong, what is it?
What's going on?
I'm sorry, Dad.
I guess I wasn't such a strong person.
I thought I was strong.
What's wrong...
Noona, is it because of that SOB?
Why? He wanted to keep it a secret.
Is he blaming you for the rumor now?
I'll kill that jerk.
No, it's not. It's not like that.
What do you mean, it's not like that?
I...
I suggested breaking up.
I broke up with him, Dad.
We agreed to end it.
While I was checking the low-sales businesses,
I noticed one of them stood out.
Do you mean the clothing brand, "Bukayo"?
Yes.
They're one of the top sellers in another branch.
The discrepancy was severe.
I'll create a report just on that.
Submit it this morning.
Don't make me ask you next time.
Okay, I'll be more careful.
Team Leader.
I think the rumor will be gone in no time.
You look even more distant than before.
The rumor didn't make things more awkward, right?
- No.
- Right?
That's good, then.
That's great.
We don't look close.
­
All right.­
Come on, I told you to sit.
You're making me feel bad.
It's okay.
I prefer to be close to you
like this than to sit down.
Thank you.
How's Black Dragon?
He's only focusing on work.
I think he's overdoing it, but that's how he is.
I can't tell if he's worse or not.
But I'm worried.
Su Jeong is like that, too.
She's always been all about work.
The rumor spread when things were already rocky.
They can't move on overnight.
It must bother them.
Although they can't show it.
Aren't you going home, Team Leader?
I should.
I'll go soon. Don't worry and go now.
Okay. I'll see you tomorrow, then.
- Get home safely.
- Thanks.
♫  You and me  ♫
♫  That one day we met  ♫
♫  I'm standing in front of you like this  ♫
♫  And you're looking at me  ♫
♫  Close to you  ♫
♫  The more I get to know you  ♫
♫  My feelings are growing deeper  ♫
♫  I'll finally tell you today  ♫
♫  When the sun goes down  ♫
♫  I'll tell you how I feel  ♫
♫  Falling down  ♫
Team Leader.
♫  The showering stars and the round moon  ♫
♫  I whisper in the river  ♫
♫  Draw me now  ♫
♫  We glow under the moonlight  ♫
♫  The moon goes down  ♫
♫  Even on dark nights, winter days  ♫
Director.
♫  It's shining on you  ♫
♫  Tell me now  ♫
♫  Our bright night  ♫
♫  We stay bright  ♫
♫  Stay bright all around  ♫
♫  The moon goes down  ♫
♫  Even on dark nights, winter days  ♫
♫  It's shining on you  ♫
♫  Tell me now  ♫
♫  Our bright night  ♫
Are you really relieved to be back to normal?
Have any of you seen the director today?
No, I haven't seen him.
Isn't he in his office?
He went home really late last night.
I left after 10,
but he was still here.
Really?
Just one moment.
He always keeps the messenger on.
It's off.
Is he at a meeting?
How strange. He always keeps it on.
Are you okay?
I need to get it approved today.
Chief.
Is the director working offsite?
He couldn't come in because he's sick today.
Is he very sick?
I'm not sure. I got a brief report as well.
He would've come in if he could.
Since he's home,
he must be very sick.
I'm worried. I wonder how sick he is.
He's been skipping meals lately, too.
He's been working all day, all night.
How could he be well?
The chairwoman will be upset if she finds out.
She'd be upset that he's sick?
The health issues
for the owner's family lead to risks.
Excuse me, then.
Wake up. Who are you to worry?
But I can worry as a human to another.
He's an adult. He'll figure it out.
I'm sure he's fine.
Will you be okay?
Our relationship could get exposed anytime
and it could be problematic for your dream of
becoming Yongsung's successor.
I think I'd be okay...
as long as I have you.
As long as you like me.
The medicine... Give me everything.
He won't eat. He passed out from overworking.
Give me everything that could save him.
­
Yes, Chairwoman.
Director.
My gosh.
Director, are you okay?
He tried to go to work in this state?
I'm sorry.
I was sorry, then
and I am now.
I only thought about my pain.
I forgot about the pain I inflicted.
But it's the same this time, too.
What if I hurt him again?
I wanted to become...
your biggest and coolest secret.
Don't go.
I...
thought I wanted someone to love me.
Even if I didn't work for it
or try hard.
But...
you gave me love like that.
Back then...
and now, too.
So, don't feel bad.
Don't hate yourself either.
You already...
are the biggest and coolest secret of mine.
Because you're my first love.
I love you.
I love you, too.
♫  Love is just like a miracle  ♫
♫  It seems close to grasp, but I can't  ♫
♫  Even if our hearts touch each other's  ♫
♫  Things went by for many reasons  ♫
♫  In the end of the faint moments  ♫
♫  You're becoming more prominent  ♫
♫  We'll meet each other again someday  ♫
♫  I'll be hoping for that  ♫
♫  As much as I've waited  ♫
♫  I hope we run into each other again  ♫
♫  I'll say it tonight  ♫
♫  I hope you'll be my miracle  ♫
♫  Can't be grasped like it was a dream  ♫
♫  We thought we weren't meant to be together  ♫
♫  As much as I thought of you  ♫
♫  I hope we meet again someday  ♫
♫  I'll say it tonight  ♫
♫  As we think of each other  ♫
When Ms. Baek entered and left the director's house...
Did Director get fired?
You're just jobless, then.
Jobless?
I'm bad at being bad at things.
The things you've been doing alone...
Do them with me from now on.
Team Leader Baek Su Jeong...
Take care of her discreetly.
What's this, Team Leader?
This makes no sense.
Could you not tell Director for now?
I'll make a choice, too.
♫  I hope we meet again someday  ♫
♫  I'll be hoping for that  ♫