[English subtitles are available]
My Lord. Old Madam.
Please investigate it.
Hong
helped Young Madam Shaolin buy herbs from her hometown.
So she threatened Young Madam Shaolin
and asked for a reward.
I can't stand it.
I fought with her
because of anger.
You want to strangle her
just because of such a trivial matter?
This lowly servant hit me first.
If I didn't fight back,
she would have beaten me to death.
Hong.
Tell us what happened.
I want money
because Mrs. Liu
asked me about Young Madam Shaoyang's personal affairs.
What did you say?
I told her the birthmark of the Young Madam Shaoyang.
So you told her.
Tell me, how did you know?
On the day you fell into the lake,
Bing changed your wet clothes.
I happened to see it.
But I only told Mrs. Liu
about the position and the shape of the birthmark.
I don't know anything else.
I've never been involved.
My Lord. Please investigate it.
You lowly servant!
Nonsense!
When did I ask you about Young Madam Shaoyang?
You have no evidence and you're framing me.
My Lord, Old Madam,
I'm innocent!
I won't accept it! I'm innocent!
Mrs. Liu.
I'm good at
making people confess.
Mrs. Liu.
Just having a tough mouth
won’t help.
Even the hardest bones
can’t withstand my methods.
There's no need for your methods.
If you have something to say, say it.
Father,
this matter concerns my reputation.
If she doesn't confess,
I won't go easy on her.
Well...
Young Master Shaoyang.
You...
Don’t try to trick me.
I didn't do anything.
I don't know anything.
Are you sure the painting you burned
was the tampered one?
This doesn’t require your interrogation methods.
The painting
Cousin Shaozhen bought
was originally a "Distant Mountains" painting by Wen Keming.
But while admiring it, the image changed.
I thought of checking the physical evidence
but found that Mrs. Liu had secretly burned it.
Were you trying to destroy the evidence?
Ah.
Young Master Shaoyang.
I did burn the painting,
but I did it
for the sake of your reputation!
So you admit to burning it.
Mrs. Liu.
Do you know that even if you burn a painting to ashes,
we can still determine
if the paper was soaked in a special solution?
Besides,
are you sure you burned it completely?
The paper you burned was treated with a special wax,
which makes it smooth like silk.
Only three shops in the entire capital
sell such high-grade paper,
so it won’t be difficult to find out
who was behind this.
Here's a new landscape painting
I had Master Wen Keming
recreate using special ink.
This...
This ink...
It’s made from ink mixed with a special solution.
Could the scent...
It's Baiqi incense
from the Western Regions.
When the incense is burned,
it causes the solution to disappear,
revealing the underlying
pattern
on the soaked paper.
Mrs. Liu.
Am I right?
You...
You’re framing me!
I didn't do anything.
You...
You’re framing me!
We’ve checked all the shops
in the capital that sell paper and Western exotic incenses.
The only person associated with
the Marquis' Mansion who purchased paper,
Baiqi incense, and a special solution
is Hong.
Unfortunately,
Hong wasn’t aware of the implications.
Your plan was well-crafted.
You thought
Hong would buy the items
and you could blame me
while shifting the guilt onto her.
But you didn’t anticipate
Hong is greedy,
so she bought ordinary ink instead.
Left with no choice
Mrs. Liu, you personally went to a distant shop
to purchase the special solution.
The shopkeeper who sold it to you is right outside.
Do you still want to deny it?
Speak!
Who instructed you?
Father, Mother.
Mrs. Liu is my nanny.
She has been very helpful
in managing the household.
A few days ago,
I complained about Xizhao in front of her,
and she must have misunderstood.
It's my fault.
Young Madam Shaolin.
It’s not a misunderstanding.
Young Madam Shaoyang punished me
in front of the servants,
humiliating me.
I was filled with resentment
and tried to slander her
to get her expelled from the Marquis's Mansion.
I also tricked Hong
into falsely accusing the Young Madam Shaoyang.
My Lord, Old Madam,
I'm guilty.
I plead guilty. I'm willing to be punished.
I'm willing to be punished.
Women are truly terrifying.
Liu Xizhao,
you’ve become quite bold.
You finally stopped pretending and showed your true colors.
Your Liu family is greedy for wealth.
Young Master Shaoyang doesn't enter your room,
so you vent your anger on me.
You little wretch!
Enough!
A servant
made you disregard your dignity and manners.
This is the Marquis's Mansion, not a marketplace.
Look at you.
You don't look like a master at all.
Master.
Guards!
Yes.
drag out this insubordinate, slanderous servant
and flog her twenty times!
Then, throw her out of the household.
No, Mother.
Mrs. Liu is old. She will die if she can't stand the caning.
She’s served us well despite her faults.
please forgive her, Mother.
You're so stubborn.
Drag her out now.
Flog her twenty times!
Let all the servants at home watch.
I beg you, Mother.
Let's go.
Mrs. Liu.
Mother.
Father.
Please spare Mrs. Liu.
Mrs. Liu
is my nanny.
She's old and can't stand the flogging.
This kind of rebellious servant
won't be tolerated
in this household.
You'd best
be quiet.
Given your work for the household,
we didn't hold you responsible for not managing her better.
Mother.
Cousin.
Have you forgotten the family teachings?
Now you're begging for mercy for a servant.
Cousin, have you lost your mind?
Young Madam.
The whole mansion knows
about how Fourth Young Master helped you today.
Why are you still unhappy?
Don't you think this is wrong?
I just want to clarify.
I didn't expect them to beat people to death.
I only know that
since you married into the Marquis's Mansion,
you've been living in fear every day.
Now that you have Fourth Young Master protecting you,
you will never be bullied again.
That's not what I meant.
Mrs. Liu made a mistake first.
She should be punished by the family.
If you make a mistake, you should be punished.
Bing.
Have you ever thought
if I was beaten today,
I wouldn't be able to see the sun tomorrow, either.
The rules here are too terrifying.
If I had known, I wouldn't have tried to clear things up.
Young Madam, you must be joking.
Only those who make mistakes will be flogged.
In this place, you could lose your life at any moment.
I can't stay here.
Young Madam.
Even if this Marquis's Mansion is a mountain of knives and a sea of fire,
I will be with you.
Please live well.
Why not?
The bracelet.
It must be the bracelet that caused the time travel.
Let's go.
Bing.
I think I'm poisoned.
How dare you be late to pay your respects to Mother.
You come in and start looking around.
What are you thinking about?
This is it.
I can go back once I get it.
I must get the bracelet from Old Madam as soon as possible.
My Lord,
why don’t you go in?
Greetings, Fourth Young Master.
Fourth Young Master, wait
Young Madam doesn't allow you to go in.
Why?
Young Madam has been praying in her room.
She doesn't see any guests.
Of course,
including you.
Me?
I just want to ask her out for dinner.
Maybe Young Madam was scared yesterday.
She'll be fine in a few days.
I will take good care of Young Madam.
Don't worry.
Was I not handsome enough yesterday?
Why the change in attitude today?
Young Madam,
since you married into the Marquis's Mansion,
this is the first time the Young Master has invited you to dinner.
Why did you refuse?
I need to get the bracelet. I don't have time for him.
By the way,
tell me about the bracelet.
The bracelet was bestowed by the late emperor.
The Old Madam always wears it and never takes it off.
But Old Madam once promised
to give it to the next daughter-in-law who would manage the household.
But she doesn't like you.
I don't think she'll give it to you.
Who would want to
manage this broken Marquis' household?
I'll be flexible later.
If it doesn't work, I'll find a way to steal it.
In order to go back,
I have no choice.
Fourth Young Madam, please wait.
I’m here to see Old Madam.
Old Madam has said
that from now on, you're excused from the morning and evening greetings.
You don't need to pay your respects anymore.
Are you saying
the Old Madam doesn't want to see me anymore?
Yes.
I've thought about everything.
But I didn't expect that
that Old Madam doesn't want to see me.
What should I do?
Young Madam.
You are so considerate.
You know I'm worried.
so he came here to make tea for me.
Young Madam,
these tea tools are for you.
For me?
If you want to please Old Madam,
you still need to restore your tea-whisking skills.
The Old Madam loves your tea the most
and says it's the best in the household.
Pour hot water here.
The tea powder you're holding is what you'll use.
Put them inside and stir it slowly.
Let me try.
What a coincidence.
Fourth Sister. Are you preparing some tea?
Third Sister, why are you here?
Let me try your handiwork.
Please.
I heard that you're good at whisking tea.
I was learning recently, so I came to learn from you.
I didn't expect...
Sorry, Third Sister.
I fell into the water a while ago.
I forgot everything,
now to mention whisking tea.
That's great.
Sister.
if you remember something,
it might harm everyone around you.
Since you're so honest, I won't bother you.
I'll go back first.
Young Madam.
Third Young Madam looks kind.
She doesn’t look like a difficult person.
Kind?
Why do I feel she's talking in a weird way?
How do your Young Madams
make Old Madam happy?
They will buy a lot of gifts to coax the Old Madam.
But our residence is poor.
There's nothing we can offer.
Find out
what the Old Madam needs recently.
Let's offer what she likes.
Little Young Master Yuenxu broke Old Madam's Nine Dragons Cup
I heard that hot water in that cup won't get cold after a long time.
But there are only a few ones left.
Even Second Young Madam and Third Young Madam can’t get them,
let alone us.
Find me a bronze craftsman.
A bronze craftsman?
It's so beautiful.
Young Madam,
is our cup really better than the Nine Dragons Cup?
Of course.
I'll show you something great later.
Why are you out?
Didn't Mother say
she didn't need your greetings?
Why are you wandering around again?
Mother,
I heard that your Nine Dragons Cup is broken.
So I asked someone to customize this thermos cup for you.
This cup is amazing.
After you pour hot water into this cup,
even in winter,
the temperature of the water inside
won't drop for hours.
This is a necessary tool for modern travel.
You're be convinced by it.
Goodness.
What a joke.
So all the maids in our mansion are decorations?
You don't use the maids who can boil water.
But you use your stupid bottle.
Fourth Sister.
we are not ordinary people.
To serve us masters to drink water,
there are special boiling maids.
The water that the masters drink
must be freshly boiled.
No matter it's winter or summer,
the maids will prepare water for the right temperature
for the masters to drink.
Alright.
When you're free,
learn something useful.
Don't focus on useless things.
Don't come here again
without my orders.
Leave.
Go.
I underestimated you.
The landing strike failed.
What's good about the Marquis's Mansion?
You even got maids who're in charge of boiling water.
It's a waste of manpower.
I'm sorry, Young Madam.
I didn't make it clear.
It's not your fault.
I underestimated your place.
Young Madam.
Young Madam, let's go another way.
Why?
It's closer to go this way.
Isn't it good to go home quickly?
People in the mansion say it's unlucky.
Don't be superstitious.
What's unlucky about it?
Young Madam.
There's a living dead here.
A living dead?