[English subtitles are available]
Bing.
Young Madam.
Young Madam, I'm sorry.
I know you're very sad.
But you shouldn't have committed suicide.
Young Madam.
Be careful.
I heard that you argued with His Lordship
because of me today.
You've just become a member of the Marquis's Mansion and haven't gained a foothold yet.
I can't be your burden.
If I die,
you can do the things that you want to do
and will have no worries.
Why are you so stupid?
You're not even afraid of death. Why are you afraid of these things?
Bing, trust me.
I will never sacrifice you
or let you...
Young Madam.
My fate is just like this.
I don't want to bring you any trouble again.
Don't talk nonsense.
Promise me
to live well.
I won't let you marry that eunuch.
Young Madam.
I'll cancel your servitude indenture.
In this way, His Lordship
won't be able to force you to marry him.
Okay.
Xizhao.
I don't think this is appropriate.
With His Majesty's favor,
Eunuch Gao has done many things to bully others.
If he likes someone, he will try his best to get her.
Once Bing leaves here,
I'm afraid it'll be more dangerous for her.
Fourth Young Master.
Fourth Young Madam.
Old Madam wants Fourth Young Madam to go to see her.
There's something she wants to discuss.
Mother.
Is Father really going to marry Bing to Eunuch Gao?
I've heard
that old eunuch is such a pervert.
He has married many concubines one after another.
Several maidens have even died because of his coercion.
When Xizhao comes later,
let's not
mention what happened to Bing.
She has been her maid since childhood.
Of couse she feels bad about it.
Women's fate
is all the same.
No matter what our family background is,
in the end,
we still can't control our own fate.
Mother.
Eldest Sister-in-law.
Second Sister-in-law.
You're in a good mood.
Just now, we were worried that
you would be sad because of
what had happened to Bing.
You worry too much.
Come on.
Let's get down to business.
I asked you to come here
because the Empress invited me to go talk with her.
I can only take one person with me to go there.
I'm thinking
I should take Xizhao to meet her this time.
I'd like to ask for your opinions.
I've met the Empress before.
I won't go this time.
Recently,
there have been many affairs in the mansion.
I also don't have time to go.
Since both of them don't have time,
then I'll take you there.
You can also socialize in the palace.
Thank you, Mother.
Thank you, Eldest Sister-in-law.
Thank you, Second Sister-in-law.
Bing can be saved.
Oh, wait!
What are you carrying?
It's a betrothal gift from Eunuch Gao.
Bing!
Where is Bing?
Bing?
Didn't you ask Bing to go out?
Oh no.
Why did Fourth Young Madam ask me to come here?
I don't know.
Ms. Bing, please wait here.
How come it's you?
What do you want to do?
Miss Bing, you still remember me?
Without seeing you for just a day,
it feels as if three autumns had passed.
Why don't you let me do some exercises first?
Let go of me!
Let go of me now!
Let go of you?
It was not easy for me to catch you finally.
I just don't want to let go of you.
Let go of me!
Help!
It's useless to call for help.
The more you shout, the more excited I get.
This fragrance of a virgin...
Are you okay, Bing?
Young Madam.
How dare you hit me?
I'm His Majesty's favorite person.
Eunuch Gao.
This is the Marquis's Mansion.
How dare you be so unscrupulous like this in the Marquis's Mansion?
You really have no respect for the Marquis's Mansion.
Vice Commissioner Lu.
Do you also want to offend me?
If His Majesty knows about this,
you should worry about yourself first.
I've given her the betrothal gifts.
This little beauty will be mine sooner or later.
Just wait and see.
I won't give up
until I bring this bastard down.
Old Madam, be careful.
You must be careful with your words and actions when you go to the palace this time.
Don't act recklessly.
It's not my first time going to the palace.
Don't worry.
Have a seat.
Marquise Lu.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
How is your health these days?
Thank you for your concern, Your Majesty.
I'm quite
healthy.
We met again,
Lady of Vice Commissioner Lu.
Your Majesty.
Have you received the skin-nourishing red wine
I specially made for you?
Yes, I have.
Your wine
tastes
mellow and sweet.
Drinking a cup of it before sleep
can help to calm the nerves indeed.
I can
sleep much better now.
If you like drinking it,
I'll continue to make it for you.
You people from Marquis of Changping's Mansion can always share His Majesty's burden.
When His Majesty encounters something important,
he trusts you the most.
Marquise Lu.
From now on, come to the palace more often.
Let's talk to each other more often.
In this way, we can also spend more time with each other.
Your Majesty.
I have something important to report.
There's no outsider here.
Tell me now.
Bad news, Your Majesty.
There's something wrong with the imperial robe you've ordered
for His Majesty's birthday banquet.
His Majesty was about to attend the birthday banquet.
As soon as he put on the imperial robe,
he discovered a hole on it.
His Majesty is very furious now.
What?
I checked it myself
before it was sent there.
There weren't any holes at all.
How come it got broken within such a short time?
When it was sent there,
it was accompanied by the people from the Imperial Household Department and the Fabric Bureau.
I also followed them all the way there.
No one touched the imperial robe on the way.
For an unknown reason,
something went wrong when His Majesty put it on.
Who served His Majesty to change into the imperial robe?
Noble Consort Jia did it.
It was her again.
She must have tampered with the robe.
What should we do now, Your Majesty?
His Majesty is going to see the ministers soon.
His Majesty can't wear
an old imperial robe at the birthday banquet.
The Fabric Bureau has replied that
now it's too late to mend the robe
or make a new imperial robe.
It's obvious that they've colluded with each other.
I have never been hostile to her.
But she kept making things difficult for me.
What on earth does she want me to do so that she can stop it?
Fine.
At this point,
I can only apologize to His Majesty myself.
Marquise Lu.
I'm sorry to let you see this unpleasant scene.
I have something important to do here.
I won't keep you here.
Your Majesty, please stay.
Your Majesty.
Do you have the guts to trust me this time?
I can help you solve the crisis.
Xizhao.
What are you talking about?
What kind of crisis can you solve?
If Her Majesty goes there to apologize now,
that woman's plot will become successful, won't it?
I have a way to help Your Majesty solve this problem.
Time is running out.
Please ask someone to get the imperial robe back at once.
I'll arrange the rest of it.
Xizhao.
Do you know that if you can't solve this problem,
you will be beheaded?
Everyone in the mansion has said that
Bing's embroidery skills
are qutie good.
But this is the imperial robe.
How could it be possible that she can embroider it?
Mother, don't worry.
Bing's mother is a top embroiderer.
Bing.
Why did you become my maid?
Young Madam, have you forgotten it?
My father
was originally an official in my hometown,
and my mother was a top-class embroiderer in the Fabric Bureau.
Originally,
the life of our family was happy and harmonious.
I had also been learning embroidery from my mother
and mastered good embroidery skills.
But later, my father was framed by a villain and put into prison.
My mother and I were also sold as slaves.
After my mother passed away,
I've been your maid to serve you.
Your background
is quite pitiful.
But I can't believe that you've mastered some embroidery skills.
I've been learning embroidery from my mother since I was kid.
I even helped my mother embroider the imperial robe.
It's done.
The embroidery is so good.
The techniques are exactly the same as the Fabric Bureau's.
You're really something
at such a young age.
Thanks for your compliments, Your Majesty.
Guards.
Send it to His Majesty now.
Don't let His Majesty's birthday banquet be delayed.
Yes.
Xizhao.
Bing.
I'm going to reward you.
You two solved the crisis for me today.
I'm going to give you a big reward.
Your Majesty.
We don't want any rewards.
I only hope that Your Majesty
can save Bing's life.
Saving her life?
Yes, saving her life.
Because Eunuch Gao, the chief eunuch in the palace,
wants to hurt Bing.
I remember that when I saw you for the first time,
it was at my sister's wedding in Marquis of Changping's Mansion.
Yes.
Your Highness, I feel nervous that
you still remember me.
We are relatives after all.
You don't need to stand on ceremony since we're relatives.
Stand up.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Aren't you curious
why I asked you to come here?
I'm stupid.
Please tell me the reason.
I've heard from my sister that
you usually work so hard for Marquis Lu,
but you've never had any complaints.
I admire you very much.
With your talent like that,
you shouldn't have wasted it
in an official's mansion.
It's all due to His Lordship's cultivation.
I've never dared to forget it.
Cultivation?
Mr. Lu,
your father is Marquis of Changping's younger brother.
You're supposed to have a share of the family property of this Marquis's Mansion.
Are you really willing to be inferior
to them like this for the rest of your life?
Your Highness, what do you mean?
My sister's reputation was ruined in the Marquis's Mansion.
What do you think I should do?
I don't know.
I only know that I dare not go against Your Highness.
If you need me to do something,
I'll try all my best to do it.
You are quite smart.
I was right about you.
Since you are so sensible,
just go back and wait for my orders.
Just wait to take over Marquis of Changping's Mansion.
Why don't you thank Her Highness for her kindness now?
Your Highness, thanks for your great kindness.