♫ Set off ♫
♫ With the latte I just brewed ♫
♫ And the long-lost sunshine in early summer ♫
♫ What about them ♫
♫ Are they waiting for an answer ♫
♫ When the breeze brushes the cheek,
stirring a strand of hair ♫
♫ Whisper to me ♫
♫ Spring grows, summer extends ♫
♫ Blooming freely ♫
♫ Is it all you ♫
♫ It's all you ♫
♫ Autumn harvest, winter storage ♫
♫ Season changes ♫
♫ With you ♫
[Episode 1 Grudges Shall Always be Avenged]
Hello.
Chi Cheng, I recently got a new snake.
Do you dare to come?
Just wait for me.
Huang Long, it's your turn.
Mom, I'll do it.
It's fine, let me do it. Today,
my future daughter-in-law is coming.
Thank you, mom.
Look, I bought three jins of crayfish for Yue Yue.
Mom, this doesn't even weigh three jins at all.
What?
Ms. Liu knew my future daughter-in-law is coming,
so she even gave me ten extra crayfish.
Mom, she fooled you.
It definitely isn't three jins.
Half bag is just water, I'm going to find her.
Son, don't go.
It's difficult for Ms. Liu to run a business.
Don't cause her trouble.
- Mom.
- I've told you that suffering is a blessing.
The more sufferings, the more blessings.
Yes, Mom. We've been like this
for all these years.
But today isn't different.
Yue Yue is coming today.
Right, why isn't she here yet?
It's okay.
She's always late when we date.
She's probably nearby now.
It's hard to find our place,
I'll go to pick her up.
This place is smelly and dirty.
Yue Yue.
Yue Yue, you're here.
We can go eat now.
My mom has already prepared the meal.
My mom is really happy knowing that you're coming.
I'm not here for the meal.
I have something to tell you.
Yue Yue, go ahead.
Wu Qi Qiong, let's break up.
Why, Yue Yue? Why do you say that?
Didn't you promise to come to my house
for the meal? Why so sudden?
What? I used to be attracted by you
because you were handsome.
But look at you now,
being with you makes me feel ashamed.
Yue Yue, what do you like?
I can change myself for you.
I can change back, Yue Yue.
We've been together for so long.
And we're about to get married.
Wang Zhen Long, what did you do?
Look at him, such a loser.
Why waste words to him?
Go for it!
Go for it, Mr. Guo!
Today, you're destined to lose.
Weren't they the best buddies?
Aren't they tired after many years of competing?
Do you think Mr. Chi's snake will win,
or Mr. Guo's?
Of course Mr. Chi's. He always wins.
I heard that Mr. Guo bought the black snake
from South America at great expense.
Today, Mr. Guo must make a comeback.
Go for it!
Go for it, Mr. Guo!
- Get it!
- Go for it!
Mr. Guo's snake has a chance.
- Get it!
Mr. Guo is going to win.
Kill it! Go for it!
Bite it!
- Go for it!
- Bite it!
Bite it!
Go for it!
Lost again.
Good!
Mr. Chi.
It's all right, guys.
Though I lost, I'm still happy.
Mr. Guo is magnanimous.
Mr. Guo is awesome.
Thank you, Mr. Guo.
Mr. Guo, I love you.
Mr. Chi is awesome.
Rest assured, I'm willing to accept defeat.
Spoils of war.
Forget it if you don't want to give me.
Li Wang.
Come on.
Long, this is my good buddy, Chi Cheng.
Go entertain him.
I've given you the person, have fun.
Chi Cheng!
[181s Glinic]
Dr. Jiang, I know you like desserts,
so I made you this cake.
Thank you, Ms. Mei Li.
You're welcome.
Mr. Li, this isn't good for your cervical spine.
Use a mirror.
Right, my girl just bought me a lipstick.
Did Wu Qi Qiong wake up?
Yes. Is this for me?
You glutton.
You're fine now.
It hurts.
Don't move, I just changed your medication.
Where am I?
This is a clinic. Your friends brought you here.
Friends?
Take it slow.
A woman?
A man and a woman.
The woman told me
to use the cheapest medicine available,
and make sure it's reimbursable.
She understands me best.
Let me tell you, she's my girlfriend.
- Girlfriend?
- Yes.
Then who is that man?
That man might be her friend.
Or perhaps a nice guy.
A nice guy.
Bro, it seems like you've been jilted.
Alright, I admit it.
Actually, it's not her fault.
Because I've become ugly,
unfashionable, and fat now.
I think you can change.
Really?
Trust me.
First shave your beard
and get a cool haircut.
The cooler, the better.
Okay.
Can you get me a haircut like him?
No problem.
Dress in a clean style.
[250 yuan]
Losing weight is the hardest part,
but you must keep at it.
If you make a big change,
your girlfriend will surely change her mind.
I'm here again.
- Okay.
- Here.
Congratulations on collecting them all.
Thank you.
I made it!
Hello.
Son, where are you?
Your dad is hospitalized, come back now.
Alright, got it.
I know.
It's okay.
Mr. Chi.
Take care of the snakes.
What's the matter? Are you jealous?
Little Jealousy.
Mom.
Why did you bring this thing back again?
Aren't you at the hospital with dad?
A caregiver is there,
so I came back to wait for you.
Let's go.
Where to?
To the hospital to see my dad.
No rush, let's go tomorrow.
Anyway, your dad is asleep right now.
I should have come back tomorrow.
I'm going to sleep first, mom.
Can't you keep me accompany for longer?
Speak.
Mr. Chi, terrible.
The snake lair was taken.
What did you say?
Why?
I don't know.
I suspect Da Kun and I
might have been drugged last night.
We slept very deeply, and when we woke up,
it's after nine in the morning.
All the snakes in the glass box are gone,
and the ones in your room were taken too.
Where is Long?
I don't know. He is gone.
Stop talking, find Long.
Aren't you hospitalized?
Lured me away?
I knew it.
I've arranged everything.
You'll start working
at the Property Department next week.
I use the back door.
How dare you!
Look at you, how frivolous.
You're already 28,
yet don't even get a decent job.
Guo Cheng Yu runs the company so well.
He is also frivolous,
but doesn't neglect business.
You can let him call you Dad. I'm fine with that.
I want him to be my son.
People called the complaint line to my office,
saying that my son is a weirdo
and with a chaotic private life.
I'm so embarrassed.
If you want your snakes to live well,
then go to work.
Table A36. Table A36.
Yue Yue, you're here.
Look, I've lost weight.
Let's go. I'll take you
to eat something delicious.
Wu Qi Qiong, can you stop bothering me?
I am here to tell you
that we can't be together anymore.
Don't send me messages anymore.
Why, Yue Yue?
You used to hate me for being fat,
messy, and unpresentable.
And I've changed. I've changed them all.
It's not about that at all.
I just look down on you being poor.
My friends around me
all carry luxury bags and eat lavish meals.
But with you, I am only eating
ramen noodles or spicy hot pot.
- Have you ever treated me to a nice meal?
- We are here now.
- Table A37. Here?
- I'm here.
This is a famous restaurant,
and I've waited in line for over an hour.
It's ready for dining.
Here. I have coupons.
[Stamp Collection]
This coupon can only be used for weekday lunches.
Sorry.
Yue Yue.
Look, it's over a hundred yuan short.
Let's switch to another place, shall we?
Let's go.
Look at you. Please go find someone else.
Wang Zhen Long.
I've told you, why waste words with him?
Who are you?
What?
Wu Qi Qiong, never-ending poverty.
With this name, you'll never rise in life.
Let's go.
Hello, sir.
Alright, I'll be right there.
Sir.
What takes you so long?
You usually ask me for projects and a raise.
But at critical moments, you're not available.
Why are you staring at me?
I asked you to fix this. Why staring at me?
Fix it.
Alright, I'll fix it now.
What are you doing?
Sir, this part is broken. We need a new one.
This one.
This part was perfectly fine. Did you break it?
No, it was broken.
Wu Qi Qiong.
You are really dumb.
Just cover the cost of the parts first.
Next month, you go
to Finance Department for reimbursement.
The money I advanced last month
hasn't been reimbursed.
My salary this month is less than 5,000.
If you think the company
treats you bad, you can quit.
Don't occupy the position here.
How dare you negotiate with me? Look at you.
Let me tell you,
if you pay the money today,
this matter will be over.
Yue Yue despises me of being poor
and ran off with another man.
Now my leader bullies me.
Everyone looks down on me.
I quit now!
[181s Glinic]
Wait, Wu Qi Qiong.
It's only been a few days, why are you here again?
I've changed my name.
To what?
Wu Suo Wei.
I want to make a comeback.
What?
What comeback?
I want to make a comeback!
[I want to make a comeback.]
Welcome.
Thank you for taking me in.
It's fine. I want someone
to help me look after the clinic anyway.
I want to start my own business,
but I'm afraid my mom will worry if she knew it.
Have you decided what to do then?
I've decided to sell candied figures.
To set up a stall at the night market
near Xiwang City.
I've heard the regulations are strict there.
No worries, I've already scouted the spot.
- Candied figures for sale!
- Fruits for sale!
We manage everything meticulously.
The management fee is paid on time.
They're coming, go now!
Wait for me.
Sir, why are they running?
This street belongs to the Yuan Duan Group,
you need a stall permit to set up a stall here.
Without a permit, they'd run
when they see someone checking.
So, did you get a permit?
I'm a small business
and often change places, it's not necessary.
Aren't you afraid of getting caught?
Let me tell you,
that person is named Hei,
and he's been looking out for us.
Average junior managers
don't dare to provoke him at all.
- That's great.
- Melons from Xinjiang.
- Mr. Chi.
- What's all the shouting about?
That big-bearded guy is the scumbag.
He often bullies others.
Let's see how Hei teaches him a lesson.
Go die!
Great!
What are you doing?
What are you looking at?
You…
You deserve it.
Sir, this guy in the suit is cool.
Make way.
You deserve it. Get up!
Mr. Chi.
When dealing with these unruly stall vendors,
we have to be tough.
Watch how I handle them.
Hey.
Li Wang, you know him?
I don't know him.
Mr. Chi, chase him.
You!
I'll catch you!
Let's get to know this guy.
What's the matter? You're nervous.
If there's someone coming for me,
don't tell him I'm here.
Alright, hide in there first.
- Okay.
- Don't make a sound.
Okay.
Don't make a sound.
What's up?
Looking for someone.
Who are you looking for?
Well…
Looking for you for diagnosis.
Alright, take a seat.
Tell me, what's your problem?
Guess.
If it's a gynecological issue,
go to the obstetrics and gynecology hospital.
Turn left and walk 30 meters,
then take metro line two.
You're really pretty.
If you're cross-eyed,
go to Tongren Hospital for consultation.
You like men, don't you?
If you have a psychiatric issue,
go to the psychiatric hospital.
[Jiang Xiao Shuai]
Jiang Xiao Shuai.
I remember it.
Did they leave?
Yes.
What a bad day.
I can't do this stall work anymore.
I need to find another job.
[181s Glinic]
Dr. Shuai, why haven't I seen you
with a girlfriend?
But I've had a boyfriend.
Sorry to disturb you.
You like men?
What? Scared?
No, nothing.
I'm leaving.
When did you take it?
When you were just talking.
My second startup is about to begin. Wish me luck.
Where are you going?
Chi, you are absent
in the class reunion again this year.
I am too busy to come.
What? Stop it.
You, Guo Cheng Yu,
and Wang Shuo who loves raising snakes
were really close before.
Now…
Okay, everyone.
After the two successful cases,
we're now looking for the third one.
Found it! Let me show you.
Isn't it good?
Alright, let's test him.
We've already connected the pinhole camera.
I'll record the whole process.
Once I turn off the phone, a miracle happens.
Are you alright?
Thank you.
You faked a fall?
You pretended to help me, but I can't fake a fall?
Bro, I'm not a thief.
I'm just recording a video. Here's your phone.
Bro, look, now you believe me, right?
I'm really not a thief.
What do you want?
I'm really not a thief, really.
You brought yourself here.
Wait, have we met before?
Bro, I have evidence to prove
I'm not a thief, let me show you.
Look, I run an anti-pickpocket account.
You're just a random passerby I picked.
This is to educate people
about some common thief tactics,
to avoid being stolen.
Trust me, bro. The livestream viewers
can vouch for me.
Look.
Look, right?
Right?
What's your name?
Wu Suo Wei.
What? That arrogant?
No.
It's my real name.
I have evidence. Wait for me.
ID card.
Look.
[Wu Suo Wei]
You are indeed named Wu Suo Wei.
Right. It's all a misunderstanding.
- Quite unique.
- Not at all.
Oh my.
Why did you throw sugar at me that day?
Bro, I didn't mean to.
I wanted to splash the one next to…
I didn't intend to splash you.
Bro, I was wrong.
Sorry.
Bro.
Bro, don't go.
Don't.
Two options for you.
Either get beaten up by me,
or have your device confiscated.
I choose to be beaten.
It's already settled.
Bro, give it back to me.
I spent a lot of money on it, bro.
Give it back to me, please.
Bro!
Mr. Chi.
Mr. Chi, I brought you the person.
He tried to escape abroad.
Mr. Chi, listen to me.
Your dad brought dozens of people to me,
and I was scared to death.
It was your dad who questioned me,
otherwise I wouldn't have told him anything.
Don't lie.
The call to the chairman's office
was made by Guo Cheng Yu's men, right?
When the chairman drove to you,
you were long gone.
Come here.
Mr. Chi.
What do you guys think of him?
Not bad, we all quite like him.
Everyone really likes you.
Wait, wait.
I'll leave him to you guys. I'm leaving.
Mr. Chi, Mr. Chi.
- Good boy.
- Mr. Chi.
Get lost.
Mr. Chi, I'm sorry.
Mr. Chi, I was wrong.
Let go of me.
- Watch out.
- Mr. Chi.
Don't let him die.
I was wrong, let me go.
Let go. Mr. Chi.
[Splendid Minghao]
Whose car is blocking my way?
Darn!
How did he park?
Mr. Chi.
Is it your car?
Drive away or it will be smashed.
What are you waiting for? Get lost.
This is the kind of man who deserves me.
Don't touch me. Focus on driving.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Darn, he blinded me.
Slow down.
Give way, give way.
Wang Zhen Long, wake up.
Wang Zhen Long, speak up.
Why did you call me back?
You're always like someone owes you money.
I'll give you one year,
if you can't find a girlfriend,
I'll decide whom you'll marry.
Okay, as long as she's not afraid of snakes.
Do you really have to carry that with you?
Our son doesn't have a girlfriend.
No matter what you say, he won't listen.
Once he has a girlfriend,
he'll understand what's important.
Right, son?
Tell me,
Old Wang's son is half-paralyzed.
Do you have anything to do with it?
Who? I don't know him.
It's best that way.
Let's go, Little Jealousy. Go home.
Leaving again. I don't even know
whom he takes after.
What do you think?
You finally appeared.
Shuai, you are still here?
I forgot you like men.
Are you avoiding suspicion
or deliberately seducing me?
Sorry.
What happened? It's like someone owes you money.
Don't mention it.
Can't do this live stream job.
My device was taken.
Then don't.
Are there any other jobs I can do?
I have a relative with a truck.
He usually delivers some goods.
Why don't you join him?
Payment by the task, and the time is flexible.
This works.
Sorry.
Recovered?
Seeing you, I recovered.
Cheesy.
Aren't you cold?
Of course, I'm feeling cold.
There's a python in my car.
I like snakes. I'll go check.
This snake is really cute.
Okay, I'll use you to comfort my dad
and take back my snakes.
We've searched everywhere we could,
and someone is watching the chairman's car.
But his routine is regular every day.
Except for the company and home,
he hasn't gone anywhere else.
Is it possible that they're in the company?
No way.
With this amount of snakes,
he has to prepare a large space
and dedicated people.
If they're in the company, we must hear some news.
Did you forget?
The company built a new storage base.
Wu.
You're the person
recommended by Shuai, so I trust you.
Just a reminder,
this batch of goods is very important.
You need the chairman's approval slip
to unload the goods.
Don't worry.
I won't open this for anyone.
I'm serious.
Alright, I trust you.
Here.
Okay, stop.
Bro.
Here you are.
What's in the car? Open it and see.
Who are you? Why should I open it for you?
The chairman said this batch of goods
cannot be opened by anyone.
Mr. Chi, found the snakes.
He's one of Junior Chi's people,
just open it and show him.
What?
No matter who, I won't open it.
Wasting my time.
Gang.
Come on, pry it open.
Don't open it.
I promised that no matter who, no one can open it.
What? I can open it.
Mr. Chi, it's all parts.
Didn't you say you found it?
Who told you to open it?
You filled the car with parts.
Why were you being mysterious?
If I don't get my wages, you…
It's you again.
What do you want?
Whatever I do, you're always there.
What are you doing?
This is Mr. Chi from the Warehouse Department.
What? I don't care which department you're from.
Compensate me.
How much?
500 yuan.
Gang, pay him 5,000.
Come, come over here.
Chi Cheng.
- She is really beautiful.
- Yes.
Really beautiful.
Why are you here?
I'm afraid once you're off work,
I couldn't catch you.
So sweet.
What? Are you envious?
Do you miss me?
Let's go.
Okay, let's go.
No wonder he's been against me all along,
causing me to mess up several jobs.
So you are Yue Yue's new boyfriend.
You're taking revenge on me for her.
Grudges shall always be avenged.
♫ I really want to tell you ♫
♫ There's more than just
the sunset and the distant sea ♫
♫ If today won't come back again ♫
♫ Don't mind the change of day and night ♫
♫ I really want to tell you ♫
♫ There's more than just stars or mountains ♫
♫ The sun rises and sets, you're all I see ♫
♫ Not fearing the halt of time ♫
♫ The last night on Earth ♫
♫ I just want to confess to you ♫
♫ Get through the doomsday with sincerity ♫
♫ Perhaps no regret ♫
♫ The last night on Earth ♫
♫ When life turns to dust ♫
♫ When seawater kisses the sky ♫
♫ I'll take you away without hesitation ♫