Weightlifting Fairy
-Hi, Mum.
-Jae-yi, will you be late today?
No, I won't.
Do you remember the dumplings
we ate the other day?
-You mean the dim sum?
-Yes, that one.
-I'll buy some on my way home.
-Okay, thanks.
Sure.
You must be bored.
Do you want some gum?
It's sugar-free, so don't worry.
Okay.
I don't have water in my car.
It's okay. Don't worry.
I'll just hold my breath.
I was so silly.
Things were going great, and I blew it.
Sorry I kept you waiting.
I couldn't find a convenience store.
I got a warm beverage
from the vending machine.
Here.
Thank you.
How is it? Are you okay now?
I think so.
The wind is cold in the morning
and evening.
You're wearing thin clothes.
You still have the hiccups.
Drink some more.
You can drink as much
as you want. It's just tea.
I started to learn swimming
when I was 11 years old.
I was a lonely, awkward...
...and nervous kid.
The water felt like my sanctuary.
Just like...
being in the arms of my mum.
In fact, I was left with my uncle's family
when I was 10...
...as my mum remarried
and went to Canada.
So the parents you have now are...
They're my aunt and uncle.
Jae-yi is my cousin.
It was okay.
My mum sent me presents
and postcards every Christmas.
I didn't think I was abandoned.
I believed we'd meet someday.
But...
Mum, do we have waterproof Band-Aids?
Are you hurt?
Check the drawers next to
the door to my room.
I realised that...
the handwriting on the postcards
were different after the first three.
It looked like...
someone tried to imitate
my mum's handwriting.
It was your aunt.
Was that day...
Yes. It was the day of the match when
I first experienced the symptoms.
Thank you.
I'm sure it wasn't easy for you
to tell me that.
Do you think it has something
to do with my symptoms?
Probably.
As I told you before...
"Panic disorder and conversion disorder
are diseases of the heart."
It can cause hearing problems, too.
I suppose you were quite shocked
that day.
You probably felt like you'd lost...
the only connection
you had with your mother.
This is good.
We now know what might have
caused your problem.
Let's take it slow to solve it.
Telling me about it
may have cured it by half.
So now... Let's see.
Which method will be
the most effective for you?
I think we need to do an experiment.
When is your next match?
Thank you for giving me a ride.
Please drive home safely.
What's wrong with her?
What is she wearing?
I gave her a good chance.
She should be wearing a pretty dress...
and show off her charms.
Only then Jae-yi would say,
"You look so charming today, Bok-ju."
But with those clothes,
it's all down in the drain.
Let me drop you off at your house.
It's not polite to let a woman
go home by herself at night.
No, it's fine. I can go home
from here even with my eyes shut.
I also need to stop by the mart
to buy something.
Okay, then. I'll see you at the clinic.
Don't forget to do some stretches
before you go to sleep.
Okay. Goodbye.
My goodness.
Gosh, you're going to break
your back, Bok-ju.
I can't watch this.
What should I do with you, Bok-ju?
Are you happy, Bok-ju? Are you?
Where is she going?
She never takes the subway.
Three.
Two.
One.
Okay, there she is.
Geez, I must've caught a cold
because of that dress.
Hey, who's this?
It's the weightlifting fairy, Kim Bok-ju.
Are you watching me 24 hours a day?
Why do we meet every day?
Right? I find it surprising, too.
Why do I always run into you?
What's that?
It's nothing. Mind your own business.
It looks like you're coming back
from a concerto.
You didn't go there...
looking unsophisticated
in a dress and heels, did you?
No way. I wouldn't wear
such an outfit to a concert.
I was checking just in case you did.
My brother despises a fashion style
that's too feminine.
Really?
No, I was kidding.
All men like feminine fashion style.
Hey.
Are you teasing me because
you saw me? You're so evil.
Don't call me evil when I paid for you.
Then why did you tease me?
I spent all of my monthly allowance
to buy those tickets.
Well, thank you for the tickets.
You should thank me.
Did you have a good time with him?
It wasn't bad.
-He drove me, too.
-You went for a drive?
You did everything, didn't you?
Watch out, Bok-ju!
Gosh, that was close.
Thank goodness for my quick motor system.
What's wrong with that driver?
Hey!
Come here, you jerk.
Jeong Joon-hyung!
Are you leaving?
Why don't you rest some more?
It's okay, I'm fine now.
You had a stomach cramp,
so I gave you a shot of painkillers.
Here's some antacid.
Remember to take it after eating.
Thank you.
Stomach cramps are usually caused by
excessive acid due to stress.
Are you stressed out these days?
Yes, a little.
Is it because of a man?
Who is he?
Who is the man that's making
such a beautiful woman sad?
You should dry your hair first.
It's all wet.
Whose fault is that?
Keep your mouth shut.
Give it to me. It'll take forever
to dry your hair like that.
Give it back.
Wait, I'll dry it for you.
Gosh.
Gosh, I'm sorry. Goodness.
Here, do whatever you want with it.
I never asked you to dry my hair,
you punk.
Seriously!
Hey.
Do you think Jae-yi noticed
that you like him?
No, I don't think he has any idea.
I don't want him to find out.
Men don't like women
who does weightlifting.
Look.
It's full of calluses.
Who would like hands like these?
What's wrong with that?
It's because you do weightlifting.
You can feel safe walking at night.
I'd be happy if I were him.
You're only good with words.
Anyhow, I had a good day.
Thanks to you, I went on
something similar to a date.
When Dr Jeong was driving me,
I felt like Cinderella riding
her pumpkin carriage.
And you know how
when the clock hits midnight,
she comes back to reality.
At least she ends up marrying the prince.
You're right.
I don't like watching movies
without a happy ending.
Did you know?
There's a toad in that fountain
that grants your wishes.
-What?
-You didn't know?
Are you sure you go to Haneol Sport
University? It's a famous legend.
You know all of our senior athletes
who won gold medal?
All of them won because of the toad.
You should work on your creativity.
I'm serious.
You may not know it,
but if you pray earnestly enough,
it grants your wish no matter what.
Why don't you pray to it...
for you and Jae-yi to work out?
You're full of lies.
Did you catch a cold?
My nose has been itching for a while.
I'm sorry,
but I have an important plan,
so I can't catch a cold. I'm leaving.
What are you doing?
I said I really can't catch a cold.
It'll last long.
My germs are very strong like me.
It's an awesome virus.
If I really catch a cold,
I'm going to...
return the virus
by kissing you if I have to.
Wait and see.
Wait for me, Joon-hyung.
Come on, be a loyal friend.
Joon-hyung, wait for me.
I must really have caught a cold.
It's so annoying.
Are you sick? You look so pale.
I'm okay.
I caught a cold myself.
Maybe today's our unlucky day.
Why won't this open?
Here, I'll do it for you.
-It's okay. I'll do it.
-Come on, give it to me.
I said I will...
I'm sorry for being too sensitive.
Even if Bok-ju moves up her weight class,
she'll do well.
Chang-geol, they want more radish.
What are you doing?
The chicken is getting burnt.
My gosh. Oh no!
It's all burnt. Oh no, what a waste.
Were you cooking or were you sleeping?
No.
I was lost in thoughts.
Focus on strengthening the torso
while keeping the same weight.
-Let's increase the number.
-Okay.
Should we increase
protein consumption as well?
Let Woon-gi decide that.
He can adjust it on his own.
I'm glad that Woon-gi decided to move up.
But Bok-ju doesn't seem probable, right?
I can't bring it up without
Mr Kim's permission.
It'll be hard for Bok-ju
to decide as well.
Hello.
You came all the way here.
Why didn't you call?
We could come to you.
I'm sure you know why I'm here.
Let's get down to it
since we're both busy.
Okay, I'm listening.
It's about what you mentioned last time.
Bok-ju's weight class.
What do you think is going on?
I have no idea.
I have a bad feeling about it.
I want to know.
I really want to know.
-It's driving me crazy.
-Stop it.
You're making it worse, so stop it.
Bok-ju, come out now.
Be quiet.
What?
Raise my weight class?
That's right.
I'm sure you're surprised.
Of course you would. I would be, too.
Head Coach and I believe...
that you have the potential.
Increasing your weight a few months
before the competition isn't normal,
but you're strong.
Off the records, you've tied with
the best record from the 63kg class.
That's when I was in my best condition.
You should make it so.
We'll make sure to help you.
As you know,
the competition for
the 58kg weight class is fierce.
In your weight class, the result of...
the competition changes drastically
depending on your condition.
Whereas for the 63kg class,
ever since Jang Ran-ran retired,
there's no one who stands out.
I'm not saying this to pressure you,
but if you go up to 63kg,
then the other girls
can try for a medal at 58kg.
That's right. It'll be
a win-win situation for everyone.
It'll benefit you and create
opportunities for the other members.
If you can gain 3 to 4kg,
it'll be totally possible.
Woon-gi is doing the same thing.
We're working on his program now.
If you can make up your mind,
we'll give you all the support you need.
But I have to talk to my dad first...
We already spoke to him.
He gave us the go-ahead today.
What?
My dad did?
How could you do this
without even talking to me?
You fool. It's not like
it was an easy decision for me.
I was tossing and turning all night
thinking about what to do.
But how can you make such an
important decision by yourself?
Do you think going up a weight class
is as easy as blowing a balloon?
Bulking up is a lot harder
than losing weight.
You know it, too!
I know. I'm aware of it,
but life is a challenge.
As a weightlifter, you have to keep
challenging yourself.
Head Coach Yoon is right.
This will put you at an advantage.
It's a pretty good strategy.
-Dad!
-I have to deep-fry chicken.
I'm behind on orders. I have to go.
-Let's talk later.
-Dad!
You always do whatever you want!
You even hung up on me!
Calm down, Bok-ju.
It will be difficult,
but it's not entirely impossible.
I agree. Gaining 3 to 4kg
isn't that difficult for you.
That's not the point. Geez,
this is seriously driving me crazy.
Why would you go crazy over this?
We'll help you.
Yes. As good friends,
we'll pig out with you.
That's not why I'm upset.
Why does it have to be now?
For goodness' sake.
Don't run! You'll lose weight.
Hey, Bok-ju. Wait up!
-Dad always does whatever he wants.
-Calm down.
What? You want to enter the match
hosted by Joongang Bank?
Why?
It's a small match
and won't be of much help to you.
Just as practice.
I see. You're right.
Getting as much practice as possible
will help you overcome the anxiety.
I think it's a good idea.
Use your guts that allowed you to
reject being Tae-hoon's partner...
to win a medal.
Everyone will badmouth Ronaldo
if he scores a goal in a minor game.
You're getting cheeky again.
All right. Do it.
Okay, thank you.
Geez, Kim Bok-ju.
That girl gave me her cold.
Why did she have to give me
her cold at a time like this?
Hey, Chubs!
Hey, how will you take
responsibility for this?
I caught a cold because of you!
I have a match next week.
How will you take responsibility?
Shut it. My head is already pounding.
Is something going on?
I don't know. Nothing is going my way.
You were happy yesterday. What happened?
-I have to move up a weight class.
-Weight class?
Wow, Bok-ju! You're finally
moving up to the heavyweight class?
But what is the problem?
Hey. Right now, I can't...
You know the bind I'm in right now.
I signed up at the clinic.
Hey, that's not really an issue.
You only go there to see Jae-yi.
Weight loss isn't your goal.
You should do what you have to
unless you quit weightlifting.
That's true, but...
Hey, you can talk easily
because it's not your problem.
Do you think all things
in life are that simple?
But then, you probably have no idea
how life really works.
You're from a good family,
you're a natural swimmer,
you're good-looking
and girls are all over you.
I was an idiot to expect advice from you.
I'm going, you stuck-up.
I should be the one getting mad at you!
How can you yell at me
after giving me your cold?
Weightlifting Department
"You should do what you have to."
He can say whatever because
it's not his problem. What a jerk.
That sly dabbler.
Bok-ju.
What's up? What brings you here?
What is it?
I left my practice journal here.
I see.
So have you given it some thought?
Pardon?
Oh, that?
You'll need to start the special
training now if you want to bulk up.
We've already come up with the plan.
I see.
Then...
I will... I'll give it a try.
Really?
You want to give it a try? Seriously?
Head Coach Yoon! Head Coach!
Bok-ju wants to give it a try.
She has made up her mind.
Is that right, Bok-ju? Are you serious?
You made the right decision.
As we told you the other day,
you can certainly do it.
Of course. Who would be able
to do it if Bok-ju can't?
Your dad will be
so thrilled to hear this.
-Then let's start today.
-All right.
-I'll train Woon-gi.
-Okay.
You should train Bok-ju, Coach Choi.
Gosh, I guess this will also be
a competition of sort between us.
Coach Choi, are you confident?
Of course. You know
how scary I can be as a coach.
You're scary indeed.
Bok-ju, you better watch out.
She might bite you.
One more round.
One more.
Coach Choi, I really can't eat anymore.
There was so much rice.
That's how much you usually eat.
You should go for another round.
It was going so well.
Why did you suddenly gain weight?
Doctor, it's because I haven't
been following the diet.
-The scale isn't broken.
-It's my fault.
It's all right. Your weight
can fluctuate at the beginning.
But I'll give you
two types of treatment today.
Lie down.
That's odd.
Your weight went up by 1kg yesterday.
Why did you lose 0.5kg?
Hey, Bok-ju.
Did you go...
to the bathroom a few times today?
Yes, I did.
We need to fix this.
Let's go fill you up again.
We're having an extra-large size
of bossam for a snack!
Bok-ju, you've got to try harder.
Woon-gi has already gained 1.6kg.
No, I still have a long way to go.
I have to increase my muscle mass.
Bok-ju will get there soon, too.
Bok-ju, eat the meat.
Gosh, your cold is lasting
for such a long time.
But then, you're practically living in
the pool to prepare for the match.
Of course the cold won't go away.
-You can't even take any medicine.
-By the way,
why are you entering that match?
Isn't that match for swimmers
who are just starting out?
You idiots.
Only the incompetent would
fuss about things like that.
Learn from us, you fools.
When I was a freshman,
I was not like you guys...
Shut it and just eat your food.
-You guys are done, right?
-Yes.
-We're going first.
-I'm not done yet.
-I'm not done. I'm still eating.
-Come on.
Do you have a match coming up?
It looks like you have a cold.
Will you be okay?
You usually get
the stubborn kind of cold.
You're really unbelievable.
You're acting like a stalker.
Is this fun for you?
How could it be fun?
It's exhausting and embarrassing,
and my pride is crushed.
But I'm really desperate right now.
You're the only thing I can hold on to.
That's just in your head.
I'm not that person for you.
I'm just myself.
Okay.
I'll leave you alone,
so finish your food.
You can't even take medicine,
so you have to eat well.
It looks like Joon-hyung keeps
rejecting you.
Isn't it too demeaning?
You're the most beautiful girl
in our campus.
Did you keep rejecting me for this?
You can always come to me.
I'll treat you better than Joon-hyung.
Get lost, you jerk.
No, no.
-I'll never finish this. No.
-Let me go.
No, no!
Why can't you eat it?
Just have some drumsticks...
and drink the broth. It's not that much.
You must be sick of fried chicken.
That's why I boiled the chicken
with ginseng and abalone.
I already had three plates of food
for lunch today.
I can only eat so much. I can't keep
shoving food down my throat.
-My gosh, you seriously...
-Pick it up! Just wait.
Bok-ju, I know it's hard,
but you should try your best.
I really think you have a shot
at winning. I can feel it.
That doesn't matter.
I'm saying I'm not confident!
Gosh, just eat it.
My arms are about to fall off.
Then put it on your head!
Or put it on your back!
-Just be quiet, you punk.
-I can't put this on my back.
-Hello, Mr Kim.
-Hi, Coach Choi.
You didn't have to go through
the trouble of making this.
I bought some pizza for Bok-ju as well.
Is that so? Shall we go inside?
-Let me carry it.
-No, it's fine.
Lifting things is what I do. Let's go.
Let's eat, Bok-ju.
-Let me carry it.
-It's okay.
-I can't eat anymore.
-Hurry up.
Bok-ju's dad makes
the most delicious food.
He is a master.
-This is perfectly seasoned.
-I know.
By the way, we can eat
as much food as we want...
with people's support.
-Weightlifting isn't so bad, right?
-That's right.
I pity those gymnasts for eating
like a bird every day to lose weight.
Eat up. Why are you picking at
the food? This is all for you.
She's right. Have some pizza.
Should I pick some drumsticks?
You like them.
You even wished chickens had four feet.
I'm already sick of chicken.
I'll soon shed chicken broth
instead of tears.
I'm actually full.
We might all end up
in the open-weight class.
Don't be so weak and give up.
We big eaters always have
our friend, soft drinks.
Help us, dear soft drinks!
Gosh. I have some coins. I'll get them.
Goodness.
One New Message
Hey, don't exert yourself.
You'll lose weight. I'll do it for you.
Let me.
"Ms Kim Bok-ju, your session is at
4:30 p.m. tomorrow. J Weight Clinic."
Your session is at 4:30 p.m.
at J Weight...
Hey, why would you go to a weight clinic?
Nan-hee, let me explain.
-Nan-hee, listen to me.
-What...
Hey! Why would you go
to a weight clinic...
when you're raising your weight class?
What on earth are you up to these days?
Nan-hee.
How could that be?
Great work today.
-So you like that guy?
-You, too. See you tomorrow.
Not Joon-hyung?
Yes.
And he is Joon-hyung's older brother?
And you wanted...
to see him at any cost...
that you signed up to get
expensive treatments.
You lied to us to keep going there...
and even lifted the rice bags for
Joon-hyung to keep him quiet.
Did I get all that right?
-Yes.
-You crazy girl!
I know. I deserve that. I am crazy.
No one in their right mind would do this.
I tried hard not to do it,
but he kept popping up in my head
that I started seeing things.
I really couldn't help it.
I just wanted to see his face.
That's all I wanted.
I get it.
He's way better than Joon-hyung
after all.
He's so manly. He looked very sturdy.
-Right? Isn't he handsome?
-Yes, he is.
He's cute. Besides, he's a doctor.
You're so sly.
You pretended you weren't
interested in men at all.
You have such a great taste in men.
By the way, how did you guys meet?
It wouldn't be like in the movie...
where he shared his umbrella
on a rainy day, would it?
He did.
Oh, my. Really?
Did he really do that?
My goodness. He makes my heart flutter.
-He's great and handsome, right?
-I want someone like him, too.
-He's mine.
-Is he? I'm so jealous.
Si-ho, it's ginger extract.
Eat it when you have a cold. Mum
Hey, what are you doing? Get some rest.
You have a match tomorrow,
but you're still sick.
-You should save your energy.
-I need to watch this.
Watching it won't help you. Get a rest.
Sweet dreams.
Fine. Gosh.
Stop nagging me. You're not my mum.
Stop complaining. Just go to sleep.
This is Si-ho.
Can you come out for a bit?
Don't tell Joon-hyung.
I'm sorry.
You must be surprised
when I suddenly called you out.
Here.
What is this?
It's dates and ginger tea.
Joon-hyung has a match tomorrow.
He won't drink it if I give it to him.
Hey.
What's that?
It's my sincere love for you.
Is this ginger tea?
Don't ask any questions
and just drink it up.
Think of it as medicine.
It's good.
I feel better now.
You do? That's good to hear.
You punk. This is why you should
play nice and not be so cold.
I mean, it's because your body
and heart are cold...
that you caught a cold.
That's what I wanted to say.
Hey, I need to go to the bathroom.
I have to go.
I'll be in the bathroom.
Finish it before I get back.
What is he saying?
Do you know how sexy his voice is?
It's not too high or too low.
It sounds so sweet.
It must sound like the prince's voice
that Sleeping Beauty heard...
when she woke up from her sleep.
Gosh, really?
I saw his face but didn't hear his voice.
When he smiles,
the corners of his eyes
would wrinkle a bit...
and he'd show a bit of his white teeth.
It makes my heart flutter.
It was enchanting.
He just melts my heart.
Let me tell you the biggest reason
why I fell for him.
This is really important.
It's...
his gentle heart.
I've never seen such a gentleman.
He's not pretentious at all.
It's his natural personality.
When I'm with him,
I feel like I'm a very beautiful woman.
I've never been treated like that,
so I don't know how that feels.
Anyway, he's fantastic.
He's sweet, gentle and reliable.
I can't believe Joon-hyung is
his brother. He's just so mature.
Hey. Listening to you
makes me want to meet him.
Why?
You're not going to make us
fight over a guy, right?
I'm a bit worried that you will.
You flirt with every guy.
No matter how desperate I am,
I won't try to steal your man.
My man?
-Oh, my.
-Bok-ju, gosh.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
We used the toilet, of course.
We were about to leave. Let's go.
Were you two...
badmouthing me?
How can you do that?
You even disappeared without me.
Don't be absurd.
We don't have anything bad
to say about you.
Of course. Don't be silly.
Let's just go out.
Why did you take only one Hamburg steak?
You should eat a lot to put on weight.
Here, take mine.
Thank you, Seon-ok.
Seon-ok, can you get me some water?
The food got stuck in my throat.
Here's your water.
Gosh, eat slowly.
It finally went down.
Wow, you're eating well today.
Here you go.
Have another.
-Are you leaving now?
-Yes, my appointment is at 6 p.m.
Is that what you're going to wear?
-Are you serious?
-Why? Do I look bad?
Yes, you do.
6 p.m., is it? Give me just 5 minutes.
Okay.
I did my best.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Are you really going?
Yes.
Fine. Let me take a look at you.
Since you're going, do a good job.
I know. Go back inside already.
I should go with you because you're sick.
It's unfortunate that I have training.
You should work harder.
You don't swim as well as I do.
You're so cruel.
Fine, you punk.
I get what you mean. Just go.
You better win first place, okay?
Did I upset you? You're so cute.
See you.
Good luck.
Focus on the start.
It's grilled abalone this time?
We had abalone chicken soup last time.
That was regular abalone
I bought at the market.
This time, the abalone is from Wando.
Just for you,
I called my friend whom
I haven't talked to in 10 years.
Please try to come
by the restaurant later.
Don't bring your friends today.
There isn't enough.
I could only get 30 abalone.
Okay, I'll talk to you later.
Where are you going?
-Are you going to the clinic?
-Why do you even ask?
I'm on my way to a competition,
so send me some good energy.
You already know you will be fine.
I don't wish you luck.
I hope you make a mistake.
Gosh, she's so mean.
I'm so nervous, but she tries
to put a curse on me instead.
You wait and see.
Hey, I'm going to get you!
What a jerk.
J Weight Clinic
Your weight increased again.
Why can't you look me in the eyes?
I'm sorry for
disappointing you, Dr Jeong.
You don't need to apologise to me.
This is all for your sake.
It isn't easy to follow
the diet plan, is it?
People around you
probably don't help either.
-Right.
-Evenings are the most difficult.
Unfortunately, socialising in Korea
takes place in the late evening.
Some patients say they want to
move to a deserted island.
I know. I can't stop
my contact with friends.
Let's try harder to lose your weight.
Please get changed for the treatment.
Okay.
Joon-hyung has a competition today.
I sent him a message to wish him luck.
He hasn't replied. He must be busy.
He'll do well. He's confident after all.
He may look it,
but he's quite tender-hearted.
It's an important competition for him.
Two years ago, he made a mistake
at the start and was disqualified.
His records from training are
good enough for the national team.
But ever since then, he always made
false starts in important competitions.
I think Joon-hyung is traumatised
by the first mistake he made.
What was that?
He always pretends to be strong.
I had no idea.
I gave him a cold
and wished him bad luck.
Geez, me and my careless mouth.
If Joon-hyung doesn't do well,
he'll blame me. I hope he'll do well.
Also... Was it his trauma?
I hope he overcomes it
so that he can do his best.
Please.
Good luck! You can do it,
Jeong Joon-hyung!
Joongang Bank Swim Competition
When you have the symptom,
not focusing on the symptom
is most effective way to overcome it.
When you start to feel nervous,
try to think of something else.
For example, focus on your breathing.
It's also effective to
count down the numbers.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Soon...
-Three. Two.
-Joongang Bank Swim Competition...
One.
Please, Joon-hyung.
Take your mark.
Five, four, three,
two...
First place goes to Lee Sang-young
from Dongha University.
Second place goes to Choi Jae-hyung
from Minju City Hall.
Third place goes to Park Jun
from Kyungjin Sport University.
Fourth place goes to Jeong Joon-hyung
from Haneol Sport University.
Results of Joongang Bank
Swim Competition
He didn't make it to the top three.
Why didn't he do better?
Did he get disqualified again? That jerk.
Joon-hyung, are you okay? Stay strong.
Joon-hyung, it serves you right.
Geez, what should I write him?
I can't send him a sweet message.
Drink it up. Don't leave a drop.
Go on.
Finish it.
Good.
Gosh, if I hadn't caught this cold,
I totally would've won the first place.
Why am I so unlucky?
You should've visited us
before the match.
Your mum could easily make you
medicine with special ingredients...
that comply with the doping test.
I should have.
I must be getting punished
for looking down on the match.
Gosh, stop it. It's completely fine.
You said it's not an important match.
Just forget about it.
-Did you talk to Jae-yi?
-Yes, I did.
His nagging is driving me crazy.
He's acting just like you.
All he does is worry about me.
Where are you?
-It's Chubs.
-Chubs?
Who is Chubs?
A friend of mine who is really funny.
Chubs sounds like the name of a dog.
What's up, Chubs? You've never texted me.
I asked you where you are.
I'm home.
I'll head back to school now.
He'll be back soon, then.
What's with this girl asking me
to come to this fountain?
Quack, quack.
Quack, quack, quack.
-Quack, quack, quack...
-What's going on, Bok-ju?
-What's that?
-Here. It's a toad.
I didn't make it because
you talked about it.
I was bored and happened to have
a few pieces of paper lying around.
Who knows? It may be your lucky charm.
You're obviously not crafty at all.
Look how it's all wrinkled up.
How many times did you
undo and redo this?
Hey, give it back, then!
You can't take it back.
It's mine now. We'll see
whether it'll bring me luck or not.
Awesome toad.
-You copycat.
-What's wrong with it?
You and your friends say it all the time.
"Awesome."
It sounds different when I say it, right?
It probably sounds way cooler.
What? You must feel better now to be
cracking a joke. Is your cold gone?
It's better.
It'll go away soon.
I took some medicine at home earlier.
I'm sorry for being harsh on you earlier.
I'm on edge these days.
Hey. You should've done
a better job, though.
I know.
I guess I was too full of myself.
Don't worry, though. I'm going
to surprise everyone very soon.
You better not beg me for
100 autographs when that happens.
I'll be at the Olympics by then.
You wish.
Let's go.
We have time until the roll call.
I'll treat you to something good.
Seriously?
-What are you treating me to?
-Something that will energise you.
Shut your mouth and just follow me.
Why are you heading to the campus?
Gosh, just a moment.
-Do you want to ride this?
-Yes!
-I want to...
-No! Not there!
I was bedridden for three days after
giving you a ride the other day.
-No way.
-Do you want to die?
Geez, I said no.
Goodness. I won't go, then.
Joon-hyung, come on. Let's go!
I'm treating you for goodness' sake.
You can't even do this for me?
Joon-hyung, get on your bike. Hey!
-The number you're calling...
-Jeong Joon-hyung!
You're seriously a piece of work.
You said you wanted to ride it.
Hey! I'm going to throw this out.
Gosh, seriously.
-Who is he?
-Say hello. This is my dad.
Hello.
-This is...
-Oh, the kid with the tab!
Yes, that's right.
-Do you know him, Dad?
-The other day...
I've been here once before
with my friends.
I didn't know it was your dad's.
What exactly is your relationship?
Bok-ju has never
brought a boy here before.
This is very interesting.
We went to the same elementary school.
He's in the swimming team.
I owe him a lot,
so I want to do something for him.
We have a lot of abalone, right?
-What?
-Abalone.
What do you mean?
Wild abalone.
You said we have wild abalone from Wando.
We have a lot, right?
I didn't know that you and Bok-ju
went to the same elementary school.
-Eat up.
-Thank you.
-This abalone is very rare.
-I see.
Hey, eat up.
No, you eat. I don't have much appetite.
Just eat!
I can't stand the feeling
of being indebted.
Eat up so that
you can fight off your cold.
-Dad.
-Yes?
Oh, sorry. Make yourself at home.
I hope you enjoy it.
Is it good?
My goodness.
-Gosh, I can't believe that I'm...
-Eat up.
Seeing Bok-ju with a boy right now.
Doesn't it feel weird, Chang-geol?
Goodness, getting
those wild abalone was so hard.
I can't believe
that weasel is eating all of them.
Why are you calling him a weasel?
He's too handsome to be called that.
To be honest, in terms of looks,
-Bok-ju isn't good enough for him.
-Just eat.
See? She likes him more.
Are you blind?
-What's wrong with my Bok-ju?
-My vision is perfectly fine.
It's 1.0 on both eyes.
-It can't get any better.
-Shut it, you fool.
Anyway, I don't like that guy.
I saw him...
giving Bok-ju naughty looks.
Who?
That guy?
In my opinion, he's in more danger.
One glance and I can tell
that Bok-ju likes him more.
What are you talking about?
She said they're just friends.
Then why is she
giving him all the abalone?
She's not the type
to share food with other people.
It shows that she's
head over heels for him.
Hey, where are we going?
Gosh, just follow me quietly.
It's so beautiful.
Isn't my neighbourhood beautiful?
It's very pretty up here at night.
Everything sparkles.
Yes.
It's pretty.
By the way, your trauma...
What caused it?
What?
I heard from Dr Jeong.
Is it caused by pre-match anxiety?
I'm not sure.
How did you get into swimming?
Did your parents tell you to do it?
No. I just liked water.
I first learned swimming when
I followed Jae-yi to a pool as a kid.
Water comforted me so much.
It felt warm as if it was embracing me.
Oh, you have quite the sensitive soul.
Did your personality change
after you started swimming?
Maybe.
I think so.
It did. You're right.
That's how I got into swimming,
but now that I'm majoring in it,
it has become quite stressful.
I can't help but obsess over my records.
I feel like a bull going on a bullfight.
I know.
"Don't worry about your ranking
and just lift weights."
I'd have so much fun
if that's really the case.
Gosh, I hate that I have to be ranked!
But you know what?
Like it or not,
it's our fate as athletes.
We have to accept it.
Hey.
Cheer up.
I'm a good judge of character,
and I know you'll achieve your goal.
I see something intense in your eyes.
Are you falling into my eyes?
Yes, I totally am.
It's so beautiful!
We can't come here when it's colder.
Gosh, Bok-ju must be so full by now.
I know.
Her dad called her, so he'd be
feeding her chicken soup.
Watching Bok-ju makes me realise...
-gaining weight is hard.
-Of course.
Raising weight class is much harder.
And Bok-ju is working so hard
to put on weight.
Name, Kim Bok-ju
Current weight, 57.39kg
Right now, I feel like
I won't get sick for one whole year.
Now I know why people are so eager
to eat wild abalone.
-Did it give you some energy?
-Yes.
I can feel my energy surging up.
Your dad's food is
what made you so strong.
Now that we ate it together,
let's work hard.
It's not like athletes...
get better overnight.
You should have good physical strength
to win the war of nerves.
By the way, how long
are you going to live a double life?
I know.
I should put an end to it soon.
Look, there's a toad!
-Do you want me to punch you?
-I'm serious. The toad was this big.
Hey! There it is!
Cut it out. You just like to tease me.
You better watch out
if you want to live. Okay?
Gosh, why won't you believe me?
There really was a toad this big.
Awesome.
What was that? That's not how you say it.
-Awesome.
This is how you say it. Try again.
Stop laughing and do it again.
You're back. You must be tired.
I cleaned your desk and bed.
Okay. Thank you.
Joon-hyung.
You're okay, right?
It wasn't a major competition.
You'll do better next time.
I didn't say anything. I'm fine.
At least I wasn't disqualified today.
That's right.
I knew you were broad-minded.
She's surprisingly cute.
Weightlifting Team
You should stick more meatballs into
the chopstick. Two aren't enough.
Bok-ju, do you want more?
I got many of them.
No, just leave them there.
I'll eat them later. Thank you.
Okay.
By the way,
why isn't Coach Choi here today?
She'd stand next to Bok-ju
during breakfast and lunch,
and shout, "Have one more plate!"
Maybe she's just sleeping in.
Hurry. We'll be late for class.
Dad
Yes, what now, Dad?
Did you make beef bone soup this time?
Be quiet and come home right now.
Dad, why did you call me here so early?
What brings both of you here?
What is this?
Tell me what it is, you brat!
Weightlifting Fairy
Get over here!
You went to a weight clinic.
Do you now see food as poison now?
Can't you see me, Bok-ju?
Is Bok-ju home?
There you are, Bok-ju!
Weightlifting Fairy, Kim Bok-ju!
I had fun today thanks to you.
-Weightlifters can date, too.
-Coach.
This is my second gift.
Today is Jae-yi's birthday.
I'm Kim Bok-ju, a sophomore
at Haneol Sport University.
I like you, Dr Jeong.
Weightlifting Fairy