♪The wind blows, but I don't see you♪
♪I added a few more strokes♪
♪To the ending♪
♪With the flowers falling
and the time passing♪
♪Leaving only memories behind♪
♪The wind blows from a long distance♪
♪Yet, you didn't show up♪
♪This love is full of regrets♪
♪You are but a dream
in this fleeting life♪
[Part For Ever]
[Adapted from the novel by Jing Mo,]
[My Lord,
Madam Doesn't Want to See You Again]
[Episode 16]
[City Lord's Mansion]
Sinner Niyue,
with a heart as venomous as a snake,
repeatedly framed Su Wan'er,
concealed the virginity mark,
and deceived His Lordship.
The lighter punishment
is banishment from Canglong City,
and the heavier punishment is execution.
Please make a decision, My Lord.
Miss Wan'er,
please save me.
I know I deserve to die,
and I am not worthy of pity.
I shouldn't have taken your place
and stayed by Ling's side,
and I shouldn't have...
I shouldn't have pretended
to have slept with him.
It's all my fault.
That day,
you left behind
the rabbit pendant in despair.
I'm returning it
to its rightful owner now.
I will leave Canglong City immediately.
Please spare my life.
♪People sit silently by candlelight
as night begins♪
♪A play of sorrows and joys,
your role, my outline♪
♪Though the dream is over,
the feelings are hard to let go♪
♪Everyone is filled
with sorrow and pity♪
♪Alas, the mortal world
has too many spectators♪
♪You turn back to ascend
the stage wearing a green robe♪
♪A song asking about heart matters,
but who will answer?♪
♪An old dream with infatuation
and resentment and complications♪
♪You sing for me♪
♪In the play,
telling of separations and reunions♪
Wan'er,
do you still remember
the fireflies we saw
in the cave back then?
That day also felt
as surreal as today.
On that day,
we both talked about the past,
but we didn't realize
that we were
the most important people to each other.
Fortunately,
after all these years,
fate has brought us
back together again.
Actually, I...
You go first.
Wan'er,
I want
to apologize to you.
I've done
a lot of things to hurt you
and said many things I didn't mean.
I misjudged people,
causing us to miss out
on so many years.
Wan'er,
I've made you sad and upset.
I'm sorry.
I didn't believe you,
and ended up causing
a lot of misunderstandings.
I'm also at fault.
Stop.
I've already apologized verbally.
Now,
you can only express your apology
through actions.
Like what actions?
Like...
♪I'm afraid the characters
in the play aren't us♪
Do you like my actions?
♪The lush and fragrant grass
made longing hard to endure♪
♪Can I entrust my heart to you?♪
♪This love is hard to fade away
as it twists and turns endlessly♪
♪On the path of emotions♪
♪Reflected in a mirror
by moonlight through a window♪
♪How much is your affection?♪
♪When the time to love is not right,
worldly matters make it hard to endure♪
♪Amid all worldly matters,
I only devote to one person♪
♪Love is silent, but it leaves traces
as deep as the sea♪
♪I accompany you
for a part of the journey♪
♪Our longing for each other
guides us through countless lives♪
♪The flowers of the entire city
blossom for a person♪
♪Let's spend
the rest of our lives together♪
Wan'er,
take care of yourself.
I apologize to you on his behalf.
I only want him to treat you well.
As for the rest, it's all in the past.
Your ten minutes
are up.
Ling Xiao,
you better treat Wan'er well.
If she suffers even a little,
I won't let you off.
From now on,
your breath should only have me in it.
When you open your eyes,
you should only see me.
You too.
Naturally.
Now that
Jing Tian has returned to Baiyu City
to inherit the position of City Lord,
and Niyue has been sent away by me.
There will be
no one standing between us anymore.
I have prepared a surprise for you.
Where are you taking me?
It smells so nice.
It's the scent of flowers.
Do you like it?
Such a beautiful flower garden.
It may be beautiful here,
but it's not half
as beautiful as you.
You once said that you wanted
to play the Guqin, wield the sword
and admire the flowers
with the young man in your heart.
Now,
shall we realize your wishes together?
With the heaven and earth,
the sun and moon as witnesses,
I, Ling Xiao, swear
to love only Su Wan'er
in this lifetime.
My heart belongs solely
to Wan'er for eternity.
Even if the time
we have together is fleeting like flowers,
my love for Wan'er
will endure endlessly.
And I you.
♪When the time to love is not right,
worldly matters make it hard to endure♪
♪Amid all worldly matters,
I only devote to one person♪
♪Love is silent, but it leaves traces
as deep as the sea♪
♪I accompany you
for a part of the journey♪
♪Our longing for each other
guides us through countless lives♪
♪The flowers of the entire city
blossom for a person♪
♪Let's spend
the rest of our lives together♪
♪My dream is rising
in my heart like a spiral♪
♪The fate of our meeting
has been decided♪
Once,
I had an unforgettable encounter
with a young man.
For a moment,
I imagined brewing tea, making wine,
playing the Guqin, wielding the sword,
and admiring the flowers
together with him.
Unexpectedly,
everything I longed for back then,
he has now helped me realize one by one.
The man before me is
the joy of my youth
and will be
my lifelong partner.
♪Amid all worldly matters,
I only devote to one person♪
♪Love is silent, but it leaves traces
as deep as the sea♪
How come there are
so many peach blossoms here,
and even tall lotus leaves?
I had someone to irrigate them
with hot spring water.
So that this garden
would bloom for you.
♪Let's spend
the rest of our lives together♪
♪White dew penetrates the sandalwood♪
♪Heading to the garden alone♪
♪The Guqin is playing among the trees♪
♪And the cicadas chirp
deep in the bamboo courtyard♪
♪A person inside a door♪
♪As we see the falling leaves♪
♪Threads of memories surround us♪
♪They become a cocoon to wrap around us♪
♪Putting on makeup as the bright moon
scattered its light on the sky♪
♪Like white frost♪
♪I look afar as my thoughts fly past
like white snow♪
♪Looking through the window, the letter
I wrote is short, yet my love persists♪
♪Thinking of you
dancing in colorful clothes♪
♪Sending it to the distant place
where I long to go but cannot reach♪
♪I was a youth when I started writing♪
♪Falling in love,
there are too many deep memories♪
♪When I stopped writing,
I was the only one aware♪
♪Of my purpose in this life,
and fate is not true♪