♪The wind blows, but I don't see you♪
♪I added a few more strokes♪
♪To the ending♪
♪With the flowers falling
and the time passing♪
♪Leaving only memories behind♪
♪The wind blows from a long distance♪
♪Yet, you didn't show up♪
♪This love is full of regrets♪
♪You are but a dream
in this fleeting life♪
[Part For Ever]
[Adapted from the novel by Jing Mo,]
[My Lord,
Madam Doesn't Want to See You Again]
[Episode 26]
I only wish for the safety
health and longevity of my family
without disasters or hardships.
I wish that Su Wan'er
and I will be together
for lifetimes,
never to be separated.
What if Bodhisattva let me
reincarnate as a man in my next life?
Then I'll ask Bodhisattva
to let me be reborn as a woman.
I will marry you as your wife.
But what if we're born in
different places
in the next life,
never to meet again?
Then I won't drink
the soup of forgetfulness.
Even if we're separated
by thousands of miles,
I'll find you.
What if I become
a rogue in the next life,
fleeing to the ends of the earth?
You won't be able to chase me.
Then I'll become a constable.
No matter where you flee,
I'll hunt you down.
You are speaking nonsense
before Bodhisattva.
You deserve a beating.
♪The lush and fragrant grass
made longing hard to endure♪
♪Can I entrust my heart to you?♪
♪This love is hard to fade away
as it twists and turns endlessly♪
♪On the path of emotions♪
♪Reflected in a mirror
by moonlight through a window♪
♪How much is your affection?♪
♪When the time to love is not right,
worldly matters make it hard to endure♪
♪Amid all worldly matters,
I only devote to one person♪
♪Love is silent, but it leaves traces
as deep as the sea ♪
♪I accompany you
for a part of the journey♪
♪Our longing for each other
guides us through countless lives♪
♪The flowers of the entire city
blossom for a person♪
♪Let's spend
the rest of our lives together♪
♪My dream is rising
in my heart like a spiral♪
♪The fate of our meeting
has been decided♪
♪Your smile under the lantern♪
♪Stirs up my thoughts like crazy♪
♪The moonlight is dancing
and the fireflies are twinkling♪
♪No one knows
how deep my love is for you♪
♪When you respond,
all is well in this world♪
This place is so beautiful.
Do you have any other wishes?
The thing I want most
is already in my arms.
You miss Fu Bao, don't you?
He's arriving tomorrow morning.
How do you know what's on my mind?
My eyes have never left you.
I know everything
that's in your heart.
I never imagined
we could be so happy like this.
Up until now,
it all feels like a dream.
Silly,
I'm right here in front of you.
You're by my side too.
From now on,
every day will be a good day.
You'll focus on being a good city lord,
and I'll take care of our family
and raise the children.
I don't seek glory or fame,
just the happiness
and health of our family.
And we can be together forever.
All right, I promise you.
I'll listen to you in everything.
♪In the play,
telling of separations and reunions♪
By the way,
when Fu Bao comes here,
there's something I want to tell you.
Don't worry,
I'll get along with Fu Bao just fine.
It's not about that.
Do you
have any secrets?
Tell me now.
♪Aren't the characters
in the play you and me?♪
My Lady,
His Lordship has gone out
to pick up the young master.
He specifically asked me
to tell you to rest a little longer.
I'm well-rested.
Once the rain stops,
I'll go to the gate to greet them.
Yes, My Lady.
[City Lord's Mansion]
I've been asked
to deliver a letter to you.
[To Su Wan'er]
Fu Bao.
Today is the first day
of our family of three being together.
We should celebrate properly.
I bought your favorite pastries
from Qinghe Restaurant.
By the way,
Ling Xiao,
I heard some rumors today.
What rumors?
I heard that there's
something mysterious in the world
that can control people's minds.
Without lifting a finger,
it can make others commit suicide.
You're knowledgeable,
do you know what this thing is?
Such nonsense rumors,
only you would believe in them.
I received this today.
[To Su Wan'er]
What's wrong?
Niyue is still the same.
Cunning and sowing discord.
Let's not let her
ruin our mood today.
Come, try this.
♪People sit silently
by candlelight as night begins♪
♪A play of sorrows and joys,
your role, my outline♪
♪Though the dream is over,
the feelings are hard to let go♪
♪Everyone is filled
with sorrow and pity♪
♪Alas, the mortal world
has too many spectators♪
♪You turn back to ascend
the stage wearing a green robe♪
♪A song asking about heart matters,
but who will answer?♪
♪An old dream with infatuation
and resentment and complications♪
♪You sing for me♪
♪In the play,
telling of separations and reunions♪
♪Pear blossoms fall
and flowing sleeves feel like yesterday♪
♪The heart is closed,
unable to gaze at the emotional eyes♪
♪This life is filled
with too much affection♪
♪Amid the applause,
who can see through it?♪