♪The wind blows, but I don't see you♪
♪I added a few more strokes♪
♪To the ending♪
♪With the flowers falling
and the time passing♪
♪Leaving only memories behind♪
♪The wind blows from a long distance♪
♪Yet, you didn't show up♪
♪This love is full of regrets♪
♪You are but a dream
in this fleeting life♪
[Part Forever]
[Adapted from the novel by Jing Mo,]
[My Lord,
Madam Doesn't Want to See You Again]
[Episode 8]
What are you doing here?
I wanted to clean the room.
I didn't expect the room
of the Lord of the City
to be this dusty.
You are overly proactive.
Suspicious.
You can think however you like.
I'm not feeling well.
I'll take my leave.
Not these.
What is that incense?
Hidden so secretly.
There must be a mystery behind it.
[Thousand Gold Formula]
[Orchid, bluish-purple.]
[After being ground and dried, it could
be made into a hallucination trigger.]
Weren't you unwell?
I have a headache.
I'm here to find a cure for my headache.
This is Niyue's pharmacy
and book.
Taking without asking
is considered stealing.
This is my own business.
I'll explain it to her.
I don't think you are sick.
I think you are feeling guilty.
You are the one frowning
when you see me.
Are you conscience-stricken?
That's because I get upset
whenever I see you.
You are also an eyesore to me.
[Thousand Gold Formula]
[Orchid, bluish-purple.]
[After being ground and dried, it could
be made into a hallucination trigger.]
He actually burned the book.
Is he hiding a secret?
I can't let it go.
I have to think of a way
to try this incense.
♪The lush and fragrant grass
made longing hard to endure♪
Get out.
♪This love is hard to fade away
as it twists and turns endlessly♪
I smelled the fragrance of this incense
during the birthday banquet.
Then my father committed suicide.
He and I both smelled
the fragrance just now,
but nothing unusual happened to us.
Maybe my father's death
has nothing to do with the incense?
But even so,
why did he hide the incense
in a secret place?
And why did he burn that book secretly?
Dry these herbs and
grind them into powder.
A sachet made from these herbs
can cool the body, relieve pain,
and is a cure for colds.
This is my exclusive secret recipe.
Ling has always liked it.
Yes.
Maybe the incense was made
specially for him by Niyue.
It's unique.
That's why he cherishes it so much.
Mr. Zhao, leads are lost.
There is no evidence
connecting Ling Xiao
and my father's death.
[Bianque Hall]
What's going on?
What's going on here?
Canglong City has always
had good weather and fortune.
When did this kind of thing ever happen?
It's a disaster from heaven!
No one can escape this!
City Lord.
There are already rumors going around
saying that it's divine punishment.
What should we do about this?
I don't believe in any kind
of divine punishment.
Hanfeng,
send someone quickly to trace
the source.
Then send the shadow guards to build
a shelter in the mansion.
Move all of the sick
to the shelter,
and summon the physicians
to discuss a strategy.
We must prevent the contagion
and appease the residents.
Yes.
You broke
this pinwheel of blessing.
You should rely on your own strength
instead of these things.
Remember,
although you are a girl,
you are not worse than boys.
You can also rely on yourself
to protect your family.
♪I foolishly think♪
♪Unable to sleep, I was intoxicated
by the fragrance of books♪
♪With you, the fragrance fills
the sky together♪
Come.
Your Lordship, here.
Drink some water.
The people of Canglong City
are truly blessed
to have a good Lord like you.
Let's go
and have a look at the apothecary.
Yes.
- Your Lordship.
[City Lord's Mansion]
This…
Look at the situation of His Lordship,
could it be true as the rumors say?
Could it be a divine disaster?
Stop talking nonsense.
Hanfeng acted according
to His Lordship's instructions.
Please ask a famous physician
to come quickly and discuss the solution.
Yes.
Observing his pulse,
Ling was poisoned.
It's not fatal.
If this is the rumored disaster
from heaven,
shall I count it a blessing
from the heavens?
♪The weathered years,
the yellow old marks♪
♪Memories of a lifetime
in the past dreams♪
♪The residual snow,
the shining stars, the hazy moon♪
♪Strong liquor cannot dispel
the melancholy of love♪
♪The green mountains form a line
and the river reflects the moon♪
♪Time flies like an arrow,
what day is today?♪
♪Spring returns with warmth again,
and birds are everywhere♪
♪This love
only awaits your reciprocation♪
♪Who will hold my hand now?
Your beautiful smile can make me drunk♪
♪A song of love,
hatred, love and romance♪