♪The wind blows, but I don't see you♪
♪I added a few more strokes♪
♪To the ending♪
♪With the flowers falling
and the time passing♪
♪Leaving only memories behind♪
♪The wind blows from a long distance♪
♪Yet, you didn't show up♪
♪This love is full of regrets♪
♪You are but a dream
in this fleeting life♪
[Part For Ever]
[Adapted from the novel by Jing Mo,]
[My Lord, Madam Doesn't
Want to See You Again]
[Episode 15]
Ling Xiao,
I care.
I've been searching for that young man.
Are you satisfied with my answer now?
♪The mountains and rivers
I've seen are painted on the fan♪
♪The flowing clouds
embrace the wind and moon♪
♪Longing immersed in the inkstone♪
♪I foolishly think♪
[Tomb of Su Junqian, Lord
of Canglong City, Daughter, Su Wan'er]
Father,
I thought he was my enemy,
but I never expected
he was the young man I met before.
Although we've recognized each other,
what's happened has happened.
Why must the fate play
such a trick on us?
Today is Mr. Su's
100th day death anniversary.
I know
you'd come here to pay respects.
Jing Tian,
thank you for remembering.
Wan'er,
we went to school together
when we were children.
Back then,
when I skipped class,
you covered for me.
When I was punished,
you snuck food to me at night.
When my grades were poor,
you tutored me daily.
It was then when I secretly vowed
to protect you for a lifetime,
and made it my primary goal in life.
Wan'er, can we still
watch the sunrise and sunset together
as we did in our childhood?
Jing Tian,
we've been like siblings
and friends
since we were little.
The so-called engagement
is just a joke among our parents.
You know there's always been
someone else in my heart.
But he...
Regardless of what's between him and me,
There is no room
in my heart for anyone else.
But I can't just leave you like this.
Wan'er,
you don't have
to reciprocate my feelings,
nor do you have to worry about me.
But this isn't fair to you.
Jing Tian,
why won't you forget me?
Wan'er,
if you can't convince yourself,
how can you
convince me to change my mind?
The Shadow Guards have located
Wang Zhen.
Keep a close watch on him.
- Congratulations, My Lord.
- My Lord.
Ling,
I've prepared a banquet to celebrate
your hundredth day as the City Lord.
I dare not ask for your forgiveness.
I only hope to see you smile.
It's unnecessary.
Cancel the banquet.
Let's go.
Ling Xiao,
are you doing this on purpose?
You know today is
the 100th day death anniversary
for the former City Lord.
Ling Xiao,
is this what you want?
What do you think?
Lord Ling, you've always
been self-righteous.
You never show consideration
for others' feelings.
You've been together all the time,
and behaved intimately.
Have you considered his feelings then?
You...
Wan'er, let's not bother with them.
Let's go.
Stop.
I forbid you to leave with him.
Sister, as the City Lord's wife,
you have to stay
and celebrate with Ling.
I've heard of
your exceptional dancing skills,
unparalleled in Canglong City.
Why not take this opportunity
to perform a dance?
Ling Xiao,
you might as well just kill me.
Ling Xiao, you've gone too far!
I won't allow you
to insult Wan'er like this.
You're willing
to die for him?
What's that got to do with you?
What's it got to do with me?
Fine,
then I'll kill him!
Will you spare him
if I finish this dance?
Since you care about him so much,
I'll grant your wish.
♪Rain falls in the courtyard,
stirring up idle worries♪
♪I spread out paper and pen,
writing a quatrain♪
♪I think of you again
as I write down the past memories♪
♪Who did I share my emotions
during those years?♪
♪Threads of emotions linger,
deeply immersed in your features♪
♪This life is also tumultuous,
what use is there to confide in?♪
♪The clear wind points
to the love and separation, so poignant♪
♪As if you haven't left yet♪
♪The wind blows, but I don't see you.
I added a few more strokes♪
♪To the ending♪
♪With the flowers falling
and the time passing♪
♪Leaving only memories behind♪
♪The wind blows from a long distance♪
♪Yet, you didn't show up♪
♪This love is full of regrets.
You're a dream in this fleeting life♪
Enough.
Stop dancing.
♪Threads of emotions linger,
deeply immersed in your features♪
♪This life is also tumultuous,
what use is there to confide in?♪
♪The clear wind points
to the love and separation, so poignant♪
Ling Xiao, let her go!
♪People sit silently by candlelight
as night begins♪
♪A play of sorrows and joys,
your role, my outline♪
♪Though the dream is over,
the feelings are hard to let go♪
♪Everyone is filled with
sorrow and pity♪
♪Alas, the mortal world
has too many spectators♪
♪You turn back to ascend
the stage wearing a green robe♪
♪A song asking about heart matters,
but who will answer?♪
♪An old dream with infatuation
and resentment and complications♪
♪You sing for me♪
♪In the play,
telling of separations and reunions♪
♪Pear blossoms fall
and flowing sleeves feel like yesterday♪
♪The heart is closed,
unable to gaze the emotional eyes♪
♪This life is filled
with too much affection♪
♪Amid the applause,
who can see through it?♪
♪Aren't the characters
in the play you and me?♪
My Lord.
Ling, what are you...
Niyue,
how long are you going
to keep lying to me?
♪The weathered years,
the yellow old marks♪
♪Memories of a lifetime
in the past dreams♪
♪The residual snow, the shining stars,
the hazy midnight moon♪
♪Strong liquor cannot dispel
the melancholy of love♪
♪The green mountains form a line
and the river reflects the moon♪
♪Time flies like an arrow,
what day is today?♪
♪Spring returns with warmth again,
and birds are everywhere♪
♪This love only awaits
your reciprocation♪
♪Who will hold my hand now?
Your beautiful smile can make me drunk♪
♪A song of love, hatred,
love and romance♪