Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Shin Ji Hyun,
you shouldn't have died today.
When you die before it's your time,
as a result of someone else's mistake,
within 49 days, you must
find three people who love you.
Then you can live again.
But how can it be proved?
The tears of the person who
loves you and cries over you is the proof.
Three drops of a hundred percent genuine tears.
Shin Ji Hyun, you can use
Song Yi Kyung's body when she's sleeping.
I am Shin Ji Hyun.
I wish Ji Hyun was just dreaming.
But why isn't he crying?
Who would have thought
Ji Hyun would end up like that?
Around us, nothing happens
by coincidence, everything's connected.
Episode 3
Eat something first.
You have the stomach to eat right now?
Ji Hyun is in that condition.
You haven't ate these past few days.
We shouldn't do this.
No.
You didn't sleep much, right?
Before the room service waiter comes,
let's rest for awhile.
Oppa, what should we do?
That's right. That's what
caused the accident to occur.
What's the matter, guest?
Are you hurt anywhere?
Are you okay?
Are you staying in this room?
No.
Then why are you here?
What are you doing here?
Why are you standing
in front of someone else's door?
Hey, hey.
When you came, did you
see anyone you know?
I didn't.
What's the matter?
I'm the room service waiter.
No, I thought I heard noise outside.
Well...
There was a woman sprawled here.
A woman sprawled? Here?
It's not a big deal, sir.
She wasn't in her right mind.
She ran away.
Wait here.
- You've worked hard.
- Thank you.
Oppa, how could you tell me this?
Now you're telling me this?
You made me look for Ji Hyun's seal,
how could you do this?
Luckily, President Shin doesn't have the spare time
to consider the problem of Ji Hyun's land.
We must find it before then.
Do you think that's something
I have the ability to do right now?
Ji Hyun's like that,
she's already in that state!
This is something that should be done.
Oppa, I feel like my heart
is tearing into a thousand pieces!
It won't tear.
In Jung.
We're not the ones
who turned Ji Hyun into that.
It's possible that it's because of us.
I'll get off work immediately
when I'm outside.
Secretary Shin, you should get off work too.
Yes, President.
You've worked hard.
Why is the color of your face off?
Does it hurt somewhere?
You're really tired, right?
What about you, Oppa?
You're not nervous?
Are you afraid?
I'm scared.
I'm afraid.
You regret it?
Can't we just call it quits now?
Let's stop.
I feel very apologetic to you.
I don't want to take it to this extent.
I really don't want to.
I'm still preparing for the wedding with Ji Hyun...
Let's run away immediately.
Of course you're in fear
and you're afraid. It's normal.
But don't have regret.
This isn't something you can regret.
Shameful things are regretful.
Answer it.
Hey, Ji Hyun.
Are you busy?
Why? Is everything finished?
I'm asking you if you're busy or not.
You're already finished. Are you
coming to the company?
Or is there anything else I can help with?
Oh, okay.
I think Ji Hyun is bored by herself.
Oppa.
Just bear it for a couple of days.
The place of Ji Hyun's car
accident was close to us.
Maybe she followed us.
She was bored by herself so she called you.
She was going to find you at work, but she
changed her mind and was on her way to find me.
I told Ji Hyun that we'll go together.
Didn't I specify the meeting time and place?
I know how tired you are.
I understand completely.
You knew but you still did this?
But In Jung, if we end it here,
what kind of guy does that make me?
I can't just stop
because of what happened to Ji Hyun.
I don't care if you do it or not, but I will.
I won't do it. I can't do it.
Think about the beginning of this.
Why did we become like this?
If we run away now, will we be happy?
If we stop, will that bring Ji Hyun back?
You really freak out and misuse that button.
You know, right?
How could I... Why did that accident
happen to me? You know, right?
Why didn't you tell me?
I got into that accident
because of Min Ho oppa and In Jung.
That... that's because I was afraid
of revealing the heaven's secret.
- Revealing the secret?
- Yes. Revealing. The. Heaven's. Secret.
You probably don't understand what
revealing the heaven's secret means, right?
You don't know?
Revealing the heaven's secret,
it's heaven meaning sky, secret meaning...
What? What's the matter?
Why are you...?
Women creatures have tears
like a never-ending stream.
So you knew but didn't tell me?
I also have to follow the rules for five years
before I get the chance to live again.
Those two had something all along!
Okay, okay.
In regards to the origin your accident,
your romance, your love triangle,
I have no interest in these types of things.
When did it all start?
I couldn't tell at all.
How could they be in a relationship?
Then why was he going to marry me?
Why are you asking me?
If you knocked on the door,
the two people involved could've told you.
Didn't you say that I can't
reveal that I'm Shin Ji Hyun?
That's right, you did a good job.
The rest is your problem.
Settle them yourself.
What can be done about her stupidity?
What am I going to do now?
Is now the time to cry over your own death?
Be worried about the present.
49 days.
No.
You should think about how
you're going to pass the next 46 days.
49 days, it's not a very long time.
Our special couple home is going to be built here.
Please help us.
Song Yi Kyung has not arrived yet?
Can she come?
Why don't you try calling her?
Would a liar put her
phone number on her resume?
Seriously Hyung, you think Yi Kyung was lying?
Hand over the 10,000 won.
We made a bet.
A bet?
Is your brain swelling acting up again?
You dare to make a bet on people?
Miss Ma Sung Jung, do you
think this restaurant is a joke?
You guys, what are you doing?
Shut up! Punks.
Get out, get out.
Oh! Sister-in-law!
Chun!
Honey!
It's so cold outside,
I told you to not come out.
I told you clearly not to
come here when it's cold.
Didn't I tell you that?
I originally didn't want to come.
So?
I was by myself in the warm and cozy house
and I was doing what you told me.
Doing what I told you.
Then suddenly, I heard that sound.
That sound? What sound?
The sound of a loudspeaker.
Sound of a loudspeaker?
What loudspeaker's sound?
I can't take it anymore!
Sister-in-law, exactly what
loudspeaker sound is it?
The fish is here, and the seaweed too.
Seaweed came, too.
They were scurrying to get here,
and I ran into them on my way.
That's what happened.
Is it our story?
So what?
What is so this and so that?
- Because you missed your husband...
- You still won't shut up?
So what?
So I prepared some fish slices for you.
What's wrong with the atmosphere here?
Atmosphere? Why? What?
Is it because of that young lady outside?
What are you doing here?
Kang.
Ki Joon, bring over the bag.
I brought my employment certification.
You brought it?
I clearly said that you
must bring it within an hour.
I even gave you money for a taxi.
The time right now is 2:27.
Take your bag and leave.
I met a friend at the hotel.
Are you making up excuses?
I also met my fiance.
I'm just saying...
That...
The two of them were together.
I saw the two of them together.
This...
Okay, okay.
Forget it, get off work for today.
Come back tomorrow.
- What happened?
- What's wrong?
- Song Yi Kyung!
- Song Yi Kyung, wake up!
- Miss.
- Hey.
Hey. What to do?
Ahjussi, what should we do?
What should we do?
Lay her down inside.
Come on.
- Don't be like this.
- Why?
She isn't a person you love,
she's not someone who you can carry.
The young man should carry her.
Fiance?
Even though you have a fiance,
you still treat Min Ho hyung like that?
you still act like an assistant.
Did you really see
your fiance and your friend?
Look, Song Yi Kyung.
She definitely worked at Seoul Hotel before.
This Song Yi Kyung,
who says it's that Song Yi Kyung?
We haven't confirmed her identity yet.
Why do you have such
a hard time trusting people?
You're dismissed.
Sister-in-law.
What soup do we have today?
I thought you weren't having any.
It's what our Hae Won likes.
It improves digestion and absorption.
It's a daikon soup with added amylase*.
(*enzyme that breaks down starches)
Why?
Deliver a bowl to the room.
Deliver to who?
Deliver the meal as well.
Oh, bring extra rice.
Pile it really high.
Was it Han Kang who covered me?
He didn't use cold water to wake me up.
That's good.
He didn't fire me.
I was lying in the hospital
from the car accident,
and they actually had a
secret meeting in a hotel room.
Then have the two of them met
behind my back in a hotel room all along?
Miss!
You didn't lose anything, right?
Go take a look upstairs.
Didn't she leave without telling us?
She left this behind.
Is she hiding any money in here?
She's probably hiding 100,000 won.
Go back.
I told you to stop.
Look at this.
I can feel it, feel it inside of me.
It keeps taking space in my heart.
Even your breathing,
I feel like it is talking to me.
Love is coming,
love has stolen my heart.
Even if I lose everything,
I am fine.
So I can love, because I can love,
I am happy.
If we stop, will that bring Ji Hyun back?
Think about the origins of this matter.
Think about why we have to do this.
No matter what you think, I will do it.
I will.
Today it's my treat.
How about chicken and beer?
I'm trying to lose weight.
Lose what weight?
Everybody's getting off work.
Why isn't In Jung coming down?
Hey! How could you be with Min Ho oppa?
Did you start liking Min Ho oppa first?
Impossible.
Or did Min Ho oppa seduce you?
That's also impossible.
How exactly did your relationship develop?
Why did you walk to my house?
What are you going to do here?
In Jung, you're not...
You and oppa just had something
to discuss. It's not anything else, right?
So that's why you met at the hotel?
Who is it?
Ahjumma, it's In Jung.
Yeah, it's okay to have a meeting
at the hotel to discuss something.
Bitch, then what was that?
What was that?
Shin In Jung, you're not even
letting me enter my own home?
I knew it'd turn out like this.
Has mother been well?
She just took sleep medication and
is having a lie down.
Okay.
But why did you come here?
I thought of coming
to see her when I got off work.
Don't mind me, carry on
with what you're doing.
What are you doing?
Mother.
I thought you were sleeping.
I was going to sleep
but I heard the door bell.
I asked you what you're doing.
It's nothing. I just thought
of Ji Hyun and wanted to drop by.
If you want to see her,
why don't you go to the hospital?
Why did you come here?
Isn't Ji Hyun at the hospital?
- Her condition isn't very good.
- So?
Has my Ji Hyun died?
She didn't die.
Why do you come and go as
you please without Ji Hyun's permission?
Come out.
I don't want you guys
to see my daughter as dead.
I know.
How long?
A month? A year? 10 years?
Just say how long.
How can you not even determine
that when you're a doctor?
I'm sorry.
Then do we have to keep waiting?
What do you plan to do?
Why did you come again?
Dad, if you're going somewhere,
inform me ahead of time.
How could you leave Ji Hyun here by herself?
I went to see Doctor Cho.
Doctor Cho?
- Why? Is Ji Hyun...?
- No.
Oh yeah, has Ji Hyun's
land been decided yet?
Yes.
Then I'll leave the remaining
matters for you to handle.
Dad, you should handle them.
You can help me.
I have to keep watch on her.
I know that you're very sad.
But it can't be worse than what we feel.
I didn't find it, oppa.
Mother won't let me enter Ji Hyun's room.
What's she talking about?
She just doesn't like my presence.
Ji Hyun still hasn't...
Taxi.
Oppa?
In Jung's oppa isn't in Seoul.
I got it. Let's do that.
Shin Young, it's me.
Min Ho, what were you doing
when I was telling you?
Listen to me today.
Mother's in weak health.
You should go see her.
You go back and sleep.
Leave this to me.
Oh really? Ji Hyun might
want to be alone with you.
Good thing I didn't go to the hospital.
Otherwise, I would've missed him.
You still don't understand?
Oppa, everyday you send
over ten text messages to me.
You'd also come see me
whenever you're free.
You told me your
mailbox ID and MSN password.
Right? Isn't it like that?
No matter how stupid I am,
I knew that you loved me.
0505.
Oppa, that's my birthday.
You told me the pass code and said
I could come whenever I wanted.
Was it In Jung who fell
for you, so you wavered?
What exactly is the matter?
Explain in detail.
Oppa.
You can see me?
There's not much to explain.
I already told you everything.
Your relationship is on this level?
You didn't find anything odd?
She didn't seem to suspect me.
She just can't get over Ji Hyun.
You're positive?
You think I don't understand Ji Hyun's mother?
That's good.
Then why didn't you
come up with a random excuse?
Say that you left
something behind in her room.
Or say that you lent her something.
When I saw her mother like that,
my mind went blank and
I couldn't think of anything.
What are you guys talking about?
You're sure that Ji Hyun's seal
is in the drawer of her vanity?
Her seal and things such
as her bank card...
She'd always put them
in the left vanity drawer.
My seal?
Here's the copy of my registry
and the certificate of my seal.
There's also my seal.
I didn't leave out anything right?
You're careless, but don't worry this time.
I gave him my seal that time.
Why is he still looking for it?
I should've checked it then.
Please don't ask me to work
at least three days before my wedding.
Don't worry.
How could we postpone group leader
Kang's wedding because of work?
This...
What is this?
Why isn't there a seal, but this instead?
That careless girl.
Please wait a moment.
Hello?
Hello, isn't this Miss Shin
Ji Hyun's cell phone?
What? Accident?
No matter how careless,
I never thought that she'd hand it over
before even checking to make sure it's her seal.
So that's why oppa
rushed to the emergency room?
Oppa, you can't go to
Ji Hyun's mother's place right now.
I even talked it over with President Shin.
Everything was signed smoothly.
Really?
Then what should we do?
Before it gets discovered,
we have to find the seal.
If Ji Hyun still has land,
our plan will fail.
I put in so much effort in trying
to get my hands on that land.
What are you going to do?
Don't worry, we'll figure something out.
Go home and get some rest.
I still have to drop by the hospital.
Don't be discovered by anyone
when you're leaving. Be careful.
What are the two of them doing?
What exactly are they doing to my dad?
What are you doing?
I'm preparing some extra clothes
for going to the hospital.
Didn't you say you didn't sleep well
even after taking the sleep medication?
Don't think about going to the hospital.
Can't I just sleep there?
Ahjumma! Pack my toothbrush and toothpaste.
Also pack shampoo and conditioner.
I'm begging you, stop.
Do you not know why I'm doing this?
Husband, I'm okay.
Not okay.
You're not okay.
Ji Hyun's not okay either.
I know that Ji Hyun's not ready to see you yet.
Is she still like that now?
I still can't recognize her, right?
I haven't seen her in a long time.
Don't always wear me down.
Quickly get my extra clothes ready.
Then get some water from the bathroom.
Sor... Sorry.
Husband, I want to die.
I want to die before Ji Hyun does.
Then what am I supposed to do?
I said I love you.
I'm saying I love you sincerely.
Why are you laughing?
Within 49 days, find three people
who can cry sincere tears for you.
Then you can go back.
If there's a person who cries
a hundred percent genuine tears,
collect them in here.
Dad.
Mom.
What should I do?
But thinking of my life without you,
tears form.
You didn't say anything, you were the one that left.
I wish it wasn't true.
It is okay for you to come back.
Just for a moment, we were separated,
that is what I will believe.
Nothing has happened,
Nothing has happened.
When I wake up tonight...
It is okay for you to come back.
Nothing has happened.
When I wake up tonight,
I will be with you again.
How much do I have to give you?
Oh, you remember me now?
Please give the receipts.
What about the health insurance money?
I still haven't received the hospital bill yet.
How much did the taxi cost?
Because it was a private taxi,
the cost was pretty high.
You're not curious of who I am?
Nope.
You're also not curious as to why
I showed up at the scene of your car accident?
It doesn't matter.
What if I told you
the reason why you went there?
If you're curious, then ask.
Please take care.
See you tomorrow.
There's still 45 days,
3 hours and 29 minutes left.
My insides are scarred,
my insides are burnt.
I tell myself I won't be able to love.
Let's forget now, please forget now.
Even though I decided to,
The picture of you in my heart
faces me.
Nothing will happen to you,
even if you forget me.
Has Unni been faced
with this kind of problem before?
And that's why you're living this way?
I cry for awhile, then laugh, then fall asleep.
I pick up the phone, then put it down.
Like I am stupid, so stupid.
I have been like this for days.
I am going to go crazy because I miss you.
I am going to go crazy because I want to forget you.
Like I am stupid, so stupid.
I cannot forget you or tell you to come back to me.
There's still 44 days,
3 hours and 29 minutes left.
Hey, now you want to destroy this?
You're confident that you can compensate for it?
I didn't call for you.
When you call for me
isn't the only time I appear.
When I call you, you don't come.
I'm irritated, leave.
Why are you being like this?
Don't you know?
Ah, you've wasted
your entire life in this world?
Is that what you mean?
I... can't live on.
That's why I came.
I came to call the elevator.
Elevator?
When's the best time
to call it down for you?
Right now it's 10:35.
I'll call it for you at 12:00, okay?
I have to give you some time
to tidy everything up here for the last time.
What do you mean?
You're saying... that...
You're going to call down
the elevator to heaven?
Hasn't it been two days since
you last used this woman's body?
Then does that mean you're
not planning on leaving this world?
When did I? When did I ever
say that I was going to leave?
The three people who truly love you...
Aren't there any?
Hey Scheduler, wait.
Even if there aren't,
you can't be this unreasonable.
There's still 45 days left.
It's 44.
There's only 44 days left?
Let's go.
Don't look at this miserable sight anymore.
Let's go directly to your next life.
Then it's set for 11:00.
No!
I didn't give you 49 days
just for you to waste them away.
I won't do that anymore.
I didn't come to work yesterday
without saying anything.
With my little ability, I'm even late today.
Maybe I'm crazy.
Then you didn't plan on quitting that day?
No, of course not.
I promise it's not like that.
I was a little...
It's a problem in my private life
that I can't tell.
Because it's caused a very difficult
problem, it turned out like that.
What about your meals?
What?
I asked you if you ate.
I haven't.
I didn't eat anything in two days.
Then, what is this?
I didn't eat that.
Isn't that a noodle?
Ahjussi, help prepare some food.
Han Kang, thank you.
Thank you very, very much.
Please enjoy your meal.
Ahjussi, she's not too bad.
Yeah, that wasn't bad.
How could this be?
Two days ago, she was clumsy.
Now two days later, she's become an expert.
There's also people like me.
She should be no problem.
That woman's getting more and more confusing.
[Incoming call, Park Seo Woo]
What should I do now?
What should I do?
What do I have to start doing?
Seo Woo.
Oh, Kang's here.
Hey, Ki Joon.
- Take the garbage out.
- Okay.
I'll do it.
Thank you for that day.
You said that you're a new worker here, right?
You're called Miss Song Yi Kyung?
You don't remember me?
Am I supposed to remember you?
Seo Woo, you said that
you're going to look after Ji Hyun?
In Jung and I. Just at night.
I went to the hospital during the day.
Ji Hyun's dad is in a terrible state...
What exactly is she saying?
He's busy with company matters,
I can't disappoint Ji Hyun.
It's the least I can do.
The problem right now isn't the company.
If we don't take care,
maybe Ji Hyun's dad will also collapse.
Let me do it.
So in order to urge Ji Hyun's dad,
we decided to meet you, Min Ho.
I got it. I'll talk to father about it.
There should be no problem
if you leave it to us.
But Ji Hyun's mother has
always been in that condition, right?
Yes. She's not doing anything at home.
She's not eating, drinking or sleeping.
Be more careful.
I... I'm sorry.
You'll get hurt.
She probably got scared.
Take her away.
Let Joon clean it up.
Okay.
Who is that? I don't think
I've ever seen that worker before.
Just a part-timer.
Kang, since you're already standing,
let's go to the office.
See you two later.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Mom.
On behalf of the management of the 49 days,
I'm notifying you the time
remaining to return home is ticking.
Did I say that I'd work until 12?
Do you really not remember?
From 12 noon to 12 midnight,
for four dollars an hour.
Will there be a day
when you can work properly?
You need permission before you can go.
Okay.
I'm going to get scolded again.
Hyung, you don't have any spare time now.
After Hyunmido expands,
can you continue to manage it?
This is something Ji Hyun's
father instructed me to do.
Ji Hyun's father?
I'm sorry again.
What's the matter?
I have something to say.
Can you step out for awhile?
I think she came not knowing I was here.
Do you want me to leave?
Say it, what is it?
I can only work until 11:30.
Your shift ends at 12:00.
I made that clear.
I was too hungry that day,
I didn't hear you correctly.
Because you didn't hear correctly,
you can only work until 11:30?
- Is that what you're saying?
- It's not that!
No matter what happens,
I must be home before 12:00.
There's someone waiting for me.
She can't move until I get back.
Okay, you can go.
I can really go?
But letting me go now doesn't mean that
you want me to disappear forever, right?
Get off work at 11:00pm.
Come to work at 11:00am.
Thank you!
Why are you so lenient with that woman?
How am I lenient?
What do you mean?
Even though you seem rash, you're
extremely dedicated to your business.
You can't handle your own matters well.
You hate the type of people
who fool around carelessly.
With her personality, aren't you
being too tolerant?
I took her in especially to look after her.
To look after her?
Look after her what?
There's something.
So this is the type of woman you like?
What?
I see that you're
completely uninterested in girls.
Exactly what kind of girl
are you looking for?
I've always been curious about that.
Turns out it's that type.
It's not that!
But, Hyung,
regardless of the time,
you never lose your humor.
What?
I'm just trying.
I think that this is what
Ji Hyun would've wanted.
Me?
Kang, Ji Hyun would do the same.
She would hope that I'd be like before,
and continue to persevere. Ji Hyun...
No!
That's right.
It should be like that.
Shin Ji Hyun...
I said no!
Definitely, definitely not!
She would hope that I'd be like before,
and continue to persevere. Ji Hyun...
Is oppa that kind of person?
If Ji Hyun still has land
under her name, our plan will fail.
Before it gets discovered,
we have to find the seal.
That's right.
My seal...
First of all, I just need
to keep your hands off it.
I'm going to be late!
Just let me be able to move things.
When I enter my room and retrieve my seal,
I'll come out immediately!
What kind of nonsense
are you talking now?
Only for a day!
No, only an hour!
By just relying on Song Yi Kyung's body,
I can't enter my house.
Seems like you need a voice recorder.
Beep! The scheduler stays
out of human matters.
Those people have their eye on my land!
No, no, it's much more than land.
I don't know how much they're planning,
but I think they might even have
their eyes on my dad's entire company.
That's not something I should know.
Then can you help me retrieve my seal?
Repeat. The scheduler stays
out of human matters.
Then what am I going to do?
- What exactly should I do?
- Don't call me into this room next time.
Every time I'm here, my mood is strange.
- You don't make any exceptions?
- Nope, I'm leaving.
I know that, if you repeat a phrase,
the door might open.
Oh yeah, recently everyone
uses pass codes, right?
How could he be like that?
He didn't help at all and
he always makes people angry.
From three to five in the afternoon,
the restaurant isn't very busy.
It doesn't need many workers.
So?
Also, if I'm not here, the
working environment would be better, right?
It's because we have you that
this job became more unpleasant. Probably.
What exactly do you want to say?
You definitely can't decide to fire me
because of what I'm about to say.
Because,
the 52 dollar salary you gave me that day,
after deducting the borrowed money and the taxi fee,
there's still 36 dollars left.
That's everything I have.
If you fire me when I'm in such poverty,
before I find another job, I'd have to starve.
Even if it's like that,
there's something I must attend to.
Are you threatening me?
I'll be away for only three hours.
Skipping work without a reason, plus being late,
and now you want to go out.
You're getting more and more troublesome.
I won't take the three hours' pay.
And you're still making assumptions.
Who said they're going to give it to you?
Then does that I mean I can go?
You'll be blessed in the future!
She's similar to a certain person.
She sure can run.
Of course, I have to follow the plan.
Even your breathing,
I feel like it is talking to me.
Love is coming,
love has stolen my heart.
So I can love, because I can love,
I am happy.
I can feel it, feel it inside of me.
It keeps taking space in my heart.
Even your breathing,
I feel like it is talking to me.
Love is coming, Love has stolen my heart,
even if I lose everything I am fine.
So I can love, because I can love,
I am happy.
I never thought the things here
are actually this great.
If I continue doing this,
it'll be bad if I get caught.
This isn't it. Where did I put it?
This is my money.
Can't I use a little bit?
You have to earn the money you need.
Who is it?
There shouldn't be anyone coming at this time.
How come mother came out?
Where's Ahjumma?
She's grocery shopping.
Is something wrong?
I came when Ahjumma isn't here.
Please go inside, Mother.
You came to take a
few things that Ji Hyun likes?
I want to take the things that
Ji Hyun likes to the hospital room.
Things such as presents I
gave her, or pictures of her parents.
I want Ji Hyun to see them and cheer up.
How did you even think of that?
I'll pick a few and take them over.
Is that okay?
Of course.
You know best about
the things our Ji Hyun likes.
Why isn't it here?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator: Tigerlilly93
Spot Translators: moey, fore
Timer: soutsada7
Editor/QC: RSK
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
I reached to where I stand today, but have you
already forgotten all the things you've done with me?
Stop talking! Stop talking! Stop talking!
I don't care what means we use,
we must retrieve my seal from the hospital room.
This time you have to conceal yourself.
Remember, if the necklace shatters,
the 49 days are over.
I advise you to just leave it.
What?
I'm telling you to stop being in the way.
Are you treating me like this
because you've developed feelings for me?
What do you take me for?
Do you think I'm a benevolent person or a fool?
What's this? Are you firing me?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com