♪I upset you for
being willful and spoiled♪
♪But you're not showing any emotions♪
♪Until you're defeated by my cuteness♪
♪I'll then consider
leaving the solar system♪
♪The universe has gravity♪
♪You're my fatal attraction♪
♪The path of half the universe♪
♪Can't stop me♪
♪I have this homeless kind of sadness♪
♪But you're as warm as the sun♪
♪Across tens of millions of light years♪
♪Just to be loved by you♪
♪I love you like how
a satellite pursues a planet♪
♪You're the attractive danger
flying by the asteroid belt♪
♪Wandering for
tens of millions of light years♪
♪Just to be found by you
and keep you here with me♪
=My Girlfriend is an Alien S2=
=Episode 30=
The long-awaited Future Group's
latest high-end perfume
Forever.7 will be launched today.
Now, it's the Q&A time
for the reporters.
Any questions that you want to ask
Mr. Fang regarding Forever.7?
You can ask now.
Mr. Fang.
Hello, Mr. Fang.
As everyone knows,
hormone perfume
is Future Group's ace product.
Now, you're launching Forever.7.
Are you worried that it will affect
the hormone perfume's customers?
Thank you for the question.
Actually, these two perfumes
are a couple series.
Hormone perfume is for men
and Forever.7
is more suitable for women.
I don't think we'll lose
the customers.
On the contrary, we'll be able
to attract more customers.
It's said that Forever.7
was flavored by you.
Can you tell us
about your initial intention?
Forever.7
is originated from my girlfriend,
Xiaoqi.
This perfume is flavored by
what I've been through with her
and all the things that
we've done together.
This is the origin of the perfume.
Mr. Fang,
are you not worried that
your future girlfriend
will get jealous with this perfume?
Xiaoqi is my only lover,
so I've decided to stay single forever
for her.
So romantic.
What? That's so romantic.
He's so loyal.
Yes.
I envy her.
So loyal.
Future Group's CEO, Fang Leng,
showed how much he loves his girlfriend
on the new perfume launching.
He said his girlfriend, Xiaoqi,
is his only lover,
and he'll stay single for her forever.
Their love relationship is admired
by the crowds.
Fang Leng is going to be alone forever.
If one day,
I have to go back to my mother planet,
what will you do?
I'll be more loyal than Fang Leng.
I'll kill myself for love
after you get on the spaceship.
No, you must live on well.
Mr. Fang, you're about to go up
to the stage.
Hold on.
Let's go.
Next, let's put our hands together
to welcome
our new painter, Fang Lie,
and his Muses Goddess, Xiaobu.
Please.
(Art Exhibition)
(Chai Chai Milk Tea Shop)
Dear,
how come you've slimmed down.
Are you not used to
the food in the U.K.?
Don't worry. I'm fine.
I'm just too busy with homework.
So, I looked a bit tired.
You have no idea how much I miss you.
I'm counting down every day.
There are another 333 days
before you come back from your studies.
I'm so sorry.
No worries. Just wait for me.
When I'm back,
I'll stay by your side 24 hours a day,
okay?
I have to hang up.
My class is about to start.
Take care, okay?
- Bye.
Men and love are not reliable.
If women want to be strong,
we need to depend on ourselves.
The large-scale entertainment show,
(Participant's basic requirements)
Sisters Who Command Wind And Rain,
is now opened for registration.
If you have a dream and aspiration,
and you love to perform,
you can register.
The registration number is
1381388888.
Hello.
Hello, I'd like to register for
Sisters Who Command Wind And Rain.
What's your stage name?
Just call me Mengmengzi.
Mr. Fang,
the launching today is a great success.
Especially your love confession
to Miss Chai.
It went straight into my heart.
When I heard it below the stage,
I was crying like a baby.
Don't you have other choices of word?
What?
Anything else?
(Alien Girl Pounces On Me)
My series novel
has been published.
I think
I can be a great author.
This could be the calling of destiny.
I always think that
only I can save the romance literature.
So,
I'm planning to resign.
Don't worry.
I've found
the new assistant.
He's my cousin.
His name is Han Jinming.
He...
He must be more excellent than me.
He must be more diligent than me.
He can take care of you better than me,
Mr. Fang.
I'm reluctant to leave you.
Although you always torture me,
I always think that
you're the best
and the most handsome boss.
Han.
If the novel is not selling well,
come back to me anytime.
They are all painted by our son?
I think so.
This is my first time
seeing his paintings.
Look.
Fang Lie.
- This looks like flower.
- Oil painting.
Is it flower?
Dear.
Why does Fang Lie
always paint about
moon and stars?
Is it nice?
It's nice.
This...
One thousand, ten thousands,
one hundred thousands, one million.
(Fang Lie, Faint Light And Stars,
RMB 1,000,000)
It's really one million.
So, that's what you're looking at.
You wouldn't disagree for Fang Lie
to keep painting anymore?
Look at you.
- Why do you always act like that?
- Siqin.
Sorry, I'm late.
There was a lot of traffic.
Siqin,
I've prepared this for you,
Jujube goji berry tea.
Shida,
I've got one for you too.
Jujube goji berry.
What's with the paintings?
These are Lie's paintings.
I don't really understand.
Look at you.
I haven't gone back to
my mother planet for a while.
I wonder
how Xiaoqi and Jiang Shiyi are doing.
They'd stayed on the earth for so long.
Will they be punished?
Ever since the new leader,
Jilisibuladakaqikaqi No. 11,
came in office,
he has repealed the DNA matching
and advocated free love from earth.
This law is not only appealed to
the citizens on Cape Town Planet,
but also all the robots.
Lately,
all the factories are working hard
on increasing the production line
to provide human bodies to
all the robots.
Master.
Who are you?
Master, greetings.
I'm Candy.
So, this is the human appearance
that you chose?
Yes. You don't like it?
No.
I'm just a bit surprised.
Master, are you looking for this?
My name is Candy.
So, after having the human body,
my first mission
is to try all the imported candies
from the earth.
I think this is the best.
You've eaten the previous one
for so long.
Change to a new taste.
(Alert, system is suddenly heated.
Please fix it in time)
It's tasty.
Thank you.
Look at this child.
What's going on?
Fang Leng
has just rejected another blind date.
How many it has been?
He's the CEO of Future Group.
He can't stay single forever.
Just stay out of their matters.
Let things happen on its own.
How can I do that?
No way. He has to join this tomorrow.
I'll call him now.
The number you've dialed
is not available.
See?
Fang Leng's avoiding me.
It must be taught by Fang Lie.
Give me your phone.
Father.
Fang Leng,
did you block my phone number?
Aunt, I told you I don't want
to go for the blind date.
I'm doing this for your own good.
You're not young anymore
and you're not getting married.
Okay, that's it.
You have to join this tomorrow.
Otherwise,
I'll leave this matter alone.
I'll leave this matter to your father.
(Lately, our city's
Scientific Research Department)
(has frequently detected
unusual magnetic signal.)
(The analysis shows that
this unusual phenomenon)
(should be related to the UFO)
(that appeared not long ago.)
(Let's look at the next news.)
(Sunny Apartment)
Fang Leng, what have you cooked?
It smells so good.
Why are you here?
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
Thank you.
Mother asked me to come and
monitor your blind date.
If you're not going tomorrow,
she will not let me go home forever.
Fang Leng,
I know you only love Xiaoqi,
but mother has been
thinking about your marriage.
Just go for tomorrow
and show your face.
Tomorrow is the final recruitment of
the Perfume Creative Department.
I need to join the final review.
What department is that?
I've never heard of it.
It's a new department
established half a month ago.
Now, it's under
the pre-construction period.
It's just recruitment.
Just let the department head handle it.
Just read the resumes remotely.
Don't be too serious.
(Because of you,
I am willing to love the whole world.)
If you're not going tomorrow,
I'll just stay here and not leave.
I'll be super annoying.
Fang Lie!
Fang Leng,
I knew you'll not reject me.
Sleep in the living room.
- Sleep on the sofa.
- Why, Fang Leng?
(Because I love you, Xiaoqi.)
(I love you, too.)
(So,)
(I think it's meaningful)
(to do anything with you.)
(I'll just hug you like this
from now on.)
(Then you won't disappear suddenly.)
After three rounds of screening,
we've selected three perfumers.
These are the samples of their perfumes.
This is not bad.
It's mainly the flower scent.
(Indole is the mixture of
pyrrole and benzene)
It's mixed with some indole scent.
(Contains indole)
Sir, what do you think?
No.
The scent is not innovative at all.
We're Perfume Creative Department.
We should keep innovating
on the new perfumes.
Too many favors.
No emphasis.
This should've been eliminated earlier.
Let's look at the second perfume.
I can tell that
this is a perfumer with style.
Others' perfume
will have the top note,
middle note and base note flavored
based on one's set ideas.
Hers is rather creative.
It's not based on any usual ideas.
She's the new intern
in our department.
I've met her few days back.
This young lady is not professional.
Her flavoring skill is average.
She's not highly educated.
I've never heard of the university
that she graduated from.
Education doesn't mean everything.
Looking at the perfume she flavored,
I can tell that
she's a potential perfumer.
Liu, smell it again.
It can combine different scents
together perfectly.
That's right.
I've long heard about that her nose
is very sensitive.
She can flavor any scent
that she's smelled before.
But I think this lady
is a bit crazy.
During the interview,
she said to me that
she has a strong feeling for earth.
My nose is super sensitive.
I'll never make a mistake.
It's from then that
I've grown interest in the earth.
She came back this time
for a special person.
She even said that
her perfume is named "Reunion".
This is the perfume I made for you,
cold on the outside
and warm on the inside.
It's called "Fang Leng".
What's her name?
I didn't bring her resume with me.
Liu,
is her name Xiaoliu or Xiaojiu?
I think it's...
Where's she?
The interns should be
in the working area.
- Mr. Fang!
Mr. Fang!
Hello, Mr. Fang.
Who are you looking for?
(Don't worry.)
(I'll never leave you.)
(Chai Xiaoqi)
(If you don't remember me anymore,)
(I'll be doing what I'm doing now.)
(I'll use any possible methods)
(to remind you of me.)
Is the new intern's name
Chai Xiaoqi?
She has just come for a few days.
I don't know what her name is.
But, she's on leave today.
She said she's going for a blind date.
(Missing Calls: Aunt Zhou)
Aunt Zhou.
Fang Leng, where are you?
Why haven't you arrived?
She has been waiting two hours for you.
I'll be right there.
Xiaoqi.
Aunt Zhou.
The girl today
is introduced by your father.
I've never met her before.
You're late for two hours.
Maybe she got angry and left.
(Xiaoqi,)
(are you back?)
♪The closer I get to you♪
♪The more I want to talk to you♪
♪I wonder why♪
♪The expected touch seems
like a coincidence♪
♪Lands on this heart♪
Sir,
you almost ran into me.
You need to be responsible.
I've planned this for so long.
Luckily Uncle Fang
and Aunt Zhou were helping me.
Otherwise, it wouldn't
have been so nice.
You can't be angry.
You lied to me before.
You made me so sad.
♪To light up the night sky♪
♪My destiny lover♪
♪At that sudden moment♪
♪My hug becomes your roof♪
♪Protect you from the rain♪
♪Oh it feels like yesterday♪
♪Realize that what's irreplaceable♪
♪Is staying by your side♪
♪My destiny lover♪
♪My long-cherished wish♪
♪Is the destined encounter♪
♪Rippling the whole world♪
♪The sunny day I've set up♪
♪Has no limit for you unconditionally♪
♪Exclusive for you forever♪
Shida,
look.
What?
He has been
waiting for so long.
They can finally be together.
Look at them, a match made in heaven.
- Of course.
- Zoom in.
Fang Leng,
didn't you promise me to go?
Why didn't you show up?
My mother will call and scold me again.
Can't you just be nice
to your poor brother?
Why didn't she call me yet?
She must be waiting
for the opportunity.
How should I reply to her later,
Fang Leng?
Okay, I need to cook for Xiaoqi.
Fang Leng.
I knew this day would come,
but I didn't know it's coming so soon.
You...
Are you missing Xiaoqi too badly
that you're confused
and having illusion?
No worries.
We can get you treated as soon
as possible since we've found out.
Yes, let's get you treated.
Fang Leng, let's go to the hospital.
Even if you can't be treated,
I'll take care of you forever.
Who will you be taking care of?
I'll call the hospital for Fang Leng.
Fang Leng, this is bad!
I have illusion, too! No way!
Fang Lie.
Fang Lie, my system is down!
Xiaobu,
what's going on?
Did it happen because
we miss her too much?
I'm sure it did!
Let's take a look again.
What should we do?
I'm sure it did! What should we do?
(One month later)
(The famous entrepreneur, Fang Leng,)
(is getting married
with his fiancee, Chai Xiaoqi,)
(today.)
(Not long ago,)
(Future Group's newly launched perfume,)
(Forever.7 was originated)
(from Miss Chai Xiaoqi.)
My wife is beautiful.
The ceremony has yet to start.
You can only call me "wife"
after the ceremony.
Why are you here?
Don't be panicked.
I'm not here
to take Xiaoqi away.
Why did you come to the earth?
Congratulations
on your wedding.
Are you here for our wedding?
Not really.
Cape Town has launched
a new delicacy policy.
We're going to abandon
the nutrition potion
that replenishes energy.
We're about to start making nice food
like the earthlings.
I'm here on the earth to
purchase some stocks.
I happened to see your wedding.
I heard that earthlings
will come to the weddings
with cash gift.
This is a token from me.
Could it be...
Shiyi.
Thank you.
Thank you
Shiyi, did you come alone?
Let me introduce.
My AI assistant, Candy.
Candy.
Hold on.
Madam, why are you fighting
for food with the kids?
Did you just call me "madam"?
Counting from the date
that I was delivered,
I'm not even one year old.
Liar.
Kubri. Fang Lie.
Who is she?
Don't you remember me?
I'm Candy.
You used to break my firewall.
Our mother planet has developed so much?
You have a human figure now?
I suspect
you're scolding me.
No.
I...
He taught me all these bad stuff.
What are you doing on the earth?
Master and I came here together.
Jiang Shiyi?
Hurry. Let's go.
Hello.
Have we met before?
I'm sorry.
I'm Miss Chai's friend,
a famous online romance novel author,
Han Zhiming.
Zhiming as in Chunjiao and Zhiming.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Candy.
The wedding is about to start. Let's go.
Master, I have yet to finish my food.
Since you like to eat chocolate so much,
why not change your name to Chocolate?
Can I?
Let's go.
(New chapter)
He's a young and talented
romance novel author.
She's a cute food lover
who doesn't talk to strangers.
A short encounter on the wedding.
He chases her.
She runs away from him.
She can hardly escape.
My wife.
Hello, everyone.
Today, I'm honored to
be here, witnessing
Mr. Fang Leng and
Miss Chai Xiaoqi's wedding.
Mr. Fang Leng,
will you be gentle and patient
in taking care of your wife?
Love her, help her.
Poor or rich,
healthy or sick,
in adversity or not,
you'll use your whole life
to protect her
and love her?
I will.
Miss Chai Xiaoqi,
will you use your whole life
to accept Mr. Fang Leng's love?
Poor or rich,
healthy or sick,
in adversity or not,
he will not say that you're fat,
ugly,
or old.
And every day in the future,
he'll give you every penny
that he earns?
Will you accept that?
I will.
Now, you may
exchange your wedding rings.
♪I'd never forget the gentleness♪
♪Deep in your eyes♪
♪It takes only a moment♪
♪To fall in love with you♪
♪But it takes forever♪
♪To forget about you♪
♪I'm afraid that I'd forget♪
Next, our handsome bridegroom,
you may kiss your beautiful bride.
- Kiss her!
- Congratulations!
♪It takes only a moment
to fall in love with you♪
- Be together forever!
- Never separate from one another!
- Have a kid soon!
- Be happy forever!
Well said!
♪I'll always remember your true love♪
♪I want to own nothing else
besides that♪
♪Even though the story
goes back in time♪
♪And starts all over♪
♪I'd never forget the gentleness♪
♪Deep in your eyes♪
♪It takes only a moment♪
♪To fall in love with you♪
♪But it takes forever♪
♪To forget about you♪
Didn't you ask me about
the wish I made?
Now, it has come true.
I can show you now.
Well, mine has come true as well.
(I wish I can stay by
Fang Leng's side forever.)
It hurts.
Dear.
I want you
to help me fulfill another wish.
What's it?
I want you to fly with me on the sky.
Well, I need to fulfill
my husband's wish.
Let's go.
Come.
♪If you're neon and I'm wind♪
♪We smile at the same time♪
♪Look at the firework that overhears us♪
♪Persuading moonlight to land♪
♪To light up the night sky♪
♪My destiny lover♪
♪At that sudden moment♪
♪My hug becomes your roof♪
♪Protect you from the rain♪
♪Oh it feels like yesterday♪
♪Realize that what's irreplaceable♪
♪My destiny lover♪
♪My long-cherished wish♪
♪Is the destined encounter♪
♪Rippling the whole world♪
♪The sunny day I've set up♪
(The end)
(Not yet, please stay)
May I know if the receivers,
Fang Liangliang,
Fang Wenwen and Fang Tangtang,
are home?
How come no one is at home?
Sir, lower your head.
I'm Fang Wenwen.
I'm Fang Tangtang.
I'm Fang Liangliang.
Kids, this is your parcel.
Thank you, sir.
Liangliang, Wenwen,
did mother buy us some nice food again?
(Receivers, Fang Liangliang,
Fang Wenwen, Fang Tangtang)
How come
it's Uncle Jiang's parcel again?
It must be Uncle Jiang's
present for us.
Be careful. Don't damage it.
What's this?
It's blinking.
Will it explode?
Uncle Jiang's present
won't be dangerous.
Maybe it's a surprise.
Stop.
What's going on?
(Made of a special material from
Cape Town, can't be controlled)
This material
is made of a special material
from Cape Town planet.
Our superpowers can't control it.
Cape Town Planet
found a special material.
Why don't I feel any pain?
- We're in pain.
Liangliang. Wenwen.
- Thank you, Liangliang, Wenwen.
- Tangtang.
I'm back.
I'm back as well.
What are you doing?
- What happened? Get up.
- I have no more strength.
- Why are you lying on the floor?
- Tangtang.
Get up.
Come, get up.
- What happened?
- Get up.
What happened?
Uncle Jiang's present.
Xiaoqi.
Yes, what I've prepared for you
is Cape Town's latest candy.
Try and see if it tastes good.
I was worried that your three children
would fight for the candy with you,
so I set it the way only you can eat it.
Uncle Jiang, you're biased.
I'm not biased, Tangtang.
Look at what I've prepared for you.
Cape Town's custom-made princess dress.
You'll look great wearing it.
Thank you, Uncle Jiang.
Liangliang,
don't you like managing a business?
Here's my gift for you.
It's Cape Town's
multipurpose calculator.
Isn't it just a high-tech product that
has stored all
the planets' currency data
which can quickly count
the galactic currency?
I'm not interested at all.
Wenwen, grow up faster.
I've gifted you many
mechanical components.
Later on, you can ask your mother
to upgrade it for you.
Fang Leng.
There's no gift for you.
Are you angry?
No.
No?
Okay then.
Then I'll eat
this super nice candy.
I'm not eating it.
It's so awful.
Right?
How can it be so awful?
Eat it.
It's indeed awful.
Right?
Forget it. I'll throw it away.
He prepared it for you.
Won't you feel reluctant
to throw it away?
Then I'll keep it?
My favorite is still the dishes
you cook for me.
Look at you.
It's the best food on the earth.
Done?
Yes.
What do you think?
This is Cape Town's unlikeness-ism.
We pursue freedom
and are not limited by the model.
We can paint whatever we want.
What do you think?
Why did you ask me to be
your model then?
What?
Nothing.
I said, your painting is nice.
The style is really new.
It doesn't care about the details,
and is unique.
Really?
Why did you say it's nice
no matter what I painted?
Can't you give me some opinions?
To me, whatever you do is right.
Without Wenwen coming out here
with us,
it feels good.
I feel the same.
This is sugarcoating. Don't buy it.
Uncle Jiang is so handsome.
Why do you hate him?
You can't betray father.
No, you can't take it.
You can't take it.
This is sugarcoating.
No.
You can't take it.
Calm down.
- Calm down.
- You can't take it.
You can't take it.
- Calm down.
- You can't take it.
You can't take it.
- Calm down.
- You can't take it.
- Let go.
No.
Where's Wenwen?
Mother, Wenwen is gone!
He's gone?
How did that happen?
Where did he go?
Wenwen.
Where was he?
He was here.
I'm here.
Come here.
Did I change back?
You did.
Naughty boy.
Mother, is my zodiac tortoise?
Wenwen,
do you remember that I told you
you must control your emotions
and don't let your system get heated?
It's because in our gene,
there's this awesome mode
where we'd become a tortoise.
As soon as the temperature
reaches certain degree,
we'd easily become a tortoise.
What do we do
once we become a tortoise?
The ice cube that we saw just now.
Yes, use the ice cube to cool down.
So smart.
When you go to the primary school,
you can't attend
the physical education class.
Primary school?
Aunt Xiaobu, can I join?
Yes.
Tangtang,
you're at the age of going to school.
Of course you can go to school.
Great!
I want to share with more children!
My Uncle Jiang is super handsome!
Come here.
Tangtang, what did you just say?
I want to share with other children
about
my father who is more handsome
than Uncle Jiang.
Childish.
That's right.
Look.
Fireworks.
Colorful fireworks.
- Green color.
- Is it nice?
Is it nice?
It's a new year in another five minutes.
- It's nice.
- Time flies.
It has been a decade
before we realize it.
It's a new year.
Do you have any wishes?
I hope that I get to eat
more nice food this year.
I want to wear more beautiful dresses.
Me, too.
Liangliang, what about you?
I hope that Cape Town Planet
will cancel the parcel delivery.
Then Uncle Jiang will not be
able to send any presents.
That's cool.
That's my son right here.
I hope that before
the parcel delivery is canceled,
Uncle Jiang will give me
a digital component that
can stop me from turning
into a tortoise.
You're smart.
Then I'll not turn into a tortoise.
A tortoise is cute, too.
I hope
we can have more time to ourselves.
I hope...
Wenwen, do you want a younger sister?
Yes.
I think we can have two more children.
Let's surpass
Fang Leng and Xiaoqi, okay?
Xiaoqi.
Let Tangtang and Liangliang
sleep earlier today.
Sleep earlier?
Yes.
Sleep earlier.
What's your father trying to do?
I don't know.
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one!
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year, Xiaoqi!
- Happy New Year!
- Happy New Year, Xiaobu!
Happy New Year!
- Happy New Year!
Xiaoqi.
What wish are you making this year?
Happy New Year!
My wish is that
our happy story
can continue on
and there will be season three.
I hope your wish will come true.
Happy New Year, mother.
- Happy New Year, mother.
- Come here.
Let me hug you.
- Look at the fireworks.
Look at the fireworks, my precious.
Isn't it beautiful?
- Yes.
Do you like it?
Don't fall down.
(This is the real end)
♪Whenever you're approaching me♪
♪Why is it familiar and strange
at the same time?♪
♪The hidden memories
are triggered suddenly♪
♪The flashing images
bring back my heartbeat♪
♪I'm afraid that I'd forget♪
♪You're the reason I followed♪
♪The faithfulness in my palms♪
♪Only when you're holding tight♪
♪That I can stand still
even when things are against me♪
♪Even though the story goes back in time
and starts all over♪
♪I'd never forget the gentleness
deep in your eyes♪
♪It takes only a moment
to fall in love with you♪
♪But it takes forever
to forget about you♪
♪I'll always remember your true love♪
♪I want to own nothing else
besides that♪
♪Even though the story goes back in time
and starts all over♪
♪I'd never forget the gentleness
deep in your eyes♪
♪It takes only a moment
to fall in love with you♪
♪But it takes forever
to forget about you♪