♪In the face of turmoil♪
♪Your roots hold firmly♪
♪To this piece of land♪
♪Chasing after the waves♪
♪My leaves flutter across♪
♪The horizon♪
♪Gazing from afar♪
♪At the end of the world♪
♪Is eternity♪
♪When we meet and then part♪
♪When we rely on each other
and then drift apart♪
♪I have never forgotten♪
♪As the glinting of swords cut♪
♪Through the mottled sky♪
♪The falling dreams♪
♪Shatter in the wind♪
♪As the wind breaks through the waves♪
♪It watches thousands of sails cross♪
♪The vast land and the boundless sea♪
♪Armor and red robes flying high♪
♪In the face of bitterness,
intense emotions, and joyful adventure♪
♪I only wish you to be by my side♪
♪Making the most of what life offers♪
♪Like towering trees with interconnected
roots, I'll accompany you to the ends♪
♪Watching fireflies land
on our shoulders♪
♪No regrets, no doubts in this world♪
=Wonderland of Love=
=Episode 20=
Do you think
you can change Lord Qin's mind?
Lord Qin
has a soft heart
despite his hard exterior.
Others look at him as someone
who fights and kills
on countless battlefields.
But actually, he has a soft
and kind heart.
With the right words,
I'm sure I can change his mind.
His Majesty has ordered Lord Qin
to reflect on his wrongdoings.
Master said that many have written
a letter of complaint
against Lord Qin, right?
When a tree is tall and strong,
it will be buffeted by wind.
Lord Qin
has made a great achievement this time.
So, others are envious of him.
Now, His Majesty is in a fit of anger.
If Lord Qin refuses to bend to him,
I'm afraid that it'll drive a wedge
between them.
And it'll badly affect
Lord Qin's future.
Greetings, Lord Qin.
Miss Gu.
I should've visited
Prime Minister Gu in person.
But I can't simply
leave my residence now.
Please apologise to him on my behalf
when you go back.
You are too courteous.
Actually, I'm not here today
on behalf of my father.
I'm here on my own volition today.
I have something
to give you.
You are too kind, Miss Gu.
I have everything I need here.
I shouldn't accept a gift from you.
This is embroidered by me.
I visited many old friends
in the capital.
And luckily, some of them
had seen your biological mother before.
So, I embroidered
this portrait of Madam Liu
according to their descriptions.
After I was done,
I showed it to those
who knew Madam Liu.
According to them, this portrait
looks exactly like her.
Lord Qin.
It took Miss Gu a long time
to look for those
who had seen Madam Liu before.
And she spent a long time asking them
to describe Madam Liu to her.
Then, she made a draft
and worked on this portrait
day and night.
Until her eyes were red.
Finally, she managed
to finish this portrait in time.
Your Highness.
It's indeed saddening
not to be able to grow up
under a mother's care.
But I'm sure that Madam Liu
will feel gratified if she knows
how valiant and capable you are.
Thank you, Miss Gu.
I'll accept
this portrait then.
You are an intelligent
and understanding man.
I'm sure you know
that Madam Liu would not want you
to quarrel with His Majesty
over her title.
Look, Your Highness.
I used gold and silver threads,
to embroider this portrait.
If you want to hang up her portrait
to be used for memorial purposes,
The color
won't fade from getting smoked
by the incense.
That's very thoughtful of you, Miss Gu.
I'm really grateful to you.
You are too kind.
I know
you can't have a guest here
for too long.
I'll get going now.
Young Lady.
I thought you wanted
to convince Lord Qin
to apologise to His Majesty.
Why didn't you say anything about it?
And you left in a hurry.
I was wrong.
Lord Qin is very serious about the title
of his mother.
Just now, from his expression,
if I tried to change his mind,
he would be unhappy.
Moreover,
he has accepted the portrait of Madam Liu.
Whenever he sees
the portrait after this,
he'll feel grateful to me.
Since I've achieved what I want,
I shouldn't outstay my welcome.
Is he really going to give up
his title as Lord Qin?
Will His Majesty punish him again?
He is the chosen one.
Things will go well for him.
For someone like Lord Qin,
others
may be able to defeat him in this round,
but they'll never
be able to win the game.
You are back.
I'm back.
Stop looking at me.
She didn't reply to your letter.
She didn't even open your letter.
I'm not waiting for her reply.
But to be honest,
What Miss Cui said
makes sense.
She said that in this current situation,
you should treat it as if it's a war.
When should you attack
and when
should you stop and regroup?
Actually,
you know what you have to do.
What's that?
That's a portrait of my mother.
They say that this portrait
looks exactly like her.
I've never seen her before.
This portrait
is very well embroidered.
It's almost lifelike.
Yes.
It's from Miss Gu.
She said that she spent
a long time embroidering it.
It's from Miss Gu?
Looks like Miss Gu
really cares about you.
Shiqi.
Is she interested in you?
Me and her
are totally different people.
Beauty is in the eye of the beholder.
I am
only interested in Miss Cui.
Miss Cui
didn't even read your letter.
Has the Grand Governor gotten better?
The physician is neutralizing the toxin
with acupuncture paired
with secret medicine.
According to him, most of the toxin
has been neutralized.
This poison
is lethal and lasts for a long time.
Grand Governor.
(Qingyun Temple)
Back then, I promised Lord Qin
that if he vowed to protect
the great imperial grandson
and put him on the throne,
I would come up with a way
to poison Sun Jing.
I was even prepared
to die together with him.
But I never thought
that I would fail.
And he even escaped to Tong Pass.
I failed to keep up
the end of my bargain.
Your Highness.
You did your best.
Everything was in heaven's hands.
Lord Qin sent me a letter yesterday.
He wrote that although Sun Jing
was defeated for now,
the threat remained unbroken.
We still need to be cautious.
Write a letter to General Han
to ask him to keep
the great imperial grandson
hidden for now.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
We have a letter from Consort Xiao.
How is my mother?
Lord Qin reclaimed Xichang.
But I didn't receive any letter
from my mother.
I was worried
that something had happened to her.
Don't worry.
Consort Xiao is alive and well.
She has
settled down in Qingyun Temple
outside of Xichang.
Now that the capital
has been reclaimed,
can we return to the city now?
Your Highness.
Consort Xiao sent us a letter
to ask us to bear with it
for a while longer.
Sun Jing has taken over Tong Pass.
We can trust
Lord Qin in the capital.
But Lord Xin and Lord Qi
are driven by wild ambitions.
Consort Xiao
has asked us
to be careful and stay hidden.
I'm afraid that there are still many
who want to hurt you.
I understand.
Lord Xin wants to lead
the Zhenxi Army to Changzhou?
Yes.
During the court meeting today,
my father asked me
to lead our army to Changzhou
to stop Sun Jing from summoning
the troops he sent to Baiyue.
And Lord Xin volunteered
to lead the army himself.
And some of the pedantic ministers said
that since the founding of this country,
the position of the commander-in-chief
has always been held by the lords.
So, they agreed
that it was best
to let Lord Xin lead the army.
That's ridiculous.
Have they forgotten how he lost Luoyang?
If he leads the army,
it's like sending the Zhenxi Army
on a suicide mission.
Not only that,
he dragged Lord Qi into it with him.
He said that Lord Qi could help him
with his wisdom.
In the end,
they almost managed
to convince His Majesty.
Has His Majesty given his decree?
He hasn't officially given his decree
to the Palace Secretariat.
But it's obvious
where His Majesty stands.
He's going to appoint Lord Qin
as the commander-in-chief,
Lord Qi as the great general
and me as the vanguard.
All three troops
of the Zhenxi Army
will head to Changzhou.
Lord Xin is trying to kill
two birds with one stone.
He wants to stay in Changzhou
to wait until his opponent is worn out.
If he can destroy
Sun Jing's troops that sent to Baiyue,
he can earn himself a great merit.
Secondly,
he wants to take away the military power
of the Zhenxi Army.
That's what my father said too.
My father also said
that Lord Xin has been eyeing
the title of Crown Prince
for a while now.
But he has yet to achieve anything.
In terms of reputation,
he's no match for you.
That's why he can't wait
to go to Changzhou to win this victory.
The troops of Sun Jing sent to Baiyue
is made up of veterans who have
a lot of experience in battles.
They may be tired,
but it doesn't mean
that they can be easily defeated.
Lord Xin is flatulent and arrogant.
He doesn't know how to lead an army.
Lord Qi
is a little bit smart
but he's not courageous enough.
Not only they can't win
a battle together,
their incompetence
will only lead the army to death.
Bite it.
Come. Bite it.
- Bit it.
- Mine is going to lose.
Your Majesty.
What is it?
Go away.
Your Majesty.
Lord Qin has written a letter to you.
Please read it.
I asked him to reflect
on his wrongdoings, right?
Does he know
what he did wrong?
Why is he writing a letter to me?
I won't read it.
Take it away.
Father.
Maybe you should read it.
If Li Ni
makes any outrageous requests,
you can reject him.
(A Letter to the Emperor)
(I've been thinking
about it day and night.)
(And I haven't been able
to sleep fitfully.)
(I've gone against you)
(for the title of my mother.)
(She has passed away.)
(And as her son,)
(I respected and loved her
while she was alive)
(and I mourn her now that
she has passed away.)
(She'll forever live in my heart.)
(The other ministers took pity on me)
(and regarded my expostulation)
(as an act of filial piety.)
(However, the proper rite of etiquette)
(is to confer the title
of Lady of Bright Deportment to my mother.)
(I dare not go against it.)
(I'll respect the decision
that you've made.)
I already wrote a letter to His Majesty
to confer the title
of Lady of Bright Deportment to my mother
to quell the ongoing discussion.
I'm sure His Majesty
will pass down his decree
within the next few years.
Your Highness.
When you go back,
please ask
Prime Minister Gu
to send the Ministry of Rites
to the imperial mausoleum
to handle the memorial ceremony
of the late empress.
Are you...
Only the child of the empress
can lead this ceremony.
I'm sure Lord Xin will not want
to miss this chance to lead the ceremony
as the son of the empress.
To be honest,
I don't want to let Lord Xin and Lord Qi
lead the army to Changzhou.
I got it.
I will relay your message
to my father.
Father.
What did Li Ni write
in his letter?
He wrote that he didn't want
to make things difficult for me.
So, he requested
to confer the title
of Lady of Bright Deportment to his mother.
At first, he rather gave up
his title as Lord Qin
because of the title of his mother.
And he embarrassed you
during the court meeting.
Why would he suddenly
write a letter of apology to you?
That's why
it's necessary to set an example
out of him to warn the others.
Look.
He has realised his mistakes
after asking him
to reflect on his wrongdoings.
Li Ni may sound remorseful
in his letter.
But maybe
he still holds a grudge against you.
Since he has already admitted
his mistakes,
I think I should confer
the title of Worthy Consort
to his mother.
After all, you and Lai's mother
has the title of Empress.
Those ministers were right too.
I have only three sons.
But only his mother
is conferred the title
of Lady of Bright Deportment.
That's indeed inappropriate.
He wrote this letter of apology to you
at this time
just because he wants
to lead the army to Changzhou.
If you let him lead the army
as soon as he admits his mistakes,
he'll become even more overbearing.
If you do that,
he will neither fear
nor respect you in the future.
Don't worry.
Since asking him to reflect
on his mistakes is effective,
I'll let him
do that for a while longer.
Lieutenant He.
Lord Qin has been grounded
for so long.
Why are you
only visiting him now?
He wrote a letter to His Majesty
to confer the title
of Lady of Bright Deportment to his mother.
But after the Ministry of Rites
received the decree from His Majesty,
in the end, her mother is conferred
the title of Worthy Consort.
It is now a foregone conclusion.
Lord Qin has already given in.
Isn't that the end
of this matter?
It can settle a dispute.
But once heart is hurt,
it can't be healed that easily.
I have to pay him a visit.
(Lord Qin's Residence)
Lieutenant He.
It's not easy for us to sneak in.
But Lord Qin's Residence is huge.
Where will he be?
You have the whistle, right?
Hurry up and ask Ear to lead us the way.
You are right.
Taozi, Lieutenant He.
Why are you here?
Take her
to Lord Qin at once.
Okay. Come with me.
Let's go.
Bring me more liquor.
Bring me more liquor!
Just put it down.
You don't have to serve me.
Are you sure you don't want me
to pour you the liquor?
It's saddening to drink by yourself.
I'll drink with you.
Why are you here?
I'm here to see if you are enjoying
an extravagant life full of liquor
and beautiful ladies in your residence.
I'm not living an extravagant life.
But right now, I have
a beautiful lady by my side.
Shiqi.
Are you okay?
Not really.
My mother
died while giving birth to me.
Ever since
I came to this world,
I've never had the chance
to be filial to her.
She came from a humble origin.
She was just like a weed
in Lord Liang's Residence before this.
No one cared about her
and no one noticed her.
Even many years after her death,
she didn't even have a title.
On that court that day,
I wanted to fight for her to give her
a proper title even if it meant
I would lose my title as Lord Qin.
Even if...
Even if it was just an empty title.
But they refused to even give her
an empty title.
My father
refused to give her anything.
In the past, I knew
that my father didn't like me.
He blamed me for my mother's death.
I thought
that he actually cared a little bit
about my mother.
But now, I realised
that he doesn't
care at all
about my mother's death.
He despises her humble origin.
She's no one to him.
Tell me.
Wasn't it pointless for my mother to die
giving birth to me?
She had suffered a lot
for me too.
According to the others,
she had taken so much medicine
that the residue could be piled up
as high as a small hill.
But when my mother was still alive,
she always told me
that the best thing
that she had done in this life
was giving birth to me.
Shiqi.
The saying about giving birth
to an evil child during an evil month
is utter nonsense
said by foolish people.
Your mother
had done so much to give life to you.
She wouldn't want
to see you blaming yourself like this.
She would want you
to live a free and easy life.
Free and easy.
There's no such thing
as a free and easy life.
At first, I thought
that after reclaiming Xichang,
I could retire from this political war.
But now,
people are plotting
and conspiring
against each other in Xichang,
in this palace
and even in Lord Qin's Residence.
What about me?
I can't even achieve something so minor.
I can't even
get a proper title
for my mother.
I don't know
what else I can do.
I feel
so useless.
I feel like such a loser.
Actually, I'm really upset.
I feel so depressed about this.
I know.
Shiqi.
Actually,
I'm really envious of Great General Cui.
Why?
Because he can always be with you.
I'm here now, right?
But you are going to leave later.
Okay.
I promise you
that I won't leave later.
I won't leave tonight.
Really?
Yes.
Taozi!
You haven't seen me for so long,
why did you run off
earlier?
Because I...
Because I went to get you this.
What's this?
(Astragalus, angelica)
These are the herbs I gathered for you.
Look.
This is astragalus,
and then there's angelica,
this is Chinese peony,
and these.
Some of these herbs
I bought at the medicine shop,
and some I dried myself
after picking them
on the mountain.
In fact,
every time I think of you,
I go to pick herbs.
Every time you miss me?
Let's see,
you've thought about me
one, two, four, six...
You've thought about me
more than 30 times.
Well,
next time, if you miss me,
you can come see me.
You can also write me a letter
like Lord Qin
and Lieutenant He do.
Really?
Of course.
So, Taozi,
have you missed me
all this while?
Guess.
I bet you have.
What makes you so sure?
Because if you didn't miss me,
you wouldn't have asked me
to come see you,
and you wouldn't have asked me
to write you letters
like Mister Shiqi.
Right?
I knew it.
I guess you could say so.
♪A fated relationship♪
♪Yet, playing roles that shouldn't be♪
♪Endless patience♪
♪Desiring to escape this conflict♪
Shiqi.
It's late.
I should leave.
♪Cut off resentment and hatred♪
Don't go.
♪This colorful array across the sky♪
♪Belongs only to you and me♪
Shiqi?
Another city,
and I'll let you go.
If Your Highness wishes,
the entire world
will be yours.
Why bother exchanging me for it?
I don't want the world.
I only want you.
You may not want the world,
but those who desire it
won't let you go easily.
Then let them have the world.
You're the only one
I want.
♪I'm willing to
abandon this world for you♪
♪No regrets in this lifetime♪
♪No matter how far the distance is♪
♪I hear your echoes♪
♪The moment when our shoulders
brush against each other♪
♪It was as if a meteor
was stopped mid-air♪
♪A familiar back♪
♪Bringing back the memories of our love♪
♪How can I forget?♪
♪You're in every scene♪
♪You're the dawn of anticipation,
hearts aglow♪
♪You're the final answer,
no regrets, no woes♪
♪My unspoken words
are depicted in scrolls♪
♪One after another♪
♪You're the sole vow,
hearts secretly know♪
♪You're the enduring longing,
forever the same♪
♪I'm willing to
abandon this world for you♪
♪No regrets in this lifetime♪
(Lord Qin's Residence)
♪Never apart no matter what♪
♪May Heaven and Earth
bear witness to our love♪
Mister Shiqi.
You're finally awake.
What time is it?
It's past noon.
I remember...
I remember I was drinking
in the pavilion last night,
and I got drunk.
And I had a beautiful dream.
What kind of dream?
A very,
very happy dream.
It felt so real.
You must have dreamt of Lieutenant He.
But there's no way she was here.
I think you've caught
a serious case
of lovesickness.
You were drinking
by yourself last night.
I wanted to drink with you,
but you threw me out.
Right.
Lieutenant He, have some.
You eat it.
I don't have an appetite.
Well, that's understandable.
You were up all night.
Shall we find an inn
in the town ahead
and rest for half a day
before continuing our journey?
No need.
I took a nap
last night.
You've traveled
a long way,
travelling day and night,
just to see Lord Qin,
why didn't you stay longer?
Is it enough
just to talk to him
for a little bit?
As long as I see him,
I'm at ease.
If someone else finds out,
there'll be a lot of complications.
I only wonder
how long it will take for him
to get over
his grief and guilt?
Either way, I still think
two lovers should always be
together forever.
Just talking for a while
is hardly enough.
I think someone
just wants to be with her Ear
for a long, long time.
Lieutenant He!
You don't say.
I've only been away from him for a while
and I miss him already.
What about you?
Do you miss Lord Qin?
Indeed,
not seeing each other for a day
feels like months already.
That's right.
(Shiqi.)
(Wolong)
Where have you been?
Taozi was here yesterday.
She said she wanted dried fruits,
so I bought some this morning.
I was just about to find someone
to deliver them to her.
Taozi came yesterday?
Yes.
She came with Lieutenant He.
I wonder
where she is now
and if she stopped for a meal.
♪Between the moonlight, your vows♪
♪Fall in my heart♪
When did they leave?
They left before dawn.
Lieutenant He said it wouldn't be good
if the imperial guardians saw them,
so they climbed over the wall
and left before sunrise.
I need to see her.
I have so much to say to her.
Mister Shiqi!
But His Majesty ordered you
to reflect in seclusion.
Isn't this defying his decree?
So what if I am?
Even if the heavens themselves come,
I must see her!
♪You lead me
to break through this night♪
♪Carrying the shattered world♪
♪You give me a firm belief♪
♪In adversity,
the only light is love that never dies♪
♪Every separation I've endured♪
♪Every second
searching for you in the night♪
(Tea)
Welcome.
Please have a seat.
Would you like
to try our new tea?
It's refreshing and cooling.
We'll have that and some food too.
All right.
Lieutenant He.
We should reach Luoyang
before it turns dark.
This is an interesting place.
You give flowers with tea?
Enjoy.
Lieutenant He, try it.
Smells great.
Why did you pour another cup of tea?
Are you still not coming out?
I'll make myself scarce.
What are you doing here?
I came to see you.
Didn't you see enough last night?
I was too drunk
to see clearly last night.
You've had a long trip.
You came all this way to see me.
I appreciate it.
I'm happy to do it.
I don't find it an arduous task.
I'll be going to you
soon as well.
Aren't you worried
that your words will be misunderstood?
I thought you'd come with soldiers
to reclaim Luoyang.
My father has always wanted
to battle Lord Qin
on the battlefield.
Are you giving him
the opportunity?
If he sends you as the vanguard,
then I'll most probably lose.
It might be a bit embarrassing
to be captured.
You must show me mercy.
Rest assured, Your Highness.
If you're truly in danger,
I will come to your aid.
Good.
I am grateful for your promise.
However, Lord Qin is truly
too valiant.
Please don't give me
such an opportunity.
I'll take your auspicious words.
Then
you'll always owe me a favour,
and you won't be able to repay it.
Li Ni is using a retreat as
a form of advancement.
He hypocritically submitted
a letter to Father,
expressing his wish
to have his birth mother
titled as  Lady of Bright Deportment.
However, Father, being benevolent,
bestowed the title of Worthy Consort
upon his mother.
Li Ni isn't reflecting in seclusion.
He's constantly scheming on how
to regain control of the Zhenxi Army!
Jun,
Father asked you to stay
and oversee the Mother's ceremony,
so he could only appoint you
as the commander-in-chief.
He let General Pei Yuan
lead the troops to Changzhou alone.
We need to be careful
of Li Ni's influence in Changzhou,
or even
taking over the Zhenxi Army.
Worry not.
As the commander-in-chief,
I won't let them have that chance.
On this mission to Changzhou, I only said
that the situation was critical.
I've instructed Pei Yuan
to lead 30% of the forces
and food supplies ahead.
He must think
that there are
larger reinforcements coming.
He wishes.
Pei Yuan only follow Li Ni's orders,
doesn't he?
If this battle ends in a major defeat,
I'll see if Li Ni
can still protect him.
Grand Governor,
you've recently recovered
from poisoning.
(Tong Pass)
You should rest.
Li Ni
is cunning.
I suspect he's planning to intercept
troops I sent to Baiyue which I'm recalling
in Changzhou.
News from the capital.
Li Ni has been relieved
of his commander-in-chief position
and ordered to reflect in seclusion.
The court may dispatch
Lord Xin and Lord Qi
as commanders
to send troops southward.
A general's incompetence is a liability
to all three armies.
With an incompetent ruler
like Lord Liang,
who imprisons Li Ni,
he's as good as cutting off his own arm.
Grand Governor!
Grand Governor, the ones sent to track
the great imperial grandson
have reported
that he seems to be hiding
in a village near Xichang.
Issue the order to capture
the great imperial grandson alive.
The others are to be executed
without mercy.
Yes.
It's truly a timely opportunity.
Destiny is here,
and fortune favors me.
Pei Yuan
sent an urgent message,
stating that the expedition
against Baiyue has crossed
the Han River
and is heading straight for Changzhou.
He urges the court to provide
additional provisions for Changzhou
and requests reinforcements
from the capital.
Father,
in my humble opinion,
the so-called expedition to Baiyue
returning from afar must be exhausted.
Moreover, with the long march
and no food supplies on the way,
they are only a few
tens of thousands of people.
Pei Yuan, being from a military family
and leading troops for many years,
should be able
to handle the situation.
General Pei Yuan
has requested aid from the court.
If the court ignores it,
it may upset the Pei family.
Lai,
you are showing compassion like a woman.
The Pei family, powerful as they may be,
are still Father's subjects.
If we constantly appease them
and grant their every request,
where does Father's authority stand?
But the court
has only allocated them
30% of military provisions.
It is indeed not much.
Father,
in the past,
when Li Ni led the Zhenxi Army,
the court never provided food supplies.
Yet, the Zhenxi Army still marched
all the way from Laolan Pass,
reclaiming the two cities.
Now,
the Zhenxi Army has been deployed again
with 30% supplies.
The so-called request for reinforcements
is just an attempt
to receive benefits
without contributing.
These are unspoken practices
in the military.
Do not be deceived, Father.
You are the commander-in-chief.
How do you think
we should respond to Pei Yuan?
In my humble opinion,
the court must issue a command
instructing Pei Yuan not to delay
and immediately launch an attack
from Changzhou
to annihilate
the Sun rebels leading
the expedition against Baiyue.
They're messing around
without any idea what they're doing!
Where are the reinforcements they promised
General Pei Yuan and the Zhenxi Army?
When it came time to march,
he was only given
30% of the forces and food supplies.
Now, without providing provisions
or reinforcements,
they even ordered us
to go out from Changzhou
to face the enemy!
Isn't this just sending
our Zhenxi Army soldiers
to their deaths?
Deliver this to Taozi.
We're already in this state,
and you're still writing to Lieutenant He?
The court refuses to send reinforcements
to support Changzhou.
Instead, they want Pei Yuan
to launch an attack.
I can't leave the capital now.
The only option left is
to seek assistance from the Cui Army
to support Changzhou.
I'll leave at once.
Mister Shiqi,
you want the Cui Army
to relieve Changzhou.
Is this going to work?
Well, I mentioned in the letter
that I'm trapped in Changzhou.
She can't just abandon me, can she?
What are you looking at?
I'm looking
at the face of the world's
number one pretty boy.
When the situation calls for it,
one must humble oneself.
A real man can adapt to circumstances.
If a letter
can save Changzhou,
then you're certainly a pretty boy
with skills no one before has mastered
and no one after will.
I dare not accept such flattery.
Looking at this because you miss him?
I don't think His Highness Lord Qin
did the right thing.
Why not?
He must know
that you'll keep fiddling with it
whenever you have free time.
Yet, he chooses to make the doll
out of straw.
What if it gets worn out
from all the handling
in just a few days?
He should have carved one
out of wood.
That would have been more durable.
Xie Chang'er thought ahead.
He wouldn't have come up
with the idea of making you
a whistle otherwise.
After all, that never breaks.
Looking at it this way,
Lord Qin was indeed
not thoughtful enough.
Lieutenant He!
Speak of the devil
and he shall show up.
An urgent letter from Mister Shiqi.
(Changzhou is in great danger. There'll
be no reinforcements from the court.)
(I can only ask you to save us
from the predicament.)
Your Majesty!
Urgent report from Changzhou!
What's the situation?
General Pei Yuan launched an attack.
But after struggling for two days,
they were was outnumbered
and besieged by Sun rebels.
The Zhenxi Army was almost wiped out,
and General Pei Yuan
has been severely wounded.
What about Changzhou City?
General Pingliang Cui Yi
arrived with the Cui Army
and successfully eliminated
the Sun rebels.
General Pei Yuan took the opportunity
to lead the remaining Zhenxi Army
across the river
and set up camp about a hundred li
from Changzhou.
But...
Cui Yi and the Cui Army
entered Changzhou City.
What?
Cui Yi has taken Changzhou City?
Father,
Changzhou is a crucial
military stronghold.
Whether it falls into Sun Jing's hands
or Cui Yi's,
it will be greatly disadvantageous for us.
Father,
Pei Yuan lost Changzhou City.
He deserves severe punishment
for his crime!
Jun,
now is not the time
to discuss blame and punishments.
Changzhou was lost
under Pei Yuan's command.
Why can't we hold him accountable?
Father refused
General Pei Yuan's request
for reinforcements.
Great General Pei Xian personally
came to the palace,
and pleaded Father
to send reinforcements
to the Zhenxi Army.
But, Jun, you said
General Pei Yuan was afraid of battle
and intentionally avoiding it.
Then, three imperial edicts
were sent to Changzhou,
forcing him to engage in battle.
Now that Changzhou is lost,
if we try to blame
General Pei Yuan for it,
I'm afraid
the Pei family will not stand for it.
Do something!
That wretch Cui Yi!
He seized Dongdu last time,
and now he's taken Changzhou!
If this continues,
what's the point of me being the Emperor?
How can I face the world?
Father,
there's someone I'd like to recommend.
If this person
leads the troops,
they can surely recapture Changzhou.
Who?
Li Ni.
Absolutely not!
Li Ni has been ordered
to reflect in seclusion.
How can he lead troops?
He has been skilled in warfare
since he was a child.
He's fought with Sun Jing
and the Cui Army
and has never lost a battle.
Besides, he is the only one
who has always had close ties
with the Pei family.
If we let Ni lead the troops
to Changzhou,
he may be able to dispel the discontent
of the Pei family
and revive the army's spirit.
Li Ni is arrogant and reckless.
Should his previous insubordination
be overlooked just so?
Who else can lead the troops
in this situation?
Will you personally
lead the expedition, Jun?
You are Father's eldest legitimate son.
Even if Father approves,
the court and the ministers
would never allow you
to expose yourself to such danger.
Enough.
Lai makes a valid point.
Issue the decree.
Lord Qin has reflected upon his actions.
His punishment shall be lifted.
He will lead the troops
to reinforce Changzhou at once.
Yes.
♪If I forget the fleeting of time♪
♪Waiting for memories♪
♪To shatter and sink♪
♪The emotional scars in your heart♪
♪Are the entanglement♪
♪I find hard to let go of♪
♪If longing is not forgotten♪
♪I long to return
to the very first moment♪
♪The affection we had
in our fateful situation♪
♪How I wish to keep it for you♪
♪If love still remembers♪
♪The promises we made♪
♪Even if this love hurts me♪
♪I'll continue living for you♪
♪Holding onto the memories♪
♪Waiting is my persistence♪
♪If love remembers♪
♪The promise I made to you♪
♪Despite going against fate♪
♪I have no regrets loving you♪
♪I'm willing to sacrifice for you♪
♪As I wait for your answer♪
♪If love remembers♪
♪The promise I made to you♪
♪Despite going against fate♪
♪I have no regrets loving you♪
♪I'm willing to sacrifice for you♪
♪As I wait for your answer♪