♪In the face of turmoil♪
♪Your roots hold firmly♪
♪To this piece of land♪
♪Chasing after the waves♪
♪My leaves flutter across♪
♪The horizon♪
♪Gazing from afar♪
♪At the end of the world♪
♪Is eternity♪
♪When we meet and then part♪
♪When we rely on each other
and then drift apart♪
♪I have never forgotten♪
♪As the glinting of swords cut♪
♪Through the mottled sky♪
♪The falling dreams♪
♪Shatter in the wind♪
♪As the wind breaks through the waves♪
♪It watches thousands of sails cross♪
♪The vast land and the boundless sea♪
♪Armor and red robes flying high♪
♪In the face of bitterness,
intense emotions, and joyful adventure♪
♪I only wish you to be by my side♪
♪Making the most of what life offers♪
♪Like towering trees with interconnected
roots, I'll accompany you to the ends♪
♪Watching fireflies land
on our shoulders♪
♪No regrets, no doubts in this world♪
=Wonderland of Love=
=Episode 14=
You have high moral integrity
and an indomitable spirit.
I admire you very much.
I'm honored to be able to see you today.
Mister Shiqi, you're
too courteous here.
I've long heard of your talents
from the military since long ago.
Now that I've met you,
the rumors were definitely true.
Mister Shiqi, I wonder
why you risked your life
to enter the capital?
Sun Jing overthrew the nation
and disrupted the order of the court.
He led to
the people's suffering.
Prime Minister Gu, today I see you,
I hope that you can contact the loyal
old subordinates and noble families
and launch an attack
with the Zhenxi Army
so that we could take back Xichang.
Sun Jing is paranoid.
Ever since the fall
of Luoyang's Duke Zheng,
he has kept a close eye on
the old subordinates and noble families
in the court.
To be honest,
if it weren't for
your elaborate arrangements,
it would've been difficult
for us to meet today.
Mister, are you here to buy fabric?
Mister,
take a look at our fabric.
Mister, are you buying it for yourself?
Or are you buying it for your relatives?
Mister?
I'm just taking a look.
Mister,
you can check out this batch.
It's quite popular this year.
Mister.
I'm just taking a look.
Attacking the city is a military feat.
As long as the old subordinates and noble families
side with us and assist us in secret.
Then, the army will take a long time
to enter the city.
If there's no one to receive us
inside the city,
I'm afraid it'll be chaotic
when the army enters the city.
So we need to depend on
the noble families to keep an eye
on the important neighborhoods
and offices.
Or, we'll lose the people's support
if the livelihood is destroyed.
Naturally. This can be planned
in secret.
The city's granaries, oil mills, wells,
irrigation canals and so on
are located in the neighborhood.
All noble families
have their private armies.
By then,
they'll definitely protect
these checkpoints.
Thank you, Prime Minister Gu.
Mister Shiqi,
seems like you're confident
that you can storm the city.
I do have a plan or two.
This is confidential.
The more people know about this,
the riskier it'll get.
Mister Shiqi,
you don't need to tell me about it.
By then,
I'll follow
your arrangements
and accomplish
the task you gave me.
If you're not buying anything,
you shouldn't bother other customers.
Don't you agree?
Get lost!
Where did this guy come from?
This does look good on me.
Father.
What are you doing?
Sorry about that, dear guests.
This weirdo
just barged inside all of a sudden.
Leave!
Our encounter with Prime Minister Gu
was a narrow escape.
It's all thanks to your plan.
Shiqi, you're actually thanking me.
My trip wasn't in vain indeed.
Refreshing vine tea is available here!
Mister and Miss,
would you like some?
Do you still remember
the day we had tea and made food
under the straw hut?
Of course I do.
This time,
if we can take back Xichang
and eliminate Sun Jing,
by then,
we can travel the Wonderland
on horseback.
Your Highness, by then, I'm just afraid
that you might be too busy
with official affairs
that you forgot about
your promise
to bring me around.
That will never happen.
No matter how busy or tired,
I will never forget you
or my promise
to bring you to the Wonderland.
The son of the heavens
has ascended the throne!
This proclamation is well-written,
especially the part
where it criticized me.
Sun Jing must die
for the innocent to be saved, huh?
Grand Governor, please spare me.
Why should I?
This is good.
Although the palace
has a tight security,
they rescued the dead Lord Liang,
from the palace in secret.
After that, he was revived.
He ascended the throne in Dongdu
and made himself emperor too.
Our enemy actually
has such fearsome abilities
and resourcefulness.
I wonder
if I'll lose my head
when I sleep tonight?
Grand Governor, please forgive me!
There's no need to interrogate
the suspects.
Execute all of them.
As for all those stubborn old subordinates,
send our troops there
to escort them into the palace
so that they wouldn't stay restless.
Yes,
Grand Governor.
Should we shut all nine cities' gates
and forbid anyone
from entering or exiting
to search for the suspects?
Since they've sent their men to Xichang
to spread these proclamations around,
naturally, they wanted
to perturb the people.
We shouldn't fall for their trick.
Li Ni and his army are closing in.
Once we shut the city gates,
the people will be restless.
It'll be detrimental to us.
Grand Governor, you're right.
However,
we should examine all those
who enter or exit the cities strictly.
Do a thorough search
in the cities as well.
You must capture the spies
who spread these proclamations around.
Chop off their heads
and send them to Luoyang
so that Lord Liang will be terrified.
Lord Liang is a timid man.
If he dies from shock,
it'll turn into
a huge joke.
Yes.
Such foolishness.
They're utterly foolish.
This isn't the right time
for Lord Linzi and Lord Kuaiji
to proclaim Lord Liang
as the emperor.
I thought they welcomed Father back
so that he could be relaxed.
They were just
trying to claim credit.
But I never expected
them to proclaim Father to be the emperor
in Luoyang.
They even announced it to the public.
Such foolishness.
Mister Shiqi,
we're in trouble.
Sun Jing's men are searching for those
who spread the proclamations.
And,
when I came back,
I heard the borough chiefs
sent a message to all shopkeepers
saying that all guests
have to be investigated thoroughly.
The shopkeepers' guarantee
was rendered invalid too.
Seems like
we can't stay here for long.
Although our fake profiles
are the same as the real ones,
the neighborhood in Xichang
is under tight security.
They can tell the difference
as long as they put in some effort.
We're in huge trouble.
I received news that the Imperial Army
has surrounded the Gu Residence.
I dare not follow them
all the way there.
Young Master.
Young Master,
luckily, the herbs delivered
by General Pei Yuan were very potent.
Judging from your pulse,
you're 80% healed.
We can act and rendezvous with our main army
once Lieutenant He is back.
Young Master.
What's the matter?
We received news from Luoyang.
Lord Linzi, Li Jun,
and Lord Kuaiji, Li Lai,
proclaimed Lord Liang as the emperor
in Dongdu.
What?
Those fools.
They're too impatient.
Taozi,
I instructed Lieutenant He
to leave her marks behind
along the way
before she departed.
Enter the capital
and tell her to leave immediately.
I'm afraid Sun Jing will be enraged
after hearing this.
I'm afraid Lieutenant He
will be in danger
if they shut the city gates and search.
Yes, Young Master.
I will go immediately.
Shu,
contact our main army immediately.
Tell them to break camp
and head southward.
If Lieutenant He
is unable to leave,
I will do everything I can to save her.
Yes, Young Master.
Let me go!
Why are you capturing me?
What gives?
Let me go!
I'm not a crook!
What gives?
These two brothers of yours
are too impatient.
They're only good at foiling my plans.
Mister Shiqi, Miss Gu is here.
Have a seat.
Why did you put on a disguise and risked
your life to come at this hour?
About 17 PM,
members of the palace suddenly came
and said that Grand Governor
had summoned Father to the palace.
Although Father wasn't willing to go,
he was afraid that the others
would be implicated.
That's why he let them detain him.
I disguised myself
as a servant during the nighttime
and snuck out of the residence
to tip you guys off.
Miss Gu, it must've been tough.
I wonder how Prime Minister Gu
is doing right now?
I have no idea either.
But back then,
Sun Jing didn't kill my father.
I assume he won't kill him right away.
That's right.
Prime Minister Gu
has a great reputation.
Sun Jing doesn't dare
to kill him that easily.
Miss Gu,
you shouldn't worry too much either.
You guys should leave.
They were searching and catching
potential suspects on my way here.
If...
His Highness, it'll be terrible
if they find you here.
The Gu Family owns several estates.
Your Highness, you can hide there
and lay low for now if it's necessary.
Don't worry.
We have our own arrangements.
But you, Miss Gu,
you shouldn't take any risks
to come out for now.
Ear,
escort Miss Gu back.
Yes.
Miss Gu, please.
Search every house in the vicinity!
Show it to me.
Come on!
You! Stay there!
You, leave.
Stop right there. Are these yours?
What's inside?
What's inside your shirt?
They're already searching
this early in the morning?
I wonder if Xie Chang'er and Bao
could evade them?
Of course they can.
Besides,
they have Taozi's aid.
They'll be here
to rendezvous with us later.
Let me see
if this lady
possesses any suspicious items.
Young lady.
Mister.
How dare you try
to strip my clothes off?
I'll prick you with my beard!
Search every house in the vicinity!
Yes, sir!
Search this place!
Over there!
- Let's go inside.
- Over here.
Check that place.
No one.
Over there.
Today, I'll show you
what I got!
Bao, get out of the way!
Get out of the way!
Bao!
You guys deserved that!
Hurry!
Search the place!
Search!
You two, head over there!
Yes!
Search upstairs!
Let's go!
- Benefactor!
- Hurry!
Benefactor, it's you.
Benefactor?
Your Highness,
we received the latest news.
Grand Governor was enraged ever since
Lord Liang ascended the throne.
Not only did he increase the inspections
in the capital,
but he also detained
many old subordinates,
forbidding them to leave the palace
in fear of them colluding with Lord Liang.
Has the messenger we sent to General Han
returned yet?
He sent us a letter.
He said he had no news of
General Han yet.
However,
he saw the bodies of
General Han's bodyguards.
I assume General Han
has temporarily escaped together
with the great imperial grandson.
No news is a kind of good news too.
Since we can't locate them,
I'm sure no one else can locate them.
Your Highness,
the citizens in the capital
are panicking.
Li Ni and the Zhenxi Army have
entered Tong Pass.
I assume they'll surround Xichang
anytime soon.
Now, we're ordering the people
to stock up more food.
Sun Jing has already relayed
a secret order
to recall the army meant for
conquering Baiyue.
If his army does return,
Xichang is easy to defend
and hard to attack.
Li Ni might not be able to defeat him.
If so, should we...
This isn't our priority.
Our current priority
is to locate General Han
and make sure the great imperial
grandson is safe.
Try to send a message to Li Ni.
I have important matters
to discuss with him.
General Han,
I would've been dead
if you didn't risk your life
to save me again.
Your Highness, this is unnecessary.
I was just fulfilling my duty.
Sun Jing's private cavalry team
was hot on our tails.
Maybe it's because loyalist army
achieved flawless victory.
This might be Sun Jing's last attempt
at struggling.
We've been making hasty retreats
for the past few days.
I wonder if Shiqi
has deployed his troops to Xichang
after restoring the eastern capital
to its former glory?
We'll know
what's going on out there
after shaking off the cavalry team.
Benefactors,
I inquired about the situation
using grocery shopping as my excuse.
Every shop
and inn out there
is searching for foreigners.
They were interrogated
even if they were affiliated
with the government.
Benefactors,
you guys may rest here in peace
for a few days.
If someone finds out,
I have my own way of covering it up.
Madam Yang,
if we continue to stay here,
I'm afraid we'll implicate
you guys eventually.
We should scale the wall
and escape during nighttime.
Taozi sent us a letter.
Tthe inspections were strict.
But luckily, she found Lieutenant He.
And, their current shelter
is safe for now.
However, they're searching
the neighborhood one by one
until they find the suspects.
I'm worried that they might be found out
if it goes on long enough.
However, Lieutenant He
can definitely think of a way
to escape from the city.
Can the hidden shops in the city help us
to contact members of the palace?
Yes.
Let's wait for a little longer.
Until Lieutenant He leaves.
Yes.
How's the preparation for our army?
They'll reach Tong Pass soon.
All right.
I'll visit Pei Yuan first.
I'll tell him that Li Ni
and Lieutenant He are in danger
and that the Cui Army
can provide aid to them.
Tell General Pei Yuan to allow us
to station our troops at Tong Pass first.
Send a message to them.
Tell them to make preparations for it.
Yes.
I have an idea.
It'll ensure that Madam Yang
won't be implicated
even if our identities are exposed.
What idea?
Madam Yang's daughter, Yang Qiniang,
is engaged to a person called Xu Sanlang.
But I've asked Yang Qiniang
about this before.
No one in the vicinity
has seen Xu Sanlang around.
Qiniang,
did you guys go to visit your friends
and relatives in the countryside
after returning from the city?
If, by then,
we have the chance to make our escape,
I'm afraid you guys
have to lay low
in your friends' house
so that your neighbors
won't suspect you.
We actually visited
the house of our relative.
We visited the house of my fiance.
His name is Xu Sanlang.
We're engaged.
But unfortunately,
he went outside to sell fabrics.
If not,
my mother and I wouldn't
need to take the risk
and leave the city
in order to procure food.
I see.
Yang Qiniang told me
that her mother already prepared
her wedding gown and
dowries for her long ago.
They were just waiting for
Xu Sanlang to marry her.
I'm almost the same age as Yang Qiniang.
And, we have similar figures.
By then,
you can pretend to be Xu Sanlang
and come to marry me.
I'll put on the wedding gown
and wedding veil.
By then,
people will think that I'm Yang Qiniang.
Once I enter the carriage,
we can leave the city without
concealing ourselves.
And, we have the wedding documents
as our guarantee.
The city guards won't make things
difficult for us.
This won't do.
If we do so,
not only will we put
Madam Yang in danger,
but it'll also
affect Miss Yang's marriage.
Benefactor, you saved me and my daughter.
Please don't say that.
This is an excellent plan.
And, she's only getting married
under my daughter's name.
There's no risk in that.
Once Sanlang is back,
I'll send my daughter to him in secret
and they can get married.
The grace of dripping water should be
reciprocated by a gushing spring.
Moreover,
Benefactor, you saved our lives.
I can only live in peace
when you're out of danger.
But Madam Yang...
Madam Yang, thank you for your help.
Shiqi, leaving the city as soon as possible
is the wiser option.
If so, Madam Yang, thank you for your help.
(Bliss)
Stop.
Mister.
I'm getting married today.
This is the official wedding document
produced by the village chief.
(Wedding document)
Xu Sanlang of the Xu Family
is marrying Yang Qiniang
of the Yang Family, huh?
Yes.
I'm marrying Yang Qiniang today.
These are He' wedding pastries
on the east street.
Please enjoy them.
(Bliss)
The He Family is known for
their wedding pastries.
I won't interrupt your wedding then.
Go now.
Thank you, Mister.
Let's go.
Your Highness,
although you took
another person's apparel,
you left your wedding suit
in his yard.
You bartered his apparel
with another suit.
You've improved a lot,
since you stole
people's items in the past.
That was an emergency.
Actually,
I do like
my wedding suit.
Lieutenant He!
Taozi.
Young Master sent us a letter.
Sun Jing's men scattered
one of our platoons.
So, he hopes that we can head to Tong Pass
as soon as possible.
Since that's the case,
let's rendezvous somewhere else.
Your Highness, are you
returning to Tong Pass?
Although it's not far away,
the terrain here is complicated.
Let me join you.
So, Your Highness, are you worried
that I might bring harm to Tong Pass
after meeting up with the main army?
Naturally.
You're devious and witty.
I have to keep an eye on you personally.
Let's go.
(Punishment)
Young Master, Taozi just sent a letter.
Lieutenant He has left the city.
What about Li Ni?
Right now, he's still together
with Lieutenant He.
He'll arrive at Tong Pass soon.
Has our army settled down?
Yes, they've settled down at Tong Pass.
Come and look at my handwriting.
One should mete out punishment
to prevent further harm.
Your handwriting looks full
and spirited.
Young Master, seems like
you've fully recovered.
My wounds are definitely healed.
Since that's the case,
we should look back at our past mistakes
and learn from them
so that we won't commit them again.
(Cui Lin)
Cui Lin sent me a letter,
saying that he could launch
a two-pronged attack with me
to recover Tong Pass.
In exchange, I have to withdraw
my troops from Yingzhou.
Cui Lin is Cui Yi's only son.
Cui Yi has exhibited how ambitious he is
ever since leaving Yingzhou.
He intends to rule the world.
Cui Lin has stepped off on the wrong foot.
And, he's recuperating at Tong Pass.
His letter
does make sense.
Back then, the Three Heroes
consist of Pei Xian,
Cui Yi, and I.
After Cui Yi
lost his wife,
he participated in battles
like a crazy madman.
Under such circumstances,
I'm sure
he won't let this opportunity
go to waste.
However,
even if he intends to rule the world,
it also has to depend on
whether he's capable enough to do so.
Yingzhou, which is owned by
the Cui Family, is surrounded.
And now, Cui Lin, his son,
is getting restless because of that.
Grand Governor,
although Cui Lin has
a convincing excuse,
he often
made contact with the Zhenxi Army.
Grand Governor, you need
to be on your toes.
This might be a trick.
This brat
thinks he can trick me.
He's way too young to do so.
Send Cui Lin a message.
Tell him that I can launch a two-pronged attack
together with him.
However,
I will only recall
the army I've dispatched to Yingzhou
after I take over Tong Pass.
Yes.
Your Highness.
General Han.
Are you used to life around here?
Huayang Town is peaceful and quiet.
However,
this place is near Xichang.
Are you sure
we won't be in danger if we stay here?
I'm afraid no one could predict
that we would seek shelter in a town
this near to Xichang.
As the saying goes,
it is dark under the lamp.
Moreover, Sun Jing
is troubled by the Zhenxi Army lately.
He's in a state of
extreme stress right now.
We can stay here peacefully
for the time being.
General Han.
Your Highness, please
get straight to the point.
Will Sun Jing still try to hunt us down
after Lord Liang
has ascended the throne?
I'm afraid he would spend
even more effort to do so.
Although Lord Liang
has ascended the throne,
Your Highness,
you're the official ruler of the empire.
You're the only descendant
of the late crown prince.
Sun Jing knows that too.
If he can capture you alive,
he can take command of the empire
using you as his hostage.
I don't really remember
what Lord Liang
looks like now.
He didn't visit the palace often
before this.
Actually, Lord Liang
is no cause for concern.
Li Ni, Lord Liang's son,
is the one we should be wary of.
Now that Lord Liang
has ascended the throne,
I'm afraid...
Will Shiqi really do that?
Your Highness,
you mustn't trust anyone easily.
Here you go.
Where did you get them?
Lieutenant He gave it another name.
Dried fruits.
Dried fruits?
I heard that it was difficult
to procure them.
I tried it, and I liked it.
Lieutenant He brought me more of them
when she knew that I liked them.
Taozi, thank you so much.
I'm only able to...
That's enough.
I'm only able
to have
such delicious dried fruits
all thanks to Ear.
These dried fruits are pretty good.
What do you mean by that?
Isn't Taozi nice
to everyone here?
Haven't you noticed yet?
Taozi
is especially nice to you.
That's not it.
Taozi is nice to everyone.
Why is she leaving?
Hey, are you dumb?
Go after her!
- Hurry!
- But why?
If not,
she'll poison you in the future.
Come on.
Just go already.
Taozi.
This time, we failed to conquer the city.
However, we alerted them
to our presence.
Seems like we need to come up
with another plan
to take back Xichang.
What plans do you have
after taking back Xichang?
By then,
I'll stop participating in battles.
I'll bring the great imperial grandson
back to the imperial court
and persuade my father
to elect him as the crown prince.
After that, I'll return to Laolan Pass.
What about you?
Will you return to Yingzhou?
Lord Liang has already
ascended the emperor's throne.
You're the emperor's son.
Are you going to return to Laolan Pass
instead of staying in the capital?
I like Laolan Pass
better than Xichang.
If not,
I wouldn't have found an excuse
to make a mistake
and made the late emperor
send me to Laolan Pass.
Back then, you were Lord Liang's son.
You were the most insignificant
imperial grandson out of all of them.
Naturally, you can go anywhere you like.
It's the same for me now.
Since my father likes
my brothers so much,
they can keep him company then.
What about you?
You haven't answered my question yet.
Will you return to Yingzhou?
What?
Your Highness, are you afraid
that the Cui Army will act like Sun Jing
and try to conquer Xichang
instead of returning to Yingzhou?
I made a wish
when I left Yingzhou.
I hope that we can stop the war,
return peace to the world,
and make sure the people
lead stable lives.
If, one day,
we do take back Xichang successfully,
peace will be restored
to the world by then.
Why would we need to start another war?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm too petty.
Lieutenant He, please be magnanimous
and forgive me for my pettiness.
If so, what do you want to do
after peace has been
restored to the world?
Me?
I haven't thought of that yet.
The world is a vast place.
I haven't been to Laolan Pass before.
There are many places in the world
that I haven't visited yet.
So,
I wish to explore all of them.
You wish to travel the world, huh?
Will you come to Laolan Pass then?
I'll visit Laolan Pass
one day.
I'll check out the windy desert
and the Laolan River you mentioned.
All right.
It's a deal then.
Say that again if you dare!
- I shouldn't have been nice...
-  Miss Taozi.
Don't come near me.
What's wrong with you?
You're asking me that?
Did I make you angry again?
But I don't know
how I made you angry.
You don't know?
You should think about it then.
Was it because
I said something wrong?
I'm sorry.
I'm not
very eloquent.
If so, tell me then.
Tell me what you said wrongly.
I...
You're so dense.
Go away!
Taozi!
You're blocking my path.
Your Highness,
we received news from General Han.
The great imperial grandson
is safe for now.
That's great news.
Buddha did bless us.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
You may rest at ease for now.
Grand Governor
concealed his military
movements deliberately.
I kept thinking that
something big would happen.
Was it because Grand Governor
had located the imperial great-grandson?
Will he dispatch that many troops
just to catch a single child?
If so, is he trying to
head to Dongdu and Luoyang?
Or is he providing
reinforcements to Yingzhou?
I don't know either.
Has the messenger we dispatched to Li Ni
provided us with any news?
He said he hadn't met Li Ni yet.
Therefore, there's no news for now.
I just hope that Grand Governor
isn't heading to Tong Pass.
Maybe...
Maybe I'm overthinking it.
What's on your mind?
I was reminded of my first campaign.
I left Xichang through Fuyuan Gate.
Back then,
I was just
a nameless infantry.
After a few years,
I was promoted to the mayor of Huaihua
after rendering merit.
I followed my superior
to get a position in the capital.
I thought the capital
was lively and busy.
It was completely different
from the desolate battlefield.
Why are you telling me this
all of a sudden?
Look.
The sun is setting.
No matter if the sun is shining on the palace's
glazed roof tiles
or on the yellow sand of
the northwest desert,
it has a crimson hue to it.
Jing.
I'm fine.
I was just suddenly
reminded of the past.
That day,
outside of Yiluolu City,
I was commanding 100,000 troops,
waiting for the rallying trumpet
under the crimson sun.
Although I was commanding
100,000 troops,
there was no end to the wilderness.
It was just as quiet as today.
I fear nothing
as long as I'm by your side.
That brat Li Ni,
he thinks he can storm Xichang
just because he took over Tong Pass?
Jing,
please stop this.
Once the world is at peace,
you and I can spend our days
in Mount Li.
All right.
We'll surely visit there.
What's wrong?
What do you mean?
You've been furious the past few days.
You ignored Xie Chang'er
even when we were taking a break.
Who does he think he is?
Why must I talk to him
when we take a break?
There's an abnormal noise up front.
There's an army nearby.
But I don't know their identity.
Let's stop here.
(Cui)
Lieutenant He,
the previous platoon that was scattered
by Sun Jing is right ahead of us.
Youren,
hang in there.
Slowly.
General Pei Yuan,
why did Sun Jing's army
appear out of nowhere?
What? Did the Cui Army launch a two-pronged
attack on us together with them?
Tong Pass.
We finally conquered Tong Pass
after so much effort!
General Pei Yuan,
many of our brothers
in the Zhenxi Army were sacrificed!
General Pei Yuan!
How did it go?
Mister Shiqi,
you're amazing.
You noticed something was off
when we entered the camp.
You told me to keep an eye out
while feeding the horses.
I took a close look.
I noticed that their military
and food supplies were pretty intact.
If what Taozi said was true,
and that the Cui Army's platoons
were scattered by Sun Jing's army,
their supplies and formations
should be affected somehow.
However, they look orderly.
It doesn't seem like they've
encountered any foes lately.
Taozi,
did Young Master send you a letter
saying that this platoon
was scattered by Sun Jing's army
and told us to rendezvous
with them here?
That's right.
You got me some hot water
for me to wash up
right after we've arrived.
But now, it's not cooking time.
Why is there fire here?
Lieutenant He, what do you mean?
Something's off.
If they were scattered by
Sun Jing's army,
naturally, they would be on high alert.
Why would they start a fire
when it wasn't time for them to cook?
But this is
the Cui Army's camp.
We saw them too.
The leader said
their platoon was scattered by
Sun Jing's main army.
Lieutenant He,
what do you think is off about this place?
When I entered the camp,
I realized that their horseshoes
were thoroughly worn.
Their boots were covered with mud too.
It looked like they rushed here.
If they were scattered,
it's likely that they would wait for
reinforcements from the main army
or wait for the arrival of another platoon
before they resume their march.
That's why I told you
to check things out
as you feed the horses.
Mister Shiqi,
if so, what should we do now?
Ying.
Since you've arrived here safely,
I'll return to Tong Pass first.
Let's leave together.
This place is near Tong Pass.
Since we've already
rendezvous with them,
let's head to Tong Pass together.
All right.
Don't fall behind.
Come on.
Those at the back, don't fall behind!
Buddy, hang in there.
We can't stop here.
It's fine. Just hang in there.
Youren!
Youren, slowly.
Those at the back, don't fall behind!
Buddy, hang in there!
(Cui)
Go.
Go now.
Don't forget what I told you.
Miss Taozi,
I know
what I said wrong.
What did you say wrong?
Bao told me about it.
I know why
you're upset.
I'm too dense.
I can't speak well.
Actually, I was saying
that you were kind
and friendly to everyone
because I wanted to praise you.
I know you treat me especially well.
But
I...
I think I messed it up again.
Enough already.
You don't speak well indeed.
Miss Taozi,
actually,
I know that you treat me nicely.
So I want to
treat you nicely too.
All right. I got it.
Really?
Are you no longer angry at me?
Did you know how terrible I felt
when you ignored me?
It depends on
my mood then.
Youdao!
Are they here?
I think I heard horses.
Youde,
hide with Youren.
I can still fight
even if I only have one arm left.
That Cui scum,
he's such an ingrate!
We saved him and the Cui Army, you know?
How could he launch a sneak attack at us?
Even if I were to die today,
I will never let him off even if I turn into
a vengeful spirit!
All right!
Hide the severely wounded in the forest.
My other brothers, take up arms
and follow me!
Yes!
All of you, don't fall behind!
Let's go!
What do you think?
There's a group of soldiers
stopping in front.
But it's a small group.
I don't know their identity.
Let's meet them head-on then.
Kill them
if they're foes.
All right.
General Pei Yuan,
I'm able to die beside you
in battle today.
My life wasn't in vain.
My good buddy.
Guys.
Attack!
Shiqi?
What's going on?
Weren't you guys at Tong Pass?
What's with the serious injuries?
Mister Shiqi, why are you only here now?
Many of our brothers are dead!
Kill her and avenge the Zhenxi Army!
Kill her!
Youde,
they're one of us.
One of us?
The Cui Army sold Tong Pass out
and launched a two-pronged attack
together with Sun Jing,
killing many of our brothers!
Now, you're saying she's one of us?
Shiqi,
you mustn't let her deceive you again!
She and that Cui scum premeditated this!
She duped you guys into heading to Xichang.
The Cui Army launched
a two-pronged attack
with Sun Jing at Tong Pass,
killed our brothers,
and sold Tong Pass out!
You crazy!
It's either you die or I die!
Ying.
I mean, Lieutenant He.
Was this one of your ploys all along?
You said you would join me, head to Xichang,
and said that you could resolve
the issue at Yingzhou, huh?
That's not it.
On our way back to Tong Pass,
you said one of the Cui Army's platoons
was scattered
and you needed
to rendezvous with them.
You knew that I would escort you there
as I was worried about you.
But you did so to lure me
to another place.
You did so to stall me
so that I couldn't return to Tong Pass.
You won't trust me even if I tell you
that I have no idea about this, right?
Shiqi,
you mustn't trust her again!
How many times has she deceived you
ever since you made contact with her?
Mister Shiqi,
she has deceived you numerous times!
How could you still trust her?
You have no idea?
You have no idea.
Many of my brothers in the Zhenxi Army
were killed.
Are you saying that it wasn't
because of the Cui Army and Sun Jing?
Since you're not willing to trust me,
I have no way to explain...
How can I trust you?
You're your young master's strategist.
This is a huge matter.
I'm sure he'll discuss it with you.
I did try to plot against you
before we knew each other.
But this time,
I didn't.
We saved you
and the Cui Army outside of Tong Pass.
How could you do this to the Zhenxi Army?
Stop right there!
♪If I forget the fleeting of time♪
♪Waiting for memories♪
♪To shatter and sink♪
♪The emotional scars in your heart♪
♪Are the entanglement♪
♪I find hard to let go of♪
♪If longing is not forgotten♪
♪I long to return
to the very first moment♪
♪The affection we had
in our fateful situation♪
♪How I wish to keep it for you♪
♪If love still remembers♪
♪The promises we made♪
♪Even if this love hurts me♪
♪I'll continue living for you♪
♪Holding onto the memories♪
♪Waiting is my persistence♪
♪If love remembers♪
♪The promise I made to you♪
♪Despite going against fate♪
♪I have no regrets loving you♪
♪I'm willing to sacrifice for you♪
♪As I wait for your answer♪
♪If love remembers♪
♪The promise I made to you♪
♪Despite going against fate♪
♪I have no regrets loving you♪
♪I'm willing to sacrifice for you♪
♪As I wait for your answer♪