♪In the face of turmoil♪
♪Your roots hold firmly♪
♪To this piece of land♪
♪Chasing after the waves♪
♪My leaves flutter across♪
♪The horizon♪
♪Gazing from afar♪
♪At the end of the world♪
♪Is eternity♪
♪When we meet and then part♪
♪When we rely on each other
and then drift apart♪
♪I have never forgotten♪
♪As the glinting of swords cut♪
♪Through the mottled sky♪
♪The falling dreams♪
♪Shatter in the wind♪
♪As the wind breaks through the waves♪
♪It watches thousands of sails cross♪
♪The vast land and the boundless sea♪
♪Armor and red robes flying high♪
♪In the face of bitterness,
intense emotions, and joyful adventure♪
♪I only wish you to be by my side♪
♪Making the most of what life offers♪
♪Like towering trees with interconnected
roots, I'll accompany you to the ends♪
♪Watching fireflies land
on our shoulders♪
♪No regrets, no doubts in this world♪
=Wonderland of Love=
=Episode 3=
Young Master.
Taozi, Chen Xing,
it must've been a long trip.
How's Father's health?
Young Master,
(Cui Army's Bodyguards,)
initially, His Lordship had a cold.
(Taozi, Chen Xing)
And, his old wound ruptured
when he was attacking Hanzhou.
That's why he rested
and recuperated for some time.
But now, he's fine.
You don't need to worry.
His Lordship misses you
and Lieutenant He.
He said
you had old wounds,
and no one could
look after Lieutenant He.
That's why he dispatched
me and Chen Xing
to the frontline again.
Lieutenant He is missing.
What?
But fortunately,
you made it back safely.
I'm afraid
you're the only person
who can locate her now.
Young Master, don't worry.
As long as Lieutenant He
uses the same medicinal powder,
I can definitely find her.
Speak!
(Bandit of Mingdai Mountain, Huang Youyi)
Why did you two sneak into our territory?
Boss, these two people
(Bandit of Mingdai Mountain,)
are wearing leather boots.
(Zhang Youren)
I'm sure they're rich.
This woman in a man's disguise
is quite pretty.
Boss,
you haven't gotten yourself a wife yet.
(Bandit of Mingdai Mountain, Qian Youdao)
Why don't you marry her?
Yeah, make her your wife.
Make her your wife.
Sell her for money.
- He should marry her.
- Sell her for money.
- He should marry her!
- Shut up!
Who's the boss here?
- Boss!
You!
Be honest with me.
Who are you?
I'll be honest with you.
Actually, I'm the concubine
of Li Ni, the imperial grandson.
Not only is my husband an imperial grandson,
but he's also
the Marshal of Rebellion Suppression.
Although he's young,
he rules over Zhenxi Prefecture
and commands 100,000 troops.
100,000 troops?
Really?
My husband
is in Wangzhou right now.
If you release me,
I'll surely reward you handsomely.
Nonsense!
You!
Tell me!
Who exactly is she?
She's
the concubine of Li Ni,
the imperial grandson.
Naturally, I'm her bodyguard.
I'm escorting her to Wangzhou
under the imperial grandson's order.
I thought the emperor and his family
were slaughtered.
What nonsense
are you guys saying?
Imperial grandson, huh?
Do you think we're that gullible?
That's right!
- Yeah!
- How dare you trick us?
You want to trick us?
Boss,
that woman said
her husband was a marshal
in Zhenxi Prefecture.
Mr. Zhao
once served
the military in Zhenxi, right?
Why don't we bring Mr. Zhao here
and let him help us out?
Go and invite Mr. Zhao here.
Where did these crooks come from?
How dare they impersonate
the soldiers of Zhenxi?
Mr. Zhao!
(Bandit of Mingdai Mountain, Zhao Youde)
Mr. Zhao, this...
Shiqi?
Buddy, it's really you!
Hurry! Untie them!
Untie them!
(He's actually Li Ni,
the 17th imperial grandson.)
Can you do it or not?
Let me do it if you can't.
Slowly.
Tie her down.
- Hurry.
- Make it tight.
Make it tighter.
Don't let her escape.
Put your back into it.
This is my buddy
in the scout team
when we were in Zhenxi Prefecture.
We infiltrated West Mongolia together
to spy on the Qing Army.
There were 12 of us.
The only surviving members
were me and him
before we reached the king's tent.
I lost an arm.
Shiqi was the one
who carried me on his back
through the desert
and back to our camp.
Mr. Zhao!
He's my savior!
Savior!
- Savior!
Come.
We're buddies.
Don't be so courteous.
My buddy.
Here!
Cheers!
This is nice.
Shiqi,
you always bragged to me
that your father owned Jiangbei
and that your family
owned 16 mu of land.
And, you also owned four top-tier cattle.
He said his father owned Jiangbei, huh?
And you guys believed him?
Of course not.
If he's the landowner's son,
I'll be the emperor's uncle.
The emperor's uncle?
You have quite the status there, huh?
Girl,
shut up.
If you keep talking,
I'll shut you up.
Buddy,
what else did you say again?
You said you would become a baron
and collect rent
for a living after
retiring from the military.
I never expected us
to encounter each other here.
Shiqi,
I, Huang Youyi,
respect loyal heroes like you the most.
I only found out that you were a member
of the Zhenxi Army that was guarding
our borders and
fending off the Qing Army.
And, you saved Youde too.
It makes us want to join
the Zhenxi Army even more now.
Today,
it was our fault.
Here,
we shall apologize!
Please get up.
Ask your brothers to get up too.
All of you, get up.
Get up.
This time,
it's a misunderstanding.
Brothers, let me offer you all a toast.
Come.
Cheers!
General,
this horse belongs
to Lieutenant He of the Cui Army.
Since her horse is here,
I'm sure she's nearby.
The mountain forest is dense.
And, we've traveled the entire day.
I'm afraid we can't catch up to her.
General,
why aren't we
taking over Wangzhou directly?
The Zhenxi Army is robust and strong.
And, the Cui Army
has their eyes on them.
Our foes are stronger.
We mustn't attack them directly.
We can only take back the city
by capturing General Pei Yuan
and Lieutenant He
and using them as our hostages.
Right now, our men are tired,
and horses are exhausted.
Our main camp was burned down,
and many of our brothers are injured.
If this continues,
not only will we not catch up to them,
but we might also
be stuck in the mountains.
Is there anywhere nearby
where we can rest?
Around Mingdai Mountain,
there's a group of bandits
who built their own fortress.
Although they rule over this area,
they do not harass the people.
Therefore,
the garrison of Wangzhou
didn't eradicate them.
Relay my order.
Take down the fortress.
Our main camp has been burned down.
We've lost a place to rest.
Let's take over the mountain
and rest here.
We shall wait here
for Grand Governor Sun's reinforcements.
Yes, sir.
Shiqi,
where did you come from this time?
And where do you plan to go?
Mr. Zhao,
Shiqi
is escorting the concubine
of the imperial grandson
to Wangzhou.
I knew that imperial grandson
was a good-for-nothing!
He's still thinking
about women
even when our enemies are coming!
After I got injured,
the imperial court said
they would reward me
with 20 mu of land.
I gave it some thought.
I thought that I could make a living
by planting crops too.
But I never expected
the imperial court to deceive me!
They built a residence
for emperor's son on our land.
Due to that, my mother
starved to death.
I joined Mingdai Fortress
out of rage.
That actually happened?
After Sun Jing's rebellion,
many villages were
destroyed by the military.
Even now, I still don't know
if anyone from my village is still alive.
Shiqi, you may not know,
but I was
the fortune teller of the village.
I could've made a living with that.
But the imperial court
kept drafting us
to do corvees.
I couldn't even survive!
I...
That's why I became a bandit!
Everyone here
has a bitter past behind them.
No matter if it's Emperor Li
or that crook Sun,
both of them are forcing us
to a dead end.
We had no choice
but to become bandits here.
Shiqi,
since you're already here,
why don't you lead us
and bring us to join the Zhenxi Army,
okay?
Boss, am I right?
Yes!
You shall be our boss now.
- Boss!
No.
There's no need to be modest.
Today's a good day.
Let's swear an oath
and become sworn brothers.
- Okay!
We'll kill this girl and offer her
as a sacrifice!
You mustn't kill her!
You mustn't.
Boss, but why?
Does anyone know why?
Do you guys know why?
We don't.
It's because...
Who knows?
Yeah.
Do you guys know why?
It's because
she's the imperial grandson's concubine.
However,
she's my beloved.
We have mutual feelings for each other.
So, it's his beloved.
We finally found the chance
to elope together.
Boss, why didn't you tell me earlier?
Her hands are still tied, you know?
The ground is cold too.
- Lady Boss!
Lady Boss, let me untie you.
I was just too embarrassed to admit it.
Sorry about that.
Sorry about this, Lady Boss.
♪There are 18 river bends
in Laolan River♪
♪The first river bend is Yinsong♪
♪The fish in Yinsong is fat and meaty♪
(Bliss)
What is this?
Boss,
we don't have much here.
We can't hold a wedding
for you and Lady Boss.
However, the nuptial chamber
is a must.
- That's right!
- Enter the nuptial chamber!
Boss, don't be shy.
Come on.
Go inside.
Lady Boss, go inside.
Go now.
- Go now.
- Hurry up.
Buddy, enjoyable moments
are short-lived.
We'll make a move first.
Let's go!
See you!
General Pei Yuan of
the Zhenxi Army, huh?
The concubine
of the imperial grandson, Li Ni, huh?
(Bliss)
Shiqi.
These are some
of the rarer items we found.
You have to put this
in the nuptial chamber.
Take them.
Don't make Lady Boss wait too long.
Okay. Thank you.
Make haste. I'll make a move first.
So, the renowned Shiqi
within the Zhenxi Army,
he's actually the imperial grandson, Li Ni.
However, the bandits have no idea.
But I know who you are.
Strange.
I thought Zhao Youde
was in the Zhenxi Army too.
Why did he have no idea at all?
So, someone
hid his real name and identity
while he was in the military.
However, he rendered so much merit
that he and his next two generations
were to be rewarded.
Due to that,
he couldn't hide it any longer.
But at that time,
Zhao Youde
had already left the Zhenxi Army.
Am I right?
So what?
You didn't expose me just now.
What?
Don't tell me
you want to expose me now?
I never expected you
to borrow General Pei Yuan's name.
You almost duped me too.
If not,
how could I have the chance
to hear someone saying
that she was the concubine of Li Ni,
the imperial grandson?
You're such a scum.
Get up.
I'll sleep on the bed.
You can sleep on the ground.
It's been a long day for me.
I need to rest well
so that I can deal with a tricky
and cunning liar like you.
Hurry up.
You're a gentleman.
You should sleep on the ground.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
Since you're my concubine,
I think we can sleep
on the same bed.
You lecher.
Since you're already calling me that,
I must live up to my name,
don't you think?
Taozi, he's one of us.
Lieutenant He!
Lieutenant He, are you okay?
I'm fine.
He's so rude.
Let me kill him so that
you can be appeased.
Go ahead.
Your lieutenant wanted to do so
from the start.
But even now, she couldn't do it.
Do you wish to give it a try?
You!
Stop!
It's my turn to say that.
They're one of us.
We're in trouble!
We're invaded!
- Boss!
Boss!
What's the matter?
Our brothers outside
sent a letter to us.
They said a large group of troops
are attacking our fortress.
They even said
they were the troops of General Guo Zhi
who was under
the General of Rebellion Suppression.
He said he was going
to take over the fortress
and offer us as sacrifices to the heavens!
That's nonsense!
Boss, it's fine.
Our fortress is high up
in the mountains.
It's easy to defend and hard to invade.
We can defeat them flawlessly
using our terrain advantage!
That's right!
Kill them all!
Do not brag!
Youde.
Mr. Zhao.
Guo is one of our old friends.
It's General Guo,
who has been stationed
at Wangzhou all along.
So, it's him.
I never expected him to join Sun Jing.
This is quite the dilemma.
Guo was born in Shuoxi.
However, when it comes to an army,
the Zhenxi Army
is just as good as the others!
- That's right.
This is my buddy
from Zhenxi Army's scout team.
He followed Guo Zhi all day long.
He also came here
to report this news to us.
There are plenty of people
in Guo Zhi's remaining army.
And, they're good with bows and arrows.
We'll be at a disadvantage
if we go against them head-on.
Shiqi,
you should leave with your wife.
Lieutenant He,
you should return to the camp first.
Young Master is waiting for you
at Bingzhou.
That's right, Shiqi.
You should leave first.
I'm here.
He has a point.
My buddy, who was a former scout,
was an expert in forest warfare.
He can definitely
defeat Guo Zhi and his remaining army.
I will stay and help too.
This female bodyguard of mine
is an expert at warfare too.
She can definitely provide you guys
with a huge boost in power.
- This is great!
- Thank you!
That's right.
Thank you!
Thank you, everyone!
- Thank you!
I can't even take one more step.
You should return to Wangzhou.
Just forget about me.
That won't do.
You're my concubine.
How could I leave you behind?
If you try to talk glibly again,
I'll kill you.
Look at you.
You have the energy to kill me,
but you don't have
the strength to walk, huh?
No.
I'm too tired.
You should think of something.
I can't walk anymore.
I do have an idea.
However,
you have to cooperate with me.
Let's go and get changed.
There's no one inside.
Are you done?
I'll be done in a second.
It's just a change of attire.
What's taking you so long?
I'm done.
Let's go.
You...
You look too clean and proper.
This won't do.
Come here.
What are you doing?
Don't move.
You have to pretend
to be a village girl.
You don't look like one at all.
What are you doing?
You'll know it later.
Put it in your shirt.
Why?
You need to pretend to be pregnant.
I can only borrow a cart
when you look like you're pregnant.
You couldn't walk anymore, right?
If so, I'll bring you
to the city on a cart.
- Pretend to be pregnant?
- Hurry up.
How do I do this?
Can you hurry up?
You should be grateful
that we have a cart.
Don't complain.
What's the rush?
Do you want people to know
that you're hiding hay in your shirt?
A gentleman settles disputes with
his words, not his hands.
I'm not a gentleman.
I'm a fair lady.
You're a fair lady.
Look at yourself.
How are you fair by any means?
Say that again?
Hey, you better stop.
I'll retaliate.
Dear, stop crying.
We can hunt again
even if we've lost our prey.
It's not worth it to be angry
over what they did.
It's not worth it.
Old mister,
excuse me.
How far are we from Bingzhou?
It's quite far away.
You still have over 100 li to travel.
There's a scar on your face.
Did something happen?
Just drop it.
Hurry!
(I don't know)
(what happened in the past few days.)
(Soldiers came to the mountains.)
(And, they even set up a checkpoint)
(on the official path.)
(My wife and I)
(were heading to a market.)
What's this?
But those people were much more barbaric
than bandits.
We'll be having roasted hare tonight.
Give it to me!
We need to exchange this for salt!
Take it.
We're hunting down the rebels
under General Guo Zhi,
who's under
the General of Rebellion Suppression.
What's wrong with taking your prey?
Scram!
Young man,
do not take the official path.
Those guys are evil.
They didn't let off
any women and maidens.
Your wife is young.
Besides,
it'll be terrible
if her baby is affected because of this.
So, are there any other paths we can take
besides the official path?
There's a small road
to the west if you go up the mountains.
However, it's a long detour.
And, it's a mountain path.
It's hard to traverse.
It'll be even more difficult
to traverse it
once the sun sets.
Thank you, old mister.
Remember, don't take the official path.
Don't take the official path.
It's been a long time since I had
the honeydew yogurt you made.
Let me give it a try.
Not bad at all.
What do you think about Li Ni?
Li Ni?
He has a modest reputation
among the imperial family.
I heard
that he was a stubborn one.
The late emperor was so furious with him
that he demoted him
and sent him to the military.
I already asked my men
to investigate his profile.
When he was sent to the Zhenxi Army,
Pei Xian transferred
his son, Pei Yuan,
from the Dragon Guards
to the Zhenxi Army.
Since then,
Pei Yuan stayed together with Li Ni.
They were always on the same team.
That old fox, Pei Xian,
is a proud person.
Since he's letting his son
be Li Ni's follower,
I'm sure Li Ni is someone
we shouldn't underestimate.
However, I heard
that Pei Xian has ten sons in total.
Some are in the military,
some became academicians,
and some even became priests.
You're scheming and meticulous.
There's no way Pei Xian will know
that you will fight in the name of justice.
Since he has no idea about that,
why would he set his pieces
at such an early time
and focus on
an imperial grandson
who was demoted
and sent to the military?
What's the matter?
Why are your hands this hot?
I'm fine. Let's go.
Come, let me take a look.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
It's nothing.
Let's go.
How can you travel in this state?
Get up. I'll carry you on my back.
Get up.
You're awake.
Do you want some water?
Where are we?
This is a place
where hunters rest
in the middle of their hunt.
It was quite late just now.
I only managed to find one herb.
I've applied it to you.
I don't know if it's effective or not.
I'm not that fragile.
Dear, stop crying.
We can hunt again
even if we've lost our prey.
It's not worth it to be angry
over what they did.
It's not worth it.
Stop mulling over it.
What if you fall sick because of this?
All right. We'll arrive soon.
Dear, slow down.
Got it.
Old mister.
Who's there?
It's you guys?
What are you guys doing here?
Who are they?
It's the couple we met today.
What a coincidence.
Really?
You're right.
Have a seat.
Help yourself.
You should take more meat.
Try some pheasant.
- Thank you, old madam.
- Drink up. It'll warm your body.
Try it.
The pheasant we used
was hunted by my husband just now.
It's delicious when
you make soup with it.
Have some meat.
Thank you, old madam.
Eat up.
My husband
loves the soup I make.
It's a shame
that I couldn't give birth
to a child for him.
If only I had a daughter like you.
Here, dear.
You did a good job today.
- What do you think?
- It's delicious.
Youngsters like you all
should have more meat.
You still have
a long way to travel tomorrow.
You'll only have enough energy
if you have your fill.
By the way, old mister,
it's quite late now.
Why did you guys come back suddenly?
Don't even talk about it.
My wife and I
was supposed to head to a market.
In the end,
not only did we not get salt,
but the soldiers
robbed us of our stuff too.
My wife was unhappy about it.
She forced me
to spend extra time in the mountains
to see if I could get a prey or two.
In the end,
I only got this pheasant.
And, the sun was setting.
I knew
that there was
a shelter here for us to rest.
I didn't expect
to see you two here.
This must be fate, huh?
That's right.
I thought crooks were approaching us
when I heard something out there.
You're traveling
with your wife.
You're supposed to stay alert.
The world is chaotic
nowadays.
That's right.
Have some soup.
Eat up.
Here.
Dear, you should eat too.
You should eat first.
Eat up.
One more sip.
Someone is coming.
And, they're riding horses.
It's likely that the soldiers
from the checkpoint are here.
Dear!
Get up!
What's wrong?
Those two people might be hiding inside.
Order the heavy crossbowmen
to surround the place.
Yes, sir.
I dug this cellar by myself
a few years back.
I use them to store my prey.
It can fit
two people.
You.
Take your wife with you
and hide down there.
That's right.
No.
Old mister, you and your wife
should hide inside.
They know us.
They won't do anything to us.
But you two are strangers.
It'll be more dangerous
if they find you.
By then, we will be implicated too.
That's right.
Go and hide now.
Hurry, good girl.
Hurry.
- Don't be scared.
- Hurry!
Search the area.
Kill any strangers on sight.
Come.
Cover it.
Hurry!
Sir,
we're hunters.
Have you seen
a fair man
who looks like a scholar around?
Sir,
this place is remote.
There's no scholar here.
Speaking of scholar,
only Mr. Shan from the town is a scholar.
Cut the crap!
Will you tell us or not?
Sir, please spare us!
We know nothing!
Bring them outside!
Go!
Sir!
Sir, please spare us!
We know nothing!
Are you sure you guys know nothing?
We truly know nothing.
Okay.
Since you guys know nothing,
I'll release you guys.
Let them go.
Go now.
Thank you, sir.
Let's go.
Where are they?
They're dead.
What?
I went out to take a look.
Both of them are dead.
Have you lost your mind?
Why did you prick me with a needle?
They wouldn't have died
if you hadn't made me unconscious.
Do you know
how many archers are out there?
Do you know what'll happen
if they find us?
We won't make it in time
if we rush outside recklessly.
They will die immediately instead.
What about now?
If we tried to save them back then,
we might still stand a chance.
But you weren't willing
to give it a try.
You're just
a coward who's afraid of death.
How dare a person like you still
dare to receive their grace?
You ingrate.
I am a coward!
Just kill me!
(Benefactors,)
(it was all my fault today.)
(I'll definitely)
avenge you guys in the future.
(Benefactor)
♪If I forget the fleeting of time♪
♪Waiting for memories♪
♪To shatter and sink♪
♪The emotional scars in your heart♪
♪Are the entanglement♪
♪I find hard to let go of♪
♪If longing is not forgotten♪
♪I long to return
to the very first moment♪
♪The affection we had
in our fateful situation♪
♪How I wish to keep it for you♪
♪If love still remembers♪
♪The promises we made♪
♪Even if this love hurts me♪
♪I'll continue living for you♪
♪Holding onto the memories♪
♪Waiting is my persistence♪
♪If love remembers♪
♪The promise I made to you♪
♪Despite going against fate♪
♪I have no regrets loving you♪
♪I'm willing to sacrifice for you♪
♪As I wait for your answer♪
♪If love remembers♪
♪The promise I made to you♪
♪Despite going against fate♪
♪I have no regrets loving you♪
♪I'm willing to sacrifice for you♪
♪As I wait for your answer♪