♪In the face of turmoil♪
♪Your roots hold firmly♪
♪To this piece of land♪
♪Chasing after the waves♪
♪My leaves flutter across♪
♪The horizon♪
♪Gazing from afar♪
♪At the end of the world♪
♪Is eternity♪
♪When we meet and then part♪
♪When we rely on each other
and then drift apart♪
♪I have never forgotten♪
♪As the glinting of swords cut♪
♪Through the mottled sky♪
♪The falling dreams♪
♪Shatter in the wind♪
♪As the wind breaks through the waves♪
♪It watches thousands of sails cross♪
♪The vast land and the boundless sea♪
♪Armor and red robes flying high♪
♪In the face of bitterness,
intense emotions, and joyful adventure♪
♪I only wish you to be by my side♪
♪Making the most of what life offers♪
♪Like towering trees with interconnected
roots, I'll accompany you to the ends♪
♪Watching fireflies land
on our shoulders♪
♪No regrets, no doubts in this world♪
=Wonderland of Love=
=Episode 7=
- Lieutenant.
- What's the situation?
The garrison of Bingzhou
is about to crumble.
Some soldiers abandoned the city
and escaped to Jianzhou.
The rest have mostly surrendered.
Now we are counting the prisoners,
food supplies, seals, letters
and many other urgent things.
Did you catch Han Li?
When Han Li saw the situation,
he escaped with the help
of his personal guards.
But I've sent out our men
to search for him.
The city gate is closed.
I'm sure he's still in Bingzhou.
Listen.
We have to capture Han Li
before the Zhenxi Army.
Roger that.
(Cui)
Guards!
Mister Lv.
Mister Lv passed out all of a sudden.
Someone is escaping!
Mister Shiqi.
This time, I've brought many men.
Where's Han Li?
Have you caught him?
I made a deal with the Cui family.
Whoever catches Han Li first
will take over Bingzhou.
Han Li ran away
as soon as the battle started.
But Bao is chasing after him.
Let's go and catch that cunning man.
Chen Xing.
Lieutenant,
Han Li is not in the carriage.
He's indeed cunning.
Qiucui, don't worry.
Our servants
are standing guard downstairs.
No one can barge in.
Miss, they say
that the army breaking into the city
will plunder
and do all kinds of evil.
Will our servants be able to stop them?
If they can stop them,
we'll be safe and sound.
If they can't stop them,
what's the point
of being scared right now?
This is Third Lady's fault.
If she didn't bad-mouth you to Master,
you wouldn't have to volunteer to come
to Bingzhou
for the ancestor worship.
If it wasn't for Third Lady,
we wouldn't be here in Bingzhou
(Daughter of Prime Minister Gu,)
and we wouldn't be in danger now.
(Gu Wan'niang)
Qiucui, that's not true.
Third Sister is right.
My father has six daughters.
I'm the only one who is not smart
and has no redeeming qualities.
If I don't work myself harder,
I'll be even more useless.
Third Lady
was just spouting nonsense.
Don't take it to heart.
Grand Governor Sun wanted to appoint
my father as the prime minister.
My father refused.
So, he was sent to jail.
All of the royal families
in the capital city
admired him
for his incorruptible integrity.
Now that he is finally free,
he's unable to leave the capital city.
I'm fortunate to be able
to travel to Bingzhou to pay respect
to our ancestors on behalf of him.
If you are always like this,
when can you live
with your head held high?
Even those servants in the residence
dare to treat you rudely now.
Don't worry, Master.
Pursuers have been lured away
by that carriage.
Is there anywhere to hide in here?
If you can barge into
someone's private residence
in broad daylight,
why don't you look
for a place to hide yourself?
Lord Han has always been a hero.
Miss.
But now, you are hiding
in a lady's room.
Don't you feel ashamed?
Lord Han.
Don't you think you've fallen too low
if you have to hold a weak lady hostage?
You won't be able to goad me.
Since you are Young Master Cui's
study partner,
now that Bingzhou has fallen,
the Zhenxi Army is holding more power.
Since you are worthless
to Young Master Cui,
maybe you should join
the Zhenxi Army instead.
You are already
in such a dire situation.
And yet,
you are worried about my future.
I'll never regret
knowing you.
And thank you
for putting me in your good graces.
What's the point of me putting you
in my good graces?
Will you let me go?
You've misunderstood me, Lord Han.
I can't thank you enough.
Why would I bring you harm?
Everyone in the city says
that you are good at business.
And that you are a wealthy man.
Now that I've been abandoned
by the Cui family,
I have nothing.
Please be understanding
and give me a hand.
Take them out.
These pieces of jewellery
are very valuable.
Take them
and join the Zhenxi Army.
Miss!
Stay away!
Miss.
If you come here, I'll kill her.
Miss!
Miss.
Miss, please forgive me.
Thank you for saving my life.
Don't move!
Lieutenant He,
should we fight them for him?
I concede defeat.
I'm not someone
who can't admit defeat.
Are you okay, Miss?
Miss.
Hurry up.
Come here.
Mister Shiqi.
Finally, we managed
to catch this cunning man.
It's too late for the Cui Army.
Han Li belongs to us now.
Congratulations, Li Ni.
Since you've managed to capture Han Li,
I'll honor our deal.
Bingzhou belongs to the Zhenxi Army now.
Thank you.
Han Li has been captured
by the Zhenxi Army.
According to our deal,
Bingzhou belongs to them now.
What?
When did you make that deal
with the Zhenxi Army?
How could you do that?
Lieutenant He,
why didn't you tell me about it?
She already informed me
about it beforehand.
She was just following my command.
The Zhenxi Army is low on food supplies.
I already
informed Young Master about it.
As soon as we entered the city,
we sent our men to clear out
the food supplies.
Now, even though the Zhenxi Army
has taken over Bingzhou,
they are still out of food supplies.
I see.
I'd like to ask you
for a favour, Li.
Are you finally going
to let me help you?
We are a family.
There's no need to be polite.
You are the commander of our army.
Just give me your order.
Now that our army is in the city,
we need to stay alert
in case the Zhenxi Army
has an ulterior motive.
I hope that you can
station a troop
outside of the city.
If something happens in the city,
you can back us up from the outside.
Just in case.
Station...
Station a troop outside?
I'm sure you have your reason
for this decision.
I'll lead a troop and station
outside of the city at once.
Thank you.
We are a family.
There's no need to be polite.
I know that you don't like him.
That's why
I sent him away from the city.
Thank you, Young Master.
No wonder Shu is nowhere to be seen.
You've sent him to the outside of the city
early in the morning
to keep an eye on Cui Li.
You know me well, Ying.
Drink some tea.
Let me pour it for you.
Say it again if you dare.
Fine.
Since you are slightly deaf,
I'll say it again.
The Cui Army
should hand over
the food supplies that you've taken
and leave the city.
The Zhenxi Army
is magnanimous and kind.
Since both of us
are fighting for the same throne,
we'll let you rest in Bingzhou
for one night before your departure.
What do you think?
The Zhenxi Army
is generous enough, right?
We are the ones who took down Bingzhou.
The food supplies belongs
to the party entering the city first.
Although we made a deal with you,
you've now taken over Bingzhou.
Why do we have to
give you the food supplies?
Do you think I'll be scared of you
just because you slapped the table?
We took down Bingzhou together.
Without the Zhenxi Army,
Han Li would've escaped to Jianzhou
and tried to reclaim Bingzhou.
How dare you say that.
I said it!
Give us back our food supplies!
Say it again!
Are you really deaf?
If we didn't attack the city,
you wouldn't have time
to catch Han Li.
Return us our food supplies
and get out of Bingzhou!
Darn you.
You brat.
I'll kill you.
Han Li doesn't have the tiger tally.
Continue to look for it.
Roger that.
- That's utter nonsense.
- You brat.
I'll kill you, you brat.
They are searching
Han Li's residence thoroughly.
Looks like
the tiger tally is not with Han Li.
Young Master Cui over there
has a fierce reputation
on the battlefield.
But now that I've seen him in person,
he's just a frail and weak man.
Never judge a book by its cover.
He's just a pretty boy.
How dare you say
that I didn't join the fight.
You were just a baby
when I was fighting in battle!
Let's fight if you dare!
- Come on then!
- Come on!
I'm not a coward who's afraid of you.
Come.
I'll teach you a lesson,
you brat.
(Tang's Confection)
Are you hungry?
I asked someone to buy these
early in the morning.
They are your favourite.
Thank you, Young Master.
You are quite strong.
It's delicious.
Where are you hitting?
I...
Let me help you wipe.
Stop it!
I'm hungry.
Let's go and eat first.
Eat?
I'm not hungry.
I say that I'm hungry.
Lieutenant He.
Looks like Li Ni found
the hairpin that you lost.
I never thought
that Imperial Grandson,
the marshal of the Zhenxi Army,
would be so greedy.
He found your hairpin
but refused to return.
And he even wears it on his head blatantly.
How shameless of him.
I'll go and get it back for you.
No.
Don't cause trouble.
Look at the big picture.
I thought Lieutenant He
lost her hairpin.
Why does Li Ni have it?
Lieutenant He gave it to him.
The Qixi Lantern Festival
has always been an important festival
in Bingzhou.
Now, we have
two major armies in Bingzhou.
Who do you think
will accept our invitation?
I hope that there won't be a fight.
Ask that pretty face of yours
to come out.
Who is a pretty face?
The Zhenxi Army is the pretty face
who wants a free ride.
Both armies quarrel so much.
A fight will break out eventually.
If the city can't be at peace,
we are the ones
who will be affected by it.
Sorry for the wait.
There's no need to apologise.
According to our Young Master,
Bingzhou has just started
to settle down.
Everyone is still living in fear.
We need to hold a lively celebration
of the Lantern Festival.
Life can only continue
when the people feel safe.
And bringing peace to the people
is why we fight for the throne.
Everyone in the Cui Army,
including Young Master,
will attend the festival.
Please take care of us on that day.
Of course.
Looks like
the Zhenxi Army
is not going to attend it.
No. That's not true.
Young Master Cui has said everything
that my general conveys.
The Zhenxi Army
will attend the festival too.
Thank you.
What's the point of having good ears?
You talk so slowly.
Why are you here, Imperial Grandson?
I need to ask something
with Lieutenant He.
She's just a lieutenant.
If it's about military affairs,
you can just talk to me about it.
Just a minor matter.
There's no need to bother you.
I heard that Lieutenant He
was stranded in Han Li's residence
a few days ago.
And that she only got out alive
because she was under your care.
I should set up a banquet
to thank you
for your help.
The Cui Army is the leading army
fighting for the throne.
It's my duty.
You are too kind.
I grew up
with Lieutenant He since young.
We have a special relationship.
So, by taking care of Lieutenant He,
you've taken care of me too.
I knew that you would come.
Why are you here, Young Master?
I just want to pay you a visit.
Greetings, Your Highness.
You may be at ease.
It was urgent today.
You are not injured, right?
Do you need a physician?
Just now, General Pei Yuan
has already sent a physician
to check on me.
Luckily, I just have some minor cuts.
Nothing serious.
I'm here to thank you.
If it wasn't for you today,
I would've died.
There's no need.
It's not a big deal.
Don't address me as His Highness.
Just call me by my title in the army.
Come in.
The weather has turned cold.
And you are not dressed properly
for the cold.
No wonder you are coughing.
If Taozi finds out about this,
she'll lecture you again.
I'm fine.
Today, after keeping a close eye on Li Ni,
he's indeed an outstanding commander
as you said he is.
We should never underestimate him.
Li Ni is indeed a wise strategist.
The Zhenxi Army is a formidable force.
If we can fight alongside each other,
we can achieve victory
with half the effort.
But if we become enemies,
to be honest,
with an opponent like Li Ni,
I'm afraid
that we won't be able to defeat them.
The Zhenxi Army is tied down
by fighting for the throne.
No matter what,
they won't become our enemies.
It's better to be safe than sorry.
Do you have any family in this city?
I can ask Bao to send someone
to take you home.
I haven't introduced myself yet.
My surname is Gu.
Named Wan'niang.
I'm from the capital city.
Last month, I came to Bingzhou
to pay respect to my ancestors
on behalf of my father.
The Gu family in Bingzhou.
I remember that Prime Minister Gu
is from the Gu family in Bingzhou too.
I heard that he called Sun Jing out
for being a traitor in court.
Then, he was sent to jail.
That's my father.
In the end, in order to gain
the people's support,
my father was released from prison
and confined at home.
So, I traveled to Bingzhou
to pay respect to our ancestors
and pray for my father.
So, you are
Prime Minister Gu's daughter.
Our country was overturned
and my father almost lost his life.
Luckily, I ran into
the Zhenxi Army today.
And our army is indeed impressive
and formidable.
I'm willing to donate our family's
food in Bingzhou to the Zhenxi Army.
May the victory be yours
and reclaim
the capital city soon.
That way, not only can you
save the people from this peril,
you can save my father too.
Prime Minister Gu is loyal
and now, you are donating
your food to our army.
You're indeed the offspring
of loyal family.
I have a favour to ask.
I hope that you can give me a hand.
Go ahead.
The nation is in chaos now.
And Bingzhou is far away
from the capital city.
I'm afraid that I won't be able
to return to the capital city by myself.
Please agree
to let me travel with the army.
That way, I'll be fortunate
enough to witness
the reclaiming of Xichang
by the Zhenxi Army.
It's not easy to march with the army.
It's not convenient
to bring ladies with us.
No matter how difficult it is,
I can take it.
If you are worried about us,
Qiucui and I can dress up as men.
We won't cause you any trouble.
It's better for me to send a team
to escort you back to the capital city.
You are busy with military affairs.
I don't want you to cut down
the size of your army to protect me.
You just need to allow me
to follow the army from behind.
Okay then.
You can dress up as a man
and join the army.
Thank you, General.
Stop right there!
Stop her.
You uneducated wench.
Madam Shen. Educate them
about proper etiquette.
Yes, Your Highness.
The crown princess
is from the internal court,
in the top rank.
Lady of the country
is from the external court,
in the first rank.
The crown princess has a higher rank.
The lady of the country should greet
the crown princess with a kowtow.
What?
Are you saying that I should
show my respect to her?
Lady of Wei is Grand Governor's wife.
Grand Governor
has achieved great merits.
So, Her Highness
has exempted you from having
to greet her with a kowtow.
I am Her Highness's personal maid.
I am in the sixth rank.
You are Lady of Wei's maidservant.
You have no ranking.
What is it?
A maidservant who has no ranking wants
to hit a personal maid
in the sixth rank?
Looks like you are confused
about where you stand.
You have no manners at all.
What a sharp tongue you have.
Thank you for the compliment, Lady of Wei.
Grand Governor is humble and polite.
Now that you've entered the palace,
you have to follow the rules
and proper etiquette as well
so that you won't be a laughing stock.
A laughing stock.
I want to see
who dares laugh at me now.
You'll be taught a lesson
if you have no manners.
You...
You crazy!
Stop crying.
To be honest,
(Duke Zheng)
the rumors are indeed quite unpleasant.
However, Xiao
is still the former crown princess.
Since the former crown prince
took his own life,
she should've followed him
if she was sensible.
Even if she didn't,
she should've become a nun to stay loyal
to the former crown prince.
Grand Governor
is a wise man.
Why is he
so taken with this woman?
She must have put a spell on him.
Think about it.
Over the years,
he had married
so many wives and concubines.
But he had never doted on anyone before.
I can't let this continue.
Don't panic.
There are still countless battles
ahead of us.
Grand Governor still needs
the Yuan Clan from Chenjun
to fight for him and
supply him with food.
He won't treat us badly.
But this Xiao
is adamant about staying in the palace.
Maybe
she has an ulterior motive.
We'll find out what it is eventually.
Then,
I'll discuss this with our relatives
and convince Grand Governor
to kill this woman
for what she did to you.
You may leave.
The river looks clear and shallow.
But how far apart the river banks are?
The Qixi Festival will be here soon.
We met for the first time
on the night of Qixi.
If I had known that this would happen,
we should've never met.
Why are you saying something
so negative again?
Are you
still mad because of Lady of Wei?
I've lived in the palace for so long.
This kind of thing happens often.
It's only normal for others
to favour the one with power.
Once you lose power,
they'll step all over you.
Today,
Lady of Wei slapped my personal maid.
If I didn't retaliate,
one day,
she would kill me with poison.
Do you think you will
punish your legal wife
for me?
I don't think she'll do that.
The Yuan Clan from Chenjun
is your wife's clan.
And you've always relied on them.
I've offended Lady of Wei today.
I should leave the palace
and become a nun.
That way,
I won't be a thorn in someone's flesh.
You are trying to goad me.
I wouldn't dare.
I'm just afraid that
if I continue to stay here,
I'll die one day without knowing
what killed me.
I better become a nun
and stay away from all the curses.
I want to see
which monastery
can handle you.
You can build a monastery for me.
At a tranquil and beautiful place.
I want it to be near to Xichang.
That way,
it'll be easy for you to visit me.
But maybe after I leave the palace,
you'll forget all about me
in just a few days.
Do you really want to be a nun?
I don't want to stay in the palace anymore.
Lady of Wei
is not a magnanimous person.
She likes to make things
difficult for me.
Moreover, everyone in the palace
has a sharp tongue.
I don't want
to be gossiped by them anymore.
Forget about being a nun.
But
your personal maid, Madam Shen,
looks like someone with great fortune.
Maybe she can become
a nun in your stead.
Finally, you've said the truth.
In order to preserve Lady of Wei's dignity,
you want to send my personal maid away
to become a nun.
Just give me
a glass of poisoned liquor.
Madam Shen and I
will drink that poisoned liquor at once.
She's your personal maid.
She offended Lady of Wei.
I have no choice but to punish her.
What about Lady of Wei's maidservant?
She offended me.
Are you going
to ask her to become a nun too?
Look at you.
You are
so eager to win in everything.
If you act fairly and punish
that maidservant too,
I'll send Madam Shen away
to become a nun.
Otherwise, not a chance.
Are you patching up your robe?
Let me help you.
Forget it.
I'm better at this than you.
When you patched up
your torn socks last time,
those stitches
were as long as centipedes.
I want to ask you something.
I heard
that you are going to let Miss Gu
travel with our army
in men's clothes, right?
Yes.
She's alone
with her maid.
She wants to return
to the capital city.
It's a battlefield everywhere.
She can't survive the journey alone.
Instead of that,
she can travel along with our army.
This is the first time.
This is my first time seeing you
treating a lady so kindly.
Are you going to become
a nagging old woman
when there's no war?
No.
I really think
that Miss Gu is a nice woman.
She's good enough for you.
She's good for you.
Looks like you've fallen for Miss Gu.
Me?
This is easy.
I'll write a letter to Great General Pei
to propose for you.
No.
What nonsense are you talking about?
You are the one who likes her.
For the first time ever,
you allowed a woman
to travel with our army.
So, stop dragging me into this.
What's wrong with being a woman?
Look at Lieutenant He
from the Cui family.
She's smart and cunning.
And she's good at commanding her troops.
She's way better than
so many men out there.
From what you said,
looks like
you are in love with Lieutenant He
instead of Miss Gu.
Nonsense.
Nonsense?
Lieutenant He.
The paper windmill.
I retrieved the paper windmill
that you left in the inn.
Show it to me.
But wait.
This is just a paper windmill.
Why did you leave it
on the counter of the inn
if you were going
to send me to retrieve it?
Look.
This is just a toy
that's sold in a market.
It's not unique and it's worthless.
And it's broken.
Why do you keep it?
It's broken?
Look.
It wasn't broken
when I gave it to the innkeeper.
Looks like
he didn't take good care of it.
It's broken here too.
This is not how you fix it.
You'll get cut by the bamboo strip.
Let me do it.
This kind of labor work is not for you.
It's fixed.
Let's attend the Lantern Festival
tomorrow night together.
Don't you have
to run the show tomorrow?
I already appointed someone else
to do that kind of boring task.
What about you?
Do you have to accompany
Young Master Cui?
No.
It's a deal then.
See you then.
Lieutenant He.
You fixed the windmill?
Yes.
Lieutenant He.
Let's enjoy the Lantern Festival
together at night.
I have things to do tonight.
I'll pass.
Are you going to accompany
Young Master to the Lantern Festival?
Sitting under the well-lit shed
for people to gossip?
I'll pass.
What is it that you have to do then?
I...
I'm afraid that the Zhenxi Army
will do something in secret.
So, I have to keep an eye on them
to find out what their plan is.
Okay. I'll go with you
to help you.
You don't have to.
You can keep an eye on Xie Chang'er
from the Zhenxi Army for me.
Not only is he
Li Ni's trusted man,
he can gather intel
from the sound of wind.
You have to keep a close eye on him.
Don't give him any chance
to act in secret.
Ear.
Why are you pulling such a long face?
Mister Shiqi has ordered us
to behead Han Li in public
during the Lantern Festival
to make a name for the Zhenxi Army.
Yes.
We've done everything
according to Mister Shiqi's order.
But he asked me
to lure Miss Taozi away
from Lieutenant He.
Why?
Since someone
doesn't want Taozi
to follow Lieutenant He,
it means that someone else
wants to follow her instead.
Just do as he said.
But how can I
lure Miss Taozi away?
Knock her out?
She uses poison and she's cunning.
If I were to fight with her,
I couldn't win.
Your brain
is made out of wood.
You can just invite her
to enjoy
the Lantern Festival with you.
Here you go.
Think about it.
Miss Taozi.
How about we enjoy
the Lantern Festival today together?
Why are you inviting me?
Because I'm alone today.
Others have other things to do.
And it looks like
you are alone too.
How about we...
So, you are inviting me
because you are bored.
No.
No. Miss Taozi.
It's not what I meant.
Forget it.
Forget what I said.
Stop right there.
Since you wanted to invite me,
you invite me then.
Why are you changing your mind now?
Who do you think I am?
No. Miss Taozi.
- Let me explain.
- I'll go with you.
Let's enjoy
the Lantern Festival together.
Thank you, Miss Taozi.
No need to thank me.
After all, you've saved me from trouble.
What trouble?
Come and take a look.
Be careful.
Why are you dressing up like this today?
You look beautiful.
Since I'm here to spy on someone,
of course I need to get changed.
This is a trick
to make others lower their guard.
You are indeed wise.
Let's get down to business.
You are so beautiful today.
I almost couldn't recognise you.
Come on in.
Awesome!
Again!
Amazing!
That's great!
Windmills.
Pretty and fun windmills.
Again!
Great.
Give me one windmill, please.
Choose one.
I'll take this.
Okay.
Pay for it.
You like windmills?
Not really.
But our lieutenant has a windmill
on her book rack.
Great!
And she's always in a good mood
when she looks at it every day.
She refused to throw it away
when it broke that day.
She even fixed it herself.
But paper windmills are not expensive.
Only two copper coins.
That's right.
I said the same thing to her.
I told her that we could
buy a new one together.
But she said that I wouldn't understand.
She said
that buying a windmill yourself
was not as fun as getting
a windmill as a present.
So, when I saw that person just now,
I said to myself
that I wanted someone
to give me one too.
I want to see
how fun a windmill can be
when it's a gift from another person.
Is that why
you asked me to buy it for you?
I'm sure you feel honored
to buy something for me.
Yes, I do.
But what's so fun
about getting a windmill as a gift?
Why don't I feel the same?
Am I dreaming
or is the river full of stars?
This place is beautiful.
The stars in Laolan Pass
are way bigger
and nearer.
When you lie down on the desert
at midnight,
the sky is as dark as silk.
As if you can touch the star
just by reaching out.
We have steppe
as far as the eyes can see in Pingliang.
When I was young,
my father would go hunting with me.
Sometimes, I would fall asleep
on the back of the horse.
When I woke up and opened my eyes,
I could see every single star
in the sky.
They looked like sugar crystals
that were about to fall.
I grew up in the capital city.
After I learnt how to ride,
I would always ride alone to go
to the Wonderland.
The Wonderland is a famous spot
in the capital city.
It's located on high land.
Standing on top of it,
you can overlook the whole capital city.
Hear the buzz and chirp in the forest,
look at the rainbow on the other side.
Feel the breeze from the west
in Wonderland.
Keep riding deep into the sunset.
May the sun never set.
So, you like this poem.
But I like the other one.
Wait.
I know which one you like.
What?
There's grass everywhere
in the grassland.
Every year, it'll wilt during Autumn.
But you can never burn it down.
It'll come back again
when Spring is here.
Is that the one?
How do you know
I like that poem?
Know your enemies well
so that you can defeat them.
I know
that Li Ni is someone like that.
That's why I know
that you like this poem.
You are amazing, Lieutenant He.
You are my bosom friend.
I like that.
Nonsense.
I didn't say
that I'm your bosom friend.
that you said that.
Why is my dress wet?
This is bad. The boat is leaky.
♪If I forget the fleeting of time♪
♪Waiting for memories♪
♪To shatter and sink♪
♪The emotional scars in your heart♪
♪Are the entanglement♪
♪I find hard to let go of♪
♪If longing is not forgotten♪
♪I long to return
to the very first moment♪
♪The affection we had
in our fateful situation♪
♪How I wish to keep it for you♪
♪If love still remembers♪
♪The promises we made♪
♪Even if this love hurts me♪
♪I'll continue living for you♪
♪Holding onto the memories♪
♪Waiting is my persistence♪
♪If love remembers♪
♪The promise I made to you♪
♪Despite going against fate♪
♪I have no regrets loving you♪
♪I'm willing to sacrifice for you♪
♪As I wait for your answer♪
♪If love remembers♪
♪The promise I made to you♪
♪Despite going against fate♪
♪I have no regrets loving you♪
♪I'm willing to sacrifice for you♪
♪As I wait for your answer♪