♪Memory of us in the last life♪
♪Still haunts now
and then in quiet nights♪
♪And turn to face
all the long lost times♪
♪Brace the pain♪
♪Let memories wake up from oceans deep♪
♪No place to hide♪
♪No way to run♪
♪New dawn counts down♪
♪I fight♪
♪I cry♪
♪I give up♪
♪Memories forgotten forsaken surround♪
♪Memory of us in the last life♪
♪Still haunts now
and then in quiet nights♪
♪Shivering, waiting for the light♪
♪When morning comes from the other side♪
=Lie to Love=
=Episode 12=
Mr. Li,
what did you promise?
You guaranteed that this auction
would be successful.
There would be no mistakes.
But what is your explanation
for what happened today?
Mr. Roman,
don't worry.
I am sorry for what happened today.
But please trust me.
I will get to the bottom of the matter.
I will give you a satisfactory answer.
Also,
I'm not sure if the singer was poisoned
by the wine?
If so,
that glass of wine was originally
served to my wife.
You must
get to the bottom of the matter!
I will give you one day.
Within a day,
please give me a reasonable explanation.
And it must not affect
Fujiade's image.
Or else, I will pull out
of the exhibition.
All losses
shall be borne by you.
Mr. Ro...
Oscar.
How's he now?
(Ambulance)
Everyone in the trade knows
that it can be used
to wipe the bracelet.
And I
am about to wipe the pick.
I need it in a while.
Mr. Huo,
I have no idea what's going on.
How could it be that guy?
Don't panic.
What's most important now
is to get rid of
all evidence and clues.
Yes.
I will deal with it right away.
Chen Heng Sheng?
(Ming Hao)
Mr. Ji.
Give me the car key.
Where are you going?
This is Mr. Li's car.
Inform Li Ze Liang
that I've found
the evidence of Oscar's poisoning.
I'll call him later.
Li Ze Liang.
(Fujiade Auction Reception)
Where's Su Xie Yi?
No idea.
I'm also looking for her.
I tried calling her,
but she didn't pick up my call.
I don't know what happened to her.
If anything happens to Xie Yi again,
you will answer for it.
Mr. Li!
Miss Su drove your car away.
She said she had found
the evidence of Oscar's poisoning.
Did she say where she was going?
No.
Su Xie Yi is really...
(Su Xie Yi)
Su Xie Yi,
where are you?
I'm tailing Chen Heng Sheng.
He must be thinking
of using the fact
that Mrs. Roman only drinks
gin and tonic
I made
and laced the lemons with poison.
Now, he's afraid that the matter
will come to light.
He must be getting rid of
the problematic lemons now.
Chen Heng Sheng?
That box of lemons is the evidence.
I can't let him destroy it.
Su Xie Yi,
send me
your location now.
I will come to you right away.
Before I arrive,
don't take any impulsive action.
Do you hear me?
Okay.
Wait for me here.
No one
should know about this matter.
Got it.
(Nanshangong Road)
(Ainong Biochemical Technology Park,
Warehouse No. 16)
Xie Yi.
(Chen Heng Sheng)
It's Chen Heng Sheng.
Hello.
It's bad.
I was exposed.
What?
When I was getting rid of the lemons,
Su Xie Yi saw me.
I've knocked her out.
Su Xie Yi?
She has been knocked out?
Yes.
She saw me.
I had no choice.
What should I do now?
I didn't want to hurt anyone.
Xie Yi!
Gosh.
Li Ze Liang is here.
What should I do now?
What should we do?
The police will suspect me.
I have a long life ahead.
I don't want
to spend the rest of my life in prison.
Xie Yi!
He's getting nearer.
He'll definitely notice Su Xie Yi.
What about
we turn ourselves in?
Shut up!
Why are you panicking?
Isn't this good?
What are you talking about?
Su Xie Yi!
Have you forgotten
the reason
we did this?
Isn't this
a great opportunity?
A great opportunity?
Use your brain
and think carefully.
As long as they don't turn up
at the press conference tomorrow,
Roman will officially announce
to pull out of the exhibition.
No matter what they do then,
they won't be able to turn the tables.
But...
But I can't
lock them up forever.
They have seen me.
If they testify against me,
I... I will be done for.
Of course, if you insist on
turning yourself in,
I can't stop you.
But your son
may also need to call
for a press conference.
Hello.
Su Xie Yi!
Xie Yi!
I'm here. Over here.
Are you all right?
(Dangerous Pollutants. No Admittance)
Chen Heng Sheng!
Chen Heng Sheng.
Are you aware of
the consequences of your action?
Stop shouting!
I won't hurt you two.
I will turn myself in.
I was forced to do this.
I have no choice!
After the matter is over,
I will come back to release you two!
(Dangerous Pollutants)
Chen Heng Sheng!
Come back!
If those two return,
they won't let Chen Heng Sheng go.
Things will get complicated then.
The lemons have been disposed of.
How will they testify?
They need to show the evidence.
Besides,
Chen Heng Sheng is also
a veteran at Ocean Hotel.
Well, do you think the shareholders
will believe
Shen Zhi Hong's daughter
or those on their side?
You're right.
I didn't expect Su Xie Yi
to be such a great pawn.
Men
can't live
without women.
Are you talking about yourself
or him?
Once men are trapped by a relationship,
they can't achieve great things.
If you follow me obediently,
you will be treated well.
There's no signal here either.
There isn't any signal
in here.
This must be
an abandoned chemical plant.
And below here
must be
a chemical warehouse.
To prevent the radiofrequency radiation
from the mobile phone
from igniting
the volatile chemical substances,
the entire warehouse
must have been
installed with a signal jammer.
Looks like
we can only wait here.
Yan,
have I done something very risky?
I rushed over to find you
recklessly.
That's also considered risky.
You just wanted
to do something for me.
You have a rather high EQ.
Well, you won't change
even if I scold you.
You're right.
Actually, this is considered good too.
There's no signal here.
We can't use our phones.
There's nothing much to bother us.
No one will bother us too.
(Sorry.)
(The number you've dialed)
(cannot be reached at the moment.)
(Please try again later.)
(Sorry.)
Previously, why didn't you
pass the medicine to me directly?
Didn't you have
Mr. Xie's medicine with you?
You don't need mine.
What are you saying?
I need it.
Ming Hao has always taken care
of my older sister and me.
He's like my family.
But you are different.
How so?
You know it well.
I've seen a movie.
In the vast starry sky,
there's a mysterious hole
where people can travel
through time and space.
It's the wormhole.
In the movie, it's known by
a very beautiful name,
the Rainbow Bridge.
Yan.
I really want to return
to the day we met.
I thought that would be
the beginning of my happiness.
I never thought everything
would change after that.
At least, there's one thing
that has never changed.
What is it?
I've never forgotten about you.
I've never forgotten about you
for even just one second.
Although I didn't know who you were
and where you went,
I kept looking forward
to your return.
If the Rainbow Bridge does exist,
I hope we can return
to an earlier time in the past.
This way,
I may encounter you earlier.
Xie Yi,
am I greedy?
Xie Yi.
What's wrong?
Are you sleepy?
No.
Just a little dizzy.
Dizzy?
(Toxic)
Not good.
There must be some traces
of chemicals left in these containers.
Let's get out of here first.
Come on. Get up.
Get to the back.
Be careful.
Come on. Sit down.
How do you feel?
I'm fine.
Here.
Hold this.
Wait for me.
The poisonous gas is getting stronger.
We must get out of here now.
Xie Yi,
did you see
the black pipe?
There must be a transom
overhead.
Now,
I'll climb up the pipe
and break the window
so we can get out of here.
Then, I'll pull you up.
You must be careful.
Don't worry.
I'm a rock climber.
Climb slowly.
Be careful.
Xie Yi,
stand to the side.
I'm going to break the window.
Be careful. Don't get yourself hurt.
Be careful.
Xie Yi,
I did it!
wait for a while.
I'll pull you up!
♪Memory of us in the last life♪
♪Still haunts now
and then in quiet nights♪
♪Shivering, waiting for the light♪
Tie the rope
around your waist.
I'll pull you up.
♪When morning comes from the other side♪
♪Looking around, don't want to be found♪
♪In silence, I become♪
♪Tired of trying to go on♪
♪I am lost in the mist of time♪
♪I'm so scared♪
Hang in there.
♪I must run and never look behind♪
♪Memory of us in darkened sky♪
Extend your hand.
♪Can I be really born another kind♪
♪Shivering, waiting for the light♪
♪When morning comes from the other side♪
We've finally gotten out.
Yan,
we've finally gotten out.
Yan.
Yan, what's wrong?
Yan,
your leg.
I'm fine.
When I was climbing up,
I accidentally scratched it.
Let's go.
I'll send you to the hospital.
Come on.
Yan,
you must hang in there.
Hang in there.
Xie Yi,
don't worry.
I'll hang in there.
I'll be fine.
I don't want anything to happen to you.
Come on.
We'll go to the hospital.
(Yunfeng Hotel, Meeting Room)
Ms. Shi,
the online discussion has died down.
Public opinion is under control.
We've contacted the media.
At 2:00 tomorrow afternoon,
we'll be holding a press conference.
Good.
Ms. Shi.
Mr. Oscar's lab report
is here.
(Jiangcheng City First People's Hospital)
It is confirmed that bongkrekic acid
has caused a toxic reaction.
This toxin
is most commonly found in starchy foods
and fungi that have gone bad.
Have you inspected the kitchen?
I've inspected everything.
No such toxin has been found.
But what is strange is
the toxin is found
in the last glass of wine
that Mr. Oscar drank.
Where's Miss Su?
She has gone missing after the incident.
I can't reach her by phone.
Ms. Shi,
although public opinion
is under control,
many of the hotel guests
want to check out.
Well,
invite the local top food safety experts
immediately
to conduct a test on
all the ingredients in the hotel.
At the same time,
open up Yunfeng Hotel's kitchen
and invite the hotel guests
to inspect it personally.
If they find anything,
we will take full responsibility.
We must regain
our guests' confidence in us quickly.
Get it?
Yes.
(Ze Liang)
(Sorry.)
(The subscriber you dialed)
(cannot be connected for the moment.)
(Please try again later.)
(Sorry.)
(The subscriber you dialed)
(cannot be connected for the moment.)
(Please...)
(Ji)
Where's Mr. Li?
I can't reach him by phone.
Mr. Li went to look for Miss Su.
Go find Mr. Li now.
I can't reach both of them by phone.
I'm afraid that something
has happened to them.
Okay!
(Jiangcheng Town Hospital
of Traditional Chinese Medicine)
Doctor!
What happened to him?
His leg is injured.
(Pre-inspection and triage)
Quick. The emergency bed.
Here.
Be careful.
Come on.
Come on. Slowly.
Send him to the first aid room.
Madam,
your hand is bleeding too.
Follow me.
I will clean your wound for you.
No need.
I'll wait for him here.
(Yan,)
(let's take care of each other
from now on.)
(All right?)
(All right.)
(Emergency)
(First Aid Room)
Doctor,
how's Yan?
Is he all right?
Don't worry.
Your boyfriend is fine.
But...
But what?
Do you know about his leg?
What is it?
There's a serious abrasion
on his
amputated leg.
It has become inflamed.
It needs to be treated
with antibiotics immediately.
Can you contact
his attending doctor?
I want to know more
about his medications.
I'm not so sure about this.
I only know that he fell
while climbing two years ago.
He fell?
That's strange.
The bone of his left leg is fine.
It doesn't look like an injury
induced by a fall.
I've given him
some broad-spectrum antibiotics.
We'll monitor his situation.
Thank you, doctor.
You're welcome.
(Inpatient Unit)
Normal temperature.
He's recovering well.
But why hasn't he woken up yet?
Don't worry.
The patient needs
sufficient sleep to regain his strength.
Once he has enough sleep,
he'll wake up naturally.
You're tired too.
Get some rest.
I'm fine.
I'll wait for him to wake up.
Okay.
Why is there not a single piece of news
on the internet?
I feel uncomfortable.
How's your recovery?
I feel dizzy and have a migraine.
I feel drained of energy.
I can't even get out of bed.
Then, who ate those fruits
out there?
The nurse.
Stop pretending.
The doctor said you are fine.
Well, you all are quite adept
in public relations.
I thought I could create
my first trending topic.
If you drank the entire glass of wine,
then it might happen to you.
What do you mean?
It has been found
that the toxic reaction
was induced
by bongkrekic acid.
It was found in the wine you drank.
What's going on?
The specifics are still
under investigation.
This toxin is usually found in foods
that have expired and gone bad.
But it was strange
that it was found
in your wine.
It must be the lemon.
What lemon?
I don't have
any solid evidence now.
It's just my deduction.
But there's one thing
I can be sure of.
Drinking milk tea
really can save your life.
I'll get to the point.
This time,
I represent the company
to pay you a visit.
I hope you will cooperate with us
to issue a clarification statement.
Sure.
By the way,
how are things going for Liang?
I can't reach him by phone.
It's only a minor setback.
I believe he can
handle it well.
I brought you some soup
to replenish your body.
Thank you.
But I still feel
dizzy and have a migraine.
I feel drained of energy.
Phone, spoon,
chopsticks, and bowl.
They are too heavy for me now.
I can't hold them.
It's too hard on me.
I'll feed you,
all right?
Okay.
It's hot.
Be careful.
How come I can suddenly
lift my hands?
This must be a miraculous soup.
A miraculous soup.
Well,
for a person who drinks milk tea,
why did you think of going
for the alcohol?
For many things,
we'll only know
whether we like them or not
after trying them.
Has your phone been fixed?
That's not right.
Who are you here to visit?
Initially, I felt touched
when you came and visited me.
But it turns out
that you're still thinking
about the test result
on my phone.
I did not.
I just feel
that I'm responsible
for your broken phone.
All right.
Stop acting.
The screen was fixed a while ago.
I'll show it to you now.
But I have to warn you
that there's one good news
and one bad news.
(Love Test)
(Li Ze Liang & Shi Chu Chu)
Isn't it good news?
It can be considered so.
After all, since childhood,
I achieved high scores
in everything I did.
You're right.
You and Liang
were top students.
And it made me look slow-witted
in comparison.
What about the bad news?
The bad news is
when I entered the data that day,
out of instinct
and conditioned reflex,
I entered
my birth details instead.
What?
What are you doing?
It's not accurate.
I didn't say it's accurate.
Childish.
I'm leaving.
The doctor said
you could be discharged tomorrow.
It's quite accurate.
It's 98 percent.
♪Sailing on the sea of life♪
♪All alone lost on the tide♪
♪Waves of silver glitters blind my eyes♪
♪Another day has gone♪
♪Another night has come♪
♪Take my boat and point it east♪
♪Where the first star holds its place♪
♪When the storm comes hailing down
my face♪
♪I close my eyes and look♪
♪To where you are♪
♪You are my guiding star♪
♪You are the compass in my heart♪
♪Rain or shine, you never falter♪
♪Always on your mark♪
♪You are my guiding star♪
♪With you, I will never lose my way♪
♪Life is a journey♪
♪Taking me back to where you are♪
You've woken up.
Are you hungry?
I'll help you get up
so you can eat something.
The doctor said you must eat
(milk)
more high-protein food
to replenish your energy.
(Blueberry and Nuts Crispy Cereal)
I've bought you
some milk and oatmeal.
Have some later.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
What happened to your hand?
I accidentally scratched it
when I climbed up.
Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
It will recover in a few days.
What's most important now
is your health.
Come on.
Xie Yi,
where's your bracelet?
Didn't I drop my phone?
I traded my bracelet
to the hospital's convenience store.
Otherwise, you won't have these foods.
The bracelet was a gift from your dad.
It means a lot to you.
There's something
that means more to me now.
Finishing all these foods
is the greatest respect
for my bracelet.
Come on.
The doctor said
your leg doesn't look like
being caused by a fall.
You fell from such a high place,
but your bone was fine.
That's really rare.
It's a small hospital.
The doctors have seen fewer cases.
That's not surprising.
By the way,
the doctor also said
that there's some inflammation
on your leg.
He needs to contact
your attending doctor
so he can find a way to treat it.
I know
my own body well.
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
Just leave it
to Ying Song to handle it.
But...
Su Xie Yi,
are you here to ask me questions
or to feed me?
Come on.
♪Baby, I love you♪
♪I feel you, I need you♪
♪I want to be happy because of you♪
♪Blindfold your eyes secretly♪
♪Telling you that I'm by your side♪
♪Just you and I forever♪
♪The train is still moving♪
♪But the seat welcomes a new passenger♪
♪The bell on the platform tolls♪
♪I wave my hands and bid you farewell♪
♪I'm still holding a one-way ticket♪
♪You're on your journey to happiness♪
♪I didn't keep your contact♪
♪And so I ask in secret♪
♪How are you?♪
♪How are you with him?♪
♪I have a bad temper♪
♪He must be better than me♪
♪You have a sentimental mind♪
♪I'm sure he gets you♪
♪Does he hug you when you're upset?♪
♪How are you?♪
♪Is everything okay?♪
♪Do you still want to hear
what I meant to say?♪
♪Romantic words
have all been exploited by love songs♪
♪Dwelling in the past♪
♪No, it's not too hard♪
♪How are you?♪
♪How are you with him?♪
♪You and the fate♪
♪Refuse to give me an answer♪
♪The price you pay to grow up♪
♪Is like a heap of gambling chips♪
♪Our bet is who can move on first♪
♪How are you?♪
♪Is everything okay?♪
♪Life isn't as complicated as imagined♪
♪Silence is my forte♪
♪Pain and struggles♪
♪I'm not afraid of them♪
=Lie to Love=