♪Memory of us in the last life♪
♪Still haunts now
and then in quiet nights♪
♪And turn to face
all the long lost times♪
♪Brace the pain♪
♪Let memories wake up from oceans deep♪
♪No place to hide♪
♪No way to run♪
♪New dawn counts down♪
♪I fight♪
♪I cry♪
♪I give up♪
♪Memories forgotten forsaken surround♪
♪Memory of us in the last life♪
♪Still haunts now
and then in quiet nights♪
♪Shivering, waiting for the light♪
♪When morning comes from the other side♪
=Lie to Love=
=Episode 30=
I found something
on the construction site in Lantian Bay.
Mr. He.
Take a look.
Are you trying to imply
that this inhaler is mine?
You know the reason that I'm here.
We both know what this is about.
Let's have a chat.
What do you want?
I'll hand it over
to the police.
I don't need to remind you
whose fingerprints are on it, right?
Don't keep going down the wrong path.
Miss Su.
You dance so gracefully.
Be honest with me.
Have you been learning how to dance
since you were a kid?
Oh, right, Mr. Dai.
I saw He Jiang Hua walking out here
with an odd look on his face.
Him?
He's just a lackey.
He refuses to do as told.
Thus, the odd look.
Mr. Lawyer, help Mr. Dai out
and advise him
on how to deal with people like him.
It's okay.
People like He Jiang Hua
would set Ocean on fire
simply by egging him on.
How smart can he be?
He thought we would help him.
Right now,
I have something on him.
If I tell him to do something,
he has to do it.
When
he's of no value,
I'll set him up
and send him to prison
and let him rot in there.
He'll pose a threat to us
if we keep him around.
Mr. Dai
is a man of his word.
You're not being yourself today.
Why are you talking so much to him?
Are you trying to help Li Ze Liang
fish for information?
You're thinking too much.
Even if I am,
I won't have a chance to tell him.
Good that you know.
Nice!
Come on.
Hurry. Drink up.
Let's drink our fill.
Come on, Mr. Xie.
No, Mr. Dai.
I have a call to make.
Look at you.
I'll be right back.
Mr. Dai, a toast to you.
Sure. Here.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
- I'll do it.
- How nice of you.
Xie Yi.
Let me do it.
Wait.
She...
I'm sorry.
Let's see. Where did it spill on?
Wait.
It's fine. Really.
Why are you being a stranger?
It's okay now.
This thing doesn't worth a thing.
All right then.
Tell me. What should I do?
Reveal the truth,
including the evil deeds of Xie Ming Hao
and Dai.
If you turn yourself in,
you'll get a lighter sentence.
Mr. Li.
If you think
that I get scared easily,
then, you're wrong.
Many people
use such an inhaler.
You can deal with it
however you want.
I won't see you out.
Look, Mr. Xie.
Don't say I didn't remind you.
(Li Ze Liang)
Things are different
now that you have a girlfriend.
Be sure
to thoroughly remove
(Recording)
the pictures of the girls,
and delete all the chat records
with them.
If she finds out,
you'll have no end of trouble.
Xie Yi, what are you doing?
I'm taking a selfie.
Why don't the three of us
take a photo together?
Give me the phone.
What do you think?
Do I look nice?
It'll be perfect if I'm in it.
Oh, come on.
Showing affection in front of me.
All right. Cut the crap.
Come on. Drink up.
I'll fill it up for you.
Here, Mr. Dai.
Come on. Let's drink.
(Xie Ming Hao, Recording)
(He would set Ocean on fire)
(simply by egging him on.)
(How smart can he be?)
(He thought we would help him.)
(Right now,)
(I have something on him.)
(If I tell him to do something,)
(he has to do it.)
(When)
(he's of no value,)
(I'll set him up)
(and send him to prison)
(and let him rot in there.)
(Zhiwei's bankruptcy)
(had nothing to do with Liang.)
It was all Shen Xie Qing
and Xie Ming Hao's doing.
What do you think I should do?
Push all the blame
on Su Xie Yi?
Then, push her out
and let her come under fire
in order
to protect Ocean's reputation?
(You did this for this woman)
(who's up to no good.)
(Is it worth it?)
(Ms. Shi.)
Don't you think
this whole thing
has many doubtful points?
If you don't want me to say it,
I won't.
But I hope you can wake up.
This isn't the time
to let emotions cloud your judgment!
I'm thinking perfectly straight.
(Ze Liang.)
(I'm sorry.)
(All this while,
I'm the one who let emotions)
(cloud my judgment.)
(This mistake that I made
serves as a wake-up call to me.)
(You two)
(are the ones who know each other best.)
(It's time I let go.)
(Ocean Group)
Ze Liang.
It was Mr. Dai
who requested the stockholders' meeting.
He's coming for you.
I know.
There's a total of nine votes
from the board of directors.
As far as I know,
he has four votes in hand.
I'm the only one who can help you now.
You know that.
Just say the word,
and I won't say no.
Ms. Shi.
This is my own problem.
I don't want to get you dragged into it.
I'm sorry.
I went out to sea last night to fish.
So I got up late.
Good morning, everyone.
(Mr. Dai, you're here.)
(Here. Take a seat.)
(Zhang.)
(How is it?)
Did you receive the softshell turtle?
Is it good?
I caught it myself.
It's very nutritious.
Go on.
This conference room
is a little shabby.
The devil's in the detail.
Like these broken chairs,
the table,
and the people.
They should be weeded out.
You're here, Mr. Li.
Sorry, I didn't notice.
Now that everyone is here,
let's get onto the agenda.
Hold on.
(Ocean Hotel's meeting of stockholders)
Allow me to introduce.
This is Miss Su Xie Yi.
I'm sure everyone knows her.
She's Mr. Dai's
temporary special assistant.
Let's have her set out Zhengde's plans
to everyone.
Hold on.
Xie Yi.
Here. Come here.
Hurry.
Come over.
To make an announcement,
you should do it
at the right place.
(Please.)
(Zhengde and Diying)
(have no objection)
to the stockholders meeting process
received in the morning.
But before moving on
to discuss how to deal
with Ocean's situation,
Diying proposes
to first deal with the accident
that took place in Lantian Bay.
Well, what do Zhengde and Diying propose
that we should do
to deal with the matter
before
moving on with the procedures?
"In view
of the wrong decision
made by Mr. Li Ze Liang
in the Lantian Bay project,
it led
Ocean stock to take a hit.
We suggest
that Mr. Li Ze Liang
must be removed from the post
of chairman.
That's because a tainted chairman
with bad leadership
will do no good
to the company whatsoever."
Come on. Let's vote.
I second that.
Ms. Shi, please take a stand.
It's more than half of the votes.
Mr. Li, I'm so sorry.
You may change seats.
I'll pick for you.
The seat over there looks good.
Please.
All right.
We can now officially
get onto the agenda.
Ms. Shi.
Please preside over the meeting.
- Ming Yue.
Mr. Xie
is now Zhengde's business lawyer,
and Su Xie Yi is now
Mr. Dai's
temporary special assistant.
What nonsense is this?
It's true.
We heard it
when we went to deliver the tea.
Ming Yue.
Didn't you say
that you believed her?
If
there's nothing else,
we'll end the meeting here.
Mr. Li.
Are you in a hurry to go home?
What will you do at home?
Go home to keep your girlfriend company?
Isn't your girlfriend
over there?
I got it messed up.
She's your ex-girlfriend now.
Mr. Xie.
If you ask me,
you're indeed a man of charm.
Both sisters vied with each other
and fell for you at the same time.
Miss Su, especially.
She gave up her position
as the wife of Ocean's chairman,
and fell in love with you.
You have to cherish her.
Dai Zi Ang.
I'm warning you
not to discuss
other people's private matters
in public.
Private matters?
Is it?
In that case,
why not make it public then?
Miss Su.
Have you broken up
with Mr. Li Ze Liang?
Tell them.
That's right.
I broke up with Mr. Li a long time ago.
We have nothing to do
with each other now.
Mr. Li.
How miserable.
You lost your chairman post
and got dumped by your girlfriend.
What's the saying?
Suffering a double loss.
A real pity.
Meeting's over.
How pitiful!
What a real pity!
Su Xie Yi.
Don't you think you've gone too far?
When others
spoke ill of you,
I foolishly
stood up for you.
From the looks of it,
you had me fooled, hadn't you?
Look what you've done to Mr. Li
and Ocean.
You're such a cold-blooded
and ruthless woman.
Was it all
just a show?
I'm sorry.
I've checked and verified it
through the fund company.
You were right.
In order
to take over Ocean,
Dai has gambled away
his whole fortune
to fight this battle with you.
How much did he pledge?
All twenty percent
of Zhengde stocks that he owns
was pledged to Aihong Fund.
According
to the performance guarantee ratio,
Zhengde's stock price
cannot fall below 30 percent.
Otherwise, it is likely
to be forced to liquidate.
He sure is aggressive.
That's right.
At that time,
Zhengde's stock price will plummet.
That Dai dude
will be forced to liquidate.
Do you think he will jump into the sea?
Hou Xiao Dong.
Not only can you sing rock songs,
but you're also even
an expert in finance.
Of course.
Thanks to the influence
from a young age.
I picked it up along the way.
I just
didn't want
to inherit my dad's business.
Ms. Shi.
You put on quite a good show today.
Likewise.
Mr. Li.
Liang.
This was the first time
I begged my dad for something.
It was all for you.
So?
So rock, isn't it?
So today's drinks
are on you.
No problem.
Oh, right.
How are you coping
with today's incident?
Although you guys
told me to believe in Su Xie Yi,
I couldn't wrap my head
around her deeds and words today.
That makes me believe her even more.
Besides,
Xie Yi is secretly helping me.
I received a text message
from Xie Ming Hao.
It was a recording.
Many people
use such an inhaler.
You can deal with it
however you want.
I won't see you out.
(Xie Ming Hao, Recording)
If He Jiang Hua
hears this recording,
he'll go berserk.
But why would it be sent over
by Xie Ming Hao?
Xie Ming Hao would never expose himself.
The only explanation
is that someone else used his phone.
It could only be Xie Yi.
Xie Ming Hao took Xie Yi
to meet Di Zi Ang yesterday.
It's possible that her phone
was taken.
He Jiang Hua
is the deciding factor.
If we can convince him,
there's hope to turn things around.
Mr. He.
Why are you here again?
I've said everything
that needs to be said.
Please leave.
Listen to this.
After that,
you might
get a good picture of things.
(He's just a lackey.)
(He refuses to do as told.)
(Thus, the odd look.)
(People like He Jiang Hua)
(would set Ocean on fire)
(simply by egging him on.)
(How smart can he be?)
(Right now,)
(I have something on him.)
(If I tell him to do something,)
(he has to do it.)
(When)
(he's of no value,)
(I'll set him up)
(and send him to prison)
(and let him rot in there.)
(He'll pose a threat to us)
(if we keep him around.)
(Mr. Dai)
(is a man of his word.)
Dai Zi Ang made you commit arson
because
he wants to have something on you.
That way,
you would have to play along with them.
I've handed
the rhinitis spray to the police.
Do the right thing now.
Mr. Li.
I get what you're saying.
But I can't afford
to mess with these people.
Do you think you can hide from them?
Will the police let you get away?
Will Dai Zi Ang let things slide?
He won't.
He'll only get worse
and make you their accomplice.
At that time,
your sin will keep running deeper.
He could make you commit arson now.
In the future, he can force you to kill.
Right now,
you have only two options.
It's either
you stay right down the path you're on,
or
you step back from the brink.
Of course.
I can help you.
Just come forward
and testify against them,
then Ocean will call off
the damage claim,
and get you the best lawyer.
Cooperate with the police investigation,
and you can obtain leniency.
Mr. He.
I believe
your original intention
when you got into the media industry
was to become
a fighter of justice.
You had a momentary lapse in judgment
and were taken advantage of.
You don't wish
to keep going down
the wrong path either.
Right?
So
as to which path to take,
I believe
you already have the answer
in your heart.
Mr. Li.
What should I do?
Do what you do best
and use it to uncover the truth.
Okay.
This is great, Ze Liang.
He Jiang Hua
has the video recorded
and is willing
to step forward
and testify against them.
When will you
be making the announcement?
Now isn't the time yet.
We have to find Xie Qing first.
I suspect
that Xie Ming Hao hid her somewhere.
But I've followed Xie
for a few days now.
Besides his residence and law firm,
he hasn't been
to any other places.
If Xie Qing is still alive,
she has to eat somehow.
Is it possible
that Xie Ming Hao has her tucked away
in his own apartment?
Mr. Li, I'll investigate it right away.
Coincidentally,
Dai Zi Ang and Xie Ming Hao
asked me out for dinner tonight.
Since they want
to rope me in,
I'll see if I can worm anything
out of them
and meet up with Xie Yi while I'm at it.
Be careful.
It's more than half of the votes.
Mr. Li, I'm so sorry.
You may change seats.
I'll pick for you.
(Ms. Shi was acting
out of the ordinary.)
(She couldn't possibly betray Yan.)
(Why would it be like this?)
Xie Yi.
(Get ready to go out.)
(Mr. Dai arranged a celebration dinner.)
Okay.
What's the matter?
I'm sorry.
I wanted
to take a bath.
But I got distracted.
(Open up!)
(The water's leaking!)
It's you.
You're really something.
You own two units?
And even two wives.
Sorry, let's talk outside.
What's wrong with you?
Two days ago,
I just complimented you
for being a good husband.
(Look at the water leakage.)
(Our ceiling and wallpaper)
(are all wet.)
(How are you going to deal with this?)
I'm so sorry.
The floor drain is clogged.
We didn't know
what had happened.
How about this?
I'll compensate you for your loss.
(On top of that,)
(I'll pay
for the emotional distress caused.)
(You're a pleasant man to deal with.)
(But you have to keep your word.)
Sorry for the trouble.
I'll get going then.
Don't you forget.
I'm sorry.
Xie Yi.
Xie Yi?
How did it go?
It's taken care of.
That's great then.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Leave it.
Clean yourself up.
We're leaving in a bit.
Okay.
(Two units? Two wives?)
(Is my sister in the unit below us?)
So the neighbor downstairs
isn't mad anymore?
Why don't
I buy something for her tomorrow
as a token of apology?
We're neighbors after all.
It's better to get along
with each other.
It's okay.
It's no issue.
That neighbor is a nice person.
Sorry.
I'm late.
My VIPs are here.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ms. Shi?
Are you surprised?
Indeed,
there were some misunderstandings
between us.
But it's all in the past now.
Let bygones
be bygones.
That's right.
We'll all be friends now.
Come on. Take a seat.
Here.
Firstly,
I want to express my deepest gratitude
to Ms. Shi.
After all, your vote
is crucial to me.
Also,
I have one other thing
to ask you, Ms. Shi.
Are you really planning
to sell your stocks in Ocean?
Of course.
There's nothing else
left for me in Ocean.
After the transfer of the stocks,
I'll stop
engaging in wishful thinking about him.
This is great.
How about this?
You can transfer
all your Ocean's stocks to me.
Don't worry.
I'll make sure you're well paid for it.
Tomorrow, I'll get Mr. Xie
to draw up a contract,
and we can sign it as soon as possible.
Nice doing business with you.
Nice doing business with you. Here.
Come on. Let's drink this together.
- Here.
- Bottoms up!
Come on. Let's dig in.
You guys must be starving.
Come on. Dig in.
Let's not wait.
Excuse me.
I'm going to the washroom.
Sure. Help yourself.
Perfect. I'm going to.
Let's go together, Ms. Shi.
Sure.
Okay.
Be my guest.
Mr. Xie, let's eat.
Can we trust Shi Chu Chu?
That depends
on if she dares to sell her stocks.
Just test her out, and we'll know.
Ms. Shi.
Don't be fooled by them.
Yan needs you now
more than ever.
I didn't betray Ze Liang.
Actually, we've been putting on a show.
Ze Liang wants me to tell you
not to worry about Ocean.
He's received
the recording you sent.
This evidence is crucial.
But right now,
there's something more important
that I have to verify with you.
Is your sister still alive?
Is Xie Ming Hao using her
to threaten you?
That's right.
Indeed, she's still alive.
So Ze Liang is right.
He said that your sister
is likely to be locked up
in the apartment building
where Xie Ming Hao lives.
Do you know the exact location?
Ze Liang wants to rescue her.
In the last few days,
I've been observing Xie Ming Hao.
Combining with what you just said,
I can basically tell
that my sister is held
in the apartment
below Xie Ming Hao's unit.
The neighbor from the unit
below said
that Xie Ming Hao
owns two units in the building
and suspects that he has two wives.
That proves that she has met him
downstairs before.
I don't know which unit it is.
But
I guess it's not too far from 1503.
This is great.
This can help us narrow it down.
Xie Ming Hao has been meaning
to take me out for a Western dinner.
How about this?
Tomorrow, I'll ask him out
at 7:00 in the evening.
Help me inform Yan
and tell him to get my sister
out of there.
Don't worry.
But if we get Xie Qing out,
what about you?
Just give me a call and let me know.
There are more solutions
than there are problems.
Be careful.
Mr. Li.
I've checked.
1603 is the only unit in the building
that's registered
under Xie Ming Hao's name.
I'm not surprised.
Xie Ming Hao
is always very cautious.
Even if he has rented another unit,
he'll not use his own name.
Should I get people
to check from house to house?
No.
This will surely
alert Xie Ming Hao.
Before you can find her,
he might already
have her transferred elsewhere.
Xie Yi.
Chu Chu has spoken to me.
I understand whatever you're doing.
But I want to tell you this.
My greatest regret in life
is failing to save Uncle Shen
on that rainy night.
So, tomorrow,
I'm going to get your sister
out of there.
I won't make you sad anymore.
I don't want you to cry
and I won't make you cry again.
Xie Yi.
To the world,
you may be one person.
But to me,
you mean the world.
Xie Yi.
Come back.
Yan.
Wait for my return.
This way, please.
Sir.
I'll ask the kitchen
to get the food ready.
Go on.
Okay.
Do you still remember this song?
This is a famous tango
in Spain.
"Por una Cabeza."
That's right.
It's like the distance between us.
So near,
yet so far like we're separated
by a galaxy.
Do you remember
the first time we met?
Of course.
It was snowing that day.
You were bullied by people
by the side of the road.
Not only were you skinny,
but you were also thinly dressed too.
If I say I was frozen
before I met you,
well, I was melted
the moment I met you.
At that time, the video store behind me
was playing this song.
I will never forget
that moment in my life.
How great would it be
if we could go back in time?
If we could go back in time,
if I could
give you that doll back then,
would I be the one you love?
Ming Hao.
There are no ifs in life.
(This way, please.)
(Hui Hu Apartment)
I left something in the car.
You guys can go ahead.
I'll go and get it.
All right.
We'll wait for you
on the third floor then.
All right.
Okay.
Sir.
Let me introduce this listing.
It's really hard to come by.
Thank you so much
for spending
such a romantic night with me.
Here's a little surprise for you.
Your favorite dessert in Germany.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hi, who's this?
Hi, is this Mr. Xie?
Yes. What is it?
Are you at home?
I'm not. Why?
Two people
came to view the units here.
They look like the creditors
in the photo you showed me.
Are you sure?
It might be a mistake
if it was only one person.
But if both guys resemble the creditors,
it won't be wrong.
Okay. I got it.
Thank you.
Xie Yi.
It's time to leave.
What's the matter?
Someone broke into the house.
I need to go and take a look.
Since someone
gave you a call earlier,
it means they'd take care of it.
At least,
let me finish the dessert first.
I said, go home.
Is anyone in there?
What's the matter?
Hi.
Have you seen this guy?
I don't know him!
Xie Qing!
It's me.
(I'm here!)
Xie Qing!
Wait here for me.
I'll be right back.
Xie Qing?
How are you?
You're having a fever.
Let's go.
Come on.
Xie Qing?
Xie Yi.
Su Xie Yi?
Xie Yi?
♪Memory of us in the last life♪
(I don't want you to cry,)
(and I won't make you cry again.)
(Xie Yi.)
♪Still haunts now and then
in quiet nights♪
(To the world,)
(you may be one person.)
(But to me,)
(you mean the world.)
(Xie Yi.)
(Come back.)
♪Shivering, waiting for the light♪
♪When morning comes from the other side♪
♪And turn to face
all the long lost times♪
Yan.
I'm back.
♪Brace the pain♪
♪Let memories wake up from oceans deep♪
♪I need you. I love you♪
♪I'll brave the waves for you♪
♪You don't need to act tough.
Believe me♪
♪I'll be by your side♪
♪Ever and after♪
♪The train is still moving♪
♪But the seat welcomes a new passenger♪
♪The bell on the platform tolls♪
♪I wave my hands and bid you farewell♪
♪I'm still holding a one-way ticket♪
♪You're on your journey to happiness♪
♪I didn't keep your contact♪
♪And so I ask in secret♪
♪How are you?♪
♪How are you with him?♪
♪I have a bad temper♪
♪He must be better than me♪
♪You have a sentimental mind♪
♪I'm sure he gets you♪
♪Does he hug you when you're upset?♪
♪How are you?♪
♪Is everything okay?♪
♪Do you still want to hear
what I meant to say?♪
♪Romantic words have all
been exploited by love songs♪
♪Dwelling in the past♪
♪No, it's not too hard♪
♪How are you?♪
♪How are you with him?♪
♪You and the fate♪
♪Refuse to give me an answer♪
♪The price you pay to grow up♪
♪Is like a heap of gambling chips♪
♪Our bet is who can move on first♪
♪How are you?♪
♪Is everything okay?♪
♪Life isn't as complicated as imagined♪
♪Silence is my forte♪
♪Pain and struggles♪
♪I'm not afraid of them♪
=Lie to Love=