♪Memory of us in the last life♪
♪Still haunts now
and then in quiet nights♪
♪And turn to face
all the long lost times♪
♪Brace the pain♪
♪Let memories wake up from oceans deep♪
♪No place to hide♪
♪No way to run♪
♪New dawn counts down♪
♪I fight♪
♪I cry♪
♪I give up♪
♪Memories forgotten forsaken surround♪
♪Memory of us in the last life♪
♪Still haunts now
and then in quiet nights♪
♪Shivering, waiting for the light♪
♪When morning comes from the other side♪
=Lie to Love=
=Episode 10=
(Mr. Li.)
(Good thing you had me follow Miss Su.)
(Indeed, someone is on her tail.)
Where is she now?
Don't worry.
Miss Su and Mr. Xie
are on their way back to the city.
She's safe now.
You mean Xie Ming Hao?
(That's right.)
Did you get a clear view
of the person who's following her?
(Rehabilitation Center)
(He was wearing a mask.
I couldn't get a good look.)
(Should I investigate it?)
It's fine.
It's probably Huo Jian's guy.
Xie Ming Hao?
Xie Yi.
You staying in the hotel
isn't a long-term solution.
I'll find you a new place.
You can move in
after you return
from your business trip.
Thanks, Ming Hao.
It's hard enough
having to take care of my sister.
Don't worry about me.
Why are you being such a stranger?
Uncle Shen had supported me.
He was like a father to me.
Even without Xie Qing,
I should take care of you too.
Is there anything urgent?
It's Li Ze Liang.
He told me to return to the hotel
before dark.
For a fake boyfriend,
he seems so immersed in his role.
He's only doing it for my own good.
Besides,
if he hadn't helped me
with Mr. Lin's incident,
who knows
what would have happened?
That's right.
I should really thank him for that.
Ming Hao.
Thanks for giving me a ride.
I'll get going now.
Go on.
Slow down.
Don't run so fast.
I know!
Mr. Li.
We meet again.
Mr. Xie, thank you
for sending my girlfriend back.
But next time,
just give me a call will do.
There's no need to trouble you.
Mr. Li.
You and I both know
Xie Yi
is just your girlfriend in name.
Even so,
that still makes her my girlfriend.
Just like you.
You're her brother-in-law
only in name.
That still makes you her brother-in-law.
Mr. Li.
Xie Yi is going on a business trip
to Yunfeng.
I hope the incidents like the one
with Mr. Lin
won't happen again.
If anything happens to Xie Yi,
I'm not going
to let the matter drop.
Don't worry.
Xie Yi is my special assistant
and also my girlfriend.
I'll take good care of her.
Let's hope so.
These are photos taken from today.
Why does this girl
look so familiar?
Her name is Shen Xie Qing.
That guy is called Xie Ming Hao.
That's right.
It's her.
Shen Zhi Hong's daughter.
If so,
it's not surprising
that Xie Ming Hao shows up here.
They were previously engaged.
I've looked into it.
Shen Xie Qing was admitted
to the hospital
because of a mental disorder.
She disappeared after Zhiwei
went bankrupt
two years ago.
And now, she shows up out of nowhere.
Su Xie Yi even went to see her.
Keep digging.
Make sure
you get to the bottom of things.
This is a counterfeit painting.
Please discard it for me.
Mr. Li.
It took me a lot of effort
to find the co-worker
he used to work with.
I found out from him
that Liu Ah Wei
engaged in such a dangerous job
entirely for his daughter.
His daughter has a hearing impairment.
Is it?
That's right.
According to his co-worker,
he has been talking about a hospital
that specializes
in this type of surgery.
But the surgery and the cochlear implant
require a lot of money.
He's been worrying
about how to pay off the medical bills.
Did you
find out the name of this hospital?
Yes.
He kept talking about it
to his co-worker.
So he remembers the name.
But he disappeared after that.
So we have no idea
if the surgery was done.
Perhaps
we should stop
looking.
You mean...
Huo Jian has been looking for so long,
but he didn't find him.
It shows that the hope of finding him
is very slim.
We can change our method.
Like
starting with
the cochlear implant surgery.
Are you saying
that he really did take his daughter
to have this surgery?
At least, there's a possibility.
If so, where did he get the money
for it?
I did ask around.
This surgery and cochlear implant
require hundreds of thousands.
Imported ones
will be even more expensive.
What if Liu Ah Wei
suddenly has the money
to get this surgery done
for his daughter?
In that case,
his disappearance
will make sense now.
Could it be possible
that he saw something
and used it as a bargaining chip
to extort money?
That will require some digging
before we can be certain.
Understood.
Ying Song, how about this?
Get in touch with that hospital.
I'm willing to donate a sum of money
to them
to set up a special fund
to help children who go to the hospital
for cochlear surgery,
especially those families
with bad financial conditions.
That's great.
Not only can we do our part
to help those children,
but we can also find out
if Liu Ah Wei
did take his daughter there
to have the surgery done.
Remember.
Don't make the donation in Ocean's name
or my name.
Understood.
(Yunfeng Hotel)
Hi, Mr. Li.
I'm Li Fei,
Mr. Chen's special assistant.
We just received news
that you would arrive earlier.
Mr. Chen will be right here.
How about this?
Get someone
to deliver the luggage to the room.
We're going to look around.
All right.
(Xie Yi, stand here. Don't move.)
(I'll hold it for you, all right?)
(Okay.)
(Xie Qing, be careful.)
(I know. Don't move.)
(Xie Qing, you're awesome!)
This place
is well laid out.
When the building was built,
my dad
personally designed the landscape.
He had a great love
for flowers and trees.
So the plants here
were selected with care.
Indeed,
Uncle Shen had a really great taste.
Fortunately, this place
wasn't demolished
during the renovation
of the Yunfeng Hotel.
If not,
we wouldn't get to see this now.
(The wines at Yunfeng)
(have always been
our major source of earnings.)
(The proceeds are highly stable.)
What's the matter?
Have a drink with me.
Isn't it a little early for a drink now?
Let's pick one bottle.
This.
Mr. Li.
Mr. Chen.
Welcome.
Why didn't you tell me
that you were coming earlier?
We didn't even prepare
for the welcome ceremony.
Speaking of which,
that was the reason
why I didn't want to give prior notice.
Understood.
We're just chilling out here
and having a drink.
Miss Su.
You sure
have a unique taste.
That bottle of wine you picked
is indeed a good wine.
But
unfortunately,
it's a bad vintage.
So it tastes slightly inferior.
I think given Mr. Li's status,
you'll be more particular about this.
Besides,
this is the first time
the two of you have come here.
We should prepare
better wines for you.
It's okay, Mr. Chen.
We're just
having a casual drink
to quench our thirst.
Even so,
Mr. Li is different
from other people.
Isn't it, Mr. Li?
You're right, Mr. Chen.
Indeed, this bottle of wine
isn't of the best vintage.
Never mind.
How about this?
I'll get you two
a good wine
as a welcoming reception.
It's okay.
We're here for work.
I want
to hold a meeting at once.
Mr. Chen.
Please see to it.
You sure are a man of action, Mr. Li.
All right then.
I'll leave you two alone.
I'll get them to prepare it at once.
Go on.
Everyone.
You must have heard some stories
about me.
Those rumors aren't fake,
but they aren't entirely true.
For some reason,
I didn't involve myself too much
in the group's operation.
But this is different.
I came to Yunfeng
to host Fujiade Auction.
It's a must to make it a success.
Yunfeng is a subsidiary of Ocean.
The success of this auction
will directly
affect Ocean's reputation.
Should anything go wrong,
I won't be able
to protect any of you
even as the deputy general manager
of Ocean.
Of course.
With your help
and support,
I believe this auction
will be a success.
After all, no one knows Yunfeng
better than you.
So I don't care
how you did things back then
or whose order you took.
I hope from this moment on
you'll understand
what you should do
and whose order you should follow.
Any objection?
- No.
Very well.
The brochure in front of you
is the introduction to the lot
in this auction.
Go back
and study it.
All right.
If there's nothing else,
I won't keep you any longer.
Dismissed.
Here, this way, please.
I was fortunate enough
to witness the romantic moments
between Mr. Li and Miss Su
at the reception.
It makes people green with envy.
So
I specially prepared
this honeymoon suite
for the two of you.
I hope you'll like it.
Xie Yi.
Look
how thoughtful Mr. Chen is.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
It's what I do.
Well, I shall leave you be.
Call me if you need anything.
This way.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
Come on.
Let's go.
Chen Heng Sheng
is a sly old fox.
Honeymoon suite, huh?
He's obviously trying to feel us out.
Don't say that.
He's quite thoughtful.
Look, this bed
is so beautifully prepared.
I couldn't bring myself
to lie down on it.
What are you doing?
The reason they put us
in a room
is to find out
if we're a real couple
or a fake one.
Then,
they'll use housekeeping as the pretext
to look for evidence.
Good thing I came prepared.
I want this room
to be filled with the breath of love.
Brilliant.
(How to win a woman's/men's heart?)
Done!
I'm used to sleeping in a big bed
since I was a kid.
You have to let me take the bed.
Well,
I've never slept on a couch.
You need to learn to yield.
But I'm a girl.
Men and women are equal.
How about this?
Whoever touches the bed first wins.
Spin around three times before we start.
Mr. Li.
You'll lose for sure.
We'll see.
Don't peek.
♪The flower that's been asleep
for too long♪
The one who peeks is an alpaca.
♪Is emanating its fragrance♪
Are you okay?
♪Be my lover♪
I'm fine.
You should just worry about yourself.
♪You're the most beautiful girl
I've ever seen♪
Look at you.
Don't get so competitive.
Keep your arms straight.
♪The brilliant moment of the firework♪
Walk slowly.
♪Says nothing lasts forever♪
Don't knock yourself out
before you reach the bed.
♪Before I can finally hold your hand♪
♪I'll Waltz and tell you♪
♪Because you're my angel♪
♪Baby, I love you♪
♪I feel you, I need you♪
♪I can feel the warmth on my chest
because of you♪
♪Like soda and lemon♪
♪I can't stop bubbling♪
- Sorry.
♪I want you
to have the entire starry sky♪
♪Baby, I love you♪
♪I feel you, I need you♪
♪I want to be happy for you♪
♪I secretly blindfolded you♪
♪I'll tell you where I am♪
♪It's just you and I, forever♪
♪Baby, I love you♪
♪I feel you, I need you♪
♪I want to be happy for you♪
I won!
♪I secretly blindfolded you♪
I'll sleep on the bed tonight!
♪I'll tell you where I am♪
♪Just you and I, forever♪
All right then.
You take the bed,
and I'll take the couch.
We didn't even receive
any notice
and they showed up all of a sudden.
So I didn't get
to swap the wine in time.
But
I have had all the wine
removed from the shelves.
They probably won't find out anything.
Don't throw yourself off the game.
The reason Li Ze Liang came
is for the auction.
Everyone in the company
has their eyes set on him.
He won't create unnecessary problems.
What worries me
is the girl beside him, Su Xie Yi.
She's quite smart.
You should guard against her.
Yes.
She almost
got me into trouble today.
Don't forget.
They are the guests.
You're the host.
Wait to hear from me
on our next course of action.
Since they are here,
we have to show them great hospitality.
All right. I'm on it right now.
(Beverage Sales Table)
Can you lend me the pen?
Why?
To write on the invitation cards.
Haven't all the invitation cards
been printed?
It's too stylized.
I want to include
some handwritten wishes.
Good thinking.
But
how's your handwriting?
Is it okay?
If I had no confidence to even do this,
how would I dare
to become Mr. Li's assistant?
Give it to me.
This pen is...
It was a gift from my dad
the year I was enrolled at the college.
But speaking of which,
people rarely write
with pens now.
What's the matter?
You don't believe me?
You can test me.
You talk, and I'll write.
Sure.
Come on.
I'll talk,
and you write.
"I want to live with you."
(I want)
"Enjoying endless dusk
and hearing endless bell chimes
in a small town."
"I want to relive
the romantic kiss
(With you)
under the stars with you."
Do you still remember
the night we spent together
under the tree
two years ago?
No.
No?
How could you forget?
Hold on.
Where are you going?
Wait for me.
What are you doing?
Let me ask you.
Two years ago,
what was your first impression
of me?
First impression?
My heart was racing.
We were hanging on the cliff.
Whose heart wouldn't be racing?
You?
It was different for me.
Were you not afraid?
I fell in love.
To be honest,
in the past two years or so,
I often recalled
what happened that night.
It was like playing a movie.
Right now,
I still remember that evening,
the starry sky,
and also
your smile under the starry sky.
You described everything
in vivid detail.
It's been two years already.
After some time,
you might come to realize
that it was just
an insignificant moment
over the course
of our lives.
But sometimes,
a moment might be short,
but it's long enough
to illuminate a lifetime.
You know what?
To me,
that night
was such a moment.
♪I need you. I love you♪
♪I'll brave the waves for you♪
♪You don't need to act tough.
Believe me♪
♪I'll be by your side♪
♪To embrace the fragility
right in front of your eyes♪
♪And hug you at the moment
you feel like crying♪
♪You'll always have me♪
What are you doing?
I...
I'm having a toothache.
Su Xie Yi.
Calm down.
Did he just confess to me?
Why did I run out of there?
Would he see that
as a rejection?
Too sloppy.
He was so handsome.
Truly handsome.
Su Xie Yi.
What are you doing?
Have you forgotten
the reason you're here?
You came here
to find Chen Heng Sheng,
not to find a partner.
Su Xie Yi.
No more toothache?
Who are you talking to?
Nothing.
I'm using the washroom.
What's taking you so long?
I'm feeling sleepy already.
I'm going to wash up and go to bed.
So many excuses.
Hello?
Mr. Li.
I've contacted the hospital.
How did they respond?
The hospital is happy
with our charity proposal
because there are indeed
too many families in need of funding.
That's great.
It's a good thing to be able
to help more people in need.
Yes.
It's even better
if we can get a few leads
on Liu Ah Wei.
You need to speed things up.
Okay.
Chestnut, enjoy.
Here's your coffee.
Miss Su.
This is the sales table
for the hotel's food and beverages.
You may have a look.
The auction banquet
is also a top priority.
(Yunfeng Hotel, Food, and Beverages)
We need to pay attention to the food
(Sales Table, Main Course Sales Table)
and beverages served.
The sales table
is a good reference.
You're right.
(Beverage Sales Table)
(Name, Riesling, Commander Red Wine)
(Average monthly sales)
(You sure)
have a unique taste.
That bottle of wine you picked
is indeed a good wine.
But
unfortunately,
it's a bad vintage.
Can I take this
and show it to Mr. Li?
I'm sorry, Miss Su.
This is internal information.
If Mr. Li wants to see it,
I'll personally send it over
for him to have a look.
It's okay.
I'll get some tissues.
Riesling
is the best-selling wine
in your hotel,
but you don't have it here?
Yes, it is currently out of stock.
But I saw it
in the lobby bar yesterday.
I'm not sure about that.
Thank you.
(Wine Cellar, No Admittance)
(That's weird.)
(Why can't I find the wine)
(that I saw in the lobby bar?)
I'm sorry, Mr. Chen.
Be careful.
Is this the last box?
Yes.
Remember.
Be sure to clean it up.
Remember to lock the wine cellar
before you leave.
Yes, I understand.
As for you,
take two days off.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
Go on.
Use the passage for freight handling.
You hear me?
Okay, I get it.
(Riesling)
Mr. Chen, you're here.
Miss Su, what are you doing here?
I heard that Yunfeng's wine cellar
contains a lot of good wines.
How can I not pay a visit?
We're honored
by your visit, Miss Su.
But I wonder
what kind of wine
you'd like.
How about this?
I'll send someone
to deliver the best wine
to your room.
Pick a bottle of wine for Miss Su.
Make sure it's the best.
Send it over to Miss Su's room.
Okay, I'll do it right away.
Hold on.
I heard
that Yunfeng's best-selling white wine
is called Riesling.
But
I couldn't find it.
Why don't you lead the way?
We do have it.
But the price of the wine
is awfully high.
So we rarely restock it.
It's out of stock now.
Well, what's in the box
that you're holding?
No, Miss Su!
Didn't you say it was out of stock?
I must have remembered it wrong.
I'll take this then.
Thank you.
What do you mean by this?
Miss Su, don't get me wrong.
I think
there is no need to bother you
with things like
selecting a bottle of wine, right?
You're a busy man.
There's no need to trouble you
with such a trivial matter.
Don't say that.
Given your status,
you don't have to personally
see to this.
Besides,
no matter how busy I am,
nothing is more important
than attending to Mr. Li.
I think
I should
personally pick a bottle of wine for you
and have it delivered
to your room later.
It's just a bottle of wine.
Are you such a miserly man?
Do you
not trust me,
the manager of Yunfeng?
Xie Yi.
What's taking you so long?
Mr. Li.
Mr. Chen, you're here as well.
I was recommending the wine
to Miss Su earlier.
Come.
What wine?
I picked a bottle of wine.
But Mr. Chen doesn't seem
to be willing to give it to me.
Is it?
Don't get me wrong, Miss Su.
But
since Mr. Li is here,
I'll just come clean with you.
This wine
is indeed
Yunfeng's best-selling wine.
But
there's a problem
with our temperature control
for this batch of wine.
So, the taste isn't as great.
I was thinking
that I can't serve
such a wine
to Mr. Li.
So I was telling Miss Su
earlier
that I came to pick another type of wine
and have it delivered to you later.
Okay.
Let me see.
Mr. Li!
You...
Mr. Li, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Didn't Mr. Chen say
that the taste wasn't as great?
How about this?
Mr. Chen,
send a bottle of the finest wine
to my room later.
Sure.
Let's go.
You did that on purpose earlier.
Why?
What did you promise me?
This wine
is my dad's favorite brand.
I remember the logo on it
very clearly.
As compared to the wine we saw
in the wine cellar,
I'm positive
that those were counterfeit wines.
So?
It means Chen Heng Sheng
is selling counterfeit wines.
Chen Heng Sheng
is the general manager of Yunfeng.
He has a well-established foundation
in Yunfeng.
The preparation of the Fujiade Auction
requires all the manpower
and material resources of Yunfeng.
No one is a better candidate than him
for the time being.
I know.
I just wanted
to find the dirt on him.
I told you I would continue
to investigate Zhiwei.
And you promised
you wouldn't interfere.
I know.
But right now,
the present is more important.
The auction
is very important to me.
The whole company
has its eyes set on me.
I can't mess things up.
Are we going to just let things slide?
Of course not.
See for yourself.
For over a year,
the police have been secretly
investigating Chen Heng Sheng.
I'm trying my best to provide evidence
and work with the police.
Is the evidence sufficient?
That's right.
This is great.
So, to catch the thief red-handed,
the police
are waiting for the right time.
This auction
is the best opportunity.
I can't give it to you just yet.
When can you give it to me then?
After the auction is over,
Cheng Heng Sheng
is going to be brought to justice.
The police will give you the answers
to all your questions.
As for now,
just relax
and do your part as my assistant.
Leave the rest to me.
Promise?
Yes.
All right.
It's a deal then.
Nice working with you.
I've managed to find out
Su Xie Yi's true identity.
She's actually the youngest daughter
of Shen Zhi Hong,
the chairman of Zhiwei Corporation.
She used her mother's last name
and went abroad when she was ten.
So, not many people know her.
So she's Shen Zhi Hong's daughter?
That explains why she wanted
to dig up the files on Zhiwei.
From the looks of it,
her intention of getting into Ocean
is pretty clear now,
which is to investigate
the bankruptcy of Zhiwei.
But why is she
with Li Ze Liang?
The daughter of a bankrupt family
suddenly showed up next to the enemy
and became his girlfriend.
Don't you
find that odd?
Could she be seeking revenge?
It doesn't matter what she thinks.
What matters
is that her identity
as Shen Zhi Hong's daughter
can be used to our advantage.
So you want to make use of that.
Su Xie Yi
may just be
the perfect pawn.
(Fujiade Auction Reception)
There are only four waiters
at the auction reception.
Not enough.
We need to double the manpower.
There's not much variety
for the pastries.
Make it more lavish.
Okay.
How is it, Xie Yi?
The preparations
for the auction reception
are basically ready.
Tomorrow, Mr. Huo
will accompany the Romans to Yunfeng.
The invited guests
will be arriving soon after.
Miss Su is very capable.
Everything is arranged
in an orderly manner.
That's right.
After the auction,
I'll have to reward you.
Mr. Chen.
Be my witness.
Of course.
It's been hard on you too, Mr. Chen.
Thank you for your support.
Don't say that.
Should you have any requests,
don't hesitate to tell us.
We'll do our best
to cater to your needs.
All right.
I'll leave you be then.
I'm going
to check up on the progress
of the banquet.
Mr. Li.
I have to say.
You have found yourself
a really good partner.
Thank you for your hard work.
This is nothing.
All right. Excuse me.
After the auction is over,
don't forget what you promised me.
Don't worry.
Oh, right.
As for the opening of the reception,
you said
that you've invited
a very talented rock singer.
Which celebrity is that?
You'll know when he gets here.
Where is he now?
He needs to rehearse in advance.
He should be here soon.
♪Baby, I love you♪
♪I feel you, I need you♪
♪I want to be happy for you♪
♪I secretly blindfolded you♪
♪I'll tell you where I am♪
♪Just you and I, forever♪
♪The train is still moving♪
♪But the seat welcomes a new passenger♪
♪The bell on the platform tolls♪
♪I wave my hands and bid you farewell♪
♪I'm still holding a one-way ticket♪
♪You're on your journey to happiness♪
♪I didn't keep your contact♪
♪And so I ask in secret♪
♪How are you?♪
♪How are you with him?♪
♪I have a bad temper♪
♪He must be better than me♪
♪You have a sentimental mind♪
♪I'm sure he gets you♪
♪Does he hug you when you're upset?♪
♪How are you?♪
♪Is everything okay?♪
♪Do you still want to hear
what I meant to say?♪
♪Romantic words have all
been exploited by love songs♪
♪Dwelling in the past♪
♪No, it's not too hard♪
♪How are you?♪
♪How are you with him?♪
♪You and the fate♪
♪Refuse to give me an answer♪
♪The price you pay to grow up♪
♪Is like a heap of gambling chips♪
♪Our bet is who can move on first♪
♪How are you?♪
♪Is everything okay?♪
♪Life isn't as complicated as imagined♪
♪Silence is my forte♪
♪Pain and struggles♪
♪I'm not afraid of them♪
=Lie to Love=