♫  Memory of us in the last life  ♫
♫  Still haunts now and then in quiet nights  ♫
♫  And turn to face all the long lost times  ♫
♫  Brace the pain  ♫
♫  Let memories wake up from oceans deep  ♫
♫  No place to hide  ♫
♫  No way to run  ♫
♫  New dawn counts down  ♫
♫  I fight  ♫
♫  I cry  ♫
♫  I give up  ♫
♫  Memories forgotten, forsaken surround  ♫
♫  Memory of us in the last life  ♫
♫  Still haunts now and then in quiet nights  ♫
♫  Shivering, waiting for the light  ♫
♫  When morning comes from the other side  ♫
I found something on the construction site in Lantian Bay.
Mr. He. Take a look.
Are you trying to imply that this inhaler is mine?
You know the reason that I'm here.
We both know what this is about.
Let's have a chat.
What do you want?
I'll hand it over to the police.
I don't need to remind you whose fingerprints are on it, right?
Don't keep going down the wrong path.
Miss Su. You dance so gracefully.
Be honest with me. Have you been learning how to dance since you were a kid?
Oh, right, President Dai.
I saw He Jianghua walking out here with an odd look on his face.
Him? He's just a lackey.
He refuses to do as told. Thus, the odd look.
Mr. Lawyer, help President Dai out and advise him
on how to deal with people like him.
It's okay.
People like He Jianghua would set Ocean on fire simply by egging him on.
How smart can he be?
He thought we would help him.
Right now, I have something on him.
If I tell him to do something, he has to do it.
When he's of no value, I'll set him up and send him to prison
and let him rot in there.
He'll pose a threat to us if we keep him around.
President Dai is a man of his word.
You're not being yourself today.
Why are you talking so much to him?
Are you trying to help Li Zeliang fish for information?
You're thinking too much.
Even if I am, I won't have a chance to tell him.
Good that you know.
Nice!
Come on. Hurry. Drink up.
Let's drink our fill. Come on, Lawyer Xie.
No, President Dai. I have a call to make.
- Look at you.
- I'll be right back.
President Dai, a toast to you.
Sure. Here.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- I'll do it.
- How nice of you.
Xieyi.
Let me do it.
- Wait. She...
- I'm sorry.
- Let's see. Where did it spill on?
- Wait.
It's fine. Really.
Why are you being a stranger?
It's okay now. This thing doesn't worth a thing.
All right then. Tell me. What should I do?
Reveal the truth including the evil deeds of Xie Minghao and Dai.
If you turn yourself in, you'll get a lighter sentence.
Chairman Li.
If you think that I get scared easily, then, you're wrong.
Many people use such an inhaler.
You can deal with it however you want.
I won't see you out.
Look, Lawyer Xie.
Don't say I didn't remind you.
Things are different now that you have a girlfriend.
Be sure to thoroughly remove
the pictures of the girls, and delete all the chat records with them.
If she finds out,
you'll have no end of trouble.
Xieyi, what are you doing?
I'm taking a selfie.
Why don't the three of us take a photo together?
Give me the phone.
What do you think? Do I look nice?
It'll be perfect if I'm in it.
Oh, come on. Showing affection in front of me.
All right. Cut the crap. Come on. Drink up.
- I'll fill it up for you.
- Here, Mr. Dai.
Come on. Let's drink.
He would set Ocean on fire simply by egging him on.
How smart can he be?
He thought we would help him.
Right now, I have something on him.
If I tell him to do something, he has to do it.
When he's of no value,
I'll set him up and send him to prison and let him rot in there.
Zhiwei's bankruptcy had nothing to do with A'Liang.
It was all Shen Xieqing and Xie Minghao's doing.
What do you think I should do?
Push all the blame on Su Xieyi?
Then, push her out and let her come under fire
in order to protect Ocean's reputation?
You did this for this woman who's up to no good. Is it worth it?
Director Shi.
Don't you think this whole thing has many doubtful points?
If you don't want me to say it, I won't.
But I hope you can wake up.
This isn't the time to let emotions cloud your judgment!
I'm thinking perfectly straight.
Zeliang. I'm sorry.
All this while, I'm the one who let emotions cloud my judgment.
This mistake that I made serves as a wake-up call to me.
You two are the ones who know each other best.
It's time I let go.
Zeliang. It was President Dai who requested the stockholders' meeting.
He's coming for you.
I know.
There's a total of nine votes from the board of directors.
As far as I know, he has four votes in hand.
I'm the only one who can help you now.
You know that. Just say the word, and I won't say no.
Director Shi. This is my own problem.
I don't want to get you dragged into it.
I'm sorry.
I went out to sea last night to fish.
So I got up late. Good morning, everyone.
President Dai, you're here. Here. Take a seat.
Old Zhang, how is it? Did you receive the softshell turtle?
Is it good?
I caught it myself.
It's very nutritious.
Go on.
This conference room is a little shabby.
The devil's in the detail.
Like these broken chairs,
the table, and the people.
They should be weeded out.
You're here, Chairman Li. Sorry, I didn't notice.
Now that everyone is here,
let's get onto the agenda.
Hold on.
Allow me to do some introdcution. This is Miss Su Xieyi.
I'm sure everyone knows her.
She's President Dai's temporary special assistant.
Let's have her set out. Zhengde's plans to everyone.
Hold on.
Xieyi. Here. Come here.
Hurry. Come over.
To make an announcement, you should do it at the right place.
Please.
Zhengde and Diying have no objection to the stockholders meeting process received in the morning.
But before moving on to discuss
how to deal with Ocean's situation,
Diying proposes
to first deal with the accident that took place in Lantian Bay.
Well, what do Zhengde and Diying propose that we should do to deal with the matter
before moving on with the procedures?
"In view of the wrong decision made by Mr. Li Zeliang in the Lantian Bay project,
it led Ocean stock to take a hit.
We suggest
that Mr. Li Zeliang must be removed from the post of chairman.
That's because a tainted chairman with bad leadership
will do no good to the company whatsoever."
Come on. Let's vote.
I second that.
Director Shi, please take a stand.
It's more than half of the votes.
Chairman Li, I'm so sorry.
You may change seats. I'll pick for you.
The seat over there looks good.
Please.
All right. We can now officially get onto the agenda.
Director Shi, please preside over the meeting.
- Sister Mingyue.
Lawyer Xie is now Zhengde's business lawyer,
and Su Xieyi is now President Dai's temporary special assistant.
What nonsense is this?
It's true. We heard it when we went to deliver the tea.
Sister Mingyue. Didn't you say that you believed her?
If there's nothing else, we'll end the meeting here.
Mr. Li.
Are you in a hurry to go home? What will you do at home?
Go home to keep your girlfriend company?
Isn't your girlfriend over there?
I got it messed up.
She's your ex-girlfriend now.
Lawyer Xie, if you ask me, you're indeed a man of charm.
Both sisters vied with each other and fell for you at the same time.
Miss Su, especially.
She gave up her position as the wife of Ocean's chairman and fell in love with you.
You have to cherish her.
Dai Ziang.
I'm warning you not to discuss other people's private matters in public.
Private matters? Is it?
In that case, why not make it public then?
Miss Su.
Have you broken up with Mr. Li Zeliang?
Tell them.
That's right.
I broke up with Mr. Li a long time ago.
We have nothing to do with each other now.
Mr. Li, how miserable.
You lost your chairman post and got dumped by your girlfriend.
What's the saying? Suffering a double loss.
A real pity. Meeting's over. How pitiful!
What a real pity!
Su Xieyi, don't you think you've gone too far?
When others spoke ill of you, I foolishly stood up for you.
From the looks of it, you had me fooled, hadn't you?
Look what you've done to Chairman Li and Ocean.
You're such a cold-blooded and ruthless woman.
Was it all just a show?
I'm sorry.
I've checked and verified it through the fund company.
You were right.
In order to take over Ocean, Dai
has gambled away his whole fortune
to fight this battle with you.
How much did he pledge?
All twenty percent of Zhengde stocks that he owns was pledged to Aihong Fund.
According to the performance guarantee ratio,
Zhengde's stock price cannot fall below 30 percent.
Otherwise, it is likely to be forced to liquidate.
He sure is aggressive.
That's right.
At that time, Zhengde's stock price will plummet.
That Dai dude will be forced to liquidate.
Do you think he will jump into the sea?
Hou Xiaodong.
Not only can you sing rock songs, but you're also even an expert in finance.
Of course.
Thanks to the influence from a young age. I picked it up along the way.
I just didn't want to inherit my dad's business.
Director Shi, you put on quite a good show today.
Likewise, Chairman Li.
A'Liang, this was the first time I begged my dad for something.
It was all for you.
So? So rock, isn't it?
So today's drinks are on you.
No problem.
Oh, right.
How are you coping with today's incident?
Although you guys told me to believe in Su Xieyi,
I couldn't wrap my head around her deeds and words today.
That makes me believe her even more.
Besides, Xieyi is secretly helping me.
I received a text message from Xie Minghao.
It was a recording.
Many people use such an inhaler.
You can deal with it however you want.
I won't see you out.
If He Jianghua hears this recording, he'll go berserk.
But why would it be sent over by Xie Minghao?
Xie Minghao would never expose himself.
The only explanation is that someone else used his phone.
It could only be Xieyi.
Xie Minghao took Xieyi to meet Di Ziang yesterday.
It's possible that her phone was taken.
He Jianghua is the deciding factor.
If we can convince him, there's hope to turn things around.
Mr. He.
Why are you here again?
I've said everything that needs to be said.
Please leave.
Listen to this.
After that, you might get a good picture of things.
He's just a lackey.
He refuses to do as told. Thus, the odd look.
People like He Jianghua would set Ocean on fire simply by egging him on.
How smart can he be?
Right now, I have something on him.
If I tell him to do something, he has to do it.
When he's of no value,
I'll set him up and send him to prison and let him rot in there.
He'll pose a threat to us if we keep him around.
President Dai is a man of his word.
Dai Ziang made you commit arson
because he wants to have something on you.
That way, you would have to play along with them.
I've handed the rhinitis spray to the police. Do the right thing now.
Chairman Li.
I get what you're saying.
But I can't afford to mess with these people.
Do you think you can hide from them?
Will the police let you get away?
Will Dai Ziang let things slide?
He won't.
He'll only get worse and make you their accomplice.
At that time, your sin will keep running deeper.
He could make you commit arson now.
In the future, he can force you to kill.
Right now, you have only two options.
It's either you stay right down the path you're on, or
you step back from the brink.
Of course.
I can help you.
Just come forward and testify against them,
then Ocean will call off the damage claim,
and get you the best lawyer.
Cooperate with the police investigation,
and you can obtain leniency.
Mr. He. I believe
your original intention when you got into the media industry
was to become a fighter of justice.
You had a momentary lapse in judgment and were taken advantage of.
You don't wish to keep going down the wrong path either.
Right?
So as to which path to take,
I believe you already have the answer in your heart.
Chairman Li. What should I do?
Do what you do best and use it to uncover the truth.
Okay.
This is great, Zeliang.
He Jianghua has the video recorded and is willing to step forward and testify against them.
When will you be making the announcement?
Now isn't the time yet.
We have to find Xieqing first.
I suspect that Xie Minghao hid her somewhere.
But I've followed Lawyer Xie for a few days now.
Besides his residence and law firm, he hasn't been to any other places.
If Xieqing is alive...
at least she has to eat.
Is it possible that Xie Minghao has her tucked away in his own apartment?
Mr. Li, I'll investigate it right away.
Coincidentally, Dai Ziang and Xie Minghao asked me out for dinner tonight.
Since they want to rope me in,
I'll see if I can worm anything out of them and meet up with Xieyi while I'm at it.
Be careful.
It's more than half of the votes.
Chairman Li, I'm so sorry.
You may change seats. I'll pick for you.
Director Shi was acting out of the ordinary.
She couldn't possibly betray A'Yan.
Why would it be like this?
Xieyi.
Xieyi. Get ready to go out.
President Dai arranged a celebration dinner.
Okay.
What's the matter?
I'm sorry.
I wanted to take a bath. But I got distracted.
Open up! The water's leaking!
It's you.
You're really something. You own two units? And even two wives.
Sorry, let's talk outside.
What's wrong with you?
Two days ago, I just complimented you for being a good husband.
Look at the water leakage.
Our ceiling and wallpaper are all wet. How are you going to deal with this?
I'm so sorry.
The floor drain is clogged. We didn't know what had happened.
How about this? I'll compensate you for your loss.
On top of that, I'll pay for the emotional distress caused.
You're a pleasant man to deal with.
But you have to keep your word.
Sorry for the trouble.
I'll get going then. Don't you forget.
I'm sorry.
Xieyi.
How did it go?
It's taken care of.
That's great then.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Leave it. Clean yourself up. We're leaving in a bit.
Okay.
Two units? Two wives?
Is my sister in the unit below us?
So the neighbor downstairs isn't mad anymore?
Why don't I buy something for her tomorrow as a token of apology?
We're neighbors after all.
It's better to get along with each other.
It's okay. It's no issue.
That neighbor is a nice person.
Sorry.
I'm late.
My VIPs are here.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Director Shi?
Are you surprised?
Indeed, there were some misunderstandings between us.
But it's all in the past now.
Let bygones be bygones.
That's right. We'll all be friends now.
Come on. Take a seat.
Here.
Firstly, I want to express my deepest gratitude to Director Shi.
After all, your vote is crucial to me.
Also, I have one other thing to ask you, Director Shi.
Are you really planning to sell your stocks in Ocean?
Of course.
There's nothing else left for me in Ocean.
After the transfer of the stocks,
I'll stop engaging in wishful thinking about him.
This is great. How about this?
You can transfer all your Ocean's stocks to me.
Don't worry. I'll make sure you're well paid for it.
Tomorrow, I'll get Lawyer Xie to draw up a contract, and we can sign it as soon as possible.
- Nice doing business with you.
- Nice doing business with you. Here.
Come on. Let's drink this together.
- Here.
- Bottoms up!
Come on. Let's dig in.
You all must be starving. Come on. Dig in. Let's not wait.
Excuse me. I'm going to the washroom.
Sure. Help yourself.
Perfect. I'm going to.
Let's go together, Director Shi.
- Sure.
- Okay.
Be my guest.
Lawyer Xie, let's eat.
Can we trust Shi Chuchu?
That depends on if she dares to sell her stocks.
Just test her out, and we'll know.
Director Shi, don't be fooled by them.
A'Yan needs you now more than ever.
I didn't betray Zeliang.
Actually, we've been putting on a show.
Zeliang wants me to tell you not to worry about Ocean.
He's received the recording you sent. This evidence is crucial.
But right now, there's something more important that I have to verify with you.
Is your sister still alive?
Is Xie Minghao using her to threaten you?
That's right.
Indeed, she's still alive.
So Zeliang is right.
He said that your sister is likely to be locked up in the apartment building where Xie Minghao lives.
Do you know the exact location?
Zeliang wants to rescue her.
In the last few days, I've been observing Xie Minghao.
Combining with what you just said,
I can basically tell that my sister is held in the apartment below Xie Minghao's unit.
The neighbor from the unit below said that Xie Minghao owns two units in the building,
and suspects that he has two wives.
That proves that she has met him downstairs before.
I don't know which unit it is.
But I guess it's not too far from 1503.
This is great. This can help us narrow it down.
Xie Minghao has been meaning to take me out for a Western dinner.
How about this?
Tomorrow, I'll ask him out at 7:00 in the evening.
Help me inform A'Yan and tell him to get my sister out of there.
Don't worry.
But if we get Xieqing out, what about you?
Just give me a call and let me know.
There are more solutions than there are problems.
Be careful.
Mr. Li.
I've checked. 1603 is the only unit in the building that's registered under Xie Minghao's name.
I'm not surprised.
Xie Minghao is always very cautious.
Even if he has rented another unit, he'll not use his own name.
Should I get people to check from house to house?
No. This will surely alert Xie Minghao.
Before you can find her, he might already have her transferred elsewhere.
Xieyi. Chuchu has spoken to me.
I understand whatever you're doing. But I want to tell you this.
My greatest regret in life
is failing to save Uncle Shen on that rainy night.
So, tomorrow,
I'm going to get your sister out of there.
I won't make you sad anymore.
I don't want you to cry, and I won't make you cry again.
Xieyi.
To the world, you may be one person.
But to me, you mean the world.
Xieyi. Come back.
A'Yan.
Wait for my return.
This way, please.
Sir, I'll ask the kitchen to get the food ready.
- Go on.
- Okay.
Do you still remember this song?
This is a famous tango. "Por una Cabeza."
That's right. "Por una Cabeza."
It's like the distance between us.
So near, yet so far like we're separated by a galaxy.
Do you remember the first time we met?
Of course.
It was snowing that day.
You were bullied by people by the side of the road.
Not only were you skinny, but you were also thinly dressed too.
If I say I was frozen before I met you,
well, I melted the moment I met you.
At that time, the video store behind me was playing this song.
I will never forget that moment in my life.
How great would it be if we could go back in time?
If we could go back in time,
if I could give you that doll back then,
would I be the one you love?
Brother Minghao. There are no ifs in life.
This way, please.
I left something in the car. You guys can go ahead.
I'll go and get it.
All right. We'll wait for you on the third floor then.
- All right.
- Okay.
Sir, let me introduce this listing. It's really hard to come by.
Thank you so much for spending such a romantic night with me.
Here's a little surprise for you.
Your favorite dessert in Germany.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hi, who's this?
Hi, is this Lawyer Xie?
Yes. What is it?
Are you at home?
I'm not. Why?
Two people came to view the units here.
They look like the creditors in the photo you showed me.
Are you sure?
It might be a mistake if it was only one person.
But if both guys resemble the creditors, it won't be wrong.
Okay. I got it. Thank you.
Xieyi. It's time to leave.
What's the matter?
Someone broke into the house. I need to go and take a look.
Since someone gave you a call earlier, it means they'd take care of it.
At least, let me finish the dessert first.
I said, let's go home.
Is anyone in there?
- What's the matter?
- Hi.
Have you seen this guy?
I don't know him!
Xieqing!
It's me.
I'm here!
Xieqing! Xieqing!
Wait here for me. I'll be right back.
Xieqing? Xieqing?
How are you?
You're having a fever. Let's go.
Come on.
Xieqing?
Xieyi.
Su Xieyi?
Xieyi?
♫  Memory of us in the last life  ♫
I don't want you to cry,
and I won't make you cry again.
Xieyi.
To the world, you may be one person.
But to me, you mean the world.
Xieyi. Come back.
♫  Shivering, waiting for the light  ♫
♫  When morning comes from the other side  ♫
♫  And turn to face all the long lost times  ♫
A'Yan, I'm back.
♫  Brace the pain  ♫
♫  Let memories wake up from oceans deep  ♫
♫  I need you, I love you  ♫
♫  I'll brave the waves for you  ♫
♫  You don't have to be brave all the time  ♫
♫  Please believe that I am by your side  ♫
♫  Ever and after  ♫
♫  Halfway through the journey on the train,  ♫
♫  a new passenger takes a seat   ♫
♫  The bells on the platform are ringing  ♫
♫  I wave my hands to see the passengers off  ♫
♫  With a one-way ticket stub in your hand  ♫
♫  you've embarked on a journey to happiness  ♫
♫  I didn't save your contact information  ♫
♫  But in my heart, I secretly ask  ♫
♫  How have you been lately?  ♫
♫  How's it going with him?  ♫
♫  I bet his temper  ♫
♫  is better than mine  ♫
♫  He's better at guessing  ♫
♫  your complicated thoughts  ♫
♫  Does he hold you when you're sad?  ♫
♫  How have you been lately?  ♫
♫  Everything must be going well  ♫
♫  Do you want to hear what I haven't said?  ♫
♫  Do lyrics of love songs stir up your emotions  ♫
♫  and recall all of our memories?  ♫
♫  It doesn't seem to be difficult  ♫
♫  How have you been lately?  ♫
♫  How's it going with him?  ♫
♫  You and fate  ♫
♫  have not given me an answer  ♫
♫  The price of growing up  ♫
♫  is like a pile of bargaining chip  ♫
♫  The wager is who can let go first  ♫
♫  How have you been lately?  ♫
♫  Everything must be going well  ♫
♫  Life is not as complicated as I thought  ♫
♫  Silence is the best that I can do  ♫
♫  Whatever pain and suffering may come,  ♫
♫  I'm not afraid at all  ♫