=Be Not Meant To Be=
=Episode 19=
What are you afraid of?
When you stabbed me,
you were just fearless.
Lu Zhuo.
If you keep pestering me,
I'll call for help.
Go ahead.
That way, your fiancé will find out
you're seducing another man.
- You're humiliating me.
- Yes, I'm humiliating you.
I'm telling you, Ye Nanzhao.
I have plenty of ways
to get back at you.
Where is Miss Ye?
I'm not sure.
You may go.
Look into it.
I want to know if Ye Nanzhao
has actually been here.
Yes, sir.
Jinxing.
Have a drink.
I have something urgent to attend to.
What's so urgent about it?
I'm catching the cheater.
Jinxing.
I'll give you a hand.
The banquet isn't over yet,
but why did you get changed?
My outfit is now dirty.
Is that so?
Then why did you
change your earrings too?
Well...
This new outfit doesn't go well
with the previous earrings.
So I changed to another pair.
Oh.
I thought it went well with them.
Why don't you
show them to me?
Jinxing.
One of my earrings
is actually missing.
Is this it?
Nanzhao.
Why were you in the garden?
I wasn't there.
You were there to see Lu Zhuo,
weren't you?
What did you do?
I really wasn't in the garden.
If so,
why was your earring there?
Why are you lying to me?
Young Lady.
The earring has been found.
Hong Dou.
Where did you find it?
Under the dining table.
You probably dropped it
during the meal.
Jinxing.
The earring's been found.
That one you found isn't mine.
Nanzhao.
Looks like I misunderstood you.
How about this?
Go ahead and get some rest.
Since the banquet is almost over,
you may excuse yourself.
How did you find that earring?
This is bad!
Miss Ye.
Governor Yan said
you should stay in the room
and get some good rest.
Governor Yan.
May I have a word with this lady?
Go ahead.
Miss.
Is this earring yours?
Yes, it's mine.
Thank you, Governor Yan.
I found this earring
in the study.
May I ask,
have you been to the study?
I've only been to the garden.
But this should be mine.
Miss.
What's going on here?
It was Lu Zhuo.
Young Master Lu.
I did as you said.
My family's business in Jiang City...
As long as
the Qinglong Society is around,
your business will go well.
Thank you, Young Master Lu.
(Young Master Lu
has been protecting you in secret.)
Maybe
there's some misunderstanding
about his engagement.
Why don't you give it another try?
Hong Dou.
I've let it go.
If you've truly let it go,
why keep the hairpin he gave you
and even ask me to put it away for you?
You might as well throw it away.
Drop it, Hong Dou.
Tomorrow is Yan Jinxing's birthday.
Help me prepare a surprise for him.
Jinxing. Why are you here so early...
Jinxing?
You call his name
in such an affectionate manner.
Lu Zhuo.
This is the dining room.
It's a public place.
Mind your conduct.
Ye Nanzhao.
You've never called me
so affectionately.
Your name only has two characters.
How else should I call you?
Forget it.
You'd end up crying again.
These flowers
are my apology to you.
Jinxing.
Happy birthday.
Who are these roses for,
Zhuo?
Jinxing.
It's your birthday today.
Of course they're for you.
You're giving me roses on my birthday?
Do you find that inappropriate?
Sorry. I don't know much about flowers.
I only like roses.
Jinxing.
Let's eat now.
I made all of these for you.
We should eat them before they get cold.
Sure.
Zhuo.
I won't keep you today.
Your cousin-in-law
made a special meal for my birthday.
I don't want you here.
It's fine.
My cousin-in-law and I
have a long journey ahead.
I'll leave you two to it.
Young Master.
Why are you so angry today?
Weren't you delivering flowers?
Miss Ye didn't like them?
By the way, Young Master, Miss Ye has never
celebrated your birthday, no?
Yang A'wen.
Can you shut up?
What I'm trying to say
is, if it doesn't work out,
just let it go.
Both of them have been
childhood sweethearts since young.
Jinxing.
Happy birthday.
I have some work to attend to,
so I'll be going.
Jinxing.
I've got you a gift.
Hong Dou.
(Happy Birthday)
Happy birthday.
Make a wish.
(I wish that
if Ye Nanzhao is lying to me,)
(no matter the reason,)
(may she die a horrible death.)
(Happy Birthday)
What wish did you make?
If I say it, it won't come true.
By the way, Nanzhao,
the new socialite Mr. Jia from Nan City
is hosting a charity auction tomorrow.
All guests need
to bring something for auction.
All proceeds will go to the military.
You should come with me.
But
I don't have anything valuable.
I remember
you used to wear a rose hairpin.
You haven't been using it lately.
Since you've grown tired of it,
why don't you just auction it?
Are you alright, Young Lady?
Hong Dou.
Put this hairpin away.
I don't want to see it again.
And this painting too.
Yes.
Put it away.
Don't let anyone see it.
However,
that hairpin is too plain.
It's not worth much.
You're my wife.
Nothing of yours is ordinary.
Or was it
from someone that's important to you?
No.
That's not the case.
If you think that'll work,
then let's auction it.