=Be Not Meant To Be=
=Episode 18=
Well,
I've learned photography.
A wedding photo
makes the best wedding gift.
It's my first time seeing
someone give a wedding photo as a gift.
Your gift is certainly interesting.
Jinxing.
You have no idea
how much I love taking photos.
In one's life,
happy moments are short.
And photography
is the only way to capture them.
I once took a photo
with the one I loved most.
Miss Ye,
what do you think?
Thank you for the kind thought.
Let's get started.
No rush.
Since it's a wedding photo,
it's improper to do
without a wedding gown.
That won't do.
As it happens,
our new wedding gown has arrived.
We can shoot with it.
Zhuo.
What do you think?
Of course.
Miss Ye will look even more beautiful
in a wedding gown.
Next time we take photos,
put on a wedding gown, okay?
Ready?
Wait.
Can we start now?
When the photo is developed,
I'll have it framed and sent to you.
How thoughtful of you.
Well,
I'll definitely hang this photo
by our bed.
That's
even better.
Congratulations to you both.
A'wen.
Let's go.
Governor Yan.
We've found the one
you asked us to investigate.
You mean
she's left the country?
She left three months ago.
It was arranged by Tie Shanhu
before he died.
Lu Zhuo never married her.
Then who exactly did Lu Zhuo marry?
Some say
he married someone who has passed away.
So he really hasn't
forgotten Ye Nanzhao.
If he can't let go,
then I'll help them with it.
Miss Ye.
These are congratulatory letters
for your marriage with the governor.
(To my husband, Lu Zhuo.
From your wife, Yanni)
(Congratulations on your marriage)
(To my husband, Lu Zhuo.
From your wife, Yanni)
(Yanni)
Slip this in and deliver it to Madam.
(To my husband, Lu Zhuo.
From your wife, Yanni)
Not this one.
Take it to Young Master Lu.
Sorry, Miss Ye. I'll see to it now.
Mm.
(Happiness)
Is this good?
A little lower.
Is that fine?
Why are you here?
To bring you the photo.
Didn't Yan Jinxing say
that once the photo's developed,
he'll hang it by the bed?
Well?
Do you like it?
Lu Zhuo, don't go too far.
Why did you say so?
I'm here to deliver the photo.
I never said whose photo it was.
Ye Nanzhao.
Take a good look at this photo.
Are you really this heartless?
Have you forgotten everything?
You can lie to people,
but not to your heart.
I can forget it.
I don't believe you don't remember
what we've had together.
I'll make you remember now.
Well?
Do you remember now?
I do.
I remember you've always
been this excessive.
What are you doing?
This is my memory.
It's mine too.
I don't want it anymore.
Besides,
I only love my fiancé now.
Ye Nanzhao.
Ye Nanzhao, what are you doing?
Lu Zhuo,
our encounter was a mistake
from the start.
I used a borrowed identity to
exchange for our wrong encounter.
Now that fate is over,
our story ends here.
We should accept it.
You destroyed the photo. That's nothing.
If you truly don't love me,
go ahead.
Kill me.
Come on.
Here.
Do it!
Lu Zhuo.
We're over.
Just think of it as me killing you.
Ye Nanzhao.
My love for you...
is over.
But my hatred for you...
has only just begun.
Young Lady.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Hong Dou.
Put it away for me.
I don't want to see it again.
And this photo too.
Yes.
Burn it.
Don't let anyone see it.
Alright.
It's just a minor wound.
There's no need to bandage it.
A minor wound?
That's a wound to the heart.
Say that again
and I'll have to ask you to leave.
Young Master.
One more thing.
I think you should
explain everything to Miss Ye.
You even married her in a photo.
You're obviously sincere about her.
Why not just say it?
I get it.
The scriptwriter won't allow it.
(It doesn't matter anymore.)
(She wants to get married.)
(She wants a happy life.)
(But now I hate her.)
(I only want her to be miserable.)
Everyone,
today
is Young Master Lu's welcome banquet.
I'd like to take this opportunity
to announce some good news.
The Cheng and Lu families
will join forces from now on
in Jiang City and Nan City.
Working with such a talented young man
as Young Master Lu,
we believe
the Cheng and Lu family businesses
will surely flourish.
Thank you
for your appreciation, Mr. Cheng.
It's my honor to be working
with the Cheng family.
You're too kind, Young Master Lu.
Let's drink
to the bond between our families.
Here, let's drink together.
Please, everyone, no need for formality.
Just relax.
Please enjoy yourself, Young Master Lu.
I'll excuse myself first.
Sure.
Jinxing.
Thank you for your hospitality.
This toast is to you.
Don't stand on ceremony, Zhuo.
Sorry.
My wine is finished.
Jinxing,
that's mine.
This toast
is from me and your cousin-in-law.
Jinxing,
I need you here.
I'll be right back.
Ye Nanzhao.
I'll be waiting for you
in the back garden.
If you're not there in ten minutes,
I can't promise what I'll do.
Perhaps
I'll kill your fiancé.
It's up to you to decide.