[Episode 16]
That day,
I was poisoned
by Third Concubine's love potion.
I could barely speak,
unable to explain to you
that the ancestral hall incident
was entirely orchestrated by her.
She wanted to get rid of me
because I stood in the way of her plans.
Nonsense!
What plan could I have?
Explain yourself!
What's her plan?
You wouldn't believe it - she pretends to
chant sutras at the Buddhist hall every day,
but really, she's
sneaking off to watch operas next door.
Lies!
Look, Master,
as early as on An He's return day,
I saw Third Concubine at the theater.
Claiming she'd quit opera long ago,
yet secretly,
she's more reckless than Zhou Yimo.
You pawned several Zhou family properties
and eastern farmlands.
After all the trust I placed in you,
entrusting family affairs to your care.
All these years,
you
played me for a fool!
Master! Master!
Third Concubine has
sold many Zhou family assets,
buying a mansion for an actor.
Now without Zhou Yichen covering for you,
aren't you panicking?
Master! Master!
I was wrong!
You schemed relentlessly
to frame me and Zhou Yimo,
trying to eliminate us,
fearing
we might someday
investigate these
messy accounts that only Zhou Yichen knew.
Master,
do you see now?
Zhou Yimo and I are innocent.
Our loyalty is to you.
She
is the true betrayer!
Shut up!
Ye Zhiqiu!
If not for you,
Chen and I would be living well!
Enough!
Hansheng!
Take her away!
I don't want to see her again!
Come, Third Concubine.
Don't touch me.
I'll walk myself.
Zhou Huaiqian!
You have five concubines,
why can't I keep one man?
You!
Hansheng!
Get rid of her.
Get rid of her!
Fine!
How should I die?
To be shot like Chen,
or to hang like Fifth Concubine?
My son
did so much for you,
was used by you,
took the blame for you,
never betrayed you even unto death.
And you?
Have you ever shown us
an ounce of mercy?
Master,
this concerns human lives.
Don't act rashly.
Perhaps,
we should confine Third Concubine
to the cold courtyard
and decide later.
Hansheng,
find that opera singer
and eliminate him for me.
Yes, Master.
Also
release Yimo.
He hasn't eaten for three days.
Quickly.
Fifth Concubine,
I'm sorry
for making you suffer this injustice.
As long as you
don't send me away.
This bit of unfairness is nothing.
Master
you must take care of your health.
♪ Resting in the underworld, ♪
♪ dreams elude me. ♪
♪ In this life I've accumulated ♪
♪ so many affections. ♪
♪ Here I am, ♪
♪ drunkenly lying ♪
♪ in the Plum Blossom ♪
♪ Temple courtyard. ♪
Do you remember
the owner of these clothes?
♪ Hearing loud shouts ♪
♪ from inside. ♪
That opera singer is way too delicate.
He can't take a beating.
After just a few strikes,
he confessed everything.
They took every secret meeting you had,
and all the gold and silver
you gave him, as evidence.
Ye Zhiqiu!
Why did you have to
treat my son and me this way?
How have we wronged you?
Even now
you still claim innocence?
If you hadn't seduced Chen,
exposing everything,
he wouldn't have died.
So anyone
who approaches Zhou Yichen with kindness
must be slandered,
framed by you?
Kindness?
Come,
let me hear
what kindness you have.
I have none.
But someone
once cared for Zhou Yichen
with genuine kindness and compassion.
But you nearly sold her to a brothel.
Do you still remember her?
Chuxue?
How do you know?
That bitch!
Bitch?
All she did was show Zhou Yichen
a little basic human kindness.
She saw you
destroying the sculptures he loved,
so she hid them for him.
She saw you
forcing him
to grovel before the master,
so she offered him comfort.
That was all.
And just for that,
you call her bitch?
Sold an innocent girl
to a brothel?
Luckily for her,
she escaped.
No.
She was rescued
by your precious son!
What are you talking about?
Is Chuxue inside?
Hurry, hurry!
Third...
Third Concubine!
I'm grinding ink for the young master.
Someone outside Zhou residence is asking for you.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
Accept your fate.
Master sold you to the south.
Please,
please let me go!
Please release me!
Second Young Master!
The moment I left the residence,
they sold me here!
I know.
I know everything.
After returning,
don't mention this to anyone.
I'll arrange for you
to work for Second Concubine.
But...
we must keep
some distance between us.
Why?
Did...
Did I do something wrong?
I'll double your salary.
But...
you can't stay by my side anymore.
To protect Chuxue from your persecution,
Zhou Yichen had to hand her
over to Second Concubine.
He watched her endure humiliation
but dared not intervene again.
My son is too kindhearted.
To sacrifice so much for
such a worthless, lowly creature...
In her family's eyes,
you're nothing
but a useless piece of trash.
What's your connection to Chuxue?
How do you know so much
about her?
Why did you marry into this family?
I spared your life
only out of respect
for your past with Zhou Yichen.
From now on,
you'll never rise again.
Ye Zhiqiu,
you'll meet a bad end!
People in the Zhou family
never come to a good end.
You're no exception.
Sister,
are you watching?
I'll make every
single one who bullied you
pay the price.
Extra, extra!
Last copy available!
Fifth Concubine of the Zhou family
and eldest son are siblings!
One copy, please!
Give me one!
The papers are selling well today.
Today's news
is worth every penny!
Bizarre twists and turns
happened right in
the wealthiest family in Wu County!
It says here
the Fifth Concubine
was framed by the other concubines.
Is that true?
Of course!
Once Master He intervened,
the truth came to light.
The fallen heiress
and the wealthy heir are siblings.
How could they be lovers?
Someone must have
bullied her behind the scenes.
So that means
crossing her
means crossing
that mysterious He family big shot?
Naturally.
That He family big shot
holds immense power, they say.
Alright.
Let me see.
Here.
Take it.
What's wrong?
What do you mean?
Look.
Extra, extra!
We made
the front page headline in Wu County today!
Just some bored reporters
writing sensational stories.
Boring news.
And all that nonsense about
a fallen heiress
and a wealthy heir being siblings.
The generations are all mixed up.
I played the role
of your brother
and your father.
What are you afraid of?
Unless
you want to be something else to me?
Shut up!
Tomorrow I'll warn the newspaper office.
If they keep writing nonsense...
No, no.
I'll have them
print a corrected version tomorrow.
Zhou Yimo!
What do you mean?
The entire publishing industry is mine.
What do you think I mean?
So these articles
were arranged by you?
Why would you do this?
Using sensational stories
to obscure our relationship?
But it's unnecessary.
I don't need it.
I say you do.
You're just pretending not to care.
But every day I see
them misunderstanding you,
slandering you,
looking down on you.
I want every newspaper's
front page to proclaim your innocence.
There are a lot of people around.
Is this
okay?
Any new leads?
I secretly checked
the housekeeper's records.
On New Year's Eve three years ago,
all the servants were together
with mutual alibis.
Besides,
they didn't have the freedom
to move around the mansion unnoticed.
Could it be the Third Concubine?
The Third Concubine is suspicious.
But Nanxi told me
that on New Year's Eve,
she accompanied the Third Concubine
chanting scriptures in the hall until dawn.
Moreover,
this was also corroborated
by the housekeeper and driver.
It's just a pity I wasn't
at the mansion that New Year's Eve.
But Nanxi's account seems reliable.
There's another person
who left in a hurry
after the reunion dinner.
Who?
The Fourth Concubine.
But investigating her
is difficult.
She hasn't returned for three years.
Young Master,
Fifth Concubine,
the Master is critically ill.
Perhaps
you'll see the Fourth Concubine soon.
Father, rest assured.
I will manage
the Zhou family's business
diligently for you.
Here,
let's add a thumbprint.
Master Zhou,
as per your instructions,
all Zhou family assets
in Wu County
have been transferred
to your eldest son, Zhou Yimo.
But properties outside Wu County
remain under Fourth Concubine's control.
After her return,
we'll make further decisions.
Dismissed.
I'd like a private word with Father.
Go.
Dad,
why are you so insistent on passing
our family business to me?
Fourth Concubine has been working hard,
raising two children.
It hasn't been easy for her.
Mo,
take it back!
Why?
It's all mine!
Why should I give it to her?
It's all yours.
She has done so much for the family.
Does none of that count?
It doesn't.
Nobody
is
taking
what's mine.
Dad,
you've always only cared about yourself.
Starting with my mother.
You married her
just to get the He family's wealth.
You think I didn't know?
Back then, you knew Second Concubine
was going to set fire to kill my mother,
yet you let it happen.
You...
You knew?
Dad,
come save my mother!
It was all your terrible idea.
You actually had them burned to death.
What's there to fear?
Zhou Yimo isn't even your real son anyway.
Later,
I'll have as many kids
as you want for you.
Good.
Bear me several more, okay?
I grew up filled with hatred,
only to discover that you turned
the He family's thriving tea business
into a cover for your opium smuggling.
I've always known about
the schemes you and Yichen were pulling.
All these years I've been biding my time,
gathering the He family's influence.
All so that one day,
I could take revenge for my mother
and reclaim the He family's legacy.
You still don't know,
that Master He you've been searching for
is me.
Also,
I like
Fifth Concubine very much.
I'll take good care of her for you.