[Episode 5]
Grandma,
Mo...
How did you
get like this?
This is the truth about how I grew up
under Second concubine's "care"
after my mother died when I was six.
She'd hit me whenever she was upset,
and after every miscarriage,
she'd fly into a rage and unleash a torrent
of abuse at me.
Until..
my brother Zhou Yichen was born.
Only then did she realize I was her only bargaining chip.
Child,
how could it be like this?
All these years,
I never gave up searching
for the truth about Mother's death.
Until a few months ago,
when the nanny who retired from the He residence
finally admitted
that back then, Second concubine
put combustible materials
in the New Year goods sent to my mother.
Mother's accident back then
was deliberately caused by Second concubine
to compete for favor.
Madam!
The house is on fire! Help!
Young master, you can't go in!
Mother!
Save me!
Someone save my mother!
Someone save her!
Mother!
Why did this happen?
Poor child.
My poor daughter.
She was actually killed by her own sister.
Why was she so foolish?
If this is true,
her fate today
is what she brought upon herself.
Zhou Huaiqian!
Mom.
I only ask one thing of you.
Tell me.
In the future,
treat my grandson
as your own child.
Rest assured, Mother.
The He and Zhou families
are one family
I hope you truly think so.
Trust me.
That's the dress the female ghost wore that night!
Why was it with the second young master?
Father!
Grandma!
I found this red robe under the floorboards
in Second concubine's room.
This proves the ghost incidents
were orchestrated by Second concubine!
Brother!
You're late.
A wasted effort.
Fifth Concubine is young and beautiful.
And she's about their age.
They're all rushing to help her.
She's very cunning.
Yimo.
Take care of Dr. Sun Quietly.
Yes.
Take him away.
Fifth concubine, you barged into
Second concubine room recklessly.
so you'll be punished
by sweeping the backyard for three days.
Yes.
Master.
Zhou Yichen.
Father.
You've been acting recklessly lately.
Return to your room
and reflect on your actions.
Yes.
What a masterful scheme.
You let Lan'er see you taking me away,
making me the prime suspect
in Second concubine' burning death.
Then you used this to expose
her past misdeeds of drugging Master.
And clear my arson suspicion.
Leveraging the He family's influence
to pressure Master,
securing your position here.
Now,
am I qualified to protect you?
I didn't expose your ghost scheme,
so we're even.
Don't get any
other ideas.
It seems,
besides Second concubine,
you have other targets.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Xiaoman.
So instead of rehearsing at the drama club,
you've been reading this?
Look,
Wu county has a hero who destroys opium.
They say he wears a Zhong Kui mask
and all-black clothing.
He goes straight to the docks
to destroy ships smuggling opium.
He's incredible!
You're the hero who destroys opium!
Save me!
Datao, he is injured!
Go find Teacher Anna quickly!
Hurry!
Okay.
Did you see a
wounded man come in?
Yes.
He ran out the main gate.
Let's go.
You're awake.
Great.
That was my first kiss.
No, no, not that.
I wasn't trying to take advantage of you.
I was giving you artificial respiration.
I'm here to save you.
Thanks.
Thank you for saving me.
I recognize you
Hero who destroys opium..
He's been shot.
Careful.
Forcing you to leave here
was to protect you.
Don't be so hard
on yourself trying to live up to
others' expectations.
Not only will I not tell anyone,
but I'm also looking forward
to your next creation.
Such skillful hands.
Third concubine.
Chen.
I made you some fungus and lotus seed soup.
Drink it while it's hot.
Thank you, Mother.
Your father values you more now,
and treats me better too.
All my hopes
rest on you.
Don't worry, Mother.
I
will not let Father leave us.
As long as you're obedient.
Master Zhou.
After years of struggle in the underworld,
you've committed too many sins of bloodshed.
You need to purge it all
to return to your youthful state.
That's good.
Give me a little more time,
and I'll return to my youth.
Master Zhou.
Based on the evidence at the scene
and the autopsy report,
her death appears to have been accidental-
opium smoking indoors
triggered a fatal fire.
Give it to me.
We reached this conclusion
for three reasons!
Alright.
I understand.
Thank you for your trouble, Captain Yu.
It's no big deal.
Wrap up the case quickly.
Give our regards to the Director.
See him out.
Goodbye.
This way, Captain Yu.
By the way
there's one thing.
I've been meaning to ask you.
Go ahead, Father.
Does He family have a mysterious mastermind?
I've heard of it,
but I've never seen them at the He residence.
Grandmother never mentioned it either.
Because your grandmother
is guarding against me.
Are you suggesting
that I should investigate it?
Yimo.
After all, you bear the Zhou surname.
As long as you prove to me
your loyalty,
the future Zhou family estate
could very well fall into your hands.
When it comes to vision,
one must look far ahead.
Do you understand?
Understood.
I know what to do, Father.
Xiaoman.
Captain Yu.
Have some respect!
Or I'll call for help.
Three years
I've been searching for you for three years.
No trace of you anywhere.
I thought you were dead.
Do you know how I've lived these three years?
I'm sorry to disappoint you, Captain Yu.
Until I uncover the truth,
I won't die.
Xiaoman.
The Zhou family holds immense power.
Their connections are intricate.
It's not simple
Stay out of this mess.
Come with me.
Are you any simpler?
Don't think I'm still that naive girl
from back then.
How did you become Captain?
Didn't you step over my sister's corpse
to climb step by step?
I had no choice back then.
If you had insisted on uncovering the truth,
the Zhou family would have silenced you.
The police would have covered up the truth.
All crows are black under the sun.
Everyone operates this way.
You don't understand.
I wanted to protect you.
I know that.
For the sake of our past relationship,
please stop hindering me.
Do you still carry
the gun I gave you?
Why?
You want it back?
Of course not.
Keeping it protects you.
That reassures me.
If you encounter trouble,
find me anytime.
Having a patrol captain as a friend
makes things easier.
It's so late.
What are you doing here?
I saw your door was open,
so I came in impulsively.
I wanted to give you a gift.
I made it myself.
This is me?
Then I can't accept it.
Didn't you say,
one should persevere
in something they love?
I did say that.
But...
Don't get me wrong.
I just wanted to give you
this gift that I carved myself.
You won't accept it?
Second Young Master.
I'm your dad's concubine.