Sir, how much would you sell me this one?
I think she’s already won it, though.
We’re ruining it by mixing it together, aren’t we?
Yeah.
Thank you, Liu.
If it wasn’t for you, Guy wouldn’t have become so mature.
Why?
I…
I think I’m in love with Guy.
I’m sorry.
I’m really worried about this lately.
I want to talk to you about it.
Do you think it’s strange that I’m in love with Guy?
No.
I’ve just never noticed that you feel this way about him.
You can say that it’s strange.
I get it.
Actually, it started on the night of the first day of the campus fair.
You left early so you probably don’t know what happened.
The boys had a drinking duel to win me.
I felt terrible that they did that to me.
But Guy…
You can’t do this to Faye.
I was shocked that he stepped up to protect me.
Though it was only a short moment,
he made me feel safe.
Do you think what I said is nonsense?
No.
This is why I want you to be the first one to know.
I know that you will understand the feelings that I have for him.
I hope that you will help me.
You are close to him but I’m not.
Can you help me get close to him?
Baifern Pimchanok
Win Metawin
Great Sapol
Jane Ramida
[BASED ON LINE WEBTOON “MY ID IS GANGNAM BEAUTY” BY KI MAENGGI]
Directed by Aticha Tanthanawigrai
This episode contains a scene depicting an eating disorder that some viewers may find disturbing. Viewer discretion is advised.
[I just noticed that Guy secretly looked at Faye. He must have feelings for him. I’m sure. #GuyFaye] (Other people may think it’s nonsense that I need your help.)
[They just walk past each other but look sweetly into the eyes. They are lovebirds. #GuyFaye]
(But you know that my relationship with him is bad.)
(Liu, you are the only one who knows how to win his heart.)
Oh, you are here.
I was waiting for you at the dorm for a while.
I thought you would come to school with me.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t know that you would wait for me.
I got up early this morning.
So I left early because I didn’t have anything to do at home.
Yesterday was great.
Are you talking about the movie for our assignment?
I’ll draft the paper and send it to you.
I’m talking about something else.
I mean overall.
I’ve never had that kind of conversation with my mom.
I’ve never known that you are worried about me.
It’s almost time for class.
I need to go to the bathroom first.
I’ll see you in class.
Okay, everyone. Today, we will learn about titration.
You need a partner to do this experiment.
I’ll give you time to find your partner before we start.
I’ll be right back.
I don’t want to be Guy’s partner anymore.
Liu, do you want to switch your lab partner?
Let’s do things differently.
Really?
That’s great. I want to be Guy’s partner.
I mean…
You said you want to do things differently.
You can pair up with Liu. I’ll pair up with Guy.
But I don’t want to pair up with you.
How could you say that?
You are so mean.
Let’s change things to get a sense of refreshment.
Right. I’m okay to pair up with Ann.
Good luck.
Thanks.
I’ll do it.
No. I’ll do it.
He is a gentleman.
It’s okay. I’ll do it.
Now, the classroom has turned into a romantic scene.
Don’t say things that aren’t true.
Right.
Stop talking about the thing that is impossible.
How could you say that is a romantic scene?
Don’t touch it. You will break it.
I want to try it.
Guy just doesn’t trust Faye.
Mork, why are you so pessimistic?
They can become a real couple one day.
Mimi, have you ever seen him doing anything alone?
He always respects other people.
He’s doing this because he doesn’t trust her.
Mork, are you trying to ruin the ship?
The more you try to ship them, the worse things will be.
Guy will get annoyed and try to shut Faye out.
He doesn’t like to be told what to do.
Faye’s fans are now turning to be Guy’s fans.
Things change so fast.
You are so smart.
If you are a bit smarter, only for a little.
You will know why Guy will never develop any feelings for Faye.
It’s because Faye likes me.
Right.
I’m leaving now, Liu.
Guy.
Can you give me a minute?
What do you want?
I want to talk to you.
It won’t take long.
Fine.
Hey, Kitty.
Come and play with it.
Kitty, say hi to Guy.
What do you want from me?
What did you know?
What are you talking about?
I just want to get close to you.
This will be good for Liu.
You know that she feels uncomfortable when she sees us on bad terms.
Are you sure it’s about that?
Yes.
I know that it’s awkward for you to suddenly befriend me.
That’s why I took you here.
We can start our friendship from here.
So you won’t feel pressured.
You don’t have to be my friend now.
But we both can befriend with this kitty.
I saw that you often like cat videos on social media.
Come on, Guy. Why don’t you pat it? It’s cute.
You need to stop doing this stupid thing.
You know that I’m allergic to cats.
I didn’t know it.
I thought we could become friends if I did this.
There’s no way that I will be your friend.
Can you leave me and Liu alone?
Did your “kitty” plan work?
I shouldn’t have made a move on him.
He misunderstood me and thought I was trying to tease him.
How would I know that he’s allergic to cats?
I saw he liked funny cat videos.
I’m sorry that I didn’t warn you about it
though I promised that I would help you.
It’s okay.
It was my fault that I did it without consulting with you first.
That was because when I asked you to help me…
Can you help me get close to him?
You seemed hesitant.
So I decided to try to do it by myself.
With what happened today,
I now understand why you were hesitant.
It’s because you know that it’s impossible for Guy to like me.
That’s why you don’t want to help me.
It’s not like that.
I was hesitant because…
I know.
I’m not good enough for him.
No.
You don’t need to comfort me.
I get it.
Although everyone thinks I am beautiful, smart, and nice.
In his eyes,
I’m just a foolish girl.
I think I should go home and try to get over him.
This way, you will no longer feel bad for me.
The girl that he likes will never be me.
I wasn’t lying.
I meant what I said.
If you want Guy to back down.
If you want to have a good reason to tell him
without lying that you don’t like him,
I think this is a good solution.
I think I’m in love with Guy.
Faye.
Don’t give up yet.
I’ll help you.
Really?
Do you really mean it?
Yes.
Really?
Thank you
Are you free today?
Yes.
I want to ask you to dine out with me.
Dine out?
Sure.
Are we going right now?
Yes, we can go now.
I have a coupon for a buy 1 get 1 free promotion at the restaurant that we went to the other day.
Are you hungry?
Yes.
I’m starving.
Spaghetti carbonara and cream sauce salad.
Yes.
I thought you would order a meat dish.
You usually don’t eat salad.
I want to try something new.
I want to eat healthy food.
After finishing the meal, do you have any plans?
Can you go shopping with me?
What do you want to buy?
Plates, cutlery, glasses, and…
I’m not sure.
But I know that you can help me.
Oh.
What a coincidence.
Faye.
You came here alone?
Yes.
Guy.
I’m sorry about yesterday.
I really didn’t know it.
I’ll pay for this meal to apologize to you.
No need for it.
We have a coupon for a buy 1 get 1 free promotion.
It’s for two people.
You are an excess.
Forget about the promotion.
Come and sit with us.
Am I bothering you?
No.
I’ll let you two talk.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Liu.
Here’s your food.
What do you want?
I came here to have a meal.
It’s a coincidence that I walked into this restaurant.
Drop your act.
I saw through your acting since the moment you walked in here.
Do you have a lot of free time to interrupt other people’s lives?
To be honest, I don’t have a lot of free time.
For this, I think it’s worth my time.
Liu.
I saw you went out with Guy.
How is it going?
How long are you going to keep fooling Liu?
I am not fooling her.
I’m just doing what I want.
Unfortunately,
I want to be your girlfriend.
Nonsense.
It’s not nonsense.
If we are dating,
Think how surprised everyone will be.
Everything we do has always been a big buzz.
We can change it into money and fame.
In the end, it will turn into power.
Using other people to become successful,
so this is your special skill.
Yes.
I’ll take that as a compliment.
You can manipulate anyone that you want.
But can’t you leave me and Liu alone?
For all this time, isn’t it clear to you how much I hate you?
That’s okay.
I hate you very much too.
So what?
Are you going to let your personal feelings ruin our opportunity?
You are a smart guy.
You should know that those feelings are for the fools.
Are you a psychopath?
Can you live like normal people?
Isn’t this what people call normal?
A young good-looking couple enjoys a wonderful and romantic meal.
Instead of accompanying by a plastic girl
and try to say that it’s normal.
I’ve never looked at it that way.
Is that so?
It’s okay
as long as Liu sees it that way.
I thought you were just trying to come between me and Liu.
But you are planning to brainwash her.
Wait.
I can’t brainwash anyone.
Things turn out this way.
It may be because she agrees with this way of thinking.
For example,
she thinks we are a good match and should be together.
That’s not true.
Liu knows that I have no feelings for you.
She also knows that…
Wait.
Don’t tell me that you think she has feelings for you.
I think you misunderstand it.
Do you think she will give up on the man that she likes for her friend without saying anything?
She helped me by taking you here.
She ordered the salad for me.
She excused herself so we would be alone.
Look at the situation.
If you are not a fool, you should be able to tell that she chose not to be with you.
That she chose not to be with you.
Stop talking nonsense.
It’s up to you.
You can go ask Liu.
It looks like she is leaving so we can be alone.
The buy 1 get 1 free promotion is meant to be for us from the beginning.
Liu.
Why are you doing this?
Faye just wants to talk to you.
Why do you believe every word that Faye says?
You know that there’s no way that I will date Faye.
You know how I feel about you.
I know. This is my answer.
This is not your true feelings.
I think you are just confused.
Because Faye said she wants to be with me
or people think that Faye is a better match for me than you.
But that’s what other people think.
How can you think that other people’s opinions are more than our feelings?
We are not living alone in this world.
Tell me.
Can we live our lives without caring about what other people think?
If we could do that,
no couples would break up or get a divorce.
If this is what I think,
aren’t you going to try to understand or listen to me?
Are you sure you want to do this because of that?
It’s true that we need more than love.
But I think we can work it out together.
All you need to do is tell me how you feel.
I’m ready to be by your side.
From everything I did, do you still not get it?
I don’t believe it.
I don’t believe that you have no feelings for me.
You can’t even say that to me.
Please don’t do this.
We can work it out together.
You need to hear it, don’t you?
Fine.
I had no feelings for you.
I’ve never had any feelings for you.
I did everything because I felt that way.
♪ You may know that it’s not true ♪
♪ Can you pretend to believe ♪
♪ The lie I must say to deceive ♪
♪ That I don’t love you ♪
Hey.
You need to tell me.
If you keep drinking and say nothing,
I don’t know how to help you.
I don’t know how to begin.
I thought that our relationship was going well.
Do you think what is her reason?
Is it because of Faye or something else?
Whatever her reason is, it’s not important anymore.
You need to accept that she rejected you.
She cried when she rejected me.
Why did she cry if that was what she wanted?
Wasn’t she supposed to feel relieved as she was able to say what she wanted?
Hey.
You need to stop asking questions that you will never know the answers.
Accept her decision.
The person that she chose
is not you.
Do you want to make rose water with me?
That’s a good idea.
Let’s go.
It’s strange.
I thought this was the right decision.
But I feel so horrible.
The worst thing is that I hurt Guy.
But you are as hurt as he is.
Now I’m not sure
if this is really the right decision.
I think you shouldn’t ask yourself if it’s the right decision.
You should ask if this is the best choice that you have.
I think this is best for Guy and me.
We feel hurt now.
But I think it’s better for us in the future.
That’s true.
When we break up with someone,
it hurts but it’s a good thing for both of us.
It’s irony.
I never had a boyfriend but I learned how to break up.
What you learned is not breaking up with someone.
You learned to love someone
You did this because you love him, didn’t you?
Saint, don’t you feel bad that I keep talking about Guy?
Why would I feel bad?
I’m happy that I am someone you can talk to.
This is how I show my love to you.
It’s unbelievable that you can casually talk about it.
I guess I’ve experienced different forms of love.
For me,
I think finding someone you are comfortable to be with is more important than love.
I think honesty and the ability to tell everything to that person are more important for relationships.
Feelings will fade away one day.
But the bond will last forever.
So?
Don’t I sound cool?
Yes.
I said that because I know I can’t compete with him in winning your heart.
It would be wrong to say that love is not important.
Anyway.
Though you may have no feelings for me now,
I will make you fall for me one day.
When that day comes,
I think Guy’s wound will be healed and he is ready to start a new relationship with someone.
I hope that he can have a new relationship soon.
I don’t want to see him sad because of me for a long time.
There’s a person who is the right match for him.
He just hasn’t noticed her yet.
Who are you talking about?
Faye likes Guy.
I think it’s the best choice.
I want to stay away from Guy.
Faye is perfect for him.
Meanwhile, I have you.
Wait, Liu.
When did Faye come into the picture?
What’s up, Ann?
Liu, do you have the phone number of Guy’s mom?
Can you give it to me?
Yes.
But why do you need it for?
What happened?
Guy is arrested because he was involved in a fight.
I called Guy’s mom.
I’m on my way to the police station.
What happened?
Guy and I were drinking at a bar.
We ran into Third, Jo, Mork, and his friends.
Third came to comfort Guy about the rejection.
But his way to comfort Guy was…
Why are you sad about it?
A girl like Liu,
you can find a dozen of them at a plastic surgery clinic.
A girl like her should know her place.
It was like a miracle for someone like you to ask her out.
How could she say no to you?
Why can’t she say no to me?
Her original face was so ugly.
If she had a boyfriend like you,
it was worth the money she paid for the plastic surgery.
I guess the surgery can only change her face but not her brain.
What the hell did you just say?
I think the person who needs surgery to alter the brain is you.
What did you say?
You are an adult but your brain is filled with bad attitudes.
Bastard.
What is wrong with you?
Didn’t you hear what he said?
I shouldn’t waste my time to comfort you.
How could you fall for a plastic girl like her?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Why do you keep looking down on her?
Come and help me stop him.
How is it going?
They are still arguing with each other.
Did you call Guy’s mom?
I’ll wait for Aunt Linda here.
You should go inside.
Yes.
You said Mork also saw what happened.
Yes. Why?
I think you should work things out.
The other party is not a stranger.
You both study at the same university, right?
It’s better for you to not have a criminal record because of this.
No.
If he doesn’t bow his head and apologize to me,
I will take legal action against him.
Guy, why don’t you apologize to him to end this whole thing?
It was my fault.
I should have hit him harder.
Assh*le.
- Stop it. - What did you say?
Don’t have another fight here.
Otherwise, you will be pressed for another charge.
Guy.
Why did you tell her about this?
Do you know what you are doing?
Why did you have a fight with him and get into trouble?
You need to learn how to control your temper.
Liu also thinks this was your fault.
You should reflect on your wrongdoings and apologize to me.
You are the one who needs to apologize.
Guy was wrong that he hit you.
You were wrong that you insulted me.
I want you to apologize to me.
Please take a look at it.
Bastard.
What is wrong with you?
You started the fight.
Why?
Why don’t I have a right to choose who I want to date?
Even if I underwent surgery to change my entire face
or I did nothing and was still an ugly girl,
I have a right to choose who I want to be with.
She is right.
If you apologize to Liu,
I’ll drop the charges.
What are you going to do?
Apologize to her.
Third.
Fine.
I’m sorry.
Like I said, I’ll drop the charges.
Who do I have to bail out?
You don’t need to do that anymore.
I’m sorry for all the trouble.
It’s okay.
It’s good that things ended well.
I got to see Liu scolding you today.
I will have a good sleep tonight.
I got to go now. See you.
I’m sorry.
Thank you for helping me.
I was the reason you got into this fight.
I’m sorry that I broke my promise.
I promised that I wouldn’t use violence.
But when it was about you, I couldn’t help it.
I know.
You did this because of me.
That’s not what I mean.
It’s okay.
What you said is true.
Everything about me always ends in trouble.
It’s better for you if we stay away from each other.
Liu.
Guy, I’ll talk to you later.
I have something I need to talk to Liu.
Saint.
Can you give him a ride home?
Sure.
Let’s go.
Thank you for taking care of Liu.
You don’t need to thank me.
She rejected you because…
You don’t need to remind me about it.
I know what you are going to say.
Maybe you don’t know.
I know.
Let’s go.
I need to apologize to you.
I’m the reason why Guy constantly got into trouble.
Liu.
You don’t need to apologize to me.
I should be the one who apologizes to you.
Apologize to me?
Guy caused many troubles to you.
Look at what happened today.
I heard that you rejected him.
I’m sorry that I tried to set you up with him.
I didn’t know…
It was not your fault.
What you did didn’t make me feel bad.
Actually, I have feelings for him.
Can I ask you something?
You have feelings for him.
But why did you reject him?
I…
I want him to be happy.
I want him to have a good life.
I want his life to be full of laughter and smiles.
That’s the kind of life I can’t give him.
I want him to be happy with someone who is the right match for him.
There’s a friend who has feelings for Guy.
My life at the university?
I need to manage my time well.
I have a lot of assignments.
It’s almost time for the final exam.
Look at this big pile of books.
They are heavy.
Sometimes, I have eye strain after reading books for a long time.
But I need to do it.
She is talented and smart.
Her beauty is natural.
She is perfect both inside and out.
To get all A's, let’s study together.
Let’s start.
She is honest.
If I can help you all get better grades, I will be very happy.
She is nice.
When someone like her says she falls for Guy,
I think he should date someone who is in the same league.
Someone who is in the same league?
What do you mean by that?
Liu.
Listen to me.
When I was dating Guy’s father,
everyone said we were right for each other.
We were perfect in every way.
But you see how it ended.
I’m not saying this because I want to set you up with Guy.
But I want you to rethink the idea of a perfect match.
No one is perfect.
The person that you think is perfect.
Maybe she is imperfect just like you.
Everyone, I need to end the streaming and go back to my study.
I’ll do the live-streaming later.
See you. Good night.
Bye. See you. Good night.
Bye.
Directed by Aticha Tanthanawigrai
Don’t tell me you guys are a thing now?
You look perfect for each other,
and similar in social standings.
You don’t want me to be on bad terms with Faye.
I’ll be very happy for you
if it’s him you’re in love with.
When I’m with you,
every tough situation feels so easy to get through.
Saint.
Can make Liu a famous perfumer?