♫ Did we agree
we would stay together forever? ♫
♫ No matter what, it will be true ♫
♫ Did we agree
we would stay together forever? ♫
♫ No matter what, it will be true ♫
♫ Did we agree
we would have endless stories? ♫
♫ About you ♫
♫ About our family ♫
♫ I'll wait here foolishly for you ♫
♫ No matter if a sudden storm comes ♫
♫ I'll have everything ready here ♫
♫ Just waiting for your word ♫
♫ I'll guard you silently here ♫
♫ I fear even my breath will disturb you ♫
♫ Maybe this is the meaning of family ♫
♫ How beautiful ♫
[Stay With Me]
[Episode 23]
What did you say to my father today?
I told him about your ambition
to become a pilot.
You told him?
Why did you tell him?
He'll definitely try to stop me.
No, actually, he was quite supportive.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
To get into an aviation university?
And become a pilot?
Don't even think about it.
He's already passed the re-examination.
Do you know how many people
in Beijing, even in all of China,
can pass the re-examination?
It's a glorious profession.
Why are you so resistant to it?
I'm not against the profession.
I just know my son too well.
An air force pilot
is not for ordinary people.
It takes arduous efforts
and extraordinary endurance.
Are you worried about him?
No, I'm not.
I'm just afraid he can't stand the hardship.
Besides,
it takes more than a healthy body
to enter an aviation academy.
The academic performance
must also be top-notch.
Even if he can pass the physical examination,
can he pass the academics?
He can.
Brother Su Yu, what are you thinking about?
I want your brother Wu Bi
to apply to the Air Force
University of Aeronautics.
What?
You're not kidding, are you?
Why would I be kidding?
You've passed the re-examination,
and as long as you can pass
the first-tier line in the cultural course,
you're likely to get into
the Aviation University.
I'm not worried about the re-examination,
but the score for the first-tier line.
A person's innate conditions are fixed,
but scores are flexible.
As long as you can…
Stop, innate conditions include brains, bro.
You're finally willing
to call him your brother.
Stop, not now.
You go play for a while.
What's your plan then?
Just taking one step at a time.
Anyway, based on my current score,
Civil Aviation University is more reliable.
Civil Aviation?
Are you going to fly passenger planes?
Who told me his dream was to be an astronaut?
Who said he wanted to give me stars?
The dream is called a dream
because it's unattainable.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Since childhood,
have you ever been persistent about anything?
Yes.
What?
It's buried under this tree.
Then you should go
and make this wish come true.
Do you even know what my wish is?
And you're asking me to make it come true.
For civil aviation recruitment,
you might be dispatched to other cities,
but I want you to stay in Beijing.
I don't want to be separated from you.
Brother Wu Bi, please don't ever leave Beijing.
I don't want to either.
But the objective conditions
are right here.
For me,
there's no objective, only subjective.
If I say you can do it, you can.
You have so much confidence in me?
I have confidence in my tutoring system.
What system?
Go to sleep.
Go to sleep?
What kind of system is that?
What do you mean by "go to sleep", bro?
Can you be gentle?
How can you still get it wrong
when I've explained it so many times?
You've never explained this problem.
This problem and the previous one are the same,
just with different numbers.
Tomato scrambled eggs
and cucumber scrambled eggs
are both scrambled eggs.
But the ingredients are not the same,
so they are not the same dish.
You only know about eating.
Sit up.
Did your interview results
for Beijing Film Academy come out?
How did it go? Did you pass?
I did.
Now I'm just waiting
for the cultural course exam.
Good job, kid.
I heard that to get into Beijing Film Academy,
one must have connections,
and it costs a lot of money.
Not at all.
At first, I was just trying my luck.
During the tryouts,
a teacher saw potential in me,
and he guided me for free.
I didn't even check the re-examination result.
The teacher called me to tell me I had passed.
By the third round,
I started to really prepare for it,
but I wasn't holding out much hope.
To be honest, I was quite surprised.
Remember to sign for me when you graduate.
In case one day you become famous,
I can sell it for some money.
Don't worry. Even if I become a big shot,
I won't act superior to you ordinary people.
Yu, what if I pass the interview,
but fail the cultural course exam,
wouldn't that be such a shame?
With a few days left
before the college entrance exam,
can you help me out?
You can get in line.
It's not your turn yet.
Right, Wu Bi,
there's something I've been
meaning to thank you for.
A few days after you hit me,
I went to attend the interview.
With a bruised face,
the interviewers said I had
a kind of damaged beauty,
so I stood out among many candidates.
How about I give you a couple more punches?
Maybe you could land a role tomorrow.
So, the cosine of the angle formed
by the straight line MA
and the straight line QK is…
D.
Right.
Why is it so easy to understand
when you explain it,
but not when the teacher explains it?
That's because you don't
listen carefully normally.
No, something's definitely different.
You explain it better than the teacher.
If you open an educational
institution in the future,
you could become the richest man.
If you ask me,
you just don't use your brain, and it's rusty.
A few lubricants can make it
take off immediately.
Wait a minute.
What lubricant?
Why are you sleeping on the table?
You were asleep just now,
so I wrote the solution method on the paper.
You can read it when you wake up.
I've never been so tired studying on my own.
The second mock exam results are out.
I've never seen him
so concerned about his grades.
He's already guaranteed a spot,
so why is he so anxious?
How is it?
Not so good.
How could it be?
I've checked the answers, and at least
I got 30 points more than last time.
Definitely enough to make the second-tier line.
You got 32 points more.
Then why did you say it wasn't good?
If you can get another 30 points,
I'll reward you with something.
What is it?
I'll reward you…
♫ I never thought about what would be
at the end of the road ♫
♫ What it would be like ♫
♫ I never considered
whether what I was doing was right or wrong ♫
♫ Let them say ♫
♫ Maybe it's best ♫
♫ To remain silent now ♫
♫ Let the fire burn in our hearts ♫
♫ We pray ♫
♫ We look far away ♫
Okay, class dismissed.
Guys, you should go for a walk.
Although the college entrance exam
is approaching,
health is still the most important thing.
Come on, let's get moving.
♫ Dark clouds block every star's light ♫
♫ There will be a dawn ♫
♫ As always ♫
♫Promise me to keep searching♫
Has Wu Bi gone mad?
I haven't seen him lift his head these days.
♫ Promise me to keep searching ♫
Su Yu, where are you going?
The college entrance examination simulation
exercises seem to be out.
And I heard the predictions were very accurate.
I'm going to the bookstore to have a look.
Why would you need that?
You don't even need to take the exam.
I voluntarily applied for it,
just for fun.
To see how many points I can get.
Just for fun?
By the way, I haven't asked you yet.
What did you apply for?
Don't even mention it.
I'm almost worried to death over this.
What, did you set your sights too high?
My dad insisted on me
applying to a military academy.
Saying things like
no one in our Han family
has ever been a soldier,
and he was counting on me
to honor our ancestors.
He also said that military personnel
have good benefits,
and a position is directly arranged
after graduation.
I couldn't oppose him,
so I gritted my teeth
and applied for it.
What was your dad thinking?
Who knows? He comes up
with one thing after another.
What should I do if I really get in?
I can't stand that hardship.
I'm nervous every day.
Don't worry, you definitely won't
pass the military inspection.
I got to go now.
Brother.
It's rare to see you by yourself.
Are you still my younger brother?
I'm talking to you, so put down the pen.
I'm doing these problems on a tight schedule.
Have you ever taken the college entrance exam?
Don't you know that you have to answer
within a set time?
My time is precious.
Isn't mine too?
Do you have any idea how much benefit I create
for the group in a minute?
Do you think I came to you to chat leisurely?
Put down the pen.
Alright, alright.
I'm going to Hong Kong.
Go ahead.
I want you to come with me.
There are great educational
resources in Hong Kong.
Your father and I have already discussed this.
No way.
I'm not going.
What do you mean "no way"?
Staying here and attending
a third-tier university is a waste of time.
Who said I'm going to a third-tier university?
I applied to the Air Force
University of Aeronautics.
That's right.
I'm going to a first-tier university.
I'm your brother.
Don't you think I know your level?
No, you don't.
Fine.
Let me ask you.
If you don't get admitted,
will you go to Hong Kong with me?
I won't.
I promised Su Yu
to grow up with Duo together,
and never to part.
I am your brother.
I grew up with you.
And you've only known them for a few years.
You'd rather waste time with them
than venture out with me.
You, don't expect to tie me down
with affection and resources.
The road of Wu Bi will be paved by myself,
not you.
Here's another question.
Say it.
Can you not live without him?
What do you mean?
Do you have your own perspective on life?
Your own values?
Why do you sound like my dad?
I don't want my brother
to become someone else's accessory.
How am I an accessory?
You've only lived with me for a few days.
Then let me ask you,
if he wants your dad's group,
will you give it to him?
I will.
You guys must be separated.
Impossible.
Then I wish you,
a place on the honor roll.
How long
do you think this ride would last?
This bike seems like a sturdy one.
The chain's a bit rusty is all.
Apply some oil when we get home,
and it will be as good as new.
I think
it can last for at least another two years.
What I meant was
how long can we ride this bike together?
However long you want it to be.
We're both going to college in Beijing.
I can even pick you up
and drop you off on my bike.
But let's make a deal in advance.
You can't live on campus.
We still live at home, even if it's far.
There's plenty of time in college.
We can spend it on the road.
You should focus on getting admitted first.
No problem, I have faith in you.
Why do I always feel
that our days riding bikes on the road
won't be long now?
What did you say?
Nothing, just keep pedaling.
Guys, the college entrance exam
is the day after tomorrow.
We're going to have a day off tomorrow.
Which means today
will be the last class
we have in this classroom.
I will also assign you the final homework.
I have prepared some wish cards.
Everyone can write your name
and the school you want to apply to on it.
Finally, stick it on the blackboard.
When you come back to school,
those who have realized their wishes
can take away your wish card.
I believe
that our whole class
will clear this blackboard.
I wish everyone success in the exam.
♫ I never thought about what would be
at the end of the road ♫
♫ What it would be like ♫
♫ I never considered
whether what I was doing was right or wrong ♫
♫ Let them say ♫
♫ Maybe it's best ♫
♫Let the fire burn in my heart♫
♫ We pray ♫
♫ We look far away ♫
♫Even if we stumble time and again,
we keep running♫
♫ Despite the torment ♫
♫ And the times we could only roar in anger ♫
♫ We have never retreated ♫
♫ Maybe it's not a coincidence ♫
♫ Dark clouds block every star's light ♫
♫ There will be a dawn ♫
♫ As always ♫
♫ Promise me to keep searching ♫
He's out. He's out.
Son, son, how did you do?
Over here.
Mom.
I'm here. How was the exam?
Come here.
Mom.
Son.
How did it go?
That's great.
- It wasn't difficult.
- Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go home.
Why isn't he back yet? Look at the time.
Mom.
Come here.
Over here.
Mom.
How did you do?
Just average.
Forget it, it's over anyway.
Don't think about it anymore.
Wait for me to take you to school.
You dare to fool me.
Classmates, the college entrance exam is over.
We're free.
That's great.
Come on, let's take a picture.
Cheese.
Su Yu.
I gave you a love letter in my sophomore year,
and you didn't accept it.
Do you remember?
At that time,
I thought it was because of Ye Wanying
that you didn't accept it.
But later,
I found out I was wrong.
If I gave you a love letter now,
would you accept it?
You can accept it for him.
A love letter written to two people?
That's wild.
You can read it for yourself.
I'm going to the toilet.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
I don't know what to give you.
I'll give you a mirror.
If you're unhappy in the future,
look in the mirror more.
There's nothing
that your handsome face can't fix.
Su Yu, I…
Alright, you don't have to say it.
I understand.
That night,
when I said Wu Bi was more handsome than you,
I was joking.
Actually, in my heart,
you're the most handsome boy
I've ever seen since I was a child.
Are you busy?
Uncle.
You're busier than me.
Zhang, a cup of tea, please.
How are things with Hong Kong?
There's one more case next week.
After dealing with it, I can go over.
Uncle, you seem to be in a good mood today.
It's Wu Bi.
He passed the first-tier university line.
I came here to talk to you about this.
You don't need to arrange for him
to go study in Hong Kong.
I really didn't expect
Wu Bi to get into a prestigious
school on his own.
I didn't expect Su Yu
to have such a big influence on him.
Now, if Wu Bi is with Su Yu,
I'm more at ease.
I never expected
that the son I couldn't teach well
would be taught well by another child.
It's quite something.
Su Yu is quite something.
Mr. Mo, here's your tea.
Are you scared?
No.
It's a pony.
This pony is mine.
He's my little knight.
You should join us too.
I'm afraid Duo will fall.
I won't, brother. You should go have fun.
Come on, there are caregivers over there.
He can watch her for us.
I've never ridden a horse before,
and I'm scared.
So you have things you're afraid of.
Come, I'll teach you.
It's okay.
Come on up, let's ride one together.
You're not at home?
I'm at the horse ranch.
The contract I left
in your suitcase last time,
I need it now.
Can you come over here?
I'm dozens of kilometers away from the city.
It's going to take a while to get back.
How about this? You go in and find it yourself.
The key is underneath the brick
on the left of the front door.
Alright, got it.
You can dig one.
Make a little heart.
Okay.
What's wrong, brother?
Haven't found it yet?
Yeah, think again where you put it.
Su Yu, did I give you
a contract the other day?
Yes, you said you were afraid of losing it,
so you asked me to keep it.
Where did you put it?
In the drawer under that desk.
Go to Su Yu's bedroom,
and it's in the drawer of his desk.
Got it.
Let's go and play for a while longer.
Come on.
He trusted such business secrets with him.
By the way,
Didn't you come back with your girlfriend?
Where is she?
She left in a hurry
as soon as she got off the plane.
I don't know who she rushed to see.
What about your little girlfriend?
Haven't seen you be two together for days.
Why aren't you accompanying her?
What's there to accompany her?
She's just a little girl.
It's just eating, shopping,
and watching movies.
I'm not interested in these.
What if someone else is?
The last time I heard such a character setting
was from my girlfriend.
Enough, bro.
Zhang, help me check something.
The high school Ye Wanying
attended before going abroad.
What if she wants to switch you?
That's impossible.
Why?
Even if it's something I don't want,
if someone else wants to take it,
there's only one outcome.
What?
Death.
Of course, except for you.
Then, you should switch to another one.
What do you mean?
She's been pestering me.
Hello, Mr. Mo, I've checked.
It was indeed that high school.
Wu Bi.
I can't believe you take the blame
for him for such things.
What else are you not willing to do?
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
Su Yu and I just had a past.
I don't care about you two.
I just want to ask you,
did Wu Bi always know about this all along?
Yes.
After you two met in the bar that day,
you went to the bathroom together.
What did you talk about?
I begged him not to tell you about this.
Then he asked me to promise him one condition.
What condition?
To stay away from Su Yu.
Why?
♫ Mila, Mila ♫
♫ You're such a beautiful flower ♫
♫ You're the summer I can't bear to part with ♫
♫ You always have so many ideas ♫
♫ Occasionally, you're not so obedient ♫
♫ But it's you who bring the worries ♫
♫ That make a complete family ♫
♫ From today, every minute and second ♫
♫ Will be the treasure of my life ♫
♫ Because with you by my side ♫
♫ Everything becomes beautiful ♫
♫ From today, every moment and instant ♫
♫ Will be the happiest time in life ♫
♫ No matter where you are, home will be ♫
♫ In that place ♫