♫ Did we agree
we would stay together forever? ♫
♫ No matter what, it will be true ♫
♫ Did we agree
we would stay together forever? ♫
♫ No matter what, it will be true ♫
♫ Did we agree
we would have endless stories? ♫
♫ About you ♫
♫ About our family ♫
♫ I'll wait here foolishly for you ♫
♫ No matter if a sudden storm comes ♫
♫ I'll have everything ready here ♫
♫ Just waiting for your word ♫
♫ I'll guard you silently here ♫
♫ I fear even my breath will disturb you ♫
♫ Maybe this is the meaning of family ♫
♫ How beautiful ♫
(Stay With Me)
(Episode 20)
Brother, which one is Gemini?
Which one is Sagittarius?
Well,
your dad gave you a car for your birthday.
Why didn't you seem happy?
Your dad gave you a car?
You can take us for a ride, right?
Not before I get my driver's license.
Then why aren't you happy?
It's nothing.
He has loads of these.
He can buy a car whenever he wants.
There's no sincerity in this.
Be content.
What my dad gave me was a lottery ticket.
What your dad gave you was hope.
Stop arguing.
Didn't you ever learn a text in school?
It's called
"The Duck and the Goose Host a Feast".
The duck and the goose
were swimming in the river.
The goose said, I've found something delicious.
Please come to my house.
Then, the duck visited the goose.
The goose took out
fresh grass roots and sprouts.
The duck left unhappily,
thinking, "why did it
treat me to such lousy things?"
The next day, the duck
invited the goose to its house.
It prepared its beloved snails and eels.
But the goose said,
"I'm sorry. I only like
grass roots and sprouts."
Keep these for yourself.
The duck understood.
Others may not necessarily like what you like.
The goose had already taken out
its most beloved food
to treat it.
So the duck said,
"I will find some grass roots and sprouts."
"Let's eat together."
So, they have already taken out
their best things
for you.
You should stop being picky.
Did you hear that?
Even a single child knows it.
If you put it that way,
doesn't that mean your mom did nothing wrong?
She loves money.
She naturally hopes you live a wealthy life.
Then why won't you accept it?
That's a different matter.
Brother, I want to see Pisces.
Let me check.
We've paid so much money,
but we only received a little.
It's not enough for me to vent.
Don't say such words, bro.
Or else, I'll share some with you.
What's the point of doing the same questions?
Can you tell if the questions are different?
No matter how many times I do,
it's like in vain.
Don't worry,
you won't have to rely on this
to make a living in the future.
Well,
should I also enroll in
an art exam training program this summer?
Next year, I will also take the exams for
Central Academy of Drama and Beijing Film Academy.
Sounds reliable.
You are going to be senior.
What should you do during this holiday?
Students, you don't need me
to remind you, right?
School's over.
Holiday's started.
Your noodles.
Here's your menu.
Su,
you're employing child labor.
It's fine if Duo comes to play,
but don't let those two come.
They are about to be senior.
Don't let their studies be delayed.
This is not my doing.
They wanted to come themselves.
We're not working for free.
It's "work-study balance."
You need to pay us at the end of the month.
Look, look.
Right, we need to save up for our trip.
Right?
Alright, you bet.
Take this over now.
It is hot. I'll do it.
Okay.
Is there no menu?
Here's your menu.
I'll have the braised noodles then.
Mom, Wu Bi's father is here.
He wants to eat braised noodles.
Waiter, the bill please.
How much is it?
Twenty yuan in total.
Then just make him whatever he wants.
Right.
I'll do it.
Take this to your dad.
The taste is not bad.
It tastes like what your mom made.
We're doomed.
What's wrong?
He said the noodles you made
taste like his ex-wife's.
Isn't it good that he likes it?
What's good about it?
I already have an ex-wife who went with him.
What are you thinking about?
(Zhou's Snacks)
It tastes good.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
He didn't say anything to you, did he?
No. He just had a bowl of noodles and left.
I am exhausted for toiling for a day.
I'm saying,
"I am exhausted for toiling for a day."
You are not tired after lifting
fifty or sixty kilograms of dumbbells
dozens of times back and forth,
but you're already tired
for carrying a few plates.
Work and exercise are not the same.
It's true.
My back is sore.
Why don't you help me stretch my muscles?
You're tired and I'm not?
Then I'll help you stretch.
Stop it.
It's not like we haven't done it before.
Easy.
(Zhou's Snacks)
I'm going to go out for supplies.
You two take good care of the restaurant.
Okay.
Why is your dad here again?
How should I know?
Here it is.
I used to not see him for a long time,
but why is he so free now?
Sit here.
Okay.
Order.
Come on. Have a seat.
Little girl, order.
Look.
Yes.
We'll have six bowls of noodles
and a portion of braised beef.
What about you?
Whatever. You guys order.
Okay.
Then let's have a large mixed vegetable dish.
Okay, okay.
That's all.
The noodles are good.
It's hand-rolled noodles. Very chewy.
I usually eat too much meat and fat,
and just want to eat this.
Isn't that Wu Bi?
Wu Bi.
Is it your son, Mr. Wu?
Yes, my son.
Is this your own noodle restaurant?
Mr. Wu doesn't have that time.
Mr. Wu, is he doing work-study here?
I didn't ask him to come here,
but he insisted on coming.
Mr. Wu, your son
is willing to work-study in a place like this.
What a good boy, right?
That's right. Yes.
Mr. Wu, how did you educate him?
For my little brat,
don't mention work-study.
It's already a blessing
if he isn't extravagant.
Brother Wu Bi, they are praising you.
I know.
Dig in.
Try this. I cooked it.
Stir-fried pork with green peppers.
The seasoning is just right.
Well done. Only working for a few days,
and you've already mastered it.
Delicious.
Eat more.
Look, what did I tell you?
There's no father in the world
who doesn't care about his own child.
Your father
has visited our restaurant twice already.
Yeah. You even said
your dad didn't approve of you.
He praised me through others' mouths.
He's really trying hard.
Some men just aren't good at
expressing themselves.
Aren't you just like your dad?
Your dad never praised you,
but have you ever praised your dad?
I won.
You may be smarter than me,
but your tongue isn't as flexible as mine.
Again.
Still not convinced?
Brother, I found a treasure
in the small statue.
What treasure?
This is evidence that Hongsheng Company
colluded with Xincheng Company
to switch the batch of goods.
What switch?
What evidence?
Your mom got the evidence before she died.
She had no reason to commit suicide.
Fifty, fifty-three.
Where are you going?
We have important business to handle.
Stay at home.
Did you get through on the phone?
No. It's busy.
Are you sure your dad is at the company?
Let's check first.
Today's order is very important.
Hongsheng Group has been watching closely.
There can't be any mistakes.
Don't worry.
We are very well prepared.
As long as you negotiate sincerely,
there will be no problem.
Why are you here?
I have something important to tell you.
I have more important things to do.
I don't have time for you.
Uncle, this matter is really important today.
We hope you can give us a few minutes to talk.
Why are you messing around with him?
I have an important client to meet.
I can't waste time.
What client is more important than my mother?
What are you talking about?
Here.
Where did you find this?
In this small statue.
So, are we still meeting Mr. Ma today?
What do you think?
Then we are going…
To the police station.
Mr. Zhang, I'm sorry to bother you again.
Mr. Wu,
haven't you watched
the traffic accident video of your wife
many times?
That place is a blind spot for surveillance.
I want to see the driving trajectory
before her accident.
Okay.
Who left this?
I'm not sure.
I went out to feed Dalang just now.
When I came back,
this letter was already here.
Who came here this afternoon?
Your sister came.
You weren't there at the time.
And then she left after a while.
How long it has been since she left?
About an hour ago.
Wu Bi, I'm sorry.
You need to live a good life with your dad.
I have evidence of Hongsheng Group's fraud.
Bring a million in cash to Baige Bridge.
Don't withdraw money with your own card.
Don't tell anyone.
Time waits for no one.
This is her record
passing this intersection twice.
In other words,
on the day when Ms. Mo had an accident,
she left the city and then returned.
She definitely had something to do.
Otherwise, she wouldn't have passed
the same place twice.
This also proves either this incident
was a traffic accident,
or murder.
There is no possibility of suicide.
Mr. Zhang, I just found out
that there is more money
in Zhou Shu's account.
This kid might have leaked the information.
Where is he? Have you contacted him?
I can't get in touch.
Have you sent someone to watch Wu Zhenghao?
Yes, he's been in the company
and hasn't gone out.
But his wife
left the city for no reason today.
What are you waiting for? Hurry up and go.
(Receipt)
No. It's too dangerous to take this.
What if something goes wrong?
What do I do then?
Mr. Zhang,
thank you.
You're welcome.
I will definitely be responsible for this case.
If I remember correctly,
this hit-and-run driver's
sentence isn't up yet, right?
Yes. He was a hit-and-run driver.
His sentence will not be up until next year.
Contact the lawyer.
Ok, I got it.
Stop mulling over. Go to sleep.
Su Yu, I'm scared.
Don't be afraid. I'm here.
I'll pick it up.
Wu Bi, your dad can
give you an explanation now.
Mom, mom!
Don't cry.
(Grave of beloved wife Mo Renci)
The hit-and-run driver
confessed everything.
Zhou Shu has also been found.
Zhang Hongsheng
has also been put on file for investigation.
What's the point of saying such things now?
Renci,
can you hear me?
Can you forgive me?
I'm sorry.
I didn't take good care of your mother.
Wu never let me get involved in
the company's affairs before.
I thought he was looking down on my abilities.
Now I know
he was protecting me.
Sis, actually Mr. Wu is quite good to you.
He is just not good at expressing.
I used to be quite jealous of his ex-wife.
I felt that Zhenghao only had her in his heart.
Now that I know the truth,
I feel quite ashamed.
Before her accident,
she was still thinking of
giving me a little sculpture.
I have only met her a few times,
but she cared so much about my son.
But now, what I do for her son
is really not enough.
She makes me feel ashamed.
Sis, don't think like that.
You've been so good to Wu Bi.
We've all seen it.
Besides, there are still so many days ahead.
Zhenghao, why are you here?
I came to have a look.
Sis, I'll leave you.
Mr. Wu, I'm leaving.
I'm really sorry,
I bought this yard without your consent.
I thought the kids could come live here.
I didn't expect…
It's okay. Isn't this great?
Weren't you going to a meeting?
I didn't attend.
It has been a long time
since we had a meal together.
(Zhou's Snacks)
Easy, watch the step.
There is soup in here. In case of spilling it.
Push it in.
Let's go.
Easy, easy.
Okay.
Be careful.
I told you to hire someone early on,
but you insisted on using the kids.
Look how good it is now.
The kids are freed,
and we don't have to rush around anymore.
There weren't so many customers at first.
Look at it now.
Look at this.
As Wu Bi lives in our house,
his dad gave us such a big order.
He definitely wants his son to live better.
We can't treat him badly.
Of course, we can't treat him badly.
Most importantly,
he's not just doing it for his son.
It's because your cooking is good.
Sweet talk, huh?
By the way, my mom called.
She said she wasn't feeling well recently.
I'm thinking of going home
in a few days to check on her.
Do you need me to accompany you?
The restaurant can't be left unmanned.
Besides, there are two kids at home.
I'll go by myself.
What about Duo?
I'll take Duo.
Grandma loves her the most.
She definitely wants to see her.
Okay, then be careful on the road.
I'm here. Don't worry.
Put it up there. Be careful.
Is there any more?
Yes.
- Hurry, hurry.
- Is there any more?
Duo, don't take so many books.
They're too heavy.
I can carry them.
Look, we're going to
accompany grandma and take care of her.
You won't have time to read so many books.
I'll read novels and tell stories to grandma.
Maybe her illness will get better.
Take them then.
Come on. Let me do it.
My girl,
remember to call me if you miss me.
Don't secretly eat candy.
Wait until I come back.
Got it.
What candy?
She likes sweets, right?
She's afraid we'll eat secretly.
What are you looking for?
I put eight quail eggs.
We agreed to have four each one.
I only ate three. How come
there's none left?
Nonsense. I didn't eat that many.
Did you eat them secretly?
You're the one who ate them secretly.
It was you who ate them.
You ate them.
You ate them secretly.
It's nothing if you ate them.
It was you.
You… I…
- Are you seeking death? Are you?
- Brother.
Fine, fine, stop messing around.
Dig in.
You ate them secretly. It was you.
I…
Stop!
♫ Mila, Mila ♫
♫ You're such a beautiful flower ♫
♫ You're the summer I can't bear to part with ♫
♫ You always have so many ideas ♫
♫ Occasionally, you're not so obedient ♫
♫ But it's you who bring the worries ♫
♫ That make a complete family ♫
♫ From today, every minute and second ♫
♫ Will be the treasure of my life ♫
♫ Because with you by my side ♫
♫ Everything becomes beautiful ♫
♫ From today, every moment and instant ♫
♫ Will be the happiest time in life ♫
♫ No matter where you are, home will be ♫
♫ In that place ♫