♫ Did we agree
we would stay together forever? ♫
♫ No matter what, it will be true ♫
♫ Did we agree
we would stay together forever? ♫
♫ No matter what, it will be true ♫
♫ Did we agree
we would have endless stories? ♫
♫ About you ♫
♫ About our family ♫
♫ I'll wait here foolishly for you ♫
♫ No matter if a sudden storm comes ♫
♫ I'll have everything ready here ♫
♫ Just waiting for your word ♫
♫ I'll guard you silently here ♫
♫ I fear even my breath will disturb you ♫
♫ Maybe this is the meaning of family ♫
♫ How beautiful ♫
(Stay With Me)
(Episode 6)
(Outgoing call)
Could you help me find out
which school Su Yu is in?
The teacher is coming.
Su Yu, come out with me for a moment.
Su Yu, I can't get involved in
your family matters.
Go in by yourself.
Let me introduce myself.
Don't bother. I know who you are.
You really live up to being Xiao San's son.
Born with an extraordinary temperament.
My temperament
has nothing to do with your wife.
I take after my dad.
Your mom is right.
You are stubborn for real.
What do you want from me? Just say it.
Your mom misses you.
I hope you can visit her when you have time.
Is there anything else?
I think she should have mentioned it to you.
We want to transfer you to a better school.
With your grades, your future is limitless.
Can I ask you a favor?
Go ahead.
Tell your wife not to meddle in
others' family affairs.
My son is your age.
His rebelliousness is even stronger than yours.
I often tell him one thing.
You can be reckless.
But when it comes to your future
and gains and losses,
you need to consider the bigger picture.
So is your son listening to you?
He will sooner or later.
Because no one would give up shortcuts
and compete with others instead.
In my eyes, both of you are the same.
Both are my sons.
For what he has,
I will do my best to provide them for you.
I won't let your mom feel
that I'm being unfair.
First,
I am not your son.
I have my own father.
Second,
I am not on the same path as Xiao San.
My life has no shortcuts.
Really. Call me next time.
No problem.
Deal?
Definitely.
Let's go, let's go.
Hello, Auntie.
You didn't tell my dad
which school I transferred to, did you?
I was freaked out.
I thought I saw him just now.
I guess my eyes were playing tricks on me.
What did the teacher want with you today?
It's about my mom.
Your mom?
Your mom came to see you?
No.
It's her current husband.
What did he come to see you for?
He came to be my mom's spokesperson.
To get me to transfer
to a better school.
Did you agree?
Nonsense. How could I agree?
I didn't like him in the first place.
Especially his aggressive attitude.
As if everyone is his subordinate
and has to listen to him.
Just like my dad.
He even compared me to his son,
which made me seem so ignorant.
If his son is so outstanding,
let him cultivate his own son.
Why is he always thinking about you?
In my opinion, his son must be a waste.
Otherwise, he wouldn't always think about you.
I feel upset.
Let me tell you, if you're unhappy,
curse his son.
Curse his son to be hit as soon as he goes out.
Are you alright?
What happened?
Maybe it's too old.
Alright, Sir, I'll definitely attend
the parent-teacher conference.
Son, tomorrow's parent-teacher conference--
What happened?
Hit by the fan.
No wonder the other day,
I heard this fan creaking.
I wanted to get a new one.
Move around and see if anything's broken.
I'm fine, Uncle, my leg can move.
It's just
that I might not be able to go home tonight.
No worries. I'll go find some medicine for you.
What for?
Hello?
Hello, is this Wu Bi's parent?
Yes, yes, I am.
There's a parent-teacher conference tomorrow.
His auntie handled his enrollment before
and only left her contact information.
But the call didn't go through.
Fortunately, the home phone number
was left in the contact list.
Alright, alright,
I'll be there on time tomorrow.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
He actually transferred school
and kept it from his dad.
What kind of school is this?
It looks like an ordinary high school.
Should I tell Wu?
No. If I tell him directly.
he will definitely be furious
and then the father and son will quarrel.
The kid will definitely
say I'm stirring up trouble.
No, no, no.
Put it under the desk lamp.
This way, every time
I turn on the light to do homework,
I can see that bottle of stars.
Not bad, not bad.
That's not right.
I think I heard
that bottle of stars can glow in the dark.
If I put it under the desk lamp,
won't the light be completely
overshadowed by the lamp?
No, no, no.
I got it, I got it.
This position is good, right in the middle.
So, every time I come in, I can see it.
What are you messing around with?
Look at the mess you've made of this room.
What's the matter with you, kid?
W-W-What are you doing with all this fuss?
You little brat, dare to run out.
Get back here right away.
Wait until the parent-teacher meeting is over
and see how I deal with you.
I really should discipline him better.
This c-c-child.
W-W-Why is he---
He what?
You, clean up the room now!
I…
Dad.
Why are you dressed like this?
I have to dress up nicely
for your parent-teacher conference, right?
I can't let you lose face.
I pressed it with a washbasin last night,
but there are still wrinkles.
How come this suit has gotten so small?
Dad,
when did you buy this suit?
I've never seen you wear it.
Of course, you haven't seen it.
I bought it when I married your mom.
Take it off.
- No, no, no.
- Take it off.
I'm going to be late.
I'm going to be late!
Dad!
Hello, sir.
Please sit, please sit.
Hello.
Dear parents, please find your seats
according to the names on the seats.
You are Mao Chong's mother.
Yeah, and you are Su Yu's dad.
Right, right.
No wonder my son always
praises Mao Chong for being handsome at home.
Turns out his mother is so beautiful.
Oh my, you are good at sweet talk.
Your son is the real elite.
My son keeps talking about it every day,
saying he can still rank first
even if he sleeps.
That's amazing.
Not really.
Alright, everyone quiet down.
Have all the parents arrived?
Wu Bi's parent hasn't arrived yet.
Poor child.
Okay, let's not wait for them anymore.
I'll introduce myself first.
I am the class teacher of our class.
My name is Wang Jianjun.
The purpose of this parent-teacher conference
is mainly about
last week's midterm exam
and sharing experiences and summaries
with all the parents.
Madam, it's almost ten o'clock.
I haven't finished my makeup yet.
It takes more than half an hour to get there.
Let them start first.
Madam, hurry up,
or you'll be too late.
The exam situation is roughly like this.
Next, let's welcome the parents
to exchange educational experiences.
First, let's welcome Su Yu's father
to share with you, okay?
Everyone, welcome.
Come.
Hello, Sir. Hello, dear parents.
Uh, I-I really don't have
anything good to share,
because I never managed this child.
Don't hide it. Just share it.
We want to learn too.
Dear parent, I'm not hiding anything.
You see, when I come home from work every day,
the child has already finished his homework.
When I get up in the morning to go to work,
he's already gone to school with his backpack.
How do I...
How can he still score first place?
Just say a few words, please.
It's so annoying.
Our child studies till midnight every day
but still fails.
You should be content.
My daughter doesn't even do her homework.
All she cares about is looking pretty.
All girls are like this.
Wang, drive faster, please.
Alright.
Next, let's broadcast the principal's speech.
Dear parents and teachers,
I believe the class teachers
have already summarized the experiences
and shortcomings of this exam for the parents.
I won't go into detail on that.
My speech today
is mainly to inspire you, dear parents.
Students in every score range
have their own goals.
For example, how could students in the top 200
squeeze into the top 100
with the help of the parents?
For students in the top 100,
let's strive for the top 10
in the next monthly exam.
For the top 10 students,
strive to rank second
in the whole school.
After all, surpassing Su Yu
is still a difficult thing to do.
Of course, Su Yu
not only has talent
but also puts in a lot of effort.
Our classmates should learn from him.
That's impressive.
Alright, thank you, dear parents.
We'll end today's parent-teacher conference.
If any parent has any questions,
you can come to me individually.
Everyone else can leave.
Uh, aren't you going to chat with him?
I won't go just yet.
Alright, I'll go over and chat.
Okay, there you go.
I need to hurry to the lottery station.
I won second prize yesterday.
This is a big deal.
My child has been working hard lately,
but the grades just won't improve.
Take it easy, Madam.
I'm fine.
It feels like I've traveled back in time.
I seem to have seen Su Zhigang
from more than a decade ago.
I must be seeing things wrong.
Encouragement is still needed.
That's right, what you said is very true.
Didn't we just say that?
You are?
I am Wu Bi's parent.
Please wait a moment.
We'll go to the conference room
for a separate chat later.
Okay, Sir, you go ahead.
Sir, what should we do with our child?
It's still a problem
with their learning methods.
How have you been feeling these past few days?
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Just walking is still a bit difficult.
How did the parent-teacher conference go?
Just one word: awesome.
I've never felt as proud as I did today.
Son, you really make me proud!
Did you see your good buddy?
What good buddy?
I saw him, I saw him.
We chatted for a long time and didn't let go.
I'll cook for you guys now.
Alright.
He probably didn't go.
How could he possibly go?
If he found out I transferred,
he would have made a fuss already.
Ms. Zhou.
Take this.
Okay.
Eat it while it's hot.
Thank you, Ms. Zhou.
Ride carefully.
Do you have the strength?
Alright, I'll really give it to you this time.
Where did you go?
Helping Wu Bi to the restroom.
You know about his mom's situation?
You know about it either?
Who doesn't know in our class?
His mom is so high-profile.
High-profile?
Yeah, on the day
of the parent-teacher conference,
his mom dressed very high-profile and flashy.
How is that possible? You must be mistaken.
How could I be mistaken?
His mom stood at the door
and said, "I am Wu Bi's mother."
Then the teacher dismissed the other parents
and had a private meeting with his mom.
My mom has a deep impression of it.
Your mom must be mistaken.
It was Wu Bi's dad who came that day.
There's no way it could be wrong.
At that time, apart from my mom,
other parents also saw it.
They were all discussing it.
If you don't believe me, go ask them.
Really? Everyone saw it?
Don't run. Wait a moment.
What's wrong?
How about I give you a ride home directly?
Don't bother. I can go back by myself.
How can you go back with this foot?
I can ride on one foot.
Right,
aren't your dad and my dad really close?
But I've never seen your dad show up.
Don't you guys live in this area?
Well, he's usually busy,
always working night shifts.
Then, how about some weekend,
I come to your house for dinner?
You can't always be mooching off my family.
My dad doesn't know how to cook.
If not eating, at least I can visit, right?
Alright. Let's go.
- Are you tired from riding?
- It's fine.
I'll ride. Give it to me.
Get on.
Hold on tight.
Let's go.
I'm leaving.
Hey, I'm Wu Bi.
Do me a favor.
Help me hire a dad.
Dad.
How did you get to know Wu Bi's dad?
Well...
His dad's company
used to be next to our factory.
When we had time, we would eat together
at a construction site cafeteria.
And as time went by,
we became familiar.
But I heard Wu Bi say
his mom was a sculptor before she passed away.
His dad was able to marry an artist.
He must not be an ordinary person, right?
His dad's business
was doing really well at the time.
But then he lost money in business.
And his mom passed away.
Didn't they just move to this area?
I'm an extra.
I'm a professional actor.
What have you acted in?
I acted as a head once.
I was playing a servant,
peeping at women
taking a bath through a window.
At that time, I stretched my head out
and I got stuck there.
I moved left and right.
From beginning to end, there was just
my head in the frame.
Isn't that funny?
Alright, alright.
It's you then.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
I would like to know
if you want me to pretend to be your dad
and go to a parent-teacher conference for you.
No. It's much more complicated than that.
I like challenging roles.
Those with
rich emotions.
When I let it all out in acting,
I even scare myself.
So, starting from today, you'll live here.
No matter who comes,
you have to insist that you're my dad.
And don't mention
that you were an extra before.
Is that okay?
It's a big deal, huh?
Why don't you give it a try
and call me "dad"?
What actor did he find me?
Dad.
I am dad.
I am daddy.
I am his father.
Hello, I am a dad.
Son.
Take a look.
Start.
Hello.
Uncle, I am Wu Bi's classmate.
My dad asked me to bring you some fruit.
Su Zhigang's son.
You've grown so much.
Come in, come in.
You even brought apples.
I'll wash the apples for you. Take a seat.
Alright then.
Luckily only one came.
If his dad came along, too.
It would have been a group scene.
You don't look like your dad.
You don't look like your dad either.
Sons take after their moms.
Come on, come on.
Eat an apple.
Alright, you have one too.
Thank you, Dad.
He is quite good-looking, isn't he?
Dad, I want to chat with my classmate.
You can stay aside for a while.
How could you talk to your dad like that?
Do you talk to your father like this?
How have I been educating you?
My old classmate's son is visiting us.
Shouldn't I chat with him?
Right?
It's also my fault.
I've been neglecting to discipline my son.
Uncle, are you busy with work usually?
To say I'm not busy,
I have to get up at six
in the morning to stake out.
To say I'm busy,
I haven't had a job for days,
just waiting for a boxed meal.
Stake out?
What do you do for a living?
I... collect debts.
Nowadays, debts are not easy to collect.
You must have a tough job.
Yeah, who doesn't have it tough?
Being a father is hard.
Your dad is struggling too.
But when I think of
my older brother,
I feel
not good.
When I think of your dad,
I feel
pain.
Pain.
Dad, I'm back.
Why are you back so late today?
I chatted with Wu Bi's dad for a while.
He's quite a talker.
He talked a lot about your youth.
Wu Bi... he's quite mischievous.
To be honest with you,
a few days ago, my classmates
were gossiping about Wu Bi's family.
I had doubts about his identity.
But after going there today,
I realized I was overthinking.
Look, look.
Even if you doubted him,
you couldn't have doubted
your own father, right?
♪ I came from Wolong Gang ♪
♫ Mila, Mila ♫
♫ You're such a beautiful flower ♫
♫ You're the summer I can't bear to part with ♫
♫ You always have so many ideas ♫
♫ Occasionally, you're not so obedient ♫
♫ But it's you who bring the worries ♫
♫ That make a complete family ♫
♫ From today, every minute and second ♫
♫ Will be the treasure of my life ♫
♫ Because with you by my side ♫
♫ Everything becomes beautiful ♫
♫ From today, every moment and instant ♫
♫ Will be the happiest time in life ♫
♫ No matter where you are, home will be ♫
♫ In that place ♫