♫ Did we agree
we would stay together forever? ♫
♫ No matter what, it will be true ♫
♫ Did we agree
we would stay together forever? ♫
♫ No matter what, it will be true ♫
♫ Did we agree
we would have endless stories? ♫
♫ About you ♫
♫ About our family ♫
♫ I'll wait here foolishly for you ♫
♫ No matter if a sudden storm comes ♫
♫ I'll have everything ready here ♫
♫ Just waiting for your word ♫
♫ I'll guard you silently here ♫
♫ I fear even my breath will disturb you ♫
♫ Maybe this is the meaning of family ♫
♫ How beautiful ♫
(Stay With Me)
(Episode 11)
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't come here at all.
This is your future family business.
To hell with the family business.
I don't want any of it, you can have it all.
Little brat.
You're only three years older than me.
But when I was still studying,
I started getting involved in
the overseas branch.
You should start learning early too.
The experience gained from work
is much more practical than from books.
Didn't my dad
come back with you?
He won't be able to come back for a while.
I returned to China early
to assist him here.
We haven't seen each other
for more than a year, right?
You've grown quite a bit.
Yeah. I've just grown taller, not wiser.
You know you're not wiser too.
Even moved out due to a quarrel with your dad.
Can a woman
who can handle your dad be ordinary?
Aren't you afraid she'll usurp your position?
Let her do it. I don't care.
Who are you living with now?
With that woman's son.
Right, it's my stepmother's biological son,
named Su Yu.
I'll introduce him to you later.
We have a great relationship.
I'm telling you
I've never met anyone as smart as him.
We studied these days, right?
Hold on.
I say you're not only heartless
but also brainless.
You leave your own home behind
and live with someone else's son.
It's not what you think.
He's not close to his mother
and his father has remarried.
He and I are in the same boat.
We're a real blended family.
What kind of blended family is it?
I've never heard of it.
You wouldn't have been brainwashed, would you?
It seems that not only is his mother powerful,
her son is not simple either.
I can't reason with you.
You'll know when you meet him.
Yes, I really need to meet him.
Aren't you coming back with your girlfriend?
Where is she?
She was in a hurry to leave
as soon as the plane landed.
I don't know who she rushed to see.
Isn't that Ye Wanying?
It should be.
Didn't she go abroad?
Yeah, I heard she's settled down abroad.
Could you do me a favor
and call Su Yu out for me?
Okay.
Su Yu, Su Yu,
a beautiful lady is looking for you.
Someone needs you outside.
Why did you come back?
Why can't I come back?
Is he your friend?
Why don't you introduce him to me?
His name is Wu Bi.
Hello, I'm Ye Wanying.
I have to go.
We will review
the content of Unit Three.
In this lesson, we will review the third unit.
Open your books and turn to page 67.
She is indeed beautiful.
No wonder Su Yu still craves for her.
Let's read the first question.
Never should a man stay in a closed-door room.
You should explore the universe.
Have dinner together tomorrow night.
How man copes with
the immense changing.
This sentence means
no one should be isolated
but should face the world
to explore how people deal with
the rapidly changing situation.
This sentence is an English proverb.
And it is also the focus of our lesson.
The key content of this chapter
will be on the test.
Who is Ye Wanying?
Her?
Oh, the prettiest girl in our school before.
And then?
She went abroad.
In another country.
Her dad and my dad are friends.
That she was able to enter the school abroad
was due to my connections.
So isn't she just using you?
So calculating.
It's just a matter of mutual benefit.
So it is the key point of this chapter.
And over the years, it's been popular
in the college entrance examination.
When you go home,
you must read today's content thoroughly,
and memorize it.
Brother,
what's the name of your girlfriend?
Ye Wanying. Why?
Nothing.
You…
Let's have dinner together.
I'll take a rain check.
As you've been on the plane for so long,
you'd better go back and rest.
I'm not tired. I'm still excited
about returning to China.
Isn't it inappropriate to invite him alone?
Take me along.
I also like beautiful women.
Okay.
Let's go together then.
Why are you encouraging her
to have dinner together?
Su Yu, look at that vineyard.
Do you remember?
We picked grapes together then.
The grape trellis was too high
and I couldn't reach it.
So you carried me on your shoulders.
We picked and ate
and almost vomited from eating too much.
I think you must be eager.
Are you back in the country to visit relatives?
No.
Then?
To visit you.
W-What's wrong?
It's nothing. I like to drink this way.
Although we've only met once,
I always feel very familiar with you.
It feels like I've seen you before.
Nonsense. I'm Mo Yi's cousin.
How can I not be familiar?
Su Yu, have you missed me in the year I left?
What? Well, with my classmate here,
it's not good to talk about this.
What's the big deal?
At our age,
we can date freely in foreign countries.
Then did you date abroad?
How is it possible?
My heart has always been in China.
Waitress.
How may I help you?
Add a portion of pork kidneys.
Why did you order this?
What teasing.
Eat some kidneys to cover the taste.
Duo,
why are you here?
The grapes freshly picked
from my uncle's greenhouse are so sweet.
What's wrong with Brother Wu Bi?
He didn't look good today.
Who knows?
Alright, go back to sleep.
Thank you.
Why waste
good grapes?
Here, you eat.
Eat! Until you vomit. Eat, eat.
What's wrong? Are you crazy?
Do you still have her in your heart?
So what if I do?
So what if I don't?
You can't be with her.
You're overthinking.
We weren't together before.
How could it be possible now?
Why are you
so afraid of me being with her?
Who's afraid?
I-I just think she's not a good person.
You've only been together for a day
and you know she's not a good person?
If I say she isn't, she isn't.
You just need to remember what you said.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
Didn't you say you were going to introduce me
to your brother?
Which one?
The one your stepmother brought.
What's there to see about him?
Last time you were praising him.
It's only been a few days
and you've already changed your mind.
He's a very twisted person.
You definitely won't get along.
The more you say, the more I want to meet him.
A twisted person
can make you, a bad-tempered,
do nothing with him.
What about your little girlfriend?
Haven't seen you be two together for days.
Why don't you accompany her?
What's there to accompany her?
She's just a little girl.
Nothing more than
dining, shopping, or watching movies.
I'm not interested in these.
Just afraid others are interested.
What do you mean?
Nothing. Just drink your wine.
Please come in.
Do you know who I am? You just let me in.
Aren't you Mo Yi?
How did you know?
I didn't tell Wu Bi that I would come today.
My hunch.
You are smart indeed.
But as Wu Bi calls me big brother,
isn't it inappropriate for you
to call me by my name?
Wu Bi should also call me big brother.
But he also calls me by my full name.
Where's Wu Bi?
He went out.
Would you like something to drink?
Apart from these, are there any other choices?
I can make you a cup of coffee.
I never drink instant coffee.
I'll take this one.
I'm back.
Brother,
why are you here?
Why can't I be here?
No. Why didn't you inform me before you came?
Do I need to tell you before I come here?
I could have prepared in advance.
Prepared what?
Prepare to get rid of him in advance?
What are you talking about?
Come out.
Are you crazy?
Why am I crazy?
Is this place for people to live?
What are you talking about?
Am I not a person?
Don't tell me
you're living here just to keep him company?
Not just him.
Next door, there's my uncle, my aunt, and Duo.
A whole family.
Which uncle? Which aunt?
Why don't I know?
It's Su Yu's dad.
And Ms. Zhou who has been taking care of me.
Wait a minute.
His dad?
Didn't your dad marry his mom?
What does it have to do with his dad?
It's a complicated story.
I can't explain it in a few words.
It's cold outside. Let's talk inside.
How about we watch TV?
No, it's too messy.
If you think it's messy,
you can go back to your hotel.
Let's chat.
What's there to chat about?
When you called last time,
didn't you say
there's an abnormal person in your class?
What is it?
The one who sleeps all day in class
but is always first in the school.
The highest-score keeper in the internet cafe,
the abnormal with a high IQ.
The last time I heard such a character setting
was from my girlfriend.
Alright, brother, you should go now.
Why are you always driving me away?
We still have to do homework.
We have to go to school early tomorrow.
You should go.
Alright, alright, I'll go by myself.
Goodbye.
Tell me, who's abnormal?
Misunderstanding, misunderstanding.
We weren't familiar at that time, right?
Besides, abnormal is a compliment in my book.
And my brother's description
is all praise for you.
W-Why are you looking at me like that?
Nothing.
Really handsome.
Your brother also works
in your father's corporation?
Yes, he is now the vice president
of the overseas branch.
That's impressive.
He's had a talent for business
since he was a kid.
He went to college at sixteen
and started learning about
managing the company's affairs at eighteen.
It seems
your father is quite nice
to your mother's family.
Nonsense.
If it weren't for my uncle's help
in the first place,
he wouldn't even be able to start this company.
Your uncle?
Mo Yi's father?
Yeah, my father could have what he has today
all thanks to the support
of my mother's family.
Why are you so interested in my brother?
Am I?
You never
mention our family.
I kind of like him.
You're kidding.
Listen, stay away from him.
Why?
He's not the same kind of person as me.
He is very absolute in his actions,
leaving no room for negotiation.
If you don't provoke him, you're fine.
Once you provoke him,
you won't even know how you will die.
Why would I provoke him?
You…
Nothing.
But to be honest,
your brother is more handsome than you.
I'm not sure what kind of person he is,
but he is indeed more handsome than you.
One can lose face, but not demeanor.
How dare you!
I'm the most handsome. I'm the most handsome.
Fine, you're handsome.
Hurry up and do your homework.
I'm asking you, am I the most handsome?
Alright, alright, you're the most handsome.
Okay, the third question.
Be careful to understand the question.
This is not just a sentence imitation.
What is missing?
A poetic line.
Yes, a poetic line.
Look at the subject. This example.
I stared intently at this math problem.
Just when I was about to give up,
I suddenly had an epiphany.
It's really like the path was blocked
and it was dark in front of me,
then suddenly a light appeared in the darkness.
The question is simple.
Who will answer it?
Zhang Xiaoxiao.
I stood by the river bank.
The soft willow branches drooped down.
Looks like the dream
of a spring breeze in February cutting plants.
Okay, sit down.
Winter vacation will begin next week.
Ye Wanying asked me out.
She said she is going abroad.
Should I go?
Do you want to go?
I'm fine either way. It's up to you.
Who got it wrong? Raise your hand.
Why are you asking me about your own business?
Liang Wentai.
If I could make a decision, would I ask you?
I-I arrived on the African continent
and instantly felt
the overwhelming atmosphere
of dark clouds pressing against the city.
I think it's better not to--
His classmate. Wu Bi!
What are you doing? Hand over your phone.
Didn't you hear me talking? Hand it over.
Why don't you confiscate his phone?
Why don't you dare to look at me?
Don't I?
Do you?
Gentlemen, what would you like to order?
Two juices.
What flavor?
It's up to you.
Whatever.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Mr. Wu's son has good taste.
Look at that girl. So pretty.
This kid is unlucky.
Daring to compete
with Mr. Wu's son for a girlfriend.
I'm telling you,
if it wasn't for his intention,
would Wu Bi send us to watch on them?
Drinking juice here and making a mess,
and we will get five hundred yuan.
Where can you find such a deal?
Yeah.
Wu Bi is really generous.
Today we can't just keep an eye on them.
We need to show some real action.
Su Yu, you've changed a lot.
Have I?
Haven't I always been like this?
You've become more handsome.
Waitress,
I want fresh juice.
How did you make this flavor?
Sir, you just said whatever.
So you can't ask me in advance?
That's right, waitress.
- What is a waitress for?
- For what?
That's for serving customers.
Do you think it's just about serving drinks?
How about we change seats?
Actually, I was thinking the same thing.
Right?
Exactly.
Do you think I'm right?
Go ahead, go ahead.
Get some tissues, hurry.
Hurry up.
How can we sit here?
Let's go. Let's change seats.
Can we sit there?
Right here, right here.
How about you come to sit on my side?
If we sit closer,
we won't be bothered by the noise.
Originally, I thought about messing with them.
But now, they're sitting even closer.
Damn kid, it seems he doesn't want to live.
Su Yu, do you know why I came back to China?
Because of me?
More accurately,
because of your phone call.
When did I call you?
Yeah, you never answered my calls.
One day I finally got through.
I was so happy.
But someone else answered.
He told me you had someone you liked.
I couldn't accept it and I didn't believe it.
I wanted to ask you in person who she is.
What am I lacking compared to her?
If you can give me an accurate answer,
I'll book a ticket and leave immediately.
So, the girl is pursuing him?
The kid is a bit clueless then.
I can't tell you.
Why can't you tell me?
Is it that you can't tell me,
or there's no one at all?
Su Yu, I knew you were lying to me.
I'm not leaving.
I'm staying here to be with you.
Don't be foolish.
Even if you stay here,
we can't be together.
Why?
What else could it be?
Because he deserves a beating.
Stop fighting.
Bro, put more effort.
Teach this guy a lesson.
Stop it.
Screw you.
I'm telling you,
we can't brag about this when we get back.
We have to calm Wu Bi's down first.
Calm him down? Why?
Think about it.
If we tell the truth about today,
how much would it hurt Wu Bi's pride?
He's just a kid
in the middle of puberty.
This might be his first love.
Right, right, right.
So,
what should we say?
We just say the opposite.
We say whatever is nice.
So we say that the guy was chasing her?
Clever.
Let's go.
They were just chatting normally.
There were no inappropriate behaviors.
What did the girl say?
She said she doesn't like the guy
and she already has someone she likes.
Right.
So honest? She actually admitted it.
Then why would she meet him if that's the case?
No, she didn't call him.
It was the guy who pursued her.
Get lost.
I read the messages.
It was the guy who kept pestering her.
The guy called her, but she never answered.
Right? The guy wanted
to keep her in China.
Right, right. The girl rejected him decisively.
Shut up!
Did the girl say who she likes?
She didn't say.
Do you think the person might be you?
Bullshit.
Wu Bi, don't worry about it.
We've already avenged you.
Right, right, right.
We gave that jerk a good beating.
I guess he won't be able
to get out of bed for three days.
Three days? I think he won't be able
to get up for half a month.
Right.
♫ Mila, Mila ♫
♫ You're such a beautiful flower ♫
♫ You're the summer I can't bear to part with ♫
♫ You always have so many ideas ♫
♫ Occasionally, you're not so obedient ♫
♫ But it's you who bring the worries ♫
♫ That make a complete family ♫
♫ From today, every minute and second ♫
♫ Will be the treasure of my life ♫
♫ Because with you by my side ♫
♫ Everything becomes beautiful ♫
♫ From today, every moment and instant ♫
♫ Will be the happiest time in life ♫
♫ No matter where you are, home will be ♫
♫ In that place ♫