♫ Did we agree
we would stay together forever? ♫
♫ No matter what, it will be true ♫
♫ Did we agree
we would stay together forever? ♫
♫ No matter what, it will be true ♫
♫ Did we agree
we would have endless stories? ♫
♫ About you ♫
♫ About our family ♫
♫ I'll wait here foolishly for you ♫
♫ No matter if a sudden storm comes ♫
♫ I'll have everything ready here ♫
♫ Just waiting for your word ♫
♫ I'll guard you silently here ♫
♫ I fear even my breath will disturb you ♫
♫ Maybe this is the meaning of family ♫
♫ How beautiful ♫
[Stay With Me]
[Episode 24]
How did you make these
scrambled eggs so delicious?
I improved the recipe a bit.
- Really?
- Added some garlic.
It's delicious.
Hurry up.
Come here.
What's the occasion today?
Our snack shop
has been doing better and better.
The landlord agreed to rent
the second floor to us for free.
There are several bedrooms on the second floor.
It's quite spacious.
When you guys go to college,
we can move over there to live.
There's also a small study room
on the second floor. It's nice.
This way, we can do a nice renovation
on our current home.
I have already arranged a construction team,
and they will come in a few days.
During this time,
you can go live with Wu Bi first.
When we clean up the bedrooms
on the second floor,
you can come back.
What's wrong with you two?
You don't seem very happy.
We are.
Yes.
Uncle, I toast to you.
Come on.
Hey, what are you doing?
What do you mean?
Stop pretending.
Why did you suddenly rent
the second floor to Su Yu's family?
Now you admit it's Su Yu's family.
Why didn't you say so at the beginning?
You are allowed to help them,
but not me?
You'd show so much kindness to them?
I don't buy it.
I don't have any kindness for him,
but I do for you.
Isn't this what you would want?
Alright, I've got to go.
What… what are you doing standing there?
It was you, right?
What did I do?
You let your brother rent
the second floor to us for free.
You, how did you know
that house was my brother's?
Your brother told me on the phone.
When was that?
When the snack bar was not yet renovated.
I can't believe you kept it
from me for so long.
I was on tenterhooks every day.
What do you mean I kept it from you?
Who kept it from whom first?
Wait a minute.
You've been in touch with my brother privately.
I don't understand your brain.
I can't communicate with you.
♫ I never thought about what would be
at the end of the road ♫
♫ What it would be like ♫
♫ I never considered
whether what I was doing was right or wrong ♫
♫ Let them say ♫
♫ Maybe it's best ♫
♫ To remain silent now ♫
♫ Let the fire burn in my heart ♫
♫ We pray ♫
♫ We look far away ♫
♫Even if we stumble time and again,
we keep running♫
♫ Despite the torment ♫
♫ And the times we could only roar in anger ♫
I finally passed the score line,
but I have to go through
another round of re-examination.
This is a trap.
At the best time of summer vacation,
everyone is eating, drinking, and having fun,
but I'm here training.
♫ As always ♫
Why are you here?
Your house is too noisy, and I can't sleep.
How could it be noisier than the classroom?
Stop dawdling and start running.
♫ This world is as colorful as bubbles ♫
♫ Tempting to touch ♫
♫ But the more beautiful it is,
the more it disguises and breaks♫
♫ I can't control it ♫
♫ Only after experiencing it
can this moment be ♫
♫ The most worthy of appreciation ♫
♫ Otherwise, how could you know joy? ♫
♫ We pray ♫
♫ We look far away ♫
♫Even if we stumble time and again,
we keep running♫
♫ Despite the torment ♫
♫ And the times we could only roar in anger ♫
What's wrong?
Is your back bothering you again?
You should rest for a while.
I'm in my forties and my back is not good.
I should see a Chinese medicine doctor.
Brother Su Yu, are you calling Brother Wu Bi?
Yes.
He didn't pick up,
and I don't know what he's doing.
Your one doesn't work.
We need to use mine.
You see, as soon as I press it, it lights up.
Wu Bi's will light up too.
He'll contact you in a bit.
Why didn't you answer the phone?
Mo Yi?
Let's talk about that kick you did.
Why are you wearing Wu Bi's clothes?
Why can't I wear his clothes?
Don't you two often exchange clothes too?
I mean,
why did you change into another set of clothes?
I got my clothes dirty in the garage just now.
I heard from Wu Bi
that your dad's struggling with back pain.
I know a national-level expert
in spinal diseases,
and your dad can go see him.
Really?
But you need to make an appointment in advance.
It's not easy to get an appointment.
Then, can you help me make an appointment?
Okay.
Just so happens, he's free at 8 am tomorrow.
I've already made the appointment for you.
Thank you.
What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
You need a haircut.
Right, I was planning to go
for a cut these few days.
No need, I can do it for you.
You?
You know how to cut hair?
When I was studying abroad,
I did all sorts of part-time jobs to make money
and gain life experience.
Do you want to give it a try?
Sure.
You really trust my skills, huh?
Anyway, every time I just get a buzz cut
at the old man's place outside the house.
It's all the same.
Being handsome really gives one
the liberty to do anything, huh?
Thanks for the compliment.
This face of yours
really is superior.
Your mom's genes weren't wasted.
It's not scary to have a superior face,
but it's scary to have a superior brain.
Then you're quite scary.
Are you scared of me?
No.
Growing up in your environment,
where did you get such confidence?
It's not about confidence.
Then what is it?
Because you are Wu Bi's brother.
So?
So I won't have any opinions about you.
Right.
The two of us,
one is a crude rogue,
and the other is a refined rogue.
Essentially we are the same,
just different in the way we express ourselves.
What are you doing?
What did I do?
Tell me what I did.
I just helped him cut his hair,
and what's wrong with that?
Why would you cut his hair all of a sudden?
I asked him to cut it.
He said he knows how to cut hair.
I'm going to wash my hair.
What are you doing here?
I have a case in court tomorrow,
and I came here to inform you.
You must be present tomorrow,
so that even if we lose, there would be
someone to support me.
What time?
9 am.
Stay away from him in the future.
What do you mean "stay away from him"?
When have I ever tried to get close to him?
He's not as simple as we are.
He can be much more complicated than you think.
I've told you,
everyone in the Mo family is a psycho,
and none of them are easy to deal with.
He can be however he wants to be.
I'm not interested.
I'm not asking you to know him.
I'm just reminding you
to be wary of him,
and don't easily consider him one of us.
But he said,
you two, one is a crude rogue,
and the other is a refined rogue.
Essentially, you're the same,
just different in the way
you express yourselves.
Same my ass.
He's just praising himself.
We're fundamentally different.
I'm tough on the outside
and soft on the inside.
He's tough on the outside
and ruthless on the inside.
We're so different
in our bones.
Hello?
Are you up yet?
Isn't your court hearing at nine?
It's only seven.
Do you think this is like a class
where you can arrive just in time?
Alright, got it.
Why are you up so early, too?
My dad has been suffering from back pain,
and I've made an appointment
with a traditional Chinese medicine doctor.
Why so early?
He's a national treasure-level expert.
You think you can just
make an appointment whenever you want?
If it weren't for your brother, I wouldn't even
have been able to get this appointment.
Su Yu, I'll drive.
Aren't you going to the court?
I'd better take you there.
I can go to court after dropping you off.
It's not on the same route.
You just got your driver's license,
so I'm not at ease.
Didn't you hit the road directly
when you just got your driving license?
Besides, isn't your brother rushing you?
Don't worry about him.
I have to take you there,
or I won't be at ease.
Get in the car.
Hello?
Where are you now?
I just got out of the community.
How much longer until you arrive?
I can't say for sure.
I have to drop off Su Yu first
before I come to you.
What did you say?
I said, can't you wait a little bit?
I'm sure I can get there on time.
I won't miss your case.
Did you get in his car?
I'll talk to you later. Gotta go now.
Did I scare you just now?
Try to avoid taking calls
while driving in the future.
What's wrong with the car?
There's a little problem.
Is it a brake failure?
It's okay, I'm here.
Close your eyes and rest for a while.
The road ahead is all straight
and there aren't many cars.
I can slow down by manual downshift.
Wu Bi?
Wu Bi.
How… how did he get so badly injured?
Call an ambulance!
It was all because of me.
Otherwise, he wouldn't
have been hurt so badly.
♫ You said that between the two of us ♫
♫ You will protect me ♫
♫ No matter how dangerous it gets ♫
♫ You will never leave ♫
♫ I believe in every promise ♫
♫ You made to me ♫
♫ You won't leave me behind ♫
♫ Thank you for exploring with me ♫
♫ Tasting everything in this world ♫
♫ Good or bad, it doesn't matter ♫
♫as long as we are by each other's side♫
♫ Thank you for never holding back ♫
♫ Even if it means giving me
everything you have ♫
♫ You've done enough ♫
♫ This time I'll guard you in return ♫
I think it's pretty amazing
that after all these years
of bumps and bruises, no scar was left behind.
I wanted to leave a scar.
How cool would that be?
But no matter how badly I get hurt,
my body always heals well.
There's no help for it.
I'm just too slick all over,
So what's your dream?
I want to be an astronaut.
Does it sound crazy?
Not at all.
With your physical condition,
if you work on your academic courses,
you can definitely get in.
Really?
Of course.
♫ The most important person in my life ♫
♫ Is also a family member ♫
♫ Thank you for exploring with me ♫
♫ Tasting everything in this world ♫
♫ Good or bad, it doesn't matter ♫
♫ As long as we're by each other's side ♫
♫ Thank you for never holding back ♫
Wu Bi, you still have the re-examination.
Wu Bi.
You have to lay him flat on the ground.
Holding him like this is very dangerous.
Don't touch him. Don't.
♫ As long as we're by each other's side ♫
Someone, help!
Can anyone wake him up?
Stop his bleeding.
The hospital just called,
and it's the morning rush hour now.
The ambulance is stuck and can't get here.
Wu Bi. Wu Bi, hang in there.
You have to hang in there, OK?
Your mom already left so suddenly.
It can't happen to you again.
Wu Bi, listen,
it's Duo calling you.
Didn't you promise we'd always be together?
Your time can't stop at this moment.
Wu Bi.
Which direction is the ambulance coming from?
East, from the east.
♫ Mila, Mila ♫
♫ You're such a beautiful flower ♫
♫ You're the summer I can't bear to part with ♫
♫ You always have so many ideas ♫
Didn't you leave?
I asked the driver to leave
and I ran after you.
♫ But it's you who bring the worries ♫
♫ That make a complete family ♫
I am your brother, and you are my brother.
We're not redundant to each other.
I finally found you.
Quick, pack your things and go home.
From today,
to the day you get married,
I will be with you
for all the holidays
♫ No matter where you are, home will be ♫
A birthday gift, six years late.
I'm delivering it for my mom.
Why does it feel like
a Superman transformation?
Who could look so handsome
during a transformation?
I'm going to set this picture
as my computer desktop.
Wu Bi, you have to be okay.
We've been through such hard times.
There are still so many places we haven't been
and so many holidays we need to spend together.
♫ When will you grow up ♫
♫ Mila, Mila ♫
In my heart,
you've always been indestructible,
always so healthy,
always full of energy,
never needing care or protection.
But at this moment, I realize how wrong I was.
You would get hurt,
show weakness,
and stay in a coma.
I realized how afraid I am of losing you.
So much so that I would give up everything
in exchange for your life,
as long as you can live.
♫ In that place ♫
[In surgery]
What a coincidence.
Su Yu, Su Yu.
Your dad married my mom,
and you're still pretending to be poor
and trying to get close with me.
How else do you want to humiliate me?
Open the door!
Do you think I want to be his son?
In their marriage,
am I not a victim too?
Why can't we have a complete family?
♫ Mila, Mila ♫
♫ You're such a beautiful flower ♫
♫ You're the summer I can't bear to part with ♫
♫ You always have so many ideas ♫
♫ Occasionally, you're not so obedient ♫
♫ But it's you who bring the worries ♫
♫ That make a complete family ♫
♫ From today, every minute and second ♫
♫ Will be the treasure of my life ♫
♫ Because with you by my side ♫
♫ Everything becomes beautiful ♫
♫ From today, every moment and instant ♫
♫ Will be the happiest time in life ♫
♫ No matter where you are, home will be ♫
♫ In that place ♫