=Coming to Court Soon=
=Episode 6=
You two really don't know each other?
Brother.
(Personal File Form)
That day, you took on
a dozen punks by yourself.
I was there.
That was so cool.
Tell me.
Why were you drunk driving?
Why did you hit the police officers?
It's all because of Li Hai.
How is it?
Do I look even better
in this outfit?
It's chilly outside at night.
Don't take off your coat.
This family is lucky to have you.
Now you realize it?
Wretched woman.
Shameless!
Li Songyan!
Are you itching for a beating again?
You little brat, listen up.
She's your elder.
She's your mother!
She isn't my mother!
She's only a few years older than me,
and you want me to call her mom?
Shameless!
What nonsense are you spouting?
He forgot my mom's anniversary.
Songyan.
No matter what, speaking to your father
like that is wrong.
You should learn
to control your emotions.
Learn to communicate with your father.
But he's so stubborn and rigid.
How am I supposed to...
You're thinking of giving up
before even trying?
But Li Hai...
If you choose to give up, I understand.
After all, your father is
an outstanding man.
He's a well-known entrepreneur,
and a philanthropist.
He built Tonghai Logistics
from the ground up.
Who's giving up?
But...
Can I really do it?
I get it now.
What I need to do isn't
to prove that he's wrong,
but to prove that I'm right.
Alright.
That's all for today.
For now, don't leave the city.
Be ready for our summons at any time.
Brother.
Can I come to you
if I ever need help?
(Xue Biao, auto repair shop owner)
(Sir Xue.)
(Haven't seen you for a few days.)
(Wanna play a few rounds?)
(Deng Xing)
(Zhou Qi)
(Zhou Qi's friend)
Zhou Qi.
(Deng Xing)
I'm so happy
you called me.
Deng Xing.
Can you lend me 100 thousand?
A hundred thousand?
Why do you need so much money?
Are you in trouble?
I just borrowed from a loan shark.
It's okay.
If you don't have it, forget it.
Bye.
Wait.
A hundred thousand isn't a small amount.
Give me a few days.
I'll figure something out.
A hundred thousand.
(Loan Agreement)
This is still way short.
Hello?
Huang Xian.
(Black Mamba Billiards Club)
♪No complaints anyway♪
Sorry.
Four concealed triplets. I won again.
What's going on?
Kid.
You're not cheating, are you?
(Ma Haoda's subordinate)
Cheating in my house?
(Huang Xian)
Do you want to die?
I wasn't cheating.
Our boss wants to see you.
♪I shouldn't have let you suffer,
continuing this act♪
♪You don't really understand me♪
♪Why should I be the one to forgive?♪
Brother Haoda, he's here.
♪If we say goodbye, don't come back♪
♪If we say goodbye, don't look pitiful♪
I wasn't cheating.
Just joking.
Kid.
Relax.
What do you want?
I can tell.
You're different from those people.
You came here
to make money.
Relax.
I'll find you a way to make money.
Play a round for me.
If you win,
we split 40-60.
What if I lose?
Kid.
Have some confidence.
I believe in you.
Brother.
Finally off work?
You're looking for me?
I like talking to you.
Let's chat for a bit.
What,
your car broke down?
Isn't it obvious?
I'll call you a tow truck
and take you to a repair shop.
Let's go.
Sir Xue.
We've got a customer!
Little brat.
Haven't seen you in a while.
Let me take a look at you.
I got into trouble recently.
Here I am.
As soon as I got out,
I came straight to you.
And I brought you a customer.
♪The ticket stubs record the places
I've been over the years♪
♪I pick up my pen and sketch your face♪
♪It's my ignorance of despair♪
♪That lets me keep smiling so brightly♪
♪The faint light
slipping through my fingers♪
♪Writes down my persistence♪
♪What would I be without you?♪
♪The summer breeze
and wheat field find solace♪
♪Raising my hand, I slowly let go♪
♪You won't see my disappointment♪
♪Slightly open palms,
light shining through the fingers♪
♪The ticket stubs record the places
I've been over the years♪
♪I pick up my pen and sketch your face♪
♪It's my ignorance of despair♪
♪That lets me keep smiling so brightly♪
♪The faint light
slipping through my fingers♪
♪Writes down my persistence♪
♪What would I be without you?♪
♪The summer breeze
and wheat field find solace♪
♪Raising my hand, I slowly let go♪
♪You won't see my disappointment♪
♪Slightly open palms,
light shining through the fingers♪