=Coming to Court Soon=
=Episode 8=
Seven Circles.
I win.
I'm done.
Kid, good job.
You're pretty sharp.
I hope you win like this next week.
You said it.
If I win,
the debt between Zhou Qi
and you is settled.
Zhou Qi.
Feels good to have someone
stand up for you, huh?
If you lose, though...
Don't worry.
I won't lose.
I like your confidence.
Your opponent
is Xue Biao.
I'll have someone help you
when the time comes.
You're sending me abroad
just to avoid the shame of me
failing the exams, aren't you?
Li Songyan.
You're going abroad
whether you like it or not.
If you don't want the U.S.,
go to the U.K.
If you don't like the U.K.,
then Australia.
Stop acting like a child.
Why must I go abroad?
I'd rather learn from Sir Xue.
Do you know what kind
of person Xue Biao is?
And what kind of person you are?
What can you learn
by following him around?
Street racing?
Getting into the news?
What's wrong with Sir Xue?
He makes a living with his skills.
If you keep hanging around with him,
I'll break your legs.
What are you two arguing about?
The neighbors can hear you.
Hai.
Can't you talk to your son calmly?
What kind of attitude is that?
Don't act like the good guy.
This idea of sending me abroad
was probably yours.
You...
Come on.
Slap me.
Fine.
If you won't choose,
I'll choose for you.
From today until you leave for abroad,
you'll stay in your room and reflect.
You're not allowed to go anywhere.
Songyan.
(Prosecutor Zhong,
I argued with Li Hai again.)
(I really don't know what to do.)
(I have nowhere to go.)
Watch out!
When do you plan to pick him up?
Prosecutor Zhong, I'm on my way.
I'm not going back.
If you dare to pick me up,
you'll never see me again.
Li Songyan...
I don't want this kid anymore.
Prosecutor Zhong.
Let him figure it out himself.
Don't touch it.
Brother.
The uniform doesn't look like yours.
Why is it hanging here?
It was my dad's.
I didn't expect you to come
from a family of prosecutors.
Is your father still a prosecutor?
No.
My parents were in a car accident
a long time ago.
The culprit still hasn't been found.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
Kaixuan.
Thank you for staying with me so late.
Mr. Li, don't mention it.
(Li Hai's driver, Sun Kaixuan)
You've taken care of me all these years.
We've been friends for over 20 years.
There's no need for formalities.
Mr. Li, why not let him stay
for a few days?
Looks like that's the only way for now.
Let's go.
Brother.
What now?
Did you find the culprit?
(Wu's Auto Shop, secondhand car,
headlight investigation)
This is the only clue?
This has nothing to do with you.
Get some sleep.
There's an old saying,
if someone feeds you,
you owe them.
Don't worry.
With me here,
I'll help you find them.
Square headlights.
Protruding front end.
High beams focused
at the center.
Intense brightness.
It must be
the first-generation Jinbei van,
China's first world-class vehicle,
produced through CKD assembly
in the 90s.
You even recognize such an old car?
Of course.
I know everything about cars
and even auto parts.
Alright. Go study.
Don't underestimate me.
I grew up around Sir Xue.
Back in his day, he was known
as one of the "Thirteen Young Masters"
in the trade.
There wasn't a car he couldn't fix.
My dad used to work for him.
His day?
And now?
Me.
Seems like you do this often.
I still have homework to do.
See you.
(Wu's Auto Shop, secondhand car,
headlight investigation)
Mom!
(Wu's Auto Shop, secondhand car,
headlight investigation)
♪The ticket stubs record the places
I've been over the years♪
♪I pick up my pen and sketch your face♪
♪It's my ignorance of despair♪
♪That lets me keep smiling so brightly♪
♪The faint light
slipping through my fingers♪
♪Writes down my persistence♪
♪What would I be without you?♪
♪The summer breeze
and wheat field find solace♪
♪Raising my hand, I slowly let go♪
♪You won't see my disappointment♪
♪Slightly open palms,
light shining through the fingers♪
♪The ticket stubs record the places
I've been over the years♪
♪I pick up my pen and sketch your face♪
♪It's my ignorance of despair♪
♪That lets me keep smiling so brightly♪
♪The faint light
slipping through my fingers♪
♪Writes down my persistence♪
♪What would I be without you?♪
♪The summer breeze
and wheat field find solace♪
♪Raising my hand, I slowly let go♪
♪You won't see my disappointment♪
♪Slightly open palms,
light shining through the fingers♪