The Divine Machine Battalion of our Great Ming
bears the heavy responsibility of guarding the capital
and preparing for campaigns abroad.
You have managed the Divine Machine Battalion for over three years.
Regarding the position of Minister of War,
I intend to recommend you to His Majesty.
What are your thoughts on this?
I am overwhelmed with trepidation.
The position of Minister of War
has long been coveted by the Eastern Depot.
I fear that...
Last night, Li Chenyang
was hijacked at the execution ground,
and Feng Hai of the Eastern Depot was assassinated.
You must have heard about it.
If I can take on this great responsibility,
I will certainly know my place
and serve the Eunuch Lord with my life.
Do you know why His Majesty
keeps the Divine Machine Battalion's
former General Lin Feng's
sword
and musket enshrined here?
Three years ago, General Lin Feng
led three hundred soldiers of the Divine Machine Battalion
to set an ambush in the canyon,
luring ten thousand Oirat cavalry to approach.
They resisted until the very last moment,
allowing Eunuch Lord Wang to lead reinforcements in time
to strike the Oirat
and win a great victory.
General Lin and the three hundred soldiers died in glory.
Ming soldiers must take this as an example.
A small gift.
Please accept it, General.
Thank you, Eunuch Lord Wang.
This is the weapon of a guard who followed me for years.
I remember his name was Ya.
He served the Eastern Depot Eunuch Lord Shang Hua.
Until five years ago,
when I became the Eunuch Lord of the Western Depot
and took control of all Ming guards.
He came to serve me.
I am not a narrow-minded person.
But he...
tried to kill me with this dagger.
In the end,
he became a ghost under the blade.
I will not fail Eunuch Lord Wang's kindness.
Keep everything hidden in your heart,
and show nothing on your face.
In this imperial capital,
I see all kinds of guards every day.
I keep thinking,
why don't they kill me right now?
If I were a Divine Machine Battalion soldier or a guard,
I would shoot and kill me.
Right now.
At this very moment.
But you have never done so.
Why?
I dare not.
Think carefully.
Who exactly are you and I sacrificing our lives for?
Do not speculate wildly.
Rebels infiltrated Linggu Temple.
Such an absurd thing,
do you believe it?
I'd rather believe
that the Snow Woman Dou E has appeared,
and Li Chenyang learned sorcery.
I heard that those who died at Linggu Temple
were all Eastern Depot sleeper agents.
The Western Depot suffered again.
Let me tell you,
tonight, many high officials and nobles
in luxury carriages
went towards the palace.
Is something big going to happen?
I heard it is to pay respects
at the prayer lantern festival held by Master Konghui.
Inviting
officials of the fourth rank and above with their families.
Consort Wan is hosting it personally.
My Lord.
Remember what I instructed.
When the palace lantern rises, all is well.
Lord Pei, Lord Zhang.
Excuse me.
For today's prayer lantern festival in the palace,
no one is allowed to carry weapons into the palace.
Accompanying guards and coachmen
must wait outside the palace.
Very well.
You return to the Grand Court of Justice first.
No need to wait here.
Yes, my Lord.
No matter how audacious they are,
they wouldn't dare trespass
into the heavily guarded Inner Court.
If you intend to shield them,
you should see the situation clearly tonight.
The one from the Western Depot
is bound to make a move tonight.
If Zhang Yi brings Tang Xi into the palace,
wouldn't it be a desperate struggle?
Embroidered Uniform Guard, listen up.
Here.
Strictly check the identities of maids and eunuchs at the lantern festival.
Prevent Tang Xi and his kind from sneaking in.
If discovered,
bring them to me immediately.
Yes, sir.
Rather than falling into the Western Depot's hands,
it is better to strike first.
Zhang Yi, do not do anything foolish.
Shuimo, Danqing.
Why have you returned?
Shouldn't you be at the palace gate
waiting for Lord Pei and Vice Minister Zhang?
Our master
never cares for such tedious formalities.
Wait until the prayer lanterns
rise within the palace tonight.
Danqing.
There are still many files to organize.
Shuimo, wait for me.
You talk too much.
Only by acting as usual will no suspicion arise.
Reporting, my lord.
We have safely escorted Vice Minister Zhang
into the palace for the lantern festival.
From here on,
it all depends on
the two of them and their fate.
If you ask me,
Lord Zhang this time is like
Wu Dalang marrying a wife in *Water Margin*.
What does that mean?
It bodes ill rather than well.
I told you to read *Water Margin*.
You only read useless things.
That storyteller stuff...
Gu Gong Dan Fu,
came galloping at dawn,
along the western riverbanks,
arriving at the foot of Mount Qi.
What I can do for Zhang Yi
ends here.
I hope the prayer lanterns in the palace tonight
rise as usual.
You infiltrate the Inner Palace.
You must be extra careful.
Find them
and regroup as soon as possible.
I await your good news.
Do not be impatient.
Your Highness.
Consort Wan.
Consort Xian is here to pay her respects.
No one stays in favor forever,
just as no flower blooms for a hundred days.
She certainly chooses to come
when one is out of favor and luck.
Consort Xian pays her respects to the Noble Consort.
May the Noble Consort enjoy ten thousand blessings.
You are usually busy attending to the Empress, Sister.
How did you find time today?
To come to my palace...
...and visit this old woman?
Perhaps...
...you have run into some trouble?
You jest, Sister.
The difficulties I encounter...
...are but a lonely courtyard where spring fades late.
Over the years, I have grown accustomed to it.
Unlike you, Sister.
You have obtained what every woman...
...in this world desires most.
It is truly enviable.
It is rare indeed...
...to hear you speak such dispirited words.
They are clearly the honest truth.
At my age...
...to still hope for a child...
...is the true joke of the palace.
Bring it here.
His Majesty specially ordered the Sewing Bureau...
...to tailor a ritual prayer dress for you, Sister.
The Empress has already inspected it...
...and specially ordered me to deliver it...
...and assist you in dressing up.
Insolence!
How does the Sewing Bureau conduct its business?
Do they think this phoenix pattern...
...is something I am permitted to wear?
Please quell your anger, Noble Consort.
The pattern on this dress was drawn by His Majesty himself.
The Sewing Bureau worked seven nights to rush it.
It was not us acting on our own authority.
Otherwise, it would not have been sent to the Empress...
...for review before being brought here.
The moon on the sea is the moon in the sky.
The one before your eyes is the one in his heart.
Most women in the harem lose favor as beauty fades.
Their honor and disgrace are tied to their family's favor.
You, Sister, are like a phoenix spreading its wings.
You have held favor in the harem for over eighteen years.
Now you even have the Little Prince by your side.
Do you still not understand...
...the weight you hold in His Majesty's heart?
So what if I understand?
Nowadays...
...no matter how much I dress up...
...I cannot withstand the ravages of time.
All women in the world desire quiet and peaceful years...
...and to halt the fleeting prime of youth.
But a woman's life...
...is like a spring flower budding...
...blooming with the brilliance of summer flowers...
...mature and bright like autumn leaves...
...and pure and imposing like winter snow.
Everything one experiences...
...is a gift.
Compared to the newcomers in the palace...
...amidst their natural charm...
...you possess more steadiness and dignity.
Rather than worrying about a fading reflection...
...it is better to ensure one does not lose one's heart.
Thank you for your trouble today, Sister.
Then I shall go report back to the Empress.
May the Noble Consort's prayers today...
...go smoothly.
Did you get the key?
I got it.
Halt, you servants ahead!
The Prayer Lantern Festival is about to begin.
We are strictly checking everyone's identity.
Reporting to my lord...
I...
How dare you!
You dare to stop Consort Xian?
You mindless fools!
The Prayer Lantern Festival is about to begin.
Consort Xian...
...must accompany the Empress's carriage.
If the hour is missed...
...and blame is assigned...
...how many heads do you have to lose?
The Eunuch is right to remind us.
We were rash.
Please forgive us, Consort Xian.
Consort Xian...
Please.
Greetings, Superintendent of the Eastern Depot.
Deputy Commander of the Embroidered Uniform Guard.
I wonder why your Excellencies have visited the Grand Court of Justice.
What business brings you here?
We received information.
Suspecting that Minister Pei Yuandong of the Grand Court...
...and Lord Zhang Yi...
...will be harmed by villains.
So we came specifically to investigate.
Superintendent, you worry too much.
Lord Pei and Lord Zhang...
...were personally escorted by us into the palace...
...to attend Consort Wan's prayer lantern festival.
How could they be harmed at the Grand Court?
Ignorant fool.
A mere Grand Court of Justice...
...what right does it have to question our words?
Men!
Search the Grand Court from top to bottom.
Leave no stone unturned.
The Li Chenyang case is settled.
Vice Minister Zhang contributed greatly and was rewarded by His Majesty.
You look radiant right now.
Doesn't it feel like spring is in the air?
Could it be that good things are happening one after another?
Is there some good news you want to announce to us?
Minister Wang, you are teasing me.
That the Grand Court could solve the case and escape trouble...
...is already a great fortune.
If...
...Li Chenyang had been handled by the Ministry of Justice...
Minister Wang...
...you might not have fared any better than I did.
Lord Zhang.
Now you are making things up out of nothing.
That Li Chenyang...
...was supposed to be the Grand Court's responsibility.
What does it have to do with us?
Minister Yuan.
You be the judge.
It is quite good.
No...
What kind of talk is that?
Minister Wang.
The dust has settled on this matter.
The outcome was decided by His Majesty.
Naturally, it is exceptionally good.
It seems Minister Yuan...
...is truly an expert at judging matters.
No wonder your family is harmonious.
With a kind mother and filial son.
You are envious?
Then go ahead.
My Yuan Ling is not yet married.
If Minister Wang shows such favor...
...it is us who are unworthy of the honor.
Greetings, Eunuch Lord Shang.
Everyone, no need for formalities.
Continue, please continue.
Vice Minister Zhang.
I just looked around.
I did not see Minister Pei of the Grand Court.
I wonder where Lord Pei has gone.
When Lord Pei first arrived...
...he suddenly felt unwell.
At this moment...
...he is likely relieving himself.
Vice Minister Zhang.
Nature calls.
If it is urgent...
...how can he be so slow?
I was merely delayed by something.
Arriving late.
Stop talking nonsense here.
And demeaning yourself.
My Lord.
Lord Pei.
What was it that delayed you?
I went across to check on my second wife.
It is my wife's first time attending a palace banquet.
She is inevitably a bit nervous.
I just went to give her a few words of advice.
To avoid any mistakes.
I see, I see.
Everyone, please continue.
I miscalculated.
I didn't expect Zhang Yi to do the exact opposite.
Letting them so boldly impersonate
the families of court officials to sneak into the palace.
Exposing them now
would undoubtedly be letting them walk right into
the Western Depot's dragnet.
Lord Zhang.
I certainly don't recall
that Lord Pei's second wife
is Yuan Ran.
She is as of today.
In that case,
Tang Xi has also snuck in among the female relatives.
What do you mean "snuck in"?
Those over there are all
respectable female relatives.
Watch your mouth.
For what purpose
do you risk your lives to sneak into the palace?
Naturally, to pray for the common people.
Wishing for peace and prosperity.
This lady looks unfamiliar.
May I ask which official's family you belong to?
It is Lord Pei Yuandong's family.
His newly wedded second wife.
Ah, Lord Pei.
Lord Pei certainly has it tough.
I have it tough too.
Lady Pei, please wait a moment longer.
Once the prayer ceremony ends,
we can leave the palace.
Thank you, Auntie.
Consort Wan arrives!
Your Highness, long live, long live, long live!
Consort Wan has changed her attire.
She must have discovered the key is lost.
If I am not mistaken,
the master of ceremonies leading the team
appears to be Eunuch Lord Wang of the Western Depot.
Have you gentlemen received
His Majesty's edict pardoning Eunuch Lord Wang?
That depends on the Emperor's will.
After all, Eunuch Lord Wang is not under our jurisdiction.
My lords,
as the Prayer Lantern Festival begins,
in Consort Wan's palace,
an item gifted by His Majesty has gone missing.
This is a grave matter.
To avoid damaging your reputations,
we will now conduct a full search.
My lord, pardon the offense.
Pardon the offense, my lord.
Routine procedure.
Lord Wang, pardon the offense.
Pardon the offense, Madam.
Forgive me, my lord.
Pardon me.
My lord.
Pardon me, Madam.
Reporting, my lord.
We found nothing.
Your Highness,
the female guests do not have your key.
After we successfully take the key from Consort Wan,
Consort Wan will surely discover it is missing.
Then the entire palace will be on lockdown.
How will we evade the search
and leave the palace?
Disguise.
No one is more skilled at
misdirection and substitution than you.
Consort Wan wears the key on her person,
which means it is an exquisitely made key.
Once we have the key,
we must quickly disguise its appearance
to become the most common,
most easily overlooked item at the festival.
I understand.
That night, all the female guests will wear hairpins.
We'll turn the key into a hairpin.
I feel that is not safe enough.
If they suspect our identities are fake,
they will definitely search thoroughly.
Each of us, along with Yuan Ran and Wu Qiangu,
must learn how to move the key
quickly among
every female guest at the scene.
As long as, when we finally leave,
it returns to us, that will suffice.
Eunuch Lord Shang.
Your Highness.
Do you think I am here,
over some dispensable item,
troubling the entire court
just to put on a show?
Guards!
Bring Lord Pei Yuandong of the Grand Court of Justice
up here.
Embroidered Uniform Guard Deputy Commander Yin Feng
greets Your Highness.
We received reliable intelligence
that Minister Pei Yuandong of the Grand Court
might be harmed before tonight's lantern festival.
So we rushed to the Grand Court
to investigate.
We happened to save the unconscious Lord Pei.
Commander Shen,
why do you not immediately arrest
this villain posing as Lord Pei?
Master Shen
Which side is your heart on?
Have you thought it through?
You dare bewitch minds at death's door?
Commander Shen
Do I really have to teach you
how to interrogate this villain?
Your subordinate dares not.
Wu Qiangu
Why did you disguise yourself as a high official to enter the palace?
You...
what exactly is your intention?
I heard that tonight,
the Prayer Lantern Festival
is being personally organized by Consort Wan.
I have long wanted to witness
the grace of Her Highness the Consort.
I didn't expect
to run into the palace guards hunting a thief.
The Embroidered Uniform Guard...
when did they become so soft-hearted,
allowing someone to be this arrogant?
Or is it your lack of discipline?
Speak!
Why did you specifically choose
to impersonate Master Pei Yuandong?
Speak!
Why did you specifically choose
to impersonate Master Pei Yuandong?
Among those near me of similar age,
there was only Master Pei.
I actually wanted to copy you, Eunuch Lord Shang,
to copy Eunuch Lord Shang's appearance,
but I'd need the opportunity.
What a loose tongue,
you insubordinate rebel!
If you don't confess who the mastermind is,
I will have you executed immediately
to set an example for all.
Superintendent Wang,
leave such a small matter to me,
so you don't dirty your hands.
Leave it to you?
What?
Do you want to make your Godfather
lose face again?
There is only one chance.
If you can't grasp it, it won't belong to you.
I overstepped my bounds.
Will you speak or not?
Will you speak?
Will you speak?!
Going out now is suicide.
If you get caught in this palace,
the entire Tang Clan will be implicated.
I can't just watch the weird old man...
If you and Zhang Yi jump out now,
everything we've done will fall short.
You will destroy the entire Tang Clan,
and he will destroy the entire Grand Court of Justice.
Eunuch Lord Wang
Although I was saved by the Eastern Depot and Embroidered Uniform Guard,
as the Chief Minister of the Grand Court of Justice,
the laws of the Great Ming...
are still fresh in my mind.
Impersonating a high court official,
claiming office without holding one,
for personal gain,
and assuming an official's name...
One hundred strokes and three years of penal servitude.
Yet you executing someone without authorization...
which article of the Great Ming Law is that based on?
Lord Pei, do you wish to shield this person?
I am merely speaking according to the facts.
I was unconscious when I was rescued.
Everyone knows that.
Very well.
One hundred strokes.
Changed to one hundred lashes.
If Wang Zhi intends to whip Wu Qiangu,
after these one hundred lashes,
death is certain.
Eunuch Lord Wang.
This old man believes...
today is the seventh day since Master Konghui's passing.
Buddhism forbids killing and slaughter.
On a day like this,
to insist on causing a bloodbath...
would affect the nation's fortune in the future,
and no one can bear that responsibility.
Consort Wan.
This absolutely must not happen.
If any misfortune occurs later,
how will Your Highness face His Majesty
and explain today's events?
Please reconsider, Your Highness.
Enough.
The prayer lantern festival will continue.
But thieves have infiltrated the palace,
and this matter involves the Grand Court of Justice.
Detain the families of the Grand Court officials for now,
to prevent further trouble.
Please.
Lord Zhang.
Until the key is found,
no one is allowed to leave.
If there is any suspicious movement,
kill without mercy.
Instead of saying these things,
you'd be better off warning
your godson, who isn't very sharp today.
Drag him away.
Girl.
Run!
I was born free.
And death...
must also be decided by myself.
See you in the martial world.
Or never see you again.
You want to see...
what kind of illusion magic scenery?
Compared to landscapes, flowers, and birds,
I'd rather see the desert scenery of the Western Regions.
But your illusion magic is all fake.
In the end, I have to imagine it myself.
Might as well go see it myself.
Who says my illusion magic is fake?
Falsehood and truth,
real and fake intermingled.
If...
I let you see right here in the capital
the scenery of the great desert,
how do you plan to reward me?
What are you looking at?
The night before last was a mistake.
A beautiful mistake.
What do you want?
What do I want?
I want...
you all to embrace the freedom of this world,
feel love,
and enjoy the life of ordinary people.
My brother-in-law told me these words.
And then?
He died.
It seems everything went smoothly.
Your Highness.
Let's go.
Who are you?
I am Wan Zhen'er.
Nonsense.
How dare you impersonate me?
In the entire Ming Dynasty,
no one would dare do such a thing.
Look at you now,
looking like neither human nor ghost.
How are you worthy of the name Wan Zhen'er?
Your virtue does not match your status.
Disaster will surely follow.
Insolence!
You lowly maid!
How dare you slander me like this!
Though I started as a palace maid,
I have served since childhood
by the side of Empress Dowager Sun.
At nineteen, I cared for His Majesty when he was two.
I shared the wealth when he was Crown Prince,
and I endured with him
the hardships when he was demoted to Prince of Yi.
He respects me,
pities me,
and protects me.
Have I not treated him the same?
But you,
blinded by the lust for power,
plotted to let villains take his life,
harm his empire,
and harm his heirs.
Can you face His Majesty after that?
Consort Wan!
Cover your mouth and nose, quickly!
Be careful not to inhale the Illusion Magic potion.
Consort Wan!
Wang Zhi!
Tell me,
did you do all of this today?
Why was there an explosion?
You organized this lantern festival single-handedly.
I never authorized the Western Depot to buy saltpeter.
Where did this saltpeter come from?
Your Highness,
this has nothing to do with me.
Do not trust that sorcerer's nonsense.
Seize Wang Zhi!
Your Highness!
Superintendent Wang,
forgive me.
After all, this is Consort Wan's order.
I believe His Majesty
will soon arrive with the Imperial Guard
and the Embroidered Uniform Guard.
Everyone, stay calm.
Zhang Yi,
they have already escaped.
Commander Shen,
go catch the escaped criminals at once!
Commander Yuan,
follow me out of the city to arrest Tang Xi and the others.
Yes, sir.
It looks like we're going to die here today.
Tang Xi,
your martial arts are the best.
If there is a chance,
Don't worry.
You'll live longer than me.
They have us outnumbered.
We cannot fight for long.
Find a way to open the palace gates
and regroup with Lu Shijie.
You handle Shen Youzhi and his men.
Beauty, you handle those ninjas.
I'll go open the palace gates.
Once the gates are open,
focus on escaping.
Do not linger in battle.
Okay.
Split up!
I am Fujii Musashi, the greatest swordsman of the East
Today, commissioned by the Western Depot
I come to take your heads
What a coincidence
The last person who dared call himself the greatest swordsman
...was buried just a few days ago
Even Japanese pirates must follow local customs
Vice Minister Zhang
Just now, Wu Qiangu
...was executed on the spot
You were coerced by bandits
...to flee to the palace gates
You need not worry anymore
Who said I was coerced?
Zhang Yi
It's not too late to turn back now
Hand over what you took
Or no one leaves here today
You must know
...you are different from them
How am I different?
We are all doing the same thing
Here's a blade for you
For the sake of us once serving as officials together
...show some mercy
Stop chasing
Go
It's useless
You shouldn't have come in tonight
I felt like it
Is it worth risking your lives like this?
At such a young age
...you've learned to hesitate before even fighting
To die without fighting
...is so boring
Only by keeping on fighting
...can one avoid defeat
Even if I die
...I won't regret it
How are you doing?
Cut the crap
Qian Ben is here to help us
You two hold him off first
We'll go open the palace gates
Okay
Go help them, quick
Leave this to me
Qian Ben
Why?
Qian Ben!
Tang Xi, catch this
Why?
Why did you do this?
Qian Ben!
Today
...the rules of the martial world
...repay kindness with kindness
...and hatred with vengeance
It doesn't end until death
Enough!
Let's see who dares take a step forward!
In my imperial palace
...Japanese ninjas have appeared
Anyone who does not kill the foreign enemy
...but kills my Ming children instead
...shall be deemed a traitor
Kill without mercy!
Shen Youzhi!
Even at the end, you are cowardly
What is the point of living?
Everyone, listen to my order!
When we arrived
...Tang Xi and the others had already killed the Japanese thieves
...and escaped through the palace gate
Is that clear?
Why aren't you leaving yet?
Don't come back
Go
Where are Zhang Yi and Tang Xi?
Womanly benevolence
Superfluous emotions
...will all become
...stumbling blocks on your path to the peak of power
I...
...when have I ever disappointed you?
Quick, quick, quick!
Move it!
Quick!
Yuan Ran
Why are there only three of you?
Where is Old Wu?