Look at yourself.
What did you play at the concert?
Secretly changing the piece is one thing,
but getting drunk and causing a scene at Jiang Bohan's house?
Don't you think you've embarrassed yourself enough?
Yao won't be going to school today.
You don't need to take her.
Let her stay home and reflect on her actions.
Who let you in?
Get out!
Does your head still hurt?
It's none of your business.
I bought your favorite rock sugar bird's nest.
Remember to drink it.
Yan Zhengwen.
I'm not leaving.
Please don't be with Yu Mingxi, okay?
Can you please not be with Yu Mingxi?
I'm hungry.
Let's eat.
Look what I bought for you.
Drink it while it's hot.
When I got drunk last night,
did I say anything?
What did you say?
I didn't say anything?
No.
You drank too much yesterday.
You slept
very quietly
and so soundly.
And I didn't cry too?
You...
didn't cry.
My mom said I cried the whole time,
screaming like a lunatic.
Is that so?
I had no idea.
Give me your phone.
Why?
To see if you took any ugly photos of me.
In my heart, you're never ugly.
What's the point of that?
Next time you want to drink, call me.
I'll keep you company.
Yan Zhengwen,
can you do something for me?
Sure.
[Close to You]
[Episode 7 Yu Mingxi, I like you.]
Jiang Bohan.
Why do you keep following me?
I'm going the same way.
I'm going to the convenience store.
I'm also going to the convenience store.
I'm going to work.
I'm going shopping.
Whatever.
Customer.
Family member.
Yu Mingxi,
are you an ostrich or just stupid?
Why are you so persistent?
It's my business that I like you.
Yu Mingxi, why are you hiding there?
What are you hiding from?
We have a witness here.
Yu Mingxi, I like you.
Manager,
don't listen to his nonsense.
You're crazy.
Do you like me or not?
♪ You are summer ♪
Of course I don't like you.
♪ And I am the breeze ♪
♪ Blowing in from the sea ♪
♪ Only then do I understand ♪
♪ Why love always leaves us not knowing ♪
Is your hand okay?
It hurts a bit.
♪ What to do ♪
So, does that mean you have to take responsibility?
Excuse me,
I don't really want to disturb you.
There are cameras here.
Alright.
Go on.
Manager,
can I take an hour off to have a meal?
Approved.
Let's go.
Dating is important.
Manager!
Go.
I...
Jiang Bohan,
can you please
stop joking around?
My heart can't take it anymore.
You're falling for me?
No, I'm not.
I have a heart of stone.
You're so young.
Have you been through some rough times?
Why aren't you eating?
Why do you always like to eat
these junk food?
How are these junk food?
I even ordered some vegetables.
High in salt,
high in sugar,
high in fat.
How are these not junk food?
But it's really delicious.
Try it.
Come on, just try it.
Really, have a taste.
How is it?
Isn't it delicious?
It's alright.
How can that be?
This is the best street food
within a two-kilometer radius.
I don't usually treat people,
but this whole table of food only costs 30 yuan.
It's economical and delicious.
You're quite easy to buy off then.
But why did you transfer schools?
Did you make some mistake at your previous school?
Of course not.
My dad
used to be the swimming coach at Jingcai College.
To honor his act of bravery, the school
made an exception to admit me.
They even waived my tuition fees.
So that's why I came here.
Then why are you still working at a convenience store?
It's because
there are always school activities,
and my mom alone can't afford to support me.
So I have to work part-time while studying.
But it's okay, I have a lot of free time,
so I can still make money.
Is that discount at your convenience store still valid?
Yes, it is.
You saw it?
Like I said, persistence pays off.
What you did is called...
relentless pursuit.
Me?
What you did at the convenience store today was...
What did I do?
What you did is called pestering.
Where are you going?
Pestering.
Is this what you meant by
buying a little?
Nothing here is on sale.
What are you doing?
I...
You're buying so much.
Can you finish all of this?
Don't waste it.
You focus on your work.
I'm leaving first.
Your things.
I bought them for you.
Eat more if you like it.
This is enough for me.
♪ You are summer ♪
♪ And I am the breeze ♪
♪ Blowing in from the sea ♪
♪ I don't understand ♪
♪ Why love always leaves us not knowing ♪
Young people these days
are really impressive.
♪ What to do ♪
Stop it.
There's nothing between us.
I believe that you have nothing,
but he does.
What's all these?
What is it?
This is love.
Full of love.
Can't you see?
Manager.
Stop looking.
Hurry and take it home.
Okay.
You got away with it last time.
You think you can run away this time?
Jiang Bohan.
What are you guys doing?
Just chatting with some friends.
It's none of your business. Go.
What a coincidence.
I was just looking for your little girlfriend.
Me?
Yes,
you.
What are you doing?
Are you going to fight again?
I'm calling the police.
What do you want with her?
Why are you so nervous?
Just want to talk to her.
Yu Mingxi,
I
have been good friends with Yan Zhengwen for many years.
Today we're just catching up.
Nothing else.
You should go now.
Alright.
Why aren't you leaving?
Really?
Go back quickly.
I'll be going then.
Have fun.
Take care.
Never mind.
What's wrong with Jiang Bohan?
He's nice one moment and bad the next.
Why is he hanging out with that thug again?
No,
something's not right.
[Close to You]