Stop looking for that guy.
I’m the one who is keeping her.
Yu Mingxi, go out first.
Jiang Bohan, watch your mouth.
This is my car.
I think you know it.
I've been tutoring her recently.
She needs a scholarship.
She needs to take the midterm exam.
First, you threatened her to drop out with her grades.
Then, you didn't allow her to take the exam.
Is this your plan?
Are you done?
I didn't force her to drop out.
With her grades,
she cannot adapt to studying in an international school.
She can't get an offer.
when she graduates.
Returning to the original school
is a better choice for her.
It's not because of her bad grades
but because of her family.
She is under too much pressure.
Her dad...
Her mom is always away.
She has to be her own parents.
As a teacher,
have you ever cared about her?
I'm concerned about her now.
Then why did you suspend her class?
Do you think I can solve
every problem in the school easily?
I have to explain to the parents
and even the school board.
Jiang Bohan,
can you consider yourself
and your future first?
Don't waste your time on a girl,
which will affect your future
and delay your studying abroad.
Don't you know why I'm not going abroad?
Don't pretend that nothing happened.
Don't think you're irresponsible.
[Close to You]
[Episode 12 Corn, how have you been?]
Mingxi,
you did nothing wrong.
Why aren't you allowed to attend class?
The school officers said they should follow the procedures.
This is bullying.
When did Jingcai College have such procedures?
Students are suspended from classes
because of some rumors, huh?
I'll go to the Headmaster.
Alright.
Forget it.
That's it.
I will take it as a rest at home for a few days.
But you are wronged.
It's okay.
Go back now.
Remember to take notes for me.
I'll tell you what happens at school.
Bye.
She needs to take the midterm exam.
She needs a scholarship.
Do you know how important this scholarship is to her?
Hello.
Do you want a haircut or a style?
Okay.
This way, please.
Hello.
Are you sure you want to sell your hair?
Cut it short here?
It's 1,200 yuan in total.
The staff at the reception will transfer the money to you later.
Hello, Mom.
Baby,
how is your school life?
I got
a scholarship of
1,200 yuan.
You don't have to give me this month's living expenses.
Really?
My daughter is excellent.
Mom,
when will you come back?
I'll treat you to something nice.
You don't even want to buy yourself delicious food.
I'll treat you this time.
I've been busy in the factory lately.
I'll be available after we finish this order.
Let's celebrate
after I go back home.
Mom,
I miss you.
I miss you too.
Take care of yourself.
Have your meals on time.
I have to go.
Bye.
Where is he?
He escaped.
Go after him!
Don't let him go.
Why did You Jingchu run so fast?
Hello.
How can I help you?
Corn?
It's me,
You Jingchu.
You Jingchu?
You are grown up now and so tall.
You're only two months older than me.
Why haven't you grown taller?
I want to know why, too.
Who are you?
Who is he?
What's your relationship?
This is my
classmate.
This is my...
We bathed together when we were young.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I'm not talking nonsense.
I have a photo.
Okay.
Stop. Stop.
No need.
By the way,
why did those people go after you?
They...
They failed to defeat me.
So, they want revenge.
It seems
you are quite naughty.
You...
You are her classmate, right?
You're already wet.
It is too crowded.
Go out.
Aren't you wet, too?
Why do you need an umbrella?
I'm going home with Corn.
Your home isn't in this direction.
What do you want to do?
Who said you can go home together?
No.
Why can't we go home together?
Give it to me.
No.
Get out!
You go out. We'll go back together.
Alright.
Stop fighting.
It seems
the rain stopped.
Since the rain has stopped,
let's go home together.
Why?
Good.
You're so chubby now.
Are you done?
There are three of you today.
So many people.
You two go first.
Who are you?
None of your business.
Get lost!
Watch your back!
Help!
Let me beat them.
Alright.
Let's go.
My bag.
Come in.
No need to change your shoes.
My clothes are wet.
I'll get changed first.
This is the school uniform you left here last time.
I washed it for you.
Thanks.
You Jingchu,
can't you wait until I get in to change your clothes?
What?
You saw my body before.
What nonsense are you talking about?
When we took a shower together in our childhood...
You Jingchu!
By the way,
did you two get hurt just now?
I'm fine. Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Who are you?
Mom,
you're back.
They are my friends.
They will leave soon.
-Hello, aunt.
Watch your mouth.
Let your friends sit down.
Aunt,
don't you remember me?
I'm Jingchu.
Jingchu.
I haven't seen you for so many years.
You're so strong.
I've been well.
Let me help you carry these things.
Okay.
By the way, Mom,
he's my classmate,
Jiang Bohan.
Hello, aunt.
Hello.
Look,
before school started, I was worried that you couldn't fit in.
Now I feel relieved
after seeing you get along with your classmates.
We're getting along well.
I wanted to come back early to cook for you
to surprise you.
Why are you back so early today?
Didn't you go to school?
I...
Yes.
Why are you back so early today?
There's an event at school today.
The school is over early.
I'll wash the fruits for you.
Did you skip class?
You haven't changed your childhood habit.
Let me help you.
Have a seat.
Who's calling?
Why don't you answer it?
Nothing.
What is it?
Where are you?
Are you with Yu Mingxi again?
I'm at her house now.
Come back quickly.
I need to talk to you.
Why can't you tell me on the phone?
Come back quickly.
What happened?
Who is it?
My mom.
Then you should leave now.
She must have something to do with you.
Nothing.
Come on.
Have some pears.
Mom,
Jiang Bohan has something to do.
He has to leave.
I'll visit you another day.
You're going to leave?
Why don't you stay here a bit longer?
No.
His mother wants to see him.
Bye.
Goodbye, aunt.
Take care.
Why aren't you leaving?
I just came here.
I have a lot to say to aunt.
Okay.
Then, talk to aunt.
Yu Mingxi, see me off.
I’ll see him off.
Okay.
Your coat.
You are really a young master.
You even need me to send you downstairs.
Jiang Bohan, what are you doing?
Why did you suddenly stop?
I'll help you
with the suspension.
I don't know
how to comfort others.
If you feel wronged,
you can bite me, too.
Are you crazy?
I'm not a dog.
Why should I bite you?
One more thing.
What's your relationship with that guy?
You mean You Jingchu?
We grew up together.
I treat him as my younger brother.
Really?
Tell him to go home as soon as possible.
Do not let him stay at your house.
Let's go.
Don't worry about the suspension.
I’m here.
Mingxi was immature back then.
She bullied you a lot.
Yes.
Look at the mark she just bit.
It's still here.
She bit you again?
Yes.
You should scold her.
She can't always bully me.
-I will scold her.
-We have grown up.
Mingxi,
Jingchu just came here.
You need to
take care of him.
Okay.
Aunt,
I
just enrolled in a sports school.
I'm not familiar with this place.
I came to you before informing you.
Sorry for causing you trouble.
Jingchu, you're too courteous.
Your father and Mingxi's father
were like brothers.
Though they died,
we have to rely on each other, right?
Maybe they are shooting the breeze in heaven.
We should live a good life.
By the way,
what did you say you majored in?
Boxing.
Boxing?
Is it dangerous?
Is it easy to get hurt?
It's okay, aunt.
I am professional.
I will protect myself.
I’m relieved.
With you at home with Mingxi,
I feel relieved
when I'm away.
But you have to sleep on the sofa.
It's okay.
It's a small house. Let's squeeze in it.
We're close,
right?
Wait, Mom,
you let him live in our house?
[Close to You]