Congratulations to the Jingcai basketball team
[Jingcai College]
on winning last week's
basketball game!
Next,
let's take a look back at
the basketball team's
excellent performance in this match.
Applause!
What's going on?
Is that Jiang Bohan?
Who did this?
Come over here, quickly!
Here he comes!
Jiang Bohan is here!
Turn it off!
Turn it off now!
Where are you going?
What?
Come with me.
Why is it her?
Like a toad dreaming of dating a swan.
She should look in the mirror.
Why does she think she can like Jiang Bohan?
First of all,
I don't know who
was so bored
to make a poster
and paste it everywhere.
But to be fair, the poster looks good.
Remember to smooth my skin next time.
Secondly,
I hope everyone will gossip less
and study more.
Otherwise, you'll be looked down upon like me,
and become the target of rumors.
Lastly,
I despise people who scheme behind others' backs.
You all want to know who wrote the love letter, right?
That's right,
it was...
What are you doing?
First of all,
today is indeed a pretty good day.
Yu Mingxi is right,
the poster looks good.
Keep up the good work.
To be honest,
I've always hated strawberry flavor.
But,
starting from today,
I like it.
Give her a kiss!
Kiss...
Was I out of my mind?
Not at all.
I think you were pretty cool.
What am I going to do
at school from now on?
Don't worry.
If the sky falls...
You'll hold it up, right?
[Close to You]
[Episode 4: If the Sky Falls, I'll Hold It Up for You]
[Headmaster's Office]
You'll hold it up.
Can you really hold it up?
If not me, then who? You?
Easy for you to say.
Come in.
You're Yu Mingxi, right?
Your grades were quite good at your previous school.
How come you're now at the bottom, even in basic bilingual classes?
Especially Academic English.
You haven't met the language requirements for the international 2+2 program.
Even if you score A in all your major courses, it won't matter.
I'm sorry, Headmaster.
I will work hard on my English.
Or is it that
your mind
hasn't been on your studies at all
and that you've been too busy writing love letters,
confessing your feelings?
Is that it?
That's not true, Headmaster.
That was truly a misunderstanding.
We at Jingcai College made an exception
to reduce your tuition fees
out of respect for your father
and allowed you to transfer here.
It's one thing if you don't put in effort yourself,
but don't affect other students.
I'm sorry, Headmaster.
I will definitely study hard from now on.
This time,
can we not let it affect
my scholarship application?
For your situation,
although you meet the application criteria for the scholarship,
it's awarded to students
who excel in both character and academics.
With your current grades,
whether you can even stay on is already in question,
let alone a scholarship.
For the upcoming GPA rankings,
if there's no improvement,
please return to your old college.
Yes, Headmaster.
This time, we'll consider it misconduct.
Just write a reflection.
We won’t pursue anything further.
Thank you, Headmaster.
Are you finished?
What are you doing?
You don't need to beat around the bush.
The student you mentioned
who was affected by her,
was me, right?
May I ask which of my grades she has affected?
If one day
I fall to second place in the school,
then you can come and condemn me.
Yu Mingxi
wrote a love letter
and that's misconduct?
Our school's moral standards
are too outdated, aren't they?
Jiang Bohan,
you're getting more and more out of line.
Can't help it,
I was raised well.
Well,
why don't you invite my father here
to lecture me as well?
What do you think?
Mom.
Mom?
Get out.
Both of you, get out!
Wait.
Stay behind after school.
Remove every love letter
stuck on the wall before you leave.
Why don't you punish
the person who put the love letters up?
You two were directly involved in the incident.
Is it wrong to punish you?
What incident exactly?
Writing love letters or defacing property?
Neither.
Jiang Bohan,
now is not the time for you to be in a relationship.
Fine.
Well, since
you've already defined our relationship,
I'll
respectfully obey.
I'm leaving.
Headmaster,
I...
Yu Mingxi,
I'm telling you very seriously,
if you don't want to be expelled,
you must strictly follow
Jingcai College's rules and regulations.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
Given your family situation,
regarding the scholarship,
I will give it extra consideration.
You can go now.
Thank you, Headmaster.
Let's go.
Manager,
I'm sorry,
I need someone to cover my shift tonight.
Yes.
It's the
super cute girl
called Wang Chunian.
Okay.
Thank you, Manager.
Jiang Bohan, why are you still sitting around?
If you don’t start cleaning, it’ll be dark soon.
Yu Mingxi.
Do you know how much tuition is per year?
Of course I know.
We didn't pay all that money
to come and clean.
You think I want to do this?
So, how exactly did you
get exceptional admission?
Because of my father.
It's all your fault that
I'm getting punished.
So annoying.
Because of me?
Yeah.
Fine.
Give it to me.
If you don't want to do it, forget it.
I won't force you.
Give it to me.
Never mind.
Give it to me!
I'm covered in dirty water.
How fitting.
Why are you wearing the old school uniform?
You think I want to?
The new uniform costs 1,880 yuan.
It doesn't matter anyway.
The headmaster gave me an ultimatum,
to improve
my grades quickly,
or drop out.
Improving your grades isn’t that hard.
It's not that simple.
I'll teach you.
Forget it.
The headmaster said
you have more important things to do.
Besides,
even though there’s nothing going on between us,
but
to put the headmaster at ease,
I should stay away from you.
What good does
staying away from me do for you?
It doesn't do me any good.
But before I met you,
I was never insulted,
never gossiped about,
and I didn't have to deal with
all these messy situations.
I didn't mean it that way.
It's because
the headmaster has high hopes for you.
You're her only source of pride.
So,
let's keep our distance from now on.
Fine.
Let's keep our distance then.
You can go back.
You don't need to clean today.
But
if I don't finish cleaning today,
I'll be dead tomorrow.
You won't.
Remember what you said.
Keep your distance.
Your clothes.
Go!
Starting today,
you'd better keep your distance from me.
Are you done talking?
You're overthinking it.
What kind of person she is
is none of your business.
I really hate strawberry flavor.
But,
from today on,
I like it.
Why can't you hold your composure?
Mom,
what are you doing here?
I just attended the school board meeting.
I saw the concert program.
Why aren't you the finale?
Did you make a mistake during rehearsals?
When did you become so mediocre?
At the next concert,
my daughter must be the finale.
I don't want to turn up
and be mocked by other mothers.
Whether you improve your skills
or pull some strings,
use any means necessary
to achieve your goal.
I understand,
Mom.
Don't expose your emotions easily
and let others know your weaknesses.
Got it,
Mom.
Jiang Bohan.
I don’t have time to mess around with you today.
It's been so long since that incident.
Why do you still refuse to forgive me?
It has nothing to do with that incident.
Moreover,
you've crossed a line.
I crossed a line?
So you’re treating me like this
all because of that Yu Mingxi?
You asked me to stay away from you.
I agreed.
I joined the cheerleading squad to watch you from afar
and cheer you on.
But what about you?
I didn't give you space
so you could
date someone else.
Give me space?
Where do you get the confidence
to say such things?
Confidence?
We've been childhood sweethearts
and grew up together.
If anyone has the right to speak with confidence, it's me, Qin Siyao, not her!
In terms of family background,
grades,
and looks,
how am I inferior to her in any way?
I have never judged someone's worth
based on material things,
Moreover, you're too obsessive.
The things you did...
The things I did,
don't you know why I did them?
So I'm sorry
that you like me.
All you have for me is an apology?
Then what do you feel for Yu Mingxi?
None of your business.
Jiang Bohan!
If you dare to like her,
I'll never let her off!
Go ahead and try then.
[Close to You]