[English subtitles are available.]
I've Fallen for You
Episode 15
Hey, be careful.
Hey, move it to the left a little.
Move it to the left a little.
Hey, OK.
My Ling,
how do you think of it?
It is OK if it's moved to the right a little bit.
Did you hear?
My Ling asked you
to move it to the right a little bit.
To the right a little bit.
Master,
what are you doing?
Sanqi, come here. Come here.
Come on.
Come here. Come here.
Have a look.
What about this plaque?
[The First Lady of Southern City is here.]
Wow, Master.
I like the name very much.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
See?
The First Lady of Southern City is here.
Dad,
we both live in the room.
You hang the plaque
that reads "The First Lady of Southern City" here.
I'll lose face.
Don't strike in.
I haven't finished yet.
Sanqi.
Look at this.
Special Assistant of the Southern Taifu Magistrate?
Right.
I especially designed the position for you.
Later
you will wear the uniform of southern city
and assist me in solving cases
on the court.
You'll take full charge
if I am absent.
Why are you staring at me?
Please design a position for me.
You want a job as well?
What can you do?
What do you want to do?
You
just stay home
to serve both your wife and the child.
Serve the child?
Come on.
Boy,
when will you give me a grandson?
Master.
Dad,
I am the First Whirly of Southern City.
You ask me to stay home and serve both my wife and the child
while you appoint her as your special assistant.
You are shaming me.
My wife can solve cases.
So can I.
I can also
appoint you as the special assistant.
OK. OK. OK.
I think that is OK.
She solves cases
while you stamp the papers,
so Xiaoling and I can be free.
Very perfect.
I just stamp the papers?
Yes.
What else do you want to do?
My Ling.
Yes?
Time waits for no one.
Let's go for our vacation.
Let's go.
Go.
Whoops.
What a bad dad.
Let's also go.
Go.
My Ling.
Yes?
Are you tired?
I am not tired.
My Ling,
it is great.
Since we have Sanqi,
I can ask her to handle the cases
on the court,
so I can stay with you
wholeheartedly.
Yes.
Why is the lamp on in the study?
Young Master is staying up to check the files.
Li Jia,
why were you so quiet?
You scared us.
Gosh.
Did you hear
what we said just now?
No.
Hush.
Young Master doesn't allow me to make a sound.
Bye.
Gosh.
It is good for him
to have a wife.
Cuo has grown up.
and he is sensible.
He knows to work hard.
Yeah.
I'm going to make some midnight snack for him.
No, no, no.
Don't do it.
You said
that you had gone home
from 5 p.m. to 7 p.m last night,
but some said they saw
you were near the victim's house from 9 p.m. to 11 p.m.
And the victim died
from about 9 p.m. to 11 p.m.
Just confess.
Alas.
That's right.
I killed the person.
Busy?
Yes.
Come on.
Here you are.
Dad,
why do you have so many waist tags?
What is this?
Deputy Taifu Magistrate?
You don't want it?
I will take it away.
You have given it to me.
You can't take back
what you already gave.
Cuo.
You must keep
the waist tag well.
You are not a common person now.
You must be strict with your job
since you are Deputy Taifu Magistrate.
Don't disgrace me.
Don't worry.
I definitely won't
disgrace you.
Did you
figure it out?
Cuo,
I was wrong before.
I shouldn't spoil you for nothing.
I saw
you staying up to read files
last night.
I saw
you solving a case
on the court today.
Cuo,
you have grown up.
Come on.
Let me hug you.
The talent of
Whirly of Southern City has finally been found.
Dad,
you have grown up as well.
Thanks for your waist tag.
Hey.
How many people have missed since this month?
This is the sixth one.
And it is reported by Shifang Village
that four young men aged eighteen have been missing.
And two young men who have been missing
in southern city
are both about eighteen.
Yes.
The missing persons' portraits have been plastered in southern city.
It can barely fit them.
How weird it is.
A group of people disappeared suddenly.
Are they playing a hide-and-seek game?
Your Excellency,
six bodies were found on the outskirts
of the city.
The cause of death was not immediately known,
but all the hearts of the bodies
were dug out.
Digging out the hearts?
This is crazy.
Go.
Let's go back check the bodies.
Gosh.
Sanqi.
How is the case
going?
Well,
the case is said to be more and more magical.
What do they say?
They say
it is done by Heart-eating Nanny.
Heart-eating Nanny?
Who is she?
It is a legend.
It is said that Heart-eating Nanny
is a siren living near southern city.
She takes human hearts
as food
and survives by sucking human yang qi.
She hides in the wild
at daytime
and
goes to the city to kill people at night.
Right.
I heard of
Heart-eating Nanny as well,
but no one has seen her.
I don't believe there is any siren.
Well,
Sanqi.
It doesn't matter if you believe it or not,
but the ordinary people believe it.
The case has been becoming
more and more magical
and weirder.
Everyone is panic
in southern city.
Sanqi,
you take charge of the case.
You are in full charge of it.
Solve it as soon as possible.
I'm leaving.
Yes, Master.
Come and have a look.
The wounds of the bodies
could not have been done by
the siren or the beast,
because the shape of the wound is very regular
and the incision is cut once
with skilled technique.
There are no other wounds
in the bodies,
which indicates the victims did not struggle before death.
They must be killed after passing out with knockout smoke.
The murder dug out the hearts skillfully
and
he or she is good at cutting,
which means it must have been premeditated.
This is a serial murder case.
The murderer is so cruel.
If we don't catch him earlier,
he'll kill more people.
I also found these remnants of powder
in the nasal cavity of other bodies.
In my opinion,
this is the smoke
the murderer used to make the victims pass out.
I have seen it before.
I've read in books
that the smoke is called Seven-Day Drunk.
It means people may be in a coma
for seven days
after taking it.
Four very precious herbs are needed
to make this kind of knockout smoke.
We can start with pharmacies
to check
the herb purchase records of these days.
There might be some clues
and it might narrow down the range of suspects.
That is the only way.
Well, Just Face and I have checked
almost all the pharmacies in southern city,
but we got no clue.
The four herbs are extremely rare.
Now
people seldom take those herbs.
So it appears
that the herbs the murderer purchased
are not come from pharmacies.
Something happened.
Our yamen is surrounded by people.
What is wrong?
It is said that another person is missing,
so the people came to ask for an answer.
Go. Let's go to check it out.
When can you
arrest Heart-eating Nanny?
Another person disappeared today.
When will we
lead a peaceful life?
Yes. Yes.
My fellows in southern city...
You officials
don't deserve our support.
We're on tenterhooks every day.
When do you arrest the murder?
Keep quiet, everyone.
Keep quiet.
Making trouble
can't solve the problem.
The yamen will
certainly find out the murder,
OK?
We must ask for an answer.
We can't feel secure
as long as you don't arrest the murder.
Never listen to the rumor.
The murder is not Heart-eating Nanny.
It is a serial murder case.
We will try to find out the murderer.
Bullshit.
Serial murder case?
We heard that
the hearts of the victims were dug out.
It must be eaten by Heart-eating Nanny.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
I saw her before.
I got drunk
and met her
one night.
Gosh.
She
has sharp claws like those of wolf,
a full mouth of sharp teeth
as well as a long tongue.
Gosh.
I was so scared
that I was sober.
I hid behind the tree without moving.
Gosh. I…
Gosh, Master Zhao.
Please work out a way,
otherwise all people in southern city will be eaten soon.
Yes.
Give us an answer.
Be quiet.
I decide to impose a curfew
for the sake of your safety.
from tonight
I will send
some runners and soldiers
to go on patrol in the street.
You
just go back home
and close the windows
as well as the doors.
Don't peek out.
Don't go outside.
Understand?
The curfew will remain
until we arrest the murder.
That's settled.
Master Zhao, don't go.
The curfew will be imposed tonight.
Everybody must close the door
and is forbidden to go out.
The curfew will be imposed tonight.
Everybody must close the door
and is forbidden to go out.
This is the traffic center
of southern city.
Anyone who
wants to do anything
has to go through here.
I don't believe
I can't arrest the murder.
What happened?
What is the sound?
Wedding music.
Who are you?
Don't you know curfew has been imposed at night?
I am Zhao Ming.
I am the son-in-law
of Doctor Gui Jianchou of Qiandu Hall.
I will go to Qiandu Hall to hold the wedding tonight
by the order of my father-in-law.
I hope you can let us go.
You can't go even to hold the wedding.
Taifu Magistrate's order was issued today.
It is the first day for the curfew.
Do you want to go against the government?
Someone!
Your Excellency!
Arrest him.
How dare you.
Who dares?
Someone!
Arrest them all.
Stop.
Hey, stop. Stop.
Stop. Stop.
Doctor Gui,
why do you do that?
You know
what happened in southern city these days.
Why do you marry your daughter
on the first day of the curfew?
Hum.
The date and time
of my daughter's wedding
were fixed early.
No matter who comes here,
he can't stop me.
Curfew?
What is curfew?
Well,
Doctor Gui,
can you show me due respect?
Just tell me.
Will you let us go
or not?
How dare you.
Who do you think you are?
Fine.
We'll let you go.
Someone.
Let them go.
Thanks, Your Excellency.
Let them go. Let them go.
Thanks, Your Excellencies.
Go.
Dad,
you just let him go?
Who is he?
You actually
made such a concession.
Well,
Gui Jianchou is a highly skilled doctor
in southern city.
He was born into a medical family.
He is a genius doctor.
It is said that
he has the skill to bring the dead back to life,
but he is a little cranky.
The poor go to see the doctor for free
in his Qiandu Hall,
while the rich need to pay
a high price
if they go to see the doctor there.
He has a good reputation
among the people of southern city.
I also heard it.
My father turned to him for treatment,
but he was refused.
Gui Jianchou's wife
died when
giving birth to his daughter,
so he treasures
his only daughter very much.
And he is always weird.
We can't stop him
from marrying his daughter today.
Hum.
It is said that
he once cured the lord
in the capital.
We'd better not
offend
such a person.
Hum.
That's outrageous.
Calm down. Calm down.
Qiandu Hall.
Xuewei works in this medical hall.
So
there are no good people
in the medical hall.
Stop it.
Let's keep guarding.
Go. Go. Go.
Keep guarding. Keep guarding.
Get up.
We found nothing
after guarding for a night.
Well,
let's go to the yamen first.
Have we found out the murder?
Get up. We're going home.
Get up.
Great, Your Excellencies.
You are all still here.
Who are you?
I am an apprentice of Qiandu Hall.
Something happened.
Lady and Mr. Zhao
got married last night.
They both are missing
this morning.
What?
My master doesn't allow me to report to the yamen,
so I sneaked out here
to tell you.
He actually doesn't report to yamen
about his missing daughter and son-in-law.
My master is always like this.
No one can persuade him.
Go.
Let's go to Qiandu Hall to check it out.
You go.
Don't look at me.
He doesn't report it to yamen.
Go.
Well.
I'm going back to have a sleep.
It is right here.
The yamen is conducting an investigation.
Open the door.
The hall is closed today.
My master sees no visitors.
Please go back.
Xuewei,
we come here
to investigate the case of
Gui Jianchou's missing daughter and son-in-law.
Please tell him.
It is useless.
My master never likes dealing with the government.
He has his own way.
We don't need the yamen to get involved in it.
He closes the hall
just because he doesn't want to see you.
Nonsense.
He has no right to refuse
since the yamen is investigating cases.
Two persons
are missing
and their lives are uncertain.
The longer time he delays,
the more dangerous his daughter is.
Even if you damn officials all die,
my daughter wouldn't die.
Who are you?
I am Zhao Quandui's son.
My name is Zhao Cuo.
Zhao Quandui's son.
I see your pulse condition is surprising.
It is rare in the world.
Well, what do you mean by that?
It seems
my master agrees to let you deal with the case.
Come in.
Let's go.
What bad temper
of Gui Jianchou.
Gui Jianchou.
This is the room
of Lady and her husband.
Let's start.
There is no sign that the door lock was broken
and the window was opened.
And people outside couldn't come in
because it is locked from inside.
There is no sign of a fight.
Yes.
Our guards didn't hear
anything last night.
Look at this.
This incense smells really strange.
Smell it.
It seems it is the smell of herbs.
It seems white poria.
My master is good at making incense
with a mixture of exotic flowers and herbs.
He made this incense
by himself.
Our Lady had been using it since childhood.
But I've already checked the ash
and there is nothing strange.
Nothing suspicious.
I want to tell you something
about the case.
But all the people in Qiandu Hall
are my master's spies,
so I can't talk here.
How about
meeting at the pavilion tonight
where we usually went?
But
you just can go there alone.
Should we go now
since there's nothing else?
Let's go.
Why is there so much residue of herbs?
Hey, Miss.
Why is there so much residue of herbs
in the yard?
Our Lady used them.
Our Lady was always bedridden
because she was weak and sick.
Luckily her husband
guards and takes care of her
While decocting medicinal herbs.
Oh.
Zhao Ming  decoctes the medicinal herbs?
Did Zhao Ming know medicinal herbs?
Of course.
Zhao Ming ran a drugstore.
He delivered all the medicinal
materials of Qiandu Hall.
Well.
It is a pity
that the couple have been taken away
without any news.
I don't know if she can take the medicine on time.
What kind of illness does she suffer?
I don't know.
She suffers lung cancer.
The herbs residue is the secret recipe of Qiandu Hall.
You can't take it away.
Since there are no useful clues
in Qiandu Hall,
let's go back
to yesterday's intersection tonight
and keep looking.
Maybe we can meet Heart-eating Nanny.
I have an appointment tonight.
I won't go.
Who will you meet?
What do you want to do?
You won't know her even if I tell you.
For official business.
Hum.
We will know her
if you tell us.
Maybe we are old acquaintances.
Right, Bai Yifei?
Oh.
Don't pretend.
Speak.
Oh.
It turns out you have something important at hand.
Well,
just go.
I will keep guarding
alone tonight.
Bai Yifei.
Thank you for
taking care of them.
Hey, Bai Yifei.
How silly you are.
Did I do something wrong?
Nothing.
Just go.
Oh.
Hey, well,
don't you wonder what he's doing?
No.
What if he is going to meet Duan Xuewei?
Didn't you see
they were mysterious?
Never mind.
Oh, you are so generous.
Of course.
Don't you want to follow Zhao Cuo
to check whether he'll meet his ex-lover privately?
Oh.
We shouldn't care about all these about love affair
when dealing with the serious case.
Besides,
I am not stingy and sly, right?
You know me well.
You are here.
Have a seat.
You said you wanted to tell me secret information.
What is it?
Oh.
Actually I want to tell you
my master has other plans.
He said he had known who the murderer was
and he had sent the servants to search for the murderer all around the city.
Who?
My master thought that Zhao Ming took away his daughter.
Zhao Ming?
Why did he take away his wife?
That's a long story.
Zhao Ming's family is engaged in medicinal materials.
The Zhao family had always admired the reputation of Qiandu Hall
and wanted to unite by marriage,
so they could join hands in doing business.
Zhao Ming had also been assiduously pursuing Lady.
But my master thought
that he was only a vain man
so he didn't allow Lady to contact him.
However, Lady was so infatuated with him
that she insisted in marrying him.
Finally, my master asked
Zhao Ming to marry into and live in Qiandu Hall.
Zhao Ming lost face.
So my master thought that Zhao Ming took away Lady
due to a grudge.
There was such a thing.
It seems that
I need to investigate Zhao Ming completely later.
Thanks.
You are leaving?
Do you have to treat me
in this way?
Xuewei.
I have told you.
Do you still remember the pavilion?
This is where we used to play
when we were kids.
Don't you forget it?
No.
Why do you
keep away from me now?
Don't you want
to tell me anything else
except for the case?
I have told you
we can't go back
since it has been eight years.
Just because of that
stupid He Jinxin?
Can the short time
you two spend together
outweigh the long time
we spent together?
I've fallen in love with her.
I can't love anyone else.
Sorry.
Fine.
I respect your choice.
Bless you and her.
But I hope
you can often come to see me
in the future.
At least
we can be good friends, OK?
I'm leaving
if there is nothing else.
Come out.
Don't hide.
Tian Sanqi.
I mean you.
Oh, you found me.
You're awesome now.
You dare tail after me.
You heard
what I said in the pavilion.
Yes, clearly
and completely.
Well,
so I don't need to say it again.
Go. Let's go home.
If I can't get it,
nobody can get it.
Hey.
Well,
given my knowledge of Sanqi,
she must have been following Zhao Cuo.
Would she fight with Duan Xuewei?
Zhao has clearly said that
he had something serious to do before he went.
It would be so abrupt
for Sanqi to go again.
Do you really think
that Duan Xuewei has anything serious?
She's obviously acting for private gain
to rekindle her relationship with Zhao Cuo.
You are not
Miss Xuewei.
How do you know her idea?
Maybe
she really has something serious.
How can you always speak for others?
Oh.
Don't argue with me.
Well,
just keep far away from the girls
who look sweet
later,
understand?
Understand?
Ouch. Ouch.
OK. OK.
Let go. Let go.
Gosh,
how sweet you are.
It seemed Duan Xuewei's plan didn't work.
What?
Well,
someone said business was important,
but followed her lover secretly.
What did Xuewei say?
She said
Zhao Ming's family is also engaged in pharmacy.
And
Zhao Ming wanted to marry Gui Jianchou's daughter,
but Gui Jianchou didn't like Zhao Ming.
However,
Gui Jianchou's daughter fell in love with Zhao Ming.
Therefore,
Gui Jianchou's daughter is missing now.
He doubted that
Zhao Ming took away his daughter.
Let's go to search for Zhao Ming's home tomorrow.
Search quickly.
Come and see.
Is this the knockout smoke found
in the nasal cavity of the dead?
That's right.
Just Face.
Come and see.
Zhao Ming knows martial arts.
Right.
This sword doesn't look like
the one displaced in an ordinary family.
Look, the blade is chipped.
It means
the sword
is often used.
So
Zhao Ming is really the murderer.
Go to the pharmacy in Zhao's front yard.
Go.
Shopkeeper.
Wait.
Guests,
what herbs do you want?
We are not for herbs.
Show me your purchase order.
Our boss isn't here.
Is your boss Zhao Ming?
Yes.
That's him.
Well,
Taifu Magistrate Yamen is investigating a case here.
Shopkeeper, please show me the purchase order.
OK. OK.
Your Excellency, this is the receipt.
Look.
These are the four herbs used to make knockout incense.
He purchased a lot of goods
from other place.
What is up?
Is there any problem?
Shopkeeper,
can we take away the receipt?
Sure. Sure.
Is Zhao Ming really the murderer?
Since the knockout incense was found at his home,
and he also was.
good at martial arts,
so he is very likely to be the murderer.
Come on, everybody.
Tian Sanqi,
how shameless you are.
You not only scramble for my husband from me,
but also stand together
with him openly.
Do you think she is shameless?
It's you again.
Cuo.
I am He Jinxin.
Don't you know me?
She is a fake.
Shameless.
Sanqi, let's go.
Do you know who she is?
Of course we know.
She is the young lady of the Zhao family.
Who are you?
Crazy and stupid.
Hello.
I am the young lady of the Zhao family.
Hey, don't go.
Hey.
Dad,
we have found out the suspect
of the serial killing.
Oh.
Who is it?
The son-in-law of Gui Jianchou,
Zhao Ming.
We found the knockout incense of the crime
in his room.
Dad,
in order to prevent him from committing the crime again,
please send more people
to search for and arrest
Zhao Ming tonight.
OK.
I will arrange it.
Someone here.
Don't you think
you have got the clues and evidence of
the case too easily?
I always feel something's wrong.
Do you find something wrong?
Help.
Help me, Cuo.
Heart-eating Nanny is going to kill me.
What?
Cuo.
Help me.
I don't want to die.
This is Zhao Ming's handwriting.
Dad,
Zhao Ming actually acts recklessly
and audaciously.
Under officials' noses,
he even wants to kill the witness.
Arrest him quickly.
OK.
I will arrange it at once.
Polygala tenuifolia, radix pseudostellariae and white poria
are not included in making incense,
why do they appear
frequently?
Bai...
Young Master Bai.
Do you know
what these herbs are used for?
They're for curing palpitations.
Cuo,
you must protect me well.
I am young and haven't got married.
I don't want to die.
I got it.
Go to sleep.
What are you doing here?
My master said
Zhao Ming would kill someone tonight,
and sent me to catch him.
I'm here to help you.
Why isn't Bai Yifei here?
Sanqi and I are enough.
I asked Bai Yifei and He Ruoyao
to help my dad.
Just stay here.
Let me go to check.
What is wrong with me?
What is wrong with you?
You killed He Jinxin
when I was away.
This is what I see
when I come back.
My daughter,
you are so unlucky.
Your husband is robbed by her
and you were murdered by her.
Master Zhao,
please help me.
Calm down.
Stop.
No, no. Stop.
We can talk on the court later.
You were killed.