[English subtitles are available.]
I’ve Fallen For You
Episode 2
Who?
See who I am.
Sanqi,
does it hurt?
Yes.
You're good.
You actually run away from home.
Go back with me.
Go.
[Blooming flowers and full moon]
[Marriage Certificate From today, they’ll become a happy couple.]
[They will get married and reach old age together. Blooming flowers and full moon.]
[By Zhao Quandui]
Honey,
let me tell you a piece of good news.
Cuo
is getting married.
Come here.
I'm sleepy.
Let's talk tomorrow.
It's about your marriage.
I will go to He's Mansion
for marriage proposal tomorrow.
Your marriage
is settled.
I won't marry her.
I don't agree. There's no room for discussion.
Yeah, there's no room for discussion.
I just tell you about it.
You like to propose a marriage so much.
You may marry her.
Nonsense.
Son,
I raised you up
alone enduring
all kinds of hardships.
I'm afraid you'll suffer wrong,
so I don't even remarry.
It has been so hard for me.
I don't urge you to gain fame
or to be self-reliant.
I just hope
you can get married and have children.
I want you to grow up peacefully
and live a good life.
They are just small requests.
Is it so difficult?
Dad,
I know you are good to me,
and you don't want me to be motivated,
because you think
I'm good-for-nothing as other people do.
You're just improperly belittling yourself!
So just hang out with your evil associates.
If you really want them to think highly of you,
you should do something.
Dad, I'm telling you.
I prefer to being called
the son of the evil official
than good-for-nothing.
You!
You're really pissing me off!
You can't hit me. You can't hit me.
You're so angry that you have a white mustache.
You!
Come on, dad.
[A clear mirror hung on high. Be a clean man. Be a good official.]
What a bold cunning man.
You actually raped a woman.
Master,
that's the case last month.
The case you mentioned
happened last month.
Your Excellency,
please help me.
The egg from my hen
was taken to
her henhouse by her hen.
That is obviously the egg from my hen.
Look at your ugly hen.
Can she lay
such a good-looking egg?
You're ugly.
Your whole family is ugly.
Well, enough.
Stop fighting!
Let the hens be quiet, too.
It's such a simple thing.
They're just two hens.
Your hen will brood the egg
on Monday, Wednesday and Friday.
on Tuesday, Thursday and Saturday.
When the chick is born,
check its look carefully.
The hen that looks like
the chick is its mother.
That's settled.
How can he handle a case like this?
This is the 39th wrongful conviction in this month.
Zhao Quandui is fatuous and unprincipled as an official.
Well, Bai.
Why are you everywhere?
You're in charge of the northern city,
while I'm in charge of the southern city.
You're just being
a busybody.
Evil official,
since you took the post of magistrate of the southern city,
you've never solved any case.
I'll impeach you before the Lord,
so as to merge the southern city with the northern city.
Bai.
Bai, don't go.
It's time to eat.
Stay to have lunch.
Bai.
Evil official. Evil official. Evil official.
Step down, evil official.
Step down.
Master,
don't take this to heart.
Good cabbage.
Pick up all these
cabbages
and take them back to the mansion.
Cook them for lunch.
The dream of marrying into a rich family is destroyed.
You didn't even meet Zhao Cuo.
Master, master.
Our family is getting rich.
Getting rich?
Zhao Quandui sent a marriage proposal.
His son will marry Jinxin.
Look. Look.
Let me have a look.
But Zhao Cuo doesn't
even meet lady.
So lady's beauty
has long spread through the city.
We'll really get rich.
Prepare a carriage.
I'm going to Zhao's Mansion.
Will I go with you?
No, you don't need to.
Go. Go. Go.
Come on. Come on.
Enjoy it.
There's no salt.
Someone!
Pull the cook out and kill him.
Don't.
What do you want to do?
Without salt,
this dish
doesn't have a soul.
It's really
unbearable.
Son-in-law,
I support you.
Kill him.
Okay.
Well, well.
Someone.
Take this dish
away. Take it away.
Come on.
Continue to enjoy the food.
Li Jia, come on.
Serve the soup for Mr. He.
Good soup.
Especially, the meat in it is fresh and tender.
It's great that my son-in-law is so honest
in our first meeting.
I'm flattered.
Well, Mr. He.
Son-in-law,
what's wrong with you?
I have venereal disease.
Venereal… venereal disease is good.
Venereal disease is
actually a common disease.
Mr. He, please listen to me.
Dad,
don't keep it from him.
I got venereal disease
in the whorehouse.
I only have a month to live.
I really don't want to drag your daughter.
A month?
Mr. He,
don't listen to him.
I…
It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter.
As son-in-law is so frank,
let's just settle the marriage.
I'll marry my daughter into your family tomorrow.
See you.
Master,
Mr. Zhao is dying as he has venereal disease.
Why do you still let lady marry him?
It's good he's dying.
You don't understand.
By then, Jinxin
will be the head of the family.
She'll have a lot of money and treasures as she wants.
Young man,
which deceased friend
are you visiting?
Wang Mazi?
You mean you want to
marry my daughter?
Think carefully.
Young man,
why do you
settle on our daughter?
My dad said
your family buries bodies,
while our family makes coffins.
The combination of our two families
means "die."
You're good.
Let me see
which short-lived guy
wants to marry me.
Oh, my God.
Ghost!
You want to marry me?
No way!
Tian Sanqi,
I told you many times.
You can't sleep in the coffin.
Come out.
Go. Hurry up.
Get down on your knees.
You'll also get down on your knees.
Marriage tree. Marriage tree.
For nine generations, the Tian family has been engaged in funeral.
But in my generation,
I only have one daughter.
My daughter is bad at
lyre-playing, chess, calligraphy and painting.
She just likes autopsy.
All men in the nearby villages
run away when seeing her.
Tree immortal,
you watched her growing up.
Please bless her
so that she can marry a man.
Sanqi is counting on your blessing.
I will collect feces
from door to door tomorrow.
I will spread the best manure for you.
Bullshit.
Who are you talking to?
Dare you say that I bullshit again?
You were wrong indeed.
You want to collect feces?
Was I wrong?
You spoiled her.
I'm telling you.
Dare you say that again?
Fine, I spoiled her.
What are you looking at?
Immortal brother,
I'll be waiting right here.
I won't marry another man.
What did you say?
You won't marry?
Listen. You have to marry.
I'll take you to Wang Mazi's house
to propose a marriage tomorrow.
I'm not going.
I'll wait for the immortal brother
to come back here.
That immortal brother you always mention
has long died.
When you were 10,
he was drowned in the river at the end of our village.
He doesn't have the brother's birthmark.
Brother,
you came here.
You're still alive.
I know you are not dead.
I promise you
I'll be waiting here for you.
I said
that was not him.
He's still alive.
Why don't you believe me?
Fine.
That was
not him.
He's still alive.
Why doesn't he come?
Where's he?
Why doesn't he come to marry you?
I don't know.
But,
he will come back.
Look at you.
You've almost gone crazy
because of him.
Sweetheart,
don't be
so rigid.
Just let it go.
I can't!
I'll just be waiting under this old locust tree.
Before he comes back,
I'm not going anywhere
and I won't marry anyone.
Fine.
You said that.
You'll just wait here.
Let me see how long you will have to wait.
Look,
you can't send meals to her.
Let her stay hungry.
She can't go back home
before she comes round.
Let's go.
Go.
You…
How dare you pull my ear?
She's spoiled by you.
The old man surnamed Ding
has two sons.
He doesn't eat for three days.
He is so hungry that he's busy cooking.
He bought two green onions
with 0.33 yuan.
He bought a watermelon with 0.77 tael.
He bought two loofahs with 0.66 tael.
And two sticks of sugar-coated haws...
Immortal brother,
what's your name?
I don't have a name,
and I don't know who my parents are.
Where is your home?
I don't have a home.
I don't know where I come from
and where I'm going to.
I only have a master.
He told me I would go back to
the place where I belong to someday.
It doesn't matter.
You still have me.
I'll always be with you.
Brother,
what's this?
This is a grimace totem of my own invention.
When no one was with me,
I talked to it.
I'm giving it to you now.
When I am not with you in the future,
seeing it
is like seeing me.
Do you know?
Are you leaving?
Some days later.
You will come back again, right?
Brother,
have some fruit.
Brother.
Young Master,
I won't marry any girl
except her.
But, Young Master,
we've used all kinds of tricks.
We also made a scene in the whorehouse.
Now all people know
you have venereal disease.
If the one you are waiting for still doesn't show up,
I don't have any other way,
Young Master.
Cut the crap.
I'll wait for you.
Lord, congratulations to your having a good daughter-in-law.
Father, I only want to
share your cares and burdens beside you.
It's really too early for me to get married.
Harmony brings wealth.
He Zhen,
I only have one son.
I hope you can get married early
so that I can entrust Taoyuan City to you.
Father.
Young Lord,
the sedan chair to pick up the bride is almost here.
You should wait for it.
Young Master,
master is…
Master?
Who is your master, me or him?
Squat.
Young Master,
listen to me.
You can't run away.
No one can stop me.
But master is right outside the wall.
You should tell me earlier.
Son,
don't be so polite.
You don't need to kneel down.
Stand up.
[Eighteen]
[Arhat Town (Array)]
[It’s all right without mistakes.]
Dad!
You lock me in the room.
Dare you open the door?
Open the door. Open the door.
[Eighteen-arhat Town (Array)]
Young Master, what's the matter?
Nothing.
I'm telling you.
After a few hours,
young master will get married.
Do not make any mistake.
Rest assured.
With Eighteen-arhat Array,
he can't escape.
Good.
A toast to you.
Thank you, Master.
Your color has faded.
Go to make it up.
Okay.
Sanqi.
I'm telling you.
My God.
Our Tian family's ancestral grave smokes.
No, it's not true.
A corpse came out from our ancestral grave.
Sanqi,
we're getting rich.
Are you Tian Sanqi?
Here's the order from Lord of Taoyuan City.
Sanqi from the Tian family
is appointed as the wife of Young Lord.
She must set out immediately
to the mansion of Lord of Taoyuan City to get married
to correct the general mood of the city.
Thank you, Lord.
[Wei Minghua, daughter of Wei Chao, Minister of Rituals]
[Cao Yingying, daughter of Cao Cong, Minister of Revenue]
[Chen Qing, daughter of Chen Zhe, General Protecting the State]
[Zuo Xiaoman, daughter of Zuo Tang, Assistant Minister of Revenue]
See?
After a month,
you still haven't found the girl Zhen likes.
Lord,
Young Lord is extremely picky.
I've found daughters of all officials in the city,
but he likes none of them.
All girls of age with a distinguished family background
in the whole city
were refused by
him by various reasons.
Don't just focus on daughters of the nobility.
There are lots of good girls in Taoyuan City.
I'm the lord of the city.
Both the nobles and civilians
are my people.
Don't say they are humble or noble in the future.
Yes, Lord.
Have you ever searched Shifang Village?
Shifang Village?
This…
Back then, Zhen escaped with bare life
in Shifang Village.
It is my son's lucky land
where people are simple and honest.
My son still can't forget there.
How about this?
I'll make a decision.
Just find a good girl in Shifang Village.
Got it.
I'm going to look for her now.
There are only 9 girls of age in Shifang Village.
Six of them have got married.
The rest three ones
are disabled
or ugly.
What shall we do?
Wait.
There's one left.
Daughter of the Tian family in Yizhuang.
Tian Sanqi.
[Tian Sanqi, daughter of the Tian family in Yizhuang, Shifang Village, Southern City, 29]
[Date of birth and the eight characters of horoscope, hibiscus,]
[the eighth, second, fifth and seventh of the ten Heavenly Stems]
Tian Sanqi.
Accept the order of the Lord.
You mean
the Lord's son,
Young Lord of Taoyuan City
picks me?
You must be kidding.
I don't even know him.
Young Lord is the son chosen by God.
He won't joke with you.
Wait.
What's wrong again?
You look familiar.
Are you the man who
acts Justice Bao in the troupe in western city?
Stop acting.
Your beard is falling off.
Help Young Lady get changed.
What are you doing?
Help!
Sanqi, you are so beautiful.
Isn't she hoodoo?
Shut up.
Don't say this.
Look, she's coming out.
She's coming out.
So beautiful.
As I said,
Sanqi has been difficult since childhood.
Yeah.
It turns out
she's the mountain phoenix among the pheasants.
Yeah.
So beautiful. So beautiful.
Sanqi,
after going to the city,
don't forget to come back to visit me living next door.
Take care. Take care.
Remember to come back.
If…
I mean if…
What if I don't want to
marry Young Lord?
In the world,
all land belongs to the king.
All people in the world
belong to the king.
According to this,
whether you want to marry or not,
you belong to Young Lord
no matter you are alive or dead.
Don't say such things.
It's a big day today.
Don't mention the word dead.
I just asked you about it.
Young Lady,
please get on the sedan.
Daughter. Sanqi.
Dad.
Mom.
I will miss you.
Daughter.
It's time to get on the sedan, Young Lady.
This boy was born with a defect in his coccyx.
The dead boy is not the one to be killed that year.
The assassination eight years ago was wrong.
I'm afraid the dead boy was a substitute.
The target is still alive.
You go back
to report it to our master.
Others stay here
to find out the persons related to the clue.
I found a girl who had contacts with
the person to be killed eight years ago.
It seems she's also looking for him.
Pretty good.
Keep watch on her.
Once there's any new clue,
we should kill him by mistake
rather than let him go.