[Haicheng Dance Academy]
♪I choose not to lean on anything♪
♪Instead, I grab the future in my hand♪
♪Never loose my hold even when I fall♪
♪The airy skirt twirls♪
♪I leap on the dazzling stage♪
♪Flowers bloom as promised
amidst clamorous applause♪
♪I believe everything
is meant for the best♪
♪Be brave, I voice my dream♪
♪Be confident,
I stand en pointe to touch the sky♪
♪Stars are coming shining on my way♪
♪The future will come into my open arms♪
♪Do not wait for fate
to knock on my door♪
♪Youth is the time♪
♪When we embrace splendors unknown♪
♪The future will come into my open arms♪
♪Never fear failures♪
♪I will grace the world♪
[Just Dance]
♪With my presence♪
[Episode 6]
[You also have... us!]
Oh my goodness...
Damn it,
what kind of role suits Pan Pan?
So there's a moment of glory
for poor students, too.
You've sobered up, huh?
How did I get back yesterday?
Have you forgotten that Xiao Bu
and the others carried you back?
I guess I'm not much of a drinker.
Do you remember what you said
last night?
What did I say?
Nothing at all.
Glad that you can't remember anything.
You came just in time.
I thought Pan Pan couldn't dance
as the Prince anymore.
I'm trying to find him a different role.
No wonder you're so confused.
So you're helping Pan Pan find a role.
Let me show you something.
I've been thinking about this
for a while too.
I finally found a role that suits him.
What is this?
The Joker.
This is a supporting role in Swan Lake.
The male dancers are required
to wear clown makeup.
This character is also very skillful.
He has mysterious identity and origin.
Every version is different
depending on the plots.
There's an interesting saying about it.
The clown's level of skill
represents the level
of the whole choreography.
I got it.
Do you mean to let Pan Pan
dance as the Joker
so that he can use a mask?
In that case,
The audience won't know
who's actually behind the mask.
Pan Pan will be more relaxed then.
That's right.
If Pan Pan dances as the Joker,
He can dance in front of the crowd
while wearing a mask.
This only solves the problem for now.
Because...
Dancing in front of the crowd matters.
You're really clever!
But I think
before he dances in front of Mr. Lin
and our classmates,
he has to try to dance
in front of the audience first.
You have a point.
We shouldn't make hasty suggestions.
I have an idea!
Isn't their diner opening soon?
Since it's opening,
we'd have an event to make it lively.
Don't be lazy.
There's another one on the right.
Have you no shame?
I'm wiping by myself without any help.
Look at you.
A man's got to keep his word.
You promised to help me.
How could I take your job?
Am I right?
Shameless!
You told the dean about
the commercial performance, didn't you?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
Stop pretending. I have proof.
Somebody told me about this.
You know what?
Getting panic is the first thing
that happens when you lie.
You're clearly stuttering.
Who?
Who stuttered?
I mean, who said
it was me who reported it?
I was trying to trick you.
I didn't realize you were
such a bad liar.
Yu Manman.
You're the Black Swan herself.
What have I done to deserve this?
Don't blame me, blame Shi Xiaochun.
Is this about Ling Chen again?
Do you know what karma is?
You reported me and Shi Xiaochun.
You're the one who got punished for me.
It's called karma.
I'm not wiping anymore!
I'll tell Ling Chen about this then!
Don't you dare!
Don't try me!
Don't tell him.
I have to hide this from Shi Xiaochun.
I have to hide this from Ling Chen too.
I'm so close to them.
I feel bad.
I'll agree to one more condition.
Deal.
[Grand Opening]
Good!
Awesome!
666!
Cool!
Great performance!
Great!
- Great!
- Well done!
Come on, kids.
Let's celebrate Pan Pan's
double happiness.
Let's drink to that.
Sir, which happiness?
First,
Pan Pan has finally overcome his fear.
The department has also agreed
to let Pam Pam play the role
of the Joker in the annual play.
We should celebrate this.
That's good.
The second one is Pan Pan's diner.
Their business is thriving
and making a fortune every day.
This is worth celebration too, right?
Definitely double happiness.
Come on, let's drink to that.
Cheers!
Here's your meal.
Mom.
Here.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you, Auntie.
Thanks, Mom.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Thank you, Pan Pan's mom.
Don't mention it.
Come on.
These dumplings are good.
Eat them while they're still hot.
So big.
Yeah.
There's even yolk in here.
Where's Ling Chen? I don't see him.
He just said he wasn't hungry and
went to help my dad hand out fliers.
Any of you knows where he went?
I think he's in the backstreet plaza.
Alright.
Let's eat.
A new Shumai shop.
Handsome guy, have a look.
Thank you.
Take a look, we have a discount.
Take a look.
Newly opened Shumai shop!
- Hello.
- Thank you.
Sure.
Hey.
Why does this flyer guy so familiar?
So it's you.
What are you doing here?
Pan Pan and the others
told me you're here.
I just came to check. Are there more?
That's it.
Only few left.
Let me help you. I'll get you
twice the result with half the effort.
Here you go.
Don't miss it!
The ballet handsome guy
is handing out fliers!
With this flyer,
you can grab some opening gifts
at the Pan's Shumai Shop
across the street!
Slow down.
Thank you.
Okay, that's it.
If you still want it,
you can go to the Shumai shop
across the street.
There's a lot of discounts there.
- Bye.
- Welcome.
Shi Xiaochun, you did great.
You've got tricks up your sleeve.
This is nothing.
In my hometown,
if you like someone, you should go
after them, regardless of their gender.
You guys are just too timid.
I've done you a great favor.
How about you teach me to ride this?
I want to learn too.
Fine.
Here.
Good.
Keep your body straight to get balanced.
Well done.
♪Like being trapped on a rainy day♪
♪Like sinking deep underwater...♪
Slow down.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
That's great!
Pan Pan has finally taken off his mask
and faced himself.
Yeah.
He really should get over his fear.
Have you ever been afraid?
Pan Pan told me that
he's afraid of making a mistake
when he's on stage.
He is afraid of being replaced.
Actually, I've had that thought too.
What about you?
I've got one too.
I can't believe you had it.
How did you get over it?
I didn't get over it.
Actually, every time I compete on stage,
I'd get nervous.
I'd be scared too.
I fear of making the wrong move.
But I've never resisted this feeling.
I call this feeling
a reverence for the stage.
The only solution is to keep practicing.
Keep getting better.
So what do we fear?
It's actually fear itself.
It has nothing to do
with wearing a mask.
We have to deal with ourselves.
It's rare for you to agree with me.
I think we've had
a lot of misunderstandings.
How about this?
Let's get reacquainted.
Hello. My name is Shi Xiaochun.
Nice to meet you.
Let's make friends.
Hello, I'm Ling Chen.
♪I cry out♪
♪What will happen to you
when you disappear?♪
[Department of Ballet]
Shiru.
45.
Two laps.
Hua Qing.
46.6.
Three Laps.
Shi Xiaochun.
[50.35.]
Looks like you've been eating well.
Not bad.
Don't laugh!
Five laps!
Have I gained that much weight?
As a dance student,
you can't even manage your own body!
Can you believe that?
Go back and reflect yourself!
You! Your turn!
Hong Jiaoyang.
Did you eat with Shi Xiaochun?
Five laps!
What are you waiting for? Go!
Come on.
Manman is not bad.
Next.
Stop.
Come here, you two.
Sir.
Well done, you two.
The rest of the class is running laps
in the big sports field.
You two are here.
What's the matter? You want to rebel?
Can you control your mouth from now on?
Oh.
Hong Jiaoyang.
You've got more problems
than just weight management.
You're out there dancing Latin.
You have to stop too.
How do you know, Sir?
I thought it was your hobby.
So I turned a blind eye.
Let's take the opportunity today.
Let's talk about it.
Now that you've entered
Haicheng Dance Academy,
you have to consider yourself
as a professional dancer.
You should fully focus
on whatever you do.
Sometimes ballet,
sometimes Latin dance,
not fully committed either way.
Which one do you prefer?
If you want to get it right,
you must choose only one of them.
Sir, I...
It's alright.
Here.
Take a look at Shi Xiaochun.
Though when she's dancing,
there are aspects to be improved,
but she's all about
getting good at ballet.
She's made a lot of progress.
You, on the other hand,
you're not making any progress.
Which means you're regressing.
It's not that the I won't allow you
to have your own personal hobbies.
You have to know the tradeoffs
when it comes to the big picture.
Know what you want.
Do your best.
That's the smartest thing to do.
I got it.
Okay.
About weight management,
it's all up to you two.
I'm still worried.
Here's the deal.
I'll look for a responsible classmate
to supervise you.
Sir, I don't think the we need it.
It's not up to you.
Go back to practicing.
- Sir
- Mr. Lin.
Hong, where should we go after practice?
What's wrong? Let us in.
Mr. Lin ordered it.
Let me supervise your weight loss
from today.
You'll have to be on a strict diet.
A daily plan for aerobic exercise too.
Not more than 1,200 calories per meal.
No way!
Your bags.
Chocolate. 589 calories.
Shrimp Sticks. 484 calories.
Get in.
Here you go.
He's got double vision, hasn't he?
How did he know
I had chocolate in my bag?
Ling Chen is so smart.
He can see right through you.
The evils are powerful,
but the justice will defeat the evils.
Plum. 180 calories.
He has no humanity.
Hong, I've caused trouble for you.
Let's go practice.
From now on, all your meals
must be weighed.
You can only eat if the meals meet
the precise measurement standard.
You got it?
This is very inhuman!
We've been eating salads all day.
You are even weighing grass now.
I think you're going too far.
Are you two okay?
Do you want the meat?
Of course!
I will pass.
Take it away.
Prince Ling.
I've been troubled by a dance-related
issue for a while now.
Please help me out.
Go ahead.
This gesture...
Should I do it this way or that way?
Don't go too high.
Do you two realize that
a chicken nugget costs 258 calories,
and a rack of ribs costs 215 calories.
Jogging for an hour
only burned 500 calories.
Go run around the sports field
after this.
I can't hold it anymore!
I'll spit it out.
- What?
- Come on.
Hold on.
Go on.
Hong, it's too hard.
I didn't expect that my weight
would become a stumbling block
in my ballet journey.
You're not the only one.
Have you decided what character
you're running for?
How about the White Swan?
Let's have a showdown between sisters.
Little Peacock.
I don't want to join the play anymore.
What?!
Have you been tortured
too much by Ling Chen?
I really don't want to join anymore.
Let's go find Mr. Lin.
Let's discuss with Mr. Lin.
Shi Xiaochun!
Ling Chen is kind to supervise you.
Why show me this attitude!
Sir.
We can supervise each other.
We don't need him.
We can do it for the ballet.
Please believe in us.
That's good, Sir.
I'll be getting ready for my show soon.
I can't spare more energy for them.
Please ask the others to supervise them.
All right.
Shut up.
Mr. Lin, I have something to say.
Say it.
I want to change my major.
I'd like to transfer to the
Department of Dance Education.
The Department of Dance Education?
Wait.
Hong Jiaoyang,
what are you talking about?
Wait a minute.
Have you recently
been stressing about
your weight control a little too much?
No, I don't.
Both Xiaochun and I understand
the importance of physical fitness.
In fact, I've been thinking
about this for a long time.
Last time, you told me to be sure
of what I wanted to do.
And then do it without hesitation.
It makes me even more determined.
Sir, I can't give up Latin.
This is not a small matter.
Don't you regret it.
It won't be easy to come back.
Xiaochun.
I've made up my mind.
Sir, don't listen to her.
Hong Jiaoyang, what are you doing?
I've really thought this through.
Such a big decision.
Leaving without any reason.
Have you considered our
Good-for-nothing League?
Does our friendship mean nothing to you?
I...
Stop it. Leave me alone.
Xiaochun!
Sir, I'll go first.
Why isn't Shi Xiaochun here yet?
She's late for the dinner.
It's not like her.
Yeah.
Hello, where are you?
Come and eat.
I'm on a diet. You guys enjoy.
She hung up the phone.
What's going on?
Shi Xiaochun is a rice lover.
I can't believe she is not coming.
She probably won't come.
What's wrong?
I told Mr. Lin that I want to
change my major today.
Xiaochun is a little upset.
You're changing your major?!
Changing your major?
Which department are you going?
Which department?
The Department of Dance Education.
I want to be a Latin dance teacher
in the future.
So sudden.
Actually,
I've been working part-time
at a dance academy.
Being with some kids.
I really feel very comfortable.
And you know it.
Make progress in ballet in this way
is impossible.
Because strength is what I'm good at.
That's why I want to change my major.
As long as you're not in trouble.
Going after your dreams
is not a big deal.
You see, my heart
belongs to somewhere else too.
I'm not as brave as you.
You are brave to change your major.
Yeah, Hong.
I think you're brave, too.
I think Xiaochun will be okay soon.
She'll understand.
Here.
The Happy Fatty meal set.
I'm not eating.
I'm trying to lose weight.
Let's make an exception today.
Let's eat.
You'll feel better when you're full.
Well, I'll eat.
I knew it.
This burger is whole wheat.
This Coke is sugar-free.
But it's still good.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Actually,
I think Hong Jiaoyang
must've thought for a long time
before she made this decision.
Think about it.
The best dancing major in Haicheng Dance
is the Ballet major.
She must be sure about her future goals
and
made this decision based on her dream.
Don't you think that
dreams are something
you keep persisting in
but you can still feel happy
at the same time?
If you were to give up ballet,
what would you do?
I...
Anyway, I understand her.
I think
dance education
is the dream she really
wants to hold on to.
But she can't just leave.
What am I gonna do when she's gone?
You still have me.
There's us, the classmates.
You have Xiao Bu
and Pan Pan.
It's good to have you guys.
Follow me.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four,
- Hong.
- Three,
Two,
- Why is she here?
- Three.
- She really likes to teach Latin.
- Four, five, six.
- You see, when she's dealing with kids,
- Seven, eight, stop.
she looks like a different person.
This is not working. Let's try it again.
One, two, three, four.
Listen to me.
Xiaochun.
- When you do this,
- Not everything
- you need to open your hands.
- must go all the way to the end.
- Let's do it again.
- Hong works here
- One, two, three.
- not just to support her family.
Four.
- She's really suited to be a teacher.
- Five, six.
Seven.
- I think we should support her.
- Eight. Very good. That's it.
Am I right?
That's good. Keep it up.
Good.
Everyone got it right this time.
Let's end the class.
See you later, students.
Goodbye, teacher.
- Bye-bye. Take care.
- Bye, teacher.
Chun Chun.
Come to me.
Let's go.
Did you learn everything today?
Hong.
Chun Chun, you can go back now.
Thank you, teacher.
Take care of yourself on your way.
Xiaochun, what are you doing here?
You like to teach children how to dance.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Actually, I've been teaching here
for a long time.
But I've been afraid to tell you.
I was too impulsive last time.
I got mad at you.
I'm sorry.
It's all in the past.
Let's hug.
When I have time in the future,
I'll come with you and
teach the children how to dance.
How about it?
Sure!
Yu Manman, your eye contact.
Your legs.
Note the rhythm!
[Shi Xiaochun]
Why can't you even follow the music now?
Yu Manman.
Don't mind the precision!
Don't follow the usual steps!
Stop.
The Black Swan needs strength and charm.
Why are you calm like the White Swan?
How can you dance so poor
for the black swan?
Ling Chen.
I let you rest,
not to play with your phone.
You should focus on
your partner's movements right now.
Fifteen-minute break for Yu Manman.
Think about the moves.
Miss, I'd like to sign up
for the Black and White Swan.
Yu Manman,
are you alright?
Hong Jiaoyang,
about this.
I read the e-mail you sent me
for the transfer request.
I also believe that you are doing
this because you love education.
That's why you chose to transfer
from ballet to our department.
But according to school regulations,
your grade average must be above 90.
In addition,
you have to play a big role
in the annual school play.
Then you'll fulfill the requirements
for transferring to another department.
It's true that our department
has no precedent for a major change.
Mr. Lin told me about your situation.
We finally decided
to let you change your major.
But you must fulfill the requirements
mentioned by Mr. Liu.
In this way, you can prove to us
your expertises are up to standard.
What do you think?
Okay, I'll do it.
I found a problem.
What problem?
You're in bad state.
You're distracted.
I couldn't find the characteristics
of the demon king.
In a nutshell,
neither of us is good.
I know why you can't dance well.
The demon king is not just strong.
He's also extremely seductive.
He will irresistibly attract people.
To put it bluntly,
you have to be androgynous.
I can't act girly.
I don't fit at all.
I'm counting on you, okay?
I really want to play as the Black Swan.
Help me.
Manman,
I'm really worried
that I'd hold you back.
I think you should
find one that's really good for
playing as the demon king.
That way you'll improve more.
Forget it.
You and Ling Chen don't want
to dance with me.
I didn't mean anything by it.
I was just,
I just don't think I'm good enough
for the demon king.
I can be your practice partner.
Don't worry.
Before you found the new demon king,
I'll always be with you.
Don't look down.
Your crown will fall off.
You look better when you smile.
Here's the deal.
You can use me as a tool.
♪Like being trapped on a rainy day♪
♪Like sinking deep underwater♪
♪The wind brushes against your face♪
♪You haven't danced since then♪
♪I cry out♪
♪What will happen to you
when you disappear?♪
♪You wobble♪
♪You keep falling back♪
♪Wait for me, I will save you♪
♪Gently♪
♪I hold you tight
at the edge of the world♪
♪The stage awaits you
no matter how long it takes♪
♪Wait for me, I will save you♪
♪Let the rain drench us♪
♪Showering away your painful memories,
I am by your side♪
♪Your heart will heal up gradually♪
♪A light is gleaming ahead,
I see you there♪