[I Hear You]
[Episode 16]
Miss Bei, here you are.
Boss has been waiting for you
for a long time.
How did he know I was coming?
Come on in.
This is indeed a good timber.
But I don't want it.
Excuse me.
Not at all.
Just take it away.
Why?
Shuwei.
What's up?
I was scared, Shuwei.
Here you are.
You left the document in the room.
I was just going to find Li,
so I brought it to you by the way.
We met again.
Why are you everywhere?
Shouldn't that be what I say?
Don't get me wrong.
I just wanted to push her away.
Shuwei.
Didn't you just say that this spruce
is good?
But I also said I didn't want it.
Let's talk in the studio.
Shuwei, the spruce…
He Yang, send her away.
Listen to me.
I know.
I have known you for so long.
I know who you are.
Besides,
you have professional integrity.
I will definitely not misunderstand you.
So you think I'm doing this
out of professional integrity?
Yes.
And you also know
what kind of person Zhang Yilu is.
I won't get you wrong.
Don't worry.
Bei Erduo.
I'm not worried that you will get me wrong
but that you will woolgather.
I understand.
I won't.
You're so self-disciplined,
and I'm not worried at all.
All right.
I'm going to look for Li.
See you at home.
I will pick you up.
No need.
I'll go back by myself.
I am leaving.
Li, stop drinking on an empty stomach.
It's okay.
I can only make it clear after drinking.
Okay, you drank a lot.
Just tell me.
Erduo, if I
quit the show,
will you blame me?
Quit the show?
Why?
The successful investment promotion
of the second season
mainly depends on Xing Zhen.
Xing Zhen and I have
wide disagreement about
the way of doing things,
the concept of the show,
and the principles and bottom line.
As the boss,
Yu Sheng often has no choice.
If I quit,
it will save everyone from trouble.
If you quit,
I will be left alone.
I will also quit then.
You have to stay on the show.
And I think
Ye Shuwei is treating you
better and better.
I think you will possibly be together.
You have to work hard to save money
and realize your dream in Japan as soon as possible.
Stop talking about me.
And you?
Aren't you going to discuss it
with Mr. Yu again?
Haven't you been doing well before?
You know what?
I had fantasies about him
until today.
I think at least
we're in step at work.
But after what happened today,
I feel like I don't know him anymore.
[Tokyo]
Erduo, why is he so capricious?
How could he abandon
the previous ideals and beliefs?
You know what?
We were full of enthusiasm and confidence
when we first started our business.
We said to make the most popular
original shows of our own.
But why did he choose something
that could make money
but had no limit so soon?
Erduo, tell me.
Why is he so capricious?
I am so sad.
Hello.
Hello, sir.
Charge the Tokyo box's bill to my account.
Okay, hold on.
And call them a chauffeur.
Okay.
Li.
After what you said, I'm really hesitant
about whether to participate or not.
Don't hesitate.
You have to go
and win the bonus.
This is the only thing
I can do for you right now.
And a great event in your life
would also be settled.
Why are you talking about me again?
I came today just to
hear you complain.
Erduo, remember.
If you like someone,
you should seriously
confirm your own and his heart.
Don't be ambiguous.
Don't hesitate.
Just take a step forward.
If he likes you,
he will definitely take the remaining
ninety-nine steps.
So you're not going to take a step?
Even if I take ninety-nine steps now,
it may be pointless.
We are already on different paths.
If you encounter difficulties
on the show in the future,
let me know right away.
I will fight for you.
What are you going to do?
To spit out all my agony.
Then it's time to start over.
Good morning.
I'm going to the recording room.
I'm going to the studio.
See you in the afternoon.
You?
I'm going to resign.
You are not a child anymore.
Don't act on impulse.
You have known me for so long.
When did I act on impulse?
Now you are.
If you don't want to
work with Xing Zhen,
I can arrange other projects for you.
No need.
I've already made up my mind.
I am here just to inform you.
I am leaving.
You'd better not drink alcohol
when socializing in the future.
Otherwise no one will care
about your headache the next day.
You are always like this.
We are tired of it.
Right, so double-faced.
Are you still my best friends?
No.
You…
Erduo, go back to rest today.
Youyou, take her out.
Okay.
Moyu, you have one more monologue.
Finish it.
Take some hot water.
Thank you.
You should ask for leave.
Why holding on?
How could I ask for leave again?
I wasted so much of your time last time.
How are you, Erduo?
Are you feeling better?
Moyu, I am much better.
I just feel sore and weak.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I am the same as you.
A woman
has to suffer a lot in her life.
Who is going to suffer?
You brought so much food.
Why are you here?
I'm just passing by,
by the way to console you.
Maybe just to console one person.
Le Tian, thank you.
I am just passing by.
Eat together. I bought a lot.
Le Tian, thank you.
I haven't had cake for a long time.
This cake tastes good.
Is there any ulterior purpose
for all of this?
Of course not.
Someone rejected me some time ago.
Le Tian, eat more cakes.
My bad.
You don't look well.
Let me take you back.
It's okay.
I can go back alone.
Erduo, let Le Tian take you back.
It's not convenient for you
to go back alone.
What's wrong with you?
Shall I take you to the hospital?
It's no use going to the hospital
in her condition.
You'd better take her home
and prepare brown sugar water for her.
Let me take you home.
I'm going back.
Sure.
Take care.
Okay.
I can walk by myself.
You don't have to hold me.
Why not?
You almost missed your step.
It's dark inside so I didn't see clearly.
You don't have to hold me.
No, I'm doing this for your safety.
Le Tian, if you keep doing this,
we can't be friends anymore.
Miss Bei,
don't think too much.
This is how I treat my friends.
Treat me as your friend now.
Let me send my friend,
Miss Bei Erduo, home.
Let her go.
Why are you here?
I'm just passing by.
What happened to you?
Don't you feel well?
I just need some rest.
Thank you.
Leave her to me.
I will take her home.
You are welcome. I am glad to do so.
But it seems that
you are not that busy with work.
No matter how busy I am,
I have time to pick her up.
Let's go.
Le Tian, we are going back first.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Are you finished?
Are you feeling better?
I am fine.
Don't force yourself if you don't feel well.
Who did your makeup?
Any problem?
No, it's just way too heavy.
Remove her makeup.
When shooting,
the light will make the makeup effect
less obvious.
I couldn't possibly give her everyday makeup.
Does stage makeup have to be heavy?
It's too much.
It depends on each person's own conditions.
I know her better.
Lighten her base makeup.
Remove blush and lipstick.
Thank you.
Please make some adjustment for her.
Let's go.
Okay.
We are now shooting a clip
of your daily life.
You two can brush your teeth
and sit there eating breakfast.
Let's try it.
Ready.
Action.
The boys can squeeze toothpaste
for the girl.
It will make you closer.
Eat the breakfast.
Right.
Feed each other.
Serve some milk.
Want more?
Okay, cut.
Let's get ready for live shot.
All departments, get ready.
Get ready for live shot.
Mr. Yu, you also came?
I ask you to make the promotional video.
So I have to be here.
Otherwise, I'm not sure
if anything would go wrong
with that guy.
It makes sense.
If anything happens,
only you can convince him.
Mr. Yu, do you think Li
has any problem at work recently?
This season, she…
I heard you've known each other
since you were kids, right?
We are close.
And both of our parents know each other
and are very familiar with each other.
In fact, Li
looks careless on the surface,
but she is thoughtful when doing things,
and sometimes she would be over-anxious.
But she never haggles over every ounce.
It's very comfortable
to get along with her.
On the contrary, I think that
she is way too cautious,
resulting in conservative thinking,
and dare not go for many things.
She is cautious
because she is serious about work.
Well,
it makes sense.
What about things other than work?
Mr. Yu, what do you want to know
about her
besides work?
You can ask her directly.
She should be willing to tell you.
Just go to the makeup artist.
Your false eyelashes are falling out.
This video
will capture your daily behavior.
And you don't have to synchronize.
So just interact with each other
and relax.
Follow my lead.
Just look at each other
or hold hands,
as what you do at home.
Try to relax.
Understand?
Let's do this.
Film with bare feet.
Take your shoes off.
When I give you a hint,
just follow it.
But do remember
not to look at the camera.
As long as you don't look at the camera,
there's no problem,
and we'll always be filming on the side.
Okay, all departments.
Get ready for live shot.
Ready.
Action.
The boy should hold girl's hand.
Yes, and put the other hand
on the girl's shoulder.
Just do it gently.
Look at each other.
Say something,
just like you do at home.
How did you sleep last night?
I have always slept well.
It looks like you have nothing
to talk to me about.
You must find it more interesting
to chat with Yu Sheng.
It's not the same.
I'm not familiar with Mr. Yu.
Really?
Why did you just chat with him
in this chair
for seven minutes and thirty-two seconds?
Okay.
You are in pretty good status.
So natural.
Please stand up
and we will film the other picture.
Girls, please stand on tiptoe
and kiss the boy's face.
Stand on tiptoe.
Lean forward a bit.
You are not tall enough.
Now you can kiss me.
Come on.
Why so shy?
Just kiss his face.
Close your eyes.
Do it.
Come to me.
Face to the right.
It turns out that I can do it faster.
- You are welcome.
- You…
Just to lift a finger.
Cut.
Pass.
Great.
Hello, mom.
What's the matter?
Erduo, where are you?
Are you busy now?
I just finished filming the promotional video.
Just come back.
I fell
while packing the closet at home.
I rested for a while.
It hurts when I move.
Come back and take me to the hospital.
Okay, stay there.
I will be back soon.
Okay, Erduo.
Don't worry.
Aunt Zhang came
to help me on the couch.
I'm on the couch and it's fine.
Take care.
Don't worry.
Be careful.
What happened to your mom?
My mom said she fell while moving something.
And her leg was broken.
She can hardly move now.
I have to go back quickly.
Let me send you back.
Thank you.
Mom, what happened?
It really hurts.
Aunt.
Ye is also here.
Don't move.
Okay, I won't.
Be careful.
Aunt, you must have sprained the ankle.
You should go to the hospital right away.
Let's go to the hospital.
Really?
Let's go.
Let's go to the hospital.
Ouch, it hurts so much.
Let me help you.
You?
Aunt, let me carry you.
No need.
I can make it.
I can move over or jump over.
Aunt.
Come on. It's okay.
All right. Sorry for that.
Take care.
Sorry to bother you.
Sorry.
I should have
lost weight earlier.
Let's go.
Sorry.
Slow down.
Thank you.
[Transfusion room, observation room, emergency obstetrics&
gynecology department, emergency registration]
Thank you.
Erduo, check with your mom first.
Give me the identity documents
and I'll go through the formalities.
It's on the outermost side of the bag.
Thank you.
Nothing.
Is she still under checking?
[Medical Institutions in Guangdong Province]
[General medical records of outpatient (emergency) service]
Doctors suspected it is
a fracture in the ankle bone.
So she needs to take an X-ray.
Has your mother's blood pressure
been normal in recent years?
She didn't say anything about blood pressure.
I have been asking her
to have a physical examination
in the past few years,
but she always shies away
with various reasons.
[Emergency Surgery]
Then she'd better do a comprehensive
physical examination this time.
Don't worry about fees.
Let's talk about it later.
I will pay you back as soon as
I have enough money.
Ye Shuwei.
Thank you.
I'll make a call and be right back.
Hello.
Uncle.
I have sent you and Erduo's
promotional video
to your email.
OK, what are you doing?
I have an appointment with a client
for dinner and talk about the project.
With Tang Li?
No, with Xing Zhen.
Do you have a crush on girls
with whom you often hang out?
Ye Shuwei, what's wrong with you?
I could hardly believe that
you asked me this question.
What's wrong?
Why are you talking
about women with me now?
I just want to give you a piece of advice.
If you like her, just go for her.
If not,
don't express caring things outside of work
to show the so-called gentleman's charm.
Are you advising me now
as Erduo's boyfriend?
Just make it simple.
I am reminding you as your elder.
What happened to him?
It's better than I thought.
Film editors can
make use of discarded things.
Really?
Didn't you find
a lot of details unnatural?
Like what?
For example, the way you look at me
and the way you talk to me
are very unfamiliar.
You should be more involved.
Really?
I don't think so.
Yu Sheng said that
there would be another promotional video
in the next recording to boost popularity.
In order to make the next video more natural,
we should practice in advance.
Sure. No problem.
How?
The first thing is our titles of each other.
You can't call me by my full name again.
How could I call you then?
As you like.
Just don't call me by my full name.
Then I will call you Shuwei?
When you call me,
add more feelings.
Now I feel that we are not familiar,
and you are calling a stranger.
Shuwei.
Better.
But it could be warmer.
Now there is no temperature in your voice.
Shuwei.
I got it.
The problem is in the last word.
Don't call me so decisive.
Decisive?
I mean to make it more colloquial.
It doesn't need fullness of articulation.
You are not an announcer.
Shuwei.
Erduo.
You call me Erduo?
Isn't it your name?
But it sounds different.
What?
Nothing.
What to practice next?
We have to exchange a secret.
Exchange a secret?
Just a secret.
When someone asks us,
we should understand each other in advance.
But I don't seem
to have a secret.
It's not so difficult.
Anything will do.
For example, who have you liked before?
If so,
could it be someone I liked
in primary school?
Who else?
In high school? In university?
How come?
Yes.
There is one.
Who?
Allen.
It should be power outage.
It's okay, Ye Shuwei. Don't be afraid.
I am going to find a candle now.
Just wait here.
I got it!
Are you feeling better?
I am fine.
Let's continue.
You won't be afraid after a talk.
Okay.
Who's that Allen
you just mentioned?
Is he your friend?
He is a composer.
He worked for
many big-budget cartoons.
Do you want to listen to his song?
No.
You must be exaggerating
about his excellence.
Allen
is the best composer in the world.
Countless people
asked him to compose.
Maybe he's an otaku.
Even so,
he's the coolest otaku.
You think he's cool?
Have you ever met him?
No.
Allen is low-key.
I am looking for his information
almost like FBI.
Is he that perfect?
Maybe you wouldn't say so when you see him.
No way,
he's always
perfect for me.
All right, the light is on.
I'm going to sleep.
How dare you doubt Allen?
Good night.
Ms. Tang, why are you here?
You…
Don't get me wrong.
I just went to socialize with Mr. Yu.
He's drunk, so I took him home.
I have something to tell him.
Please come in, I will wake him up.
Ms. Tang, I prepared a cup of honey water.
When Mr. Yu is getting better,
let him drink it.
I will leave him to you then.
Li.
Where is Xing Zhen?
Wasn't she who took me home?
She's left.
You didn't pick up my phones.
So I came to take a look.
Thank you, you know me the best.
You should thank Xing Zhen.
You…
I came for Erduo.
I hope you to take care of Erduo
in the show
for the sake of us
knowing each other for so many years.
Erduo is both my guest and my friend.
Of course I will.
Good.
Well, Li.
Don't have a prejudice to Xing Zhen.
She did everything for the company.
If it wasn't for the sponsor she got,
the second season still remains unknown.
So you two are the best partners now?
Please make a clear distinction
between public and private interests.
I do make a clear distinction.
We have nothing to do
with the public interests.
Let's talk about the private ones.
You said that you two have no relationships.
What about us?
Except work,
do we have anything to do with each other?
For so many years,
I always thought that
we had tacit understanding.
If I think too much,
I am sorry for that.
Let me make it clear.
I like you.
And you?
♪I don't want to say my actions out♪
♪So that no one can see my sorrow♪
♪I never doubt every moment of life♪
♪For I stay true to my inner choice♪
♪I've always enjoyed silence♪
♪But I feel something is missing♪
♪I hear the sadness played deep down♪
♪I pass by you gently♪
♪How to grab you♪
♪I remember every time♪
♪You're always there for me♪
♪Days and nights go by♪
♪I'm alone in the world♪
♪Try hard to make you out of the wind♪
♪This song is me♪
♪You're unique in my heart♪
♪Hovering right now♪
♪All the stars surrounding my ears♪
♪Ups and downs of fingertips♪
♪Sing slowly from the strings♪
♪Leisurely echo with persistence♪
♪This song reminds me♪
♪You're always a firm choice of mine♪
♪I miss you at every moment♪
♪All the joy we have together♪
♪Like the heartbeat♪
♪So many stories are hidden♪
♪In your voice♪
♪And the most beautiful story♪
♪The one in my plot♪
♪It's happening right now♪