[I Hear You]
[Episode 21]
We are very honored to have
the triennial International Violin Making Competition
in China this year.
In this competition, I'm very happy
to see the violin-making industry of China
progressing rapidly step by step.
I believe that the violin-making industry
of China will be even better.
The Silver Prize winner of this competition,
Mars from Italy!
Congratulations.
The Golden Prize winner,
from China,
Ye Shuwei!
Let's welcome the Golden Prize winner
to deliver a speech for us.
Thank you.
Thank judges for your recognition.
Mr. Zheng Tongsheng,
the violin-making master of China
once said
that the meaning of life
is to realize one's own value.
I don't want to sound too arrogant,
but I hope I can follow his footsteps
and create more possibilities
for China's violin-making industry.
The winning violin of this competition
will be used by
a world-famous young violinist
on her world concert tour.
Now let's welcome the violinist,
Miss Lin Qingzhuo.
Round of applause!
Congratulations.
I know it has to be you.
Hello, everyone.
I feel very lucky
to play the violin made by my good friend.
Some of you may not know...
What's the relationship between them?
Are they close?
I don't know either.
He's a good composer, too.
Later, Shuwei and I
will present a great performance to you.
Let's start.
The award ceremony
of the 5th International Violin Making Competition
has come to a successful conclusion!
Finally, you've found the place
you should be at.
I've liked him since I was little
but I wasn't brave enough
to tell him face to face.
When I met him again as a grown-up,
he said he's your boyfriend.
I couldn't accept that I've lost to you.
But just now,
I let go of all my frustration.
Because I saw the one I love
is together with a better match than me.
I should feel happy for him.
Bei Erduo, I'm going to find my world
and you should go back to your world, too.
Don't mess around in other people's world.
Coming.
I'm so happy now.
Yeah, because I love skewers.
Here you are. Your skewers.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Thanks.
Madam, two bottles of beer, please.
Iced ones.
Okay.
Thank you.
Come on.
Alicia, can we finish these?
Of course. It's not that much.
Even Erduo and I can finish it.
Come on, have a try.
But you...
You've been eating very little before.
I...
Here you are.
Okay, thank you.
Come on.
Iced beer and skewers.
Okay.
Perfect combination.
Okay. I'll have this one first.
Have a taste.
Okay.
How's that?
Have a try.
Good.
Is this called Heaven on Earth?
You mean delicacy on Earth, right?
Don't throw that word around.
Try the potato slice.
Okay.
Tastes good, too.
If not for this competition,
I wouldn't have tasted so much great food.
Don't you think it's a pity?
You mean, losing to Allen?
It's fine.
There's a saying in Chinese,
why is there...
Why is there always someone smarter?
Right. Although I want to say this,
I think
this is just an excuse for losers.
I'm still young. It's fine.
Okay. For your future.
Cheers.
I'm really thankful
that I got to know you.
I'm really happy to meet you, too.
Yes.
But your happiness is different
from mine.
Before meeting you every day,
I keep wondering
that when you'll say yes
and when you'll agree to be my girlfriend.
If you say yes,
I'll introduce you to my parents
and siblings right away.
They will like you very much for sure.
Then we can get married
and we'll have three children.
Although I like daughters,
she needs to have two elder brothers.
So, if anything goes wrong,
they can protect her.
Did you give the wrong change again?
Well, it's not a big deal.
As long as the customers are happy,
it's okay.
This is not the first time.
I mean, can you...
Lamb skewer for you.
Look, it's so well grilled.
Don't be angry.
I cook this every day
and you're offering it to me.
As long as you're happy.
If we have an argument,
will you do this to me, too?
Of course.
Because I like skewers too.
But what am I thinking about?
I feel like I'm dreaming.
Although I know you're not prepared,
I'm willing to wait for you,
no matter what.
You try again. Maybe I'll agree with you.
Okay.
Then...
Alicia,
will you marry me?
Yes.
You're kidding, right?
I'm serious.
You're serious?
Of course.
I am.
It's so ugly.
But I like it.
Don't go back on your words.
I won't.
Good morning.
Good morning. Coffee?
Yes.
Thanks.
Erduo,
I have something to tell you.
What?
The violinist yesterday
is Lin Qingzhuo.
She's the daughter
of my violin-making instructor
and just came back from Italy.
Yesterday, my instructor called to ask me
to take care of her
during her stay in China.
Recently, she has a theme song performance
in collaboration with me.
It's the project you dubbed.
And she needs to break
in that winning violin, too.
I have to make some adjustments with her.
So she hopes to live
in my place for a while.
I've agreed.
I'll pick her up tomorrow.
I'm telling you this in advance.
That's good.
I've long been preparing to move out
but hasn't done it until now.
Now I can spare a room for her.
That's not what I mean.
There're plenty of rooms here,
why are you moving out?
It's part of my plan to begin with.
Your competition has finished
and your health has almost recovered.
And my mom needs me back...
No, I mean...
But the show has just finished.
If you move out so quickly,
there will be rumors.
No one will notice.
But... It's near
your recording studio here.
Isn't it more convenient for you
to live here?
You must be Erduo.
I'm Lin Qingzhuo.
Hello.
Sorry for bothering you
and thank you for your hospitality.
My pleasure.
Didn't I say I'd pick you up tomorrow?
I'm bored alone in the hotel.
I was thinking
if I could come to work earlier.
I wanted to give you a surprise.
Did I scare you?
I'll leave you two alone
and go downstairs to make breakfast.
Shuwei, help Qingzhuo
carry the luggage upstairs.
Come downstairs for breakfast
when it's all sorted.
Thank you, Erduo.
You're welcome.
My parents heard that you've come back
and invited you to dinner at our home.
Really?
I really want to see them, too.
I have a tight schedule this time
and don't have much time to pay visits.
What are you doing?
Breakfast is ready.
Tell Qingzhuo to come downstairs.
She said she'd come soon.
How will you get
to the internal celebration
of New Journey to the West?
If you're free, meet me at my studio
and we can go together.
No, thanks. I have to record something
and I'll go with my colleagues.
Okay.
Shuwei, I brought you souvenirs from Italy.
Sorry, I have too much luggage
to bring you more.
I'm sorry, Erduo.
When I left Italy, I didn't know
you're here, too,
so I didn't bring you gifts.
Hope you don't mind.
It's fine. Not a problem at all.
You're so kind.
Erduo, do you know
that Shuwei kept growing taller
when he was in Italy?
After a while,
the clothes he bought before wouldn't fit.
In the end,
he bought clothes more often than I did.
That's not the case now.
I brought coffee beans from Italy, too.
I'll make espresso for you.
You can't.
Why?
You don't have moka pot?
It's easier to make Americano.
Let's have breakfast first.
I made two cups of Americano for you.
I remember that you only drank espresso.
At that time, I practiced violin
for over ten hours each day
and you were learning
to make violins from my dad.
Every morning,
we'd go to a café in Italy
for a cup of espresso.
We weren't used to drinking it standing then,
and people there would hurry us.
Espresso tastes great,
but it's not necessary.
But you never drank
other types of coffee in the past.
Habits change.
I'll go buy a moka pot then,
so you can have espresso
every day.
Thanks, there's no need to.
Do we have to spend the whole morning
discussing coffee?
Well, Qingzhuo, how about this?
We'll have Americano today
and have other coffee later.
I haven't tried espresso yet
and I want to have a taste.
I'll make espresso for you another day.
Enjoy your breakfast.
I have something to do upstairs.
Qingzhuo,
we'll drive Erduo
to her recording studio first,
then we'll go to my studio
to adjust the violin.
Okay.
You've finished?
Erduo, we'll drive you
to your recording studio first.
Get ready.
Erduo?
This beauty comes
to our studio often recently.
A violinist needs to
break in the new violin.
With the best violin maker
adjusting by the side,
perfect results can be achieved
as soon as possible.
Don't you trust our boss?
Of course I trust him,
but she's in love with him.
Hello, Le Tian,
did you meet the Senior?
How's she?
We met this afternoon.
She's nice.
Forget about that.
Do you still have your level test materials?
Yes.
I need them for consolidation
so of course I still keep them.
Great.
Can I borrow them to get a copy?
I've registered for the next test.
I wonder if I can learn
from your tips for the test.
Sure.
I'll sort them out
and bring them to you tomorrow.
You don't need to.
It's already so kind of you
to lend them to me,
how can I ask you to deliver them yourself?
If it's convenient for you,
I'll come and take them later.
Okay then.
Here you are. A gift for you.
You're too nice.
Of course I need to thank you
for lending me your test tips.
I walked past a cake shop
and bought the cake you like.
Thank you.
But there're a lot of materials
and I haven't sorted them out yet.
So wait a moment, please.
I'll wait outside.
Why wait outside?
Come in.
There're really lots of materials.
I need more time.
It's too late.
I don't want to cause you trouble.
I'm staying outside.
What trouble?
Come on.
Have a seat.
Anything to drink?
No thanks, I'm just here for the materials.
Okay then, wait a moment.
I'll go upstairs and bring them to you.
I think the two measures next
are still imperfect.
We can try more.
Okay. We will...
Excuse me...
Le Tian, I've...
Erduo, is he your friend?
This is my friend Le Tian.
He came here for study materials.
Enjoy yourself.
I'm taking the violin back to my room.
Who is she? You three...
Here are my notes.
Le Tian, want some water?
No, thanks.
I'll return them to you tomorrow
after photocopying them.
Look,
these two are the most important notes
I made in my everyday studies.
Those tagged are all very important.
Have a good read, okay?
Okay.
Bye.
I'm leaving then.
I'll see you off.
No thanks. I'll leave myself.
Take care.
Bye.
What's up?
Are you feeling guilty?
Why should I?
Le Tian was just here for the materials.
Can't he make notes himself?
Why does he have to
read other people's notes?
Ye Shuwei, can you talk nicely?
Which word of mine is not nice?
I mean...
Shuwei,
can you come?
I have something to discuss with you.
Erduo, make a cup of coffee for me.
Shuwei, good morning.
Erduo has left early.
You want coffee?
Just a minute.
Thanks.
Erduo, are you home?
[Erduo, are you home?]
Shuwei, it's late.
Let's go home.
[Dear Bei Erduo, you have passed the written test
of Tokyo Academy of Arts.]
[Please come to the designated place
next Tuesday for the interview.]
What happened?
I've passed the written test
of the voice acting school in Japan.
I'll have the interview next week!
You're overreacting.
You're so talented.
I knew you'd pass.
Congratulations, Erduo.
Thank you.
I didn't know you'd go to Japan to study,
otherwise maybe I could help.
Thanks, but you don't need to.
I've been preparing for it for so long
so I'm very confident of being admitted.
I'm here to return things.
Ah, my shoes for interview.
I don't know how to pick shoes for girls,
so I picked the ones
with the simplest design.
They're probably right for the interview.
Of course.
This kind of shoes
is very comfortable to wear.
Comfortable to wear and good-looking, too.
Thank you.
How did you know my shoe size?
I checked it visually.
Visual check?
Ten yuan.
You want some change?
No. You need to pay
because I delivered your shoes to you.
Mr. Ye, you're returning shoes to me.
It's different.
Okay...
Go back and get some rest.
Bye.
I have to prepare for the interview.
Bye-bye!
We're arrived?
There's one stop to go.
Sorry.
I'm so tired these days
and I didn't sleep well.
Who's the woman with Ye Shuwei that day?
That's Lin Qingzhuo, Ye Shuwei's friend.
Her dad is Ye Shuwei's instructor.
He hopes that Ye Shuwei can look after her
these days.
We've arrived.
Let's go.
I can go home by myself.
How will you get back?
I'll take Bus No. 4212. It's coming soon.
You go home first.
I'll wait with you.
No, thank you.
It's late. Go home.
Here are the materials.
Okay then, I'm going home.
See you.
- Bye.
Take care.
Okay.
How can I...
I'm leaving.
What's up?
What are you doing?
A two-timer living with two women?
Is this your business?
Did you think of Erduo?
What would she think?
In what capacity
are you asking this question?
I'm her...
I'm her friend.
Okay then.
Erduo's friend.
Thank you for your concern.
Listen,
Erduo is my girlfriend.
We'll sort out the things
between us ourselves.
It's not your business.
If you care about her,
please cherish her.
Don't take advantage of her kindness
to hurt her!
Thank you for your advice.
We'll be good.
Erduo.
Erduo!
What's up?
I have something to tell you.
After knowing you're going to study in Japan,
I contacted my friend there.
He works in the anime industry, too.
If they need voice actresses,
you can go have a try-out.
I've told him about you.
Thanks.
But don't bother, really.
I don't want others to see me
as someone who only gets there using connections.
Never mind.
I did this to thank you
for taking care of Ye Shuwei these days.
And I believe
you're talented enough for that.
We don't know how Erduo's situation
in Japan will be yet.
Forget about this for now.
Qingzhuo, I have something
about work to discuss with you.
Come with me.
Okay.
Good night.
What are you doing?
Tying my shoelace.
Aren't you wearing slippers?
Ah, yes.
No wonder I was...
My belly aches. I need to go to the bathroom.
♪I don't want to say my actions out♪
♪So that no one can see my sorrow♪
♪I never doubt every moment of life♪
♪For I stay true to my inner choice♪
♪I've always enjoyed silence♪
♪But I feel something is missing♪
♪I hear the sadness played deep down♪
♪I pass by you gently♪
♪How to grab you♪
♪I remember every time♪
♪You're always there for me♪
♪Days and nights go by♪
♪I'm alone in the world♪
♪Try hard to make you out of the wind♪
♪This song is me♪
♪You're unique in my heart♪
♪Hovering right now♪
♪All the stars surrounding my ears♪
♪Ups and downs of fingertips♪
♪Sing slowly from the strings♪
♪Leisurely echo with persistence♪
♪This song reminds me♪
♪You're always a firm choice of mine♪
♪I miss you at every moment♪
♪All the joy we have together♪
♪Like the heartbeat♪
♪So many stories are hidden♪
♪In your voice♪
♪And the most beautiful story♪
♪The one in my plot♪
♪It's happening right now♪