[English subtitles are available]
[My Journey to You]
[Episode 14]
Tell me.
Whose blood is this?
Young Master Shangjue.
This is what we found.
On the shoe soles, there's blood
and some shards of porcelain.
[Lasting Prosperity]
Shangguan Qian is Anonymous.
Why did she attack Lady Wuji?
Her target
is not Lady Wuji,
but me.
Young Master Ziyu
just happened to have sneaked out of the Gong residence at night
and Lady Wuji happened to have come to look for Young Master Ziyu.
That's why
Lady Wuji was implicated.
Lady Wuji treats me as her family.
I'm suffering more than anyone from her bloody disaster.
Shangguan Qian is a member of your Jue residence.
You have to take the blame.
I was negligent in management
and gave the villain
a chance to kill.
I should be punished.
But you
ignored the rules of the Gong residence
and left the Gong residence with Yun Weishan without permission.
How should you be punished?
My negligence was unintentional,
but you knowingly violated the rules.
You knew that once you became the Sword Wielder,
you can't leave the Gong residence.
The rule is that I can't leave Jiuchen Valley.
Don't subtly try to change the concept.
As the Sword Wielder,
I think I have the right
to take my wife out.
When my father was the Sword Wielder,
he took my mother out to look at the festive lanterns.
Your father was the Sword Wielder,
so he had the right to take his wife on a trip.
But you didn't even pass the Trial of the Three Realms.
How dare you call yourself the Sword Wielder?
And you and Yun Weishan are not officially married.
How is she your wife?
It's only a matter of time before I become the Sword Wielder.
Enough.
Now that you're in the position of the Sword Wielder,
you should know the rules that the Sword Wielder has to abide by.
You took Yun Weishan out of the Gong residence
without asking the Council of Elders for permission.
And you're still making excuses.
I'm really disappointed in you.
If you break the rules,
you should be punished.
Even if you're the Sword Wielder.
Later,
please go to the Council of Elders Hall's confinement room
and reflect on your mistakes.
Now is not the time to evaluate the right and wrong
of the Sword Wielder's actions.
The most important thing now
is to confirm if Shangguan Qian
is Anonymous.
She's indeed a suspect.
We need to interrogate her properly
in order to confirm it.
Elder Yue was killed.
The Jue residence promises to find out who Anonymous is.
During this period,
I've been suspecting that the killer was inside the Yu residence.
But now,
the suspect actually appeared in the Jue residence.
And
it's even the future bride
selected by Young Master Shangjue himself.
Gong Shangjue.
Don't you have anything to say?
Shangguan Qian has been detained in the prison.
Naturally, I'll interrogate her properly.
Also, you previously suspected Lady Wuji.
Now, her life is at stake.
Shouldn't you apologize for that?
It's still too early to apologize.
Shangguan Qian
might not be Anonymous.
We have solid evidence and a witness.
You still want to protect her?
Shangjue.
Did you
notice another problem?
There are two things that I'm puzzled by.
Firstly,
the blood left by Anonymous on the screen in Gong Ziyu's room
this time
was obviously left in a hurry.
She left
before the last stroke was finished.
And from the time I entered the Yu residence
to the time I entered Gong Ziyu's room,
there were no suspicious figures
or unusual noises.
The person was able
to escape without a trace
in my presence.
There are few people
in the world
who possess such Lightness skills.
Shangguan Qian
doesn't have such great Lightness skills.
So she's not the person who wrote the words in blood.
Then are you saying the killer
can disappear into thin air?
The one who left the words in blood
either has superior Lightness skills
or
she didn't leave the room.
That's ridiculous.
You were the one who said
that only you and Lady Wuji were in my room.
Are you pointing out
that you are Anonymous?
Do you still suspect Lady Wuji?
This is ridiculous.
Young Master Shangjue.
I really want to agree with your guess.
But I checked Lady Wuji's wound.
Her wound was on her back.
The cut was extremely accurate.
Someone must have
secretly attacked her from behind.
The sword was stabbed in with one thrust.
It couldn't have been done by oneself.
Lady Wuji's wound is very deep
and narrow.
It means
that the killer used a thin and resilient sword.
It's a weapon that's commonly used by Wufeng.
Wrong.
There was only a soft sword with blood in the scene.
This soft sword was hidden in the belt.
This belt
belongs to Lady Wuji.
Isn't that even stranger?
Lady Wuji
stabbed herself with her sword?
Elder Yue, be patient.
The second puzzling point
is even stranger.
Everyone should remember
that when the former Elder Yue was killed,
the Meeting Hall
was neat and clean
and everything was in place.
With Elder Yue's superior skills,
the fact that she killed him in one move
shows that Anonymous is highly skilled.
However, when Lady Wuji, who has ordinary martial arts skills,
was assassinated,
the room became a huge mess because of the fight.
If Shangguan Qian
had such a hard time dealing with Lady Wuji,
how could she have
killed Elder Yue in one move?
Right now, our conjecture is
that since the person could approach Elder Yue
easily in the Council of Elders Hall,
it must be someone who's close to Elder Yue.
But Shangguan Qian
is only a bride who just entered the Gong residence.
How could she have gone in and out of the Council of Elders Hall freely?
Even if she had a reason to approach Elder Yue,
Elder Yue wouldn't be defenseless.
Then why did Shangguan Qian
wander around in black clothes
and head to the Yu residence?
We don't know about that for now.
But I'll know the answer soon.
Young Master Shangjue, I hope you
won’t show mercy
just because she's the bride you chose.
I will definitely give all the elders an explanation.
But
I’m curious about one thing.
How did Elder Hua know
that the person in black clothes is a woman
and that she's injured,
and ordered
for all residences to be searched?
Um...
Who are you?
There is no woman with such martial arts skills like you in the Gong residence.
It was because the Yellow Jade Guardian by my side
encountered a suspicious person.
During the fight,
judging from her voice and figure,
he determined that she was a woman.
I see.
Since Shangguan Qian has been imprisoned,
we'll wait for the result of her interrogation.
Anonymous appeared again.
Lady Wuji was attacked.
The Gong residence is now heavily guarded.
I can't come here for the time being.
My return date is uncertain.
I'll resume with the unfinished research
when I come back.
If it's urgent,
you can fly this gold leaf kite in the air.
I'll come to you as soon as I see it.
Don't worry.
From Xiaohei.
Who will miss you?
You're not Jin Fan.
The servants just informed
that the elders locked up the Sword Wielder in the confinement room
to get him to reflect on his mistakes.
He won't be back tonight.
Miss Yun, he asked me to tell you
to rest early.
Don't worry about him.
If I hadn't suggested to leave the Gong residence...
Don't blame yourself, Miss Yun.
It was also the Sword Wielder's decision
to leave the Gong residence.
He has accepted
the punishment willingly.
I'm just telling you what he said verbatim.
It doesn't represent my personal opinion.
Young Master Ziyu doesn't blame me.
But I know
you must have resentment towards me.
Miss Yun, you shouldn't have wandered around indeed.
Not only did you make Young Master Ziyu worried,
but also caused trouble.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize to me.
I'm just a Green Jade Guardian.
I can't afford it.
I just hope that...
you wouldn't let the Sword Wielder down from now on.
He...
is a foolishly good person.
Rest early, Miss Yun.
Wait.
Have you found the injured woman
after searching the residence tonight?
Yes.
It's Shangguan Qian.
The wine bowls are still full.
It seems
that it hasn't gone that far yet.
You've endured the whipping and clamping.
But...
this is just the beginning.
The razor in my hand
is durable and sharp.
It was forged by the Gong family's hidden weapon forging technique.
This razor is called
the Cicada Razor.
It can cut every piece of meat
into slices as thin as a cicada's wing.
Just slicing a leg
would take an entire day.
It's worse than death.
And this mask.
Such a beautiful face.
What a pity.
And this bowl of wine.
The razor and mask just now
are not worth mentioning
when compared to Brother Yuanzhi's poison wine.
So,
are you going to confess?
Trust me.
You won't be able to take it.
As long as you tell the truth,
I promise you won't suffer.
Can you keep me alive?
If I tell you,
would you believe me?
Just tell me your perspective.
I'll make the judgment myself.
I'm not a Wufeng assassin,
nor am I the so-called Anonymous
who you're talking about.
But
I'm not the daughter from the Shangguan family indeed.
Then,
who are you?
An orphan of the Gushan Sect.
I entered the Gong residence
to protect myself.
The Gushan Sect?
Yes.
Back then, Zhuo Mei from Qingfeng Sect
fell in love with my uncle,
which met with strong opposition
from the Qingfeng Sect Leader, Dianzhu.
To force the Gushan Sect to hand over my uncle,
Dianzhu, who was already seeking refuge with Wufeng,
led the Wufeng assassins
to Gushan Sect
and wiped the sect out.
The entire Gushan Sect was wiped out.
I've never heard
that there were any Gushan Sect descendants who survived.
My father hid me in the secret tunnel.
That's how I survived.
Later, I wandered around
and was homeless.
Fortunately, I was saved by the Shangguan family
and they raised me.
The Shangguan family didn't want their daughter to marry into the Gong family.
In order to repay them
for raising me,
and for myself,
I pretended to be Shangguan Qian
and got married in her stead.
I swore
that I'd avenge my father
and my sect.
On the Lantern Festival that year,
I ran into a gangster.
You were the one who saved me.
That's why I came up with the plan to enter the Gong residence
to have someone to rely on.
Only with the power of the Gong family
can I take revenge.
Then what does this have to do with
you trying to assassinate Gong Ziyu?
Gong Ziyu?
My target was Wuji.
Why?
Because I heard that day
that you suspected that Wuji is Anonymous.
And every one from Wufeng
is my enemy.
When I went to the Yu residence,
I saw Wuji in Gong Ziyu's room.
So I observed her from behind the window.
But I saw
that Wuji had a soft sword in her hand.
That sword was thin and tough.
It's no different from the sword that people from Wufeng usually used.
So I was sure
that Wuji is Anonymous.
But I was discovered by Wuji.
She's stronger than me in terms of martial arts skills.
Since she's stronger than you in terms of martial arts skills,
why
was she still stabbed by you?
Wuji did it herself.
She deliberately let the sword escape from her hand
and I grabbed it,
and she charged towards me to get stabbed.
You mean
she got stabbed on purpose?
Yes.
Is everything you said
true?
It's
all true.
Do you really want me
to torture you?
Everything I said
is true.
I'm not afraid of your torture.
I have proof that I'm from the Gushan Sect.
Untie me.
I'll prove it to you.
I'm already seriously injured.
If you are even afraid of me in this state,
you don’t deserve your reputation in the martial world.
Prove it.
♫You whisper loving words in my ear♫
♫Yet we have no choice but to part♫
♫I hold the blade in my hand♫
♫And slice through the night♫
Are you feeling better?
Brother.
I'm fine.
Did you find anything out from interrogating Shangguan Qian?
Brother, tell me.
Did Shangguan Qian confess?
Although she didn't poison the porridge last night,
I still don't believe her.
She told me she's not from Wufeng,
nor is she Anonymous.
Brother.
Do you trust her this much?
Shangguan Qian
has the birthmark of the Gushan Sect on her body.
This birthmark
represents the bloodline of the Gushan Sect.
There is a clear record of this in their family record.
Although the Gushan Sect has been wiped out,
there are relevant files
in the Gong residence.
I have reviewed them and verified it already.
Gushan Sect?
The descendants of Gushan Sect may still be from Wufeng.
Over these years,
there have been many righteous sects in the martial world that have fallen and joined Wufeng.
Indeed.
That's why I need to wait until Wuji wakes up
to hear what she has to say.
After all, there are so many puzzling points
that still can't be explained.
I don't trust Shangguan Qian,
but I don't trust Wuji even more.
You shouldn't believe
what she says.
Young Master Yuanzhi.
Young Master.
Lady Wuji is awake.
Brother.
I'll go with you.
No need.
Focus on your recuperation first.
Whether it's Shangguan Qian or Wuji,
I have my own plans.
Jin Fu, lead the way.
Lady Wuji.
You're awake.
Anonymous' target
was actually me.
I was the one
who implicated you.
I'm glad you weren't there.
At my age,
it's no big deal if I die.
But you still have to be responsible for the future of the Gong family.
Lady Wuji.
Calm down.
Luckily, Anonymous from last night
has been caught.
They are interrogating her now.
You've been avenged.
They've caught Anonymous?
Yes.
It's Shangguan Qian.
I heard you woke up,
so I came to visit you, Lady Wuji.
Thank you.
May I ask
if you remember
what happened last night?
Lady Wuji just woke up.
Her head isn't clear yet.
The doctor will determine
whether her head is clear or not.
Lady Wuji,
do you remember anything?
I also want to know
what happened.
A few days ago,
a small batch of fox fur arrived.
At night,
I wanted to get you to pick one
to make a cloak for you.
But Ziyu wasn't around.
Just now, Ziyu told me
he caught Shangguan Qian.
I didn't expect her
to be Anonymous.
She's not Anonymous.
She's not Anonymous?
Have you interrogated her?
If she weren't Anonymous,
why did she sneak into Yu Lineage
and stab Lady Wuji?
Shangguan Qian said
she heard our conversation during the day.
So she wanted to test Lady Wuji
and see
if she was Anonymous.
Ridiculous.
Is this
the soft sword you hid in your belt, Lady Wuji?
Yes.
Lady Wuji,
were you hurt by this soft sword?
When I arrived at the Yu Lineage,
I found the blood on the wall.
Shangguan Qian arrived
before I could call for help.
She attacked me
without any reason.
I can only draw my soft sword to fight the enemy.
I was no match for her.
She snatched my soft sword
and stabbed me in the back.
But Shangguan Qian said
she was no match for you.
It was you
who purposely ran into
this soft sword.
Enough.
Shangguan Qian was caught red-handed.
It's fine if you don't suspect her.
But you easily trusted
the nonsensical words
of a desperate prisoner.
This is not the brain
you should have, Gong Shangjue.
My father used to love to say,
"If one's not stupid, one must be evil."
I don't think you're stupid.
During the day,
I only just mentioned that Lady Wuji
might be Anonymous.
On that very night,
Anonymous attempted to assassinate her.
Isn't this
too coincidental?
Actually, this soft sword
can prove that
Lady Wuji isn't Anonymous.
What do you mean?
Elder Yue’s wound was thin and narrow.
But the width of this sword
is obviously longer than the width of Elder Yue’s wound.
So,
this sword is not the weapon used to kill Elder Yue.
And I think
there should be no reason
for Anonymous to change weapons
when they killed Elder Yue.
You're right.
But...
How did you know
how narrow Elder Yue’s wound was?
Unless
you're very familiar with
the murder weapon
we're looking for.
I told her about it.
When you were not here,
we were talking about this.
I told her
Master Yue
was killed by Wufeng's thin sword.
Shangguan Qian is indeed an orphan of the Gushan Sect.
The birthmark of the bloodline can't be faked.
With the previous inference,
it is enough to prove that
Shangguan Qian is not Anonymous.
Since she's not Anonymous,
then...
who left the words
on the screen?
I'm afraid the real Anonymous
hid in the dark
and deliberately left the blood writing
to confuse the witnesses
and cause panic.
Shangguan Qian
injured Lady Wuji.
But her action was understandable.
The torture she
received in prison
will be considered her punishment.
Can we
release her now?
Her background
is really pitiful.
The former leader of the Gushan Sect
was loyal and righteous.
It was also a rare sect in the martial world
who always supported the Gong family.
But in the end, they were killed
by the Qingfeng Sect and Wufeng.
Since
this is a misunderstanding,
I think
we can let her out.
Shangguan Qian
belongs to Jue Lineage.
Shangjue,
handle it yourself.
Yes.
Right now, Anonymous
is still at large.
I'm afraid they will continue to create trouble.
Should we
consider activating the Infinite Heat
to threaten Wufeng
and ensure the safety of the Gong family?
No!
No.
This
is not a good idea.
Elder Xue,
what is
the Infinite Heat?
Why have I never heard of it?
You will know about it
once you pass all three trials.
Sword Wielder, you should start
working on the second trial soon.
I'm here to visit Miss Shangguan Qian.
Young Master Shangjue,
Miss Shangguan is seriously injured.
Fortunately, it’s only external.
I prescribed some medicine and ointment.
She'll be fine after half a month of rest.
Okay.
You may leave.
Yes.
Looks like
you still showed mercy.
The fine brew I made
remains unutilized.
No hurry.
We'll use them eventually.
Not now,
nor on Shangguan Qian.
Sir.
Young Master Yuanzhi.
Miss Yun Weishan is here.
She said she wanted to visit Miss Shangguan Qian.
Hmm.
Let her in.
Yes.
Wait.
Did she bring anything?
Yes.
She brought a brocade box.
Stop.
Recently,
there are a lot of incidents in the Gong residence.
The Jue Lineage is heavily guarded.
My brother has ordered
to check everything that goes in and out
of the Jue Lineage.
Miss Yun.
Please open the box.
Hey.
Leave the box.
It's just an empty box.
Leave it.
Are you okay?
It's nothing serious.
Thank you for your concern.
Shangguan, your hands and feet are so cold.
It seems that your body is still weak.
I brought some ginseng for you.
I passed it to the servants.
The ginseng is of high quality.
It will help with your recovery.
Remember to eat it.
Thank you, Sister Yun.
I didn't expect you to be
an orphan of the Gushan Sect.
Is Lady Wuji really Anonymous?
Yes.
It seems that we're connected by fate.
I heard that your master is
Zhuo Mei.
You live in the Yu Lineage,
you spent the longest time with Wuji.
I don't believe you didn't suspect her.
It really is fate.
And now, we meet each other here.
What a coincidence.
I hope we can spend more time together in the future.
My family was destroyed and I was alone.
All these years,
I have no one to share my thoughts with.
Whether you really don't know or are playing dumb,
Wufeng's spies
won't interfere with each other.
If you don't mind,
you can come to me often.
Have a good rest.
I won't bother you.
I'll visit you again.
Brother.
Are you still worried about Anonymous?
Anonymous did not complete
the final stroke on the wall.
Obviously, they stopped when someone came.
If this person could come and go without a trace right under my nose,
I'm afraid the whole Gong family
is no match for Anonymous.
I've brought Yun Weishan's brocade box.
It's ginseng inside.
Shall I check it?
Yes.
Check both the ginseng
and the brocade box.
That's my brother.
I've packed the luggage for tomorrow.
Do you have anything else for me?
We haven't caught Anonymous yet.
I think Gong Shangjue
is still eyeing Lady Wuji.
When I'm not around,
you must protect Lady Wuji.
Don't give him the chance
to slander Lady Wuji again.
Understood.
That aside,
did you find anything
in Housekeeper Jia's house?
Housekeeper Jia's wife and child have moved away
one month before
the former Sword Wielder and Young Lord were killed.
What's more suspicious is...
According to the neighbors,
someone looked for his wife
and child before us.
Was it someone working for Gong Shangjue?
I think so.
The two people who came
also asked
why
Old Man Jia's family moved away.
Their family
moved away before the Laba Festival.
It seems that they moved away before the former Sword Wielder was killed.
There was another strange thing.
What?
Do they have any relatives?
They seldom have contact.
Because of their son.
People around here
were afraid of him.
What's wrong with his son?
Old Man Jia
got a son at such an old age.
He was very happy.
But two years ago,
his son suddenly got seriously ill.
No one could cure him.
They almost prepared a coffin for the kid.
Later, a physician from the Gong family cured him.
He came back to life?
The child
was cured, yes.
But since then,
he became a little weird.
How so?
That kid
became very strong
all of a sudden.
When he was playing with other kids,
he shoved
a little girl away
by a couple of meters.
Her head bled from the shove.
Isn't it scary?
So scary!
Housekeeper Jia's son was seriously ill.
In the end, he was cured by a physician from the Gong family.
But after he recovered,
he became very strong.
Keep investigating.
Understood.
We're already in the wild, right?
Yes.
It smells like grass.
I can smell the moisture in the wind.
We must have
left the secret tunnel.
Lord Sword Wielder.
We're here.
You can take off your blindfold now.
Elder Yue.
This is not the front hill.
So,
just call me Young Master Yue.
Young Master Ziyu, please come with me.
[Jue]
Young Master Yuanzhi.
Are you disappointed I'm not my brother?
Don't pretend to be pitiful.
My brother can't see it.
Young Master Yuanzhi, you must be joking.
Look at my wounds.
Do I look like I'm pretending?
Are you hoping that
if my brother sees you
looking so miserable,
he'll take care of you?
I know my place.
I've been injured for so long.
Young Master Shangjue has never visited me.
Unlike when you were injured,
Young Master Shangjue was always by your side.
I'm his brother.
You cannot even begin to imagine
the bond we have growing up.
If one day,
Young Master Shangjue would care for me
even a tiny bit as much as he cares for you,
I'll be satisfied.
I don't think you're the kind
to be satisfied so easily.
There is a word carved
between your eyebrows.
Greed?
Or ambition?
Wufeng.
Yuanzhi.
I heard from the servants that
you came here.
Don't worry, Young Master Shangjue.
Young Master Yuanzhi didn't disturb my rest.
He just came to check on my injuries.
I didn't say
he was disturbing you.
I was here to check on you either.
Why don't you take your medicine?
Thank you.
Yuanzhi.
Yuanzhi?
Why are you drinking alone?
Wine is not medicine.
Of course I drink it alone.
Should I wait for someone to feed me instead?
You're angry about that?
Young Master.
Young Master Yuanzhi.
News from the base of the valley,
about the thief on the night of the Lantern Festival.
Brother, you were right.
That night, the thief did not steal Yun Weishan's things
by coincidence.
It was indeed to distract Gong Ziyu.
The thief is a habitual offender of Jiuchen Valley.
According to him,
Miss Ziyi instructed him to do so.
Ziyi?
I can't believe Yun Weishan went to meet her.
Did she not find her dirty?
Have you investigated Ziyi?
Yes.
Her original name is Ye Xiao.
Her parents and brother used to be slaves of a wealthy merchant in Jiangnan.
Then, they were sent to the human hunting range.
What's that?
It's a game for the leisure and rich.
They put people in the forest
and hunt them like animals.
Her father and brother died in the hunting range.
So the human trafficker sold her to Wanhua Pavilion
and named her Ziyi.
She is also a pitiful person.
So Yun Weishan
went to see her
because she was jealous?
Of course not.
If she were just jealous,
there was no need to
fake the theft
and distract Gong Ziyu.
Yun Weishan is Gong Ziyu's legitimate wife.
If she wanted to establish her place,
she should have
brought Gong Ziyu with her.
Send two jade guardians
to keep watch in the Wanhua Pavilion.
Yes.
Elder Yue,
what is the content of the Second Realm's trial?
No hurry.
I have a few questions
to ask Miss Yun first.
Ask her?
Shouldn't it be me?
Elder Yue,
if you have any questions,
please go ahead.
The boat has docked.
[Gong residence back hill - Yue residence]
Let's go ashore first.
[Air Frost]
[New Snow]