She is not my wife.
What she is wearing
is my wife's skin.
My wife!
This...
My wife.
So not all the people in Luoxian Town are locals.
That's what it means.
Spider-Man?
Anti-gravity?
Why did you expose it?
Madam.
What exactly are you, madam?
Protect the master.
Be careful.
Madam.
Madam,
what exactly are you, madam?
Notice updated.
Monster updated.
Corpse Puppet.
Rules updated.
The transformed Corpse Demon is indistinguishable from a normal person before awakening,
unless triggered by a keyword.
Weaknesses: Fire and sunlight.
I see.
I told you
there's definitely something wrong with this town.
Madam.
She is no longer your wife.
This is a Corpse Demon,
crafted from a stolen body.
It hasn't fully developed yet.
Otherwise,
it can only be destroyed by True Sun Fire.
Lin Mo,
remember,
you owe me one.
Find your second and third brothers.
We have work to do tonight.
Wait.
You cannot enter the Lin Manor without an invitation.
Also,
there are other non-human entities in Luoxian Town.
I'm telling you this for free.
We are even now.
Thanks.
Let's go.
Madam.
Village Head.
I know you are very sad right now,
but I have other questions to ask you.
Stop torturing him.
What do you want to know?
I'll tell you.
Fine.
Village Chief,
please hurry and lay your wife to rest.
It's getting dark.
Let's go to my house first.
Master Feng.
I have arrived home.
Thank you for escorting me.
Meeting Miss Xiaolan today
is truly
a blessing I earned in my past life.
Looks like my second brother is getting me a sister-in-law.
Be quiet.
Watch the show.
I will take my leave then.
You should rest early too, sir.
Then,
I will also take my leave.
I wonder when I can see you again, Miss.
Miss Xiaolan,
Why are you so sad?
Mr. Feng,
I'm afraid I won't be able to see you again.
Why is that?
Mr. Feng,
You'd better not ask.
You can't fight them.
Although I am not a hero,
I have some cultivation.
In this Luoxian Town,
there is no force that I fear.
He is completely manipulated.
Are you really willing to help me, sir?
This woman doesn't look like a good person.
Please come into my humble abode for a chat, Mr. Feng.
Okay.
What do we do now?
Sneak in.
Are you saying
the anomalies in Luoxian Town
are all related to the Lin Mansion?
They come to the town from time to time
to arrange ghost marriages and take women.
I'm afraid my little sister
is already on their list.
So I'd rather not go herb gathering
and stay to protect my sister.
Then,
what's with the funerals?
When red lanterns hang at the Lin Mansion's gate,
it means a ghost marriage to take women.
When the lanterns change color, it's a funeral
to collect the dead from the town.
I just heard the village head say
his wife was taken away
and came back as a corpse demon.
Also,
what happens to the people taken by the funeral procession?
Will they also be like the village head's wife
and be turned into corpse demons?
This is the first time I've seen this kind of situation.
Before, I accidentally
heard the herb shop owner say
the coffin-carrying procession is ghost soldiers passing through.
Mortals cannot look,
or their souls will be taken.
So we never dared to look.
Then in the town,
how many women were taken by the ghost marriage procession?
What happens after they are taken?
Probably dozens.
And none have ever returned.
It seems
the source of all monster troubles is in the Lin Manor.
I must find a way in.
How many men did you bring?
Don't worry, Boss.
I brought everyone who knows how to handle a weapon.
We definitely have enough men.
When do we make our move?
We can't use force.
Those people can't be defeated
just with a little martial arts.
Then, Master,
what should we do?
Don't get too close.
They can sense us.
Lie in wait nearby.
We will wait until those two brats are alone
before we strike.
Okay.
Boss.
But let's not strike too late tonight.
Lin Manor.
Lin Manor opens its doors tonight.
I know.
So, have you figured out how to get into the Lin Manor?
No.
Then what are you thinking about?
I was wondering
what that Beijing girl from today
is doing right now.
Aha!
I knew there was something going on between you two.
What? What are you thinking?
Scumbag.
You've only been here a few days,
and you're already hooking up with a foreign woman.
You really don't give people any peace anywhere you go.
Who am I hooking up with?
I was just wondering
if she would test the rules I told her today.
Besides,
we're getting a divorce anyway.
Say that one more time.
Stop making a scene at a time like this.
Also,
today,
that girl who called you young master,
who is she?
Her?
She was my personal maid when I was in the Lin Manor.
She grew up with me.
Her name is Mo Xiaolan.
A maid?
How do you know that?
You...
Did you awaken your memories from before transmigrating?
Now is not the time to discuss this.
We must figure out a way to get into the Lin Manor.
This place is affected by the rules of Luoxian Town,
so magical powers cannot be used.
Even if we get into the Lin Manor,
our methods won't be able to handle it.
Feng.
A moment of a spring night is precious.
Since you are willing to help me,
then I
will not decline.
What are you doing, girl?
I just helped you.
Why are you messing with me?
Shh.
Humans and demons walk different paths.
If you weren't lusting after beauty,
how could you have fallen into my trap?
Your vital essence
is a great tonic for me.
Don't worry.
I will be quick.
How long are you three going to just watch?
We were just afraid
of interrupting your business.
If you were any later,
I would have been sucked dry.
Little lady,
my second brother is too skinny.
Why don't you
consider me?
I can't bring myself to do that.
So it's a wood demon.
It feeds on mortal essence to cultivate,
isn't afraid of the sun,
but fears fire.
I've never heard
of a demon that isn't afraid of fire.
You finally took the bait.
Brother.
If we could use magic here,
we wouldn't be so restricted.
Without this rule,
what demon would risk coming here?
Move away.
Burning it with fire
is easy enough.
I have plenty of strength
to play with you slowly.
Today is a full moon.
Her demonic power will only grow stronger.
Do you have any other way?
Yes.
Right?
Isn't that right?
Yanhua,
get to work.
What's with this morning bell?
It hasn't been used in years.
Suddenly ringing in the middle of the night.
My magic is restored.
It seems this rule is true.
Who is ringing the morning bell?
It should be
that girl from Beijing causing trouble.
A person from Beijing.
Why does she know so much about the demon troubles
in our Daqian?
The Governor of Huaiyang said
she is a demon refiner from Beijing.
So
she knows no less than we do.
I'll go take a look.
Wait for me.
I'll go with you.
Let's go.
I'll wait for you at home.
Why did the bell suddenly ring?
It's you.
Without some preparation,
how would we dare intrude on your territory?
Monster,
your time is up.
My powers are restored.
I feel full of strength.
Step back.
Alright.
Before the bell stops ringing,
we must take her down.
Wait.
She is stalling for time.
Let's hurry.
I know how to get into the Lin Mansion.
Your target
is in the Lin Mansion.
You can't enter the Lin Mansion without an invitation.
You think I don't know that?
The Lin family is arranging for their second young master, Lin Fan,
to have a ghost marriage.
A ghost marriage requires a banquet.
Find a way to attend the banquet, and you can enter the Lin Mansion.
Interesting.
How do you know so much about the Lin Mansion?
That's none of your business.
If you want to enter the Lin Mansion,
I have a way.
On the condition that your people stop bothering me.
Xiaomei.
Xiaoying.