=The Demon=
=Episode 4=
You have a lot of nerve showing up.
Chief Fan,
I know what happened to you.
Shen Wangchen, I'm warning you,
think twice before you speak.
I can help you.
What?
What tricks are you pulling now?
Drop your act.
I know
everything you're plotting.
You're ambitious
and righteous,
but you lack understanding
of rites and morality,
and discernment of good and evil
in people's hearts.
I'm willing to lend you
a helping hand
to actualize your great ambition.
Shen Wangchen,
just speak plainly.
Don't play dirty tricks on me.
I can help you
become a great king admired by all
and ruling the land.
I don't need you to teach me that.
Get lost!
Guards.
Shen Wangchen!
Shooting star!
Oh, Heaven.
Please let the king treat me better
and make me a legendary demon hero.
Your wish will come true.
What are you trying to do?
I... I'm warning you,
you're playing with fire.
Help! Help us!
Be careful, Your Majesty.
Save us, Your Majesty!
Be careful.
This one looks good.
You'll do.
Your Majesty!
Wait, wait!
Maybe let him throw us away.
As long as we don't die, we'll run back.
Enough!
I... I...
I promise you.
See you tomorrow.
Don't get hurt, Your Majesty.
We're not afraid.
We're not afraid at all!
Young master,
will this plan
really earn Fan Dayao's trust?
Isn't it too dangerous?
Can your body
handle such a big plan?
Isn't there an easier way?
Don't give me so much next time.
But young master...
Say no more.
We must cast a long line
to catch a big fish.
Fish?
What fish?
When she's in cat form,
she won't guard against me.
Your Majesty, you've overstrained
yourself recently.
You need to watch your kidneys.
No.
I can't just sit on my hands.
Stop massaging.
I'll scout the enemy myself.
Switch legs, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
(Perfect timing.)
(I'm going to)
(get to the bottom
of who you really are.)
(Why are you touching me again?)
(You!)
(Why are you always)
(so handsy?)
You're quick to recover.
(Oh no! I forgot about that.)
Looks like this acupoint
does help you recover.
You enjoy this so much.
Since we're fated,
we're friends.
I'll give you a name.
(A name?)
(Today is the second day
of the twelfth month.)
A long wind blows through a clear sky,
like the breath of spring.
(Be gentle.)
I'll call you "Xiao'er".
(Xiao'er?)
(That's awful.)
Xiao'er.
(You came up with a name like this)
(after all that poetry?)
Only if
you can find me the cat demon.
(Very good. Carry on.)
Someone wise said
the cat demon can help me
turn misfortune to fortune.
(Turn misfortune to fortune?)
(That's your reason?)
(This massage feels nicer.)
(It'd be good)
(if he could massage me more.)
(No! I mustn't fall into this!)
(I'm going to conquer)
(the demon realm.)
(How could I be swayed)
(by a mortal's gentle touch?)
(You'd better watch yourself.)
(How to Become A Good King?)
How to become a good king?
Exactly.
Do you know what you need
to become a good king?
I know.
Iron fists, iron strength,
and an iron heart.
It's knowledge
and the trust and respect of the people.
I don't like reading
human books.
That's a shame.
Wait.
(The Path of Overlords)
The Path of Overlords.
(The Art of Kings)
The Art of Kings.
That's perfect for me.
Come.
Bring them all here.
You must memorize these two first
before reading the others.
Otherwise, it'll backfire on you.
All of them?
(A Good King)
Young master,
these are classics of governance.
Why rename them?
To strike at the vital point.
This is Fan Dayao's weakness.
(The Path of Overlords)
First is timing.
Second is the advantage of place.
Third is...
Quiz time. What's the third point?
Shen Wangchen!
If you don't study hard,
you won't be able to protect them.
First is timing.
Second is the advantage of place.
Third is harmony among people.
Then, four directions, above and below,
left and right, front and back.
Clear every doubt
by asking as many questions as possible.
The heart rules over the body.
The ruler leads his minister.
Your Majesty?
You must be tired now.
Take a rest.
Rest now,
or I'll kill you.
No matter what you do,
you must be patient
and calm.
Chicken Spirit.
The work here is endless,
and no rest at all.
Everyone's been wanting to leave.
But the king is overbearing.
No one dares to speak up.
This time,
with Mr. Shen's help,
we can finally escape her control.
Exactly.
Let's go and find Mr. Shen.
I almost fell for his trick.
Why am I memorizing these?
I must figure out a way to kill him.
Rong Momo,
I'll give you one last chance.
Pour this Truth Serum
into that mortal's food.
Yes, Your Majesty.
(Once I find out)
(the source of your divine power,)
(I'll find your weakness.)
(You're doomed, Shen Wangchen.)
Today,
I've prepared some liquor
as a reward for your hard work.
You've suffered enough
these days.
Your Majesty,
it's our good fortune
to serve in Fort Aowu.
Thank you so much, Your Majesty.
Let's drink to Her Majesty.
To Your Majesty.
Cheers.
Of course,
the one I must thank most is Mr. Shen.
We may get off on the wrong foot,
but without Mr. Shen,
I'd never have known
to care for my subordinate.
A toast to you, Mr. Shen.
You're too kind, Chief Fan.
Cheers.
Come.
Eat to your fill. Don't be shy.
Have some fish, Mr. Shen.
Mr. Shen,
I have a few questions
I'd like to discuss with you.
Yes, please.
Mr. Shen,
are you the son
of the lord of Moyuan City?
You're wise, chief.
How old are you?
Twenty-five.
How many people are in your family?
Why are you asking that?
I just mean...
After putting up with this tigress
all these years,
we finally get a decent meal.
She only bullies us
because she's bigger than we are.
Bah!
She must've been struck by lightning
to come to her senses.
Young master.
What's wrong with them?
No, Your Majesty.
I'm just telling the truth.
Truth Serum?
Rong Momo!
I added it to the fish.
You have to believe me, cousin.
Cousin?
You're her relative!
Rong Momo.
What's Truth Serum?
To make you spill the secret
of the divine power so I can snatch it.
My goodness.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
I'm feeling dizzy.
When the Truth Serum
is mixed with the liquor,
it makes people drunk instantly.
Chief Fan, your Truth Serum
really works wonders.
How dare you!
Shen Wangchen, you're cunning indeed!
I put it in the fish.
How can it be?
Chief Fan.
You...
What are you trying to do?
Why do you need my divine power?
To kill you, wipe out Moyuan City,
and avenge the demon race.
Life has been unbearable
under this tigress.
Mr. Hiss,
flattering her all day
must be rough on you.
Ms. Chickie,
I can't stand this place
another day.
Do you really think
they followed you
willingly?
How dare you all!
Chief Fan,
why don't we find another place
to discuss the divine power?
I want to quit!
I just can't do this anymore.
Just you wait.
Shen Wangcheng, you...
Tell me the truth
about the divine power.
I want to quit!
♪Where did I lose my direction?♪
♪Only emptiness is left♪
♪Restless, sleepless, we part ways♪
♪As sorrow slowly grows within ♪
♪Tears can't heal, smiles still ache♪
♪Because my heart's with you♪
♪Your gaze melted the haze♪
♪Waiting so long for your return♪
♪The setting sun reminds me of you♪
♪If the clear sky is torn
by storm and rain one day♪
♪Tears will flow♪
♪I will still wait here with no regrets♪
♪Waiting so long for your return♪
♪The setting sun reminds me of you♪
♪In the amber desert,
you turn away with tears in your eyes♪
♪I'll welcome you back in a red dress♪
♪Waiting forever with no regrets♪