That's why I decided
I wanted to become
a police officer that day.
- I'm sorry.
- Um...
I should excuse myself now.
Arikeeno.
What's going on?
You're looking sad.
Huh?
It's nothing. I'm okay.
I was just being indecisive
because they all look good.
Maybe these. I'll take these two.
You're sharing with your boyfriend?
Excuse me?
Things are not going well with him?
Huh?
Min yi shi wei tian.
What was that? Min yi... what?
It means that the most important activity
for a human being is eating.
It's a Chinese proverb.
If you eat together,
there will be no problem.
But this is for--
Matching stomachs make a good couple.
Cheer up, sweetheart.
Thank you, Auntie.
Satoru...
I don't want to be an obstacle for you.
But I can't hold back anymore.
You are more important to me...
Incoming call...
Sir, I'm heading out to do
some legwork on Volunteer.
You're going to Wang Jianbin's factory?
Make sure you coordinate
closely with Koda.
But sir, I can...
go on my own.
You might find this surprising,
but she's sharp-minded
and quite the woman of action.
It's "better roughly right
than precisely wrong," as they say.
Work together in cooperation.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me, Tayama. Could you please
wipe this table clean nicely?
Yes, sir.
Don't you think Lieutenant Iiyama
is acting strange today?
I can't blame him.
An extra burden is going to be put on him.
You mean, the person who's coming today?
Yeah.
What is he like?
If I were to describe him in one word,
it will be an "ogre".
Did you say an ogre?
You mean, a monster?
For us, he could be like a devil.
Devil?
Or he may be a dragon
that could carry us to heaven.
Dragon?
You're not making sense at all.
Whatever he is,
our division will have a handful for sure.
Hi, Mr. Shack.
- You're late.
- I'm sorry.
Were you already worried about lunch?
Well, you know...
Why are you coming with me
instead of Mr. Arikino?
I'm so sorry.
Just don't stand in my way.
Lieutenant Iiyama
is totally overestimating you.
Oh, here she is.
Hello, Mengqi.
It's great to see you.
I brought some food.
How about you join us?
You're here again? Stop it!
Last time, you didn't take
the Guangdong food I brought,
so today, I brought Sichuan mapo tofu
with rice.
Last time?
You come many times, but I don't say.
I don't want to talk about Volunteer.
Mengqi, wait.
Go ahead and call me
when you feel like you want to talk.
My lunch was in there, too.
So far, she's the only clue we have
to how Volunteer operates.
Can you somehow talk to Lin Mengqi?
If she could call me at least,
I think I could somehow manage
to pull it off.
I wish she would...
Oops. I'm sorry.
You look pretty good with that green hair.
I'm sorry, but I can't speak Chinese.
Forget it. Um...
Where’s the International
Investigation Division?
- Uh...
- I think he's looking for something.
INCOMING CALL
MARI KODA
Tell him I'm getting an interpreter.
I'm sorry. My bad.
I don't need an interpreter.
Lieutenant Agawa?
Lieutenant?
I'm your partner starting from today,
Greenhead.
You're my partner?
Is everyone here? Then, please go ahead.
I'm Hiroya Agawa.
‎INTERNATIONAL INVESTIGATION DIVISION
As of today, I've been assigned
to Higashi Shinjuku Police Station.
I'm joining the International
Investigation Division
of the Organized Crime Section.
All right.
Lieutenant Agawa was transferred
from the Shinbashi West's
Community Affairs Division.
But prior to that,
he was with the International Division
at Kamiazabu Police Station.
He's fluent in Chinese
and has a lot of experience.
He's what you call
"a veteran of many battles."
Koda, make sure to learn
as much as you can from him
while you're working together as partners.
I would be more at ease on my own.
Mitsui's team continues to track down
the safehouse of the suspects
responsible for the recent
shop robberies in the area.
And Shiraishi, your team will...
Come on, let's go.
Yes?
‎SHINJUKU SERIAL CONVENIENCE STORE
‎ROBBERY CASE
- Next, we will...
- Something important is...
- Hey, wait.
- Wait.
Those two have left.
What?
Lieutenant, our briefing is not over yet.
The Detective Division
is leading the case, right?
Our division is just there
to fill up the room.
We get things done faster
by gathering intel on the field
instead of sitting in meetings.
Boss, when are we going?
- Mr. Agawa, everything alright?
- Mr. Agawa, it's great to see you.
These two scumbags have been robbing
convenience stores.
Do you know them?
No, I don't.
These are familiar faces, aren't they?
I'm surprised they talked.
They're from Shanghai.
The suspects are
from Northeast China, right?
So, they don't get along very well.
You can't lump them all together
into one category.
Each province has its own language,
and people grow up
in entirely different environments.
That's interesting.
Should we go check out
their potential safehouse?
No, thanks.
Greenhead, relay the information
to the incident room.
Pardon me?
We need to let
the Detective Division shine.
Yes, sir.
Miss Koda finally has a partner?
I thought no one except Mr. Arikino
could handle her.
When you think about it,
I wonder why Miss Koda
favors Mr. Arikino so much.
They often eat together, don't they?
They get along
because they have "matching stomachs."
That's it.
TOKYO METROPOLITAN POLICE DEPARTMENT
Hey, Arikeeno.
I thought you might be somewhere
around here.
Are you doing all right?
Yes, I am.
I'm sorry about the other day.
No problem.
You'll have this, right?
Well, I've already eaten.
Are you kidding me?
I bought two on purpose.
Here we go.
- There's someone new at our division and...
- Um...
I'm sorry, but I have to go.
What's the matter? Is something wrong?
If you want to talk, I'll listen.
No. Nothing's wrong.
But...
Excuse me.
Wait, Arikeeno.
I had no idea that Mari was there
at that scene.
Have you talked to her since then?
No.
She doesn't know anything about me.
That's because you don't tell her
anything, right?
You know something
that's always bothered me?
You always hold back like that.
That's such a bad habit of yours,
Arikeeno.
Leave me alone.
I think she is well aware
that you are holding back.
But she still keeps the same stance
with you.
People like that are hard to find,
you know?
There you are. You found this place okay?
Yes.
Have a seat.
What would you like to drink?
I'm going to go do some shopping.
Eat these for now.
See ya.
- See you.
- Bye.
I heard
that you now have
a Chinese speaking investigator.
Yes,
we actually do.
Since I don't get those random
work requests from you anymore,
it's made my life easier.
I knew you'd say that.
Oh, I know! Listen now.
Do you remember Lin Mengqi?
She's the one who introduced Volunteer
to Wang Jianbin,
the man who protected the baby.
I went to see her so many times
to ask some questions,
but she just wouldn't talk to me.
I bet you've been trying to build
a rapport with her using food again.
How did you know that?
Were you watching me go around
carrying food?
I don't need to see it to know.
I just wish the folks at headquarters
were more serious
about investigating Volunteer.
Then I wouldn't have to be out here.
Anyhow,
Mengqi seems to be avoiding the police
and wouldn't talk.
And I'm not sure how much Japanese
she can speak.
So, I was wondering
if you could come on Monday and--
Actually, on that day,
I have something else going on.
I didn't even finish my sentence.
All right, then.
If you are not going to help me,
I'll ask Lieutenant Agawa.
Agawa?
You mean,
Hiroya Agawa?
Um, yes.
He got transferred last week
and we are partners now.
Do you know anything
about Lieutenant Agawa?
You should never trust him.
YAKITORI, LOCAL SAKE, DRAFT BEER, SOURS
Hey there, Lieutenant.
I heard you're back in the field.
Congratulations.
Is it Volunteer?
Your promotion makes me happy too.
You know that people in higher positions
tend to keep their secrets well.
Where are you now?
Not far from you at all.
The police has changed a lot
and has become rigid.
So, I'm moving around.
Let's make money together again.
You'll hear from me soon.
TOKYO METROPOLITAN POLICE DEPARTMENT
What are you doing?
Hello, Arikino. It's been a while.
It's all right.
Will you excuse us for a minute?
Yes, sir.
Why didn't you let me know
that Agawa would be back in the field?
You didn't even properly greet me.
YUKIHIRO TOYOZUMI
SUPERINTENDENT
Why would you send Agawa
back into the field?
It's just a routine transfer this time.
You're lying.
I personally haven't taken my eyes
off Hiroya Agawa yet.
I will investigate
and expose him this time.
Four years ago,
headquarters dismissed my report,
saying that it lacked objective evidence.
If you couldn't bring charges to him then,
why would you try now?
You know the Volunteer case in Shinjuku?
It feels just like the case
Agawa was involved in four years ago.
If Volunteer makes a move,
Agawa might make a move too.
How would you investigate?
Are you going to have his partner
spy on him again
like you did with Oda?
If you involve Sergeant Koda,
I won't forgive you this time.
Shin-Okubo is a town
with many gods, isn't it?
With many gods?
There's such a variety of food
from different countries here.
There are Christian churches.
There's a Hindu temple,
and even a Taiwanese Taoist temple.
Of course, Japanese Shinto shrines
are there, too.
I guess it means
you need spiritual support
when you live far away
from your home country.
Wherever people have their gods,
that's also where their community gathers.
But anyway,
people who can believe in something
wholeheartedly are strong.
You should never trust him.
Lieutenant,
do you know Volunteer?
Volunteer?
I was wondering if you came across
that name when you worked
at Kamiazabu Police Station.
I may have.
Is that the guy who's called Volunteer
because he makes free passports
for illegal residents?
Yes. That's it.
Do you know anything about him?
That's an urban legend.
I've heard about him somewhere,
but it never went beyond rumors.
Or do you have a reliable source
of information now?
So far, what I know for certain is...
Zero! There's nothing.
But I have my own theory.
Given the scale of their operation,
I believe it's an organized operation.
They make passports for free
and they ask for favors in return.
That's their approach.
For example,
that's how they recruit mules.
In Wang Jianbin's case,
he was asked to take a kidnapped child
out of the country.
That's how they send people who are
illegally overstaying to the mainland
and sell them to human traffickers
in exchange for a reward.
If they can be used as mules as well,
it's killing two birds with one stone.
I haven't found out
when Volunteer started operating in Japan.
But there's a high chance
that there are already many victims.
We need to expose
the full extent of the organization
as soon as possible.
Well, even if your hypothesis
is correct, I doubt
headquarters would take any action.
Why wouldn't they?
The victims are invisible to us.
Illegal residents are not even allowed
to live in Japan in the first place.
The ones that are targeted
are not Japanese,
and the victims are not killed in Japan.
Whatever happens
to those illegal residents
has nothing to do
with ordinary Japanese citizens.
Oh.
Excuse me.
Hello?
I can't...
I can't talk about Volunteer.
It's difficult.
Mengqi, is that you?
Mengqi?
Please bring Officer Oda
from Kamiazabu Police Station.
I will talk to Officer Oda.
Officer Oda? Do you know his first name?
Other people, no.
Only to you and Officer Oda.
Okay.
Meng--
Mengqi?
Oda?
Satoru Oda from Kamiazabu Police Station?
Do you know him?
Officer Satoru Oda was my former partner.
He was?
And...
So...
which station is he at now?
Oda is...
He's dead.
He died four years ago.
YOYOGI PHANTOM KILLER INCIDENT
"Yoyogi Phantom Killer Incident"?
THE PERPETRATOR WAS CAUGHT IN THE ACT
"...were awarded the Police Chief Award."
Oh, that's Arikeeno.
And Lieutenant Yanagi?
He's the one from...
Lieutenant Yanagi.
What do you need this early?
I'm sorry,
but there's something I need to ask you.
What is it?
How did Sergeant Satoru Oda die?
I know it's insensitive of me to ask.
You were his supervisor
when he was a new recruit
at the station, right?
Why do you bring this up now?
Eight years ago,
you arrested the Yoyogi Phantom Killer.
YOYOGI PHANTOM KILLER INCIDENT
And you received
the Police Chief Award together.
Actually,
I was at the scene when it happened.
And Sergeant Oda helped me.
I don't know
how you even found the courage.
Not everyone can face a criminal.
Why are you giving me such a dirty look
when this could be a nice reunion?
I bet you've heard about it.
A detective from Kamiazabu Police Station
had been misinterpreting a lot
during questioning and interviews.
And that Arikino leaked the information.
Yes, I have.
EXCLUSIVE SCOOP:
THE DARKNESS INSIDE THE POLICE FORCE!
"DELIBERATE MISINTERPRETATION"
AN INSIDER OF KAMIAZABU POLICE STATION
An attorney for a Chinese suspect
had concerns
about the police's interpretation.
He requested the audio recording
of the questioning sessions
during the trial.
Kamiazabu Police Station stated
that the sessions were not recorded.
But in reality,
the audio recordings did exist.
Part of the recordings
was leaked to a weekly magazine,
exposing the misinterpretation.
Two detectives were mentioned
in the article
and were condemned by the media.
One of them was the detective
who interpreted during the questioning.
It was Lieutenant Agawa.
What?
It was Lieutenant Agawa?
And the other one was...
his partner at that time.
It was Satoru Oda.
One week after the article was published,
Oda did...
He committed suicide.
So now you know.
You now understand why Arikino
always keeps people at a distance.
He was despised
and hated by everyone at the station.
But still,
why did people think that Arikeeno
was the one who leaked the information?
How was he related
to this misinterpretation incident?
At that time,
Arikino was with the Security Division
at Kamiazabu Police Station.
He had been requested
by Superintendent Toyozumi
to conduct an internal investigation
into Agawa.
So the only suspicious person
who was familiar
with the inside information was him.
That kind of look is typically given
to perpetrators.
Are you repeating the same thing?
Lieutenant Agawa.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
You want to talk about four years ago?
Yes, I do.
Well, how should I say?
If you look into Oda's case,
you're inevitably led to that incident.
I should have told you about it earlier.
Forgive me.
Sure.
I don't know if it's appropriate
to say this,
but misinterpretations can happen
no matter how hard you try.
Misunderstandings can happen
even between Japanese speakers.
So, when more than two languages
are involved, it's inevitable.
What's important is how you respond
when you realize you've misinterpreted.
Can we acknowledge our mistake
and offer the correct interpretation?
I'm just repeating
what someone I know always says.
Ouch, that hits a nerve.
I failed to do that back then.
I deserved to be taken off the field
because of that.
But here I am.
I somehow made it back on the field.
Maybe it's God.
Maybe God has given me one last chance.
What do you mean, "last chance"?
When you reach this age,
you start to see, you know...
You see the mountain.
The mountain?
You begin to see the last mountain
you can climb.
What is it?
Oda gave me a look like that, too.
I know you're debating,
Greenhead.
You're not sure if you can trust me
as a partner.
ODA
I'm sorry for contacting you
about your brother so suddenly.
It's all right.
These are his personal belongings
that I've kept.
Our mother got rid of everything left
at our parents' house because it was
too hard for her to see it.
Can I touch them?
Go ahead.
How about things like his cell phone
or day planner?
The police took them,
and we still haven't gotten them back.
They said they couldn't find
an SD card or something.
They asked me many times
if it was among his stuff.
An SD card?
Yes.
I see that your brother was a smoker.
He may have been, but he never smoked
in front of his family.
- I'll make some tea.
- Thank you.
- By the way...
- Yes?
Was your brother in a relationship
at that time?
He never discussed
that kind of thing with his family.
I see.
Please bring Officer Oda
from Kamiazabu Police Station.
- I will talk to Officer Oda.
- Oda is...
He's dead.
So now you know.
You now understand why Arikino
always keeps people at a distance.
Hello? Lieutenant Yanagi?
What's the matter?
What?
I know you're busy. I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
It's about Lin Mengqi.
She was murdered.
She was murdered?
With a single slice
to her right neck artery.
They say
it's probably not an amateur's job.
I think she was killed
because I contacted her about Volunteer.
MARI KODA
So, I can't back out.
I can't back out anymore.
You know what she said?
She said she could talk about Volunteer
only to Officer Oda
from Kamiazabu Police Station.
To Oda?
Yes.
Arikeeno,
you were close to Officer Oda, right?
We were at the police academy together.
I looked into some records.
And I found out that Officer Oda
had questioned Mengqi
for violation of Amusement Business
Control Act.
That was probably
when she thought she could trust him.
Hang on a minute.
Do you think the murder of Lin Mengqi
is connected to Oda?
To figure that out,
I need to clarify a few things.
About four years ago.
I need to know what happened
when Officer Oda died.
I also want to know
what kind of person
Lieutenant Agawa really is.
About the misinterpretation incident
Lieutenant Agawa was involved in.
And the truth about the information leak.
The truth?
Four years have passed already.
Arikeeno, there's something
I want to know more than anything.
I want to know why you're pretending
that you're the one
who leaked the information.
Let me be honest with you.
I don't really care
about the police's internal information
being leaked to the press.
But something bothers me.
It bothers me that people hate you,
thinking you're the one
who leaked the information.
Because I know
that you'd never do anything like that.
I knew that this would happen.
Huh?
I knew that some day
you would grill me
about what happened in the past.
I knew that you would start saying
that I'm not that kind of person.
When Oda died, I swore to him
that I would bury this case forever.
But still...
Please stop digging into my past.
I beg you.
I'm sorry, but we're closing.
Whoa, taking a trip down memory lane!
It's been five years already, I guess.
They came here together on opening day.
Baijie!
Hey, Satoru!
- Congratulations on your grand opening.
- Thanks!
You can drink from this bottle
even when you come here alone.
I'll never come here alone.
Satoru?
It's you, isn't it?
- It's been ages!
- Hey, you guys.
How have you been?
I've been great.
Long time no see.
Yeah.
You haven't changed at all.
Really? You two haven't changed either.
Mr. Arikino.
You might find it surprising,
but he's very delicate on the inside.
So, take good care of him.
Huh?
I've been so focused on Arikeeno's past
that I'm losing sight of who he really is.
I understand that he's been affected
by losing someone precious to him.
But why on earth
did he have to leave the force?
And why would he shut his heart
so tightly?
What happened between him and Officer Oda?
They may have looked happy,
but whatever happened between them
stays between them.
Maybe you're right.
But...
But I want to know more about Arikeeno.
The series of misinterpretations
appeared to be intentional.
‎NEXT STORY
Will you let me know?
It was Satoru Oda, wasn't it?
Satoru probably couldn't tell him
because he cared about him too much.
Are you planning to do
something by any chance?
FOUR YEARS AGO
‎Don't push me!
Hey, Oda!
Yes, sir.
We have a session.
Yes.
Many women have been brought in
from the raid to an illegal
adult entertainment establishment.
We're expected to verify
their identities one by one
and check with immigration
for their eligibility.
What's wrong?
Got something on my face?
No, sir.
What's going on? You look pale.
Come on, let's get it done.
Yes, sir.