♫ Because I'm this kind of person, not so very good ♫
♫ Just your normal l average man ♫
♫ I'm not a weak person, never was sensitive until I met you ♫
♫ It was strange when we first locked eyes ♫
♫ You made me realize I'm not the same ♫
♫ You made someone like me understand ♫
♫ You are the meaning of my life ♫
♫ You've changed the life of my day and night? ♫
♫ I like the way I am ♫
♫ I like it when you're close to me ♫
♫ Do you know why? I've changed because of you ♫
Hey, why are you in the way Toei?
You can't enter.
Khun Ran for bids you
How can he not let me?
I have deliveries for him. There's a bunch in the trunk. Go see.
Khun Ran said if it's you,
you can't enter whatsoever.
In that case,
can I put the stuff right here?
If it's convenient for you,
go ahead.!!
Toei.
4,000.
4,000?
-Mm.
-Nope.
He's greedy.
Max, 5,000.
5,000.
-5000?
-Mm.
Hurry!
Hurry up and get out of here!
This country is in shambles is because
of corrupted people like you!
Go! Hurry! Drive away!
Come on Toei.
I have morals you know!
Thanks.
Grandma, can I go help Mommy work?
You can't. P'Pim will be busy today.
They have to finish making the doll today
It'll be done right?
Yes.
Why don't you two come with me instead?
It's almost my birthday.
I plan to have a party but you two don't have outfits yet.
I'll take you to get your outfits made with P'Da.
Then afterwards we can go get ice cream. Sounds good?
Okay!
Oh Jam.
The kids will step out with me.
Go let Uncle Rong know
Sure.
Kids,stay with Mommy first. I'll be back
Mommy.
Where's Daddy?
I don't know.
You're busy everyday.
Once I'm done working, I can come play with you all day okay?
Promise?
Mafeuang, Mafai.
Let's go.
We will miss you.
Very much?
Thank you.
Come.
Bye bye.
-Bye bye. See you later.
-Bye bye.
Bye!
This you won't see.
So how would you know how I feel?
Is all of this fabric here?
Yes.
Is it? Okay you can start cutting then.
As Mode A and Model B.
Okay that will be it.
Oh.
You're here early.
I had deliveries
but the owner won't let me enter.
P'Ran?
Yeah.
He forbids you but you're still persistent
I want to see Pim.
You can't see her so you come to see me instead.
Yeah.
Be careful dear.
Hello.
-Hello Lada.
-Oh hey Nai.
-Hello.
Why are you here?
I haven't seen you in a while.
Yes.
P'Ran probably doesn't want to see me
so he forbade me from entering the farm.
-Oh Lada.
-Yes?
Can you take the twins measurements?
I want an outfit for them for my birthday party.
Sure.
Come on.
- I'll take you guys upstairs.
-Please watch them.
Nai.
Come talk with me outside.
Sure.
I'll be selling the dolls tomorrow at the association.
If you want to see Pim,you can see her there.
What about P'Ran?
I'll find a way for him to catch up later.
Why are you helping me?
I'm not helping you.
I think Pim wants it to be like that.
Why?
I think there's some kind of deal between her and Ran.
-A year?
-Yeah.
You're thinking the same as me right?
It's like there's an agreement between those two.
Yes.
If it's what I'm thinking
whether Pim stays or go is no different.
She has no future.
If you like her,
they will probably break up after a year.
But it won't be strange if she breaks up with him now and starts dating you.
We just have to find out what agreement they have.
Pick up the pace
It's finally done!
How's it going? Did you finish?
Yes.
P'Toei.
Gosh what?!
Toei.
What?!
Ma'am.
Help pack the dolls in the bag.
Yes.
Once you're done,deliver them at the event. Make sure you get there in time.
Yes Ma'am.
Go to the event with me Pim.
In case the people there are interested.
Yes.
Can't you go faster Uncle?
I have other business.
You really want to go to that association thing?
You knew that so why did you schedule to meet the customer?
I didn't but Khun Chu gave me the order.
Aunt Chu gave you the order?
Correct.
You go help in front of the shop
In case there's more orders.
Don't you want the money?
Yes.
By the time the one year is up and before you go,
you should be earning a lot of money.
Let me ask. Why one year?
What you'll learn today will be more than what you will save in a year.
Why don't you ask Khun Ran?
He should have a better answer than me.
-Hello Aunt Chu.
-Hello.
Pim.
-Setting up the shop?
-Yes.
Good. I'll help.
Sure, Come on.
What's wrong?
Hey
There's an event happening with the association. You never missed it.
I want to stay home today.
Hmm?
You're tired of attending events?
Is something wrong?
You haven't gone out in like a couple days now.
Hey.
Why don't you go see Ran?
You guys will become distant
Go get dressed and head to the event.
I think Ran will be attending the event
I want to stay home today.
Too lazy to get dressed.
Why do you want to be home?
Dress up nicely and go see Ran.
But l have nothing to talk to him about
Then tell him I will offer him corn seeds for free.
But the villagers must grow them and sell the corn back to me.
Let's see what Ran thinks.
Go, Get up. Hurry
Get up! Go.
Okay.
-Hello Madam
-Hello.
Aren't you Khun Kullachat's daughter?
Yes.
I was your father's customer.
You've opened up your own factory now?
Pim is working with me.
How lucky of you to have her help you.
I still remember her father's doll
were good quality, affordable. l ordered like 300 of them.
Yes. Thank you.
Let's go discuss the details at the cafe
-Yes.
-Right this way.
-Okay.
-Please.
Wow.
The daughter of the owner of a doll factory?
But right now I'm just an employee.
Why did your dad stopped?
The factory burned down.
Mom and Dad didn't survive.
Just me and brother that did.
Sol had to...
move in with Grandpa at the farm
Pim.
Are you okay?
I just miss my parents
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have asked.
Don't cry.
Look at these sheep.
People still remember and said they look like they just came out of your dad's factory
Did you forget
that your parents are always with you?
In here.
You say it's not.
Khun Ran!
You say it's not
but what I saw it is!
Nai likes you.
Seems like you like him too.
You're able to think for yourself so why are you asking me?
Can you stop speaking " Thai "to me?
However Is peak is my business.
In that case, however I speak is my business too right?
That's your business.
If I say I love you
and want to call off that contract,
I will do everything to have you stay with me.
Will you marry me for real this time?
Hey!
Don't let go of my hand.
I won't let go!
Khun Ran!
P'Nai call the ambulance! Khun Ran got shot!
Please be okay Khun Ran.
I have an answer!
I have an answer Khun Ran!
Open your eyes!
Open your eyes! Don't lie still
Don't lie still!
Khun Ran!
The job is done.
I don't owe you anything now
Is he dead?
I couldn't do another hit
because people came to help him
If he's not dead,
the debt is still on the table.
What a shame.
He should have died.
I told you to kill Pim so why did P'Ran get shot?!
Why won't you answer me?!
You gave the order.
But I told you to kill Pim.
He probably missed the shot.
The nature in you never misses!
You're the one that told him to kill P'Ran didn't you?!
Yes.
You have no right to do this!
I do.
You want to kill Pim
because she married Ran.
I want to kill Ran
because he's in my way of happiness
And since the deal to coexist is off,
whatever I want to do
I will do.
I will file a report.
Try me.
That clip
isn't just for me to watch.
You...
-You are--
-Evil?
You know me best.
I've missed you.
Let's go talk in my bedroom
Let go!
Do you wanna do it here
or go do it quietly in my room?
Don't let anyone disturb me.
I want to be alone with Orn
This happened because Ran helped you and your brother!
If Ran dies,
just know that it will be your fault!
I'm sorry.
I didn't want it to turn out like this.
Drink some water first.
Thank you.
Nai likes you.
Do you want to reconsider?
Leave now
so you won't create more problems for us.
No need to wait for a year.
-I took out the bullet already
-Okay.
But the patient lost a lot of blood.
AB Rh negative blood type is very rare.
The hospital ran out too.
I can give him some.
AB Rh negative blood type?
Yes.
What do I have to do?
Follow me.
You!
Whether we live or die, you don't seem to know anything!
What?
I'm hungry!
What's there to eat?
Nothing!
You don't know that our boss was shot and is hospitalized right now?
Gosh, he's only injured.
He didn't die!
Why is your mouth like this?!
Let me kick you just once!
Why are you stopping me?!
Le time!l
Mom!
Come here!
Get up!
Don't! i Don't!
Mom stop! That's enough!
-What?!
-That's enough!
Are you still human?!
He saved your life
and you're gonna talk like this?!
You asshole.
Go pack up and leave right now!
You son of a bitch!
You bastard!
Auntie.
You're just a servant.
If you want to kick the brother of your boss's wife.
I think you need to be more than a servant.
Are you using your mouth to talk?!
Do you want me to use my feet?
-Stop.
- Why are you stopping me?!
He deserves to get kicked!
So he can stop talking shitty!
Don't mess with him.
Khun Ran shouldn't have saved him.
Snake!
think they're back.
Your purse.
Oh.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
How's Khun Saran doing?
Still not good.
Where's Pim Khun Danai?
Still at the hospital.
Noi.
Pack some clothes.
Have Toei or Rong take it to the hospital for Pim.
Sure.
Thank you so much Nai.
You're not worried about Khun Saran?
I know you're bad
but I didn't think you would be this bad.
Believe me
there's still some good in me.
You should know it in your heart.
No one will be hurt at all
if everything didn't start with you
Khun Saran's family?
The patient is doing a lot better.
We'll be moving him to the recovery room.
Yes.
Thank you!
You've been sleeping for days now.
When will you wake up?
Can you wake up to hear the answer to your question?
I want to marry you
and l promise
never to let go of your hand.
Lunch Khun Orn.
I'll put it in front of your room then.
How will you survive if you won't eat anything?
Bunga.
Yes?
She didn't eat anything at all?
Yes.
How long?
A few days now.
Khun Orn refuses to eat anything
I knocked on her door but she wouldn't open it.
Orn.
Hurry!
The patient overdosed.
Nus.
I bought you dinner.
Come eat.
I bought extra for tomorrow too.
You got paid and this is what you want me to eat?
The money
is saved for the rent, water, and electric bill.
We can't splurge.
Why?
It's the end of the month where you get paid so we should be eating good food!
We're not rich.
We need to save!
Save?!
I used to live an easy life!
I can pay whatever I want to wear and eat!
But now l have to spend only five, ten baht on things?!
Then get a job! Help me earn some money!
-So you'll have money to spend!
-l want it easy!
If I knew I was going to struggle, I wouldn't have come!
If you want it easy,
you don't want to work, you want money to spend then find a new man!
Thank you
for not letting go of my hand.
What are you doing?
Can you come up and sleep with me?
No.
You'll be in pain.
Cuddling you
will make me heal faster.
It hurts?
I'm sorry.
You see?
I told you you were going to be in pain.
A little.
Can you scoot closer?
I've missed you so much
By the time you woke up.
do you realize how long you've slept?
No.
But it feels like
I haven't hugged you in so long
If it's that long.
do you have an answer for me?
If you can marry-me for real.
I think l heard you say yes
But I don't know if I was dreaming or not.
You weren't dreaming.
Can you look at me?
Will you marry me?
Nodding
means okay?
Yes.
How's Ran doing?
Still not home.
I think he's not awake yet.
Can you visit him?
Why?
If he's not awake yet,
go make him not wake up anymore.
But I went to shoot him just like you told me to.
I thought you said it will be over?
I told you if he's not dead,
the debt isn't off.
But if I do it right now
Pim will know that it's me.
If he won't die
then you will.
Why did you do this to yourself?
I don't want to wake up anymore
You shouldn't have brought me to the hospital
Because of Ran?
Or because of his wife?
Latching on to him like a tick
If she was n't around
you will be much happier right?
You won't hurt yourself either.
If you want him.
you have to get him
Don't care about whether it's right or wrong.
If you really ran out of options,
my guys can help end this problem.
Just let me know.
I will help you.
You ran out of money?
Is that why you're back?
You can leave.
I came to visit you but you're kicking me out. Isn't that kind of rude?
To someone like you,
I don't need to have manners!
Get well soon.
Take care of the people around you.
If you know you don't suit P'Ran,
then break up with him!
You're pregnant.
♫ The reason we got to meet today ♫
♫ is because something happened and that is I love you ♫
♫ It can only be a dream, I can only think of you ♫
♫ Because I know that one day I will have to wake up ♫
♫ When I open my eyes, you might not be there that day ♫