♫ Because I'm this kind of person, not so very good ♫
♫ Just your normal l average man ♫
♫ I'm not a weak person, never was sensitive until I met you ♫
♫ It was strange when we first locked eyes ♫
♫ You made me realize I'm not the same ♫
♫ You made someone like me understand ♫
♫ You are the meaning of my life ♫
♫ You've changed the life of my day and night? ♫
♫ I like the way I am ♫
♫ I like it when you're close to me ♫
♫ Do you know why? I've changed because of you ♫
Really Toei?
Yes really.
Khun Ran wanted to drop something off for Grandpa Ruj.
So he had me bring the greens from the farm.
-Oh the one you had me go pick?
-Yes.
So what happened with Grandpa Ruj?
What did Boss say?
He said...
he wants to kill someone.
Huh?! Kill someone?!
That's right.
Why are there so many problems?
Grandpa doesn't seem well.
Plus P'Vee keeps spending money like it's some piece of paper.
Will Boss really kill someone from that family?!
I think so.
From the looks of it, he seemed really serious!
No!
-What?!
-Who is your boss going to kill?!
-I don't know.
-I didn't see.
You don't know? You didn't see?
So what were you guys talking about?
Khun Ran told us to come fix the fence, He said the rope came off.
Yes.
-Is it this one? Yes it is!
-You're not going to tell me?
Fine.
Hey!
What are you doing?!
If you won't tell me, I will untie all the ropes!
You won't be able to do it if you're not crazy!
Will you tell me or not?
Khun Ran will go kill your brother!
P'Toei!
If we don't tell her, she won't stop bugging us and we won't get our job done!
Where are you going?
Go see your boss!
We're gonna be in trouble!
It's your fault! It has nothing to do with me!
Hey you.
How did you get in? Why didn't you use the front porch?
I came to see Saran.
You need an appointment to see him
You can't just crossover whenever you want to see him
I can wait.
I won't let you wait.
You should leave.
You can come back another day.
It's fine.
I'll talk to her first.
Don't you need to go check the plots that will be planting today?
It's fine.
I can talk to her first.
Have a seat.
You said you were going to kill my brother?
You know how your brother is.
You might have power around here
but it doesn't mean you can hurt anybody you want!
There's laws in this country, Do you know that?
If there's a problem, just talk it out.
If you don't like something, then I'll
have P'Vee come apologize to you
What?
You have money so you think other people's lives are meaningless?
People who can think like this isn't human!
And how do you know I was going to kill your brother?
I heard.
That depends if that person you heard it from is reliable or not.
I don't need to answer you.
If you're here to talk about this then leave.
Fine I'll leave.
But I'm going to go file a report.
If something happens to anyone in my family,
you once made a threat.
Be careful not to get charged with perjury.
He probably bribed the whole police station in this area to say I would dare commit perjury.
Your subordinate said so himself and
you're gonna say you didn't say it.
What a thick face!
Where's Grandpa P'Vee?
I haven't seen him.
Grandpa.
Two people must sign it?
Vee.
-The usual?
-Yes.
On the rocks.
Oh Vira,
you wanna move some place else?
May be we'll make money faster.
Sounds interesting
You're already rich
Why do you care?
I have money but l also want freedom
What do you think Vira?
I'm in.
Nus.
Get up.
Right now.
What is it?!
Go inside the house, Don't wait up.
Where did you go with Nus?
To have a drink.
P'Ran, just let Vee go.
What's your deal?
We went to have some fun.
Someone who isn't fun like you don't like that right?
Think about your sister, Will she be happy or not?
You're a thoughtless brother.
P'Ran!
Enough. That's enough
If you can't go home on your own
then I'll drop you off.
-P'Ran!
-Come.
P'Ran!
Early in the morning like this,that knuckle face probably isn't guarding his grass yet.
Speaking of the devil My sheep haven't eaten the grass yet!
What is this?!
Let me go!
P'Vee!
- P'Vee!
-I better not see your face again!
Hey!
Why did you hit P'Vee?!
You think you can do anything to us now that Grandpa isn't here?!
Hey, you're really going to try and kill my brother aren't you?
What are you?
You have money, power, but no heart.
You think you can do whatever you want?!
Fuck off!
My family can't compare to how much your family has!
But you will never be superior!
Karma catches on like 5G now.
Just wait and see. Karma will catch up to you!
I want to buy this whole farm
I won't sell it.
I rather starve to death than sell it to you!
Name the price.
You don't want to keep a land that is mortgaged right now
-Sell it and take the money.
-l told you,
I won't sell it!
I will never sell it to a person like you!
That's fine.
I can wait.
If you don't like me so much,
sell it and move someplace else.
P'Vee.
Our farm is being mortgaged right now.
What do we do if we don't sell it?
We can't afford to buy back the land.
Pim.
Trust me.
I can handle this.
This is a bank withdrawal slip
Just sign it.
So I can take out the money to pay the installments.
Here'syour1,500,000
Take it.
Thank you Sia.
Here.
The power of attorney and land sales contract that l have signed
The only thing missing is my sister's signature
In conclusion you're selling the land to me for 1,500,000
Another 500 K that you have to pay back the bank.
That's right Sia.
Even when the rancher Saran came to buy it from me, I didn't even sell it to him.
las sure you this time
you will get to humiliate him completely.
Good,
That will be satisfying.
Here's 500K.
For the loan agreement,
at the end of the contract it says you will
give me your sister to pay off the debt.
Thank you Sia.
Auntie.
Can l have half a kilo of the pork bone?
Going to boil it for the dog?
I'll pick ones with some meat on them.
Auntie.
One kilo of Samgyeopsal.
I don't have that!
There's only my foot, you want that?!
Auntie, calm down!
So what do you want?
One kilo of pork belly.
It's that simple.
I don't have any Samgyeopsal.
It will actually be nice that you
give your shoe to him to boil.
It must be sticky
like having rubber teeth.
Pim!
It's me!
Go sh! Are we really neighbors?!
This is yours. 45 baht.
-Okay There's a lot of meat on it.
Your dog will like it.
Thank you Auntie.
See ya.
Pork bones for the dog.
Yeah.
I'm the dog.
Here's yours.
Auntie!
This is your shoe! Gosh!
-I ordered Samgyeopsal. You know?!
-Yeah!
200.
Pim! Pim!
-Pim!
-What is it?
Do you want to come over for some barbecued pork tonight?
No.
I don't want to see your boss.
Gosh! We're eating it in the backyard.
Khun Ran won't go there.
Just come. It'll be fun.
Fine.
I'll bring some vegetables.
See you.
Why so many things?
Orn.
You came to see Ran?
I brought the stuff needed for Nus's birthday party here first.
Since you're here, do you want to stay and join me for a meal?
Sure.
Noi, make extra for Orn too
Taew.
-Go call Ran to come eat
-Okay
Taew.
Can you go put the dress in the guest room?
Sure.
Ran is here. Are you hungry Ran?
Orn came to drop off some stuff for Nus's
birthday sol invited her to eat with us.
You go ahead.
I'm heading back to the farm with Uncle Rong.
Really?
The grapes have been infested lately
So Ran has to check in on it often
It's okay.
-Excuse me.
-Sure.
What is it Da?
Did you forget about the dress you ordered?
If you forgot your order, l will follow you to your house
Yeah l didn't forget.
I came to drop off some things at Nus's house first.
You want to see Nus or P'Ran?
P'Ran left to the farm.
He guards that farm better than a house dog.
Gosh you.
It's noon.
Let's go have lunch.
I'll bring you your dress, Send me the location on Line
Okay Sure thing.
If you had ordered and forgot
I was going to expose you during live.
Your shareholder probably doesn't mind.
Can even loan it for free.
Nus doesn't mind but I mind!
I'll hang up now, See you at the restaurant.
Wire me the money for the dress too.
Okay.
Auntie
Da had me go take a look at Nus's dress
I probably can't stay for lunch anymore.
Oh really?
That's okay.
You go do what you need to do.
-You don't need to make extra now Mom
-Oh
How come?
What do you think?
Once Khun Ran left, Khun Orn changed her mind real quick.
She sudden had errands to do.
She probably wants to eat with Khun Ran.
More like eat Khun Ran.
Let me smack you for once!
Why do you joke around?
Who says I'm joking Mom?
I'm being serious!
I even heard her say Boss guards
the farm more than a house dog!
Did Khun Chu hear her?!
I don't think so.
She was having fun talking on the phone.
Is at near her and I heard with my own two ears!
You were being nosy right?
Yes.
Gosh!
If Boss marries this girl,
we are bound to grow chrysanthemum all over the farm!
Chrysanthemum?
What's that?
It's a gold --
That beautiful yellow flower dear.
Ohh...
Pim.
I'm going to step out.
Oh.
You won't eat pork porridge first?
That's okay.
See ya.
Hey!
Why didn't you tell me first so
I wouldn't have to make extra?
I forgot to invite you for the barbecued pork!
All done.
Shall we go eat something delicious in town then?
Sure. We should go to our usual place.
Sure.
When did P'Vee and his sister become close?
Auntie.
Pim will be joining us.
Okay.
The more the merrier
It's rather fun.
When did you invite her?
I saw her at the market this morning.
And?
I saw her buy pork bone to cook I took pity sol invited her.
Pork bones?!
What can you do with that?
May be she's boiling it for a dog.
Pim only has sheep no dogs.
Oh.
That's true?
It's good you invited her.
Ever since her grandfather died, Pim must be struggling.
Uncle, you go ahead.
I'll be back.
Okay.
Hey! Hey! Are you guys done gossiping?
I'm hungry, Is it done?
Let me look
Hey!
This collection is nice.
Good designer
Sure.
Hey Da.
Why don't you start your own business?
A shareholder like Nus don't seem to be helping at all.
Don't call her a shareholder.
Call her an investor instead!
But you get equal profits?
Is that fair?
Who cares?
-After you.
-Thank you.
For two.
Who is she here with?
My nosy self has been notified
I wonder too.
Do you think P'Ran knows?
Those two talk a lot.
Everyone is going to find out about us soon.
Those two are your friends?
Yes.
Should we go say hi?
No.
It's good that we're pretending not to see them.
Okay
Go sh, all of them looks delicious.
Here it is Dad.
Come. The fire has started.
P'Toei, did you bring chopsticks?
Even chopsticks come in pairs.
But "I love you" must have you!
Do you need help with anything?
Help use at is good enough!
What is this?
Corn?
Chili peppers too.
I noticed that you guys like eating spicy.
There's a lot of them growing back home sol brought you guys some.
-Thank you.
-Speaking of peppers,
It's spicy,
But if you're talking about cool,
it's me!
Stop talking Toei!
If you're that cool then a duck is superman!
-Dad.
-Who's your dad?
Come! Come eat! Hello there!
Oh, Boss said he was going to join us but l don't know where he went
Saran will be joining us?
Yes That's what he said
I'll go home then.
Hey! Eat first!
No.
He's even stingy with grass. I probably won't get to eat the pork.
Who wants to stay and let your boss scold me?
Not me.
Why would I scold you?
Boss.
Sit here.
-Sit.
-Please have a seat.
Eat up.
Why didn't Pim eat one bite?
Probably feels considerate of Khun Ran.
Why be considerate?
Khun Ran is a kind person.
If I wasn't close to him, I wouldn't eat either :
Seeing Khun Saran calm like that.
he must be feeling awful too.
Why don't you talk
in your native language?
You hate it?
I don't hate my native language.
I just don't want to speak
it to someone I'm not close to.
The barbecued pork is for you to eat.
Not stare at.
I don't want to eat your food
Then why are you here?
I'll leave then.
Eat first.
I had Uncle Rong put your bike
on the back of the truck already.
Huh?!
Hey! You had to take away my bike
just to force me to eat your pork?!
Just eat.
I'll drop you off.
No.
I came here on my own. I can leave on my own.
Alright.
Eat.
No.
I rather go home and eat my food.
If I eat your food and you ask for it back,
wouldn't I have to throw it backup?
I won't ask f on it back.
Or do you want me to feed you?
What's it gonna be?
No need!
I can feed myself.
This is what they mean by eating five porks a day.
Crispy pork, roasted pork, grilled pork, pork belly, and barbecued pork!
So delicious!
Thank you.
Did you plant the grass I gave you?
Not yet.
Where is it?
Right here.
Why?
You're scared l will take the sheep to eat your grass?
Leaving it in the sack will dry it up!
I already told you the water in my farm won't reach that area.
They'll be dead even if I plant them.
Aunt Noi gave you some things too.
I'll put it in the kitchen.
That's okay. I'll take it!
You're in such a hurry.
For what?
What are you doing?! It's okay! I'll do it!
I'm sorry.
I put it right here I'll take my leave now.
Good thing the pork porridge did
not fall. Otherwise, it :ll be a waste
Aunt Noi gave me so many things!
She's petite.
She should be able to manage for days.
P'Vee!
I'm sorry.
I was being too loud
It's okay.
I was waiting to talk to you anyway.
What's the matter?
Are you dating that knuckle face's sister?
Gosh! We're just friends!
Hey.
Everyone knows he's so protective of his sister.
If he finds out, he will kill you.
Look.
Didn't I tell you we're just friends?! You weirdo!
Go. Go to bed.
It's late.
I'm sleepy too.
You hate the brother but wants his sister?
You're gonna get hurt for nothing if you
mess with his sister and he finds out
Boys', be careful with what you're carrying.
Don't let it get damaged.
Put the vase in the middle.
Got it?
You don't listen to what I'm saying
huh? You don't even turnaround!
Taew.
Nus is having a lot of people over?
Seems a lot.
Spending money like this,
when will she grow up?
Have they been here since morning?
You're the bad one.
You didn't even stop your sister!
You let her spend however
much amount of money she wants
She knows how to spend
but don't know how to earn.
Will she be able to grow?
Just let her Auntie.
Nus only has me and you now.
She didn't get the chance
to live with her parents.
If spending money is
what makes her happy,
I'm okay with that.
Because you think like
this that's why Nus is spoiled
Every time it's Nus's birthday,
I just miss P'Pat all over again.
Two years ago,
if P'Pat didn't have to come to Nus's birthday,
the accident wouldn't have happened.
Yes P'Pat?
I'm gonna stop by Nus's birthday party this year.
You can come?
Daniel is meeting up with a friend who is
a client sol thought of stopping by
Will my kids becoming too?
The women are going to think you have a wife
and kids already by calling them that.
They call me dad though.
True.
- The two monkeys won't be going.
-My turn!
-Please!
- Daniel doesn't want them traveling. It's far.
It's two hours to get to the airport by car then they have to fly afterwards.
I'll see you in two days okay?
Sure thing.
I miss you so much.
If P'Pat hadn't come to Nus's birthday...
the car wouldn't have crashed.
Don't talk about sad things Ran.
It's your sister's birthday today
Can you manage the coordinators?
-I'll go check on the farm.
-Okay.
Go! Hurry!
Go!
Hurry!
Slow!
Eat it.
Once l have money to install the water pipe,
we don't need to beg him to eat his grass.
I don't know how many times I told her
not to let the sheep come eat grass on this side
She just won't listen.
I give her grass to grow but she refuses
Seeing you guy seat grass like this
makes me hungry.
I ll be eating good today
After put the sheep away, I'll have to stop by and thank Aunt Noi.
Savory!
Compared to those fine dining food
it's not as delicious as this grilled pork
with sticky rice and chili dipping sauce!
Eating this
makes me think of Grandpa.
Grandpa.
How are you up there?
Are you doing well?
Look.
This...
is your favorite food.
Don't worry about me.
Me being here,
I'm eating well.
Your sheep
are happy too.
But...
I just miss you.
It's my birthday, Why don't you come?
I can wear anything?
Who's that?
My neighbor.
She's cute.
I want to get to know you.
Your family owes debt so you're trying to catch a man around here or what?
Where's your brother?!
Are you crazy?!
Your brother Vee ran away with Nus!
♫ The reason we got to meet today ♫
♫ is because something happened and that is I love you ♫
♫ It can only be a dream, I can only think of you ♫
♫ Because I know that one day I will have to wake up ♫
♫ When I open my eyes, you might not be there that day ♫