♫ Because I'm this kind of person, not so very good ♫
♫ Just your normal l average man ♫
♫ I'm not a weak person, never was sensitive until I met you ♫
♫ It was strange when we first locked eyes ♫
♫ You made me realize I'm not the same ♫
♫ You made someone like me understand ♫
♫ You are the meaning of my life ♫
♫ You've changed the life of my day and night? ♫
♫ I like the way I am ♫
♫ I like it when you're close to me ♫
♫ Do you know why? I've changed because of you ♫
I'll give you back the land.
In exchange for what?
For a period of one year,
you have to be my wife.
Wife by name?
My real wife.
Huh?
Then...
-I have to do wife duties?
-Yeah.
Huh?!
Wife duties
and also mom duties
Look after me and the twins.
And...
the duties...
Bed activities?
Regarding that,
when you're willing to do it then we'll talk.
So that means throughout the period of one year I'm not willing to...
Then you don't have to do it.
How long will it take?
About ten months
But you'll have to make sure you're married
and able to prove you're ready to raise kids.
Orn.
What's your problem?!
You sent someone to shoot P'Ran didn't you?!
I sent someone to catch Pim.
Why did you have to shoot them?!
Ran was there.
So they had to shoot to threaten them.
If I really wanted to shoot your boyfriend Ran,
you would have to make reservations at the temple by now
If you're lonely and he doesn't want you,
you can come back to your ex like me temporary
I won't mind.
Save your energy for your bed activity with Pim!
Don't you like them young ones?!
If you want her like this
I probably have to find opportunities for you to approach her much easier.
So nothing gets in my way either.
I know your type is Khun Orn
I'm not even an inch of your type.
Good that you know
I want you to convince everyone that we're really sleeping together.
Even if I am sleeping in my office to make you comfortable.
But you better not sleepwalk
Because I get aroused with a woman that sleep walks.
Especially the touchy ones,
I like it even more.
Are you a psychopath?
Do I sleep walk?
Or...
at the hospital,
was I sleep walking and took advantage of him?
I should wrap myself up.
In case l sleep walk and go to his room to take advantage of him.
-Daddy! Where are you?
-Where are you Daddy?!
Daddy!
-Daddy!
-Good morning!
Daddy!
Good morning Daddy!
Mommy!
Mama.
Mama, Daddy.
-Good morning.
-Good morning Mama.
We love you.
Mommy, you haven't given Daddy a good morning kiss yet.
Mommy bit Daddy!
Very funny!
Come kids.
Go shower so you can go down stairs to eat.
Okay.
Come.
Let's go shower.
Trying to sleep until noon or what?
She's the daughter in law.
Instead of waking up early to prepare everything,
she still has n't come down yet by now.
Taew.
Go call her down here to come eat, It's getting late.
Okay.
Why aren't you going?
I've been waiting until the kids already ate and went outside to play.
She still hasn't come down
Do you want me to wait until noon?
Ma'am.
Pim was in the kitchen since early morning.
She probably took the kids to go play with the sheep right now.
Really?
The breakfast this morning was made by Pim and Mom too.
Oh, that's good
It's good she woke up early
If she's awake then go tidy Khun Ran's room.
Okay.
Once Pim was done, now it's my turn.
Yesterday was your doing, wasn't it?
What did I do yesterday?
Hey!
Don't accuse me without any proof
Everyone knows you desperately want Grandpa Ruj's land
You had your men go burn Pim's house.
You even sent someone to shoot me when I went to Pim's house last night.
This doesn't include you trying to kill me at the hospital.
Where's the proof?
If you don't have any then don't blabber.
Threatening me with the cops too?
I'm not threatening you.
But I have proof that a murder happened last night.
Really?
Here?
Pardon me. Here's the search warrant.
Lead the way Khun Saran.
Found it.
Where's the body? I don't see any body
Where's the body?
There's actually two bodies.
What's next? Will you keep digging?
But if you do keep digging
you might find the oil well
We didn't find the body like you reported.
Okay.
I'm sorry I wasted your time.
Excuse us.
-Sure.
-Wait Officer.
You won't press charges on him for filing a false report?
Khun Saran did not specify that you did it.
He only reported that an incident happened right here.
Is that so?
Excuse us.
I can press charges on you.
For filing a false report to incriminate and defame.
I think you did do it.
You just managed to get away with it.
Let's go.
I burned him here Boss
Good thing you knew ahead.
I'm sorry.
If not you,
it was going to be us.
Don't!
Forgive me.
Let's go.
Where did it fell?
He wanted to put me in prison
You can't attack him directly,
The bed is so firm as if no one slept on it.
Where did they sleep?
Oh!
Crystal clear!
First night and you guys had a tournament in here.
Their lives must be too basic and expensive so it had to be...
the sofa!
Juicy!
Khun Ran.
Come here
Right here.
Come.
With this, the twins will be getting a sibling soon!
Scoop more
Thank you
for saving them
It was Khun Ran.
He told me to take care of them.
The day of the fire, he told me to bring the sheep here first.
He also told me to bring more grass.
They like eating his grass.
He's actually a kind person.
Even though he's mean like a dog!
Who's mean like a dog?
Daddy!
Who are you calling a dog?
I meant...
it would be nice if there was a dog guarding the sheep.
Did you eat yet?
I made fish congee for you since you left so early.
I haven't.
I was waiting to eat with my wife.
But late already.
P'Pim ate with P'Toei and P'Taew.
I invited her to come eat but she refused
Really?
A huh.
Then should we invite P'Pim to have lunch with us?
Yay! Can I sit with you?
I want to sit with you too
We need to talk.
About last i night.
Toei.
Yes?
Take the kids to go see Jam in the kitchen.
Pim and!
-will go see the damage done at the stable.
-Okay
Come on guys!
We, the three rangers,
will go attack P'Jam!
Let's go!
Hurry!
Come on!
They didn't find anything at Khun Tin's farm?
How is that possible?
I know right?
But I saw that they were burying something.
I saw with my own eyes too.
They threw someone down there.
But the police went to dig and found nothing?
Yes.
So will Khun Tin not pursue the matter with you?
An influential person like him will not stand idly and let you attack him.
Think about it.
She said she's the wife.
The other day he bought my whole collection.
I think he's very infatuated with her.
You're not going to say anything?
What do you want me to say?
I thought you like Pim?
She has a husband and you're not gonna say anything?
I'm just not sure
if they're really married.
It is real. They have the marriage certificate.
Well, yes.
But isn't it too soon?
Have you see n P'Ran go pick up or drop off
or even court Pim?
Never.
Bingo.
Crazy!
If they don't love each other, why would they sign the certificate?
Some people don't even sign the marriage certificate when they remarried.
Who wants to share their assets?
You would need to split it in half and it's not even worth the profit you make.
That's another reason.
But I think...
there's something strange about it.
So you're just going to easily let Pim go like this?
Have I told you
that I was?
What are you waiting for?
If you say you're not sure if they got married because they love each other,
are you going to wait until they do love each other?
Because if you don't start today,
if they do love each other already,
you will lose that right!
Don't run or you'll fall!
Don't run!
Don't run! That's enough!
You see?
I told you not to run or this will happen.
Taew.
Go wash your face.
Okay.
Sit.
Kids, eat up.
Last night's shooting was like world war!
Really?!
Rong! Why didn't you wake me?!
Was that a gunshot?
Gunshot!
Noi!
Noi! Noi wake up!
There were gunshots! Wake up!
Wake up Noi!
My eyes!
Right in my face!
Aren't you exaggerating?!
I'm not a heavy sleeper! Why didn't you wake me?!
"I'm not a heavy sleeper! Why didn't you wake me?!"
This is proof!
Foot right in my face!
-Whose foot?
-Yours!
Khun Ran said she saw Khun Tin's men burying something in the back of their farm.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Speaking of that farm, it's so scary
It's like the Twilight Zone
People can enter but not leave
So many people died there.
The ghosts must be wicked!
The ghosts are wicked.
Yes, wicked.
Ghost! Ghost!
So scary!
What?!
It's me! Why are you scared?!! Scaredy cat!
You freak! What are you doing?! You scared me!
Yes?
My wife.
Gosh! Why do you mind the kid?!
He was just scared!
What happened dear?
I fell.
What mud did you fell in to?
You have lemon grass all over your face.
These are seaweed from vegetable soup Dad! It's not lemongrass!
My goodness! Go and wash your face!
Why would you put your face in vegetable soup?!
Crazy daughter!
Your daughter Mom!
Your dad's daughter!
My daughter now?
Go! Get going!
Crazy just like your father.
Wait.
Throw this away too.
You freak!
What freak?
The food isn't good?
No.
Then eat.
She's probably not familiar with it.
Don't you usually eat sticky rice with chopped fermented fish?
So she's not used to eating other proteins.
Hello Auntie.
Hello Orn, Danai.
-Hello P'Ran.
-Hello.
The witch is here.
-I'm full.
-Me too.
You guys are full?
I bought snacks for you guys too.
Here.
Thank you.
When I'm done talking to your dad.
I'll go play with you okay?
Okay.
The twins seems to like you.
You have a job, nice family,
you have an education.
I regret you so much.
Uncle had me come discuss the price of the corn for next batch.
Oh really?
Let's go talk in the living room.
-Ran, come with us.
-Okay.
Why are you here Nai?
I came to accompany Orn.
Why don't you come with us then?
I'll wait here.
Up to you.
I heard you got married?
That's enough! You're full now! Stop!
Gosh!
Go! I need to wash the dishes.
I was just enjoying it.
Dig in.
Thanks.
I want to be the sticky rice.
So your hands can touch me, feel me.
Pim's aura is screaming madam.
Khun Ran must be really in love with her.
Why do you say that?
This morning, I went to tidy Khun Ran's bedroom.
And then?
Bed so firm!
What does the bed being firm has to do with being a madam?
-Yeah.
-The bed is firm Dad
but the sofa in his office...
it was like world war three!
Were they like in those boat race with full force and what not?
I don't know either but...
II just saw what was left after the deed!
This boy!
We're gossiping right now!
Do you think they did it all night?
I don't know either!
-Auntie.
-You talk as if you're familiar with it.
-What?! Not now!
I'm gossiping right now.
They probably did do it all night.
What are you guys talking about here?
I'm going to go fix the stable
-I'll help.
-Okay come on.
We were in the middle of gossiping.
You're not going to help me wash' the dish?
-You two go ahead. I'm leaving.
-Gosh Dad!a
-P'Toei too.
-Right?
Oops!
So close
She probably heard everything.
I think so!
I came to tell you
they're done eating.
Oh really?
Mom, let's go get the plates.
-Where did I leave the tray?
-Where is it?
Where is the tray?
-Where did you leave it?
-I'm just gonna go!
-Mom! Wait for me!
How is it being the madam of Saengtawan Farm?
The same.
Don't call me madam. Just call me like before
How can I?
Right now you have...
Khun Ran as a husband?
Yeah.
Is it not true?
It's true.
But it's not.
Perhaps next year l might be an employee selling fertilizers at your shop instead!
If you want to be my employee,
I'll look after you in P'Ran's place.
If I were to have a wife
I would not let my wife struggle.
Taking the guest on a walk?
Yes.
Nai is no stranger here. He can go walking by himself.
I asked Pim to take me
I wanted to check out the corn.
I wanted to see how it was doing.
Na i's organic fertilizer is working right?
Yes.
But too much worms.
Too much worms?
That means the soil is perfect.
The new fertilizer goes well with the soil here then.
Sometimes suitability doesn't mean we like it.
But some things are n't suitable and are bad.
Plus it's not likable either.
I'm going to go check on the kids.
So you can continue with your business.
Orn.
I won't walk you out.
See you at the meeting this afternoon.
Didn't I tell you
if we let them be, P'Ran will fall for her even more?
He's already crazy about her right now.
You guys seem close.
If you guys are any closer, he can be your husband!
Khun Ran!
Or is it not?
You guys were being chummy out there.
You weren't being considerate of your husband like me!
Is that your mouth talking?!
You tested it.
Do you think it was my mouth?
I might be your husband by name
but you should be considerate of me too!
You can't just flirt with other men like that!
You just ignored my existence!
I wasn't doing like you said
Good that you didn't.
But if I see you two walking alone again,
I will kiss you!
I will show him that you're mine!
Just for one year.
When I get my property back,
I will leave!
You have to go to the Provincial Agriculture Committee Meeting with me.
-I won't go.
-You have to!
You have to go!
Dress nicely too!
Can't you smile a little?
Why do I have to smile?
You came here with your newly wedded husband.
You should be a little happy.
Smile.
Smile like you're happy.
I'm not happy!
If you're happy then you smile.
Today I'm happy.
If you're not happy then that's your problem
Excuse me.
P'Ran.
I go there a while ago. I thought you would be here already
Why didn't you bring your sister this time?
Yes Ran, where's Nus?
Nus couldn't make it.
But I brought my wife to introduce to you all today
Wife?
Congratulations Khun Orn.
You didn't tell us you had a private wedding
This is her.
Pim is my wife.
Isn't she Grandpa Ruj's granddaughter?
Yeah.
How did she marry Khun Ran?
Trying to leech off his money.
She probably took the money to pay off her grandfather's debt.
I heard they owe the bank as well?
P'Ran, they want to discuss the price on the corn.
Let's go.
Do you want water?
I didn't put any sleeping pill in it.
Get away from me.
You announced to everyone that you're the wife of the most eligible bachelor.
There should be some competition
But don't forget
your brother sold you to me already.
I already bought you too.
Bastard!
How much did you spend?
A little.
How much is little?
A little over 300K baht.
Nus.
They froze your credit card.
If you saved up your money, you will have enough to pay rent for months.
So what if it's frozen?
I still have a lot in my account and this is my happiness.
We'll struggle if you run out.
You won't earn money but you want to spend.
Hey!
What's the matter with you?
You won't go anywhere with me You won't go shopping with me.
You criticize me when I buy some little stuff!
You're boring.
You just splurge!
You won't listen to me!
Hey!
You're bored of me?! What exactly is boring to you?!
What?! Tell me!
What the hell is wrong with you Nus?!
I'm your husband not your servant!
You can't boss me around!
If you're still going to act like this I don't think we can be together!
Jerk!
Go then!
There will be a day when you soften up to me
Where is Pim?
What you're doing is not okay?
And what you did is okay taking my wife like that?
I came to collect the promise your brother made.
I have nothing to do with that!
Khun Tin probably took her home with him.
♫ The reason we got to meet today ♫
♫ is because something happened and that is I love you ♫
♫ It can only be a dream, I can only think of you ♫
♫ Because I know that one day I will have to wake up ♫
♫ When I open my eyes, you might not be there that day ♫