(We mix dramatic imagination
with scientific knowledge.)
(All people, organizations,
places, incidents are fictitious.)
(Staff ensured the children's safety
in the filming of this drama.)
(Episode 16. Brain Works)
The person you have reached is...
Why won't Detective Geum pick up?
Dr. Brain's not answering either.
They left a while ago.
How strange.
Do you think something happened?
(Captain Seul, Subsection chief)
What have you done?
Okay.
Starting now,
we'll play a game.
A sympathy game.
A game to turn Dr. Shin into a murderer.
(Power off)
The phone is turned off. Please...
His phone was turned off.
Something must've happened.
Let's trace them.
Okay.
Dr. Shin.
You know what equipment
this is, don't you?
What is it?
Don't keep it to yourself. What is it?
It's a neural coupling.
When two people see or hear something,
the machine measures...
how similarly our brains react.
For example,
if you see a crying child...
and you both feel pity,
your brains will show the same pattern.
I don't get what that means.
Sounds like fun. I'm not afraid at all!
Let me put it simply.
If you sympathize with each other,
the waves will show the same pattern,
and you two will win.
Sympathize?
With Dr. Brain?
That's right. Sympathize.
If you sympathize with each other...
and the waves
are over 80 percent identical,
your handcuffs will open.
What if not?
Then the brain waves will not match...
and you'll all become murderers.
Instead of dying,
we become murderers?
Why?
Do we get to kill you?
The people...
you'll end up killing.
Here they are.
(Camera 1)
- Auntie!
- Yi Na!
Mo Ran!
(Camera 1)
(Crystal Bathhouse)
How did you end up here?
Her dad texted me.
I went to a house in Pyeongchang-dong.
Then I suddenly passed out.
When I woke up, I was here with Yi Na.
Me too.
You too?
Ha Ru lived in that house as a child.
I'm here because Hwang Dong Woo
asked to meet me there.
I think this is his doing.
Hwang Dong Woo?
- Who's he?
- He's...
I'll tell you later.
Yi Na!
Mo Ran!
- Yi Na!
- Stop it.
They aren't here. They can't hear you.
You must want to know
why I'm keeping them there.
I'll show you.
Excuse me, sir! Help us!
Excuse me? Hello?
You...
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Turn off the water valve at once.
Let them go right now, you scumbag!
If you guys win this game,
we will turn off the water valve.
But if you lose,
we'll keep the water running.
You psychopath!
You see, I'm not the only one.
There's another one...
with the brain of a psychopath.
Because of his psychopathic brain,
Dr. Shin lacks emotional empathy.
Therefore, he can't win this game,
which means...
they'll all drown and die.
Shut it!
What you want won't happen.
My brain...
is not like yours.
Wait.
Look, I'll do whatever you say.
So please...
Please let them go, okay? No.
I'll die instead of them.
I'll die, so just let them go!
Dr. Shin, this man's brain
is completely different from yours.
Because the two of you are so different,
you certainly won't win this game.
Shut your mouth.
Let's begin.
Dr. Brain!
Fine.
Then let's get started now.
- Mom.
- Yes.
It's okay. We're here together.
Yes, Yi Na. Don't be scared.
We'll get out of here. Right, Ms. Kim?
Yes, that's right!
Please...
All right. I'll play a video...
on this screen.
And over here, the emotions you feel...
while watching the video will be
displayed as brain wave patterns.
Then the match ratio between
your brain wave patterns...
will be displayed as a graph.
If it's over 80 percent,
your handcuffs will be unlocked.
All right.
Then let's now begin the Sympathy Game.
They don't match!
You guys lost.
Yi Na, are you all right?
Gosh, sorry.
I wish we had something sharp.
Ms. Kim, could you look? Yi Na, you too.
I don't see anything.
My hands...
All right, then. Here's the next video.
They don't match.
What?
How does that make you feel?
Well...
I'm not sure
how it's supposed to make me feel.
Flinch! Didn't it make you flinch?
Not really.
Why should I flinch?
How could you not flinch
after seeing that?
It's because of his psychopathic brain.
All right. The next one.
Help...
Please save us.
They don't match.
Please don't kill us.
- Yi Na!
- Help us!
If you want me dead, go ahead and kill me!
Don't use such a dirty trick.
What? "A dirty trick?"
You pretend to be one of them,
but you're no ordinary man...
because of your brain,
and I'm doing this to prove it.
If you think I'm wrong,
try to sympathize with him.
All right, next.
- Coming through.
- Ms. Jung, where is your husband?
The guitarist's case?
Ms. Jung In Young?
I managed to trace it.
It was turned off in Pyeongchang-dong.
In Pyeongchang-dong?
That's where they went.
Something must've happened.
I should go there myself.
- I'll come with you.
- Sure.
Only 27 percent.
The two of you worked on the same case...
but felt such different emotions.
You two are too different.
You'll never win this game.
Shut your mouth.
Show us the next image.
Sure.
Okay, next.
Help us, sir!
Please help us!
Look, sir.
This is considered attempted murder.
If you just let us go...
My husband is a cop.
If you get caught, you'll be in
deep trouble. Do you realize that?
Hey!
You're laughing? You lunatic!
Dr. Brain, what on earth do you feel?
What about you?
What do you feel?
Don't fight.
Look at their faces for one last time.
With their deaths, I will prove...
that Dr. Shin's brain is
wired differently from yours.
It was turned off
within a 1km radius from here.
There are so many buildings here.
How will we find them?
Oh, how about we ask the detective
who was in charge of the case?
We may be able to find some clues...
about the house.
You're right. Yes.
Yes.
Hey, Detective Yoon.
You know, the house where
the doctor couple was murdered.
Right, that house in Pyeongchang-dong.
Do you remember where that house was?
(Crystal Bathhouse)
You don't remember?
Come on. See if you can remember
some things about the house.
How close was it to the subway
station? Was there a tree?
What? A window?
An arched window?
They don't match!
Please help us.
Help!
Help.
Yi Na...
Let's try to get on our feet.
We can't.
Not when we're tied up like this.
Let's give it a try though.
All right. On the count of three,
we'll stand.
Good.
One, two, three.
Mom!
Mom.
Help!
Mom, are you all right?
Mom?
Mom!
Are you all right?
Auntie...
Take a good look at them.
You'll be responsible for their deaths.
He's wrong, Dr. Brain.
It won't be your fault.
This is on him!
I gave you a chance.
The brain of a murderer
that lacks sympathy.
The issue lies with Dr. Shin's brain.
Free will? Metacognition?
It's all nonsense.
We humans can feel superior all we want,
but we will forever be poor beings
who let their brains control them.
Here you are proving that.
What?
Someone's here.
In here. Help!
Help!
Well...
No one seems to be home.
But there's the arch window.
And the house seems old enough.
Let me see.
The trees are trimmed,
so the house can't be abandoned.
Could the owner be out?
Help!
Cut the shouting and answer my question.
How did that photo make you feel?
What?
I felt bad, of course.
How could someone do that?
- Compassion?
- That's right.
But I can't describe it
with just that one word though.
Why do you ask?
I know what those photos have in common.
What they have in common?
Yes, the people in them were scared.
That's right.
He knows that my brain doesn't react
to others out of fear...
and chose those photos on purpose.
Since I now know how they made you feel,
I'll consciously think
of those emotions too.
Then our brain waves
will be somewhat in sync.
I'll trick my own brain.
Really?
No one seems to be home.
It's not like we can jump over the wall.
This is frustrating.
The houses here look similar to me.
- We'll keep searching.
- Sure.
Gosh.
We can beat the test
if he shows us a similar photo.
I hope we make it work.
Your colleagues were here,
but they left.
- Help us.
- Help.
Help.
Whatever. Get on with the game.
You sound desperate.
Fine.
Next.
Compassion.
- Compassion.
- Hey, kid.
Hey, kid.
- Compassion...
- Hey, kid.
Compassion.
Seriously?
He made me relive a traumatic event...
to stop me from feeling compassion.
Darn it!
That house we were at.
No one came to the door,
but I saw the curtains move.
I want to head back there.
Okay, I'll check other places.
- Call me if anything happens.
- Sure.
An arch window.
Wait. There's one.
Detective Geum! Dr. Shin!
Captain Seul!
Yes!
- Captain Seul.
- Captain Seul?
Captain Seul.
- Captain Seul.
"Crystal Bathhouse."
The house the doctor couple was killed in.
In Pyeongchang-dong.
Do you remember where it was?
Try to remember.
You darn scumbag!
This will be the final problem.
I'll let you say goodbye.
Auntie.
Ha Ru? What's going on?
What are you doing?
Dad. Save me!
- Dad!
- Save us!
Wait, Yi Na.
I'll come for you, okay?
Hang in there!
Dad. Get here soon.
Be quick!
Okay, I'll be there!
Don't give up, Yi Na!
Yi...
You. Darn you, you psycho scumbag!
There.
You've got to say goodbye.
It's time for the final problem.
I really don't like to say this,
but I must.
I'm sorry.
For having a brain like this.
It's not on you.
Whatever the outcome,
it's not on you, so don't apologize.
It's all on that psycho!
Now,
here's the last problem.
Dr. Brain.
Pretend the dying man is your friend.
My friend?
My friend.
Algernon.
My only friend's a lab rat.
How come your only friend's a mouse?
If you don't have a friend,
pretend that's me.
How would you feel if I died?
Dr. Shin...
wouldn't bat an eyelid even if...
the likes of you were to die before him.
He has the brain of a murderer.
Don't you dare say that.
Dr. Brain's different
from complete trash like you.
He developed an affection
for human beings...
that the likes of you
will never understand.
Kill me. Kill me, and you'll find out!
That's a great idea.
Let's do that.
Dr. Brain.
You poor man.
How did you end up
meeting a mad murderer like him?
How about we say
today is our first day as a couple?
Help me, Dr. Brain!
- Hold me tight.
- I will kill you.
No!
You'll become a murderer.
No, Dr. Brain.
No.
What...
We did it.
I can't hang on.
No, Yi Na.
Yi Na.
- Yi Na.
Wake up, Yi Na.
Don't fall asleep.
Yi Na.
Yi Na. No.
Yi Na!
- Yi Na.
- No.
Detective Geum.
My gosh.
Why didn't the water stop?
Was that a lie?
- No.
- Lift your head.
Lift your head.
Yi Na! Lift your head.
- Yi Na.
- Your...
Yi Na, lift your head!
Mister!
Please let my Yi Na go.
Are you okay?
Yes. Goodness.
It's okay. The tap's off.
But where could that be?
I think I know where they are.
I saw the bathhouse earlier. Let's go.
I'm freezing.
My pretty face is getting wrinkly.
- Run! Come on!
- Detective Geum.
Follow us!
What's going on?
Are we chasing or being chased?
- What happened?
- Where are they?
- My gosh.
- Oh, dear.
- Mom.
- Yes?
I can't do this anymore.
- My head hurts.
- No, Yi Na. Stay awake.
Yi Na. The water stopped. Hang in there.
Yi Na.
Yi Na!
- Auntie!
- Get Yi Na!
Yi Na!
- Yi Na.
- Auntie!
- Are you okay?
Are you okay?
Dad's here.
- You're okay.
- Get Yi Na first.
Detective Geum.
Yi Na.
They might get hypothermic.
Take them all to the ER.
- Okay.
- Get Yi Na first.
- Dad.
- It's okay.
I'm here.
Get over here and help them out.
Can you drain the water?
- Are you all right?
- I can't do it!
(Incoming Call)
Hey, kid.
It's time for the last game.
You know where I am, right?
Detective Geum.
Take care of the rest here.
Where are you going?
I have to go meet Hwang Dong Woo.
- Are you all right, Yi Na?
- What's going on?
- Let's go.
- Let's get out of here.
Welcome.
You have a triumphant look on your face.
Of course.
I won the game
that you said I'd never win.
It was very thrilling.
I should thank you for giving me
the chance to participate...
in such an incredible brain experiment.
I hope...
you're not deluding yourself
into thinking that...
you were able to truly sympathize
with that detective.
You saw it with your own two eyes.
No.
You're incapable of doing that.
Your high IQ...
allowed you to trick your brain
for a moment.
You know that
your brain is incapable of sympathy.
No.
My brain has transcended its limitations.
We can never transcend
our own limitations.
You're wrong.
You can overcome your limitations...
the moment you connect with others.
Just like how Detective Geum...
helped me become a better person.
A better person?
Do you truly mean it?
- Of course, I do.
- Fine.
Then how about a fun game
of Truth or Dare?
We'll find out whether or not
you truly believe...
what you said.
If you believe it to be true,
it'll be a match.
If not, it'll say it doesn't match.
Fine. What are we betting?
Our lives.
One of us...
will die.
This is morphine.
The winner will inject
the loser with this.
What do you say? Are you in?
Sure.
We'll go inside
and search every nook and cranny.
We must catch them no matter what.
Yes, we'll catch them at all costs.
Hey, go with them and see a doctor.
I'll wrap things up here
and meet you there.
- Okay.
- Hurry, Dad.
That man who was with us.
He's in on this too.
- Make sure you catch him too.
- Okay.
Wait. Have you heard from Ha Ru yet?
So?
Should I go first?
No.
I'll go first.
All right, then.
Feeling connected to others...
helps the brain
overcome its limitations...
and helps us...
become better people.
I...
proved it.
As human beings,
we're all slaves to our brains.
The human brain...
can never transcend its limitations.
Okay! I won.
See that?
You're the one who doesn't
truly believe in what you say.
This can't be.
Something went wrong.
No. You may not want to believe it,
but your brain does.
The moment you saw
my brain sympathize with others,
your brain realized it.
"I was mistaken. I was wrong."
"I can..."
"overcome my limitations."
No.
Something went wrong. I'm sure of it!
Why?
Are you afraid now that you have to die?
Of course not.
In any case,
you won.
I shall die.
Inject me.
With that needle.
Finally, you're getting your revenge.
Injecting it in my neck
wouldn't be a bad idea either.
Anyway, go for it.
Let's do this in one go.
Do a clean job.
That's how I killed your parents.
Nice and clean. At once.
Shut your mouth!
Your beliefs are wrong.
I am...
not like you.
Make your choice.
You can either...
rot in prison for the rest of your life...
or commit your last murder.
There's only one person you can kill now.
Yourself.
Oh, right.
Before you die,
you should at least know this.
Do you know why we got such results?
It's because...
your brain desperately wanted
to feel such a connection.
Dr. Brain! Are you all right?
Hwang Dong Woo is inside.
Go in and arrest him at once.
Oh, you have to be careful though.
He has a syringe filled with morphine.
If he injects you with it, you'll die.
Okay.
I was never wrong.
I do not want human connection.
What the...
Hwang Dong Woo!
He seemed like a smart man.
Why did he have to go out this way?
Is it because his brain
was programmed this way?
It's because he blamed
his brain for everything.
He thought too less of it.
Exactly. Someone with
a nasty brain like yours...
can turn over a new leaf, so...
My brain isn't nasty.
It's exceptional.
Fine.
Dr. Brain with an exceptional brain.
I was touched.
The thought of me dying made you sad.
Yes, I was upset.
Really?
I had to be the one to kill you,
so you dying in another's hands...
saddened me.
You just had to ruin the moment,
didn't you?
Do you get it?
You can't die until I kill you myself.
Keep that in mind.
Is that a threat or a confession of love?
I'm confused. Gosh, it's cold.
Dr. Brain, wait for me.
It's cold. Warm me up, will you?
Get lost.
I keep sticking to you.
Get away from me.
The cold brings me back to our time
in the freezer warehouse.
Get lost.
I'll be reminded of your warm embrace...
every time it gets cold.
Don't think about that incident.
I can't help it.
Stop it while I ask nicely.
I can't hear you.
Gosh, it's so warm.
Stop it!
Ji Hyung, I was about to contact you.
I only want to know why.
Why did you do it?
It has been eating at me all this time.
I'm actually relieved...
to come clean.
That day,
someone came by to see Jae Sung
while he was on the phone with me.
I heard weird noises,
and then the call got disconnected.
It didn't feel right,
so I hurried over there.
Someone opened the front gate,
so I thought all was well.
Dr. Shin?
- Professor?
- We should...
talk.
Why?
How did this happen?
His disrespectful attitude
left me with no choice.
He brought this upon himself.
You know how he was.
Dr. Shin has always been disrespectful...
and arrogant.
Ha Ru...
What did you do to him?
Oh, the perky young boy?
Is his name Ha Ru?
He's alive.
Ha Ru, it's me!
He's outside.
If you wish to save the boy,
you'll make...
a deal with me.
That dead woman over there.
He's the son of the woman
you were secretly in love with.
What is it that you want?
Just do as I tell you.
Then nothing will happen. Actually...
Since Dr. Shin is no longer with us,
I'll make you...
the best neurosurgeon
at Korea National University Hospital.
Professor...
The dissertation
Dr. Shin was working on...
will be yours.
I made the best decision I could.
To save Ha Ru...
Don't use Ha Ru as an excuse.
My patience to tolerate you
is already running out as is.
(Research on
the Regulatory DNA Function...)
(of the Brain-Nervous System,
Shin Jae Sung)
- Ji Hyung...
- I'll make an official report...
stating that your dissertation...
was plagiarized.
Ji Hyung, wait.
I'll step down...
on my own accord.
I know I did wrong,
but I've been good to you and Ha Ru.
Ha Ru was raised well...
all because I helped.
You overlooked a murder.
Nothing could make up for that.
Ji Hyung, please.
In return,
I'll let you take over as director.
I'll pull every string to...
Even at this moment,
you remain an opportunist.
It makes me sick.
Right.
The family members of...
the Neuroscientific Investigation Team...
who were held hostage
by serial killer Hwang Dong Woo...
were rescued when I jumped
into the water and...
Chief Kim,
that would be wrong.
Right, of course.
Thank you for correcting me, my savior.
I mean,
the hostages held captive
by the serial killer...
were saved...
thanks to the outstanding teamwork...
of the Neuroscientific Investigation Team.
And the brains of the operation
is Dr. Shin Ha Ru.
The brains?
As in the smart one?
This team does not rely on one individual.
All its members...
solve cases
through the brainwork they offer,
making us a balanced and democratic team.
What if you changed the team's name...
to Brain Works Team instead?
The Brain Works Team?
That sounds nice.
I'm the one who came up with that.
Sure.
Detective Geum Myung Se
is nowhere to be seen though.
Is it true that he resigned?
Well, you see...
(Resignation Letter)
The person you have reached
is unavailable.
Why on earth isn't he picking up?
Chief.
I have something to tell you.
Sure. What is it?
Detective Geum handed in
his resignation because...
Yes?
While working on Yi Na's case,
I got very frustrated,
so the phone records...
Captain Seul, we must go somewhere.
Hey.
Why weren't you answering your phone?
Did you call? What for?
What else?
What should I do with this?
Should I process it?
Of course not.
I'll explain later
since I'm a little busy.
Captain Seul, you must come with me.
Hurry.
Sure.
Where are you going? What about me?
Stay here, sir.
- Hurry. Go on.
- Sure.
Did he just brush me off?
- Captain Seul, hurry.
- But...
- Keep running.
- Where to?
- Up the stairs. To the rooftop.
- Sure.
- Here?
- Head up the stairs.
What's going on?
Is someone attempting suicide?
- Don't stop and keep running.
- Sure.
- Don't stop.
- I won't.
What's going on though?
What the...
We're here.
Where...
What the...
What?
I couldn't get it to look that pretty.
Here.
You're more likely to say yes...
when your heart is racing,
so I'll cut right to the chase.
Captain Seul.
If it's okay with you, could you...
reactivate your love system?
Gosh.
If you will turn it on again,
I'll try my best...
to see that it doesn't turn off.
No. You don't have to try.
My love system...
never once turned off.
Captain Seul.
Could you...
call me by my name now?
Oh, sorry.
I'm so used to calling you "Captain Seul."
Thank you so much for saying yes.
So Jeong.
That's so embarrassing.
My goodness.
Who could it be at this important moment?
(My daughter Yi Na)
It's Yi Na. You should take it.
Okay. Excuse me.
What's up, kiddo?
Come and join us.
What?
Who are you with?
Okay. Hang up.
What?
Let's not bother him.
It feels ominous.
He's with a woman.
- I'm positive.
- So what if he is?
Your dad's a single man.
What's going on? I was worried for you.
Didn't you want to get back with him?
Well, I did some soul-searching,
and I think we're better off as friends.
I have a specific type.
- The Hollywood type.
You sweet thing.
Algernon. When I saw the word "match,"
I felt such a thrill.
As if my brain would explode.
It was the best experience of my life.
My heart's still pounding.
(Detective Geum)
Who is it?
It looks like I have someone
other than you now.
A friend.
Why are you calling me again?
Why must I be there when I'm not a cop?
(Model Detective Award Ceremony)
It's my first award in 30 years.
(Seobu Police Station)
(Model Detective Award Ceremony)
This is my second award this year.
That's a multiple score.
Who do you owe that to?
You and your darn bragging.
How is it bragging if it's a fact?
Okay, fine. How typical of you.
How about a group photo?
Of course.
- Join us.
- Okay.
Come on.
Hurry up. Stand in a row.
That's it.
The Neuroscientific Investigation Team.
No, the Brain Works Team.
Smile.
Yes.
Why the weird faces?
Were you all forced to be here?
My gosh.
I guess I should take the lead, then.
How about you all laugh like me?
- Captain, laugh.
- Okay.
Like this?
Subsection chief.
(Model Detective Award Ceremony)
(Brain Works, 2023)
How's business?
The same as always.
Pour me one too.
Wel...
Oh, gosh. Where are you going, Dr. Brain?
Join the team for dinner.
No, thanks. Why would I join
when I'm not a cop?
You're on the Brain Works Team.
You got an award too, remember?
I clearly said I'd quit.
I just stayed on way too long.
It would be such a shame
if you were to leave like this.
Quit your disturbing attempts
to be cute...
and go and eat and drink.
Wait. Hold up.
Mr. Yang?
A video call?
Detective Geum.
- Look.
- What's that?
Mr. Yang.
Wait. Dr. Brain.
Look at this.
Help me. Help, Detective Geum.
What happened?
Mr. Yang!
Did you see that?
Was that a zombie?
I got what that zombie is.
Is it what I think it is?
It is.
Let's go zombie hunting.
Okay. Let's go zombie hunting.
(Neuroscientific Investigation Team)
(Thank you for watching Brain Works.)
(Brain Works)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)