I must go there to search for something.
What is it? Tell me.
It is Klaikot Lek Lai.
Uncle Chaem told you
to stay and attend to me.
My father told me to keep you company,
not to be your servant.
- I'm going to kill Pud.
- Once you kill Pud,
your secret dies with him.
Tonight, our son will finally have a wife.
What is this?
Spirits of the dead, unite with the living
I'm starting to wonder
if you're still
the same Blur I used to know?
Why?
When you killed those two,
your eyes didn't look like yours.
Blur!
Everything I've been through
has taught me one thing,
only the strong survive.
If we don't kill them, they'll kill us.
In the year we were apart,
you must've gone through a lot.
And because of that,
my purpose is clearer than ever.
To learn sorcery at Khao Phrom
and find the Klaikot Lek Lai.
The old saying goes,
"Dark Lek Lai drives men mad,
rambling nonsense, dabbling in alchemy,
till their clothes are torn to shreds."
What if the Lek Lai you're chasing
doesn't even exist?
This map,
Old Master Khrua Phut gave it to me.
This map will lead you
to the Klaikot Lek Lai cave.
Whether you find it or not
depends on your fate.
Something this precious…
why give it to me?
These are corrupt times.
The wicked rise to power.
Use the power of the Lek Lai
to help the helpless,
and be a refuge for those in distress.
And if I fail to find it?
Then abandon this path
and never return to Tha Khiri again.
We're here.
If we follow the stream upstream,
we'll reach the Lek Lai cave.
The deeper we go,
the more dangerous it becomes.
Are you sure
you want to risk your life with me?
Whether it's heaven or hell,
I'm going with you.
And you're not afraid
I'm no longer the same Blur?
You may have changed, but I trust you.
Why do you trust me?
I almost died,
and you risked your life to save me.
I know this man
would never let anything happen to me.
Let's go. Maybe my brother
has already reached the cave.
The Siamese government
will build a railway from Bangkok
to the port to expand trade.
Soon, my city
will surpass every southern city.
I've already bought up
all the land along the route.
Any investment will pay off.
Your Excellency,
If progress arrives, I fear
governing will only become more difficult.
The authorities will send
their own people in. And if that happens…
As long as Your Excellency
remains governor,
there's nothing to fear.
Or does Khun Paeng doubt your authority?
Huh, Tim.
If you're so scared,
go home and raise buffalo.
I'll make Pae the new Khun Paeng instead.
Big ambitions, tiny courage.
No wonder Khun Paeng never rises.
I'll turn Tha Khiri
into a city of pleasure,
casinos, brothels,
liquor dens, opium halls.
We'll bring in foreign traders,
Chinese, Arab,
and Westerners, to invest here.
What do you say?
That sounds good.
I'm good at trade.
Just let me be the tax collector.
Two of my prophecies
have already come true.
First, within three days,
your wife will die by a venomous creature.
Second,
your son will bring great ruin
upon Chum Suea.
Only one remains. Just one more.
That's not a prophecy.
It's a curse.
Prophecy or curse,
you cannot escape it.
Those twins
share a bound fate.
If one dies, the other will follow
within three days, seven at most.
I surrender.
Whoever you are,
please save my children.
Please, Grandma. Any sin,
let me bear it for them.
Even if it costs me my life.
You don't need to beg.
Death is already waiting ahead.
Use what time you have left
wisely.
- This must be the cave.
- How do you know?
It's too clean, too peaceful.
No birds, no rats, no bats.
Cool, damp air. Perfect for Lek Lai.
Does the map say what to do next?
It does.
"Kindle the flame toward the southwest.
Below the cave shaft, stars aglow.
The tragic legend of Meri's death.
At dusk, honey drips.
The ore begins to flow."
What does it mean?
I don't understand any of it.
Lek Lai is more powerful than any sorcery.
Only by following the proper order
can one claim it.
That's why it's written in riddles.
"Kindle the flame toward the southwest…"
Southwest?
So we light a torch and head southwest.
Hold my hand.
Hold your hand? Does the map say that too?
No. I just want to hold your hand
so you won't run away.
After coming this far,
I wouldn't know
how to find my way back anyway.
Your daughter is not here.
I've searched for her in every direction,
yet found no trace.
I don't know if she's alive or dead.
People suffer because of their thoughts.
If you do not think, you do not suffer.
For now, your daughter is safe.
Go back. When the time comes,
you will meet her yourself.
Once the railway cuts through here,
Chum Suea will really come alive.
It'll be even easier to rob
the merchants passing through.
Pae, if you keep robbing merchants,
when will you ever get rich?
Brothels and gambling dens,
that's where the real money is.
Oh.
Such a goldmine like that,
will the Governor really allow it?
Why wouldn't he? Can't we all share?
I've dealt with both Khun Yod
and Bandit Wad.
All the credit he gets is because of me.
Then I suppose I should
reward you properly, Bandit Pud.
Hey?
Who's there? Show yourself!
Hey!
Hey, Uncle.
Whoa, Lasor.
I'll take him, Uncle.
You had the nerve
to destroy my father's Chum Suea.
And you used me to kill Khun Yod.
That's because
you were stupid enough to fall for it.
I was stupid
because I wasn't vile enough
to match a bastard like you.
What do you want?
I want your life.
Hah. It won't be that easy.
Pud, your Saming Eye
can't touch me anymore.
Lasor, don't kill me!
I didn't mean to do it! Phraya Decha
and Khun Paeng forced me.
I didn't want to do it!
If they ordered you to die,
would you?
I'm scared. I'm scared!
Nisa-wasu.
Pud, you won't escape me.
At least you only lost one eye.
Instead of helping me,
you let that bastard rip my eye out.
You damn nephew!
Whoa, Uncle. What could I do?
Even your Saming Eye couldn't touch him.
His sorcery is terrifying.
Where did he learn such power?
Wherever he learned it doesn't matter.
What matters is that he won't spare us.
Then I must report this to the governor.
Uncle, you rest here. I'll go myself.
These must be the ones
who came searching for Lek Lai
and never found their way out.
I hope my brother never came in here.
Blur.
Look. The path we walked in on is gone.
We can only move forward now.
There's no turning back.
Do you know the way?
What did you say, Pae?
Lasor, Bandit Wad's son, has returned.
Then what was your Uncle Pud doing?
Lasor gouged out his eye.
He's being treated now.
He's coming for revenge
for the men I had hanged.
I'll deploy the police to hunt Lasor down
and reinforce your security.
Find capable men
to protect my daughters as well.
Yes, sir.
Yeah.
Noree woke up before dawn
just to cook this for you.
I was worried
the meat wouldn't be tender enough.
I'd be embarrassed if it wasn't good.
Eat up. Don't you have duty after this?
There's robbery every single day now.
When people are desperate,
they turn into bandits.
With so few police,
how can you fight them?
You can't win against bandits.
It's delicious.
You're a great cook, Noree.
If you like it, have more.
You'll need strength to catch criminals.
Noree would make a perfect housewife.
She never falls short
when it comes to household duties.
Anyone who marries her
will live easy for life.
Interested?
Pun, orders just came in.
We're to report to Phraya Dechanurak,
the Governor of Tha Khiri.
- When?
- Now.
I'm thinking of inviting merchants
from other towns
to buy local products
and setting up a trading company
to trade with Penang and Malaya.
What do you think?
Good.
Besides pepper, I'm planning
to buy coconuts, betel nuts, nutmeg,
and coffee as well. What do you think?
Good.
Hey.
Don't you know how to say anything else?
I'm a barber's son,
not a merchant's son like you.
What would I know about trade?
Honestly, I don't even
want to be a merchant.
But my dad forced me.
He wants me
to inherit the family business.
If not a merchant,
what would you want to be?
I want to be
a painter.
That won't even put food on the table.
Being a wealthy tycoon is much better.
Far more comfortable.
Money can't buy everything.
But without money, you can't buy anything.
So I'd rather have money.
You're right.
Money isn't everything,
but everything starts with money.
It's getting late. I'm heading back.
Wait.
I couldn't sleep last night.
Come stay over with me tonight.
That way. The wind's coming from that way.
There must be an exit. Let's go.
I'm so cold I can barely walk.
Then rest here. I'll make a fire.
"Below the cave shaft, stars aglow…"
Blur.
Over there.
The cave shaft.
That's it. This must be the place.
We're on the right path.
The fire won't light.
Could this be
the next riddle from the map?
"The tragic legend of Meri's death."
What is the tragic legend of Meri?
"She spoke, her body growing weak,
collapsed upon the cliff's edge.
Her heart suffocated,
her breath withheld.
Meri died upon the mountain peak."
So how did Meri die, Yiam?
She died from holding her breath.
That's what the verse says.
According to the legend,
Meri died from holding her breath.
Then maybe… we have to hold our breath
while lighting the fire.
Try it.
It worked.
"Kindle the flame toward the southwest.
Below the cave shaft, stars aglow.
The tragic legend of Meri's death.
At dusk, honey drips.
The ore begins to flow."
Hold your breath
and light the fire to the southwest,
beneath the cave shaft at night
when the stars shine…
Then the Lek Lai will descend
to drink honey.
Honey.
Om, sawa hom mama mama
narakja cittang phanthanang.
Did you chant it wrong, Blur?
No. I remember every word.
Or maybe…
we still haven't solved all of it.
"Kindle the flame toward the southwest.
Below the cave shaft, stars aglow.
The tragic legend of Meri's death.
At dusk, honey drips.
The ore begins to flow."
Under the stump.
Om, sawa hom mama mama
narakja cittang phanthanang.
Blur!
Blur.
I'm cold.
- I'm cold…
- Blur.
What should I do?
Help me…
Please don't die, Blur.
Where are you rushing off to?
Let go of me, Blur.
You were hugging me all night.
You were about to die.
What was I supposed to do?
Then tell me,
what exactly did you do to me?
- I don't know.
- But I do.
What do you know?
I know that…
I survived because of you.
- Can you let me go now?
- No.
I should've just let you die.
If I died, you'd be a widow.
Have you no shame?
You're my wife already.
What's there to be shy about?
You're shameless.
How did I end up sleeping up here?
Eat.
I don't eat raw eggs.
Just eat it.
Or do you want me to feed you?
- Here.
- No. I can eat by myself.
Why didn't you blow on it first?
Here, water.
This is all your fault.
My tongue's completely wrecked.
Today I'm going
to inspect land for a warehouse.
Come with me.
Why do I have to go?
Your father told you
to look after me. You forgot already?
- You're eating a lot.
- It's delicious.
What's wrong?
It feels like
something's moving inside me.
It must be the power
of the Klaikot Lek Lai.
I saw it vanish into your body.
Even though I obtained it,
I don't know how to control its power.
My dad once said
Lek Lai chooses its master.
You'll figure it out in time.
Orror,
if one day I change,
if I'm no longer the Blur you know,
will you still love me?
Why would you ask that?
I'm afraid I'll lose you.
If you ever change into someone else,
I'll be the one
who brings the real you back.
Lasor will definitely come here.
Go prepare black dog's blood for me.
I'll give him a proper welcome.
Are you sure
you want to use such a dirty trick?
I don't care.
As long as I can take his head
to the governor, that's enough.
It won't be as easy as you think.
Pae, I killed Khun Yod myself.
What can some useless kid do to me?
You've already lost one eye.
Still not enough?
You're not Pae!
It's too late to realize now, Pud.
Lasor.
Narai's Transformation Spell,
the one you said
you'd teach me, Pud.
What are you going to do to me?
Did that buffalo hide taste good?
Nirujjhanti tesang vo
pasamo sukho.
This is for what you did to my people.
Uncle, I brought your favorite dried meat.
You're sleeping this early?
Uncle… Uncle…
Huai Yao's a small district.
You can trade whatever you want
as long as you don't cross
Phraya Decha, the Governor of Tha Khiri,
and Thongyoo, that bloodsucking tycoon.
The tax farmer
who monopolizes royal duties?
That's him.
He works with the Governor,
always scheming to fatten his own pockets.
He doesn't care
how the common folk are squeezed dry.
If people are suffering,
why not submit a petition?
Who'd dare go looking for trouble?
They've got powerful nobles backing them.
Fight them and you'll only lose.
Look there. Speak of the devil.
More!
Hurry up.
What's going on, Duen?
Why are there police all over our house?
Dad must've ordered them to protect us.
Protect us from who?
From Lasor, the son of Bandit Wad.
I am Pun, a police officer
from Huai Yao Station.
I will carry out my duty of protecting
you both to the best of my ability.
It feels safer
with police protection, Duen.
For your safety,
you must follow police regulations.
What regulations?
First, you must not leave the residence
at night under any circumstances.
You're grounding me?
Second, you must not be alone.
A police escort must remain
with you at all times.
I'm not a prisoner. I don't need
police tailing me everywhere.
- Third--
- Enough.
I can't do this. I can't do that.
How annoying. Where I go is my business.
Did I say something wrong?
You didn't do anything wrong.
Duen's just like this.
Please don't take it personally.
Lasor!
Stop right there. Don't move.
Say what you came to say.
I brought the head of Bandit Pud,
the one who killed Khun Yod Pakdee,
to present to Your Excellency.
Lasor, you're acting as a vigilante.
Killing Bandit Pud is a crime.
Come with me to the station now.
So I'm under arrest?
Leave. I'll talk to him.
But he's a dangerous criminal, sir.
Get out.
Go!
Pud robbed and slaughtered families.
A wicked bandit like him deserved to die.
Not bandit Wad and his son Lasor, sir?
Pud was behind everything.
Khun Yod's murder,
and the raid that destroyed
Bandit Wad's Chum Suea.
I had nothing to do with this.
Are you sure
you had nothing to do with it?
I'm sure.
You and I were never enemies.
You wanted to study at Khao Phrom,
I even wrote you
a letter of recommendation.
Tell me what you want.
I'll give you anything.
I want justice.
I want my name and my father's cleared
for crimes we didn't commit.
Can you do that?
Of course. His Excellency and I
will clear your names.
Good. Don't you dare
break your word.
Otherwise, I'll rip out your tongues
and feed them to dogs.
The Governor announced that Bandit Pud
slaughtered Khun Yod Pakdee's
entire household.
Wasn't it Bandit Wad and his son Lasor?
No. It was Bandit Wad's son
who took down Bandit Pud.
Seriously? How did it flip like this?
Good bandits became bad bandits,
and bad bandits became good bandits.
They say the governor's going to
reward Lasor
and appoint him
as the new Village Chief
of Khuan Phra-ngam, replacing Pud.
Things you never thought you'd see,
you're seeing them now.
I think so too.
I don't agree. Lasor is a bandit,
yet you're appointing him
as your governor's assistant.
Tha Khiri is crawling with bandit dens.
I need someone the people fear
to keep this city under control.
Using bandits to rule over bandits?
Yes. Who understands bandits better
than bandits themselves?
Let them deal with their own kind.
That's the best way.
And we benefit from it too.
You're keeping a cobra at your side.
One day, it'll turn and bite you.
It's been a long time, Lady Duen.
I thought you'd have died
a horrible death by now, Lasor.
If I died,
you wouldn't get to see my face again.
A bandit like you must die
so the land can rise higher.
Bandit this, bandit that.
Even if I'm a bandit,
I've got blood, flesh, and a heart,
no different from yours.
If you don't believe me…
you can try touching for yourself.
Let go of me!
- You should've spoken to him nicely.
- Why should I speak nicely to him?
Look at him.
He's terrifying and disgusting.
Just talking about him gives me chills.
Then he must have something good in him.
That's why Father appointed him
as a close aide.
Is there really
no one better in Tha Khiri,
that we have to let that damned Lasor
be governor's assistant?
Lasor might look scary, but I still think
he's better than Bandit Pud.
They're both evil.
Once we cross this mountain,
we'll be in Huai Yao.
You've finished studying at Khao Phrom.
You've found the Lek Lai.
What will you do next?
Go ask for your hand.
Or do you not want to marry me anymore?
I do.
But before I go ask for your hand,
there's something important
I still have to settle.
More important than me?
It's not like that.
But it's something I must do
for my family.
Blur, take me to meet your family.
My father, mother, and little sister
were all murdered.
If you catch that bandit,
you'll hand him over to the police, right?
If there's no justice in this world,
then I'll use my way.
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.
You disappeared for an entire year.
And now you're Sir Lasor,
Governor's Assistant?
Both Bandit Wad and Lasor have been
completely cleared of all charges.
I am Khun Yod's son,
Village Chief of Khuan Phra-ngam.
Khun Yod's son isn't dead.
Can you tell me where to find him?
I want to meet him.
Why does my body
feel like it's burning alive, Old Master?
Your mind is restless. In turmoil.
There is no Blur anymore. Only Yiam.
Khun Yod's son, whose entire family
was slaughtered by Bandit Wad and his son.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon