Wad, we're in trouble.
The governor's men are raiding Chum Suea.
Burn Chum Suea to the ground!
- Dad!
- Masa namo.
Chum Suea is finished.
Huh?
Wad! Why did you kill him?
I'm going to skin you
and make a tattooed jacket out of it.
I told you to stab his anus!
Dad!
Phutthang chivitang yawa nippanang.
If you two have fate together…
Forgive me, Yod.
I came too late.
I couldn't save you or your family.
Who the hell are you?
So you're about to ordain? Guess I should
get ready to pay my respects.
Who are you, to dare show up
before the Buddha?
Don't go to Khao Phrom.
It's pointless.
Believe me.
I'm going. No one can stop me.
Even if you go,
it's not like they'll teach you sorcery.
I have a letter of admission
from the governor.
They'll have to accept me.
Fine. Suit yourself.
Lasor, have you forgotten already?
Your father wants you to ordain.
Huh?
Lasor.
Manusso si…
Ama bhante…
Your father wants you to ordain.
Manusso si. Ama bhante.
Yiam.
Dad. Mom.
Sleep here tonight, Yiam.
No matter what you hear or see,
do not come out
until dawn.
Why?
Just do as I say.
Yiam.
Come see me.
Come to me, my son.
Dad.
Mom.
Yam.
We've come to take you with us.
Let's go home.
Yiam, I want to hear Phra Aphai Mani.
Never trust mankind.
Their depths are endless, beyond measure.
Even twisting vines
are not as crooked as the human heart.
Come with us, Yiam.
I missed you beyond words.
I want to be with you.
Please stay with me.
Where are you going?
What was that, Master?
What you saw
was created by your own mind.
When it appears again,
stay focused, and it will fade.
Is that the spirit
of my father, my mother,
and my little sister, Master?
No.
Everything arises, exists, and ceases.
Nothing lasts forever.
Everything will be gone one day.
If you still cling to them,
you will never be free from suffering.
Master, I wish to learn sorcery.
For what purpose?
So I can…
take revenge.
I will teach you medicine.
That is no longer what I wish to learn.
Dawn is breaking.
Go gather herbs for the medicine.
But…
Lasor, I've prepared everything
for your ordination.
Lasor.
Nui.
You've gone too far to turn back now,
Lasor.
You should've stayed
to say goodbye to Father Wad.
If Dad saw me, he'd never let me leave.
But he truly wanted you to ordain.
Even if I did, I'd disrobe anyway.
The robe would burn. I'd leave in the end.
After you learn sorcery at Khao Phrom,
what will you do?
I'll make Dad acknowledge me.
Nui,
did you hear that?
Hear what?
I only hear crows.
Wait for me here.
Okay.
- Who are you here for?
- Hey!
Hey?!
Are you trying to kill me?
You came out of nowhere.
I had to protect myself.
Are you Yiwha?
This is Chaem,
another one of your father's friends.
They studied at Khao Phrom together.
Greetings, Uncle Chaem.
So you know
this skull-kicking wild mare too?
What's going on?
Yod is dead,
and Wad's Chum Suea
was completely wiped out.
It's not safe there anymore.
So Wad asked me to bring his daughter here
to stay with you in Huai Yao for a while.
Make yourself at home.
Just think of this place as your own.
You can even stay here
for the rest of your life.
Thanks, Chaem.
That's what friends do. We look out for
each other when everything goes to hell.
Here, have some hot rice porridge.
- Niem.
- Yeah?
I've prepared bedding for you.
As for Yiwha, you'll sleep
in the same room as Noree, my niece.
If you need anything, tell Chang.
Yes.
Oh, Pun. What brings you here?
I brought zongzi for you.
Come in.
Thanks.
Here, eat this.
Alright.
Have you heard any news about Yiam?
The police still haven't found his body.
Maybe he's not dead yet.
If I ever become a police officer,
I'll investigate the case
and get justice for Yiam.
Chang,
who's that woman?
My Dad's friend's daughter.
Her name's Yiwha.
Why? Are you interested?
She's pretty. And cute.
Alright.
I'll introduce you to her.
But I'll warn you.
She's not ordinary.
Pun.
Noree.
Your true match is right here.
Where'd you go?
I went to the market to buy vegetables.
I've gathered
the medicinal herbs for you, Master.
What did you get?
Wild cardamom, for severe fever,
bloating, indigestion,
colic, urinary disorders.
‪Rang Jued is used to detoxify poisons.
It reduces fever
and relieves swelling and pain.
This wild krawan leaf
can't be used yet. It's rotten.
Rotten herbs like these
are like a restless mind,
unsettled,
useless.
Worse, they can even cause harm.
Master,
I want to learn sorcery.
Please have mercy and teach me.
Tomorrow, go gather them again.
But…
You still won't tell me your name?
My name is Orror, Blur.
So we're just going to
keep calling each other that forever?
It doesn't matter what our names are.
As long as I'm me, and you're you.
That's enough.
I don't know your name.
I don't know where you live.
So if one day you disappear,
how would I ever find you?
Even if the world is vast,
our hearts will find each other.
I'll trust you, Orror.
One day, we'll find
our way back to each other.
- Hey, Pun.
- Hm?
How's your father's shop doing?
Same as always.
My dad still wants me
to take over the business.
I told him I don't want to,
but he never listens.
I stitched the tear in your shirt.
Thanks, Noree.
I embroidered this handkerchief for you.
- Thank you, Noree.
- You're welcome.
I feel bad taking it.
Yiwha.
Noree, this is Yiwha, Uncle Niem's niece.
She'll be staying with us.
You should get to know each other.
I'm Yiwha.
I'm Noree.
Wow. It's so pretty.
Did you embroider it yourself?
Can you teach me sometime?
What flower is that? It's beautiful.
A peony.
Chinese people believe
- it represents--
- Love.
Chinese people say peonies
symbolize good fortune and wealth.
It's beautiful,
and the meaning is lovely too.
Anyone who receives it
would surely be happy.
Right?
Yes.
- I like Yiwha.
- Huh?
You just met her once
and you're already into her?
Yiwha is the one I've been looking for.
And what about Noree?
You know that.
I see her like a little sister.
I've never thought of her that way.
I don't want to see her get hurt.
Noree is like my real sister.
Chang, you have to help me.
Help you with what?
Help me to end up with Yiwha.
You've got to be kidding.
Help me, please.
Please, Chang, my best friend!
Please.
Do you like Pun?
I…
We're both girls. Don't be shy.
But Pun doesn't feel that way about me.
Why not?
You're pretty,
and you're good at housework too.
I can't compare to you.
I'm an orphan Uncle Chaem took in.
No one would ever care about me.
You want me to help?
Help?
Help you end up with Pun.
Your plan was incredible, Pud.
You tricked them into killing each other.
And you even got the authorities
to declare Bandit Wad an enemy.
Brilliant.
Now Khun Yod has been dealt with.
Only Wad is left.
I've sent my men to hunt him down.
If they can't take him alive, kill him.
Bandit Wad can't have gotten far.
As for his son, Lasor,
I've sent men to wait at Khao Phrom.
The moment he arrives,
we'll clap him in stocks immediately.
Don't let him escape again.
Yes, sir.
Once we catch Lasor,
luring his father out won't be hard.
Wad will come for his son.
When we catch Bandit Wad,
I'll chop him into 10,000 pieces.
Then I'll be satisfied.
And Bandit Wad's men
the police captured, sir?
Hang them.
Yes, sir.
Nightmare, Lasor?
Yeah.
What did you dream about?
Nothing. Forget it. Sleep.
Okay. I'll go back to sleep then.
Rotten herbs like these
are like a restless mind,
unsettled, useless.
Worse, they can even cause harm.
No matter what you hear or see,
do not come out.
Not until morning.
Ylang-ylang helps ease dizziness,
strengthens the heart,
and helps with urinary trouble.
Black lily, or neraphoosi,
used to nourish
and support pregnant women.
I sorted only fresh herbs.
Not even a trace of rot.
Good.
Keep doing it. Make it a habit.
Master.
Please show me mercy and teach me sorcery.
Every herb
has its proper time.
Some must be picked late, some early.
Some in summer,
some in the rainy season,
some in winter.
Some by day,
some by night.
It depends on what is appropriate.
But Master,
I have to learn sorcery.
Someone is here to see you, Master.
Let him in.
Tomorrow, go gather them again.
The Master allows you to go in.
Wait here, Nui. Don't follow me in.
Okay.
If those two meet, will it be all right?
Khao Phrom is sacred ground.
No one may fight to the death here.
I can't take you as my disciple.
GOVERNOR OF THA KHIRI
Venerable sir,
I have a letter of introduction
from the Governor.
Why won't you accept me?
I teach sorcery
only to those I am able to teach.
I'll study hard.
I'll remember every word you teach.
Whatever you tell me to do,
I'll do it all.
All beings follow their own karma.
Go your own way.
What do you mean?
You're a monk.
You're supposed to help people!
The Master won't teach you. Leave.
Stay out of it.
I hacked my way
through the jungle to get here,
and you're just
sending me back this easily?
If you keep being stubborn,
I'll have people drag you out.
I'm asking one last time.
Will you teach me or not?
You think I don't dare?
Go back.
I will confess an offense.
Lasor,
did Old Master Khrua Phut accept you?
He's guarding his knowledge.
He won't teach me.
Huh? But everyone says he's compassionate.
Nui, don't say his name again.
Let's go back.
Alright.
Where are you rushing off to, Lasor?
I'm not going!
Die!
Lasor, run!
- Go after them!
- Go!
What do we do now?
You won't get away now.
Worst case, we die.
- Ugh!
- Brother!
You!
Nui.
- Die!
- No, you die!
Push the needle up,
loop the thread into a circle,
then go back down in the same spot.
Pull it tight.
Run the stitch under the fabric.
Push the needle up.
Try it.
Push the needle down.
Yeah, push the needle up.
Loop the thread into a circle.
Yes, and go back down in the same spot.
Do it again.
‪Alright.
Then pull it tight.
Run the stitch under the fabric.
- Run--
- Ugh.
This is hard.
Throwing knives is way easier.
You can throw knives?
Can you teach me?
Sure. I'll teach you.
Okay.
Pun, did you come to see Uncle Chaem?
Well, I…
I…
He wants to ask Yiwha
to go for a walk at the market.
Come with me, Yiwha.
Sure.
Come on, Noree. Let's go to the market.
Here are some vegetables.
What would you like?
Huai Yao's a small district,
nothing like the bustle of Tha Khiri.
You must be bored here.
Then you should take Yiwha out
for walks often, so she won't get bored.
I won't be bored.
I've got Noree as a friend.
There's a lot we want to do together.
So what do you like doing?
Making flower garlands?
Sewing? Cooking?
Ah.
Everything you just said,
I can't do a single one of.
Then you must like dressing up.
Perfect.
Pun's father is a big merchant here.
Let him take you to his store sometime.
There are lots of pretty things for women.
I don't like dressing up.
I don't like makeup or lipstick.
And I don't like perfume
or scented oils either.
Then what do you like?
I like…
throwing knives.
Oh.
I've been wanting to ask you.
Did your dad teach you to throw knives?
That's wild. I've never seen
a father teach his daughter that.
Uncle Niem taught me.
My dad doesn't like me
doing stuff like that.
All my stuff is ruined!
So what?
Are you going to pay
the easy way, or the hard way?
I really don't have anything, Saeng.
I haven't sold a thing this morning.
Don't have?
Then sell your daughter to me.
No.
She's still young. Please, have mercy.
Don't take her.
- You're so tough, huh?
- Mom!
- Help me!
- Stop screaming!
You wanna get slapped?
Picking on women and kids?
Real men don't do that.
It's none of your business.
Saeng's Khun Paeng's man.
Don't mess with them.
You're with the authorities and you think
you can bully villagers however you want?
Hey.
Teach this mouthy bitch a lesson.
Yes.
I'll protect you, Yiwha.
Hey.
Saeng pissed himself.
Saeng pissed himself!
- He pissed himself.
- Look.
Saeng pissed himself.
This isn't over yet.
- Let's go.
- Go.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
It's good you're safe.
Yiwha.
Uncle Niem.
I told you, didn't I?
Not to go out and stir up trouble.
I didn't start it.
They did.
You're talking back?
They were bullying people
who couldn't fight back.
How could I just stand there?
We have to help people in trouble.
- You taught me that.
- Talking back?
Don't run!
Uncle Niem,
Saeng started it with the vendor first.
Yiwha just went in to help.
It's true, Uncle.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Alright, alright. It's done.
Let's talk about what to do next.
Saeng's close to Tim.
By now he's probably run back
to report to his boss.
Dad,
can I ask you something?
Mm.
Who exactly is Yiwha?
She's Niem's niece.
Come on, Dad.
Don't play dumb.
What kind of woman is that skilled?
Yeah, I watched her throw knives
right at Saeng's men.
Even I was stunned.
Right. Who is Yiwha's family?
If I tell you, keep your mouths shut.
Yiwha is Bandit Wad's daughter.
Huh?
Bandit Wad?
The one they're hunting
for killing Khun Yod's whole family?
Then that means
Bandit Wad has two kids,
Yiwha and Lasor.
So Yiwha's the daughter
of a bandit-murderer.
Don't jump to conclusions.
Something about this is off.
Bandit Wad and Khun Yod
were fellow disciples at Khao Phrom.
There's no way Bandit Wad killed Khun Yod.
Friends kill friends all the time.
How do you know he didn't?
Because Niem and I are his friends too.
Come in.
This cave stores the collected scriptures
of all disciplines
taught at Khao Phrom,
medical texts, astrology manuals,
and texts of sorcery.
Sorcery?
Not everyone is allowed to enter this cave
Only those granted permission
by the Master.
Absorb whatever knowledge you can,
according to the limits
of your own wisdom.
Nui.
Nui, wake up.
Wake up.
Nui.
Brother.
How did we end up here?
I don't know either.
Nui,
I'll go find Siam weed leaves
to stop the bleeding. Wait here.
Brother…
Brother.
Don't leave me.
Nui,
you're like my own little brother.
I'd never leave you.
Whose laughter is that?
You heard it too?
Come on, Nui. I know how to save you now.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Slowly.
Hang in there.
Come on.
Where are you?
At last,
you've come to me.
A ghost? Is he a ghost?
No.
He's not a ghost.
How do you know?
I think I've met him before.
If you're really brave,
then come closer to me.
Nui,
wait for me here.
Slowly.
Lasor.
If you're going to kill someone, kill me.
But let my brother go.
You want to learn sorcery
so badly, don't you?
I'll teach you myself.
Yiwha said she was going to
look for her brother.
That's asking for trouble.
I'm sorry, Uncle Niem.
I just want to see Lasor once.
A ghost?!
- How did you get here?
- Do you miss me?
Yod's talisman? Did you kill Yod?
Why wouldn't I kill someone like him?
Etesang sappayaka…
I never trusted them.
You mean Khun Paeng or Bandit Pud?
Both of them.
I need something for my offering.
- What is it?
- His life.
You still won't abandon the idea
of going back for revenge?
My suffering will only end,
when they face
the consequences of their karma.
You killed my family.
Finally, we met.
Come on!
Hey!
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon