Let them do what they want.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid that prophecy will come true.
Just don't let Dad know
I've been secretly treating your baby.
Don't let me find out
you've been sneaking around
using the healer skills I taught you
to treat people again.
Behind the mountains north
of our district, there's a hidden city.
A hidden city?
They've seen a beautiful woman
and then she vanished
into the thicket over there.
I have something I want your help with.
For as long as I can remember,
Wad and I have never crossed paths.
Tell me what you want me to do.
I'll do anything.
Fine. I'll teach you sorcery.
In exchange,
bring me the Boar King's tusk.
The Boar King's tusk?
Where are we supposed to find that?
Then let your brother go get it
if he's got the guts.
But the Boar King is a sacred beast.
It has supernatural power.
Blades and bullets can't harm it.
Who could possibly kill it?
This is sacred black coral.
It grants invulnerability and protection.
If you want it, I'll give it to you.
Fine.
I'll bring you the Boar King's tusk.
It's just a wild boar.
How dangerous could it be?
The remedy needs climbing vine,
ebony bark,
water spinach root,
hoof fungus, dung fungus,
fairy-root, mong root.
Everything's here,
except Nang Yaem root.
Are you asleep yet, Lasor?
Lasor.
Nui?
Where's Lasor? Where did he go?
I can't tell you.
He told me not to tell anyone.
Nui, if you don't tell me,
I'm telling Dad.
No.
Please don't tell Father Wad.
If he finds out, Lasor is dead for sure.
Then tell me now. Where did he go?
Thongyoo the tycoon
lives right in the heart of Tha Khiri.
He's backed by powerful officials.
No one dares touch him.
He's seized farmland all over the area.
Prices are sky-high
because everything's under his monopoly.
Then why not sell to the Chinese?
I hear they pay better than anyone.
Transport costs make it pointless.
So the villagers have no choice
but to let him bleed them dry.
Still, I need to thank you, Wad,
for helping us rob Thongyoo.
When you're in trouble, I help.
For now, get some rest.
When the timing's right,
I'll let you know.
Thanks, Wad.
I won't forget this.
Dad.
He couldn't stay put
and went off to hunt the Boar King?
He's begging for death.
They say the Boar King has crystal tusks
that make one invincible.
Lasor must be after them.
When I find him,
I'll whip him until his back splits open.
Niem, Yai, Nui, you're coming with me.
You, Yiwha,
go home.
Can't I come with you,?
I'm worried about Lasor.
This is no place for a woman. Go home.
He's so stupid.
I never thought Bandit Wad's son
would be this stupid.
He really thinks killing the Boar King
is easy?
Dream on. Even seasoned hunters
with powerful magic went after it,
not a single one came back alive.
I'm dying to see Wad's face
when he finds out
his son got gutted by a boar.
Well, Uncle… maybe not.
Maybe he won't die.
The sacred thing you gave him
might actually protect him.
Sacred my ass!
It's just some coral I picked up.
I muttered a few fake spells,
and that idiot believed it was sacred.
Damn, this is fun.
So you sent him off to die?
You're pure evil, Uncle.
That's called being smart, you moron.
Using someone else's hands to kill,
while mine stay clean.
With a brain like that,
you deserve another drink.
Please protect Lasor.
Found it, the Nang Yaem plant.
A king cobra.
Snakes come with heavy rains.
I'll teach you a spell to subdue them.
Instead of teaching me a snake spell,
you could teach me herbs for snake venom.
Better safe than sorry.
Some snakes are deadly.
They can kill in minutes,
like the king cobra. If it bites you,
there's no time to search for herbs.
Learn protective magic.
You'll need it when it matters.
I wouldn't be that unlucky, Dad.
Don't move.
Help me.
A king cobra
only tracks movement in front of it.
Keep its attention on you.
What?
I said keep it focused on you.
I'll find an opening and kill it.
Killing is a sin.
You're about to die,
and you're worried about sin?
Who's there?
Come down here and talk to me.
Are you a ghost or a man?
If you're scared, then go back.
You challenging me?
The Boar King is coming
to lick the mineral earth.
How do you know?
Watch the wind.
Mo-thon, phut-khlon, tha-thon, ya-lut.
Cast the spell, hold your breath,
and stab it in the throat.
Without my gun,
how am I supposed to shoot it?
It's coming.
Who is that?
That's the same voice. No doubt.
Lucky I'm downwind.
If not,
I don't even want to think about it.
Shit, the wind changed.
Please help me.
Cast the spell, hold your breath,
and stab it in the throat.
Mo-thon, phut-khlon, tha-thon, ya-lut.
Lasor!
Dad?
Please forgive me.
If I hadn't killed you,
you would've killed him.
It's just a dead snake.
Do we really have to bury it
and give a eulogy?
A snake values its life
just like people do.
If you hadn't barged into its territory,
it wouldn't have attacked you.
Understand, Blur?
Blur this, Blur that. That's not my name.
Then what's your name?
You tell me yours first,
then I'll tell you mine.
I don't care.
I'll just call you Blur.
Blur, Blur, Blur!
Fine. Then I'll call you…
Orror.
Hey! Are you saying
I'm all twitchy, like some skittish filly?
It suits you perfectly. Orror.
Orror, Orror, Orror,
Orror.
Blur, Blur, Blur!
Orror, Orror, Orror!
I can't be bothered arguing with you.
Running away because you lost?
Blur, Blur, Blur.
- Blur.
- Orror.
Are you sick?
No. Why?
Your face is as red as a tamarind gourd.
Do you want me to check you?
It's almost daylight.
You're from… the Hidden City, right?
Oh, Yiam.
You scared me.
You're up very early, ma'am.
I haven't slept at all.
Oh? Why?
I'm afraid the buffalo will be stolen.
Especially now, the work buffalo
at the Tha Khiri's governor's sugar mill
have a disease and are dying off in herds.
It's hit the sugar factory owners hard.
So those damned thieves keep stealing
villagers' buffalo and selling them,
because the price is good.
Ever since my dad became
Village Chief of Khuan Phra-ngam,
there haven't been many robberies.
Just hearing Khun Yod Pakdee's name
makes them run for their lives.
Don't worry, ma'am.
Khuan Phra-ngam and Tha Khiri
are right next to each other.
It's just a short walk away.
How could I not worry?
Then how about this?
If you still don't feel safe,
I'll figure out a way to protect them.
If you do that,
won't thieves still steal them, Yiam?
I'll smear lime behind its ear.
Even if they steal it, we can track it
and get it back. Don't worry.
Yiam.
You're here. Something big happened.
Is someone hurt?
Don't ask yet.
Once we get home, you'll know.
- I'm heading out, ma'am.
- Okay.
Dad!
I risked my life, killed the Boar King,
and brought back its tusks
and you shot them to pieces!
Or did you want to test it
to see if the Boar King's tusks were real?
Is this the time to joke, Nui?
Every damn day you give me headaches.
If that Boar King
had gored you to death, then what?
I killed it, Dad.
Instead of praising me,
you're yelling at me?
Let me ask you this.
Have I ever mattered to you?
Everything I do is wrong.
Lasor!
If Wad didn't love you,
he wouldn't have brought the whole village
out to search for you.
The more I forbid you,
the harder you push back.
I say it's wrong, you insist it's right.
Listen to me, Lasor.
You had no protective magic at all,
yet you still went alone
to hunt the Boar King?
How can you be that reckless, huh?
Why? Does your life mean nothing to you?
Don't you love yourself?
I'm not dying that easily. Don't worry.
Even if I don't have magic like you…
I've got something good on me.
Something good? What is it?
This, Dad. This is it.
Black coral?
Yes.
Who gave it to you? The pirates?
Who gave it to you?
Dad!
- Dad!
- How the hell is a piece of scrap stone
supposed to protect you?
One step,
and I could crush it under my foot.
That's not true. I don't believe you.
So you believe those filthy pirates
more than your own father?
Burn this into that head of yours, Lasor,
you're alive
because your time hasn't come yet.
Not because of some worthless little rock.
Stop being stupid.
Yeah, I'm stupid, Dad.
I'm pathetic.
I don't even deserve to be your son.
Go on.
Beat me to death.
Don't you dare challenge me, Lasor.
Yiam is here.
What's happening, Dad?
You're back, you troublemaker.
The medicine you gave me,
it seemed to work during the day,
but once night fell,
he became feverish again.
You went and treated people again,
didn't you?
Where do you get the nerve
to treat people like that?
Come with me. Now.
I'll fetch a doctor to your house.
For today, go home first, alright?
Dad.
I told you already, didn't I?
Don't go around
treating people recklessly.
Your medical knowledge
is worth less than a toad's tail.
You're just stealing bits and pieces,
reading what I made you transcribe.
If you make a mistake and someone dies,
do you have the means to repay them?
That's why I asked
to study medicine in the capital,
so I can come back
and treat them properly.
A stubborn show-off like you
isn't fit to be a doctor.
Where have you been?
Why are you back so late?
I went up to pray on the hill.
Just to pray?
And I helped someone
who was bitten by a king cobra.
Don't let your father find out.
He already doesn't want you
wandering outside.
Yes, Uncle.
Has Lasor come back yet?
You ungrateful son!
I'll whip you until you learn your lesson!
Didn't I order you
not to get involved with those pirates?
They can't be trusted. They tricked you
and you didn't even realize it!
Dad, stop!
Lasor won't dare do it again.
Stubborn like him?
You think he'll listen?
Dad!
Please, I beg you. He's already hurt,
he's barely alive.
- Don't you help him.
- Father Wad.
Beat me instead.
I'm the one who took Lasor to them.
Nui,
don't stop him.
If he wants to beat me to death,
let him.
Nui,
get your big brother out of my sight.
I don't want to see his face.
Lasor.
- Lasor.
- Brother.
I'm not sure
whether I should tell the children
about Grandma Chi Pa Khao's prophecy.
If you were going to tell them,
you would've told them long ago.
You wouldn't wait until now.
My wife and I were afraid
that prophecy would become
a scar in their hearts.
If word gets out and people find out,
they'll hate Yiwha and Lasor,
call them cursed,
bringing trouble to others.
Don't worry
about what hasn't happened yet.
It only makes your heart
miserable for nothing.
I mean to raise them well,
to change their fate.
To make sure the other two parts
of the prophecy never come true.
No power is greater than karma.
Karma's results
don't follow belief. They follow truth.
All things arise
from causes and conditions.
You reap what you sow.
When you create good causes,
good results will follow.
Hurry and apply this
before the abscess bursts.
That way your manhood won't rot.
And for now, stay away from the brothel.
No more. I've learned my lesson.
Thank you so much, Yiam.
Alright.
So you're really not going
to treat anyone anymore?
It's my dad's order.
What can I do?
I don't want to go against him.
Such a shame.
If you ever got to study medicine,
you'd be a great doctor,
helping so many people.
Aren't you going to read
"Phra Aphai Mani" in the library?
Father chained the door shut.
No idea what he's so protective of.
He's angry I snuck out to treat people, so
he banned me from reading medical texts,
and you ended up losing
your Wat Ko tales too.
Don't you want to be
a village chief like Dad?
I don't want trouble with anyone.
I want to study medicine,
work at Siriraj Hospital.
Then I can bring our family
to settle in the capital.
Why move? It's already good here.
Tha Khiri is full of bandit dens.
I don't want you and Mom
risking your lives here.
With Dad here,
what's there to be afraid of?
So what story
do you want to hear today? I'll tell you.
"Phra Aphai Mani."
How's Lasor doing?
He still hasn't woken up.
Too bad for him.
Uncle Niem,
the other day I heard you
talking to Dad about the prophecy.
What really happened?
Why is he so afraid of it?
What prophecy?
Where's that damn Chi Pa Khao hag?
I'm going to kill her.
Didn't you promise that if I told you,
you wouldn't let it get to you?
How can I sit still?
If that filthy hag hadn't run her mouth,
I'd have learned sorcery ages ago.
Why didn't he ever tell me
and Lasor about this?
Some things aren't worth remembering.
Maybe he just loves himself
and is too scared to die.
Don't talk like that, Lasor.
Your father isn't afraid of dying.
He's afraid he'll die
by his own child's hand.
He doesn't want you two to rot in hell.
That's why he wants you
to escape that fate.
The prophecy said you'd bring
a great catastrophe to Chum Suea,
and I'll bring death to my own father.
If he's been haunted
by Grandma Chi Pa Khao's words,
then we have to make sure
the other two parts
never come true.
How?
You have to help me.
Four chang, two tamlueng.
Phraya Raksa Thani.
Two jars of pickled lychees.
Four bolts of silk.
Six porcelain bowls.
Fourteen chang, three baht, two fueang.
Did you price it wrong, Pa?
Why is it so expensive?
You know
what it takes just to get goods ashore?
We had to gamble
on whether pirates would raid the ship
and whether we could even land the cargo.
And we still have to pay fees
to Phraya Dechanurak.
What's left is a fistful of profit.
At this price, it's still cheap.
Where are you going?
You're not done with the accounts.
Being a merchant is this hard,
and you still want me
to inherit the business?
You little brat.
You don't want to be a boss?
Then how are you going to be a real man?
I've taught you since you were a kid,
to the point
my mouth's about to tear to my ears,
and none of it's gotten
into that thick head of yours?
You nag me every day,
but I still want to serve in government.
Haven't you heard what they say?
"Ten merchants aren't worth one official."
Forget those police-whatever jobs.
I'm not allowing it.
All they do is chase criminals.
The moment they see a blade,
they shrink back.
Standing guard on the road
is all they ever do.
Pa,
that's the person's fault, not the job's.
Your son will become a patrol officer.
Just wait and see.
Chaem is waiting on the veranda
to cut your hair, sir.
Alright.
I'll come back and help
finish the accounts later, okay?
Hey, hey, hey.
Pun! Come help me first!
Where are you going?
Oh my…
Hello, Uncle Chaem.
Hey, Chang.
Let me help.
Thank you, Chang.
Uncle Chaem, please take your time
cutting Pa's hair today.
If you finish too fast,
I'll get dragged back to work too soon.
We were thinking of seeing Yiam.
Khun Yod's keeping him on a tight leash.
Doesn't look like he can leave the house.
I knew it.
Every time I invited you, you never came.
Just don't go stirring up trouble again,
you two.
- Yes.
- Alright. We'll head off then.
Where are you two off to now?
Every time you bunch up together,
something happens.
You're always leaving me
to clean up after you.
Since you were kids, you've never changed.
These kids…
Saeng, Khun Paeng's servant,
is here to see you, sir.
I told him you were
in the middle of a haircut,
but he says it's urgent.
He has to see you right now.
This month,
Tim's already sent people
to squeeze money out of me twice.
Perfect.
I've been wanting a haircut anyway.
Chin Seng's rich.
Pay my haircut fee for me.
You won't even break a sweat, will you?
Uncle Chaem, here's the haircut fee.
I'll pay for Saeng myself.
Why would you pay for him?
Doesn't the government pay you wages?
He must be broke.
Otherwise he wouldn't act like a beggar.
It's just a haircut fee.
He can't even pay that.
Since he's already asking people
to feed him a haircut,
we're going to Khun Yod's house,
do you want to come beg for food there?
Chin Seng,
your kids have mouths this filthy
and you do nothing?
You just let them curse me
right to my face.
I may not have a title,
but I'm Khun Paeng's right-hand man.
Show some respect.
My son
is this handsome man here. That one's not.
Whose kid he is doesn't matter.
Tell him to apologize now.
Or this won't end well.
What do you want me to apologize for?
For Chin Seng's son
paying for your haircut?
Or for inviting you
to come eat at Khun Yod's house?
Oh.
Sorry, my hand slipped.
Mind picking up my scissors for me?
Khun Paeng sent me
to discuss the tea-and-hot-water fee.
I didn't come for trouble.
But it seems
Chin Seng isn't ready to talk.
I'll come back another day.
Hey, Chaem.
People say you've been ordained
your whole life.
Your hands have only ever held scissors.
So you don't know blades or weapons,
is that true?
Oh, that's good.
Finished bathing already, dear?
Are you hungry?
Not yet.
What are you making?
Fermented beef. We had too much meat
and couldn't finish it,
so I'm curing it. It keeps for days.
Make coconut curry with it
for me sometime.
Of course.
Mom.
Is Dad home today?
Hm?
Looking for him?
Going to make up with him?
That's good. Don't stay angry
with your father too long.
If he's not home,
I want to sneak into the library
and read the medical texts.
He went out.
He might be back late this evening.
If he's out, can I have the key?
You…
Wait a second.
Here.
Thanks, Mom.
Your father told me that when he takes you
to study at Khao Phrom,
he'll ask Old Master Khrua Phut
to teach you medicine-making too.
But I heard
Old Master Khrua Phut chooses
what each student learns.
He might not let me study medicine-making.
- Yiam!
- Yiam, are you home?
Pun, Chang,
I'm here.
I heard your father tore you apart?
Yeah.
Look at you,
droopy as a miserable chicken.
Don't tell me
you were sniffling and crying.
This idiot.
No, I didn't cry.
Are you sure you're okay?
We were supposed to go
to Pun's house, and you didn't come.
Oh, yeah.
I kept thinking
about the fight with my dad.
Come on.
Fathers and sons fight, it passes.
Don't overthink it,
or you'll get constipated.
Yiam, I'm in trouble.
What happened, ma'am?
My buffalo is missing. I've searched
everywhere and can't find it.
What happened, Yiam?
Pun, Chang, come with me.
Your Excellency,
the stolen buffalo has already
trampled several loads of sugarcane.
Ever since I moved here,
everything's been easy.
No need to watch my back
like in the capital.
And last night,
we got another one too, sir.
My men are flawless, no faults at all.
They've tied it up behind the sugar mill.
Those bandits stole buffalo
and sold them until the pens overflowed.
- Is that so?
- Yes, sir.
Good.
That one's my neighbor's buffalo.
Buffalo all have two horns and four legs.
How do you know it's the same one?
Yeah.
Look behind its ear.
I smeared lime paste there.
Damn, Yiam,
how did you even think of that?
Caught red-handed, right on the hide.
Hey.
My father said
the sugar mill, the gambling den, and
the brothel belong to the new governor.
If your buffalo's tied up here,
does that mean the governor
is stealing villagers' buffalo?
A fancy noble for nothing,
still squeezing the villagers.
I'm going to tell everyone.
If you're taking the buffalo back,
take it, but don't make it a big deal.
Yeah, I'm with Chang.
I still can't even face my father
after the last mess.
Let's leave it for now.
Are you done yet?
Almost.
I hear people coming. Hurry!
I'm hurrying.
Hey! Are you stealing
the governor's buffalo?
Somebody!
Buffalo thieves!
Hey! No!
- Help!
- It's not like that.
Someone's stealing a buffalo!
Hey, they're stealing
our governor's buffalo!
- No.
- They are!
What are they crowding around for?
- Hey, don't talk.
- Look at them.
- Don't let them get away!
- My men tied the buffalo there.
Let's go take a look.
Move! What are you crowding for?
And this is the governor's buffalo.
Give it back!
Hey. What's all this commotion?
Last night, thieves stole a buffalo in
Khuan Phra-ngam. I came to take it back.
From Khuan Phra-ngam?
What proof do you have
that this buffalo is yours, kid?
I marked it with lime paste
behind its ear.
Take a look.
Let me see.
It's true, Khun Paeng.
If it were Your Excellency's buffalo,
you wouldn't have lime paste
smeared behind its ear, would you?
You--
Hey.
Buffalo?
I can buy as many as I want.
If anyone thinks a governor like me
would steal villagers' buffalo,
then that person is more stupid
than the buffalo.
It's probably just a misunderstanding.
You found the buffalo you wanted.
Take it back.
Send someone to teach them a lesson.
Don't let them come
running their mouths at me again.
But that's Khun Yod Pakdee's son, sir.
Then don't let his father find out, idiot!
Yes, sir.
Did you give him
the medicine like I told you?
Yes, both the oral medicine
and the ointment.
Keep an eye on him.
See if he runs a fever.
If he gets worse, come tell me right away.
Yes.
Father Wad.
- He'd be happy to know you're worried.
- No.
Don't tell him I came.
A silver barb.
And it's huge.
Aunt Phon, let's cook silver barb tonight.
Lasor said he wanted to eat it.
What kind of tusk is this?
Let me see.
A boar tusk. Look at that huge tusk.
That must be the Boar King!
The Boar King?
They say the Boar King has crystal tusks
that make one invincible.
Lasor must be after them.
It's rare, Yihwa.
Keep it on you. Blades can't pierce you.
My goodness, I can't believe
it wandered into the trap.
You've got real merit.
Then should I give it to Dad?
I heard Khao Phrom's school
doesn't worship charms
made from tusks, ivory, shells, or horns.
They respect the spell craft
you carry within yourself.
Your father already has strong skills.
Just keep it.
Oh, and don't give it to your brother.
Your father doesn't want him
obsessed with cursed charms like this.
Is this black coral stone the real thing?
Of course it is.
I saw you bump into her on purpose
and snatch her bracelet.
Thanks for catching the thief for me.
Who's that woman?
Is that his wife?
Does this stone have any power?
Do you like it?
I like it so much.
Do you like the bracelet
or do you like me?
Then let me walk you home.
Lady Duen,
pretty face, pretty name.
That's my type.
I like her.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon