I'll make you taste the same agony
you caused my father.
Ehi klai klai, piyan ma-ma.
Lasor!
I'm warning you about your enemy.
Rip the Lek Lai out of his body.
Then you can kill him.
I'll drag you two down
to face the karma you created.
I'll find the evidence
to prove their innocence too.
I'll clear them of your accusations.
That black-masked bastard again?
I told you to look into him!
And you still haven't found anything?
Song said the man can't be shot or cut.
I think he must be someone with sorcery.
Could he be one of Lasor's men?
If he finds out we betrayed him,
we're completely finished.
His sister is in our hands, sir.
He won't dare do anything.
You bastards! Why did you capture me?
Watch your mouth.
You're standing before the governor.
It's fine. I don't mind.
After all, you're Lasor's little sister.
What does my brother have to do with this?
Lasor practices sorcery.
And worse, he's a bandit's son.
I never know when he might turn on me.
So I need you as leverage.
Or you could say as a hostage.
My brother
will never fall for your tricks.
Lasor is stupid. Stupid again and again.
Stupid like a buffalo.
Even if he dies and is reborn,
he still won't be smarter than us.
If Lasor finds out, he won't let you live.
I'm not afraid of your brother
because I have you.
Actually, you're young and pretty.
I think you'd be better off
cooperating with me.
Cooperating how?
If you become my woman
and persuade your brother
to swear loyalty to me,
I promise you both
power, fortune, and comfort for life.
Interested?
Let me think about it.
No need to think too long.
I can't hold back much longer.
You venomous snake!
You've got a lot of nerve!
One more step,
and you can start
planning your boss's funeral.
Yiwha?
Hey!
Back off! Back off!
Go.
The black-masked man. You die!
Sangkhalikapi khanthakhanthang
tharangi niwirari.
I surrender. Tell me what you want.
You're the one
who ordered Chin Seng's death, aren't you?
Yes.
I ordered Lasor and Pae to kill him.
You heard that clearly, didn't you?
And the slaughter
of Khun Yod Pakdee's family?
You were behind that too, weren't you?
Tell me the truth.
I don't know!
You're the one who sent men
to kill Khun Yod Pakdee
and framed my father and brother.
There's been an order from above.
I was ordered to kill Khun Yod Pakdee.
By whom?
Phraya…
We have to get out of here. Now.
So now you finally see how rotten
your brother Lasor really is.
Lasor might've been used.
There's no proof he killed Chin Seng.
But he worked with Pae
and raided Chin Seng's house.
Do you still think
there's no blood on his hands
Before Duang died, he confessed
there was an order
to send people to kill Khun Yod Pakdee.
But he died before he could finish.
The one who truly killed your father
must be that Phraya he mentioned.
He was afraid to die. He said
whatever would save his own skin.
If it wasn't true,
then why was he silenced?
Even if someone ordered Duang,
the ones
who brutally slaughtered my family
were still Lasor and Bandit Wad.
My father would never
do something that vile.
I'll drag them out
and make you see it with your own eyes.
You're blinded by hatred.
I'm done talking to you.
Someone's following us.
They're gone.
Where are you going?
To find proof that my father and brother
aren't the monsters you claim they are.
There must be something hidden
behind all this. The name just came out.
We can't go anywhere right now.
Duang was part of the government.
With him dead like this, the authorities
will hunt us down until they catch us.
I don't want to run away with you.
We're already in the same boat now.
If I let you go alone, you won't survive.
Besides, you can't die yet,
not until you see the consequences
of the karma your father created.
Yiam!
Let go. Let me go.
Duen… what should we do?
Dad has left us…
There were so many of you,
and you still let my father be killed.
When I regained consciousness,
everything was already like this.
His chest
was torn open, his heart ripped out.
Only a madman
could be that brutally savage.
Do you have any idea who did it?
If it wasn't Lasor's sister,
the daughter of Bandit Wad,
then it must have been
the masked man who helped her.
What does this have to do with Yiwha?
How would I know?
All I know is they're on the same side.
They killed the governor.
Who exactly is that masked man?
Tim! Stop this right now! Tim!
I said stop!
What is this?
Phraya Dechanurak is dead.
You can't stay here anymore.
What right do you have to chase us out?
This is my father's residence.
Why can't I stay?
This is the governor's residence,
not your father's house.
A new governor is coming from the capital.
I must clean up all the trash
before he arrives.
But Duen and I have nowhere to go yet.
Can't you give us a little more time?
No. These are orders.
Take your things and leave.
A corpse-crow feather?
I was cleansing Lasor of the dark magic.
Someone sent corpse-crows to take him.
I fear it might be him.
There are many
who can summon corpse-crows.
It might not be him.
Besides, he already died.
We all saw it with our own eyes.
Petch!
And what if he isn't dead?
If he's still alive,
he would've shown himself by now.
Put your mind at ease, Wad.
Petch will never come back.
I'll go look for Lasor.
You two,
please help me take care of Yiwha.
Yiwha went to look for Lasor
at the governor's residence yesterday.
What did you say, Niem?
She went to question her brother
about Chin Seng's case, and Yod as well.
Yiwha…
Why does she always
bring trouble upon herself?
Search everywhere!
Someone's coming. Wad, hurry and run.
Search every corner. Go.
What's going on, Khun Paeng?
Prisoners escaped.
I'm here to look for them.
What crime did they commit
for you to come looking here?
They murdered Phraya Dechanurak,
the governor of Tha Khiri.
I suspect they're hiding here.
Since when did my house
become a hideout for violent criminals?
Since your niece
teamed up with that masked man
and killed the governor last night.
The masked man?
Yiwha killed the governor? Impossible.
Hey, Saeng!
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Take them to the residence
for questioning.
Yes, sir.
Go. Walk.
- Go.
- I can walk on my own.
Walk.
- Hey.
- Walk.
I can walk on my own.
Hey? Dad--
Why did you stop me?
I'm going to help my dad.
Even if you go, you can't help.
Worse, you'd get arrested too.
So what do you want me to do?
Just stand by and watch them
take my dad away?
They hold all the power.
You have to think carefully.
Don't act rashly.
Otherwise, you'll end up dead
like a stray dog.
I need to send word to Pun right away.
Hey! You're blocking our way.
Are you looking to die?
Bandit Wad?
Release my friends and get lost.
Dream on. If you come any closer,
your friends will become forest ghosts.
Pathetic weapons like yours
can't do anything to them.
You wanna try?
Why don't we get serious then?
You're tough, huh?
I'll get back at you!
Hey! Why the rush?
I haven't even finished stretching yet.
Hey, don't forget,
disciples of Khao Phrom
never bully the weak.
Chaem, Niem,
I have something
I need you two to help me with.
PATROL UNIT
Khun Paeng testified
that Bandit Wad intercepted
Uncle Niem and Uncle Chaem
while they were being escorted
for interrogation at the residence.
Where is my dad now? Is he safe?
I don't know.
But judging by Khun Paeng's condition,
I think your dad should be fine.
I think Uncle Chaem,
Uncle Niem, and Bandit Wad
are trying to find a way
to help Yiwha right now.
I never thought Yiwha
would dare kill the governor.
I don't believe it either,
but Khun Paeng insists
that Yiwha and the masked man
murdered Phraya Decha.
The masked man? Again?
This is starting to feel
far from ordinary.
What does the masked man
have to do with this?
Does he even know Yiwha?
The masked man
handed Song and Pae over to the police.
He was also present at Duang's death.
That means he's here
specifically to punish the wicked.
Right now, the police
are trying to gather clues.
That mysterious masked man
might also know something
about Lasor's disappearance.
The one who probably knows the most
is Tim,
but he'll never confess,
no matter what happens.
Don't forget. There's still Bandit Pae.
GUARDING SCHEDULE
DAENG, MHAN
Pae,
are you ready to confess yet?
No. I'm not ready.
Phraya Decha,
the governor, has been murdered.
If you keep your mouth shut,
more people will die because of you.
The governor is dead?
Yes. And the next one could be you.
Can you stop pressuring me?
I'm already stressed to death as it is.
If you don't tell the truth,
there's nothing I can do to help you.
Just wait until it's my turn.
Where are we going, Duen?
Stupid question.
We'll find a way back to the capital.
It's far. How are we getting there?
Do you even know the way?
Where are you two beauties headed?
None of your business.
Move aside.
Well, well. Feisty? I like that.
Hey.
You take the older one.
I'll take the younger.
Hey! Follow them!
Where are you going?
Please let us go.
Don't hurt me and my sister.
Let you go? Sure.
After you become our women.
I'd rather die
than be the woman of hell-beasts like you.
Big mouth, huh?
Lasor.
Pathamang phinthukang
chatang, trinikattawa, nana.
Hurry up.
The tracks go this way.
Where did the tracks go?
Where did he go?
Did he fly?
Yeah. That masked man
must have powerful sorcery.
Idiot!
No human can fly.
No matter how strong his magic is,
he won't escape me.
I'll drag him out and rip his heart out.
Go. Search everywhere.
WANTED DEAD
MASKED MAN, YIWHA
Idiot! You couldn't catch the masked man
and you still dare show your face?
Whoa!
Sir, we searched
the entire forest, but found no trace.
Could they have fled Tha Khiri?
He ran with Yiwha.
They can't have gone far.
But Yiwha's as capable as any grown man.
She's still a woman.
Hurry up. Gather more men.
We must catch the masked man and Yiwha
before the new governor arrives.
- Go!
- Yes, sir.
Tim's men are gone.
But they'll come back for sure.
Then we should split up.
I don't like following orders.
To wait, to eat, to sleep.
Here.
Take it.
We split up here.
You never listen.
Look at this.
WANTED DEAD
MASKED MAN, YIWHA
By now, your face must be everywhere.
How are you supposed to escape alone?
I can survive on my own.
And where exactly are you planning to go?
If you can't think of anything,
come with me.
We'll hide for now
until we find who really killed Duang.
That's final. Follow me.
Ordering again.
You must be tired. Let's rest.
I'm not tired.
- You're hungry, right?
- I'm not.
Do I have to feed you myself?
So where are we going to hide?
Khao Phrom.
Old Master Khrua Phut
will get dragged into trouble.
We won't hide there for long.
Old Master Khrua Phut is well-versed
in both white and black sorcery.
He'll definitely know
whose handiwork those black claws were,
the ones that ripped Duang's heart out.
Why are you following us?
I'm just following.
- Just get lost. Go!
- Duen.
It's good to have Lasor with us.
What if the forest bandits come back?
Someone like him is no different
from low-class forest bandits.
Lasor, I'm sorry.
Duen is still shaken.
She spoke without thinking.
I don't mind.
Dogs bark. They don't bite.
You hell spawn! Are you calling me a dog?
You dog-born bastard!
- Duen, enough.
- How dare you?
We're lucky Lasor came to protect us.
Or do you want to risk our lives
and let bandits kill and rape us for real?
I'm so exhausted.
Hang in there, Duen.
Where did Lasor go?
He abandoned us for sure.
I knew it. That rotten bandit.
Once he saw we had no valuables,
he disappeared.
See, Duangjai?
Did you say he'd protect us?
How did you believe that?
Damn lunatic bandit!
Lasor went to fetch our bags. See?
Lasor.
Where did you disappear to?
Our gold and jewels are all still here.
Thank you so much, Lasor.
The bags were far away.
You came back in no time.
You're really amazing.
Let's go bathe and change clothes.
I'm sticky all over.
Don't follow us.
- Duangjai.
- Yes, Duen?
Do you think he's sneaking around?
I'm right here.
What's there to be afraid of?
You never know.
You can't trust bandit scum like him.
Whoa, Duen. Lasor wouldn't sneak around
watching you bathe.
I'll say this now.
I'll only let him escort us to the pier.
After that, I'll kick him far away.
What are you waiting for?
This is the perfect chance.
Make her yours.
I have something important to do.
I must destroy
the Lek Lai inside Yiam first.
And I must eliminate everyone who knows
that I caused Khun Yod's family
to be slaughtered.
You can't deal with that yet.
The police are hunting you.
Handle what's in front of you first.
This is a golden opportunity.
You'll get what you want.
But Lady Duen
hates me to the bone.
Then just force her. She'll be tamed.
Nui. Mind your own damn business.
Don't worry. I'll take care of it myself.
Nui, don't.
Come sit here, closer to the fire.
You'll freeze to death.
I won't die that easily.
I'm a bandit's daughter.
But you're the son of a noble lord.
Now you're circling back
to your father again?
Your father, Bandit Wad,
slaughtered my entire family.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Do you know that Yiam,
Khun Yod's son, is still alive.
He escaped that night.
How do you know?
I met him.
Then where is he now?
What's wrong?
You went quiet all of a sudden.
Nothing. It's nothing.
But my father would never kill a friend.
Your father is a bandit. That's why he
did something so despicable to a friend.
It's time.
Time for what?
Time to ascend to heaven.
I'll take care of her little sister.
Stop right there, Nui.
I can't stop.
I've wanted to try it for so long,
wanted to taste it for so long.
What are you going to do?
What are you--
Lasor? How dare you lay a hand on me?
You bastard!
Lady Duen.
Duangjai?
Duangjai! Duangjai!
What did you do to my sister?
What did you do? Where is my sister?
Where is my sister?
Ohm, sacred gaze,
bind her sight, ensnare her eyes.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm cold.
Thought you said
bandits' daughters don't get cold.
Nui! Stop!
No!
Nui!
You don't see me
as your master anymore, do you?
Lasor, I did it for you.
For me? You did it for yourself!
You wanted human flesh
and you used my name!
No. No, Lasor. No…
Duangjai…
Lasor! How could you let my sister die?!
You bastard! Why wasn't it you instead?!
Huh?! Why wasn't it you instead?!
Lady Duen.
I'm sorry.
Sorry?!
Sorry?
Will my sister come back to life then?
You're gone.
How can I live alone?
Why did you leave me?
Don't, my lady.
She was mauled by a tiger.
It's not a sight you should see.
Then how did my sister get mauled
without me knowing?
I was half-asleep.
I remember…
you… I saw you…
It wasn't me. It was a spirit tiger,
a tiger possessed by an evil soul.
Don't worry, my lady.
I will protect you
with my life.
My plan worked. See?
Nui!
Lasor, I just want you to be happy.
Don't ever act without my order again.
Don't kill anyone unnecessarily.
Otherwise,
I'll send you back into the grave.
Lasor, I'm scared now.
But what about you and the lady?
If I used sorcery,
I'd only get your body,
only for a fleeting moment.
I'll make you
love this man, Lasor.
I want all both your body and your heart.
Not your business.
Wiwi buddho iti…
Why am I back here again?
Yiam.
I should thank your sleeping smoke.
It gave me a nice rest.
So, how was walking
in the forest all night? Fun?
This was your doing.
Let me go.
Let go.
Let me go my own way.
I can't stay with someone who wants
to kill my father and my brother.
Once you're safe, I'll leave you.
There's no safe place for me anymore.
But you still have a way out.
They don't know who the masked man is yet.
Why are you running away with me?
You slipped away
because you were worried about me.
I wasn't worried.
I just didn't want to be your burden.
That's what worry is.
Yiwha…
I swore I wouldn't soften my heart.
I won't soften mine either.
Dad.
What?
Whoa. Wad walks like he's flying.
Maybe he's using
a shortening-distance spell.
Yeah. He's regained a lot of his strength.
But he was rushing
because he said he found some clues.
What clues?
Then follow him. So we'll find out.
Who are they?
I don't know. I don't know them.
How did you get here?
So the masked man was you.
Buddho me natho, Dhammo me natho,
Sangho me natho…
Saka pha cha Bucha cha maha bucha Issawa
su Itipiso bhagava.
Lek Lai, awaken and grow.
Yiam, don't. Listen to me first.
Yiam!
Don't!
The power of Lek Lai…
Master, I'm not driven by hatred.
I'm punishing evil.
Mettancha
sabba lokasming mana sambhavaye…
Buddho lalui, dha lalui, ya.
Release your mind.
Wad?
Wad!
- Uncle Niem.
- Wad.
- Hey, how are you?
- Yiam!
- Wad.
Go after Yiam.
Stop, Yiam.
Extinguish the three fires…
Let go. Accept. Be calm.
Yiam, calm your mind.
Now that you've seen my father,
let's talk first.
I won't talk!
Yiam.
Stop right now.
You are a righteous man,
that is why you can wield the Lek Lai.
But never use a sacred power for evil.
Or it will turn against you.
Listen.
We were your father's sworn brothers.
Na!
Yiam, don't!
Lek Lai exists to punish evil,
not to avenge.
Or its power will turn on you.
I'd rather die!
I'll die right here with you!
Your time's up, Pae.
Confess everything.
You want to die that badly?
Don't do anything foolish.
Do you want to die?
You're the one who must die.
Today I'll kill you,
so my dad can finally rest in peace.
Look up.
If you want to kill my master,
step over my dead body first.
If you think this bastard is so righteous,
don't call yourself my son.
He intends to use Lasor
as a pawn to take revenge on me,
but I have something
I need your help with.
Subtitles translation by:
Panuwat Baikeawon