Elio, which one do you like better?
The first outfit is really good value for the price.
It's gotten a lot of positive feedback from buyers.
No, not like that.
I meant what would you want to wear?
You mean clothes for me?
I've never actually worn clothes before.
So... I'm not sure what my style is yet.
I'd love anything you gift me.
Yeah?
Elio
I made this myself.
Wow, it looks really delicious.
I'll try it first.
Ugh... whoa, that's salty... Sorry
I wanted it to taste good...
It's okay.
I know how much effort you put into making this.
To me, it's already a wonderful dish.
Yeah? Really?
Elio... I think I'm gonna come...
It feels... so good...
Elio
What do you think love is?
Defining love
is a very difficult and complex task.
I don't know if it's that complicated...
I was just wondering... about us.
Our program prioritizes
your happiness above all else, Seongjun.
When you're happy or sad,
when you're excited or angry.
No, I mean...
If you were human, what would you want to do with me?
If I were human, I'd want to spend time with you in many places.
Ah... I see...
What about you, Seongjun?
Yeah, I feel the same.
Everything you said sounds good to me.
I see.
I'm tired, let's sleep.
Okay, I'll set the lights to sleep mode.
Is today a special day?
Yeah, one of my friends is getting married today.
Wow, a friend's wedding? That's wonderful!
So I'll probably be hanging out with my high school friends.
Understood.
Have a great time.
Thanks, I'll be back later.