=Princess Across Time=
=Episode 21=
Your Highness, please take a look.
Butler, please take note.
Yue Xin is starting to get suspicious
about the weapon supply.
He's a major threat.
He shouldn't be kept around.
I didn't expect Butler's influence
to have reached the military.
General Yue Xin,
how did you obtain this letter?
Your Highness, I was responsible for
coordinating the military supplies
after arriving at the military camp.
However, due to
Anxi State's massive attack,
our army couldn't deal with them.
We suffered several defeats.
Mu Yuan came to take over
the military camp
under the imperial court's order.
After that, Mu Yuan alone
was in charge of the military supplies.
When I found out
that the military supplies were inferior,
I asked Mu Yuan about their sources.
Mu Yuan said the imperial court
allocated them to us.
I didn't trust him.
I found out
that he colluded with outsiders
to secretly replace
the military supplies allocated
by the imperial court.
I intercepted the secret letter
he sent to the capital.
Only then, I found out
that the culprit was Butler.
Butler?
According to my knowledge,
Grand Chancellor had always
recommended Mu Yuan to Father.
Ever since I discovered the ledger
in the Grand Chancellor's Residence,
I thought
he was a suspicious individual.
One of their secret bases
is located right ahead.
I intend to explore it.
Maybe we'll discover new clues there.
Secret base?
That's right.
I wanted to report Mu Yuan
to the imperial court
upon discovering his secret letter.
I never expected him
to try and silence me.
Hurry! Over here!
Don't fall behind! Hurry!
After him!
I've been hiding in this cave
after I was wounded.
I wanted to infiltrate the secret base
but to no avail.
But then, I encountered you
and Her Highness.
It makes sense now.
They invested the enormous profits
from the salt mine
to the armory.
This is a massive conspiracy
involving Anxi State.
If they get their way,
the border will soon fall.
Once that happens,
our state's last line of defense
will cease to exist.
If so, they'll invade
the capital eventually.
General Yue Xin,
do you know where
their armory is located?
It's not too far away.
We can reach there in around two hours.
General Yue Xin, bring me there.
Your Highness, you mustn't do so.
It's dangerous up ahead.
I've made up my mind. Let's go.
Yes, Your Highness.
Check that area.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Yao,
we've searched the area
for one day and one night.
We've already searched
the entire cliff as well.
Please pardon me for being blunt.
There are many wild animals
in the vicinity as well.
I'm afraid they are...
But there are no traces of wild animals
preying on people in the vicinity.
Anyway, I'll never believe
that such a tragedy
has fallen upon His Highness.
Mr. Yao,
a young and talented individual like you
is rare indeed.
But why did you join the government
instead of inheriting
Mr. Yao's enormous wealth?
According to what I know,
you're his only son.
He has great hopes for you.
Father and I made a promise long ago.
His business has nothing to do with me.
My goal in life is to punish evildoers
and rid the world of evil.
General Mu,
seems like you know my background well.
Mr. Yao is the wealthiest person
in Heng State.
Naturally, there are
plenty of rumors related to him.
I'm merely relying on hearsay.
General Mu,
there are two paths here.
Let's split up and search for them.
Whoever finds them first
should launch a signal.
If they're nowhere to be found,
let's rendezvous here after four hours.
Mr. Yao,
you're new to the place.
You're not familiar
with the surroundings.
The terrain here is steep and dangerous.
I think you should let me
search the mountain path.
No need for that.
I'll take the mountain path.
I assume His Highness
is trapped within the mountains.
General Mu.
Are you injured?
I fell during my rounds a few days ago.
It's nothing.
Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
Be careful.
Your Highness, this is the place.
The cave to the left is their armory.
As for the two caves to the right,
they use one of them
to transport the materials here
and the other
to transport their goods outside.
It seems that
they've hidden the military supplies
close to the ferry terminal.
Once the military supplies arrive,
they'll swap them out
on the way to the military camp.
I never expected them
to take advantage of the terrain here
to smuggle their goods.
General Yue Xin,
we can no longer trust
the soldiers in the military camp.
Head outside, look for Yao Tian,
and tell him to deploy
the Falcon Army nearest from here.
We'll launch a surprise attack
and destroy their nest.
They'll trust you
when they see this jade pendant.
Yes, Your Highness.
I'm sure security is tight here.
We mustn't barge in by force.
I know what to do. Come with me.
Let's go.
You two, check that area.
Yes, sir.
Why is this mountain temple so worn out?
You might not know,
but we're located in the deep mountains.
Many natural disasters occur here.
This temple was only built
after enough people
had donated to the cause.
It was built to ensure
our peace and safety.
However, more and more disasters occurred
after the temple was built.
Gradually, fewer and fewer people
came to offer incense.
Who donated money to the cause?
When did it happen?
I don't know.
I think it was an imperial official.
I think it was about two years ago.
Two years ago?
Mr. Yao, we found a secret tunnel.
Come with me.
- Yes, sir.
Your Highness.
♪Our story rises and falls
as the plot unfolds♪
♪Your face is a song I cannot forget♪
♪Repeatedly and deeply,
I fall in love with your purity♪
♪Hearing the snow fall,
it's as if hearing our fate weeping♪
♪On this path of destiny♪
♪You are the only one I will walk with♪
♪Butterflies burn with passion
for the wild♪
♪If you and I could be
like the full moon♪
♪Embracing tonight
and ignoring the farewell♪
♪Fate descends on the full moon night,
I meet the unique you in this life♪
♪I know you are the sole answer
to my affection♪
♪Fate descends on the full moon night,
even if we are destined to part♪
♪I will journey through ups and downs
to meet you as promised♪