♫  I'm thinking of you again somehow  ♫
♫  The happiness and sorrows keep replaying in my mind  ♫
♫  I thought I could love you until eternity  ♫
♫  I have never stopped missing you  ♫
♫  I can’t stop missing your tenderness  ♫
♫  I’ll always be waiting  ♫
♫  I’ll be there waiting for you  ♫
♫  For no reason at all  ♫
♫  I only want us to be together  ♫
♫  I’ll be there waiting for you  ♫
♫  For the rest of my life  ♫
♫  All I need is you  ♫
♫  I’m always missing you  ♫
What's its name?
Qiu Qiu.
Qiu Qiu?
Zhou Tian?
Come on, Qiu Qiu.
Let's go.
Zhou Tian.
Sunday.
I even didn't think about this.
You are not supposed to leave.
As a gentleman, you can't break the appointment.
And, she's a lady.
Lady? Zhou Tian?
Forget about it.
She regards me as an unlovely,
unhandsome, and even a little cold-blooded animal. She must be crazy.
You must keep the appointment.
What are you doing?
I'm going to delete her,
and end this ridiculous thing right now.
Aren't you expecting the meeting with her?
Imagination is beautiful, but the reality is horrible.
I see.
You're afraid that you will fall in love with her,
if you stay with her for too long.
I will never fall in love with a flippant and disobedient woman
who almost knocked me down and unconditionally
challenged my tolerance.
You are temperamental and domineering.
As an employee, she just tries hard to survive.
She didn't mean to knock you down.
You think she is disobedient because you are always self-centered
and have no sense of team spirit.
She's just trying hard to do her job well.
She's doing her own job.
Sunday is Zhou Tian.
And I am the crocodile in her zoo.
But I even teased myself with her.
That's your problem, not Zhou Tian's.
Do you like her?
Yes. I do like her.
She's warm, generous, kind, and considerate.
She often inspires me suddenly.
She let me think carefully about my relationship with Ji Nian.
I think she is a reliable friend.
So, you like her as a friend. That's good.
But I'm not sure if we will have a new relationship in the future.
The person who has a good relationship with her is you, 1003, not me, Ji Chen.
Aren't you just 1003?
She just gets used to your look when you are working.
She has never seen your look in daily life.
Just have a try. She will accept you.
Don't flatter yourself.
She will never like you, because she hates me.
She may hate me, but it's not up to you.
It's up to her.
Fine. I will make you hopeless.
It's already 12:30.
Did anything happen to him?
♫  Hands up, everybody, hands up, hey!  ♫
♫  Hands up, everybody, hands up  ♫
♫  Come inna di dance and you haffi dance up  ♫
♫  When di hear Reggae music and you put yuh hands up  ♫
♫  And you smoke di ganja and you put yuh hands up  ♫
♫  Everybody...  ♫
P-President Ji. Why are you here?
I have a business appointment.
Business appointment?
Here?
Hello, Sir. What can I do for you?
My friend and I want to help you with the dogs and cats charity.
I'd like to offer 10,000 yuan first.
Thank you, Sir. Thank you, Miss.
We are not...
President Ji. My friend is coming.
And you are sitting in his seat.
He hasn't come yet.
But he will be here soon.
He can take the seat when he comes.
Hey, why are you so shameless?
I have refused you so obviously.
It's not working time now.
Please don't let me see your ugly capitalist face.
Get out of here.
What are you doing?
I...
President Ji, I...
Please drink some water.
Here. Enjoy yourself.
Indeed, my cat behaves exactly like me.
Hope he will leave as soon as possible.
Don't disturb my meeting with 1003.
You won't suffer any losses. Eat some food.
No, thanks, President Ji. I'm waiting for my friend.
What time is your appointment?
Twelve.
He's almost an hour late.
You should ask him if he will still come.
What friend is it?
Boyfriend?
Nope.
Is it a online friend?
President Ji. This should not be a part of your business.
So, I'm right.
I should care about my employee's daily life.
After all, in this big world, there are all kinds of people. And even liars.
I don't want you to be deceived, which may affect your work.
Don't worry, President Ji.
I know my friend very well.
He is not a liar.
If you really have so much time,
you should care more about others.
You have never seen him.
You can't judge him so carelessly.
The more you expect, the more disappointed you will be.
He's my friend. I know him well.
He's not capable like you, who has a good career.
But that guy is sensible,
warm, and loves life.
President Ji. If you don't have any other requests,
please go back to have a rest.
It's the weekend today.
You don't have to supervise my work, do you?
It's so late.
He may not be here today.
We made an appointment. I believe he will come.
But he doesn't come.
I will wait.
What's wrong?
Did he break the appointment?
President Ji. Enjoy yourself.
I have to go.
Why is there such an annoying species in the world?
I submitted the resignation letter.
I can finally get rid of that annoying guy.
If there is no dream, there will be no life.
I love life.
So I have to keep enduring you.
I...
Is the crocodile really so annoying?
What's wrong with 1003?
Why doesn't he reply to my message?
Qiu Qiu. Are you worried about him?
Yes.
You are worried.
I will help you ask him.
Well.
No. Calm down.
Sorry.
There was an emergency to Huskie. And I left my phone at home.
So, I couldn't reply to your message.
So, it was your dog who stalled you.
It doesn't matter.
I thought you had met an accident.
It's good that you are fine.
Did you get angry?
In fact, the crocodile made trouble again.
Fortunately, you didn't come.
Or the meeting would be unpeaceful.
Anyway, I'm glad that you are fine.
Tomorrow, I will go with the peacock for an exhibition.
I have to go. Bye.
Qiu Qiu. He's fine.
Look. She thinks you like that.
You should stop chatting with her.
In her eyes, you are just a cold-blooded crocodile.
Do you know what a crocodile is?
A kind of animal being watched by visitors in the zoo.
You are not better than me.
You called her Huskie.
She calls me like that, because she doesn't know me well.
I will give her time to know me,
because I like her.
I like her?
Qiao Yi. Let's talk about the working plan in the next half year.
You published a new book every year these years.
All of them are popular.
I heard that some of them have been revised as scripts of dramas.
- God bless me.
- Could you tell us something?
Have everything go well today and no accidents.
"Silent Cry" is going to start filming soon.
I will participate in the production.
Why didn't I know this?
Could you tell us some details?
I will be the scriptwriter of the play.
Excuse me. We have more work to do next. Sorry.
- Brother Yi.
I know he's always dissatisfied with the revised script.
But I didn't expect...
Zhou Tian. You were too careless.
Don't you know once he has the revision right, he will be able to decide everything?
If they deny it in public, we will be embarrassed.
- What should we do?
You were on the spot, but you didn't stop him. What do you think we should do?
Make the best of a mistake.
I get it.
President Ji, do you mean we should invest in a net play named "Silent Cry"?
Then we invite Qiao Yi to be the scriptwriter.
But, will Qiao Yi agree to that?
He said this just because
he dislikes the revision.
Zhou Tian, take Qiao Yi to see the director on Monday,
and talk about the script.
Then there will be no problem.
President Ji, you are always wise.
You always have a good idea when we need it.
You solved such a complicated matter in an instant.
It's cool.
They still needed thirty percent of the investment.
I asked my friend to invest in it.
Besides, other investors are also not satisfied with the script.
Now, the writer, Qiao Yi, wants to have a try, so the investors are expecting his work.
The director can't have any objections.
Got it.
I can't understand why every one of you is so nervous.
Is my work really so bad?
It's not bad, is it?
You are not a rookie in this circle.
Do you really think it's easy to change a scriptwriter when everything is read?
Of course, I know it's not easy.
But, I have Ji Chen.
He's my talent manager. He has to solve all my problems.
Otherwise, why should I hire a talent manager?
Well, I'm hungry. Please cook some food for me.
Cook it yourself.
Do you think I can't do anything without you?
I'm going to order takeout.
But you forget that my house is very remote.
I don't even think you can get your takeout before you starve to death.
Then let me starve to death. I'll die in your house.
Then I'll always stay here as a ghost.
It's boring.
I'm going to go cook some food.
There are so many ingredients.
Stay here if you don't want to eat.
You're so mean.
Please cook me some rice noodles.
How is it?
We'll take Qiao Yi to see the director next Monday.
Is that so easy?
The boss is so cool.
But the next Monday is your birthday.
Really?
You reserved seats with Chuan Style Restaurant.
Yes. I reserved it half a month in advance.
Will it take a long time to talk about the script with the director?
- What time is the appointment?
- Two in the afternoon.
If you talk fast, it will be finished before five.
It won't take too long for the first time.
Great.
But... Qiao Yi may make trouble.
Could you finish your words at once?
But he may not really make trouble.
However, Qiao Yi is a man of high demands, just a little,
especially when it comes to scripts.
When his last novel was revised to be the script,
he fired four scriptwriters.
- Four?
- Yes!
So, you have to gently remind him in advance
that he should at least respect the director's ideas.
Brother Hao, I'll head home if there is nothing else.
Fine. Take care.
Gigi. It's a little late.
Go home and rest early.
Brother Zhang Hao. Look. I am a girl.
The shop closes at 10 every night.
I have to go home late every day.
Don't you think it's very dangerous?
I'll drive you back.
No bother.
In fact, the second floor is not occupied.
Can I live upstairs?
Besides, I've been short of money recently.
And I can guard the shop at night.
What do you think?
But the room upstairs is messy and dirty.
It's not suitable for a girl to live.
It's all right.
When you were not here, I've cleaned the room.
I also moved my luggage in.
Now I just need to tidy them up.
You already did it before you asked me.
All right. You can live here but take care.
Thank you, Brother Zhang Hao. You are always so nice.
However, you can't always be so nice to everyone.
Or the people who care about you will think you don't pay enough attention to them.
- Really?
- Of course!
I read this on the Internet. Now I share it with you.
I'm going upstairs to tidy up my things.
All right.
In that case,
I should be nicer to Zhou Tian.
Do it from her birthday.
Hello, Brother Yi.
I will arrive in about ten minutes.
Are you ready?
All right, okay.
Should we go there a little earlier?
Then it will show our dedication to work and respect to the director.
All right.
Get everything done before dinner.
Qiao Yi.
Both the novel and movie are art to tell stories.
Is there any difference between the ways they perform?
I'm just a rookie. I don't know so much.
Could you teach me?
You have chosen the right person.
About ten of my novels have been revised to make TV series and movies.
Indeed, they are both art to tell stories,
but there is a big difference.
Writers, scriptwriters, and directors have different jobs.
He is not as stubborn as I thought.
He knows the common sense.
But you have to know that the reason why my novels are so popular is that
I focus on the moods of characters and the artistic conception.
Therefore, I have to insist on these two points.
Then I won't fail my readers.
The summary meeting for this week and the report on industry information are arranged for tomorrow afternoon.
The headquarters have sent us the running principles.
Five hundred pages in total. We haven't translated it yet.
- That's Roh Cake.
- Yes.
(It's expensive but very delicious.)
Who sent her this?
It's her fellow brother.
Does he want to chase her?
Xia. You are Zhou Tian's close friend.
Tell us about their relationship.
According to my observation,
they keep a special feeling for each other.
But nobody confesses it first.
It seems that Zhang Hao takes the initiative.
That's the ice cream cake
Zhou Tian likes very much.
Every time when she is unhappy, she will buy it.
She said it could cheer her up.
Look at the huge bunch of flowers. Is he going to propose?
No way. He would come in person if he proposed.
Well. He spent so much money buying such a huge bunch of flowers.
What else does he want to do?
President Ji.
- President Ji.
Where is this cake from?
It's Zhou Tian's birthday today.
Who sent such unhealthy food on her birthday?
Where is she?
She went with Yi to set the makeup.
Since she's not here, you can share the cake.
We don't have her permission.
If we eat her cake, it will be impolite.
Should we put it in the refrigerator?
The ice cream cake is so huge.
It will take a large space in the refrigerator. But what a waste if we put it here.
Zhou Tian is generous. She won't mind it.
Just share it.
Don't worry, President Ji. I often buy cakes in that shop.
They always put a lot of ice on with cakes.
There won't be any problem if we put it for four or five hours.
Yeah.
You like cakes in that shop very much.
From tomorrow on, I will buy you three cakes every day.
Thank you, President Ji. But you don't have to buy so many.
You must finish them all.
Let me take a photo and send it to Zhou Tian.
Give me the flowers.
Here.
Her fellow brother, Zhang Hao, is so considerate.
President Ji.
Are you bored?
The running principles. Let her translate it.
Yes.
Five hundred pages in a foreign language. Finish them before getting off work.
Five hundred pages. Today?
You shouldn't have provoked him.
Go for it.
How did I provoke him?
It's actually Zhou Tian's birthday.
Does her birthday have anything to do with me?
A fortune-teller told my mom that
my future wife was born on this day.
But I don't know what time Zhou Tian was born.
Are you also bored?
Help her do the translation work.
He said I didn't understand the movie.
But he doesn't even understand "Silent Cry".
How annoying!
He doesn't even understand what the novel says.
How can he be the director? It's ridiculous.
As the saying goes, there are a thousand Hamlets in a thousand people's eyes.
It means that your novel is great.
Calm down. Look.
Have a rest first. I'll talk to the director.
The ice-cream cake Senior Zhang Hao sent you in the morning.
Forgive me. I just have time to reply to your message.
He's so nice.
He never forgets it every year.
How is your situation?
Can you come back before dinner?
I'm not sure.
But the cake can't hold so long.
Hello, Miss.
This is the director's new idea. Please let Qiao Yi read it.
All right.
And it's about dinner time.
Should we send food to Qiao Yi?
Do we have to continue this after dinner?
We're just afraid that he may be hungry.
We'd better be quick and finish this before dinner.
If he feels hungry, I will ask the driver to buy him food.  Thank you so much.
All right. Please excuse me.
- Well, thanks.
- It's nothing.
I want to go back to eat the cake.
Hope there won't be any accident when they are discussing work.
Most importantly. I must eat the food in Chuan Style Restaurant.
I've been expecting this for three months.
Please God, it's my birthday.
Please let me enjoy the food there.
Is it your birthday today?
Yes.
- Happy birthday.
- Thanks.
Oh. When is your birthday?
The first of January.
You share the same birthday with the crocodile.
What a coincidence.
Oh. Do you like ice cream cake?
Not really.
When I was a child,
I couldn't often eat desserts in the sports team.
I could only eat them on my birthday.
So, I always expected my birthday.
I thought that I could go home
and spent my birthday with my parents this year.
I could eat the noodles my dad cooked.
But I can't eat anything,
and have to work overtime.
Why don't you take them here?
I go to work early and come back late.
If they come here and see me working until midnight every day,
they will be sad and lecture me.
I'd rather not.
Oh, you said the noodles your dad cooked are very special.
That's right. The noodles my dad cooked are all made by himself.
There will be pork fat, scallions, fried garlic,
one soft-boiled egg, and four slices of luncheon meat.
Every year, he would bring it to me
I would see the noodles.
But I haven't eaten it for many years.
I can only see them on my phone.
What? He wants me to write according to his outline.
Are you kidding me?
Did you eat the noodles this year?
Qiao Yi, this is the director's habit.
He needs to control the script of every movie.
Or he can't make the best movie.
If he doesn't like my work,
he can give up on it.
Qiao Yi!
Answer the phone, Kevin.
You can leave if you don't want to.
But this is my novel.
I must be responsible for my novels and their derivative products.
You must be responsible for your novels. And I must be responsible for my movies.
If you don't respect the difference between novels and movies,
though you are the original author of the novel,
I will refuse to work with you.
Great. I also refuse to work with the director who doesn't respect the original work.
Qiao Yi.
Director, we are just here to talk casually.
It was going well when we arrived.
Why...
It comes to my movie. Neither the famous scriptwriter nor the original author can butt in it.
I have my own creative ideas.
That's respect to the movie art.
If he refuses to respect it,
I also refuse to make the movie.
She's gone. What are you waiting for?
I'm waiting for you.
Hey, today is her birthday.
But you asked her to do so much work.
I didn't know it.
You know it now.
Won't you do anything?
Go to find her. Bring her some food.
Ridiculous.
That's just an employee's birthday.
Why should I do something?
All right.
If you refuse, don't regret it.
It's just a birthday.
I also spent my last birthday working overtime.
Why is it different when it's her birthday?
President Ji, bad news. Something happened to Qiao Yi.
He is arguing with the director.
Really?
Great.
Well, President Ji. I was too anxious just now. Did I...
I heard it very clearly. Let's go there.
Qiao Yi is arguing with the director.
Bring some gifts for them. Get ready.
Oh, I see.
President Ji, you are so wise.
Should we take the chairman's wine or the herb President Jiang Hanyi sent you?
Director Li Han likes Sichuan cuisine.
Listen. Go to the restaurant named Chuan Style,
and pack up all the popular dishes.
But, President Ji. The restaurant is too far.
If we pack up the food there...
Make sense.
Listen. Go to Chuan Style Restaurant directly, and take the chef over.
Is there any problem?
No problem.
Let's go.
I'll call Zhou Tian first, and tell her we are going there.
She needs to keep Qiao Yi there.
Director Kevin.
Are you and President Ji going to find Qiao Yi later?
- What's the matter?
- Could you please take this cake to Zhou Tian?
The ice can't keep it for too long. It is going to melt.
We are busy now. Forget the cake.
But it will be wasteful if it melts.
Or I'll call a deliveryman.
Give it to me.
I said to give the cake to me.
Xiao Xia is right. We can't waste it.
Give it to me.
Turn on the air conditioner. Warm air.
President Ji, heating mode in this weather?
I feel cold.
All right.
President Ji. Are you sick?
Are you drained because of overworking?
It's all my fault.
Turn the heat up to full blast.
♫  It was raining that day when you held me  ♫
♫  A shooting star fell in my heart secretly  ♫
♫  It found a place in your eyes and witnessed my promise to you  ♫
♫  Eventually, it brightened my whole universe  ♫
♫  Finally, you’ve walked into my life  ♫
♫  After all is said and done, we’ve missed out so much  ♫
♫  We tried so hard to engrave each other’s face  ♫
♫  I’ve made up my mind to drift with you all my life  ♫
♫  But you remained calm and silent  ♫
♫  You’re afraid our life would be dull and uncertain  ♫
♫  Don’t worry, I decided to be your support  ♫
♫  I’ll make the future ahead more promising  ♫
♫  It was raining that day when you held me  ♫
♫  A shooting star fell in my heart secretly  ♫
♫  It found a place in your eyes and witnessed my promise to you  ♫
♫  Eventually, it brightened my whole universe  ♫
♫  I’ve spent my entire life finding you  ♫
♫  I’ve never been in love this deep before  ♫
♫  Loving you made me become a better me  ♫
♫  I’ll be a shooting star and shine for you forever  ♫
♫  Shine for you  ♫
♫  It was raining that day when you held me  ♫
♫  A shooting star fell in my heart secretly  ♫
♫  It found a place in your eyes and witnessed my promise to you  ♫
♫  Eventually, it brightened my whole universe  ♫
♫  I’ve spent my entire life finding you  ♫
♫  I’ve never been in love this deep before  ♫
♫  Loving you made me become a better me  ♫
♫  I’ll be a shooting star and shine for you forever  ♫
♫  Shine for you  ♫