♪Pink hands so fine♪
♪Gold-branded wine♪
♪Spring paints green willows
palace walls cannot confine♪
♪East wind unfair♪
♪Happy times rare♪
♪In my heart sad thoughts throng♪
♪We've severed for years long♪
♪Wrong, wrong, wrong♪
[Si Jin]
[Adapted from Si Jin,
by Dong Tian De Liu Ye]
[Episode 13]
I'll take it back
and tend to it with care.
Whenever you wish to receive it,
I'll bring it over.
I shall take my leave.
Mr. Yu!
Eavesdropping and spying
are not the actions of a gentleman.
This is already the second time
you've done this.
I never claimed
to be a gentleman in the first place.
My apologies.
I thought
you were fond of Mr. Zhen.
I...
Who I favor is none
of your business.
Of course, it is!
Must you
be so distant with me?
Aren't we…?
Aren't we what?
Neighbors?
You must be joking.
The begonia I sent
as a housewarming gift
was returned.
Clearly, I was overestimating myself
in thinking I could be close
to such a distinguished neighbor.
It was returned?
I never sent it back!
It must have been Long Dan.
That fool
who only ever ruins things.
The soil has some issues.
I wanted to trouble you
to take a look at it.
What's wrong with the soil?
The soil…
Yu!
I can't hit the target!
Is my bow broken?
Come take a look at it!
Long Dan!
Take a look at it!
Yes, sir.
The soil is a bit loose.
Really?
Yes.
You'll know when you see it.
Why didn't you say something earlier?
I wasn't given a chance to.
Today wasn't my day off.
I took time off
to teach Jiang Zhan archery and riding,
and to ask
if you were troubled by something.
You dreamed that Jiang Zhan would die?
But dreams aren't real.
What if it becomes real?
That dream felt so vivid.
I saw him fall into the water.
I saw the restaurant engulfed in flames.
And I saw a memorial tablet
with my brother's name on it
added to our ancestral hall.
If Zhan really might die,
I have to prevent it.
I hit the target!
Yu! Si!
Look! I hit it!
Come over and see!
Just look at Jiang Zhan.
If you keep him locked up
at home every day,
it will only backfire.
He'll find every excuse to sneak out.
Instead of that,
why don't we take turns accompanying him
whenever he goes out?
What do you think?
You don't think what I'm saying
is ludicrous?
I know you care about him.
Miss Si really said that?
Yes.
I've already told her.
We'll put aside
talks of marriage for now.
Oh, you!
A bride already within reach,
and you let her slip away!
Mother, we should
respect
Miss Si's wishes.
So be it. I was too impatient.
She was set up
at Madam Jiang's birthday banquet.
I knew the Count of Dongping's Mansion
was a place filled
with schemes and plots.
I was hasty and made a rash decision,
thinking that if I could get her
into our family sooner,
she would suffer less.
Looking back,
I shouldn't force her.
Everything you did is for me.
What's your plan now?
Just give up on this marriage?
Recognize one's shortcomings,
then improve.
Aim for the peak,
then strive to reach it.
I shall not give up
so long as Miss Si does not
give her hand to another.
Good.
[Yesterday is gone like autumn leaves.
Tomorrow is long and full of hope.]
♪A sudden glance,
just like our first meeting♪
♪Feelings remain,
but things are ever unclear♪
♪Memories replay♪
♪My heart hesitates♪
♪Can I make it through
another long night?♪
Chief.
How much are you writing?
♪Afraid of losing you again♪
Is this big enough for you?
Keep… Keep going.
♪The pain lingers deep inside♪
♪Leaving dreams incomplete♪
Yesterday is gone like autumn leaves.
Tomorrow is long and full of hope.
♪Past lives fade like smoke,
can the dreams be undone?♪
♪I still can't let you go♪
♪No matter how far the journey takes me♪
♪If love is strong,
what is there to fear?♪
♪In this lifetime♪
Can all our troubles really be solved?
♪Can I make it through
another long night?♪
♪Afraid of losing you again♪
♪The pain lingers deep inside♪
♪Leaving dreams incomplete♪
♪I count the petals as they fall♪
♪Each one a time I've thought of you♪
♪Past lives fade like smoke,
can the dreams be undone?♪
♪I still can't let you go♪
♪No matter how far the journey takes me♪
♪I'll do anything to save♪
♪Our shared past♪
Please take another look!
[Lushengxiang Store]
Half-price for a limited time!
Madam, please have a look.
We're offering a limited-time discount.
Madam.
Half-price at Lushengxiang Store.
Would you like to go inside?
Half-price for a limited time.
Would you like to take a look?
Buy something for your wife!
No.
Half-price at Lushengxiang Store.
Greetings. Come inside and take a look.
Our products smell exquisite.
Only half price for a limited time.
Check it out!
No.
Miss. Come on.
[Lushengxiang Store]
The shop was finally renovated,
but business has plummeted.
We've gotten no customers
for days in a row.
Even our regular patrons
have been returning their purchases.
When I asked them privately,
they said that a certain noble person
had spread the word.
Anyone who dares to buy
from the Lushengxiang Store
would be making an enemy of her.
They wouldn't say
who the noble is.
If it's someone of that importance,
then it's definitely not
the work of our business rivals.
Perhaps we've offended someone.
Several of our regulars
are family members
of high-ranking officials.
For someone to intimidate them
into staying away,
who could it be?
I'll ask Miss Si.
Wait here.
Miss, come inside
and look at our fragrance dew.
Miss Si and Mr. Zhan.
What do we do?
No one is willing
to step foot inside our store.
Everyone, stay calm.
Commandant Yu is already
investigating the matter.
As they say,
good things are worth waiting for.
I refuse to believe
that anyone has the power
to stop every single patron
from coming to us.
Si is right.
I know some friends.
I'll treat them to a few drinks
and ask them
to introduce some customers to us.
No.
Why not?
What use do you think
your drinking buddies are?
Are you just looking for an excuse
to go out and make merry again?
Do you seriously think
I'd be in the mood
to fool around right now?
How could you think that of me?
All right.
The bottom line is
that you are not going to them.
Fine.
[Lushengxiang Store]
Oh, you give me such a good laugh.
All right. That's enough.
Don't let the fun get you down.
This is the first time I've ever heard
of a younger sister
keeping her older brother at home,
not allowing him to step out at all.
What do you know?
My sister is doing it for my own good.
[Zhang Sheng]
She wants me to fool around less
and work harder to improve myself.
All right.
I'll be on my way now.
Wouldn't want to interrupt
your self-improvement.
Wait, no! Don't go!
Come back!
You have no idea
how boring it is to drink alone.
A grown man
so obedient to his sister.
Wouldn't it be embarrassing
if word gets out?
So what?
My sister is
way smarter than me.
Can't go wrong with her judgment.
The more obedient you are,
the less she'll respect you.
My sister would never look down on me.
I suppose?
She's your sister.
Would she tell you that to your face?
What use do you think
your drinking buddies are?
Are you just looking for an excuse
to go out and make merry again?
If I pass
the Imperial Insignia Guard selection,
she will change her opinion of me.
She'll never think I'm useless again.
And if you fail?
What?
Are you certain you'll pass?
Not at all.
Zhang, you know me.
With my flashy but useless skills,
no matter how hard I practice,
I still feel uncertain.
These women.
I don't get what they're thinking.
Why do they always expect
a man to have an official title
to be considered successful?
What's so great about being
an Imperial Insignia Guard anyway?
Harsh conditions
and hard work every day.
True.
Have you no other way
to impress your sister?
Zhang.
Do you know
any wealthy ladies
who might want to buy fragrance dew?
I do.
Really? That's great!
Here.
Ji.
Jiang Zhan took the bait?
Of course.
Get the job done,
and Her Highness promises
that there will be a position
in the Office of Ceremonies for you.
I will not disappoint Her Highness.
I bid you farewell.
Zhang.
This buyer of yours,
she's not some courtesan, is she?
What does it matter who she is?
What matters is that she's rich.
Anyway, tonight's lady
is extremely generous.
If you can close this deal,
Lushengxiang Store won't have to worry
about business for an entire year.
Promise me
you won't get on a boat
or go near the river!
It's just a boat ride!
Maybe I should just forget it.
If my sister finds out
I came to a place like this,
she'll never let me live it down.
You're always talking about your sister.
Can you even live without her?
What do you mean by that?
Of course, I can live
without her!
Is that so? Prove it.
Come on. Let's go.
Slow… Slow down.
Come on.
Here.
Fill his cup.
I'm not drinking.
Drink.
Let me help you.
- Come on.
- Zhang.
I must have the wrong place.
Leave us.
I had no idea
that Your Highness was here
with the company.
My friend
took a wrong turn.
We've disturbed your gathering.
Apologies.
Wait.
It was us who told your friend
to bring you here.
Your Highness, what do you mean?
Weren't you curious
about who's been disrupting
Lushengxiang Store's business?
I shall answer you.
It was me.
Impossible!
Everyone knows
that Your Highness is kind and virtuous!
You would never do such a thing!
This… This must be my fault.
I've always had a bad habit
of running my mouth.
Everyone here knows that.
I must have offended
Your Highness somewhere.
I humbly ask you to enlighten me.
You're quite the clever one.
Very well.
I'm in a good mood today.
I'll be gracious
and let this slide.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I didn't say you could leave.
There are no seats left.
Princess Mingyue's private banquets
aren't something
just anyone can attend.
Jiang, since you're here,
you must have a few drinks.
Someone, bring Jiang some liquor.
I…
Your Highness…
Finish these three jars,
and I will leave
Lushengxiang Store alone.
What do you say?
It...
Your Highness.
Do you mean it?
Of course.
I thank Your Highness
for your generosity.
I forgot to mention.
This is Scorching Spirit,
brought all the way
from the Western Regions.
A few drops will have you intoxicated.
My hands slipped.
What's your problem?
Her Highness has granted you
such precious liquor,
yet you still hesitate to drink it?
I will drink it.
I will.
I didn't think much of it
when Zhang Sheng came over
a few days ago.
Who knew that after dinner today,
Zhan would be nowhere to be found?
Don't panic just yet.
Maybe he just sneaked out drinking
like last time.
You're spilling.
Give him a hand.
What are you doing to me?
You two search along this road.
We'll check the other side of the river.
Jiang Zhan, looks like today's your day.
Come on, run!
Cui Yi, this is the imperial capital!
You can't do this to me!
I'll fight you!
With what?
[Yang Shengcai]
I'll admit, in just a few months,
you have improved somewhat.
You want to practice?
We'll give you some.
Get him!
Enough.
Hold him down.
You spilled earlier.
Take it easy this time.
There's no hurry.
Jiang Zhan!
Mr. Jiang!
How was that?
Speak!
What?
Kill me.
Kill you?
He wants us to put him
out of his misery.
That's a first
for me!
Drink up. Take your time.
Breathe!
Don't play dead.
Ji.
Is he…?
Jiang Zhan.
Jiang Zhan?
Zhan!
What are you doing?
I'm not your brother.
Excuse me.
Zhan!
Oh, no.
He… He has stopped breathing!
He's too weak.
He's dead! What…?
What do we do, Your Highness?
Strip him.
Sorry.
Zhan.
Are you all right?
Your Highness.
He's really dead.
Boring.
What do we do?
What's the big deal?
It's just a worthless life.
Even if he's useless,
he's still an heir to the count.
Then let's just throw him into the river
and be done with it.
Someone.
Throw him in the river.
Jiang Zhan!
Not bad.
Look! Someone fell into the water!
What happened?
Probably drank too much.
Wake up, Zhan!
He fell into the water!
Someone fell into the water!
Mingyue!
What are we going to do
if Uncle learns about this?
Then have them get rid
of these servants.
By tomorrow,
I don't want to see them in Ling'an City
ever again.
- No!
Your Highness! Mercy!
Move it.
Move!
Hurry up!
For what happened
with Jiang Zhan tonight,
everyone present shall be
richly rewarded!
- Thank you, Your Highness!
- I appreciate it, Your Highness!
Zhang Sheng.
You are today's biggest contributor.
You brought Jiang Zhan here.
A big buyer
of fragrance dew, huh?
The fact
that he actually believed it
is hilarious!
I'm flattered.
It was Ji's idea.
Ji gets the credit.
- Ji.
- Yes.
Ji.
Oh, stop it!
You can handle it.
We're just here for a bit of fun,
right?
Jiang Zhan
didn't even flinch.
I just draped a cloth over him
and poured some liquor on him.
Before I even got to enjoy myself,
he stopped breathing.
Good thing Her Highness
had him stripped.
Yes.
Your Highness,
did you enjoy yourself tonight?
No.
Tell me. What's the difference
between a person
and an ant?
None.
They both belong to Your Highness.
I want
Jiang Si dead.
Cui Mingyue,
I'll make you
pay for your blood debt now.
Jiang Zhan!
Fire!
Run!
Miss Jiang.
Those animals.
Yang Shengcai. Zhang Sheng.
They tortured my brother
to death
and then threw him
into this river!
[Xiayue Pavilion]
Remember.
You were with me the entire night.
You were nowhere else.
Chief!
There's an extremely steep cliff
downstream.
If Jiang Zhan really got swept away
by the current,
I'm afraid his chances
of survival are slim.
Keep searching!
- Yes.
[Princess Royal's Mansion]
Princess Royal.
Princess Mingyue
must apply medicine daily
to prevent scarring.
Be gentle, Mother.
Now you know pain?
Cui Mingyue!
Look at what you've done!
Come out!
Don't move.
Lie face down.
So you remember
that she's your daughter.
Can't you see
how badly she's hurt?
So what if she got injured?
At least she's still alive!
But Cui Yi? He's dead!
He was barely in his twenties!
He was my brother's only son!
How am I supposed
to explain this to him?
Are you blaming his death
on Mingyue?
Did she start the fire?
Did she kill him?
You…
Everyone in this mansion knows
she's always ordered him around
like a servant!
She's never shown an ounce of respect
for her own cousin.
And
she's an unmarried lady,
sneaking out at night
with a group of men!
And now look. A burned-down tavern,
two dead, one crippled,
and another missing!
She's committed
a terrible catastrophe,
yet you, as her mother,
still defend her?
I'll tell you this.
If you keep spoiling her,
one day,
she will lose her life because of it!
Never curse
my daughter!
Mother.
What exactly happened last night?
Tell me everything,
down to the last word!
[Duke of Anguo's Mansion]
Easy.
Bear with it, Chongyi.
Physician,
how is
my son's leg?
Madam.
His injury is far too severe.
I'm afraid
he may never walk normally again.
My son is still young!
He can't be crippled!
We'll pay whatever it takes
to cure him!
Madam,
you should seek another physician.
Physician, please!
You…
Save my leg, Physician!
Mother!
Physician, please, think of something!
Physician!
Mother, save my leg!
Ji Chongyi.
If you hurt the baby in my womb,
I will never forgive you.
I'm severely injured,
and you won't even spare me a glance!
How can you be so heartless?
You speak to me of love?
Ji Chongyi,
you are nothing more than a tool for me
to marry into this mansion.
I couldn't care less
whether you live or die.
You… You vile woman!
I told you
Princess Mingyue was arrogant
and a tyrant.
People in Ling'an City fear her
at the mere mention of her name.
Yet you insisted
on getting close to her.
Look at the fate
you brought upon yourself now.
You're a merchant. What do you know?
Everything I've done is
for the future of this family!
The Princess Royal holds immense power
over the imperial court.
Do you think I can afford to offend her?
The court is treacherous
and unpredictable.
Even your father couldn't
outmaneuver her.
What makes you think
you can?
You're just digging your own grave.
If it wasn't
for the child I'm expecting,
I wouldn't even bother
explaining all this to you.
Chongyi!
You're saved!
The Princess Royal has sent a carriage
to fetch you.
The imperial physicians at her mansion
who can surely heal your leg.
That's wonderful, Mother!
Let's go!
What are you doing over there?
Hurry up and help!
He cannot go.
What did you just say?
Are you hoping my son never recovers?
Mother.
I have married into this mansion.
I am already in the same boat
as all of you.
Please think carefully.
Last night's fire killed two people.
One was the son of the Chief Censor.
The other was the nephew of General Cui.
The missing one is the grandson
of Director Sun.
Every one of them is someone
we cannot afford to offend.
Yet why is it that only he
and Princess Mingyue survived?
What are you implying?
My son is also an heir apparent.
His status is no less than any of them.
Stop deceiving yourself.
The Duke of Anguo's Mansion
is in decline.
If we get involved in this mess,
he could lose his noble title
altogether.
The Censorate. The Office of Ceremonies.
Neither are to be trifled with.
They would not let their own kin
be sacrificed in vain.
Lives have been lost.
If there has to be a scapegoat,
tell me,
who do you think
the Princess will choose?
That's right. She must not harbor
kind intentions.
Then,
what do you suggest we do now?
He must not go
to the Princess Royal's Mansion
at all costs.
Here's what we do.
Inform the Princess Royal
that Chongyi's leg is too injured
to be moved.
All right.
I'll go right away.
I didn't expect you to have
even a sliver of conscience.
I'm not doing this for you.
I'm doing this for my unborn child.
What was the true cause
of last night's fire?
Even if it's for the sake
of this mansion,
you should tell me the truth.
There weren't
just five of us last night.
There was someone else.
Are they searching for bodies?
I heard many people died.
It's too dangerous!
Well? Did you find anything?
No.
Long Dan.
Take some men and search over there.
Yes. Follow me.
Yes.
A reward of 1000 liang
to whoever finds my grandson!
A thousand liang!
Come on! Let's help find him!
Hurry！
Over there!
A thousand liang!
This is the Jinshui River.
It's not some small creek.
Even the most skilled swimmers
can lose their lives here.
Please withdraw your reward.
The Capital Administration Office
has failed to find my grandson.
Why shouldn't I conduct my own search?
The more people searching,
the higher the chances
of finding my grandson!
Over there!
Search over there!
Quickly!
Your Grace! Miss Si!
Anything?
No sign of him there either.
No news is good news.
He will be fine.
We will find your brother.
He's always been a troublemaker.
Troublemakers live long.
Someone's in the water!
Sir! Over here!
They found him!
They found him! Hurry!
Let's go!
- Come on!
- Master!
Move! Out of the way!
- Over there!
Hurry! Over here!
Save him! Pull them up!
Over there!
Master!
Hurry! Pull him up!
A purple robe.
Sheng loved wearing purple robes.
Sheng.
How cruel you are
to let a grandfather bury his grandson!
Chief!
Miss Si!
Si!
Quickly! Bring her home.
Yes.
Miss Si.
You haven't eaten anything all day.
At least have some soup.
Aman.
Any news of Zhan?
It's all my fault.
I'm to blame.
Mr. Jiang.
You need to take some rest.
I'll stay here and keep watch.
Why is the Jinshui River so deep
and so long?
You mustn't overexert yourself.
If you wear yourself out,
how can you search for him?
If he's found,
will he still be alive?
Yes.
Surely, he will be.
I am unfit
to be a father.
I never really
cared for him as a child.
Once he grew up,
all I did
was criticize him.
I never truly cared about him.
He was mischievous,
but good at heart.
I've wronged him.
Rest assured, Mr. Jiang.
I will find him.
We will.
Yes.
Your Highness.
You must seek justice for me!
My son's face was burnt so horribly
that he's barely recognizable!
It's an absolute tragedy, Your Highness!
Please accept my condolences, Mr. Zhang.
But I don't understand.
Why did your son
end up
with Princess Mingyue?
Your Highness, please be discerning.
You have shown me a great favor,
and I have
remained ever loyal to you.
Zhang Sheng
is the son of my concubine.
He has always been unmotivated
and unambitious.
He has failed the examinations
time and again.
I neglected to discipline him.
I cannot fathom how this wretch
became entangled
with Princess Mingyue.
Even though he was of a lower status,
he was still your own flesh and blood.
To have him burned to death
in such a senseless manner
is heart-wrenching.
Your Highness.
It's all the fault
of the Princess Royal's lax discipline.
Princess Mingyue
never showed any propriety.
Her debauchery and licentious behavior
have brought disaster upon herself
and taken away the lives of so many!
Your Highness.
I will report this matter
to His Majesty.
Princess Mingyue
must be punished for her deeds!
[The End of Episode 13]
♪Through endless twists♪
♪In the mundane world♪
♪The breezy wind blows♪
♪The heart grows tender and bitter♪
♪I ask the Sun♪
♪If the light has taken root♪
♪As it prospers♪
♪Our love story writes itself♪
♪We lock eyes
and promise to stay together forever♪
♪After countless challenges,
we are still us♪
♪Our inseparable souls♪
♪Can weather all storms♪
♪We cross paths
and promise to stay together forever♪
♪The tapestry of destiny
is filled with our youth♪
♪Our blissful time together♪
♪Will lead us♪
♪To the sea of stars♪
♪Our destined paths♪
♪The years will hold♪
♪A light shines at the tunnel's end♪
♪Where happy endings will transcend♪
♪We cross paths
and promise to stay together forever♪
♪The tapestry of destiny
is filled with our youth♪
♪Our blissful time together♪
♪Will lead us to what we desire♪
♪We lock eyes
and promise to stay together forever♪
♪Through frost-kissed trails,
and starry space♪
♪Moon-silvered dreams♪
♪On love's embrace♪
♪Hearts bound as one,
through time's soft grace♪
♪Love's tide guides,
beyond our mortal space♪
♪A moment kept with your embrace♪
♪Where blooms have found their place♪