♪Pink hands so fine♪
♪Gold-branded wine♪
♪Spring paints green willows
palace walls cannot confine♪
♪East wind unfair♪
♪Happy times rare♪
♪In my heart sad thoughts throng♪
♪We've severed for years long♪
♪Wrong, wrong, wrong♪
[Si Jin]
[Adapted from Si Jin,
by Dong Tian De Liu Ye]
[Episode 6]
[Count of Dongping's Mansion]
I'll be gentle.
Bear with me, Qian.
Mother,
Father went to Madam Ruan's chamber.
Let him be.
That heartless man might as well
die in that wench's place.
He only cares about his career,
and not his family.
Mother,
did you know?
I envy the main branch now.
Jiang Si was shoved accidentally
into the river by Ji Chongyi.
She wasn't even hurt,
yet Uncle Ancheng defended her fiercely.
He annulled the wedding
and brought the case
to the Capital Administration Office.
If Jiang Si was the one injured now,
he would have confronted the Cao family
for an explanation.
If only Father loved me
half as much as Uncle Ancheng
does his daughter,
perhaps Cao Xingyu
wouldn't dare to hit me at all.
Qian.
It's all my fault.
I made this marital arrangement.
It's my fault.
Mother!
Why are you doing this?
It seems like marrying into the nobility
doesn't bring a happy ending either.
You finally get it, Pei.
Since I was young, I have always envied
Qian.
Who would have thought
that she's had
such a miserable life?
You know what?
I should stop
dreaming of marrying into nobility
and find a scholar,
a frail one
who can do nothing
but write.
That way,
he won't hit me.
Exactly!
Mother.
You were just trying to secure
a bright future for me.
You're the only one here
who cares for me.
Grandmother and Father
will never protect me
as fervently as you do now.
My poor child.
I carried you
for ten months.
It hurts more
to see him hit you
than to be hit myself.
Mother!
It's not your fault.
It's mine.
I'm to blame.
Madam.
I beg of you.
Please don't send Miss Qian back
or she might truly be killed.
Qian.
Worry not.
I will protect you
at all costs.
I won't let you
suffer the same anymore.
Mother!
Who's there?
I have a solution.
Ridiculous!
And I thought
you had a great idea.
You're trying to do Qian in.
Didn't Qian say
that she
would do anything to free herself
from that scum's torture?
If we take it
to the Capital Administration Office,
she
might be able to leave him.
Let's say you're right.
Qian went
to the Capital Administration Office
and brought a case against Cao Xingyu.
What about the Marquis of Changxing?
Will he spare her?
But there's no
other option now.
If she goes back, she'll live in fear
and pain.
And one day, she might lose her life.
When that happens,
Cao Xingyu can just claim
that she died from an illness
and remove all evidence.
We won't be able
to do anything.
You saw Uncle Anmou's attitude
just now.
He's not going to defend anyone.
Two women like you here
don't have
a final say regarding repudiation.
No.
If we involve
the Capital Administration Office,
Cao Xingyu has countless other ways
to make my life miserable.
Jiang Si.
I had no choice
but to send you to them.
Do you hate me so much?
You're trying to profit
from my misfortune.
You're pushing me
so you can use me
as your weapon.
If I keep quiet, I might live.
Seriously?
You're simply resigned to your fate.
Based on the ligature mark
on the corpses,
we can deduce
that these ladies
were strangled to death
by the same man using a rope.
Anything else?
Not at the moment.
Why is
her ligature mark different
from the others?
Perhaps her constitution was different.
Or perhaps she put up a fierce struggle
before she died.
It's hard to tell
by looking at her body.
Check if there's anything
inside her throat.
Sure.
Please take a look.
This is...
a button.
Yu Qi
said that?
Yes.
He said
it didn't implicate Anzi.
And he wanted to interrogate you.
Oh?
It didn't implicate Anzi?
Then someone has to take his spot.
My dear sirs,
I came
with an important piece of information.
While Anzi has confessed to his crime,
I thought it was rather bizarre.
He was
an honest man.
He wouldn't have the audacity
to murder someone.
You were so sure
that he was the culprit.
And your father killed him.
Why?
This happened not long ago
and now, you're changing
your allegations?
Does life mean nothing to you?
But his death
isn't unjustified.
Father was fair
in his handling of matters.
I combed through my mansion
and found out
that Anzi wasn't the culprit,
but the accomplice.
[Justice Prevails]
Then who
is the culprit?
It's none
other than my spouse,
Jiang Qian.
Stop barking.
[Arrest Warrant
Issued by the Capital City Garrison]
Cao Xingyu accused Qian
of wrongdoing?
Yes.
He claimed that Jiang Qian
was the culprit of the murder.
Miss Qian!
Qian.
They are the culprits.
This is unfair!
Madam Qian,
please follow me.
Si is right.
I should have listened to her
and brought Cao Xingyu to justice.
What do I do, Mother?
Fear not, Qian.
You're not leaving.
Seize her.
What are you doing?
- Miss Qian!
- Stop!
- Qian!
Find Jiang Si!
Only she can help me.
Mother!
Let go of me!
[Capital Administration Office]
You might as well confess
to your crime now.
You had an affair with Anzi.
He was close
to those women,
and you became jealous.
Thus, you asked Anzi
to murder them.
I have married an accursed soul.
Nonsense.
I did no such thing!
I haven't never met
those women before.
Why would I kill them?
Believe me, sir.
Like those women, I am a victim
of Cao Xingyu's physical abuse.
Yet we are too afraid to take action.
To my dismay,
he framed me for murder.
Sir,
please check the wounds on her body.
They are the same wounds
as the ones
on the victims.
But I have evidence
proving that this wretched woman
had an affair with Anzi.
She then asked Anzi to commit the crime.
This is a button
Jiang Qian left in Anzi's abode.
Anzi's wife also
testified in writing
that she saw them committing adultery
and plotting the murder.
Bring it to me.
He's framing me!
He has but found a random button
and threatened Anzi's family
into lying
to frame me, sir!
I saw with my own eyes
that Anzi buried the bodies.
And that night,
Jiang Qian
was sleeping in her chamber.
She couldn't possibly be the culprit.
So you were the one
who reported the incident.
Sir,
they are sisters.
They must have put the blame on me
because their deception
is about to be discovered.
You must help me, sir.
[Jiang Qian and Anzi had an affair.
She killed out of jealousy.]
Summon the witness.
Summon the witness!
Sir, the witness is here.
What is your name?
My name is Chi Shuying, sir.
Tell me.
Do you know the Jiang sisters?
No, they have nothing
to do with me.
Do you know
Cao Xingyu then?
Yes,
sir.
This wicked man
lured me
to the Marquis of Changxing's Mansion.
He then imprisoned me
in the Western Garden
where he tortured me every day.
I...
I saw how he murdered the victims.
Liar!
Come back.
Sir, she seduced me first.
She wanted me to leave my wife.
I said no,
so she's taking revenge on me.
Sir, my wounds
are the evidence.
Miss Chi.
You saw Cao Xingyu murder someone.
Did you see the weapon he used?
Sir,
he used a horsewhip.
Run! I dare you!
Is it fun?
Isn't it exciting?
She
is trying to frame me.
Do not believe her.
I will preside over this trial
with fairness.
Do you know
where the whip is?
It is
in the Marquis of Changxing's Mansion...
Miss Chi!
Think twice before you speak.
I am the heir apparent to my father.
You can't just accuse me like that.
You might be the heir apparent,
but in my court, you need
to watch your behavior.
Miss Chi.
Do not fear.
Please continue.
I am speaking the truth.
The weapon is
in the Marquis of Changxing's Mansion...
Shut your mouth!
Miss Chi.
Miss Chi!
Long Dan!
Commandant Yu!
Are you all right?
Let go of me!
Get up!
How dare you,
Cao Xingyu.
You endangered the lives of others
in my court with a weapon.
Take him away.
I am the heir apparent
to the Marquis of Changxing.
You can't touch me!
Long Dan!
Put him in a cell for his trial!
Yes, sir!
Let go of me!
Commandant Yu!
Get a physician.
Are you all right, Commandant Yu?
I'm fine.
Commandant Yu!
Sir,
how is Mr. Yu?
He was fortunate
to receive prompt treatment.
Any moment later
and he might be too far gone
for even the greatest physician.
Most of the toxins in his body
have been cleared out.
What wonderful news.
Thank you, sir.
However, do not leave his side tonight.
Notify me
if anything happens.
Come with me to my store
to get some detoxifying herbs.
Miss Jiang, could you...?
Don't worry.
I'll stay
to look after Commander Yu.
Let's get the herbs.
You thought I was the Saintess.
Yet you didn't kill me.
You even risked your life to save me.
You're awake.
Thank you for taking care of me,
Miss Jiang.
You were injured because of me.
I will not forgive myself
if I don't take good care of you.
I'm already used to
such trivial injuries.
Do not worry about me.
This is not a trivial injury.
The physician said
that if we arrived later,
we might
have to bury you.
Commander Yu.
You and I are strangers.
Why did you risk your life to save me?
I didn't expect
the arrow to be poisoned.
Miss Chi and you
are strangers too.
Yet you risked your life to save her.
Right.
Who would have thought
that the arrow was poison?
Let me get you some water.
Miss Si, let me do it.
Aman, I can do it.
Miss Jiang.
Mr. Zhen.
Let me do it.
Sure.
What do I do?
What am I supposed to do?
Cao Xingyu
is imprisoned.
His father will do everything he can
to clear his name.
If Cao Xingyu is freed,
Qian
will be in danger once more.
Anmou, help us.
Anmou!
Mother.
Mother, help us.
Qian grew up
under your watch.
You won't sit by
and watch her die, will you, Mother?
Anmou,
do something.
See if you can find any aid
in the Imperial Court.
Mother.
Qian
is also my proudest daughter.
I too care for her.
I have asked around today,
but I was shunned by all.
They are afraid
of the Marquis of Changxing too.
But Mother,
an opportunity
might present itself in the future.
Hurry up and help Mother unwind.
I should leave you two be.
Anmou!
Don't go, Anmou!
Please.
Commandant Yu.
Have some water.
Right, your hand is injured.
Let me feed you.
My left hand's still good.
Can you
put the cup next to me?
So,
how are you?
Nothing much.
Did you find the evidence?
I did.
Every time I encounter cases like this,
it reminds me
of how depraved
humanity can be.
I have adjudged
many cases,
yet I still cannot
get used to it.
Mr. Zhen, that's because
you have empathy.
And thus, you can adjudge
with fairness.
No innocent men
will be wrongfully convicted,
and no criminal can walk away
scot-free.
You seek a life
of accountability.
Miss Jiang...
That's why the people need
the Capital Administration Office,
Mr. Zhen.
Especially you.
Laws cannot force everyone
to be kind.
But it can make them
think twice
before doing
evil.
You're right, Commandant Yu.
Miss Jiang.
But some people
are not afraid of laws.
Because they are not humans.
They are animals.
Ease your mind, Commandant Yu.
The evidence is as secured as it can be.
Cao Xingyu will not get away.
But Mr. Zhen,
you must take precautions.
The Marquis of Changxing
will be taking action
before the trial.
He will use all his connections
in the Imperial Court
and do anything
to put you under pressure.
I am impressed
by your foresight, Miss Jiang.
Worry not,
Miss Jiang.
Whatever it is,
I will not cave
under any pressure.
I
can vouch for that.
He is quite impervious.
See?
His injury is almost healed.
Thank you for the compliment,
Commandant Yu.
You know what?
I
will look after Commandant Yu today.
You have had a shock just now,
so you ought to take some rest.
Long Dan
went with the physician
to collect some herbs.
He'll be back soon.
I can stay
to brew the medicine for Commandant Yu.
Don't.
That is a menial task.
Long Dan can do it.
I can do it too.
Perhaps Miss Jiang should stay.
I gave Long Dan
some other tasks.
For the Capital Administration Office.
Or I can arrange for two guards
to come here.
You can't possibly ask Miss Jiang
to stay up all night for you.
Since when did you learn
to be so protective
of women?
Thank you, Mr. Zhen.
Have a good rest, Commandant Yu.
I'll visit tomorrow.
Miss Jiang,
let me see you out.
Sure.
Please stay, Mr. Zhen.
You need to look after Commandant Yu.
Commandant Yu.
Is it just me
or is Miss Jiang
quite different
from the other ladies out there?
She was so ravishing
when she stood her ground
in the courthouse.
Besides, she's
very grateful for her savior.
Commandant Yu?
Did you hear me?
Well,
if I had taken the arrow instead,
perhaps...
Perhaps we would have a funeral repast.
A repast?
That
would be great.
The Cao family is horrible.
I feel sorry for Qian.
Shu,
this is
my family.
[Madam Ruan, Jiang Anmou's concubine]
Qian is my daughter.
So I do care for her.
Please don't blame me.
I didn't know
things would turn out
this way.
I thought I could just power
through it with grit.
Alas,
Cao Xingyu turned around
and accused us of wrongdoing.
He
is imprisoned,
but there's nothing much we can do.
If the Marquis manages to save him,
Qian
will suffer a lot.
Even if the Marquis manages to save him,
so long as Qian
is freed from the wicked man's torture,
you, Qiao,
Pei, and I
remain together.
That's better than anything.
Anmou, the future
is full of possibilities.
Just believe
that what goes around, comes around.
Well said.
Shu,
you're the only one
who knows
how to comfort me in this family.
You and your daughter
killed my entire family,
forcing me to leave Zhou.
And you continue to hunt me down
to the Southern Frontier.
Today is my wedding day.
You are the Princess Royal.
Just because your daughter
is in love with my husband,
you now want me to pen
a letter of separation
and jump off this cliff?
Sooner or later, you will be punished
for your cruelty!
Yu Qi should feel honored
that my daughter fancies him.
Whoever my daughter wants,
I'll get them for her.
Jiang Si,
you can't think
that a man
will stay loyal to you forever.
Pen the letter of separation
and Yu Qi will know
to give up on you.
Mingyue and he
are bound to get married.
Just give up already.
I will not pen the letter.
Someone.
Qi!
What did you do to him?
Let go of me.
Don't hurt him!
You will decide
what I'll do to him.
Pen
the letter of separation
and jump off the cliff,
and I will spare his life.
Otherwise,
his life
will be at my mercy.
Stop!
Don't!
[Yu Qi]
Yu Qi,
despite our time together,
I haven't been
completely honest with you.
When we met,
I was all alone
and was looking for someone
to fall back on.
♪A sudden glance,
just like our first meeting♪
I now realize...
♪Feelings remain,
but things are ever unclear♪
that I do not love you at all.
♪Memories replay♪
Thank you for looking after me.
No need to search for me.
♪Can I make it through
another long night?♪
From now on...
we're on our own.
♪Afraid of losing you again♪
♪The pain lingers deep inside♪
♪Leaving dreams incomplete♪
♪I count the petals as they fall♪
♪Each one a time I've thought of you♪
♪Past lives fade like smoke♪
[Jiang Si]
♪Can the dreams be undone?♪
♪I still can't let you go♪
♪No matter how far the journey takes me♪
♪If love is strong,
what is there to fear?♪
♪In this lifetime♪
♪Can I make it through
another long night?♪
♪Afraid of losing you again♪
♪The pain lingers deep inside♪
♪Leaving dreams incomplete♪
♪I still can't let you go♪
♪No matter how far the journey takes me♪
♪I'll do anything to save♪
If there was a second chance
and I managed to avert all misfortune,
perhaps we
wouldn't be separated
and reach
a bitter ending.
Miss Si, here's your perilla drink.
Miss Si?
Miss Si,
are you worried about Commandant Yu?
Didn't you say
he was fine and would recover
in a few days?
Are you letting your worries
get the better of you?
Aman.
Tell me.
If there's a man in your life,
you know
that he and you
might not have a happy ending.
Maybe it's a misunderstanding.
Perhaps...
Regardless,
he and you might end in misery.
Will you
stay with him?
That depends
on whether we're meant to be.
What if you are?
Miss Si,
did Commandant Yu confess to you?
I'm asking you a question.
If it were me...
I...
would stay with him.
It's hard
to find your other half
in our short life.
On many occasions,
we cannot
be our authentic selves.
If two souls in love
cannot express their love freely,
then what is
the joy
in life?
How come Yu
was arrested?
Didn't you handle everything already?
A witness suddenly came forth.
How could this be?
Is the witness...?
Don't worry about the witness.
They want to find out the truth.
I'll make them find a body instead.
They'll be stumped.
When will Yu ever be freed then?
He won't eat
or sleep well in the prison.
He's suffering.
Enough!
Quit whimpering.
Where
is the Golden Plant I bought in Lingnan
for you?
- Wu!
- You're here.
Thanks for your hard work.
Get some food.
Thanks, Wu.
Enjoy while it's warm.
I'll leave you two be.
I go inside first.
Thank you.
Miss Chi, your food is here.
Thank you, sir.
You must be starving.
Eat something.
Chief was right.
You are the mole among us.
[Haitang House]
Si.
Zhan.
Where are you going?
I want
to check on Commandant Yu.
Great.
I want to pay him
a visit too.
Let's go together.
Sure, let's go.
Sir.
Didn't we just visit Commandant Yu?
My sister cannot be alone
with him in a room.
Besides,
can't you smell how delicious it is
the soup she's carrying?
Mr. Yu.
Yu.
Jiang Si brewed the soup for you.
Try it.
Thank you.
It smells good.
Like good liquor,
soup is best enjoyed together.
Perhaps Jiang,
you should do the honor first?
No.
It's for your recovery.
It's okay.
I can't do that to you.
Bring us a bowl.
But sharing
makes this more meaningful.
Here.
Mr. Yu, there's another bowl here.
- See?
- We have a bowl.
I'll dig in then.
Be my guest.
Never have I
had such refreshing fish soup.
There's not even a hint of gamey taste
in it.
Yu, I'm not just bragging
about my sister.
But this soup has
such a nuanced flavor profile.
She put her soul into it.
And she's also thoughtful.
She knows you're wounded
and must avoid spices.
So she didn't add pepper.
It...
Do we have pepper?
Here.
Mr. Yu.
Thank you so much.
You have been so kind
toward me
and I do not know how to repay it.
Perhaps I...
No need to betroth her.
Perhaps I can repay your kindness
with more sumptuous meals.
Drink while it's warm.
Slow down,
or you'll choke.
I'm sorry that I couldn't give you
a more comfortable life.
Once
we find our way
back to Ling'an,
I'll cook you
a feast of delicious dishes.
What
will you make?
I have to imagine it.
Sure.
I'll find
a fresh crucian carp
in the Jinshui River.
Then I brush egg white
and huangjiu on it
to marinate it.
After that,
I put it in a hot pan
and fry it till it's golden brown.
Then, I'll add condiments
such as ginger and chenpi
before simmering it for two hours.
The fish will be flavorful
and tender,
and its soup will be a milky color.
Miss Jiang.
Miss Jiang?
My hand is still wounded.
Don't worry about it.
Thank you.
♪Through endless twists
in the mundane world♪
♪The breezy wind blows,
the heart grows tender and bitter♪
♪I ask the Sun
if the light has taken root♪
♪As it prospers,
our love story writes itself♪
♪We lock eyes
and promise to stay together forever♪
♪After countless challenges,
we are still us♪
♪Our inseparable souls
can weather all storms♪
♪We cross paths
and promise to stay together forever♪
♪The tapestry of destiny
is filled with our youth♪
♪Our blissful time together
will lead us to the sea of stars♪
Miss, you know what's good.
This is a dagger
used by Nie Yinniang.
Check it out.
It's genuine. I'm not lying.
You can trust us.
I knew I made the right choice.
Sir,
did you just say
this was a dagger used by Nie Yinniang?
Sir, do you want it too?
Miss, he...
It's you.
I was wondering who in this world
would believe
that this was a dagger
used by Nie Yinniang.
You want what I want.
Are you doing this on purpose?
- Me?
- Sir.
I wanted this dagger first.
Right.
How much is it?
Fifty liang. It's very cheap.
I offer 60 liang.
That's a good offer.
Seventy.
Miss.
I offer 100 liang.
And I'm buying other things too.
You...
Can I see this?
What a fine choice, sir.
This is the legendary
Twelve-Hour Plate
from the Imperial Treasury
of the Tang Dynasty.
Each hour on top
has a corresponding zodiac sign.
Twelve-Hour Plate, huh?
Yes. It's one and only
in the world.
Can you count it?
How many hours are there?
No need to count.
It's for you to check the time,
right,
sir?
Eleven hours.
So this is...?
And this one.
Sir, could this be...?
This is the remaining last stone
used by the Goddess Nyuwa
when she was repairing the sky.
Exactly.
What do you think of this stone?
Why do I feel like
he's a scammer?
That took you so long!
He is a scammer.
Let's go.
But I...
What's going on?
So
Nie Yinniang's dagger
is also fake?
No such dagger exists
in this world.
You're quite smart.
You know how to identify it.
Everyone on this street except for you
knows it's fake.
Thank you for helping me out.
You can have this back.
Seriously?
You...
I ran some errands, earned some money,
and decided to repay my debt to you.
My money is back.
Come on. I'll buy you a meal.
Great!
[Guangju Parlor]
Bravo!
I might not
have enough money to buy you a meal.
Oh, my dear money!
Have some.
This too.
- Great!
- Splendid!
- Wonderful!
- Excellent!
For today's tales of oddities,
let's talk about the cursed soul,
the Seventh Prince.
Do you still remember
the battle by the frontier 20 years ago?
It was a dim night.
Those Nanwu scoundrels
attacked our realm
without a sign.
Our soldiers were taken by surprise,
and many people died.
Yet that night,
the Seventh Prince
was born.
The Imperial Palace was basking
in merriment.
Yet
as news of the defeat
spread to Ling'an,
everything
changed.
What happened to him then?
Stop running
or I'll ask the Nanwu barbarians
to take you away.
As the crisis approached its precipice,
the Directorate of Astronomy
submitted a memorial,
claiming that the Seventh Prince
was the reincarnation of misfortune.
His birth
had brought about unrest at the border.
That night,
hundreds of officials
knelt in the palace,
urging His Majesty to eliminate
the Seventh Prince
to save the realm.
But he was born moments ago.
His Majesty didn't have it in him
to do so,
so he had someone
send the baby
to the Southern Frontier.
If he makes it through, it's up to fate.
Should he die,
it will offer solace
to the valiant soldiers.
And that was enough to placate
everyone in the palace.
Interestingly,
since then,
we
have never won a battle.
Our realm shrinks in size.
All because
the embodiment of misfortune lives
in the army.
That's right.
Sheesh.
- Exactly.
- Indeed.
The accursed Seventh Prince...
Who did that?
What's going on?
What the heck?
This is unacceptable!
What is the meaning of this?
You
fabricated a baseless story.
I shall rip your tongue out.
Spare me, miss. I'm just doing my job.
Chuchu?
Long Dan?
[The End of Episode 6]
♪Through endless twists♪
♪In the mundane world♪
♪The breezy wind blows♪
♪The heart grows tender and bitter♪
♪I ask the Sun♪
♪If the light has taken root♪
♪As it prospers♪
♪Our love story writes itself♪
♪We lock eyes
and promise to stay together forever♪
♪After countless challenges,
we are still us♪
♪Our inseparable souls♪
♪Can weather all storms♪
♪We cross paths
and promise to stay together forever♪
♪The tapestry of destiny
is filled with our youth♪
♪Our blissful time together♪
♪Will lead us♪
♪To the sea of stars♪
♪Our destined paths♪
♪The years will hold♪
♪A light shines at the tunnel's end♪
♪Where happy endings will transcend♪
♪We cross paths
and promise to stay together forever♪
♪The tapestry of destiny
is filled with our youth♪
♪Our blissful time together♪
♪Will lead us to what we desire♪
♪We lock eyes
and promise to stay together forever♪
♪Through frost-kissed trails,
and starry space♪
♪Moon-silvered dreams♪
♪On love's embrace♪
♪Hearts bound as one,
through time's soft grace♪
♪Love's tide guides,
beyond our mortal space♪
♪A moment kept with your embrace♪
♪Where blooms have found their place♪