JEW
Number 23, please.
Number 27, please.
PLENGPIN
Do I seriously have to remind you again?
No one can know we know each other.
Chill, no one saw.
No need to tell me off.
And you're talking back to me.
This is also a no.
Just one. No one will smell it.
I said no. Cut it out.
Ajin, listen.
I'm about to go on stage for the audition.
So?
So I wanted to relax a bit, okay?
I may look fine, but I'm all stressed out.
No means no.
Then... help me focus like you always do.
Fine.
Close your eyes.
Next up, number 0056.
What if I told you
this world holds things you can't see?
Would you believe me?
Like white and black.
Belief and truth.
In this world filled with lights,
how much darkness do you think exists?
Beneath the charming surface
lies something deeper, darker.
The principle of balance
no one can escape,
and not everyone understands.
But those who understand,
the ones who shine brightly,
able to hide their darkness perfectly,
will get everything they ever want.
Especially here,
a place full of lights...
lust and seduction,
and darkness.
You can't look away.
GUYS, BIG NEWS.
DAMN, AUDITION TO FIND NEW FEMALE LEAD?
M.L. IN THE FLESH
THIS WILL GO VIRAL
THRILLING
THIS IS WHAT THE INDUSTRY NEEDS
NEW STAR IS BORN
WHO'S THIS ANYWAY?
My concept of Grandfather?
M.L. RAY
M.L. DANGRAYRAI PORAMANTIWA
He's my ideal,
not that I want to call myself
a national artist like him.
But he was a true artist.
He was obsessed with perfection
and understood all his crafts to the bone.
As you can see, his legendary works
speak for themselves.
All of them.
But his final work
was on a whole other level.
Bu-nga Muen Phamorn
was the final novel he composed
before he passed away.
He gave a clear order
to keep it a secret for 66 years.
Why?
I don't know.
His artistic whim, maybe?
But his instruction was clear.
After that, it must be published and
adapted as a stage play simultaneously.
And here's the best part.
The lead actress of this play will wear
the dress he made before he died.
So let me take this chance
to officially announce
that in six months,
I'll hold the biggest event ever
to find the lead actress for
Bu-nga Muen Phamorn.
I have only one task for you.
This is the first page of the novel.
No synopsis. Interpret it in your own way.
If you think you're ready, come prepared.
I'll see you there.
YOUR LIFE IS ABOUT TO CHANGE
Hey! Let go! I said, let go of me!
COUNTDOWN: 6 MONTHS TO
BU-NGA MUEN PHAMORN
You piece of shit!
You can't do this to me!
Your client made the first move.
He grabbed me!
What the hell?
Shit!
YOUR LIFE IS ABOUT TO CHANGE
Your name's Pin, right?
I met this family
who gave me your contact details.
You... don't look much like your photos.
- Wait.
- Hey! Let me go!
Calm down.
Can't you tell I mean no harm?
What do you want?
Why bury your past
and leave everything behind?
Do you even realize what you have in you?
What?
You want to audition
for Bu-nga Muen Phamorn, right?
I want access to the prize dress.
So if you're ready
to leave your past behind
and do whatever it takes
to win your dream role,
I'll help you win.
Who the hell are you?
Let's just say,
I'm a star maker.
Okay, all set.
Let's continue the interview.
Sure.
Your name is Plengpin, right?
Yes.
You've got a great foundation
in traditional dance.
Have you been training long?
Lift your foot a little higher.
My family just wanted me to have a hobby.
So my mom had me
start dancing from a young age.
So why did you decide to join
Bu-nga Muen Phamorn?
It just felt like fate, honestly.
My mom has been a huge fan
of M.L. Prisanan's novels for years,
so I've always felt
a strong connection to his work.
I've read it so many times,
and when I found out
about this competition--
Excuse me.
Your mom actually named you
after the novel when you were born?
Yes.
So it's not a new name
you've adopted recently?
Why are you asking?
Just that...
I saw online that you registered
your account only six months ago.
What a coincidence!
Oh, that.
My account got hacked,
so all my info was wiped.
How about this?
Tell me which verse is your favorite.
Didn't you just say
you've read the book multiple times?
To be blunt,
we're only looking for the real deal
in this contest.
Fakes... are just a waste
of hard disk space.
The lyre's melody, forlorn
Whispers, laments, and yearns
A love profound, enchantingly drawn
A sonnet begging for a knight returns
The lyre string breaks a soul's demise
Blood freely pours
The song of love by the lyre forsakes
Silenced forevermore
To be blunt too,
whether you believe me
or want to question who named me,
it doesn't matter to me at all.
But if you're gonna do me dirty
and accuse me of being fake,
you'd better be ready for me to hit back.
Damn. That sweet-looking girl
named Plengpin,
she's got a sharp tongue, man.
Right?
I was shook.
But...
But I kinda love it. Can I root for her?
Me too. We need someone like her.
That's what makes it fun.
Totally. Serves Aekasit right!
He was being a jerk anyway.
Oh no! Someone fainted!
- Who's that?
- Miss, are you okay? What's wrong?
Lie down first.
- Do you have an inhaler?
- No, I don't.
- No one has an inhaler? Anyone?
- No.
- Hey, call an ambulance, now.
- Calm down.
- Any inhaler?
- I'm sorry.
- Please, ask around.
- Call the hospital, please.
Hello. Hi!
- Why is she...?
- Miss, breathe slowly.
- Slowly.
- Easy, take it easy.
Breathe slowly.
Take it easy.
Did she hit her head?
Any inhaler?
Have you asked already?
Shit.
Hey, this didn't need to
turn into a huge deal.
We just talked for a second.
It's not about how long you talked.
The point is,
you disobeyed a direct order.
I told you to stay away from Anya.
- Was that really so hard to understand?
- Yeah, it kinda was.
All you ever say is, "Be careful."
You never give a real reason.
What do I know after six months?
One.
DO NOT ENGAGE
She's a famous model.
Two.
She used to date you.
Who is she really?
What makes her dangerous?
You've never told me any of it.
You could've at least said
how things ended between you.
You really think I don't know
why you were trying to get close to me?
Enough.
There are things better left unknown.
Just focus on what you're supposed to do.
Changing the subject again.
Plengpin, listen.
Our deal was that you would enter
this competition, and you'd win.
All I want is access to
the Bu-nga Muen Phamorn dress.
If anything goes wrong
and you're eliminated,
we're done. End of story.
I know that.
I will win.
We made a promise, didn't we?
Did we?
Nothing's guaranteed.
We might lose.
You know how unpredictable M.L. Ray is.
So what?
We've come too far to quit now.
These past six months,
I've trained my ass off
and followed every single plan you made.
And you?
You've been digging up info
like your life depends on it.
UNKNOWN FIRE
BURNS VICTIM ALIVE IN LAB ROOM
And besides, you're not exactly normal.
With the two of us
working together this hard...
it's time you stop doubting.
Good.
Then...
let's start prepping for the semifinals.
POETRY FROM THE NOVEL
BU-NGA MUEN PHAMORN
THE BEGINNING
From what I can tell, this should be
the first verse of the novel.
It's about a famous dressmaker
named Bu-nga.
She was cursed.
Any outfit she wore made her skin burn.
Until she found a magical fabric
that kept her cool.
But, of course,
it belonged to the city ruler.
Blah, blah, blah.
Anyway, looks like the next round
is gonna be based on this.
But seriously, what's with M.L. Ray?
He's totally eccentric.
We have to dig out a VHS player for this?
What a pain in the ass.
Yeah, he's nuts.
But you know what?
The whole thing's
about to go viral online.
GUYS, ISN'T THIS TOO INDIE?
Someone posted that the tape won't play.
Now people are dying to know what's in it.
And the harder it is to access,
the more obsessed people get.
M.L. Ray may seem quirky,
but whether it's the previous trick
or this VHS stunt,
I'm sure he planned it all.
That guy's more dangerous than we think.
Come on, let's practice the dance.
What's wrong?
I was just thinking,
if he's really that smart...
just copying the dance
feels kind of basic, doesn't it?
So?
SOUL BURNED INSIDE THE HEART
Wow.
The lighting team's giving us
something stunning here.
Damn, she went all in!
That's gutsy as hell.
Seriously.
If it were me,
I'd be dying of embarrassment.
Oh, please.
Just look at your outfit.
You clearly planned to pull
the same stunt.
What? No way!
I just happen to be wearing
two layers today.
You, on the other hand...
Your outfit underneath
is probably way skimpier.
We'll see, won't we?
What do you think?
This one's definitely
making it through, right?
No idea.
I guess we've got nothing to worry about.
Staff!
Geez, today was brutal.
Ajin?
EVERYTHING IS IN HERE
Would it kill you to wait
and hear the results with me?
Whatever.
And the result is...
ELIMINATED
ANYONE KNOW WHO MADE IT?
TONS OF PEOPLE DIDN'T PASS.
EVEN THE ELIMINATION CARD
IS DRAMATIC. SO EXTRA.
What the actual hell is going on?
Sorry, the number you have dialed
is currently unavailable.
Sorry.
Oh!
Do we know each other?
Oh, no.
You're Anya, right?
I'm actually a big fan.
Really? That's sweet of you.
I hope you make it through.
Thanks.
But watch out for that guy.
The moment you're no longer useful,
he'll drop you like you're nothing.
Yes?
Excuse me.
Hey there.
You're here already?
Here you are.
It's cold here. Have something warm first.
Thank you.
Also, sorry for calling you in
for this last-minute reshoot.
But didn't I get eliminated already?
Everyone got the same letter.
But the truth is, you actually made it.
M.L. Ray just wants to keep it top secret.
Okay, let's get to the interview.
Introduce yourself.
Hello, I'm Plengpin Piengamorn.
I'm 27 years old.
What do you do for work?
A little of everything.
Events, commercials...
I'm open to most kinds of jobs.
Open to everything, huh?
Hold on a sec.
Sorry. Your top's done up a bit tight.
Can you unbutton one for me?
Nice.
So when you say "open to any job,"
how far are you willing to go?
- What do you mean by that?
- Sorry.
You mind unbuttoning one more for me?
Isn't this already too much?
What's the problem?
I saw you were showing way
more skin earlier today.
In this industry, if you're too uptight
and overthink everything,
you're not gonna last.
I need to call my manager first.
Hey, careful.
If you fall over now,
it'll spoil the goods.
You... What the hell
did you put in my drink?
Hey, man.
Oh, you're awake.
Don't panic.
What the hell did you do to me?!
You really don't get it, do you?
That "you made it through" story?
Total lie.
You really were eliminated.
Your manager didn't want
to leave empty-handed,
so he sold you to us.
Which means
I can do whatever I want with you.
No, no, no! This isn't real.
- Don't overthink it.
- Let me go!
You'll get used to it.
No! No!
She's tough.
Here, take this.
Now tell me...
Which style do you want to go for?
- My clients are into all kinds of things.
- I said let go!
You want to go the sexy route?
Or bloody and intense?
It's all on the table.
I said let go!
Hey! Hey!
What the hell is this?!
Let me go! What is this?!
This isn't real.
This can't be real.
It's not real.
Help!
Somebody help me!
Can anyone hear me? Help!
Any last words before you die?
What the hell is this?!
What do you want from me?
Any last words before you die?
I asked you, what do you want?!
Who are you?! Say something!
Any last words before you die?
Talk to me!
- What do you want?! I'm talking to you!
- Any last words before you die?
Can't you say anything else?!
Any last words before you die?
Mom.
Mom, are you watching?
I'm sorry...
I never made you proud.
But today, I finally found
something that matters.
Something that could've made you proud.
And I failed again.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I miss you.
We'll see each other soon, okay?
And that was the performance
from Plengpin,
our final contestant of the show.
Your show was extraordinary.
It felt so real.
I am truly impressed.
And now, the real competition begins.
Who will win?
Who will be chosen by Bu-nga Muen Phamorn?
Stay tuned.
This round's challenge recreated
a scene from the novel
when Bu-nga was about to be
executed by the city ruler.
But her heartfelt plea
triggered a miracle.
From being spared to being tasked
with crafting a magical dress,
the beginning of an incredible journey.
After an intense battle
where no one held back,
we finally have our four finalists,
each equally exceptional.
Anya, the talented model and actress.
At the time,
I just wanted to give it my all
so I wouldn't regret anything later.
Jew, the skilled dancer
and multiple-time competition winner.
Huge thanks to M.L. Ray
for helping us break past
so many boundaries.
Myday, the influencer everyone's watching.
This really took my performance
to the next level.
I'm seriously blown away.
And Plengpin, a fresh face
with a one-of-a-kind character.
Now I get it.
No wonder M.L. Ray is so famous.
Real talk.
What they did to stage that scene,
that was messed up.
Under normal circumstances, he'd be sued.
Yeah, but who'd dare sue him?
Everyone, once you're done with touch-ups,
let's get ready to shoot the final part.
It's getting late.
Time for bed after this.
Move it, girl!
Still sulking?
All good here?
Bastard.
Come on!
And to keep things absolutely secret
for the next two months,
all four contestants will be hidden away
deep in the forest
at the Poramantiwa family's old estate.
A place no outsider has ever seen.
But before the next round begins,
there's still one final event,
M.L. Ray's most special surprise.
Come in. Take a seat.
I'm so excited.
Even though I can't show you
the actual preserved dress yet,
this will be the first time
we're seeing a completed image
of the authentic Bu-nga Muen Phamorn dress
that my grandfather crafted.
At that moment, it felt like...
Okay, maybe this sounds dramatic,
but it really felt like time just stopped.
Everyone froze, totally in sync.
I remember...
my hands went completely numb.
We've only ever seen
unfinished sketches before, right?
But seeing the real thing
is breathtaking.
It doesn't even feel like
something made by human hands.
Why am I crying?
I don't even know.
I'm just overwhelmed.
Only one of you
will earn the highest honor
of wearing this dress to perform.
Even I am jealous of you.
And so the day ended with smiles
and awe from all four contestants.
There will be many more
challenges to come,
but they're ready for it, fully motivated.
Who will be the winner?
Let's cheer them on together.
See you in the next episode.
Goodbye for now.
Okay, wonderful!
You've all truly impressed me.
So, sir, no comments or edits?
Your impeccable work
leaves me nothing to fix.
Actually, just one thing.
The girl named Plengpin.
Why didn't we use more of her interview?
How I felt seeing the dress
for the first time?
I felt...
uncomfortable.
Yeah, uncomfortable.
Something felt off. I don't know why.
No, seriously, I really felt that way.
What else do you want me to say?
Good thing we didn't use that.
Everyone, excellent work.
I'm counting on you.
So this is where you've been hiding.
How's today been?
It was fine.
Let me guess.
Ajin told you not to talk to me?
Wow, your face gives it away so fast.
You're terrible at hiding your emotions,
you know that?
Come on, what do you really want?
Give me one?
I forgot to bring mine.
That'll cost you.
Wait, you don't even know how to smoke.
So why are you here?
I came to tell you to drop the hell out.
I'm saying this
out of the goodness of my heart.
You're the only one
who can't keep up with the show.
What's that supposed to mean?
That fake execution scene earlier?
Everyone else knew.
They just played along.
So sad, right?
Crying and calling for your dead mom.
But the important part is,
you don't know the truth about
the Bu-nga Muen Phamorn dress, do you?
What are you talking about?
Ajin hasn't changed.
He's still just using people.
This dress is way too dangerous
for a regular person,
someone who doesn't understand magic
like you.
Magic?
You noticed it, didn't you?
You were the only one
who felt uncomfortable.
Others felt it too.
But they knew how to deal with it
in their own way.
Real insiders in the world
of magic all know
M.L. Ray's grandfather was
a legendary practitioner.
He created some seriously cursed objects.
There's one artifact,
and legend says he secretly sacrificed
no fewer than ten virgin girls,
flayed their skin,
stitched it onto fabric with spells,
and sealed it with his own blood.
That became the most dangerous
cursed dress ever made.
That's right. What you saw today was fake.
Just cheap CGI for filming.
The real one?
They can never show it to the public.
And that's the real
Bu-nga Muen Phamorn dress.
Now do you get it?
This isn't some regular casting
for a TV drama.
M.L. Ray is way more unhinged
than you think.
He probably doesn't even
realize it himself.
But what he's really doing
is looking for the right sorceress
to wear that cursed dress.
Kinda funny, huh?
Under the lights and cameras,
the person who hides
in the shadows the best
is the one who wins.
You think I actually believe any of that?
Fine, don't believe me.
But I'll say it one last time.
Normal people can't handle this.
Especially here, where no one
from the outside can get in.
You probably don't have Ajin
to help you anymore.
Right?
Just quit.
I'm only saying this because I mean well.
I don't want anyone to end up dead.
Listen, Plengpin.
This competition is seriously dangerous.
The winner will not only need to
understand magic the best
and know the entertainment world
inside out.
She also needs to be able to lie
to everyone else.
If you can do that, we win.
But if the lie's too perfect,
isn't that boring?
What did you just say?
Thanks for the warning, Anya.
But you got three things wrong.
First, my mom's not dead.
That crying, that whole monologue?
Totally acting.
Still, I'm flattered that someone
like you thought it was real.
Second,
you said I'm just a regular person?
Wrong again.
So what?
You practice magic.
But do you really think
you're gonna beat me at this game?
And finally...
you said Ajin can't help me in this place.
I don't think that's true.
How is that possible?
I've already said too much.
Not gonna spoil anything else.
But thanks again, Anya, for your concern.
Let's hope this competition...
turns out to be fun.
Yo, hotshot! You spacing out?
Sorry about that.
Here are the show details for tomorrow.
When my assistant got sick out of nowhere,
I thought we were screwed.
But with you stepping in, I can relax now.
Welcome aboard
as my new assistant, hotshot.
Thanks.
I'm gonna make this show
as fun as possible.
This next round won't be solo.
You'll perform in pairs.
This whole contest is really about finding
out who the cursed dress will choose.
These challenges,
all the games we're competing in,
they don't matter at all.
Someone put shards of glass
in Myday's shoes.
An enemy is still an enemy.
But acting like a jackass like this...
- Stop!
- Are you messing with me?
...doesn't really help anyone.