♪When the past turns into an old story♪
♪The satisfaction from victory♪
♪Insignificant happiness in every meal♪
♪Who would care anymore♪
♪When diligence turns into talent♪
♪Free from the past♪
♪Every bite is the salvation of tastes♪
♪Understand everything♪
♪Take back the lost pride♪
♪I know how difficult each step is♪
♪Silence is burning,
it ends up as the trap of ashes♪
♪Take back the lost glory♪
♪I know how difficult each battle is♪
♪Hold the knife in hand
to be worthy of the brilliance♪
♪Take back the lost laughter♪
♪I know how difficult the next goal is♪
♪Face challenge,
exert all the strength to defeat mockery♪
=Sweet Trap=
=Episode 22=
I'm not here for the first time,
but I still wanna say,
dang it, capitalists!
You're here not for the first time.
Can you tell me
where the kitchen is then?
The kitchen is...
I'm sorry, guys.
There are too many guests today.
Sorry about the impolite welcome.
Impolite indeed.
We've prepared an open kitchen
for the dinner party.
I'll take you there now.
Let's go.
Did you see that?
Let's talk about it later.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
As per your list, we've got
cooking utensils,
condiments and vessels for you.
Just let me know if you need anything,
including the bathroom.
If I remember it correctly,
when you still had problems
losing your way here,
my brother had been able to hide
in the hidden compartment
of Grandpa's study.
You were worried for nothing.
You're right.
After all, Jiang Jie used to live here
for eight years.
Oh right.
Given the duration of stay here,
no one lives longer than the gardener.
I'll let you work.
Got to go.
In the nick of time.
Why did Zheng Fangxing appear here?
And he's dressed in a chef's suit.
Waiting to get the goods on you
and then replace you.
This is what the sous chef does.
I'm not talking about you.
But if you want to, I can help you.
Stop talking nonsense.
What's going on
between you and Cao Liang?
Nothing. We're just goofing around.
Jiang Xiu.
This way, please.
I want you to go shopping with me.
Okay, okay. You're the boss.
- I wanna go to the cinema tonight.
- Okay, no problem.
Answer me.
Can your cooking rival Jiang Jie's?
I'm merely a sous chef.
- It's none of my business.
- Xuyang, calm down.
Today, it's not about cooking.
It doesn't matter how good his cooking is.
Yes.
After today,
he won't deserve to compare with me at all.
We've spent so much time,
energy, resources and money on you.
We've got to make it work.
Do you understand?
Still worried about Zheng Fangxing?
I can't help feeling uneasy.
Can it be Jiang Xuyang has convinced
Jiang Ziqing to open chain restaurants?
Impossible.
In Jiang Ziqing's eyes, nothing is
more important than the Jiang family.
The plan of chain restaurants,
in some way,
will destroy the seven families'
credibility.
Jiang Ziqing won't allow anything
to shake the Jiang family's position.
Guys, mind your manners.
Mr. Chen, Mr. Wang, long time no see.
- Hello. Hello.
- Please enter.
My grandpa has been waiting inside.
Hello, welcome. Welcome.
Long time no see.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
What? You won't be the host,
but a sunshine boy here?
I just don't want you to catch a cold.
You know what,
getting sick may
liven things up.
Cao Liang
- is a lot more fun than you.
- Xiu.
We've broken up. Don't call me that.
I never agree to break up with you.
What's wrong with you today?
Why are you being so cheeky?
Xiu. Xiu.
I don't agree to break up with you.
Even if you wanna goof around,
your playmate can only be me.
Give me one more night.
I'll definitely tell you everything.
Silly.
If you trust me,
you should tell me.
Sorry.
It's inconvenient for me to greet you.
The Xue's way of slicing fish.
The double slices
can not only preserve the fish's nutrition.
The fish slice is also bigger.
Your basic skills are great.
It's thanks to my master's teaching.
You're a member of the Li family,
but you're apprenticed to Xue Congming.
The young people like you are
what the seven families need.
As my master said,
cooking is all about pleasing oneself
and satisfying the eater.
No wonder he was defeated by Jiang Jie.
Since you've beaten Jiang Jie,
you should be somewhat ambitious.
She's the least ambitious person.
Mr. Jiang,
please don't push her.
I'm afraid that she'll fail
your expectations.
She may vanish into thin air
if she's not careful.
- Are you blaming me?
- Of course I dare not.
We're here mainly to celebrate
your birthday.
Wish you a long life
and boundless happiness.
You're so different from your father.
I'll leave you alone.
Don't be mad.
The last one to whom you expressed
birthday wishes was almost arrested.
I'm not mad.
I just can't believe
he just talked about my dad so calmly.
Rest assured.
He'll pay for it. Definitely.
My waist is so sore.
Any better?
I'll go to the bathroom.
- I'll go with you.
- No need.
Keep an eye on those dishes.
In case anyone may mess around.
Take care.
- Rest assured.
- Go ahead.
- Does that guy know about this?
- No, he doesn't.
I'll take you to the break room. Go.
Chef Jiang, Chef Cao.
The dinner party is about to start.
What are you doing here?
Ms. Cui said her brother was practicing
his speech in the break room.
I'm worried that he may be hungry.
So, I wanna ask him to eat something.
I've told you.
Jiang Xuyang's secretary
is indeed a capable woman.
She could manage a five-star restaurant
before.
Now she can manage
the whole Jiang family.
Does she meet your requirements?
She's the assistant I want indeed.
But I guess Mr. Xuyang must be reluctant
to let me have her.
Chef Cao, you must be kidding.
There's nothing I can't bear to let go.
We were talking about
your capable secretary.
That's too flattering.
Since Chef Cao has given you
such a compliment,
Miss Zhu,
should you give him a toast
to say thanks?
I've emptied this.
Chef Cao has had a drink,
you can't hurt his feelings, right?
I've taken a sip of this.
How about getting another glass
to make a toast to him?
Miss Zhu, here's another reminder.
I have some issues with Cui Can.
You'd better not worry about
if he is hungry.
Tonight,
just stay where you should be.
Don't cause trouble for me anymore.
Master Jiang, congratulations.
Congratulations.
Welcome. Welcome.
Please be seated.
Take a seat.
Look. Here comes Cui Can.
Ladies and gentlemen, good evening.
I'm Cui Can,
the host for tonight.
- Host?
- Today is Master Jiang's birthday.
Master Jiang, here's a birthday wish to you
on behalf of the Alliance.
Wish you a long life
- and boundless happiness.
- Great!
I'll empty it. Be my guest.
Thank you.
Guys, I wonder if you're satisfied
with today's food.
Absolutely.
Great that you like it.
I hope you won't hate me
for holding you back from eating.
I've been asked to do a favor.
Someone has ordered two dishes
for Master Jiang
and also wanted me to tell a story.
Salted Pork Soup.
Grandpa, I'll go to the bathroom.
I'll be right back.
Here's the story.
Once upon a time, there was
a medical family.
Mr. Yao, who owned a clinic,
had twin sons.
His older son was considerate
and down-to-earth
but his talent was mediocre.
His younger son was a bit talented
and yet aggressive.
One day, his younger son competed
with someone.
He promised if he lost,
he'd leave home himself.
Guys, guess how it went in the end.
The younger son lost.
Yes, finally, the younger son lost.
Grandpa, there are so many guests here.
Don't you want to hear the story out?
But later on, the younger son
went back on his word.
He couldn't give up the position
and wealth of the Yao family.
So, he begged Mr. Yao with tears.
And Mr. Yao adored his younger son.
He made his older son take the blame.
Eventually,
the older son was expelled from home.
All this is your plan, right?
I'm sorry to have kept this from you.
Dad.
What?
What do you mean?
Didn't you say my old man agreed with me
to come back?
Why did I have to take the back door?
I've put in a good word for you
in front of Grandpa. A lot of good words.
So, he reluctantly let you back home.
I've told you
about today's situation before.
Don't cause extra trouble, okay?
No extra trouble.
Me causing extra trouble?
The old man is a dotard.
Are you a dotard too?
Jiang Jie has come back.
If I don't come back,
Jiang Xiu and Jiang Jie
will overturn this family soon.
Dad.
What? Are you gonna tell me what to do?
Grandpa has been not well lately.
The doctor said he must
keep a light diet.
He can't be crossed.
You're finally back here.
Mind your manners.
Everybody,
I've finished the story.
As for the one to offer birthday wishes,
he'll arrive soon.
Guys, I'm sorry. I came late.
Dad, wish you a long life
and boundless happiness.
Jiang Yuanfeng?
As per our arrangement,
it should be Mr. Ge.
My master is here too?
Where is he?
He's in the room back there.
Guys,
enjoy the dinner.
It should be done by Jiang Xuyang.
Here's the thing.
You'll go and find out
what Zheng Fangxing is doing.
- I'll go to meet my master.
- Okay.
Li Nai, thank you.
I'm really happy.
Master.
- Thank you for coming.
- Never mind.
Chef Jiang, is it you who invited
Jiang Yuanfeng here?
It should be Jiang Xuyang's arrangement.
It's a bit surprising,
but Jiang Yuanfeng's appearance
just makes things better.
Is this good for us?
It should be an intentional arrangement.
The greatest resistance of his plan
of chain restaurants is Jiang Ziqing.
He must want to bring him down
by leveraging us.
Master, I'll leave this to you then.
Salted Pork Soup.
This season is
the best time to eat this. Here.
Here, Dad. Please try it.
Dad.
It's been a while.
You should be mollified now.
Master Jiang.
Are you not satisfied
with the dish I ordered?
Guys, long time no see.
Ge Qunshan.
Aren't you already retired?
Are you still trying to make it
to the seven families?
You got me wrong.
Today, I'm here mainly to give
my disciple a boost.
And passingly, I'll tell you a story.
- Jiang Jie is your disciple?
- Can't you
tell from the Salted Pork Soup,
the signature dish of the Ge family?
Smash it. Even if you smash everything,
you can't change
the existence of this dish.
Nor will it change the fact
that you once lost to me.
Isn't it Jiang Yuanshan,
Master Jiang's elder son,
who competed with Mr. Ge at that time?
That's what I believed before.
So,
I ruined an innocent cook who was
passionate about cooking.
Oh I remember.
No wonder the Yao family's story sounds
so familiar.
The medical family in the story
is equivalent to the cooking family.
Yao family is equivalent to Jiang family,
the head of the seven families.
Master Jiang
covered up for his younger son
by sacrificing his older son.
- But aren't they both his sons?
- Tell me about it.
That's total nonsense.
Am I talking nonsense?
Why don't you take a look
at the last dish?
It has taken Eating at Dusk
a lot of effort
to prepare the two dishes for today.
This dish,
Uncle Yuanfeng,
I guess you are familiar with it.
You chose not to make Ginger Duck Stew
back then.
Is it because you lost to my master
on this dish,
or is it because you feel a bit guilty
for your brother took the blame for you?
(Fish Flavored Shredded Pork;
Pre-made dish)
Is Jiang Xuyang gonna use
these pre-made dishes to
- fulfill his dream of chain restaurants?
- You'll soon know
whether he can make it.
Stop looking. Keep working.
Fangxing.
Why are you becoming like this?
Do you know
what the pre-made dishes mean?
Cooks will be replaced.
Customers can only eat those
replicated dishes
that look delicate and yet emotionless.
Cooks aren't respected in Baichuan at all.
Don't you know that?
Those nights when the cooks are pushed
around like dogs by the Alliance
and have to worry about being censored.
So, we should change the Alliance
so that every cook can
open a restaurant freely
rather than help the snobs
like Jiang Xuyang
to turn the cook into an object.
The Alliance has a history of 200 years.
How can it be changed easily?
It's at least better than holding a candle
to the devil.
Dad.
Dad, help me.
Dang it!
How dare you collude with your brother
to deceive me?
Back then, how did you make your brother
a scapegoat for you?
And why did he come to me and say
he was the one who lost the game
to someone else?
Tell me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, everyone.
I failed to educate my sons properly,
but I really didn't know about this.
Yuanshan and Yuanfeng
are twin brothers.
Yuanshan has adored his brother
since their childhood.
I didn't expect them to do this.
What a shame!
Yuanshan passed away too early.
Otherwise, I'd clear his name for sure.
Well said. Well said.
It's not too late
if you stand up for him now.
Yeah. I must report this to the Alliance
and put this matter on record.
Old man,
this is not what I mean.
Well,
what is it then?
What are you doing?
Back then, when you hurt your brother
and ruined his hands,
did you treat him as your brother?
Jie,
is what you said true?
Weren't our father's hands ruined
by himself?
Yeah, his hands were hurt by himself.
By himself?
18 years ago,
on January 13,
was it a ghost that I saw when I hid
in the wardrobe that night?
Yuanshan,
don't blame me for being too ruthless.
It's because you like showing off
- that our father wants you back home.
- You jerk!
So...
I don't know that.
- You jerk!
- I have no idea.
Let go!
Yuanfeng,
is what Jiang Jie said true?
- Dad.
- Don't call me dad.
Tell me. Where did you go that night?
Is it really you who cut Yuanshan's hands?
Dad.
That's because he had two faces
and always acted against me.
He said he wouldn't compete with me
for being the Chef.
But he still opened a restaurant
by himself.
And he also put it on the map.
He was your brother.
How could you...
Dad.
Isn't this what you taught me?
Since you've picked me,
you shouldn't have paid attention to him
when he opened a restaurant.
You also said you'd regretted
your decision.
You...
You unfilial son!
I did regret my choice.
I shouldn't have
indulged you.
- Grandpa.
- Master Jiang! Master Jiang!
Grandpa. Grandpa.
- Are you alright?
- Call an ambulance.
This has nothing to do with me.
Call an ambulance!
(Chang'an Traditional Chinese
Medicine Hospital)
They still didn't give up the idea
of the chain restaurants.
Zheng Fangxing is making pre-made dishes.
But I don't know what he is up to.
We must have been used.
- What?
- Jiang Xuyang must know Cui Can is a spy.
He deliberately used us
to get rid of Jiang Ziqing.
Then in the name of Xijiangyue,
the No. 1 restaurant of the year,
he proposed his plan.
I was too careless.
And your father's name
wasn't fully cleared.
You've done enough.
Jiang Xuyang
must have been ready
when Jiang Ziqing made that choice.
What should we do now?
Let's go. Master, we'll go back first.
Okay.
Xiu.
- Go away!
- I won't!
I don't want us to be apart.
You don't want us to be apart?
Based on what?
Cui Can, do you think you're awesome?
You pretended to break up with me
and worked undercover,
trying to prove my father innocent.
What? Should I be grateful to you now?
- I don't.
- You do.
I hate it most when someone is arrogant
to think it's for my own good.
Xiu.
Cui Can,
we're done for good.
(Xijiangyue proposes)
(from now on,)
(the three-star restaurants nationwide)
(will start trial operation
of the chain restaurants,)
(and increase dish-serving efficiency)
(in the form of pre-made dishes.)
The seven families' signature dishes
become pre-made dishes.
How dare they!
What can we do?
It's the proposal by the No. 1 of the year.
The Alliance can't veto it.
Besides, most members of the Alliance
agreed on the proposal.
Because the chain restaurants
with pre-made dishes
can save costs and create more profits.
This pattern does save the costs.
And it can save the chefs too.
They only care about interests.
There's a way to stop them.
What is it?
That is, Eating at Dusk obtains the No. 1
of next year and proposes a new plan.
Don't worry.
Let's work together.
Well, we don't have a choice.
But I'm still unconvinced.
Unconvinced?
Then we can only go on a date.
Can't you give your boyfriend
a chance to cheer you up?
How sweet of you!
Of course I am!
But I need to go home and get changed.
Sure. I'll pick you up later.
Xiu.
Did you sleep well last night?
Look at this.
Does it look like me?
Now it looks like you.
Don't come to me anymore.
Xiu!
Cui Can.
Aren't you coming home?
Being a spy for a woman's sake?
Now you've failed, you're mad at me.
I did all this to protect the people
I care about.
Aren't I protecting you
and the Cui family?
- Your protection is to cheat and scheme.
- You!
Do you think the so-called justice
can bring you any benefit?
What you're doing is a total joke.
So what?
I won't regret my choice
even if I fail 100 times.
Because justice isn't absurd in my eyes.
Do you have a minute, Chef Li?
I wanna talk with you.
I'm sorry. I have things to do.
It's about the knife-seizing contest
between you and Jiang Jie.
Hello, Li Nai.
(Hello, Jiang Jie.)
Where are you?
(Something has come up.
I'm afraid we have to put off our date.)
What happened?
(Well, it's...)
(Something happened to Li Jidong.
It's nothing serious.)
Okay. Call me if anything.
Okay.
I haven't congratulated you yet.
You've passed the Alliance's
five-star review.
Mr. Jiang, don't beat around the bush.
Just cut to the chase.
Then I'll get this straight.
About your competition against Jiang Jie,
someone did manipulate the votes.
Why did you tell me this?
I thought you and Cui Jing were allies.
I just don't think you should
be kept in the dark.
Jiang Jie is a really thoughtful man.
You must know that well.
Don't tell me you think
he has no clue about it.
Since he knows that,
why did he still join Eating at Dusk?
Are you saying
Jiang Jie is harboring evil designs?
He's Ge Qunshan's disciple.
He can challenge you anytime.
You're the one harboring evil designs!
Do you think
you've reached your goal at the party?
Supposedly,
Jiang Jie and I are no longer
a threat to you,
at least within one year.
- This is the truth.
- No.
Not really.
Even I was almost cheated by Jiang Jie.
Apart from waiting for one year,
I have another way to stop you.
To seize the Jiang family's knife.
If the Jiang family isn't the head
of the seven families,
your proposal would be invalid then.
Thank you for the advice.
Chef... Chef Li.
♪When the past turns into an old story♪
♪The satisfaction from victory♪
Li Nai.
Turn around and raise your head.
♪Who would care anymore♪
♪When I stake myself as the bet♪
♪The journey will no longer be smooth♪
♪Each cut is a path of loneliness
with no return♪
♪Win or loss, there is no return♪
I'm so pissed off. How can he try
to sow discord between us?
Thank you.
I've decided to seize the knife.
No problem.
Won't you stop me?
If you wanna do it, let's do it together.
Okay, let's seize the knife.
♪Hold the knife in hand♪
But what about Jiang Xiu?
♪I become your pride♪
Grandpa,
I remember
when I was little, it was you
who taught me to hold the knife.
I was too young at that time.
Somehow,
my parents and brother
were all gone.
So, for a while,
I was dependent on you.
Now, whenever I recall that period,
I feel
very disgusted.
Jiang Yuanfeng has been arrested
for assault.
Jiang Xuyang doesn't come to see you
not because he's busy
helping his father out.
He's just released a new term
at the Alliance Meeting.
Now, I assume
he's busy opening chain restaurants.
When you abandoned my father,
you should have expected this to come.
But Grandpa,
this is not over yet.
♪So many nights, so much trouble♪
♪So many answers,
outside the door of insomnia♪
♪Try to avoid the rain,
try to turn the head♪
♪But we are getting used to♪
♪The warmth between crossed fingers♪
♪So many expectations, so much waiting♪
♪So much bravery, but silence is remained♪
♪Worry about the ending,
worry about the should or shouldn't♪
♪The former damage turns into dependence♪
♪Following the light, I came♪
♪Towards the love that makes me cry♪
♪Two lonely specks of dust♪
♪Bloom on the deserted heart♪
♪Unspoken confession♪
♪Unrequited love in the corner♪
♪My mind is haunted♪
♪I thought I could deny my love for you♪
♪Hold the future in hand,
and the past and present♪
♪Never letting go, because of you♪
♪Irreplaceable♪
♪Following the light, I came♪
♪Towards the love that dries my tears♪
♪Two lonely specks of dust♪
♪Bloom on the deserted heart♪
♪Unspoken confession♪
♪Unrequited love in the corner♪
♪I cannot leave♪
♪I cannot deny my love for you♪