♪When the past turns into an old story♪
♪The satisfaction from victory♪
♪Insignificant happiness in every meal♪
♪Who would care anymore♪
♪When diligence turns into talent♪
♪Free from the past♪
♪Every bite is the salvation of tastes♪
♪Understand everything♪
♪Take back the lost pride♪
♪I know how difficult each step is♪
♪Silence is burning,
it ends up as the trap of ashes♪
♪Take back the lost glory♪
♪I know how difficult each battle is♪
♪Hold the knife in hand
to be worthy of the brilliance♪
♪Take back the lost laughter♪
♪I know how difficult the next goal is♪
♪Face challenge,
exert all the strength to defeat mockery♪
=Sweet Trap=
=Episode 20=
Jiang Jie.
Where's she?
- Who?
- Li Nai.
- Li Nai?
- Is she alright?
Li Nai has been away with your sister
for ten minutes.
Got it.
Do you know where they have gone?
The Jiang family.
The Jiang family?
Why on earth do you demand
to meet my grandpa?
Because someone gave me a test.
It's time to check the result.
I can't fail.
Oh, it's my brother.
I just can't get it.
You two keep tormenting each other.
Got to say you're really meant
for each other.
I really wanna be your sister-in-law.
Shame on you!
So what? As my dad said,
to find a spouse, one must be cheeky.
Fine.
My grandpa is in there.
Your grandpa and I
used to have a bond.
I've never met my grandpa.
But everyone knows about you in Baichuan.
The members of the Alliance
all respect you a lot.
Xiu told me
you had something important
to discuss with me.
I do have a favor to ask of you.
Tell me about it.
You know, Eating at Dusk
will have the five-star review.
My family's succession has been severed
for two generations.
I really don't know how to handle
the review.
The star review
is the rule
set by my grandpa.
It's mainly to encourage the young people
in the Alliance.
As long as they work well,
it won't be hard
to pass the review.
I've tried my best.
But rumor has it
that someone doesn't want me
to pass the review.
As you said, it's a rumor.
But the rumor isn't necessarily fake.
I wonder where Mr. Yuanfeng is.
I was honored to meet him once
the other day,
and he also asked me to wait for him.
I thought I could see him today.
He has gone to the capital city
on behalf of Xijiangyue
to attend the anniversary party
of the Chinese Food Association.
What are the odds?
Tell me about it.
If you wanna find out
who smashed your restaurant,
I can help you.
But it seems that these people
have done this a lot.
Maybe it's just that the tall tree
catches much wind.
It may not be a scheme against you.
I've just sent someone
to smash the restaurant.
Big deal.
The old man is such a nuisance.
The older he gets,
the more cowardly he becomes.
How dare Li Nai force me!
I'll let her know what she'll get
for offending me.
Mr. Yuanfeng, what will one get
for offending you?
You're here for Li Nai?
18 years ago, the price of offending you
was a pair of hands.
18 years later, you seem to become wussier.
What do you want?
You're right. Even if I have evidence,
I can't catch him anyway
if someone is behind his back.
You're twisting my words.
We've got to pursue justice.
You're young.
You shouldn't be so negative.
Forget it.
If I really can't pass the review
this time,
I'll follow Jiang Xuyang's example.
It seems that he intends to make all
restaurants in Baichuan into chain restaurants.
Even if I don't have the title
of a five-star restaurant,
I can swagger about in another province.
Mr. Jiang, it's late now.
I won't disturb you then.
Wait.
What do you mean by saying
the chain restaurant?
Don't you know that?
Jiang Xuyang and Cui Jing
have been purchasing the restaurants
below three stars under the Alliance.
I know that.
That's for the Alliance's development.
But I heard
they purchased these restaurants
not only for the unification
of the Alliance.
His idea is to test the waters
outside Baichuan with these restaurants
and then open chain restaurants
in the form of pre-made food.
I haven't been in business for decades.
The Li family
is also a member of the Alliance.
The seven families are supposed to be
an integral whole.
I can do you
a favor.
(Eating at Dusk)
Good luck with the new business.
Jingjing, our restaurant
is successfully upgraded today.
How about not charging the first customer?
No problem.
A free meal to the first customer, huh?
What about the first employee?
(Eating at Dusk;
Certified by Chefs' Alliance in Baichuan)
What's going on?
I passed the test.
Look at your smug face.
Can you be prudent?
After all,
you're the boss of a five-star restaurant.
Don't be jealous.
Although he's seized your knife,
I've seized his knife too.
It's all the same.
I'll treat you the same way.
Jiang Jie, come here.
What's wrong?
Your button isn't well done.
Let me handle it for you.
Li Nai,
you deliberately drew Jiang Yuanfeng
to the coffee shop, right?
The Jiang family has the most complicated
relationship I've ever seen.
What they have is just this big.
The old generation doesn't let go.
The middle generation
is incapable and troublesome.
The young generation is ambitious
but their ambition is too big.
I think if you're really looking for
a breakthrough point,
you should turn to Jiang Yuanfeng.
That's a real loser.
What did you tell him to irritate him?
I told him about your dad.
Sorry for leaking your private matter.
Do you know
he'd probably come to hurt you
if Jiang Ziqing didn't send him away.
As you said, I was bound to lose.
Of course I had to take some risks.
The fact proved that I won the bet.
You talked about the plan
about me before. What's that?
Jingjing. Zhao Jingjing!
- What's wrong?
- What a good day today!
We passed the five-star review
and Jiang Jie also joined us.
Let's have a celebratory dinner tonight.
You're the most obedient
and reassuring kid in this family.
Answer me.
What's the base of the seven
cooking families in Baichuan?
The seven chefs with unique skills.
Then why are you trying
to open chain restaurants?
Do you think I'm old?
Do you think I'm deaf?
Do you think I'm blind?
Opening chain restaurants
can make more profits.
I get it.
But opening the chain restaurants
lies in the brand,
not the cooking skills.
If you open chain restaurants,
you may gain popularity.
But the seven families in Baichuan
will be rotten radically.
I'm sorry, Grandpa.
It's the succession of 200 years
and seven families.
How can you lay your fingers on it?
Get lost.
- Are you alright?
- I'm fine.
Xuyang.
Tell me. What's wrong?
Jiang Jie
has officially joined Eating at Dusk.
I've underestimated Jiang Jie.
I didn't expect that
he'd be willing to bend.
I've belittled Li Nai.
I thought she was the woman
who climbed up
because of Jiang Jie's soft heart.
I didn't expect her to meet my grandpa.
What should we do next?
How did Li Nai know
about the chain restaurants?
Cui Can hasn't joined the plan
of the chain restaurant yet.
It's a huge thing.
It means that
we're not doing it well enough.
It doesn't matter who leaks this now.
Most importantly,
my grandpa has known about this.
He'll intervene with
the Alliance's affairs.
Do we have to continue waiting?
You've waited for years
and finally got such an opportunity.
No more waiting.
I can't wait anymore.
I was laughing at Cui Jing and Cui Can
about being too attached.
Now as it appears,
I've been not heartless enough.
Since we've got obstacles,
I'll get rid of them myself.
Mr. Zheng,
you're working at Xijiangyue.
Chef, there you are.
Let me introduce him to you.
This is our new Sous Chef.
We had only one Sous Chef before,
but somehow, Mr. Jiang
assigned him here.
Jiang Xuyang?
Are you following Jiang Xuyang?
Does my brother know about this?
I'm following his example.
He has gone to work for Eating at Dusk.
Why can't I work for Xijiangyue?
What benefits does he give you?
If it's the Head Chef
of the chain restaurants,
you'd better give it up.
Because my grandpa has canceled his plan
of the chain restaurants.
Or are you
aiming at the position of the Head Chef
at Xijiangyue?
He can give me what I want anyway.
Fine. I hope you won't regret it.
(Sir, I need five copies of my resume.)
Wait a minute.
Mr. Zheng, you haven't got a job?
I'm not as capable as you.
Got a new job right after resigning.
Among the five-star restaurants,
Firewood Rice and Cao's Fish both
rejected you.
Among the four-star restaurants, Yanyu and
Wooden Fish Collection dare not hire you.
Can it be
you'll be reduced to joining
a three-star restaurant?
Do you forget
Chuncheng also started with one star?
But that's because of Jiang Jie.
Couldn't I do anything without Jiang Jie?
What a waste of food!
Can't you even follow
the basic principle of the chef?
As long as you want to,
you can be the Sous Chef at Xijiangyue.
And Mr. Jiang promises
you'll be the Head Chef in one year.
This is what your deceased father
yearned for most
but couldn't get his whole life.
Wish a brisk business for Eating at Dusk!
Let's start eating.
(Jie, Zheng Fangxing agreed
with Jiang Xuyang to join Xijiangyue.)
(But I don't know what they're up to.)
(Okay, got it)
Miss Li, is it too stingy of you
to treat us to this for celebration?
Look at Sous Chef Jiang.
He doesn't eat anything.
Should you have a drink as punishment?
Sure.
That's not necessary.
I have no problems with this.
It's just that something came to my mind.
Come on. Let's eat.
Are the dishes not to
Sous Chef Jiang's taste?
Li Nai. There is a snack street at the back.
How about taking him there?
Sure. I'll buy you
whatever you want to eat.
Don't bother. These are okay.
- Let's go.
- Don't bother.
- Li Nai.
- Go. Go.
Have you eaten this before?
You want this?
It's already enough.
We may go back now.
The last one.
Ma'am, I'd like a sugar painting.
In the shape of a sunflower.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
Look! Isn't the night market lively?
But when the day breaks,
all this will be gone.
Likewise,
the glory brought by knife seizing
looks dazzling
but is actually vulnerable.
Jiang Jie,
I've lied to you.
The first day you were back in Baichuan,
I told you if you wanted to seize knife,
Eating at Dusk would be your best choice.
I know.
You've never thought of seizing knife.
Your father's tragedy
and my master's
are both due to knife seizing.
So, Jiang Jie,
I hope we can
bring Eating at Dusk
to the No. 1 of the year
and then abolish knife seizing
at the Alliance Meeting.
Li Nai,
the abolition of knife seizing
is far from enough. Look.
Among the people we met
on the way here,
some of them are working part time,
just like what you did before.
Some of them can't afford to open a diner.
But more of them
are forced to come here because they can't
pass the Alliance's review.
Have you thought about who's responsible
for the review?
They're merely some laymen
who are attached to the seven families
and can't cook at all.
Why do the seven families have five stars
at the beginning?
And we common people have to work hard
our whole life starting from one star.
Some of us can't even pass the review
and have to run a food stall,
just like those peddlers.
Li Nai,
I've got the knife of the Ge family.
Well, you...
Come here.
Li Nai,
let me ask you again.
Will you work with me
to change the current situation
of the Chefs' Alliance in Baichuan?
Yes!
Are we on the same side now?
Let's go. They're still waiting for us.
Hurry. Let's go.
(Harmony at home brings prosperity)
Li Jidong, it's time to eat.
I wanna have a fried egg.
This is a fried egg.
The fried egg is supposed to be round.
It can be heart-shaped too.
The fried egg is round.
Li Jidong,
don't get on my bad side.
Hello.
What?
Something came up in the restaurant?
(Eating at Dusk)
Why isn't that young man here?
Right, why is he not here?
- Where is he?
- Yeah.
I've been waiting here for a while.
Will he not come today?
I've finally put on makeup today.
Are you robbed?
- I'd rather be robbed.
- What's going on?
I don't know. I was free this morning,
so I came to work early.
Those people just ran after me
upon seeing me.
Why the face?
Turns out you're not attractive to boys,
but to girls.
Come off it.
I don't wanna admit this,
but they were calling Jiang Jie indeed.
Jiang Jie.
Here comes Jiang Jie.
Jiang Jie is coming! Jiang Jie!
Open the door.
- Come again if you like our food.
- Okay, no problem.
Hello, do you like the food?
There are so many customers.
You've just joined us since yesterday.
Your fans have reported your whereabouts
to the Alliance.
It may not be done by my fans.
I have a lot of enemies.
Sous Chef Jiang.
- A customer demands your service.
- Take this.
What kind of enemy will demand his service?
(Eating at Dusk)
What's written on your sleeve?
Sous Chef Jiang, chef service.
Here it goes.
Smell this. I feel it has gone bad.
Sous Chef Jiang.
- Chef service.
- Actually, my daughter also cooks well.
Is it okay...
Here.
Hold on.
Jiang, service.
What chef service? I've got this.
If you have any questions,
you may ask me.
We have no questions.
If you don't need anything,
I'll excuse myself. Please enjoy.
Thank you.
Mr. Meng.
Chef Li.
Well, is there any specialty today?
Today, we've got the Pith-Removed
Orange Bowl.
Would you like to try it?
Then I'll have an Orange Bowl.
- And the Sweet and Sour Spare Ribs.
- The Sweet and Sour Spare Ribs.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- I can cook the roasted goose too.
- It's my favorite lately.
- Roasted goose, right? I like it too.
Why is he here again?
- Who is he?
- The guy over there.
He's come here to eat for over one month.
Looks like he's really fond
of Li Nai's cooking.
Oh yeah?
I don't think he only likes her cooking.
(Eating at Dusk)
Won't you continue your chef service?
I'm afraid if I keep taking over
the Chef's job,
I may be fired for putting my left foot
across the door first tomorrow morning.
Your worry is unnecessary.
Given your influence,
which boss can bear to fire you?
Same here.
- What?
- Chef Li, you've progressed in cooking.
Your customer has come to the restaurant
for one and a half months in a row.
I've never met one in Chuncheng.
You mean Meng Shitong?
A regular customer indeed.
You're even aware of his name.
Don't tell me you know
what he likes to eat too.
Of course I do.
- Chef Li, someone wants to meet you.
- Coming.
Today I must thank you
for dining with me.
That's too flattering.
Mr. Jiang, it's my honor
to eat with you.
Cui Jing, you've managed the Cui family
well these years.
The Cui family isn't
one of the seven families,
but it still has a history of 200 years.
It's sorta connected
with the seven families.
To be honest with you,
Jiang Xiu is the Head Chef at Xijiangyue.
Our family's root
is in Xijiangyue.
Cui Can.
Mr. Jiang.
What do you think of my granddaughter?
Mr. Jiang, frankly speaking,
Jiang Xiu and I
were in a relationship before.
Oh yeah?
- That's great.
- But we've broken up.
We won't get back together.
Grandpa, Mr. Cui and I were goofing around.
Afterward, I found he was tedious
and brainless.
So, I quit. I got tired of him.
- Jiang Xiu.
- I didn't say anything wrong.
You wanna ally with them.
Maybe they wanna have a meteoric rise
with the help of the Jiang family.
Miss Jiang,
even if my family can ride on the wind
of the Jiang family,
why would I have to butter you up myself?
You're not in charge
of the Jiang family.
Cui Can.
Grandpa, I'm not feeling well.
- Where are you going, Xiu?
- I'm out of here.
You'd better remember what you've said.
Where's Jiang Jie?
I noticed he had gone out.
The mob is broken.
So, he has gone to buy one.
When he left, a pretty fan was waiting
for him at the door.
I'm done with this.
I have things to do. Got to go.
It's normal that Jiang Jie has many fans.
Don't be upset.
Get in the right mood.
I'm not upset. Who's upset?
Jiang...
Chef Li.
Mr. Meng.
Did you leave anything behind?
Oh, yeah, I've left something behind.
I was waiting for you.
Waiting for me?
I know
Eating at Dusk doesn't open
until 5:30 pm.
So, do you have time at noon tomorrow?
Will you watch a movie with me?
I...
She won't be available.
Jiang Jie.
Where is your fan?
She's got plans tomorrow.
She won't have time.
- The day after tomorrow then.
- Still no.
- Then two days after tomorrow.
- Not even then.
We have a lot to do at Eating at Dusk.
Mr. Meng,
let's talk outside.
(Eating at Dusk;
Closed)
Li Nai.
I'm talking to you.
What did he say to you?
No. What did you say to him?
I told him two days,
or three days after tomorrow...
You can't go to the cinema
with him anytime.
Why?
Because...
- Because...
- Jiang Jie.
Why can't I go to the cinema with him?
Because I have a crush on you.
I have a crush on you.
And we're on the same side now.
You can't leave me.
I'll stand by your side forever.
Well...
How do you feel about me?
I have feelings for you too.
Li Nai.
Where is she?
Li Nai!
What's wrong?
On second thought,
it's better that you go with me.
I'll go too.
You'd better not.
My dad doesn't want to see you.
Your dad?
Li Nai. Li...
Well, see you tomorrow.
Boyfriend.
See you tomorrow.
♪Not ready♪
Boyfriend.
Girlfriend.
♪Don't waste♪
♪The aftertaste of the sunset♪
♪Looking at the moonlight,
I still can't sleep♪
♪Pursue forward♪
♪Snuggle back to back♪
♪Turn around and you'll be mine♪
♪To face up♪
Well, see you tomorrow.
♪Quietly, listen to it say who you love♪
Boyfriend.
♪One look and my heart misses a beat♪
♪Love can make one impulsive♪
♪I guess I'm a little flipped♪
♪One look and I'm going to blush♪
♪Love can make a person throb♪
(Boyfriend.)
♪Love can make a person thaw♪
(See you tomorrow.)
Boyfriend.
♪Love can make a person passive♪
(See you tomorrow.)
Boyfriend.
♪Pursue forward♪
♪Snuggle back to back♪
♪Turn around and you'll be mine♪
♪To face up♪
(Jiang Jie.)
(Why can't I go to the cinema with him?)
Because I have a crush on you.
I have feelings for you too.
♪One look and my heart misses a beat♪
Li Nai.
♪I guess I'm a little flipped♪
Jingjing came at a bad time indeed.
♪I've been dreaming of you all night♪
♪Love can make a person thaw♪
♪I guess I'm a little flipped♪
♪Unconsciously partial and indulgent♪
♪Love can make a person passive♪
What brought you here?
I'm here for your father.
Uncle Li.
The Papercutting Club has an activity.
Ms. Wang has taken him there.
I'll get some water for you.
♪So many nights, so much trouble♪
♪So many answers,
outside the door of insomnia♪
♪Try to avoid the rain,
try to turn the head♪
♪But we are getting used to♪
♪The warmth between crossed fingers♪
♪So many expectations, so much waiting♪
♪So much bravery, but silence is remained♪
♪Worry about the ending,
worry about the should or shouldn't♪
♪The former damage turns into dependence♪
♪Following the light, I came♪
♪Towards the love that makes me cry♪
♪Two lonely specks of dust♪
♪Bloom on the deserted heart♪
♪Unspoken confession♪
♪Unrequited love in the corner♪
♪My mind is haunted♪
♪I thought I could deny my love for you♪
♪Hold the future in hand,
and the past and present♪
♪Never letting go, because of you♪
♪Irreplaceable♪
♪Following the light, I came♪
♪Towards the love that dries my tears♪
♪Two lonely specks of dust♪
♪Bloom on the deserted heart♪
♪Unspoken confession♪
♪Unrequited love in the corner♪
♪I cannot leave♪
♪I cannot deny my love for you♪