♪When the past turns into an old story♪
♪The satisfaction from victory♪
♪Insignificant happiness in every meal♪
♪Who would care anymore♪
♪When diligence turns into talent♪
♪Free from the past♪
♪Every bite is the salvation of tastes♪
♪Understand everything♪
♪Take back the lost pride♪
♪I know how difficult each step is♪
♪Silence is burning,
it ends up as the trap of ashes♪
♪Take back the lost glory♪
♪I know how difficult each battle is♪
♪Hold the knife in hand
to be worthy of the brilliance♪
♪Take back the lost laughter♪
♪I know how difficult the next goal is♪
♪Face challenge,
exert all the strength to defeat mockery♪
=Sweet Trap=
=Episode 12=
Jiang Jie,
happy new year.
Happy new year.
Li Nai.
Stop playing with your phone
and go to bed.
Good night.
Xiu.
Why are you sitting there?
You're awake?
It's late.
Let's go home.
No.
I don't wanna go home.
That place
isn't my home.
Okay.
We won't go back.
But can you get down first?
Here.
You...
Do you like me?
What are you doing?
Let's pack everything up,
and we can leave.
Didn't you say we ran out of gas?
I found the oil container in the trunk
where the spare tire is stored.
I missed it yesterday.
Come on, let's pack up.
This is for you.
What kinda flower is this?
I dunno.
It looked pretty,
so I picked them yesterday.
Just take it.
Why are you giving me flowers
out of the blue?
Isn't Uncle Li
learning Chinese art recently?
Let him practice with these.
After Jiang Jie took Li Nai
away last night,
he didn't go home.
They didn't show up
at Chuncheng today either.
Li Nai?
Xue Congming's disciple?
This is interesting.
Then, keep an eye on them.
Sorry to trouble you.
Okay.
(Eating at Dusk)
Hello.
Miss,
do you serve Western food?
We don't.
Well, thank you.
Most Western restaurants
should be closed by now.
Yes, I asked quite a few restaurants.
I saw that you're still open,
so I came over to ask.
Today is my daughter's birthday.
She never had Western food.
This is my fault.
I was so busy,
I didn't keep track of the time.
We don't serve Western food
but we serve a new type of
Western-style Chinese food.
Would you like to try?
Is it expensive?
You are our first customer.
It's free.
She made these look so lovely.
Here you go.
Enjoy your meal.
I'll go get your dessert.
Sure, okay.
Here.
Mom, have this too.
It's delicious.
This is better than the Western food
my classmate mentioned.
Later, you must thank her.
She is a skilled cook.
Here are your desserts.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I hope you enjoyed them.
Miss, your cooking
is the best I've ever had.
Enjoy your meal.
Sure.
Thank you very much.
No problem.
Come.
Say goodbye to her.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye. Take care.
- Goodbye.
- Bye-bye.
Mom, wait for me.
Miss.
What is it, Zhouzhou?
Do you have any flyers?
My mom can help
promote your restaurant tomorrow
when she's open for business.
Sure. Thank you, Zhouzhou.
Happy birthday.
You're welcome.
I made a wish just now.
I wanna become an amazing chef like you
when I grow up.
Let's go.
Why did you come
to the restaurant this late?
Aren't you here too?
It's normal to be at my own restaurant.
That's not important.
Jiang Jie,
I'm really, really, really,
really happy right now.
What made you so happy?
Because
you're worth every penny.
That's very flattering.
A new batch of ingredients arrived.
Wanna try them?
Yeah.
Let's eat.
Okay.
We'll eat at the coffee table.
Don't just stand there.
Help me serve these.
Chef, please sit inside.
I usually like to sit in this spot.
Can't you
be gentler?
Be glad I didn't step on you.
Here.
Try it.
What do you think?
Delicious.
Go on, then.
You have some, too.
Were you laughing at me?
No.
You were laughing.
You saw wrong.
As thanks for this crab,
I'll pretend you didn't.
Thanks for the treat, Chef.
You're welcome.
I'll go get you water.
The wine is in the room's wine cabinet.
I never learn my lesson.
It's only been a month and a half
since you seized my master's knife.
Li Nai,
I...
I'm sorry.
I should have known you were like this.
Don't you wanna know
why I challenged your master?
Come with me.
Why did you bring me here?
Noodle Shop of Xue's Apprentice.
I remember the Chefs' Alliance forced it
to close down within a day.
What do you want to say?
Back then,
my dad loved cooking.
Despite being told that he had no talent
and that his cooking was mediocre,
he loved cooking so much
that he wanted to open his own restaurant.
After he was expelled from the house,
he opened up a restaurant of his own.
What happened next?
It closed down, of course.
Others believed that he was expelled
from the Jiang family
for being unfilial,
so he was judged to be unqualified
for the one-star review.
And the person who made that judgment
was my dad's best friend,
Zhong Haiyang.
- But that's the rules.
- Rules?
Who made them?
Are they the high-and-mighty seven families
who boast a century of heritage?
My master has never
had the authority of the seven families.
But he had at least enjoyed the benefits.
Selfless,
kind,
and loyal.
These are the things people say
about your master.
But that year, after my dad...
After my dad passed away,
Jiang Xiu and I were about to be sent
to the welfare center.
I knelt right there.
I begged him to adopt Jiang Xiu
but he refused me.
(He feared offending the seven families)
(and the Jiang family.)
Impossible.
In any case,
you shouldn't use others' efforts
to challenge the authority
of the seven families.
Is it their effort
if they can't defend it themselves?
Li Nai,
do you think
there is a fairer way to challenge them
than seizing their knives?
Someday,
I will also challenge you.
Okay.
I'll be waiting.
Li Nai.
Do we have customers?
Make a call for me.
My phone has shut down.
If you aren't receiving any calls,
it means she doesn't intend
to call you at all.
No.
She must be busy.
Yes.
Do you think I'm not busy?
We don't have customers, anyway.
Welcome.
- Are you here to dine in?
- Yes.
- Table for two?
Come on in.
We have customers.
Over here.
Please have a seat.
Is Jiang Jie up to something?
Your restaurant is really hard to find.
I thought Zhouzhou's mom
was joking with my mom.
Did she recommend our place to you?
Yes. We're regulars at her store.
She highly recommended your restaurant.
We got curious,
so we came to check you out.
- Don't worry, we won't disappoint you.
- Okay.
Welcome.
Is this "Eating at Dusk"?
- Yes, yes.
- I'll serve them.
This way, please.
- Hurry up, Li Nai.
- Okay.
(We're sold out for the day.
Closed early)
Where is Li Nai?
She is on leave.
- From whom did she request it?
- From you.
She said she sent you a text message.
I never check my texts.
Besides, I haven't approved it.
Who uses texts nowadays?
(Chef, I need the day off today)
She wasn't hoping you'd approve it anyway.
I'll refill the soy sauce.
(Make way, make way.)
(This patient here needs
to go to the ER. Make way.)
(Make way.)
Are you at the hospital?
Yeah, I accompanied Li Jidong
to the hospital.
Are you looking for me?
Chef?
Is Uncle Li okay?
He's fine. He came here for a checkup.
Number 26, Li Jidong.
(Are you here?)
(Here, here.)
(Chef,)
it's our turn now. I'm hanging up.
Have you hung up?
I have.
Li Nai,
I didn't expect you
to open up a restaurant
behind Jiang Jie's back.
Just between us,
this sort of secret operation
is quite exciting.
If you're doing something like this again,
you'd better count me in.
Don't bring that up.
When you were talking to him,
- I thought you spilled the beans.
- Spill what beans?
How many times
have I watched Spy x Family?
Okay, back to business.
What should I do?
You came to me
because your income and expenses
aren't reaching a break even level, right?
That's very normal.
It's because you're completely
influenced by Jiang Jie.
Other things aside,
Jiang Jie is nitpicky
about the quality of his ingredients.
You are subconsciously influenced by him.
So, when you pick your ingredients,
you followed the standards for Chuncheng.
But mine is just
a newly opened small diner.
What I can do now is
to reduce the cost of ingredients
or raise the price of the food.
Stop. Increasing the price of the food
is gonna backfire on a small diner.
Did you come to me
to supply you with cheaper ingredients?
I wish I could help you.
Zhong's shop may be small,
the ingredients he supplies
are not cheap.
Have you spoken to your master?
Xue's Noodles has been opened for years,
it should have its own suppliers.
I'm still far from challenging anyone.
So, I don't wanna trouble my master.
Forget it.
I'd better contact other suppliers.
Wait.
It's not often I get to see
Jiang Jie being defeated.
I will definitely regret it
if I don't get involved.
Actually, there is another way
to ensure the quality of your ingredients
and cut your cost by more than half.
What is it?
You only need to look for one person.
Who is it?
(Some restaurants are
similar to the old Zhaoyeqing.)
(They purchase
the highest quality ingredients)
but there is actually an optimal
freshness period to use them
before its expiration date.
(High-end restaurants
will get rid of ingredients)
(that have reached
their peak freshness)
(but have not yet expired or spoiled.)
Hello.
Are you Chef Li?
Nice to meet you.
- I'm Li Nai.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm Jiang Xuyang from Xijiangyue.
Xijiangyue?
So, you and Jiang...
Jiang Xiu are...
Xiu?
Xiu is my younger sister.
Do you know Xiu, Chef Li?
No, no. I've only heard of her.
- Please come inside.
- Sure. After you.
Please enjoy your meal.
Chef Li,
come sit with me.
Sure.
I heard you would like
to purchase batches of ingredients
that are past their peak freshness
from us.
- Yes.
- At Xijiangyue,
we value environmental protection
and the quality of ingredients.
That's why we place
great importance on ingredients
that are close to their expiration date.
Truth is, when I heard from Chef Zhao
that you want to purchase our ingredients,
I was really surprised.
Don't misunderstand. I only hope
that everyone
who purchases our ingredients
can properly bring out their potential.
After all, every ingredient
shouldn't go to waste.
Am I right?
Don't worry.
Although my cooking skills
are not outstanding
and this diner is not famous,
I promise you
that I will value each ingredient.
Okay.
I trust you.
I got the answers I wanted
from your dishes.
However...
Is there a problem?
I believe partnership
is a process
where both parties test each other.
I wonder if I may invite you
to Xijiangyue
to inspect
our ingredients on site.
May I?
Of course.
It's your right to do so.
Thank you.
Are you cold, Chef Li?
Should I turn up the air-conditioning?
No, it's fine.
I saw someone I know.
Do you mind if I get down and say hello?
Sure, no problem.
I'm quite free today.
He is very different from Jiang Jie.
(Lake Hill Yuntai Garden)
What a coincidence.
(Fire Exit;
Do Not Block The Way)
Li Nai.
What are you doing?
Wait for me.
Are you okay?
Why were you hiding there?
I remember
there is a good spice over there,
so I came to have a look.
Spice?
This isn't really good.
My leg hurts so much.
Quick, help me inside.
Walk slower.
- Does it hurt a lot?
- Very.
Let's find a place to sit down.
(Let's talk about a partnership next time.)
Bear with it, okay?
♪So many nights♪
♪So much trouble♪
♪So many answers♪
♪Outside the door of insomnia♪
♪Try to avoid the rain♪
♪Try to turn the head♪
♪But we are getting used to♪
Feeling better?
Much better.
Do you see yourself as the Divine Farmer?
Don't you know you'll end up poisoned
if you eat random things?
Don't do that again.
♪But silence is remained♪
Hold this.
♪Worry about the should or shouldn't♪
♪The former damage turns into dependence♪
♪Following the light, I came♪
♪Unrequited love in the corner♪
♪I cannot take my eyes away♪
♪I thought I could deny♪
♪Our love♪
He didn't leave last night?
He was just passing by?
Or...
He's not inside.
Chef, what are you doing here?
To pick you up.
I'm fine. Look.
Besides, I fell down myself.
Don't feel bad about it, Chef.
It's fine, okay?
Get in.
Are you two dating?
Lunch time is over
but he is still here.
Isn't he waiting for you?
We're not dating.
It's the unusual reaction of a cunning fox
being crushed by a rock
called moral standards
after it hurt a young girl.
This dish needs to be simmered
for an hour.
Are you going to stand here for an hour?
This is the last dish.
Just keeping an eye on it
won't make it delicious.
I'll do it.
Why are you still standing here?
Go and sit down.
What do you think of the Chef?
He is infuriatingly outstanding,
has lots of experience,
and is accurate as a robot when matching
ingredients and their cooking time.
What about
as a man who might like you?
Did you sprain it again?
No, no.
Don't tell me horror stories.
What is it?
Li Nai?
We're here.
I'll send you upstairs.
No need.
I'll be going now.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, no need.
You're here, Chef Li.
What happened to you?
Are you hurt?
I'm sorry about yesterday, Mr. Jiang.
You don't have to force yourself.
It's okay to come by
after you've recovered.
I'm really okay.
I'm very healthy.
So, shall we take a look
at the ingredients?
Okay.
- Come with me.
- Okay.
Mr. Jiang is here.
- Jiang Xuyang?
- Yes, Chef.
It seems he brought a business partner
to check the ingredients.
Chef set is ready.
I'll leave the other dishes to you.
Okay.
No wonder Xijiangyue is this.
The quality
of your ingredients is excellent.
Even if they're close to expiring,
their quality is much better
than other restaurants.
It's worthy of a five-star restaurant.
Mr. Jiang,
are you really willing
to resell these ingredients
to my unknown diner?
I told you before
that I found the answer I wanted
in your dishes, Chef Li.
I think you shouldn't be so modest.
I think Eating at Dusk
is comparable to the seven families.
Perhaps, it just needs
a little bit more time.
I hope you're right.
I only speak the truth.
Eating at Dusk?
Is that what you and Cui Can
have been plotting every day?
Xiu, why are you here?
What's wrong?
Don't you know that you will bump into me
if you come to buy ingredients
from Xijiangyue?
I'm here because I'm willing
to take the risks.
How tough.
Say,
how would my brother feel
if he finds out that his assistant
secretly opened up a diner outside?
I can't hide it from him forever.
But you don't look all that relaxed.
Don't worry.
I won't tell my brother about this
because I look forward to the day
he finds out himself.
That way, Jiang Jie will understand
that the only person
he can trust in this world
is only me.
I'm sorry, Chef Li.
She has always been like this.
Please forgive her.
Did something happen
between you and Jiang Jie?
My relationship with Jiang Jie
is a bit complicated.
So, can you
keep it a secret
that I opened Eating at Dusk?
This is your private matter.
By right, I shouldn't have asked
but Jiang Jie is my younger brother.
I hope you won't hurt him.
I just want to get something back.
♪So many nights, so much trouble♪
♪So many answers,
outside the door of insomnia♪
♪Try to avoid the rain,
try to turn the head♪
♪But we are getting used to♪
♪The warmth between crossed fingers♪
♪So many expectations, so much waiting♪
♪So much bravery, but silence is remained♪
♪Worry about the ending,
worry about the should or shouldn't♪
♪The former damage turns into dependence♪
♪Following the light, I came♪
♪Towards the love that makes me cry♪
♪Two lonely specks of dust♪
♪Bloom on the deserted heart♪
♪Unspoken confession♪
♪Unrequited love in the corner♪
♪My mind is haunted♪
♪I thought I could deny my love for you♪
♪Hold the future in hand,
and the past and present♪
♪Never letting go, because of you♪
♪Irreplaceable♪
♪Following the light, I came♪
♪Towards the love that makes me cry♪
♪Two lonely specks of dust♪
♪Bloom on the deserted heart♪
♪Unspoken confession♪
♪Unrequited love in the corner♪
♪I cannot leave♪
♪I cannot deny my love for you♪