I was just as scared as you were.
I was scared of losing you.
Tell me!
Who threw that woman into the sea?
Pong.
Mr. Phum, I...
I have to find out who that woman is
and why she hates my father so much
that she's trying to kill him.
Mr. Phum.
You don't seem very happy to see me.
That's because I'm already used to
this kind of behavior from you.
I know
why you've been hanging around here.
Do you want Sarai's land that badly?
Are you keeping it as a memorial
to your love or something?
After she betrayed you like that,
you're still hung up on her.
You're such a fool.
I've been a fool
ever since I made you my wife.
Mr. Phum.
I'm sorry.
Let go of me.
- I'm sorry.
- I said let go.
No. I'm sorry.
Mr. Phum! Mr. Phum!
After she betrayed you like that,
you're still hung up on her.
You're such a fool.
Sarai. Sarai.
The moment you got home,
you came straight to Sarai's room?
You even brought her a gift.
Too bad
she'll never get a chance to use it.
Where's Sarai?
I asked where Sarai is.
She's gone.
You drove her away, didn't you?
She ran away with another man.
I don't believe you.
Sarai. You're disgusting.
You shameless woman.
Bill, please.
You can just send me off here.
There's something I want to ask of you.
What is it?
I don't want you
getting involved in this anymore.
- But--
- Well.
I'm worried about you.
That woman ghost might hurt you.
I'll handle this myself.
I can't promise you that.
Why not?
Because I'm worried about you too.
We'll investigate this together.
Okay?
Okay.
Agreed.
But we haven't sealed the deal
with a handshake yet.
Is that really necessary?
Of course.
Otherwise, how can it count as a promise?
Thank you for worrying about me.
Well, I should go inside now.
Okay.
Where have you been?
I've been waiting forever.
What's wrong? Why is your face so red?
Are you sick?
No.
What's going on?
Oh, that sacred thread.
You found it?
I asked the Venerable Sir for another one.
Now I'm not afraid
of that woman ghost anymore.
Mook, call Mr. Phum again.
I'm ready to tell him everything.
What's wrong?
I met Mr. Narathon today.
So I told him everything.
I don't see a problem.
They're father and son.
But Mr. Narathon
wants to investigate this himself.
You mean we're not
telling Mr. Phum anymore?
What does Mr. Narathon suspect?
I don't know either.
Have some hot cocoa. It's good for stress.
Thanks.
You've got it bad.
Who's showing up this late?
Dad?
He reeks of alcohol.
Your dad really went all out.
He actually drank himself unconscious.
As long as I can remember,
I've never seen him this drunk.
I don't think
he's sobering up anytime soon.
Looks like we'll have to sleep
in the living room tonight.
No problem. I'll go get the bedding ready.
Sarai.
Sarai...
Why did you do this to me?
You shameless woman.
I'll kill you. I'll kill you, Sarai.
Why aren't you doing
what I ordered you to?
If you still don't make a move,
I'll hire someone else.
No one will take this job.
Why not?
Because the police have sealed off
all of Skull Island now.
Damn it!
This is bad!
How long do I have to wait
before I finally get the treasure?
Calm down.
Once everything quiets down,
the police will leave on their own.
I'll make my move right away.
Hurry up.
You're so slow.
It's you!
You still haven't learned your lesson?
You still haven't learned?
Fine. I'll give you one.
Pong, Pong!
What did you say?
Do you remember everything now, Sompong?
I remember.
You... You're Pong!
What else?
You...
You threw the woman into the sea!
She fell into the sea! She fell!
And then what?
And then...
she floated up and down.
She floated away.
Floating up...
- Bastard. You scared me.
- ...and down...
I thought you remembered
that we killed that...
Pong really threw a woman into the sea?
Yes.
Pong.
You must want to know it so much
that you follow me all the way here.
Pong, wait. I didn't mean to.
I've been suspicious about
what that madman kept saying.
I didn't mean to.
I swear I won't tell anyone.
I promise.
You know you're like my idol.
I really look up to you.
That much?
Yes.
You know I'm a coward, but you see this?
I endured the pain of getting this
because I wanted to be like you.
I really look up to you.
I promise I won't tell anyone.
Please don't hurt me.
I swear
with all my pride. I won't tell anyone.
I really won't.
I'm sorry, Piak.
Why, bro?
You...
You killed again.
And I have to kill you too...
before you remember more.
No.
Where are you going?!
Damn it!
I'm sorry
for using your body.
But I have to find out
who it was
who ordered the murder of me
and my child.
May you be blessed with long life,
grace, happiness, and strength.
Sathu.
Where is Cherd today?
I usually see him offering alms
with you every day.
Cherd went to help
put out a fire last night.
He got back almost at dawn,
so he couldn't wake up.
Where was the fire?
At that crazy Sompong's hut.
He must have gone mad
and set the hut on fire.
He got burned to death in it.
What terrible karma.
I have to go now, Venerable Sir.
Did I really get that drunk?
Thon...
Mr. Phum, you're awake.
Yes.
I knew you and Thon
would probably wear the same size.
You prepared the clothes for me?
Yes.
Where's Thon?
Well, he went to the police station.
The police called him in.
They wanted additional questioning
about what happened on Skull Island.
Ms. Kaimook, are you sure
you were...
really taken by a ghost?
Officer,
are you saying that my daughter is lying?
Please don't misunderstand me.
The reason I asked Ms. Kaimook
to come in for another statement
is because the police
searched the entire island,
but we found nothing unusual.
Officer,
if a ghost doesn't want you
to see it, of course you won't.
Mr. Narathon is here, sir.
- Send him in.
- Yes, sir.
Can we leave now?
Yes.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
If anything else comes up,
I may have to trouble you again.
Of course. We're happy
to cooperate fully with the police.
Thank you very much.
Goodbye.
Hello.
If you hadn't gone to intern at SAVE SEA,
you wouldn't have had all this trouble.
Let's go.
We'll be going now.
Well, there's something
I want to talk to you about,
but calling probably isn't convenient.
You can message me.
POLICE MAJOR NATTAPONG BOONPHU
INSPECTOR
What are you doing, Mook?
I'm looking for information
about the missing pirate ship.
You're still interested
in that crazy ghost on the island?
I want to know who he really was,
and why he died on that island.
That's interesting.
Why haven't any of
the relevant authorities looked into it,
even though everyone suspects
it might be connected
to the missing ancient gold?
I think I know now
why the story went quiet.
Why?
Because there's no evidence at all.
I've been searching for hours.
There's nothing.
It's like everything was erased.
Who erased it?
RESTRICTED AREA.
STRICTLY NO ENTRY TO THE ISLAND.
MR. NARATHON
I WANT TO SEE YOU.
WHEN?
NOW.
IT'S ALREADY LATE.
IT'S URGENT.
I'LL WAIT AT THE BEACH
IN FRONT OF YOUR HOUSE.
OKAY.
Kaimook.
Venerable Sir?
Go back inside now.
Go inside.
Yes.
Hey.
What kind of ship is that?
Is that the ghost ship
everyone talks about?
Oh?
- No.
- I'm scared.
Why are you interfering in my affairs?
Go back to where you belong.
Don't create more karma.
Not your real body?
A man like you has cultivated
the Dhamma to this level?
The past cannot be changed.
But if one sincerely
turns toward good thoughts
and good deeds, it is never too late.
Your merit in this life is exhausted.
You should let go of your desires
and go to the realm where you belong.
Why stubbornly remain
half-ghost, half-human,
forcing your body to keep suffering?
Don't preach to me.
Just mind your business.
Mook, wake up.
Mook.
What is it?
Na and I are going back. We're going
to stop by somewhere else on the way.
Go ahead.
Okay. See you in Bangkok.
MR. NARATHON
I must have waited until I fell asleep,
then dreamed
that Mr. Narathon messaged me.
Dear,
you keep bending up and down like that.
Don't complain later when your back hurts.
It's just a little exercise.
Mook, you're awake?
Yes, Mom.
Did you sleep late last night?
What were you doing?
I saw you go into your room early.
We're heading back to Bangkok
later this morning.
Go have breakfast first.
I prepared it for you.
- Okay.
- I'll go pack your things for you.
Okay.
I'M WAITING FOR YOU AT THE BEACH.
Who's messaging you this early?
Oh, just a sales account.
They send messages all day.
I should probably mute the notifications.
Wait.
Isn't this your scarf?
Yes. Why?
You dropped it in front of the house.
I went for a walk this morning
and picked it up for you.
Thank you.
Mr. Narathon.
I saw your message,
that you wanted to see me and Da.
But Da went back to Bangkok with Na.
They were stopping somewhere on the way.
I see.
Is something wrong?
I wanted to ask Ms. Da
for more details about that woman ghost.
But it's all right.
We can arrange to meet again in Bangkok.
You're going back to Bangkok today too?
Yes. What about you?
I'm going back today too.
Then I should go.
Wait.
Excuse me.
You know how to tie scarves?
Yes.
Someone taught me.
A woman, I bet.
Yes.
Then, I'm leaving now.
Hey, wait.
Why are you suddenly
using that tone with me?
What tone?
Before you misunderstand anything,
the woman who taught me
was a 60-year-old foreign lady.
She was the family I stayed with
when I studied abroad.
When I lived abroad,
it was different. it was very cold.
It was necessary
to use scarves. So I learned it from her.
You didn't have to explain that much.
I don't want you to misunderstand me.
I was just kidding.
What's wrong?
I thought
you were jealous of me.
Well, I'm sorry.
You should go back inside.
If you ever do anything suspicious,
I'll definitely deal with you.
I'm going now.
I'm feeling better now.
I finished all my breakfast this morning.
That's good.
Can I leave the hospital now?
If the doctor approves,
there shouldn't be any problem.
You'll take me with you, won't you?
I won't trouble you for long. I promise.
I can do housework. I can cook,
do laundry, wash dishes.
I can do everything.
You don't believe me?
Well, when I first saw you,
I thought you were a rich person.
But the qualities
you just described sound like...
Like who?
- Like...
- So you've been holed up with this woman.
Sairung?
This is...
You shameless woman!
Stop.
What are you doing, Sairung?
Let go of me. I'm going to kill her.
This shameless woman
dares to steal my husband!
If you want to go crazy,
go do it somewhere else.
Before I lose control
and hurt you worse than this.
You dared to slap me?
I'm sorry for what she did.
Are you alright?
I should apologize to you instead.
I made her misunderstand you.
Now I understand why you can't help me.
I won't trouble you anymore.
Don't say that.
I'll take you with me.
Really?
I'll go settle the hospital bill first.
Are you full now?
It'll be several hours
before we reach Bangkok.
I'm not very hungry.
By the way, what should I call you?
Could you give me a name?
Name you?
I found you by the sea.
It should be something related to
the sea and coral.
Pakarang?
How about Pakarang?
Sure, that sounds good. I love it.
Then from now on, I'll call you Pakarang.
Okay.
I'm done eating.
Bill, please.
What happened? I'll go check.
Mr. Phum.
Wait in the car.
Sir.
What's going on?
Hey, take her!
Come here!
‎Come.
Let go of me!
Where did Sarai disappear to?
Mr. Thon, do you know this woman?
A life must be paid for with a life.
Sarai, don't.
Sarai.
Who is Sarai?
Could you tell me about Sarai?
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon