- Let go of me.
- I won't. I love you.
Let Ms. Pat go right now.
Mr. Phum.
Or maybe Mook disappeared because of...
What's happening?
Ghosts are crawling out of the graves!
Mr. Narathon!
Mr. Narathon, can you hear me?
I'm in here.
You can't run away from me, Kaimook.
You have to stay with me.
Kaimook, you're going to
stay with me forever.
Kliang, you don't need to go with us.
Let Na drive instead.
We don't know how many days we'll be gone.
You stay here
and help Kaew take care of the house.
Alright?
Yes, sir.
- Hello.
Is Kaimook home?
Do you need something
from Kaimook, Mr. Phum?
I came to invite Kaimook
and all of you to my gallery opening.
Most of the works displayed there
are photographs taken by Kaimook.
I hope all of you
will honor me by attending.
Yes.
An art exhibition and charity auction?
In the end, it all goes straight
into your own pocket anyway.
You misunderstand me.
I understand you perfectly well.
Even when your own son could be
dead or alive, you don't even care.
Sorry,
we don't have time for your nonsense.
Let's go.
Excuse us.
Come on.
Sorry, sir. I have to go too.
Wait. What's going on?
What happened to Narathon?
Everyone who went to the research center
on Skull Island has disappeared.
Right now, no one can contact them at all.
Where is everyone?
It's almost afternoon already.
Oh, where's Ms. Kaimook?
Didn't you find her?
We still haven't found her.
We searched all the way
to the back of the island,
but there's still no sign of her.
And didn't the female ghost
lead you to Ms. Kaimook?
She did.
But we found nine graves instead
and we encountered other ghosts too.
Luckily we made it back.
We barely survived.
So the nine graves
really do exist on this island?
You know about those graves?
I overheard the previous research team
talking about them once.
Why were they talking about it?
It sounded like
someone found an old journal
at the old research center.
They were reading it together.
I only heard bits and pieces
while serving coffee,
but I never thought it was true.
That means if we can find that journal,
there may be clues
that can help us find Kaimook.
Right.
Then let's go search for it.
Where is it, Auntie?
This way, please.
These are all just general records.
These are all summaries of underwater
coral reef restoration research.
There are only books
about coral reef restoration.
A journal?
You found it?
Yes.
It looks like an ordinary diary.
But this note
from the second day is interesting.
Read it.
"Tonight, we heard strange sounds,
like the sound of a ship."
"But when we went outside to check,
there was nothing there."
"Could it be the island's curse,
just as the rumors say
about the ghost ship
that often appears before sailors
and travelers near Skull Island?"
"They say the ship
once belonged to pirates."
Hurry up!
I surrender. I'm scared.
I surrender. Please don't hurt me.
Please don't kill me. I don't want to die.
Please. I surrender.
Please don't.
Hey!
Hey?!
"But then,
the pirate ship suddenly vanished
without a trace."
"Also, a government ship transporting
ancient gold treasures was robbed."
"It is believed that, driven by greed,
the pirates betrayed one another
and killed each other on Skull Island."
My goodness.
Does that mean the nine graves we saw
and those ghosts were the pirates?
My goodness.
So there really are ghosts on this island?
And Ms. Kaimook disappeared
because the ghosts took her away?
I think
we should leave this island
- as quickly as possible.
- Yes.
- Please.
We should notify
the rescue team or the police
and let them help
search for Ms. Kaimook instead.
I tried calling several times
since this morning,
but the phone didn't work
There's no phone signal either.
It's like we're stranded on this island.
We're screwed.
Don't worry.
The boat that dropped the staff off
should return around three this afternoon.
So, you can go pack your things.
- Thank you.
- Auntie, let's go.
- Let's go pack.
- Let's go.
Hey.
You're not planning
to leave this island, are you?
No.
Take everyone back first.
Report everything to the police
and get them here.
As for me,
I'll keep searching for Kaimook.
Hey.
Then I'm staying with you.
I'll help you find Kaimook.
Ms. Da,
you should go prepare too.
If you two are going to stay,
you need me too.
Mook and I
have been friends for a long time.
Sure, we fight sometimes,
but I can't abandon the friend
who once saved my life.
Well.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't want to leave you behind.
Honestly, if it were anything else,
I'd fight to the death.
But ghosts...
Don't worry about it, Auntie.
After everything that happened,
I don't want everyone
risking their lives here either.
As soon as we reach the mainland,
we'll notify the police and rescue teams
to come help.
Thank you.
Also, there's still instant food
in the kitchen.
Canned food too. I stocked up quite a lot.
Don't worry, Auntie.
We'll take care of ourselves.
- Then I'll get going now.
- Okay.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Safe travels.
Let's prepare to save Kaimook.
I need to go grab my things
from my room first.
Thon and I will go prepare too.
Let's go.
Buddy, are we really
going to use guns to fight ghosts?
Still better than going empty-handed.
If I'd known this,
I would've brought holy amulets
from every monk possible.
Let's just call it a life experience.
At least we'll have something
to tell our grandkids someday.
Sathu. Please, let us make it out alive.
Thanks, my friend.
For not abandoning me.
How could I abandon you
when you refuse to abandon my student?
You seem even more worried
about her lately than I am.
I'm worried about everyone.
Hurry and finish packing.
Trying to dodge the subject?
You think I can't tell, Narathon?
Go pack your things.
Fine. I'll go prepare food supplies.
Didn't you say
you weren't scared of ghosts?
Anyone would be scared
in a place like this.
Good thing I ran into you.
If I'd walked here alone,
I would've run too.
What are you laughing at?
At you.
You just don't seem like the type
who'd be scared of ghosts.
Are you complimenting me or insulting me?
I'm complimenting you.
If I said someone like you
doesn't need to fear ghosts,
that would definitely sound offensive.
How?
Back in school,
my friend used to tease girls
who were afraid of ghosts
by saying,
"With a face like yours,
even ghosts would run away."
You don't seem like
someone who'd tell jokes either.
Are you complimenting me
or insulting me now?
I'm complimenting you.
So you're not scared anymore?
I'm not afraid of anything anymore.
Let's go then.
Okay.
This is my fault.
I'm sorry, Kaimook.
If you'd been afraid,
you probably wouldn't have left your room
no matter what you heard.
I'm sorry.
But I promise,
I'll bring you back no matter what.
Did you get a boat?
They agree to go to other islands.
But no one will go to Skull island, Dad.
Even when I offered
two or three times the money.
- My goodness.
- That's crazy.
What are we going to do?
No.
He's a madman.
He must be hungry.
A woman... fell into the sea.
Here.
Take it. Don't be afraid.
Use it to buy food.
Woman!
A woman fell into the sea.
- She disappeared.
- No.
I'm not trying to hurt you.
This is for you.
Use it to buy food.
Food, okay?
Okay?
Our family has always done good.
Why did something terrible
have to happen to Kaimook?
We can't even find a boat to go save her.
Dad, look over there.
Should we try asking them for help?
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Don't go! Don't go!
You'll die.
Don't go!
Excuse me. We urgently need a boat.
May we rent yours?
Whatever you want for your time,
we're willing to pay.
This boat belongs to my boss.
He asked me
to bring it here for his friend.
He's here now.
- Mr. Phum.
- Hello, Mr. Phum.
You still haven't gone to Skull Island?
We couldn't find a boat.
No one would take us there.
If you don't mind,
you're welcome to come with me.
Sir, my boss asked me to tell you
he'll coordinate with the police
and have them follow you
to Skull Island as soon as possible.
But if you despise me that much,
you can wait and go with the officers.
I'm going with you.
Please.
- Dear.
- Dad.
Dear, what's wrong?
I'm fine.
- Dad.
- Dear.
Call an ambulance now.
- Yes.
- Dad.
Dear.
AMBULANCE SERVICE
Prepare to lift.
I'll take care of Dad.
Na, you have to bring your sister back.
Yes, Mom.
Thank you very much, Mr. Phum.
My pleasure.
I'm going now.
Don't worry.
My friend owns this hospital.
I've already coordinated with him.
Your father will receive
the best care possible.
Thank you very much.
Let's go do our part.
Wait, Mr. Phum.
I know a shortcut
to Skull Island.
Would you let me drive the boat?
With a sea captain
standing right in front of me,
I'd be a fool to say no. Let's go.
- Yes.
- Go prepare the boat.
Hey. Men.
You...
You dare abuse your dark magic
and desecrate
the treasures of the kingdom.
You shall be punished accordingly.
Who are you?!
Who dares challenge me?!
Son.
I'll never give up!
I will become what I once was again
no matter how many people I have to kill!
Kaimook,
you're going to stay with me forever.
Where could it have gone?
When I arrived on the island,
it was still here.
Under the bed?
Did I drop it?
It's not here.
Dad.
Sarai.
Sarai, my girl.
I saw that female ghost again.
Where is she now?
She's waiting over there.
Hurry and follow her.
Since when has there been a ship here?
Exactly.
I'm sure it wasn't here during the day.
Or is this the pirate ship?
That female ghost is on the ship.
Or maybe Kaimook
is being held on that ship?
Hey, there's a rowboat over there.
We should split up and search.
You go with Ms. Da.
I agree.
Ms. Da, Ms. Da.
She must be stressed, so she fainted.
Then,
you stay here and look after her.
I'll search for Kaimook myself.
Be careful.
Ms. Da.
No.
I can't give up hope.
There has to be a way.
I have to get out.
Kaimook.
Ms. Da,
how are you feeling?
What happened to me?
You were probably under too much stress
from following that female ghost,
so you fainted.
Female ghost?
When did I follow her?
Why don't I remember anything?
Where are we?
This isn't my room at the research center.
Ms. Da, we're on a ship.
You were the one who led Thon and me here.
I saw a ghost in my room.
The same ghost that took Kaimook.
It lunged at me
and after that, I don't remember anything.
Are you saying
you were possessed by a ghost?
Yes.
We fell into its trap.
Now we're screwed.
Kaimook,
where are you?
What's happening?
We're screwed.
That ghost tricked us onto this ship.
What do you mean?
It possessed Ms. Da.
She didn't even know she came here.
It's trying to kill us for sure.
What are we going to do?
We have to stop the ship first.
Come. Follow me.
Is that Skull Island ahead?
Yes.
I think we shouldn't approach
from the front side.
Why not?
We don't know what's happening
on the island right now.
If we go in from the front,
we might become targets.
You're very cautious.
Then I'll steer around
to the side of the island instead.
Do you know how to drive a ship?
- No.
- What do we do now?
This is bad!
An island!
The ship's gonna crash into the island!
There's no time.
We have to stop the ship
before it crashes into the island.
It's so stiff. It won't budge at all.
Hurry up! What are you guys doing?!
I'm using all my strength.
You'll all die!
There's no way you can help Kaimook.
Mr. Narathon, Mr. Phum.
Don't go there, Kaimook.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon