Where did Sarai disappear to?
You know this woman?
A life must be repaid with a life.
No, Sarai. Don't.
Sarai...
Who is Sarai?
Would you mind telling me about her?
All my life, I knew my father
had never been a good man.
But I never thought
he could do something like this.
I'll go talk to him.
Wait.
What are you doing?
I didn't want you to go.
Why?
If your father really
had something to do with Sarai's death,
you could be in danger.
You're worried about me?
Yes.
No need to rush.
I promise.
You promise not to act rashly, right?
I promise I won't tell anyone
you're very heavy.
Thank you
for bringing me back to my senses.
Promise me
you won't act rashly like that again.
We'll investigate this together,
as carefully as possible.
I promise.
We'll help each other
seek justice for Sarai calmly
and sensibly.
So it's you.
Nice place.
No wonder Mr. Phum hides you here.
Sister.
So you're cornered enough
to call me sister now?
Even if you called me mother,
I still wouldn't spare you today.
You shameless woman!
Ow!
You dare slap me?
Yes.
I've put up with you for long enough.
I'm going to tell Mr. Phum.
Go ahead.
Then we'll see who Mr. Phum listens to,
you or me.
You're more vicious than I thought.
Leave
before I change my mind and kill you.
You still don't what I'm capable of.
I already told you.
We can't go to Skull Island right now.
I have another job for you.
Easy work, quick pay.
Interested?
What job?
Win!
Pat, why are you so startled?
And why are you here?
Win, look at that.
There's nothing there.
Pat, you still haven't answered me.
Why did you come here?
I came to look at this photo.
Hey, Pat.
Honestly,
I don't see what's beautiful
about this Black Coral photo.
It looks terrifying.
But it's worth an enormous fortune.
What?
The black jewel of the sea.
People say it really exists.
At first, I didn't believe it.
But once I saw this photo,
I decided I had to find it.
Are you going to help me?
And what will I get in return?
You already know what you'll get.
Sairung.
Why won't you turn around?
- I'm in a hurry.
- I said turn around.
Turn around right now.
What happened to your face?
It looks like
you got into a fight with someone.
If I tell you, please don't scold me.
What did you do?
Last night, I went to a party.
I drank too much,
so I got into a fight with a friend.
I think you have far too much free time.
Try doing something useful for once.
You're wasting time on nonsense.
I'm going to do something meaningful,
just like you want.
The details
and half the money are in here.
Finish the job,
and you can come collect the rest.
What's this?
What the hell?
What is it?
It's nothing.
What the hell is wrong with my brain?
What are you doing in here?
I asked what you're doing in this room.
Why can't I be here?
I ordered that no one come in.
Then why did you come in?
Get out.
Why?
Are you afraid I'll find something?
What are you talking about?
Stop pretending, Dad.
I know that...
What do you know?
I know
you're still the same man
you've always been.
What are you talking about?
Because of your womanizing.
Because you found someone new
and forgot the old one.
That's why Sarai was heartbroken
and ran away. Isn't that right?
Of course.
In your eyes,
I will always be a terrible father.
But know one thing.
This terrible father
loves you more than anything,
whether you believe it or not.
You did the right thing
by not saying anything.
I understand how you feel.
I want to see you too,
but no one is home right now.
Na has gone out to sea,
and Dad and Mom went to a party.
They'll probably be home late.
How about this? Come see me at my house.
I'll make something delicious for you.
Okay. See you soon.
You really made this yourself?
I don't want to brag. Try it first.
Alright.
How was it?
Are you sure this is really spaghetti?
Why?
Try it.
It's good.
Who said it wasn't?
You're really something.
So what did you put in this?
It's really delicious.
My heart.
You have to pay attention
from the step of boiling the pasta.
You tricked me into getting happy again.
Well, you tricked me first.
So now we're even.
Eat before it gets cold.
Can you eat shrimp?
Why?
Because you're a conservationist.
You should know
I can eat shrimp.
What are you smiling at?
I didn't expect you
to be such a homemaker.
You've misunderstood.
Na says I can only be
a house ghost.
I'm glad to see you're less stressed now.
I feel confused
every time I talk to my father.
Sometimes he acts like
he knows something about Sarai's death.
But other times,
he acts like he knows nothing at all.
This case seems very complicated.
You need to stay calm.
I'm trying.
Dad.
Hello.
We need to talk. Please come with me.
I'm sorry
for coming to see Kaimook
without asking for permission first.
But
I give you my word as a man.
I haven't done anything improper,
and I will never do anything to damage...
the woman I love.
Are you telling me
you love my daughter?
Yes.
I love Kaimook.
Good. Then this will be easier.
If you really love Kaimook,
you wouldn't want the woman you love
to be in danger, would you?
Of course not.
I don't want Kaimook
to intern at SAVE SEA anymore.
You saw what happened to my daughter.
She almost didn't make it out alive.
So if you love Kaimook,
you should help support her decision
to leave SAVE SEA.
Dad,
- but I have to--
- I know.
I've already contacted
another place for you.
I guarantee their organization
is just as large as SAVE SEA.
I'm counting on you.
Dad,
my internship at SAVE SEA
is very important to me.
I know you need a portfolio
to apply for your master's degree.
It's not just that.
I want to be part of an organization
that really helps conserve
and restore damaged natural resources.
And SAVE SEA is the only place
that aligns with what I want.
That place is full of trouble,
both human and ghostly.
I can't let you intern there again.
Dad, please.
Mook,
I've let you have your way in everything.
But this time, no.
I'm not doing this
for myself. I'm doing this for you.
- But Dad.
- Mook,
stay calm.
He's in strict-father mode right now.
Don't row a boat against the current yet.
I'll handle it.
Don't worry. Trust me.
Yes, Mom.
Dear.
Mook's getting more stubborn
the older she gets.
Someone must be stirring her up.
Don't blame other people.
Our daughter is stubborn just like you.
Oh? Why would you say that?
Isn't it true?
She got
that conservationist blood from you.
You're the one who instilled
these things in her since she was little.
Now she's following in your footsteps.
But all of a sudden,
you're trying to stop her.
Isn't that a little dictatorial?
Hold on.
So now worrying about my daughter
makes me a dictator?
Worrying so much
that you refuse to listen
to your daughter's opinion,
if that isn't dictatorial,
what would you call it?
Mook will never understand
that kind of concern.
What should I do?
Meet her halfway.
"Right now, shallow coral reefs
in the Gulf of Thailand
have been damaged
and greatly reduced in number."
"This has caused
harmful effects to the ecosystem."
"Shallow coral reefs
are extremely important,
whether as habitats
for aquatic animals and marine fish,
or in helping reduce the force of waves
and preventing coastal erosion."
I don't see what's beautiful
about this Black Coral photo.
It looks terrifying.
But it's worth an enormous fortune.
What?
The black jewel of the sea.
People say it really exists.
At first, I didn't believe it.
But once I saw this photo,
I decided I had to find it.
Who's that?
Go.
Miss.
Miss. Excuse me.
What are you doing out here in the dark?
Miss.
I asked, what are you doing here?
There was a man
sneaking around behind you.
I think you should go home.
I can escort you.
No need. I live in the condo right here.
What? Such an easy job,
and you still managed to fail.
Don't contact me again. If anything
comes up, I'll contact you myself.
Useless.
Oh!
Mr. Phum?
Hey. Mr. Phum.
Mr. Phum.
Pong?
Who's he?
Mr. Phum.
I asked. Who is he?
Well...
No, Mr. Phum, don't.
The number that you've dialed
cannot be connected at this time.
Who is he?
Just a friend of mine.
Don't let me find out
that you're planning something vile.
I'm not like your beloved Sarai.
Ever since she cheated on you,
you see everyone in the worst light.
How many times have I told you
not to say that name again?
Fine.
Then I'll talk about that Pakarang woman
you're keeping at the condo.
Whatever I do has nothing to do with you.
Do not mess with Pakarang.
Otherwise, don't say I didn't warn you.
It's raining today.
Yes.
But it doesn't rain every day,
does it?
Yes. You're right.
There are still plenty
of good-weather days.
So,
no matter how heavy the rain is,
or how strong the storm gets,
we'll walk through it together.
Okay?
Okay.
Thank you very much.
It's no problem.
Dad.
Hello.
I'm heading back now.
You're very lucky to have a father
who loves and understands you.
That's really rare.
What do you mean?
Dad.
Thank you so much, Dad,
for understanding me.
I love you the most.
Hey.
But you must promise
to follow the conditions
I asked Mr. Don for.
Yes. I promise not to go off-site.
I'll intern only inside the company.
Good. Then that's settled.
We meet halfway.
But why did you suddenly change your mind?
Because I didn't want your mom
to call me a dictator.
Mom?
Yeah. Your mom worries about you
just as much as I do.
I know. I love you and Mom the most.
Do your best in your internship.
I'm leaving.
Yes, sir.
Welcome back to your internship.
Thank you.
So this is
what the sky looks like after the rain.
Is something wrong?
Are you thinking about Sarai?
Or did you find out something new?
I'm not like your beloved Sarai.
Ever since she cheated on you,
you see everyone in the worst light.
You once told me Sarai was innocent.
More importantly,
she loved Mr. Phum very much.
I don't think a woman like that
would have an affair.
I don't want to believe it either.
Could it have been a misunderstanding?
A man like my father
would never believe something easily
without evidence,
or without seeing it with his own eyes.
So you think Mr. Phum
might be involved in Sarai's death
because he was angry with her over this.
Sarai tried to communicate with me,
probably to ask me for help.
If my father wasn't involved,
she should have communicated
with him instead.
Don't you think so?
But before we have evidence,
I don't want you to jump to conclusions.
Because if it isn't what we think,
you'll be committing a sin.
Then I must have
been sinning for a long time.
Because I've never felt good
about my father,
ever since he caused my mother's death.
Why couldn't I have a father
who does good things,
like other people's fathers?
This is the sea around Skull Island.
You know Skull Island?
No.
Did I say that?
Try to think carefully.
Maybe you're from around there.
I...
I can't remember.
Uh...
If you can't remember yet,
don't force yourself.
You'll just get a headache.
Well,
I want to remember everything already.
Being idle like this
makes me feel so useless.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
How about this?
I'm organizing a photo exhibition.
You can help me,
so you'll have something to do.
But I don't know anything
about photography.
And I don't remember anything,
Who knows. Maybe you're one of the people
who knows the sea best.
Alright, then.
You're so much like her.
Why are you so much like...?
Who?
Who do you think I'm like?
It's nothing.
How dare you walk away from me?
It isn't time for him to know
who you are yet.
No! No!
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon