CHOKUDOMSAP 8
YEARS LATER
Are you sure you didn't forget anything?
Probably not.
But even if I did, what's the big deal?
I can just come back and get it.
I'm more worried you won't come back.
The place we're going isn't just
five or ten minutes away, you know.
It's about two hours from shore.
I know.
But what you still haven't told me is…
from this main island
to the diving spot,
how long does it take?
An hour.
Hey. Tell me.
Is there some rare fish
you wanna photograph there?
Something like that.
You going there to preserve fish
or looking for something else?
Is there something to look for?
Pong, the boat's ready.
The boat's ready.
What about you? You ready yet?
I'm ready.
The thing you need
to be most careful about
when you rise to the surface
is that the air you breathe from the tank
will expand.
If you hold your breath,
your lungs could rupture.
I know that.
Good.
But a ruptured lung
and losing your nerve
are two different things.
- Let's go.
- Nice, bro.
Look ahead. Don't turn around.
The moment you look back, you die!
What's wrong with him?
He's just a madman. Don't mind him.
Just leave him alone.
Don't go. Don't go!
Don't. Don't go!
What are you talking about?
Look ahead. Don't turn around.
The moment you look back, you die!
- Die!
- Hey, sir? What are you talking about?
‪Die…
It's in the water.
It's dark. It's scary.
Die! Die!
- Die!
- Sir.
Hey.
Go away if you don't wanna get hurt.
It's dark.
Dark my ass. Get lost!
Madman.
- It's so bright.
- Go away.
- We're working now.
- Hey.
I told you to leave him alone.
Let's go.
I really saw it.
It wasn't a rock,
but I'm not sure it was coral either.
Coral?
I don't know.
Where's the picture?
The water was so murky.
Maybe you imagined it.
Maybe.
I should've swum a little closer.
Good thing you didn't.
With currents that strong, you could've
been sucked in and never made it back out.
Are the currents normally like that?
Depends on the season and the weather.
But the weather was fine when we went out.
None of the underwater photos came out.
But the photos
I took on land and on the boat
are all there.
Maybe that's a good thing.
Better than capturing something scary.
Maybe the camera's busted.
Look ahead. Don't turn around.
If you turn back,
you die.
For underwater photography,
I never use zoom
because it increases the distance
between the camera and the subject.
That reduces both sharpness
and color quality.
So that means
you get really close to the subject?
Yes.
And when you think you're close enough,
you actually need to get even closer.
What about shutter speed?
It depends.
For stationary subjects
like starfish, coral,
or rocks,
it should be set at the lowest.
It shouldn't go
beyond one-30th of a second.
I have a question.
And what if you need to photograph
mysterious underwater entities?
Mysterious entities? Like what?
Well,
ghosts, demons, underwater spirits.
There's no need
to adjust the shutter at all.
Because no matter how you shoot,
you won't capture them.
But if they want to show up,
they'll show up on their own.
I have no further questions. Do any of
the other professors have any questions?
No for me.
Me neither.
Alright.
That was all of my presentation today.
Thank you.
Good job.
RESERVED BY MR. PHUM WITASSANAI
RESERVED BY MR. PHUM
Black coral.
The angel of the sea.
The angel of the sea?
Yes. What do you think?
It's amazing.
Black coral.
It's a type of coral called
"Antipatharia."
Right.
But this isn't one.
I don't understand.
It's actually a photo of a large coral
taken against the light shining down
from the surface.
That's why it looks like black coral.
It isn't actually Antipatharia.
Really?
How do you know?
Because I took the photo.
- Kaimook?
- Yes.
You're Kaimook?
Yes, that's me.
Oh.
You like this photo, don't you?
No, I don't.
Oh?
Is it not beautiful?
No. It's not beautiful. It's terrible.
Hey, my friend.
Yeah, hi.
You're so early.
Sorry, man.
I had to sign some documents,
so I came down late.
You already saw the exhibition, right?
How was it?
It was good. Beautiful.
Not bad.
What's wrong with you?
Just say if you like it or not?
I don't.
Give me a reason.
No reason.
And I don't understand.
What don't you understand?
I don't understand who that girl is.
And why did my father
reserve every single piece here?
Satisfied?
No. Just tell me straight.
Why did you come here?
If it's this model,
you need to ask her.
You know how to use it?
I'm not that good.
It's just that most of the photos
you saw downstairs
were taken with this camera.
No wonder.
No wonder what?
Does this model
have problems often?
No.
But I suppose it depends on the user.
If they know how to use it,
there shouldn't be any problems.
Well,
Kaimook,
can you please check
what's wrong with my friend's camera?
The camera can't speak, Professor.
We need to ask
the person who used it first.
What exactly happened to it?
Or…
maybe someone recklessly
pushed the wrong button.
Mr. Phum?
What?
It's not like I've never come in
while you were showering.
What are you doing?
Working.
You should take a break.
I said I'm working.
Let's do something else first.
I've prepared a hot tub for you.
Hot water will help you relax.
You must be exhausted.
Thon.
You're not even going to greet me?
I'm glad you finally came home for once
instead of staying
at your beach house all the time.
I'm only staying here because of work.
If it weren't necessary,
I wouldn't even set foot in this place.
I know you're still
angry with me about your mom.
But your mom died because of
heart disease, not because of me.
I'm a man
without heart disease,
and seeing that scene just now
almost gave me a heart attack.
Imagine how Mom felt.
I…
Don't bring it up again.
I don't want to hear it.
Why did you buy that girl's photographs?
What are you talking about?
Oh, Kaimook?
What wrong with that?
Because someone like you
never does anything
without expecting something in return.
What photographs?
And who is this Kaimook girl?
Someone like me can do good things too.
I bought them
because I wanted to make merit.
Kaimook is going to use the money
for a marine conservation project.
May the merit
help free you
from your endless lust someday.
So who exactly is Kaimook?
And how do you know her?
Hey…
Mom! Mom!
Mom.
Mom, what's wrong?
Nuan.
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Mom.
Hello?
It's Kaimook. I'm calling
to update you about the camera.
So what's wrong with it?
I don't know.
From what I checked,
nothing seems wrong with it.
If nothing's wrong, then why…?
I don't know. I've never encountered
a case like this before.
I didn't know what else to do,
so I sent it to the shop.
You can contact them tomorrow.
Which shop?
Which shop did you buy the camera from?
Okay, got it.
Anything else?
- Yes.
- What?
A thank you.
Do you know how to say it?
I do. Thanks.
Very good. Goodbye.
What a jerk.
Going diving?! The boat's about to leave.
DIVING
Hop on the boat.
The boat's about to leave
You wanna go diving?
The boat's about to leave.
What do you think?
- Let's go.
- You're going? This way.
Wait for me. Na.
- I'm coming, honey.
- Ugh.
Sorry for…
For making everyone wait.
- Everyone's here now, right?
- Yes.
I'll set sail then.
Looks good.
Alright. Turn left a little bit.
Nice. Just a bit.
One, two, three.
One, two, three. Good.
Let me see.
- Here. Isn't it nice?
- Let me see.
- Na, I can't see the sea.
- It's here. This looks good.
Hm. You could take
the same shot at the Mekong River.
- Take it again. Get the wide open sea.
- Alright.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Make sure you capture the sea.
Okay.
Hello, Professor.
Kaimook?
I didn't expect to see you here.
It's school break.
I gotta find something exciting to do.
So, about your friend's camera…
Well, he already got a replacement.
Hopefully, this one won't fail him again.
I'm honestly asking, Professor.
Does your friend
even know how to use a camera?
Of course, he does. Why?
I don't think the camera was broken.
I think your friend
just doesn't know how to shoot properly.
Really?
Well, please tell your friend
that if he's still not
very good at photography,
he should just use auto mode.
At least the pictures
won't come out ruined.
Alright. I'll tell him.
Alright then, I'll go change.
- Have fun diving.
- Okay.
Hey, someone once told me
this area is cursed.
A real story or just a legend?
What kind of curse?
They say
people who come here
rarely make it back.
People just like to spread rumors.
If you're scared,
you don't have to go down.
If something happens to you,
everyone else will be in trouble.
I'm not scared.
Just surprised.
I've
never heard that story before either.
Most importantly,
I've dived around here many times.
I'm not going to cause trouble for anyone.
We're here.
You can jump in from this point.
The boat will be around this area.
Okay.
Are we there yet?
I can't wait to see the coral reefs.
Mana, why are you so slow?
Don't stray away from your buddy.
There are whirlpools around here.
If you run into one,
back away immediately.
Yes.
Who took my child?!
Help me!
But this house is haunted.
Then why doesn't it haunt anyone else?
Why is it only haunting you?
Mr. Narathon…
When the time comes,
no matter how hard you try to stop it,
they're destined to meet anyway.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon