Grandfather, why are you leaving?
So, does that mean you agree?
I agree!
Did you hear that? Grandfather has agreed.
Can you please let me know about these things in advance next time?
I don't like surprises like this.
Are you upset?
I just wanted Grandfather to know that you're a good woman.
But our current relationship isn't presentable before family members.
I'll get the divorce done tomorrow.
Wait for me.
Dad.
Tomorrow, I'll be divorcing Fu Yancheng.
Maybe this is the best ending for us.
If only you were by my side right now.
Dad,
I miss you so much.
Time passes so fast.
In the blink of an eye, you've grown so much.
I really wish Dad could stay with you longer.
He just fell into a coma.
That old devil actually left all his property to that little wretch Sheng Mian.
We need to make plans earlier.
Don't worry. I'm here.
After Sheng Zhong dies,
we don't have to keep our affair a secret anymore.
I see.
No wonder Su Lan was able to easily transfer company funds.
So, they've been conspiring for a long time.
I bequeath all my shares in Sheng Group and all my assets
to my youngest daughter, Sheng Weiyuan.
The will must have issues as well.
Grandfather, I didn't mean to hide it from Yancheng.
Mian Mian, you're a good kid.
I know you must have your reasons for doing this.
I'll keep this secret for you.
When you're ready to tell him, you can tell him yourself.
Grandfather, I came today to ask for your help with something.
What is it?
It's about my family.
Previously, Fu Group gave Sheng Group two rounds of financing.
Logically, there shouldn't have been any issues with the cash flow.
But during my father's critical illness,
the company's accounts were completely emptied.
I suspect something is wrong.
Fu Group and Sheng Group have close financial ties,
so I wonder if it could be investigated through Fu Group's records.
Also...
I suspect my father's will has issues, too.
Do you have any suspects?
It's likely Su Lan, but this is just a guess.
To expose her, I need solid evidence.
So, I want to ask for your help.
Mian Mian, I can help with other things, but I'm old.
I struggle with reading through account books.
I really can't do much here.
I didn't think this through clearly, Grandfather.
However, I do know someone who can help you.
I'm not sure if you'd agree...
Of course, if you recommend them, I'd be more than willing!
All right, I'll talk to Yancheng about it and have him look into it for you.
Grandfather!
Look at you!
Didn't you just say you'd be completely willing to go with my recommendation?
Currently, the person most familiar with Fu and Sheng Groups
and has the most connections, is that guy.
If you refuse, don't blame me for not helping you.
But…
Mian Mian, don't divorce Yancheng for now.
Having the status of Mrs. Fu will make your investigation easier.
Once your father's matters are settled,
whether you divorce or not is up to you.
I promise not to interfere with your decision again.
Is that okay?
All right, Grandfather. I'll take my leave now.
Good move.
Grandfather, did Sheng Mian visit again?
She agreed to file the divorce today, but changed her mind again.
Yes. Sheng Mian was just here.
There she goes again.
But Mian Mian said that a forced relationship doesn't bear sweet fruit.
She'll definitely divorce you,
but before that, she needs your help.
Something has happened to her family.
Again?
Tell me, Grandfather.
What happened to her family this time?
Her stepmother likely colluded with outsiders to transfer funds.
You should investigate and find out what's going on.
Also, once you solve this matter,
I promise you can marry Penny.
Are you serious?
Of course, but you must first help Sheng Mian uncover the truth.
Fine, I'll start investigating immediately.
Hey, wait a minute.
Keep this matter low-key and handle it yourself.
Since you and Penny are in love, have her join you.
Okay, I understand.
I refuse to believe that after all this,
Sheng Mian will still agree to divorce him.
- When is our meeting with the client?
- At 3:00 p.m.
There's still an hour left. Plenty of time.
President Fu.
What a coincidence!
Such a small world.
Director Liang.
When did you switch careers to cleaning?
President Fu, such a coincidence.
I'm here to work on the renovations for this hotel.
Just surveying the area.
Did you really think splotching your face like that would make you unrecognizable?
Liang Hanqing.
Are you still going to continue hiding the truth?
What's really going on between you and Penny?
This is so tough for me.
I can't afford to offend either side.
No matter what, I'm doomed.
Fine, I'll tell you the truth, President Fu.
Penny and I... the two of us are a fake couple.
I meant no harm in lying to you, really!
Say that again.
I said we meant no harm in lying to you.
- The sentence before that.
- The sentence before that?
Penny and I are a fake couple.
I knew it.  Penny has better taste than that.
Exactly, exactly... What?
Here's a gift for you.
The password is Penny's birthday.
Rich people sure know how to insult others.
But I like it.
Don't tell Penny we met today.
If she finds out, I wouldn't mind making the studio disappear.
Don't worry, President Fu. I definitely won't.
That guy is so strange.
No wonder Penny doesn't like him.
Why has so much money been funneled to this company?
Why did Dad never mention it to me?
Are you hiding something from me?
Oh, no!
Grandpa must've slipped and told Fu Yancheng.
What do I do now?
"The Page You Appeared On" - Joynam
♫  Crossing the border of rain,
I came to the sunny day you walked through  ♫
♫  A moment of light brings to mind your gentle prophecy  ♫
♫  You will defeat everything and rush to my side  ♫
♫  Like a fairy tale world with a happy plot forever  ♫
♫  When the beautiful things disappear and disillusionment breaks down,
when the world can't fall asleep  ♫
♫  You will remember the accidental encounter,
but it's a pity that the two of us go our separate ways  ♫
♫  I wandered around and broke into the page where you appeared  ♫
♫  At the edge of the seaside forest, like the wind wandering past  ♫
♫  Half of the moonlight lit up the other half of the world  ♫
♫  Maybe on a day that you and I didn't get there  ♫
♫  I unknowingly walked past the page where you appeared  ♫
♫  Letting half of the fairy tale disappear before writing forever  ♫
♫  What I thought was eternal and unchanging was only half the story  ♫