Lawyer Wang,
how about working with us?
This way, we have a chance to get back at Su Lan.
Compared to Su Lan,
I hate the Sheng family even more.
Seems like he's mistaken Penny for Sheng Mian.
Lawyer Wang, you don't think holding a woman hostage is enough to threaten me, do you?
Didn't Su Lan tell you? I don't care about her at all.
I only brought this woman here to get back the money I've invested.
As for you, instead of implicating others,
you should think more about how to save yourself.
Penny, are you all right?
How are you feeling?
So, their relationship is still so stable.
In that case, Sheng Mian cannot keep that child.
Penny, your top priority now is to take care of yourself and the baby.
As for the rest, do you trust me to handle it?
But you were too impulsive today.
No wonder Lawyer Wang mistook you for Sheng Mian.
Fortunately, Lawyer Wang hasn't met Sheng Mian before.
Regardless, this had nothing to do with you.
I dragged you into this.
If something really happened to you, what was I supposed to do?
I admit I overreacted today.
Fortunately, Fu Yancheng doesnt suspect anything.
I just want you to divorce Sheng Mian as soon as possible.
I won't act that way again.
I've already sent someone to keep watch over Lawyer Wang at the hospital.
Fortunately, it was a scare that turned out okay.
You should go rest now.
I'll go rest then.
Send me a picture of Su Lan's brother.
I remember that the Sheng family once invited him to their banquet,
so he should have been there.
Take another look to see if there are any group photos.
Oh no!
I hope I'm not in those group photos.
Okay, I understand.
I want to have a bite, too.
♫  I shouldn't care  ♫
♫  After all, there are too many beautiful memories  ♫
♫  The world is upside down  ♫
♫  There is nothing worse than now  ♫
♫  Blame me. It's not your necessity  ♫
♫  I can't control our huge distance well  ♫
♫  My thoughts have left me nowhere to run  ♫
You can enjoy yourself tonight.
♫  I regard you as higher than the sky; no one can replace you  ♫
♫  Is it a little ridiculous?  ♫
♫  The hug I once coveted  ♫
♫  I never had it for a second  ♫
Fortunately, I'm not in those photos.
Otherwise, I'd have to get Grandfather to shut Qi Chen up.
What? The shoes have been reserved by someone else?
Didn't we agree that you'd contact me when they arrived?
I'm so sorry, Miss Xiao.
Those shoes were reserved by President Fu from our group a few days ago,
and they have already been engraved with the other party's name.
President Fu specifically instructed that they must be delivered before his friend attends an event tomorrow.
- I'm so sorry.
- Whose name is on them?
Let me check.
It's 'Penny'.
Miss Xiao, would you like to come to the store and take a look at other designs?
No!
That wretched Penny!
Always trying to compete with me for everything.
- Xiao Chuqing, what a coincidence!
- It's you?
Go back and tell your sister not to steal the things I like.
Whether it's a man or items, I will take them back one by one.
How can you call it "stealing" if you haven't obtained those things yet?
You haven't obtained them yet, which only proves your incompetence.
Don't get too cocky yet.
Your sister is using Penny's identity to trick Yancheng.
Let's see how things will come out in the end.
Remember this, Xiao Chuqing.
My sister is pregnant.
I just accompanied her for her prenatal checkup.
The doctor said it's very likely to be a boy.
With the eldest grandson of the Fu family,
no one can shake my sister's position in the Fu family anymore.
You'd better make peace with my sister soon.
Tomorrow's the Sheng family's annual gathering.
If you can come and apologize to my sister,
I can consider persuading her to forgive you.
Xiao Chuqing, you'd better seize this opportunity well.
So, Penny is going to attend the Sheng family's annual gathering tomorrow.
It's still uncertain whether the eldest grandson of the Fu family will be able to survive.
The will was indeed fake!
The matter of Su Lan illegally transferring the Sheng family's assets
and creating a fake will has finally been clarified.
President Sheng literally invited trouble into his own home.
Now that that is all of the Sheng family's issues, shouldn't we discuss ours next?
Penny.
I don't care about the grievances within the Sheng family.
I only know that once this matter is cleared up, I will be free again.
Open it.
This is a gift for you.
You mentioned before that you have an important event tomorrow.
You can wear these.
Your feet are a bit swollen because you're pregnant.
So, I bought you a size larger.
Thank you.
They're very pretty.
I've heard that giving shoes to a lover can lead to a breakup soon.
I don't care what other people say.
I'm giving you these shoes because I want to spend a lifetime with you.
♫  Crossing the border of rain,
I came to the sunny day you walked through  ♫
♫  A moment of light brings to mind your gentle prophecy  ♫
♫  You will defeat everything and rush to my side  ♫
♫  Like a fairy tale world with a happy plot forever  ♫
♫  When the beautiful things disappear and disillusionment breaks down,
when the world can't fall asleep  ♫
♫  You will remember the accidental encounter,
but it's a pity that the two of us go our separate ways  ♫
Do you still remember the last ball where you wore a veil and danced with me?
I remember.
At that moment, it felt like we were already married,
but there was a veil separating us.
After tomorrow, the veil will vanish.
♫  Letting half of the fairy tale disappear before writing forever  ♫
♫  What I thought was eternal and unchanging was only half the story  ♫
Sis!
I thought you weren't going to come.
This is the first annual gathering of the Shengs since Dad passed away.
How could I miss it?
Sis, I know you're upset about the division of the inheritance.
Although Sheng Group is mine now, we're still sisters, aren't we?
Can we go back to being like we were before?
If Dad really wanted to give the company to you,
Of course, I wouldn't be unhappy about it.
Let's go inside, Sis.
The baby...
"The Page You Appeared On" - Joynam
♫  Crossing the border of rain,
I came to the sunny day you walked through  ♫
♫  A moment of light brings to mind your gentle prophecy  ♫
♫  You will defeat everything and rush to my side  ♫
♫  Like a fairy tale world with a happy plot forever  ♫
♫  When the beautiful things disappear and disillusionment breaks down,
when the world can't fall asleep  ♫
♫  You will remember the accidental encounter,
but it's a pity that the two of us go our separate ways  ♫
♫  I wandered around and broke into the page where you appeared  ♫
♫  At the edge of the seaside forest, like the wind wandering past  ♫
♫  Half of the moonlight lit up the other half of the world  ♫
♫  Maybe on a day that you and I didn't get there  ♫
♫  I unknowingly walked past the page where you appeared  ♫
♫  Letting half of the fairy tale disappear before writing forever  ♫
♫  What I thought was eternal and unchanging was only half the story  ♫