If it's you who takes care of Next.
But I won't, if Tanya is in the picture.
Please don't work yourself up, Granddad.
We'll make sure to make things right.
Vee, we need to talk about Next tonight.
That's good, actually.
We need to come up with a way to turn the table on her.
You look like a brother superhero duo who's about to kick some bad guys' butts.
I'll be here rooting for you,
and I'll help you both in any way I can,
I'm afraid she won't hesitate to thoroughly squash us,
and take Next as her own, like Granddad said.
Wake up, boss.
Let's start working.
What?
Wait.
Why are you two...
Mirin called me last night.
She asked me to help liberate Next.
Hot coffee and sweets from my family to give you good energy.
Let's get going, Mirin.
Let's go, boss.
My girlfriend is so sweet.
I wish I had one too.
Jirawat Sutivanichsak
Supassara Thanachart
Ishikawa Plowden
Phatchatorn Thanawat/Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee
Phanuroj Chalermkijporntavee/Chayakorn Jutamas
Directed by Ekkasit Trakulkasemsuk and Pantip Vibultham
THE HAPPIEST MERRY-GO-ROUND
Girlfriend.
There are no customers in this age group in here.
What if we add this in?
Girlfriend, didn't you say you have a headache?
Everyone, let's go back to work.
Let's follow this plan.
I think we call it a day.
So we can visit Granddad at the hospital.
Good.
Thank you two for coming to help us here.
My pleasure.
That's right.
If there's anything else you want me to do, let me know.
I'll take care of it.
I think our plan is pretty good.
Now, we wait and see if Tanya will make a move like we've predicted.
Girlfriend.
Thank you so much.
If I didn't have you,
things would have been much harder.
You're welcome.
You are my boyfriend.
If there's anything I can help, I will do it.
I will help you all the way.
Thank you so much.
Thank you too.
Mr. Chanon, don't worry.
I'll help you all the way
as your secretary.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Are you mocking me?
I'll let you borrow my hand.
Thank you.
Dad.
How long have you been awake?
Do you need anything?
I'll call the nurse.
No, it's okay.
I want some water.
Sure.
Where are my grandsons?
They are resolving the company's problems.
Since they are working together,
there's nothing we need to worry about.
What's wrong, honey?
Dad.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
If I didn't get so competitive,
If I didn't instill my resentment in Chanon,
things wouldn't have turned out this way.
We both wronged each other.
I wronged you.
But I still need you.
You also still need you.
This is how family is.
Let bygones be bygones.
Granddad, how are you feeling?
I'm much better now.
Next time, if you feel unwell, you need to tell us.
Whether it's serious or not, you need to tell us.
I saw that you were working on your problems,
how could I tell you about my problem?
We found a plan to fix the problems.
Our company will be fine.
The most important thing is that you two are doing alright.
Do you know why I am so worried about the company?
I'm doing all this for my family.
I hope that my daughter and grandsons can continue to live good and comfortable lives like this.
The company is the only thing I can leave for you.
It's what I can build when I'm still alive.
Then you can't leave us yet.
When Non and I,
When we take Next back,
Granddad
Grandpa
you will get to see the company grow bigger.
Tomorrow,
we will make you proud.
A group of application users who are affected by the data breach and have not been compensated is gathering at Next Innovation.
There are no updates from the company's CEO, Mr. Chanon, and the majority shareholder, Miss Tanya.
(Protestors demands for compensation from Next Innovation.)
Did you see the news?
I think Tanya has made her move.
Let's fight back.
What should we do, Miss Tanya?
Mr. Chanon is not here yet.
We should hold a press conference regarding the compensation right away.
It's not going to cause any deficit to us anyway.
If you do nothing, our company may be sued for bankruptcy.
Shh!
Why do you look so anxious?
You are just employees.
Are you worried that you may lose your job?
About the protestors,
I cannot take any action on behalf of Chanon.
Because I'm not the company's CEO.
But you can vote for me to replace him as the new CEO.
Then I can fix the problem for you.
It won't take long before you can sip your coffee
and get back to your work.
Come out now.
Come out.
Come out!
Does anyone want to go out to meet them?
If you keep hesitating and the company is sued and has to close down,
you will be in trouble.
This is not a problem that anyone can fix.
I vote for Tanya to be the new CEO.
For the future of Next.
I vote for you too.
Me too.
Hold on, everyone.
What?
Mr. Chanon and Mr. Veekit have arrived at the company.
They are holding a press conference.
Hello, I'm Chanon.
I'm Veekit.
Firstly, we would like to apologize
for the delayed compensation process.
We are very sorry.
We are contacting the users via a messaging service
right now.
The process is taking so long
because we think this is a big problem.
We wanted to investigate what the cause of the problem was
and how it happened.
So we will not repeat the same mistake
and offer suitable compensation to the users.
From our investigation,
we found that the data was not leaked due to the system error.
It was actually a plan to sabotage me.
The person behind it was
Miss Tanya Kanokkul.
Miss Tanya?
Miss Tanya, your new partner?
Was this a power struggle in the company?
The incident occurred when the company was under my management.
Tanya is my friend.
She's an investor that I secured.
Chanon, what are you doing?
Miss Tanya did that so I could become the new CEO.
Are you accusing Miss Tanya of the incident?
Mr. Chanon, do you have evidence to prove it?
Please reveal your evidence.
The evidence has been sent to the police.
It's being sent to the company's executives as well via email.
It's revealed along with two witnesses.
They are our programmers.
They can provide evidence of a financial transaction
that they were hired by Tanya to leak the user data.
They have witnesses.
I insist that this problem was caused by the conflict in our company.
Chanon and I will discuss with the executive board what we are going to do next.
What if Miss Tanya denies your allegation?
If that's what she chooses to do,
she needs to deny it to the police.
What will happen to Next?
Is what they said true, Miss Tanya?
I would like to return the CEO position to Veekit.
Because Next Innovation would have not existed
without him.
Wow.
This is great.
The two brothers have reconciled.
Woo-hoo.
Woo.
We will discuss this with the executive board again.
The final decision will rest with the company's founder, Mr. Prapob.
Thank you.
See.
I know my grandsons can do it.
From now on, we just watch them taking the company higher.
Way to go, guys.
You look so cool.
I love it.
Hello.
Dad, you need to help me.
(Quiet.)
(Get out of there quietly.)
(Don't let the reporters see you and answer their questions.)
Dad.
Dad, please help me.
(Veekit and Chanon have offered you a way out.)
(You need to listen to them.)
(If the allegation is proven to be true, )
(no one will want to do business with you.)
(Admit your fault and back down.)
(The well-known app developer, Next Innovation, successfully overcame the crisis.)
(It restored the existing users' confidence)
(and also attracts new users.)
(Both local and international investors keep tabs on the company.)
(They are looking for a chance to buy the company's shares.)
(The company currently ranks first in terms of revenue.)
Are you ready for the general meeting today?
Of course.
Today is Granddad's first day back to work.
We should celebrate.
He is too eager to come back to work after he has recovered.
I don't get why he needs to hurry back to work.
That's how a teenager is.
Teenager?
Let's go.
Mr. Vee.
Didn't you tell me that you would call me when you arrived?
Right.
You agreed to tell Mirin before you came up here, didn't you?
I forgot.
Sorry.
What is behind you?
What's it?
It's not ready yet.
What are they doing?
Why are being so secretive?
It's done.
Okay.
Tada!
Wow.
Oh my god.
Did you make it, Girlfriend?
Yes.
Aew-aes came up with the idea and helped me arrange the cake.
This is to celebrate the one-month anniversary of you getting back to work together.
Everything is going great.
So we want to do a little thing for our bosses.
Thank you.
From its look, it must taste good.
I'll cut a piece for you.
You should cut a piece for me first.
Okay.
What is that?
A cake.
I can tell it's a cake.
It surely doesn't look like a pie.
It's orange and chocolate cake.
It's my new recipe.
It's sour and a bit bitter.
I guarantee that it tastes good.
Where is my cake?
You can take mine.
It's quite good.
But it will be better if it's less sweet.
I think we should order a cake for the next meeting.
Serving sweets in the meeting will help reduce everyone's stress.
For Mr. Prapob, I want clean-eating desserts.
Do you get it?
I'll prepare it with my heart.
I have the chocolate cake. It's my favorite.
Everything seems to going well.
Thank you, my grandsons.
If you don't mind,
I would like to nominate the person I currently think is most suitable to be CEO.
Before I make the nomination,
I have a question to ask you.
My grandsons, who do you think is suitable for the position?
Good.
It's good that it turns out this way.
I would like to announce
the person who is suitable to be the CEO
and knows Next well.
I believe that this person can lead the company to a better future.
That person is...
Sroyphet, my daughter.
Dad.
Please advise me, Aunt.
I'm ready to follow your lead in everything.
You are the most suitable person for the position.
I'm sorry that I've overlooked you for a long time.
I'll leave the company and my grandsons under your care.
Get used to the room.
This room is now yours.
Thank you.
When I suddenly fell ill and was hospitalized,
I realized that I had many things that I wanted to do
and there were many people I needed to apologize.
Neeraaumpan.
I know this may upset you.
But for me,
she is a part of our family.
She was the woman that your brother loved.
She is Veekit's mother.
I want her to be a part of our family again.
Of course.
I also want to amend my wrongdoings.
I need to apologize to her as well.
I'll talk to Veekit.
Here, my boss.
Thank you, my secretary.
What's wrong?
Stay still.
I told you to stay still.
I keep trying to read
What's in your heart but I must concede
I have something to talk to Veekit.
You can stay.
It's not a big deal.
It's okay.
I'm about to go out to get a document.
Please have a seat.
What do you want to talk to me about, Aunt Sroy?
I...
I want to apologize for everything I have done to you.
I'm not apologizing to you because you supported me in the board's meeting.
The reason is
when your grandfather felt ill, I was shocked.
I realized that things would be better
if I was a bigger person.
Your grandfather hopes
Neeraaumpan will be a part of our family again.
It's my wish as well.
I'm not sure
if you will give me a second chance.
Right now,
my mom lost most of her memory.
I think it will be good for all of us
to a fresh start.
I'll take my mom to see you.
Aunt.
Thank you, Vee.
Your grandfather will be happy to hear it.
Thank you.
It's lucky that things ended well.
I was so worried when things were messy.
Su, does this mean we can visit Veekit's mother?
How is his mother doing?
From what I heard from Mirin,
she is physically healthy.
But her disease is incurable.
All we can do is provide palliative care.
When we visit her,
she probably won't remember us.
We all forget things sometimes.
I don't mind if she doesn't remember me.
You are all here.
Hello.
Have you eaten anything?
If not, you should stay and have dinner with us.
You gave Mirin a ride home.
Come here.
Yes?
What do you want to say?
About the new application that we are working on together,
give me some updates.
I think it will turn out great.
I'm testing the new system.
I'll prepare a presentation for you.
I'm excited.
Swing your arms.
Like this.
Keep it going.
Your arms are so long.
Try this. It's delicious.
Try this. It's tastier.
I did my best to cook it.
Try this, too.
Thank you.
I'm not going to spoon out the food for you.
I know that.
When are you two going to get married?
Noi.
Aunt Noi.
I'm just asking.
I saw that his new application has been completed.
So it may be time for them to get married.
That's enough, Aunt Noi.
We want to focus on our work first.
There's one more thing.
Please tell Chanon that I still want to invest with him if he wants it.
He will be glad to hear it.
That's enough.
Now, it's dinner time.
You should put your work aside.
Veekit.
Next time when you come here,
take your mom with you.
Sure.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking about what Big Noi said earlier.
About the investment with Mr. Chanon, right?
I think...
No, not about that.
You really don't know my mind.
I'm thinking about our wedding.
Mr. Vee, you don't need to think about it.
Now, you should focus on the company.
I think this way we will have time to save up money.
Because I am very pricey.
Is that so? Okay.
Miss Jewel in the Crown.
Miss Gold Bullion.
But I can't put it off for long.
I want to marry you.
Look at me.
Mr. Vee, get in the car.
Hurry.
Get in the car.
Go.
You don't need to be shy.
I'm not.
Go.
Get in the car and drive safe.
Bye.
What?
I'm happy that my granddaughter is getting married.
What marry?
I need to make a lot of money first.
When I am rich, I'll take you on vacations.
You don't need to do that.
For us, seeing you happy is good enough.
You've done well.
For everything that you've been through, you did well.
I remember something.
It must be the dress that I bought her.
I told you that I would bring you good luck.
You got a good job and a great man.
Mom, how can you say that?
But she is right.
Mom!
Let's hug.
Mom.
Vee, you are home.
I'm home.
You remember me today.
That's great.
How is your day?
I...
I ate a lot today.
That's great.
Mom.
Can you go with me tomorrow?
Someone wants to see you.
You will be safe because I'm going with you.
Mom, do you remember this place?
You are here.
Hello, Aunt Sroy.
Come on. Let's go in.
Dad is waiting for you.
Mom, let's go.
I'm going with you.
Mom, sit here.
Dad will be here soon.
Wait here.
I'll go get you a drink.
Thank you.
Mom, I'll go see Non.
Can you wait here?
Miss.
Miss, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Can you get up?
I'll help you pick them up.
I can do it.
Are you okay?
Let me help you.
You are all wet.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Neeraaumpan.
You just spilled my water.
You don't need to apologize to me.
It's not about the water.
I...
I'm sorry
for everything that I've done to you.
I hope that you will forgive me one day.
I don't remember any of them.
But I forgive you.
You seem to be very caring and welcoming to me.
Let's end our feud here.
Your necklace is beautiful.
Can I call you Sroy?
You are here.
Dad.
Hello, Neeraaumpan.
I'm Prapob, your husband's father.
He's Veekit's grandfather.
Let's have a meal together.
Are you hungry?
Let's go. I'll help you carry it.
Be careful.
You don't need to greet me anymore.
You've done that three times already.
Vee.
Your grandma gave this pin to your father.
It's a set with the ring that your mom is wearing.
Your mom always wore it.
Until the day she had a fight with me.
I'll take this chance to return the pin to your mom.
It's pretty, Sroy.
Thank you so much, Aunt Sroy.
Mom.
I have a favor to ask you.
Why did you take me here?
This place.
I have a lot of memories here.
The day my mom went missing.
The day that I met you.
It's the place where I became blind
and also the place where I can see the best thing in my life, that is you.
Mirin, thank you so much
for making me see things again
with my eyes
and my heart.
Why are you saying these things?
I'm shy.
I hope that I won't get hurt again at this place.
Don't say that.
What else can hurt you now?
You have everything.
No.
Not everything.
Come here.
Which carousel horse do you want to ride on?
But it's closed.
Do you really need to do this?
Come on.
Let's ride the merry-go-round.
Hurry.
Okay, Mr. Vee.
Which one do you want to ride on?
Hurry, pick one.
It doesn't look nice.
What?
If you accept this ring,
even though the carousel horse that you pick is ugly
I will ride it with you.
Whatever you want to do,
I'll do it with you.
Wherever you go,
I'll go with you.
In simple words, I'll do everything you tell me to do.
What if I don't accept the ring?
What if you don't accept the ring?
Then you have to do everything that I tell you to do.
Does this mean whether I accept the ring or not
I will still have you in my life?
Yes.
Is this...
an engagement ring?
Yes.
Do I need to say it out loud?
You need to say it out loud.
It's important to me.
Okay.
Marry me.
Wait.
Wait a second.
Would you marry me?
That's all.
Sometimes it seems we're in sync
Your heart to mine, there's a link
If you cut to the chase, it would have been done a long time ago.
But other times it seems you're so distant
So what is your answer?
We are so different
I've already said it, Miss Ceremonialist.
The notebook that you carry around with you.
The one that you jotted down the hot chocolate recipe.
You never looked at other pages, did you?
Notebook?
It leaves me in a daze
To Mr. Veekit.
Can't tell if it's you through the haze
Whenever you want me to be by your side,
Is it you who will come around
And turn my whole world upside down
Whenever you want me to be by your side,
I'll be there for you.
And turn my whole world upside down
My love will shine onto you
no matter how far away you are from me.
I know that nothing can come between us
as long as you don't stop loving me.
My heart
will always be yours.
Rich man, poor woman.
Yes, I do.
Okay.
This is the ring
that my dad gave to my mom.
I'm asking her to give it to me.
How is it?
Do you like it?
Yes.
Can we hold the wedding at the merry-go-round?
Sure.
I can look but I just can't see
Your true feelings for me
Hidden like a mystery
From now on,
Won't you please just tell me?
Every night when I go to sleep,
You will be the last person I see.
Won't you please just tell me?
The first person I see the next morning
What could our relationship be?
Will also be you.
Roger that, Mr. Veekit.
Please help me truly see
You're my true love for eternity
Directed by Ekkasit Trakulkasemsuk and Pantip Vibultham
Do what my mom orders.
Sure, I'll take care of it.
If you have nothing else, why don't we go have dinner with Big Noi today?
I can't.
I have an interview to find my new secretary.
Aew-aes got a promotion.
You still can't find a secretary that you like.
I think you have interviewed every job seeker in the country.
I'm sorry.
Miss Aew-aes told me to come in.
Yes, come in.
Please introduce yourself.
Sroyphet.
My name is Sroyphet.
Did you recruit her?
No.
I didn't recruit her.
I swear.
Wait.
Is that creally your name?
Yes.
My mom's name is Sroy.
My dad's name is Phet.
So they named me Sroyphet.
I think you are likely to get the job.