Wow!
When you get on the ride,
hold on steadily so you don't fall off, alright?
Yes, Mom.
I promise to be careful.
Wait for me for a minute, Mom.
Only a minute.
Alright, hon.
I'll be fine.
You go on.
I'll wait right here.
Yes, Mom.
Hi, Mom!
Mom, it's so much fun.
Mom?
Mom!
I don't want to play anymore.
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
- Are any of you this boy's mother? - Mom? Where are you?
Are you his mother?
Mom...
Is this your mother, boy?
- Mom! Mom! - Or this?
Are any of you this boy's mother?
Mom!
Oh, no. Hey! Hey!
Boy!
Hey!
Jirawat Sutivanichsak.
Supassara Thanachart.
Ishikawa Plowden.
Phatchatorn Thanawat / Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee.
Phanuroj Chalermkijporntavee / Chayakorn Jutamas.
Directed by Ekkasit Trakulkasemsuk and Pantip Vibultham.
NEERAAUMPAN
Look straight, please.
Alright.
That's it. We're done.
Is anything wrong with my grandson?
Physically, everything's normal.
His condition likely stems from a mental cause.
Mom!
I would say the patient has what is called prosopagnosia,
or known commonly as "face blindness"
where patients can't distinguish faces.
It's either a result of some malfunction in the brain,
or it could be because of extreme emotional distress.
Did something that might have a great impact
on the patient mentally happen recently?
I think it could be the disappearance of Neeraaumpan, his mother.
Good morning, Mr. Veekit.
'Morning... Nittaya from HR.
Here's the list of all the new recruits in our IT department.
I'll have them introduce themselves to you in your office right away.
Do that after I have my first cup of hot chocolate.
Non.
I believe there should be a cup of hot chocolate on my desk right about now.
(There should.)
(But only after you finally select your new secretary.)
Now zip it and make your own hot chocolate until then.
I'll see you later.
Chanon.
Don't tell me you pulled an all-nighter again.
Just a bit, Mom.
Just a bit?
I doubt it's "just a bit" at this point.
Is your Mr. CEO going to do nothing at all?
Does Veekit plan to make you do all the work?
I'm not going to take that sitting down, you know?
Come on now.
I think I might finally find Vee a new secretary today.
I have to, in any case. We're running out of candidates.
Truly.
He's such a picky boy.
Nobody is ever good enough for him.
And it all comes down to you.
I'd love for your grandfather to see him like this.
Grandpa needs to stop putting his golden boy on such a pedestal.
Even I don't complain as much as you do, Mrs. Sroyphet.
You worry too much.
But I guess that's how much you love me.
Of course I love you.
I don't want anyone to take advantage of you.
Listen.
Stop devoting all your time for Veekit, Non.
Put yourself first sometimes, you hear me?
Yes, Mom.
But after I find him the genius he wants for a secretary.
Alright?
I'll let him fend for himself after that.
Promise.
I'm going to take a shower.
As you should.
Non, get cleaned up quickly and come down for breakfast.
Thank you for this, Mom.
And for this.
Wash your face.
Three brownies and two yogurt for Si.
Last house on the first street, on the left.
Thank you.
Two orange juice and one cookie for Jaidee.
The house with the green fence on the third street.
Now for Joy.
Two low-sugar butter cakes and two sugar-free banana cakes.
Noi!
Your delivery is here!
I'm here!
Her name means "minimal," but she sure isn't.
Two small butter cakes.
Use stevia instead of sugar, per some random recipe she found on Facebook.
Two boxes of brownies, "and prove there's no weed in it," she requested.
How do I "prove it"?
Does she want me to try it right here and now and not get high?
You're late.
Very late, Mirin.
I'm just fashionably late, Noi.
Here.
Try it.
Have you got yourself a job yet?
No.
Hold it.
There's nothing in the brownie.
I was just caught off guard because you asked such a pointed question.
What a relief.
Well, you graduated two years ago
and you're still delivering brownies for your mother.
Kids these days are all the same, aren't they?
Don't be so picky with jobs.
Just do what you're offered.
Well, what do you do?
Why? Why'd you ask?
I'm just curious.
Since you seem to have so much free time
to poke your nose into other people's business.
Here's your brownies.
Enjoy.
I'll keep this.
Rest assured that the brownie's poison-free.
And even if it isn't,
no poison is strong enough to kill someone like you anyway.
Was that a dig at me?
It's good.
Hey, Su.
Hmm?
You think Rin's going to get the job this time?
Good question, Mom.
I don't know how she keeps missing her shot.
My baby even graduated top of her class!
I feel bad for her.
Somehow she keeps getting rejected.
Listen.
If she gets turned down again this time around,
I don't want her to try anymore.
Just let her leech off of old people like us.
What's the harm in that?
Mom, don't say that.
Rin's an adult now.
She needs a job.
It's not like you can keep doing this, Mom.
Your legs are frailing and your back hurts.
Your heart is no longer strong, either.
What?
My heart?
Look.
My heart is as good as when I was 30, I'll have you know.
I'm still kicking.
Sure.
Rin.
- Coming. - It's me.
Yes, Grandma?
You have an interview today, don't you?
I was at the market the other day and saw a dress I thought you might like.
You haven't gone shopping for a while now, have you?
Wear this one. You'll look great.
Here.
Look.
Grandma.
Look, look.
You shouldn't have spent your money on this.
It's just an interview.
Come on.
It's a pretty dress.
Something like this was all the rage when I was young, you know?
More importantly, I saved up for this dress just for you.
Fine. Let me see.
Is it very expensive?
What's this here?
To fuel your body.
You need to take care of your body so you can keep on going.
Thank you.
I love you so much, Grandma.
I have both your dress and your support.
I have nothing to fear now.
Of course you have nothing to fear, my amazing girl.
Isn't that right?
Alright, Mirin.
Time to become Neeraaumpan.
The definition isn't... very good...
Excuse me. It's Nok from housekeeping.
Your hot chocolate, sir.
Bugs...
That's not what I asked for.
Take it away.
But I made it exactly the way you instructed, Mr. Vee.
I can tell just by the look of it that it's not the case.
But...
Is the interview for my new secretary going to start soon?
Mr. Chanon's secretary said it'll begin in an hour.
Tell Mr. Chanon...
Start immediately.
I can't take it anymore.
I need the right kind of hot chocolate!
Right now!
Y-Yes, sir.
Right away, sir.
Grilled pork!
Come get your grilled pork!
Best grilled pork on the block!
Hello? Yes?
What?
The interview has been moved up?
Yes. I'll be there right away.
Excuse me! I need a taxi!
Next Office, please.
Boss.
Boss!
Yes, Miss Eas?
Mr. Veekit moved the interview up.
He said he couldn't take it anymore and needed a secretary right now.
Are all the candidates here?
Yes, except for one Neeraaumpan.
Neeraaumpan?
Yes.
Here.
Tell Veekit to wait.
But he would be furious.
Trust me.
He'll want to meet this one.
Y-Yes.
Here, sir.
And here.
Thank you.
We're waiting for one more candidate.
She should be here soon-
Oh!
Sorry. I'm so sorry!
Sorry.
Really sorry.
Oh!
So it's Miss Vintage Dress here
who has been wasting my time?
I would have been on time
if it wasn't for the sudden change in the schedule.
I'd say it's a convenient change,
rather than "sudden."
But-
She's disqualified.
With that dress on, she's totally disqualified.
Vee.
I think you should-
You decided that based on how I dress?
Yeah.
What an outdated way of thinking.
Not as outdated as what you're wearing.
You can't just judge me based on that.
I'm much more than what meets the eye.
Are you now?
Then, why don't we start?
I'll let you have a go before anyone else.
How many languages do you speak?
Were you educated abroad?
Where else have you worked before?
Do you have any experiences with applications?
No.
Do you even know what qualifications I need in a secretary?
Do you know anything?
Vee, enough.
This is the first company that developed applications seriously.
It started with general applications,
but gained traction and made a breakthrough
after switching to apps focusing on wellness and health.
Good Life is an app for health monitoring,
and Get Well Soon, a pill reminder app that offers details on medicines.
Every app has its strength in ease of use,
which is suitable for people of all ages, and even patients.
And?
And there should be a new app,
which I think would be perfect for people in this day and age,
that can reveal a person's true ability
even through their armor of elaborately constructed facade.
Who is this arrogant woman?
How did you let someone like her in here?
My name is Neeraaumpan.
Neeraaumpan Paisarnpisai.
Wait.
Meet me in my office,
Miss Neeraaumpan.
It says here in your application that
you graduated top of your class.
That's so basic.
There's nothing else worth noting besides that.
Tell me something good about you.
Convince me why I should hire you and give you a chance.
I have a very good memory and I learn quickly.
I don't know if you'd believe me but I'd do anything to get this job.
Anything.
Good to hear.
Go get changed.
What?
Why?
You dress like an old lady.
And it looks uncomfortable.
Non.
Get her something that people in this century actually wear.
Not something that makes it look like fashion died in the year 2000.
Do you even know how much this dress means to me?
I'm not changing.
It's my company.
I set the rules.
If you don't change what you're wearing,
I'm not hiring you.
Here.
This is everything you need to remember by tomorrow.
If you can't do that,
I'm also not hiring you.
This is all of it?
Has your printer been broken since the year 2000?
Hey-
That's enough.
That's all for now.
You can memorize it bit by bit.
Don't, Non.
Don't get in her way.
You wanted more, didn't you?
Memorize all that by tomorrow,
Miss Top-of-Her-Class.
And you will present yourself in a more... fashionable way.
Ten times more.
Well, then. Please.
She's here for a secretary interview
but keeps arguing with her potential boss?
Who does that?
Now I look like a bad guy.
It's all her fault.
You dork!
Was I too harsh?
So he's the nice one, huh?
Hmm?
Did you say something?
Oh, I...
I saw people smiling at you.
So I thought you must be a nice boss.
I do get fussy, you know?
And when I do, I'm worse than Veekit.
Do you need help with that?
Oh, it's alright.
It's my job. I should be able to take full responsibility for it.
Mr. Non.
Will Mr. Veekit continue with the interview now?
I don't think so.
This is Neeraaumpan.
Veekit's new secretary-in-training.
What?
She's hired?
Wow!
Well, how long do you think you'll last?
A long time.
Definitely a long time.
This is Miss Aew-eas, my secretary.
You can ask her if you have any questions.
You really live up to your beautiful name.
I'll keep the contact info of the rest of the candidates
in case we need another interview.
Just to be safe.
Can you please take these binders to my car?
Miss Neeraaumpan and I have a little makeover to get to...
Maybe not quite so little.
Yes.
Do your best.
I think most people care about appearances.
You do?
I bet anyone does.
Imagine this.
You just meet someone,
and you know nothing about them.
Not who they are, what they like, what interests them.
How would you assume what kind of a person they could be?
Their appearances.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
Alright.
There are millions and millions of books in the world.
If the content is great and interesting,
but the cover is old, crumbling, unattractive,
and says nothing about the book,
who'd want to pick it up, right?
I guess.
That's it.
Vee is just trying to redesign your cover.
He's interested in your skills.
But your work experiences are much more limited than others.
If you don't change your look,
what'd he tell the other candidates why he chose you?
Why do you think that is,
Miss Mirin Paisarnpisai?
You...
Changing your name works wonders for you, doesn't it?
Whoever gave you that name?
My mother told me to change it.
She said changing my name will bring good luck.
But how'd you know about the name change?
You applied for a job here several times.
I remember you.
Would you mind me asking where your mother got that name from?
It's rather an uncommon name, don't you think?
It's my mother's best friend's name.
Not that I ever met her.
Mom said she was her childhood friend.
But they went their own ways in their adulthood.
Why?
What was your name before this?
Mirin.
Mirin was both my legal name and my nickname.
My mother just called me Rin, though.
Mirin.
That's a cute name.
It's a shame you changed it.
Let's take a look at some of these, shall we, Miss Neeraaumpan?
Get her more of this.
And sort out her shoes.
Next up is your hair.
What?
You're late.
Was the traffic really bad?
Are you tired?
Are you hungry, hon?
I am.
I haven't had dinner.
Go get cleaned up.
Your grandma made some soup for you.
Oh?
What happened to your hair?
Where are your glasses?
And what's with all these shopping bags?
They're clothes.
Rin, isn't this a bit much?
It wasn't me.
It's on the company's dime.
Company.
Company?
- I got the job, Mom! - You did?
What? What? What's going on?
What is it?
Grandma, I got the job!
Well done, my girl.
Grandma, it worked.
Your dress totally brought me luck.
Good job, dear.
Oh, but... I'm still on probation.
I don't know how long.
But don't worry.
I'll make sure they hire me.
From now on, you two don't have to work hard in the kitchen anymore.
I'll take care of you.
Oh, baby.
You're the best.
Rin, you're still up?
I'll go soon.
I have to memorize everything.
What are you baking today?
Apple pie.
We have some orders, 40 pieces to be exact.
That's all I'll make today.
Alright. I'll help.
No, you won't.
Go to bed.
Sleep for a few hours.
But I'm not tired.
I'm so ready.
I can't wait to go to work.
I got it all memorized.
I can help.
Let's go.
Come on. I'm not tired.
The guest list for the event tonight.
Miss Tanya will be coming with her mother.
Mrs. Sroyphet invited her.
Thank you.
Mr. Non.
Overall, well done, Miss Neeraaumpan.
Why don't you go say hello to Veekit?
See if he approves.
Good cover.
Great content.
You're an attractive book now.
Trust me.
Good morning, Mr. Veekit.
It's Neeraaumpan, your new secretary.
Strange.
Yesterday you smelled of
grilled pork,
marketplace,
and traffic.
But today,
you smell...
Delicious.
You smell like...
You smell like apple pie.
Alright.
Here comes your first test as my secretary.
And that is making hot chocolate.
Go on, Miss Neeraaumpan.
Don't even ask me how to make it.
It was in one of the binders I gave you.
If that's the kind of hot chocolate you want, you have to wait.
Wait?
How dare you suggest-
With the ingredients you have,
no matter how many times you try,
you would never get the flavor you want.
Something you just need to trust other people to do it.
Don't be so self-centered,
even if you're the boss here.
Fine.
But if I wait and I don't get exactly what I want,
you're getting fired today.
Yes, sir.
Do you think she'd make it?
I even dare say she's the one.
What makes you so sure?
Because I like her better than anyone we ever found for Veekit.
Neeraaumpan.
Directed by Ekkasit Trakulkasemsuk and Pantip Vibultham.
Here, baby.
Wow!
Your hot chocolate is the best, Mom.
Then drink all you want, dear.
I'm taking her on a field trip.
The party we're going to is a thank you party for our partners.
You must stay by my side and tell me who's approaching me.
That's Mr. Methawee, your partner and investor.
Keep Up is a diet app that helps users reach their goal weight.
I send you my admiration, Mr. Veekit.
Where have you been?
You said you'd be with me at all times.
Your good memory is meaningless otherwise.
All you have is brains, and nothing else!
Try to learn and listen!