I’m not being a spoiled brat.
Neeraaumpan handed in her resignation letter two days ago.
I’m going to go look for her.
I’m coming with you.
Are you sure you’re not the reason she disappeared?
Do you have a place you go to to take a breather?
Actually, I do.
Mirin!
Do you have any idea how long I’ve been looking for you?
Because there is something I really did you wrong.
What did you do?
Just tell me.
This woman is Neeraaumpan.
Mr. Vee.
Actually, I…
What face are you making?
I feel heavy-hearted.
I feel guilty that…
that you disappeared?
You should be.
Do you know when you disappeared,
everyone was worried about you?
I really hate it when someone disappears from my life.
Mr. Vee.
I’m begging you.
Don’t disappear again.
I felt like…
my heart went missing
after my mom disappeared.
I…
I mean…
Mr. Vee.
Please stop.
If you keep talking,
I won’t be able to tell you that I…
Jirawat Sutivanichsak
Supassara Thanachart
Ishikawa Plowden
Phatchatorn Thanawat / Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee
Phanuroj Chalermkijporntavee / Chayakorn Jutamas
Directed by Ekkasit Trakulkasemsuk and Pantip Vibultham
WHO IS THAT WOMAN?
I know everything.
Huh?
You have feelings for me.
You think it’s wrong.
Because I am the CEO of the company.
I’ll tell you something.
It’s okay.
I’m the CEO of the company.
I can amend the company’s regulations.
You can come back to work.
Don’t worry.
Mr. Vee, it’s not what you think.
Or…
are you saying that…
you not only have feelings for me
but you actually fall in love with me?
Mr. Vee, listen to me.
There’s something that I did you wrong.
It’s very wrong.
It’s the kind of wrong that you will never forgive me if you find…
I don’t want to hear it.
If it is something so big that you decided to disappear from my life,
Mr. Vee.
Whatever the truth is,
I don’t want to hear it.
I don’t want to lose you again.
This is from the heart of the man you called the Sun,
the Nemesis,
the center of the universe,
the three-legged scorpion,
the blood-sucking spider,
the utility pole,
every nickname you ever called me.
I love you, Mirin.
Wait a sec.
Hello.
Yes.
I found her.
She’s with me.
Sure.
Yes.
Bye.
Big Noi said she wanted 15 boxes of brownies tomorrow.
It’s compensation for making her worried about you.
Did Aunt Noi know about this?
Of course.
She will be lecturing me until my ears bleed.
That’s what you deserve.
You are lucky that all you will get is being lectured.
The thing that you are going to tell me,
what is it?
You can tell me.
So we can work things out like other couples.
Other couples?
Hurry and tell me.
Are you free this Sunday?
Are you asking me out on a date?
Why are you asking me that question?
You are my secretary.
I will not approve your resignation.
Then
I’ll tell you everything this Sunday.
Do I need to wait for a week?
Alright.
I can wait.
Girlfriend.
Remember this.
From now on,
your only nickname is Girlfriend.
If I call you that,
you need to answer me, okay?
What should I do with you?
Give me a lot of love.
Don’t ever leave me.
Can I hold your hand?
If you agree to use those photos like I told you,
you will get everything you want.
With one stone, you can kill all the birds.
Non, you will get everything that you want,
the company,
your grandfather,
and Mirin.
If you want to be on top,
sometimes, you need to step on others,
even if that person is your family.
That’s enough, Tanya.
This is important.
Give me some time to think.
What else do you need to think?
Tanya.
I have been working hard for more than ten years.
You can’t suddenly tell me to use this ploy.
Please respect my effort.
I always respect and admire you.
What about your grandfather,
your company,
your cousin?
Have they ever shown you any respect?
If this was concerned only you,
you could take as much time as you wanted.
I wouldn’t care.
But this is also about me.
I can’t give you much time.
Rin.
Where have you been?
I’m sorry, Mom.
You should have told me where you went.
You shouldn’t disappear without saying anything.
Is this because I told you to resign from the company?
Did it go well?
Did you submit your resignation?
Did you tell him the truth?
I submit my resignation.
I tried to tell him the truth but…
But what?
He said he loves me.
What did you tell him?
I love him too, Mom.
My poor baby.
Mom.
I will try to tell him the truth.
Please give me some time.
Rin.
Love can’t be denied.
There should not be any secrets between lovers as well.
Remember my words.
You start this relationship with lies.
You will have to continue to lie to him.
I’ll tell him soon.
I promise.
I’ll tell him everything and face the music.
He can be mad or hate me if he wants.
Good.
This woman is Neeraaumpan.
Veekit’s mother who has been missing.
I always respect and admire you.
What about your grandfather,
your company,
(your cousin?)
(Have they ever shown you any respect?)
Mr. Vee, what are you doing here?
I’m here to pick you up.
Girlfriend.
Mr. Vee.
Let’s go if we don’t want to be late.
Wait.
Should I go in and greet your mom and grandma first?
We will become family soon.
Stop.
Stop right there.
Okay.
Get in the car.
Do I need to open the door for you?
It’s okay.
Hey, Girlfriend.
When we are outside, you are my girlfriend.
But when we are at the company,
it won’t look good if we act all lovey-dovey.
I hope you will understand me.
You can’t pick up a fight with me over this later.
Yes?
It’s great that you understand.
Mr. Vee.
I think I should go back to my desk.
If we are doing this, people may find out.
Sit here and do your job.
Don’t worry.
I’ll take care of everything.
Mr. Vee, I haven’t agreed to be your girlfriend.
Oh.
What you said hurts me.
I’m very hurt.
Fine.
If you want to make it official,
Go get the document from the printer.
What?
Now.
[Will you be my girlfriend?]
Will you be my girlfriend, Mirin? [Will you be my girlfriend?]
Will you be my girlfriend, Mirin?
I will give the universe
that revolves around me
to you.
Mr. Vee.
So?
Are you saying yes?
Yes?
Yes, yes.
Say it.
Will you be my girlfriend?
Mr. Vee.
Okay.
I’ll take that as a yes.
Just do your best today.
It will be over by the end of the week.
What will be over this week?
What?
What will you do this week?
Are you going to the church?
Yesterday, everyone was worried about you.
If you are going to take a breather, you should tell me.
I’m sorry.
You don’t need to apologize.
But you can’t secretly submit your resignation again.
Heart-shaped marshmallows?
I want them too.
Can you make another cup for me?
You can secretly make it behind Veekit’s back.
He is so possessive about his hot chocolate,
his secretary,
and everything.
I can’t understand him.
I can make a hot chocolate for you.
But I ran out of heart-shaped marshmallows.
Why am I so unlucky?
It’s okay.
I still have normal marshmallows.
I’ll make the drink for you.
Hello, Tanya.
About what you told me to do,
I’ve slept on it.
I think it’s a good idea.
(Great.)
(You finally do something for yourself.)
It’s probably too late.
Since it’s probably too late,
I will wait for the best timing.
(You want to make the call when to do it, don’t you?)
Yes.
I made hot chocolate for Chanon this afternoon.
I don’t like it.
But I’ll let it slide.
All Non does is work.
He is serious about everything.
I think the hot chocolate could help him relax.
Non told me that he has a place for taking a breather.
Sometimes, he felt exhausted.
Look at his mom.
His mom sets high expectations for him.
It must be tired to be him.
I’ll permit you to make hot chocolate for him from time to time.
Mr. Vee.
What?
Thank you
for everything.
Thank you too, Girlfriend.
You’re welcome, Boyfriend.
Are you smiling, Boyfriend?
No, I’m not.
- Are you smiling, Boyfriend? - No, I’m not.
- Are you smiling? - Keep your voice down. I’m not smiling.
The application that we are working on with Big Noi,
It’s undergoing a legal assessment.
The other applications that we have launched have superb performance.
The number of users in every app is on the rise.
It has been increasing to date.
What about the feedback from the shareholders?
The shareholders?
They are very happy with the performance.
Good job, Veekit.
Everyone looks happy, BF.
Thank you, GF.
Okay, this is our last agenda.
I’m holding a party to welcome our investors from overseas this Friday.
Please get all of our business plans ready to present to them.
Yes, Grandpa.
I’ll do my best.
Yes, Granddad.
This party is very important.
Though it may look like a casual party,
it can affect our reputation.
I need to ask you to supervise the party planning.
I’m happy to do it, Dad.
Then the meeting is adjourned.
Aew-aes, can I have the latest update on all the applications?
I also have to ask you to stay late at work today.
Anytime.
If you give your all in, so do I.
If there’s anything I can help,
you can always tell me.
So you can compete with Veekit.
I know Non will do well.
I’m sure of it.
Yes.
I’m sure of it too.
You can do it.
Because I gave Mirin permission to make hot chocolate for you.
You are saying as if he is owning something to you.
She just makes hot chocolate for him.
Isn’t that a part of the secretary’s job?
She is not just a secretary.
Wait.
Are they dating?
Veekit, keep falling as far as you can.
I’m rooting for you.
He is not falling, Mom.
Don’t you see?
He’s doing better every day because he has Mirin.
Then I need to kick her out as soon as possible.
Hello, Tanya.
I know when we are going to use those photos.
Great, Non.
This is what a friend is for.
Tell me your plan when you are ready.
I also need to have my own plan to deal with Veekit.
Let’s call it a day.
We can continue to work on it later.
We need to wait for confirmation from other departments anyway.
Alright.
What?
Are you tired?
I’m okay.
But I’m not okay.
Come on, let me charge my battery.
I am scowling at you.
I don’t care if you are scowling or not.
Because I can’t see it anyway.
Come on.
My girlfriend is so petite.
I’ll protect you.
I won’t let anyone hurt you.
I won’t let anyone hurt my boyfriend as well.
Charging battery.
I’m feeling sleepy.
Is this okay?
It looks okay.
Is this okay, Boss?
I want the food to have a mild taste and a vast variety.
Don’t forget to send the guest list to me to check.
Make sure that Tanya sits next to Veekit.
Yes, Mrs. Sroyphet.
Why didn’t Manit come to meet me?
I have many details I want to ask him.
Manit is having a meeting with Mr. Chanon.
So he can’t come to meet you.
I’ve been trying to make an appointment with him all week.
How can a programmer be busier than the CEO?
Do you have anything I can help you in the meantime?
No. You can go back to work.
Yes sir, CEO.
The models for the other two applications
will be completed this evening.
You don’t have to worry about them, Chanon.
Thank you.
I haven’t started work on Veekit’s project.
I chose to work on your project first.
Be careful. Veekit may be pressuring you.
I don’t think he will stay here long
I think I should work on your project first.
Thank you so much, Manit.
Please take care of the rest.
Sure.
I’ll keep you posted.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
The employees started to choose sides.
It’s only Manit.
He doesn’t like Veekit.
Not only Manit, but I’m also on your side.
Veekit is dating Mirin.
Huh?
Since when?
I just found out the other day.
They held hands and walked out of the meeting room
in front of me and Chanon.
This is why Non agrees to do it.
Do what?
The plan to destroy Veekit.
I can’t believe that he is really dating his secretary.
A secretary?!
Although she seems to be naïve,
I think she does everything to seduce Veekit until he falls for her.
I’m sure you can bring him back.
You are a catch no matter what.
It doesn’t matter if he will come back to me or not.
Right now, all I want is to get rid of his secretary.
I’ll deal with other things later.
Why are you acting surprised?
You stole my man.
You shouldn’t be surprised by this.
Stop pretending to be the damsel in distress.
Well done.
You are so good at it.
I give you credit for it.
Teach me.
How should I flirt or seduce him so that he will fall for me?
Being a wealthy and high-profile woman must be a wrong move for me.
I should have pretended to be poor,
have low education,
not know much about social etiquette,
and act like a helpless woman like you.
Miss Tanya.
What?
What, Mirin?
Are you upset?
Why don’t you run and tell Veekit about this?
Do it.
Please stop it.
I’m sorry that you feel hurt.
But I am sure that I didn’t do anything wrong.
You have never been my choice.
Are you sure about what you said?
I have never been more sure in my life.
I’m sorry but can I be honest with you?
I never liked your perfume.
I never liked your voice.
Okay, you dress well.
You have a good taste.
But I never find you pretty.
Veekit.
If you continue to talk badly to Mirin,
I will not let it slide.
Is there anything else you want to say?
If you have, then say it to me.
If not,
please excuse us.
Mirin.
You are so dead.
Are you okay?
Did Tanya do anything to you? Are you alright?
Why did you put up with her?
Why didn’t you walk away?
If everyone finds out that I am dating you,
this is what I will be constantly facing.
I don’t know how bad it will be.
No.
Don’t let anyone talk to you like that.
This is the reality, Mr. Vee.
No one will think that I deserve you.
What do you mean that you don’t deserve me?
Is it because I'm rich and you’re poor?
I don’t care.
We didn’t do anything wrong.
All I know is…
I love you.
What about you?
Do you love me?
Say it, Mirin.
We will find a way out together.
I’ll be by your side.
I’ll protect you.
I’ll give you what my mom never got.
What do you mean?
My mom,
she felt very pressured
while she was married to my dad.
She had been nagged or criticized all the time.
My dad barely stood up for her.
Because he didn’t want to offend anyone.
I promise.
I will never let that happen to you.
Thank you.
Thank you for treating me well.
Today is Thursday.
Wait until Sunday.
Then say these things to me again.
Excuse me, I need to get back to work.
Good job, Aew-aes.
Can I have the second batch of documents?
Tanya.
What’s going on?
What happened?
You knew about Veekit and Mirin, didn’t you?
Why didn’t you tell me?
You are useless.
I thought you would take Mirin away from Veekit.
Because you also like her.
Why didn’t you fight for her?
Why didn’t you tell her that you like her?
You are as wealthy as Veekit.
A woman like her,
she is willing to date any rich man, don’t you know?
Tanya, it’s not about my wealth.
Then what is it about?
What else can it be?
You are good-looking and rich.
You have everything that Veekit has.
Why wouldn’t she choose you?
It would be nice if I knew the answer.
We love them before they love each other.
I can’t accept it
if things are not going my way.
I love him.
I will have him.
I’m willing to do terrible things to have him.
I have to have him.
Has your cousin ever shown you any respect?
Why are you here with my secretary?
I want to drink hot chocolate. Let’s go.
Let’s do terrible things together.
Let’s be partners in crime.
Aew-aes, is Veekit standing by at the back?
Yes.
Mr. Non said he was going to brief Veekit on something.
I think your beloved boss should be ready by now.
Hello, everyone.
Next, please welcome Mr. Veekit Kraipiwat.
Ladies and gentlemen, Mr. Veekit from Next Innovation.
Hello.
I’m Chanon Kanchanarak.
I’m here on behalf of Mr. Veekit who has an emergency errand.
I would like to introduce
all the interesting applications of Next Innovation.
Mr. Vee.
Who sat next to you?
Who was that woman in the photos?
Who sat next to you? Tell me.
Mr. Vee, please hear me out.
I can’t see faces.
But I remember that these are your clothes,
your bag,
and your hairstyle.
Tell me the truth.
The woman sitting next to you was my mom, wasn’t she?
Answer me!
Directed by Ekkasit Trakulkasemsuk and Pantip Vibultham
Where?
Is this the one?
Look if it’s in the box.
Where is it?
Is this the one?
Mom.
I saw Aunt Sroy wearing a different ring every day.
But why do you have only one ring?
I have many rings.
But this ring,
it’s the one I love the most.
Because your dad gave it to me.
Will you wear it for the rest of your life?
Yes, for the rest of my life.
I will never take it off.
Remember my words, honey.
This ring
is a symbol of your dad.
It means that he is always with me.
You are the only woman in the world
who can make me the biggest fool.
Get out!
Where is Mirin?
How did you know that?
A woman who has the same name as your mother applied for a job here.
Anyone could tell that she was going to use you.
(Please let me take you to see your mom.)
(Tell me where my mom is.)
Go pick up Neeraaumpan from the church tomorrow.
Call me when you get her.
I want to talk to her.
I want to know where she has been hiding all these years.