The incident occurred while it was under my supervision.
This causes damage to the company.
From now on,
I guess you need to rebuild it.
I think the best solution for everyone is that I should resign.
The person who will replace me as the new CEO is
Mr. Chanon Kanchanarak.
Hello, I'm Tanya Kanokkul.
We are going to work together to manage Next Innovation.
How did Chanon let it happen?
Who are you?
Don't.
Do you remember anything?
I remember that...
Sroyphet was mean to me.
Mr. Vee.
How is Aunt Nee? Has her memory returned?
No.
I asked her what she remembered.
She doesn't remember anything recent.
The only thing she does remember is...
how mean Aunt Sroy was to her.
Mean?
Yes.
Seen said the reason her condition is so severe
is because of the trauma she went through in her past.
What will you do now?
I think I'll ask her about it when she comes to.
It will probably be helpful with her treatment.
Oh, hey, you went to Next today, didn't you?
Did anyone do anything to you?
Hmm?
Let me see.
Mr. Vee.
Who would even dare?
I'm a fighter, I'll have you know.
A fighter? The size of a chihuahua?
Mr. Vee.
Sorry.
I'm kidding.
What about the matter with Big Noi and Next?
What's going on?
It's over.
What?
Non is just going to let Big Noi go?
"Throw away" is a more fitting term.
Mr. Chanon said so himself,
something along the line of, "aren't suitable as business partners."
Big Noi did ask him if he had consulted Mr. Prapob about this.
But Mr. Chanon insisted this was his decision to make alone.
If we look at it from Non's point of view,
I guess Tanya alone would be enough.
If it's just about money,
I bet Tanya is even richer than Big Noi.
But when it comes to credibility,
Big Noi definitely wins in that department.
However...
Non and Tanya,
they are both young.
Maybe they can pique young people's interest.
So that's why Mrs. Sroyphet wanted her as Mr. Chanon's business partner.
Exactly.
I'm afraid there's still a chance for the game to turn around, though.
What do you mean?
The way she acted at the press conference.
I'll be honest,
I don't trust Tanya.
The person who will replace me as the new CEO is
Mr. Chanon Kanchanarak.
Hello, I'm Tanya Kanokkul.
We are going to work together to manage Next Innovation.
We will restore your trust.
We will take Next Innovation higher.
Jirawat Sutivanichsak
Supassara Thanachart
Ishikawa Plowden
Phatchatorn Thanawat / Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee
Phanuroj Chalermkijporntavee / Chayakorn Jutamas
Directed by Ekkasit Trakulkasemsuk and Pantip Vibultham
THE UNCONTROLLABLE GAME
Yes, Aew-eas?
(Hello, Manit.)
Mr. Chanon wants to meet you at 10 o'clock tomorrow, if that's okay with you.
(Of course.)
I'm always at the office.
Feel free to call for me anytime.
The thing is, Mr. Chanon doesn't want to meet at the office.
(I'll send you the location later.)
Alright.
Hold on, what is this meeting about?
(I don't know, either.)
(Mr. Chanon didn't say.)
So the meeting is at 10 o'clock tomorrow.
(Can you please relay the message to Maewkwak?)
Of course.
(Goodbye.)
Bye.
What could this be about?
Mom?
Vee.
Mom.
Do-Do you remember now?
Please sit down.
I'll get you breakfast.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Was I gone long this time?
Did I cause you trouble again?
It was no trouble at all.
It just took me by surprise.
Mom.
I have something I need to ask you.
You said... Aunt Sroy was mean to you.
Will you tell me about it honestly, Mom?
This could affect your treatment.
Your father...
Your father once told me that
your Aunt Sroy doesn't like us much because
she was indignant that she put all her effort into helping your grandfather build the company,
only for him to give it over to your father as soon as he graduated.
Aunt Sroy must have felt about Dad
what Non is feeling about me right now.
But your grandfather loves Chanon.
He's the first grandson born into the family.
But when...
When your father married me and we had you,
you became...
A direct heir?
Am I right?
Y-Yeah.
Your aunt...
Your aunt doesn't like me much.
She told me every day
that I only married your father for his money.
I put up with it.
Then your father passed,
and it just got worse and worse.
When I realized I was getting sick,
I couldn't help but be afraid—
Afraid of what she could do to me.
And I was also...
I was also afraid that I would be a burden to you.
Mom, Mom.
Mom.
Mom, listen to me.
I never think of you that way.
Even if one day you don't remember me anymore,
I will never forget that you're my mother.
Hello, Mr. Chanon
Please take a seat.
Thank you for coming out here to see me.
It's no problem at all.
What can we do for you?
How could you take an order from Tanya without consulting me first?
What you did could have ruined Next.
Oh?
But Maewkwak and I thought that order came from you.
You and Miss Tanya are best friends.
I doubt you weren't clued in on the matter.
From now on, please only take orders from me directly.
But wasn't it exactly because of Miss Tanya's order
that put you in the CEO chair right now?
We even got a bonus for it, you know?
Mr. Manit.
I promise we only did it because we thought you were in on it.
Imagine if I let slip that it was actually an order from an executive.
It really could ruin Next, like you said, don't you think?
But Miss Tanya promised me a reward,
and that's the only thing stopping me from spilling the beans.
Why don't you start thinking right away about how big a bonus I should get?
Excuse me.
Hey, wait.
Don't you think that was a little too much?
He's our boss.
If I didn't intimidate him now,
they are definitely going to make us take the blame for this.
Rich people are like that.
They use you and throw you away,
and then they act like they have nothing to do with it.
We need to talk to Tanya.
Gotta know what she's planning.
And if I don't get what I deserve,
I'll expose them all.
What the hell is so important that I "must" come right away?
Please, have a seat, Miss Tanya.
Mr. Chanon just sat Maewkwak and me down for a talk.
He was furious that I took orders from you without consulting him.
Are you planning to make us your scapegoat, Miss?
Don't tell me you're asking for more money.
I believe the two of us very much deserve it.
How about you give me a bonus for pitting me against Mr. Chanon?
And I'll tell you what to watch out for.
What?
What should I watch out for?
Mr. Chanon really looks like he doesn't want anything to do with this.
He's properly angry.
He could likely decide to just ditch you.
Do let me know anytime if you need any help, Miss Tanya.
Hey.
Catch.
What the hell?
Well?
It's snacks.
You can't tell?
Of course I can.
But why are you giving it to me?
Eat.
Might get your sanity back.
If that's all you want to say, you can shut up now.
It's annoying.
But you see, I think we—
What the hell?
But it's so good.
Smells great.
What do you mean you can't finish it in time?
You told me you could definitely meet the deadline.
You should be able to deliver what you promised.
I don't care what working with Veekit was like.
You're working for me now so you adjust to me.
Excuse me.
Goodbye.
Mr. Prapob wants to see you, sir.
Ugh, fine.
Then, I have three favors to ask.
Finish up these old documents.
Second, give the design team a little nudge.
They're going at snail's speed.
Third, give me a rough estimate of how much we need to pay to clean up the mess Tanya made.
I thought it was Mr. Veekit who leaked those data.
Manit leaked it on Tanya's order.
But people might think it was your doing.
I know.
I'm working on fixing it.
Why don't you go meet Mr. Prapob first?
We'll work this out later.
Thank you for understanding, Miss Eas.
Of course.
Holy crap.
Did you want to see me, Grandpa?
Yes.
Sit down, Chanon.
I talked to Big Noi.
She told me you had ended our partnership with her.
Yes, and there are only a few papers left to finalize the matter.
She's the best investor for Next Innovation.
She doesn't invest easily, and yet she chose us.
How could you make such a big decision on your own?
Why didn't you talk to me?
Big Noi wanted to invest with Veekit, not me.
She doesn't feel comfortable working with me,
and I share her sentiment.
Tanya's credibility will never come anywhere near Big Noi's.
I do believe my credibility alone is enough.
One more thing, Tanya's investment is much more generous.
Sure, we might need two investors for this,
but that will make up for what Big Noi has offered.
With her attitude at the press conference the other day,
are you sure you can still trust Tanya to be a good partner and executive?
Everything's alright on my end.
How about yours?
It's all done.
I'll have Aunt Noi sign the papers as soon as possible and send them back to you.
Oh, and, we might need you to show up on the day they investigate the leak.
They want to talk to every involved party.
Are you okay?
Oh. Yes, I am.
I've been busy lately so I'm just thinking how I'll fit that into my schedule.
Excuse me for now. I have to get ready for a meeting.
Mr. Vee?
What are you doing here?
I'm here to pick up my adorable teeny-tiny girlfriend, of course.
Hey, Miss Girlfriend,
do you want to go on a date?
A date?
Now?
Yes.
We haven't been spending some quality time together, you know?
All we do every day is try to solve some problems,
which you've been a big help to me.
It's my pleasure.
That's why I want to thank you.
Thank you.
You're like the personification of all the vitamins rolled into one.
Wait.
Hmm?
Did you just give me another pet name?
Why? Do you prefer being called a chihuahua?
Mr. Vee.
Where do you want to go?
I want to take you to see an entirely ordinary world.
Something... someone like you wouldn't be used to.
What are you thinking about?
Oh...
I'm just thinking about how many children we will have.
What?
Why are you so surprised?
Don't you want to get married?
Wait, are you infertile?
I am not.
I mean I... don't know.
You just took me by surprise because...
I was also thinking about how many children we'll have.
I'm fine with anything.
How about this?
Once everything is over,
let's just do it.
If you don't mind, of course.
Sure don't!
Oops.
Did that make me seem easy?
I am even easier, then.
How about we make a "horn" pose together?
What are you playing?
Huh?
This is so silly.
I'll run you over.
- You're cheating.
- You can never reach my hand.
That's cheating.
Is everything ready, Miss Eas?
Is my grandfather here?
He's on his way.
Everything's ready to go.
Everyone seems a little confused with this emergency meeting, though.
Some people are too busy for some pop-up meeting, does he know that?
Do you know why your grandfather called us in?
I have no idea.
What the hell is this emergency meeting about?
I cancelled my yoga class for this, you know?
Miss Eas, is there any information on the agenda Grandpa told you to prepare?
There's the old project between Miss Big Noi and Mr. Veekit,
and the budget for next year.
Next year's budget?
Then there's nothing urgent to call us in for—
You can call it urgent, but I guess it can also wait.
Dad.
Are you all ready?
Apologies for the short notice.
I just finished setting up an internal affair investigation team.
I want your cooperation with the interrogation.
Wait a minute.
This is the first I've heard of an investigation.
I just finished setting up a team, Miss Tanya.
And you didn't think to consult me or Non while you were setting it up?
You left both the CEO and the major shareholder clueless?
Which part of this plan do you take an issue with, Miss Tanya?
It's—
The issue is you're bringing total strangers to investigate an internal affair
without notifying either the CEO and the major shareholder.
Are they qualified? Who are they?
Why does it have to be this team?
At the very least, I'm sure they are hired on the company's dime.
You should give us a heads up.
Tanya.
Well, allow me to ask,
excuse me for being blunt,
but what is your role in this company, Mr. Prapob?
Besides being the founder, that is.
Tanya.
Chanon is the current president, and is responsible for managing the company.
I am the major shareholder.
I have my share of management.
Putting the matter with Veekit aside,
what do you do here, Mr. Prapob?
Tanya.
Your Grandpa is old enough to think about retiring, don't you think?
Watch it.
Stop what you're saying.
If you guys are going to get so emotional,
just keep your business and your inferior complexes in the family, maybe?
I'm taking Next Innovation further.
We've been walking in the same spot for far too long.
You don't own this company.
But of course, I do, don't I?
The shares I hold and the money I spend on this company
is enough to rival the CEO.
I can easily fire him, even.
If anyone neglects to keep me in the loop, like he did,
then I have a right to drop all kinds of decorum.
Try me and you'll see what I can do to this company.
Stop it, Tanya.
Stop fight—
Sir?
Grandpa!
Dad!
Sir!
- Grandpa.
- Dad!
Grandpa.
Hello?
- Dad! Dad, what's wrong?
- We need an ambulance at Next Innovation.
Right now!
The ambulance will be here soon, Dad. Please, hold on.
Non.
What happened?
Did the doctor say anything yet?
What happened to Granddad?
They just took him inside just now.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean for something like this to happen.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
My Granddad, your Grandpa, will be alright.
Hello.
Bring me my share purchase agreement and the CEO's.
Immediately.
I know you're not hungry, but please drink some water, or you'll get sick.
I won't bother you about eating again.
Sit with me.
Yes.
Don't look so expectant.
I'm not venting to someone like you.
Oh. Right.
I'm thinking if I should be mad at you.
Sorry?
I'm thinking who I should blame,
who I should berate,
who I should punish.
But I realize there's no one here to blame but me.
I think—
Don't talk.
Yes.
I should have...
I should have been kinder.
I hate it even more now that you can see.
Do you hate me so much?
I don't hate you.
I'm mad at you.
And I'm hurt.
Like anybody would be, if their big brother betrayed them.
I'm sorry.
Mom was just telling me...
You're Granddad's favorite grandson.
Because you were the first and only boy born into the family,
until I came along.
I couldn't care less about our Grandpa-Granddad thing.
Can you imagine that?
I never even paid it any mind.
All I knew was that...
You're...
You're my big brother.
I never thought they treated me better than you,
or loved me more than you.
Not until I couldn't see people's faces, at least.
My dad died.
My mother disappeared.
I couldn't see faces.
At that age,
it wouldn't be strange
that Granddad pushed me more than others, would it?
He just didn't want me to be a burden to anyone.
I'll be really happy
if it's you who takes care of Next.
I'll help. I'll do anything for you.
But I won't, if Tanya is in the picture.
Are you Mr. Prapob's family?
Mr. Prapob is conscious now.
But we should remain wary.
I've actually asked him to retire several times before
because stress could affect his condition.
His condition?
Mr. Prapob has a heart disease.
You are not aware of this?
He probably doesn't want anyone to worry about him.
His condition has worsened, especially within the last couple of years.
How about this?
Mr. Prapob is already in his room, and wants to see his family.
I suggest you stay with him for now.
We can discuss this matter afterwards.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault things turn out this way.
Dad.
I can't make you realize
how much I love you all the same.
It's my fault that an aunt couldn't love her nephew.
It's my fault that two cousins fought.
Everyone fell apart.
And now a stranger is taking over our company.
A total stranger evicting me from my own company!
Dad.
Please don't work yourself up, Granddad.
I promise you I won't allow it to happen.
Non and I...
We won't let anyone do such a thing.
Vee's right.
Please focus on getting better, Grandpa.
We'll make sure to make things right.
I'll stay with your grandfather.
You two should go.
Find a way to fix this.
Please take a rest, Dad.
I will be right here with you.
How is your grandfather?
He's more or less alright.
Yes. But he still needs a lot of rest.
What a relief.
Vee, we need to talk about Next tonight.
I have something to tell you.
Alright.
That's good, actually.
We need to come up with a way to turn the table on her.
Well—
Have Mirin take your car.
I'll go with you.
Drive carefully, alright?
Text me when you get home.
You're so cool!
You look like a brother superhero duo who's about to kick some bad guys' butts.
I'll be here rooting for you,
and I'll help you both in any way I can,
starting tomorrow.
Do your best, my heart.
I'm sure Granddad loves us both equally.
But Mirin?
She has no place in her heart for anyone but me.
It was Tanya who had Manit and Maewkwak leak those users' data.
What?
And you let her?
Easy there, bud.
I didn't know.
I swear I didn't.
Like I would ever discredit our company with such a dirty scheme.
How could I, when we've worked our asses off for this?
In our defense,
both Mom and I really didn't think Tanya would do such a thing.
You got any proof?
I have Manit and Maewkwak.
They were extorting me for some bonuses all so shamelessly.
Did they lose their minds?
It must have been quite a blow to Tanya's ego when you turned her down.
That's probably why she's going on a rampage right now.
We should keep our guards up
because I don't think someone like her would stop at this.
What do you mean?
I'm afraid she won't hesitate to thoroughly squash us,
and take Next as her own, like Granddad said.
Directed by Ekkasit Trakulkasemsuk and Pantip Vibultham
Hey there, my very talented favorite journalist.
Oh, you know me too well, bestie, if you can tell right away I have a favor to ask.
But I'm not just asking you, you know?
I'll give you something for the trouble, like usual.
I want you to write something about how Next won't likely compensate for the leak.
No one will sue you.
It's not a lie if they really didn't take any actions after promising they would.
You're just speeding up the process of justice as a journalist.
Maybe come up with something that might...
make a few hundred people show up to protest in front of their office.
I'm sick of Chanon's hesitation.
I don't want to wait anymore.
Get this done for me as soon as possible, and I'll wire you the reward.
(Share Purchase Agreement)
People affected by the leaked data incident are showing up outside of Next Innovation.
I think Tanya has started.
What are we waiting for, then?
I'm afraid I can't take action in Chanon's place
since I am not the CEO of the company.
But it is not too late for you all to vote for me to be in charge.
If they work together, there's nothing to worry about.
We will all make you proud, Grandpa.
I know this might make you feel uncomfortable,
but I want her to be a part of our family again.
Neeraaumpan.