The
Practice of Unpretentious
Episode 15
Crane.
I miss you.
You did better than she did.
proven
Where is he?
Boss Qin
Qin,
At least sleep a little bit,
Don't get angry.
Qin
Get away from me.
Day & night
Episode 18
Thank you, really.
Your
небольш
contribution to our Longda
this year
is the 4th already.
Let me tell you, Mr. Zhang,
our education
is actually
quite difficult
to make money.
I really admire you.
Today,
you have done a great job for Longfan University.
Thank you.
I'm very grateful
for all you've done
for Longfan University.
Education is the foundation.
But actually,
in education,
there are many times
that we really need someone like you
to help us.
If there were
more excellent entrepreneurs like you,
I think
we...
Let's toast to you
with this.
Mr. Zhang,
you're too kind to me.
I'm sorry.
I just did
something that I could do.
I can't say anything.
Besides,
I donated to Longfan University.
Who doesn't know that Longfan University
is led by Professor Bu.
All young people are elites.
I think my money
is worth it.
Let me.
Mr. Zhang,
first of all,
I want to tell you something.
Longfan University
is not under my leadership.
And there is another thing.
I really hope
there are more people like you.
The people we train
are all elites.
Just like you,
you can contribute to society.
I'm not an elite.
I'm just a businessman.
You're not just a businessman.
I heard
you've done a lot of charity work, right?
Three years ago,
you also founded
an orphanage, right?
What's the matter?
Our society
is also grateful to you.
Mr. Zhang,
you're really
a good person.
I think it's my pleasure
to be friends with you.
So today,
let's
have a good chat
and have a good time.
Let's have a good chat
and drink.
After drinking,
you don't have to drive back.
I'll find you a driver.
Mr. Hu,
I tell you,
my license plate is in Longfan.
No one will check it.
Mr. Zhang,
it's not about who checks it or not.
If something really happens,
it's irresponsible
to you and others.
If something really happens,
we should spend some money.
It's not about spending money.
Well,
don't be offended by what I said.
What if
I pretend to be a dead man
and die?
Mr. Fu,
there are many ways
for people like us.
What ways?
Since we've drunk so much,
I'll give you a place.
We'll talk about it later.
Okay.
If it's really so unlucky,
we can find someone to make it up to.
It's just spending more money.
We can solve everything with money.
It's not about money.
It's about money.
If we can find someone to make it up to,
how much will it cost?
Two million.
Is it enough?
You can get rid of it.
Mr. Hu,
this is the current society.
I can't sacrifice myself
for someone who doesn't matter.
It's impossible.
If you spend money,
you can
escape the law.
You can leave with your life.
You can do nothing.
You can...
Listen to me.
If society
loses its business like mine,
how will society move forward?
Let me tell you.
How much money
will my charity organization donate?
How many people will my company support?
If I have to take legal responsibility
for a small mistake,
my company will face the risk of bankruptcy.
Do you know how many people will lose their jobs?
Are you trying to kill me?
No.
Listen to your logic.
Grant the journalism
as you Zak Multi ponytail.
But if I did
this,
I will be fair to others.
Do you know
There is also such a saying
In the face of law
It should be equal
If it's really like that
Do you think it's fair?
What are you talking about? I don't understand
Between people
Shouldn't there be a price?
Mr. Zhang
I'll call you Mr. Zhang again
Do you really think you are a charity?
If I'm not wrong
Seven years ago
You used this method you said
To kill a little girl
You didn't spend a lot of money at that time
You let people go to the crime
If your memory is not so bad
You should remember
What is the girl's last name?
Her last name is also Bu
This is a dragon
I think there are several names
You tell me
Did you do it?
Did you let people go to the crime?
I don't want to talk
What are you doing?
You are recording
Yes
I want to say
Since you already know the truth
Then I apologize
You tell me
What compensation do you want?
How much money do you want?
You are lying
It's not about money
It's about money
It's because of you
I lost my daughter
I lost everything in my life
You are a kind person
You are punished with your intelligence
You know
You bastard
Are you okay? What do you want?
Surrender
You are punished with your intelligence
You want me to surrender?
I tell you it's impossible
Don't go
You are crazy
Surrender
Dong Summer
Chief Qu
I know
this thing
is really hard to get over
So I'm here to tell you
that you actually
It must look awful to me, doesn't it?
I grew up in an orphanage
The people around me
are leaving me alone.
I thought I was used to losing.
But I'm not.
It's not honest.
She told me so much about the past.
I should have known she would do that.
I've studied psychology for so many years.
I've done so many people's test.
But I can't even
understand my own teacher.
Qin Ming.
I know you're sad.
I'm sad too.
But now,
you can't be immersed in your own emotions
in this way.
It won't help you in any way.
And you won't be honest.
We're the doctors.
I just want to find the murderer.
Don't you want to?
Qin Ming.
Without you,
I can't do it alone.
Whole Cู่ng.
Just bring Tang Ci back to the prison.
Yes, institute.
Yes, chef.
Chef Lin,
the Blend heavy pulled a report
towards Duan County
with the dump of Han Qianfeng.
Our guys
are monitoring the beast precisely.
The biscuits look
like Han Qianfeng
from distance.
Ask him to bring Han Qianfeng back to the prison.
And
tell the mestYU file.
protective team.
That's it.
I'm in Hanning Park.
There's no one here.
How's Qin?
Okay. I'll send someone to check.
Shiyu.
Help me look after Qin.
Why did you break up?
When was the last time you met?
What was the last thing she said to you?
Did she contact you recently?
Then help me recall.
During the time you and her were dating,
did she tell you anything special?
Tang Sisi.
You were her ex-girlfriend.
Such a close relationship.
You probably don't know her at all.
I hope you know.
If you know anything that you can hide,
you can call me a coward.
That's all for today.
If you need anything, I'll contact you.
But if she contacts you,
and tells us in time,
that's the only way you can help her.
Chief Qin.
If you can trust me,
I'll do it.
Rest in peace,
Qin準備好了
到發票了
如果沒事,
我 Drake
看看你們兩個
有 stiff  됩니다
Si Ini
you check check
anderen teams
If there are anyetz그렇
take us as bait
if there areHz
go ahead
Brother Lin, this is the letter from Professor Fu.
Who sent it?
Professor Fu.
I'm going out.
I'm Puping.
I killed Zhang Jun.
As a professor at Longfan University Law School,
I know the law and break the law.
I didn't regret it.
Instead, I held on to my lucky mind
and made things complicated.
At the same time, I made a lot of trouble for the public security officer.
I apologize to you here.
Secondly, as a teacher,
I didn't make a lot of trouble for the public security officer.
Instead, I committed an unforgivable crime
for my own grudges.
No matter what the reason is,
I shouldn't challenge the power of law.
So in front of the law,
I'm willing to accept any punishment.
Thank you.
Tang Sisi?
Hello?
Animal nutrition
Nutrition is the instinct of animals.
In the natural world,
it is always a big show of animal nutrition.
Whenever there are animals,
many animals will come to fight for the best time.
Why is the door not open?
What are you doing?
We are going to buy gold.
Why are you here?
I'm so excited.
I can't stand it.
I'm afraid I can't sell it.
When will the door be open?
My brother has been working on this for a long time.
Why?
It's so hard to buy gold.
Auntie, who is still in line?
You can buy gold on your phone.
You can download the gold wallet app and see the price at any time.
It's very convenient to buy and sell on your phone.
The most important thing is that you can make extra profit by buying gold here.
I'm so excited.
Look, my business is going well.
It's so convenient.
I don't have to be in a hurry to party anymore.
Yes.
Gold wallet can buy gold and make money.
Really?
Go to the gold wallet and buy gold.
Why?
Why would you install so many ​​g shake-tuk
Renaissance
That's awesome.
I'm going to my mother's house.
Someone is here.
Really
Do you have to?
So many béiene lay in зас
Is it possible?
Not really.
But it's not certain if he will come back to get something important.
Maybe a lunatic like him will take the risk.
Let's just think about it.
A person like him who is intelligent
shouldn't make such a mistake.
So you mean
we are stupid to do this now?
No, we are...
Hush.
Can you see the face of the hater?
Hello.
Are you the director of the troupe,
Liu Da?
Yes.
I'm the legalist of Longfan Public Security Bureau.
My name is Qingming.
I came to ask you some questions.
Sure.
I've been watching this troupe for over 20 years.
There are many things in this troupe.
I know a little bit about them.
Tell me.
What's your background?
I want to ask you, He Guangyu.
Do you know him?
Yes.
Who doesn't know him?
He was in jail.
When he first joined the troupe,
he was still a young man.
We knew him.
When he first joined the troupe,
he had a good business.
He was a good man.
He jumped off the building and committed suicide.
He was in jail.
Look at him.
Do you know why he was in jail?
He was fighting.
He was drunk and fought with someone.
He almost killed someone.
What happened after that?
Is he out now?
Or is he still in jail?
He's out.
He was out last year or the year before.
After that,
I haven't seen him again.
Why?
Maybe he went to work in Guangdong.
I heard him talking.
Do you know
where he lived after he was released?
I know.
It's just...
It's just a turn forward.
Not far.
Go.
You're right.
He feels comfortable
and has a good place to stay.
Search carefully.
There should be a dead person's finger print.
Captain Lin, I found it.
Look at the clothes.
Thank you for coming, Shiyu.
Why are you thanking me?
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
What's on your mind?
Nothing.
Just tell me.
Don't hold it in.
We broke up.
When did that happen?
A few days ago.
Sisi,
you told me
such a private thing.
That means you trust me.
Maybe you can't hear
what I'm saying.
But I want to tell you,
no matter what happens,
we can change our perspective.
Sometimes, he's not that bad.
Shiyu,
I want to know
if he broke up with me
because he was afraid of dragging me down.
It's important that
we figure out something first.
What kind of person
deserves our love?
deserves to be loved?
Sisi,
Han Tianfeng is not worth it.
But when we were together,
when I was with him,
I thought he was a very gentle person,
a very,
a very delicate person.
Once we had a fight,
I was very angry,
and he came up
and touched my hair.
At that time, I thought
he also liked children very much.
He also,
Sisi, calm down.
Han Tianfeng is not worth it.
Did you hear it clearly?
He is a police wanted criminal.
How many lives did he carry?
You can't be together.
I'm sorry.
Maybe what I'm saying
is not appropriate now.
But you have to know
that once he finds you,
I hope you can tell me at once.
I'm sorry.
Lin Hao.
What's wrong with you?
Look.
The wall
has a problem.
Come and get the hammer.
Yes, cook
Here
I'm sorry.
Dr. Niu.
How did you find this place?
I see.
You're here to save that female forensic doctor.
No?
What do you mean?
What's wrong with you?
Is she really your girlfriend?
Where is she?
You should call her.
Go back.
Be careful on the way.
Call me when you get home.
Let's go. Bye.
Bye.
Go.
The evidence may might be here.
Trust me.
Goodbye, Director Tong.
We'll replica it.
No.
ated does not know to give the direct answering.
until it's under our eyes.
Give me one.
I found the blood donation bag
on the carpet in the office of the army.
It's already out.
It's indeed Zhang Jun's.
I put the important
unauthorized book in my pocket.
Tan Jun took it away.
What did he do?
Zhang Jun was killed.
The real murderer
is not Qin Daofu.
The board of directors has held a meeting.
The first decision is to
expel Hu Bin and Han Tianfang from the agricultural university.
I want to turn myself in.
Sorry.
The adviser is gone.
You found him.
What do you want to say?
Answer me.
What's wrong with you?
Qi Lin.
The adviser has been in the office for 24 hours.
Why are you not anxious at all?
The key to victory
is to have the mentality.
We can't go back to the point.
It seems that his father
is not missing at all.
What should we do now?
Wait for him to come to me.
Are you sure
he will come to you?
I turn myself in.
I want to enter the name of Qin.
Qin.