The Long Ballad
Episode 35
Miss Jiang is indeed a good woman.
She can even gamble in the capital
and enter the world of no one.
I really admire your beauty.
I'm just lucky
to have some tricks to trade for money.
You're too modest.
I entered the world at the age of 20.
I've been in the world for ten years.
I've never met anyone like you.
But I've never seen anyone like you.
Your majesty is good at sitting on the ground.
You're talented.
You even know how to eat fire.
You can't fight, you can't kill,
you can't hold on to people.
Now that I know I'm good at it,
why don't you join me?
What can you do?
I've already figured out the map,
the time and route of the maid.
Tonight, I can count the resources
and hand them to you.
That's one thing.
Second, you'll gamble tonight.
It's obvious that you're not interested in gambling.
The key is to check the money
that you've spent with me.
With your ability,
you must have checked the bank,
but you didn't act.
I think you can't do it alone.
Someone needs to help you.
It's very risky.
Think about it.
I'm not afraid of danger.
As long as I can save Qingtai.
She's just a maid.
Is she worth it?
To me,
Qingtai has never been a maid.
She's a family member.
Can you play the flute?
I know the rules,
but I don't play it often.
Come to the study tomorrow.
I'll teach you.
There are five pieces of the chess piece.
The gambler will play the chess
according to the number of pieces.
The higher the number, the better.
I can tell you clearly
that the owner of the gold and silver workshop
is the current Crown Prince.
If a maid can
make a scene on his territory,
she will definitely lead him to confront you.
Then everyone's eyes
will be on you two.
I can go to the bank
to investigate.
It's your turn.
You'll lose this game.
Okay.
Five pieces of each.
The first three pieces,
I'm three black,
the chess piece is three white,
and the rest two pieces.
If I get the same color of the bull,
it's all black.
If I get two white,
it's also the same color.
They're all the same color.
One is sixteen points,
one is fourteen points.
One is a lot.
This is the worst case.
But four black and one white
are also eleven points.
You want to win me,
unless you get the red.
Although the red is high,
the probability is very low.
So no matter how this game is combined,
it's all my idea.
That's right.
Others play chess,
they all think it's luck.
But they don't know that before the game,
they can analyze the results of the previous round,
and then analyze the next time
the probability of the color.
If you don't forget,
you can practice a little bit,
you can be more generous in the gambling room.
This time,
I choose five.
Add it.
It's a
You're cheating.
Where's the evidence?
I saw it clearly just now.
Yours is not a roucai at all.
What you see is not important.
What is opened
is the key.
With your ability,
it's enough to deal with ordinary gamblers.
But to deal with the people we want to deal with,
it's not enough.
Why is it a roucai again?
You want to attract the attention of the crown prince,
you have to be like me,
do as you please.
The truth is different.
I want you to learn to play chess in three days.
Combine with your ability to count,
you can hold the crown prince
and fight for me.
Continue.
Don't use force.
Your palm should relax,
leave space for the wooden frame.
But the root of the palm,
the root of the finger,
must be strong.
Don't shake it.
Feel how my hands move.
I found the feeling.
It's still a secret.
I'm not a man.
I'm a man.
Now your level
is enough to deal with ordinary gamblers.
But only the luck
shows some flaws.
What flaws?
Think about the gambler's room that day.
What did you see
in the gambler's room?
They all wear masks
and can't see clearly.
Although they wear masks,
their eyes won't lie.
Think about it again.
The gambler's room.
I know.
It's the eyes.
The real gambler
won't think like me
with one eye open.
They are all greedy.
Yes.
Ordinary gamblers
won't notice
the opponent's mistake.
But we are going to deal with the crown prince.
He is suspicious, cunning and a man of the world.
Your small flaw
is enough to get us to make a move.
If I'm old
but my eyes are like a newbie,
the crown prince will be suspicious.
The crown prince likes gambling and color.
The trick that you used
to me before
can be useful.
You mean
I'm trying to seduce you?
I'm not interested
in an ill-mannered woman.
You are a little bit of a thief.
I know the people who are afraid of the rich.
That's all for today.
I'm going back.
Have you thought it through?
You will get me involved in the fight with the crown prince.
If you regret it,
you can leave now.
I won't.
Let's go.
Why are you going to the water today?
This time, you and I
are going to the water.
You are the one
living overseas.
Where is the water?
It's back in my Flint.
I came back
from the
ancient summer mountain.
You must've known
all the places
which are full of fishIES!
I'll take a look at it secretly after I enter the gambling house.
I have news.
The crown prince has been going to the gambling house these days.
Your task is to keep making money
until the crown prince is forced to gamble with you.
Huacai, five steps.
What?
Eat and get off the horse.
Huacai, five steps.
Kowtow and horse are all taken.
You have to be the first to win.
Are you still playing?
I admit defeat.
Let me do it.
Huacai, five steps.
Are you still playing?
Let me do it.
This lady won.
I admit defeat.
Master, something big happened.
Tonight, a young lady came.
She won eight times in a row.
Eight times?
I know.
The master is best at this.
Prepare.
How about you kill that young lady's concubine?
Take a look.
Here.
Anyone else wants to bet with me?
The young lady won nine times in a row.
She's the first to win.
Who dares to come up and touch your eyebrows?
Then I'll have to change the money and go home.
Let's go.
Wait.
So many horse.
This is a master.
It's said that wine is the best skill.
It's better than winning.
I'll try it.
Really?
What?
Are you afraid of losing?
Please.
Master.
Let's start.
Yes.
I say, third brother.
You're good at everything.
But you're not good at it.
My mother is just a maid.
I can't see it.
But I'm different.
You help me.
We two brothers work together.
And with my money,
the remaining officials in the court,
are you afraid of losing?
Second brother.
I'll tell you the truth.
I'm not interested in
your relationship with my brother.
I'm not interested in your relationship with my brother.
Don't go.
I haven't finished talking yet.
If you...
Your Highness.
The Guard of War by Prime Minister's side wants to see you.
I have something to do.
I'll go first.
Sit down.
He is Prime Minister's man.
He came to me with initiative.
Let him have a look.
Second brother.
Didn't you say you wanted to win the court?
Prime Minister
is the leader of the court.
Right?
Yes.
You're right.
Invite him in.
Yes.
Third brother.
I said,
as long as we two brothers work together,
we'll be a family.
Don't go.
Come on.
Your Highness.
Prime Minister asked me to say something to you.
It's about the Crown Prince.
Tell me.
Don't say it.
I didn't say it.
Prime Minister prepared a big gift for you.
In the gold and silver gambling house,
you can take it to him.
Gold and silver gambling house?
Third brother.
Come with me.
It's so lively.
It must be about the Crown Prince.
When I get his handle,
you can go with me.
If you don't go,
you'll hear what he said.
Be careful that someone will blame you for covering up.
Go.
You should have known it.
Another circuit
The去了 is at 14.
Brother Lv, you're great.
He is awesome!
Lu Cai, 16 points
Interesting
Cai Yalan
It's the first step to lock the dead body
The most important thing is
you need to get the jade pendant on her
Cai Cai, 11 points
It's a pity
Han Yuncai, 3 points
Toad
Dwash him
Nod his head
triumph
疑娘子果然好手气
Why I ask this
Hanshi
The rules of the gambling house
cannot be disobeyed
We go on
I'm a little tired of winning tonight.
If you want to bet with me,
why don't you bet on the heavens?
What do you want?
You are a real woman.
My jade pendant is of great value.
But if you want my jade pendant,
I want to trade it for yours.
Okay.
I'm not good at other things.
Then let's play a simple bet.
That's good.
I'm tired of seeing this.
Let's trade.
Oh no.
Shen Zan hasn't taught me this.
I promise.
Now you can see my fate.
Please.
Small.
One, one, three, small.
Nice hand.
I'll open this one.
This girl is as rich as the moon.
She is just like me.
Good opportunity.
Small.
Big.
Young Master, you look like a man.
Can you help me light the incense?
Give it to her.
The incense is here.
Don't sell the coffin.
Open it.
Do you want a big one or a small one?
I want a big one.
Two, one, two, small.
Wrong.
Big.
Small.
Bell.
The Shu family doesn't talk
The Ying family doesn't make a move
Continue
Investigate the Ying family
I only need one week
Before that, you must hold on
Shen Zaiye
From now on
I will try my best to delay the time
But I can't hold on for too long
So
You must be quick to stop
I guess
Two, three, six, big
Again
After three, four, five, six, big
Area verliered
It looks that you, a house on…?
It seems that any person can even win Devious Mudunchan
Brother-in-law mouse
It is time to you
I'm afraid you're out of luck
Yes
Think it over
I'll press the button
Then you should open it
Open it
If I lose again, I'll lose to Guangwei
One, two, three, go
Still bet?
I think the winner is decided
It's better for you to admit defeat
Boss, bad news
I'm not Shen Zaiye's horse
I have something important to do
If you don't want to bet
Wait, the last one
You don't have enough chips
What do you use to bet with me?
Bet on myself
Good
My lady's salary is really high
How much is it worth?
You can open it yourself
500,000 taels
The compensation for this time
It's only a million taels
If you agree
My lady is alone
Just on top of a city
I'm talking about gold
Gold
What are you doing?
One bet is a win
My lady is happy
What is Shen Zaiye doing?
I can't hold it anymore
So this is the good show that Prime Minister Shen said
Really wonderful
They say the Qin family is the richest family in the Qi
But second brother
You may not dare to take this game
Where did he get so much money?
This is your turn
I open
Please
Damn it
Shen Zaiye, why are you still not back?
Come in
I
I bet
Go
Big
I bet
You open
Five, four, three, two
Great
500,000 taels of gold
Even gold and gambling
It's the biggest bet
Yeah
Someone just told me that the bank was broken
The time was just after you and I bet
Now I think
You
I'm afraid you're not on the same side
Is it?
Go
Yes, yes, yes
Catch them
Kill them all
Go, go, go
Huaijin, why are you here?
Don't be angry
There are many people here
Let's go back to the room first
I'm the third
I have to find them
Moqi
I know
The woman and the bank's break-in
It has nothing to do with it
But I just saw it clearly
There's a man
next to the woman
Helping her
They must still be in this building
Don't hand them out
They've been catching me for three or four days
They don't kill me or kill me
They just change the place and then they do
What are they doing?
Eat a bun
Bun?
Who are you?
Zhan Lu, Zhan Lu
Zhan Lu
You little girl
I brought you food
But you hit me
You're not a big person
But you're not a small person
Then
How do you know I'm here?
The masters made a mess here
I have time to
Look for it from the third floor
Then what are you going to use to save me?
I stole it
You're so shameless
Don't fall on the ground
Thank you
The east camp orders
Search the place
There are peach blossom smoke
The woman is in a hurry
After searching, cut off the mess
Go, go, go
Next, next
Stop
Don't run
Raise your right hand
Next
Right hand, right hand
Raise your right hand
Then raise your right hand
Next, next
Right hand, right hand
They're looking for me
Although the cuffs and tattoos are painted
I can't wash them now
Hurry up
You go first
When you go out
Find a way to save me
Aren't you afraid?
I'm afraid
But now we're both dead
You must run out
Young master
Run
Save yourself first
You go quickly
I'll distract them
You are a stubborn person
If you are caught
This is not a bad thing
It will be a big deal
Come with me
Hide first
I hope the back hand I left before
Not a dead end
Back hand
By the way, second brother
Your people are not moving fast
Be careful to get the Prime Minister's attention
I'll bite you later
No hurry
Let them make a fuss
The bigger the fuss, the better
I can do it
Search them
Second brother
What are you doing?
Next
Go
Hurry up
Take her away
Go
Don't move
What should I do?
I'm going back to my mother's house
If the general knows
I have to beat you to death
You go into the closet first
Let's go to the side
Go quickly
Go in quickly
Hurry up
My lord
I'm afraid
It's good to be quick
Hurry up
My lord
Marquis of Xinyao?
I don't have time to care about these things.
If you dare to say one more word,
I don't mind
helping General Wei Yuan
to get out of here.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.
Don't let go of every corner.
Yes.
Open all those cabinets.