YoYo English Channel YouTube
Episode 16
Zhan Lu.
My lord.
Go and keep an eye on Qing Feng in Mu Wuying's mansion.
Get him here and interrogate him.
Qing Feng?
The blood marks on the scene of the crime
are the same as those of the Peach Blossom Blood Enforcer.
I've disposed of it in Third Prince's mansion.
It's a custom-made item.
Second Prince's death may be related to Third Prince.
Qing Feng is Mu Wuying's confidant.
We must get rid of him.
But I'm afraid that just by the blood marks...
That's enough.
Meng Huarui's case is over.
But Mu Wuying wants to use this to frame Fourth Prince.
I have to settle it with him.
Go.
On the night of Second Prince's death,
someone saw you enter the Spring Moon Tower.
You've been hiding in the dark.
When Meng Huarui left,
Second Prince was only injured.
Third Prince arranged for you to kill him.
I was right.
If you don't confess,
Third Prince can afford to bear
the consequences of your death.
I'm innocent.
I really don't know.
Prime Minister,
I've lost my job.
Qing Feng committed suicide.
Qing Feng is dead.
Only the heavens and the earth know about this.
You know about it and I know about it.
How would Mu Wuying know about it?
I'm innocent.
I didn't kill Second Prince.
He killed himself.
I'm innocent.
Meng Huarui.
First Miss,
I beg you.
I'm innocent, First Miss.
Please save me.
I'll be your mother's maid.
I beg you.
I have my parents.
Please save me, First Miss.
My father is weak and my mother is sick.
They can't let the people they love go to waste.
They're all members of the Meng family.
I won't let them down.
Don't worry.
Thank you, First Miss.
Brother,
the moon you saw that day
was as strange as tonight.
Meng family is so big.
It can't fill up as many lives as it can.
But it's very small.
When I saw you leave,
I thought it was no longer home.
But it's very small.
Don't worry.
You have to protect the Meng family even if you have to sacrifice your life.
I will protect you to the end.
Summon Meng Youxiang to the front.
I'm not a good steward.
You're so rude to the Meng family.
How dare you buy the exam?
Please punish me.
I'm willing to
resign myself to the position of chief examiner.
I'll retire and return to my hometown.
I hope you can allow me.
You said the same thing when Huaijin made a mistake.
You said you would resign twice a year.
I think you can't hold the official seal well.
The Meng family is the first family in the Great Qi.
There are many people in the family.
There are inevitably some unfilial children.
I'm old.
I know I'm busy with official affairs.
I will not be afraid of anything.
Yes.
Your family is the first family in the Great Qi.
There are many people in the family.
Officials climb up.
They can't avoid your family.
For a hundred years,
whoever is the king will depend on your family.
I definitely dare not.
Actually, it doesn't matter to you
if you're the first family in the Great Qi.
But have you ever thought
if you're no longer the first family in the Meng family,
do you think the Qin family and the Duan family
will let you rest in the future
or kill you
so that your family will have no chance to rise again?
Meng Zhongyan,
so this Xiang Yin,
do you accept it or not?
It's up to you.
Shen Zaiye,
you dare to arrest my people in broad daylight?
Third Prince is the first son of the Great Qi.
Third Prince, please calm down.
On the day of the second prince's death,
someone saw Qingfeng in Chunyue Brothel.
There are also Qingfeng's footprints in the secret room.
Second Prince,
I'm here to buy jade pendant.
Get out.
I know that jade pendant is a good thing.
I also know that you've sold a lot of people.
You...
You have to sell it if you don't sell it today.
I'll see what you can buy.
I'll buy it.
The footprints left in the secret room
are also the same as Qingfeng's.
But please rest assured, Your Highness.
Since Qingfeng is your confidant,
I will treat him well.
Treat him well?
You're using torture, aren't you?
Yes.
Qingfeng knows a lot.
You're really going to use torture?
Whether it's going to use torture or not,
we both said it.
His Majesty said it.
Since the crown prince fell off the horse,
His Majesty only has three princes.
If he knows that
Third Prince killed the second prince
and then gave the fourth prince the throne,
I wonder how cruel His Majesty is.
You really want to go back on your word
and regret it
and let the peach blossom die?
I did promise Meng family
not to pursue this case.
But I haven't said
my conditions to you.
What else do you want?
I want Third Prince to
withdraw from the imperial examination.
I thought you would continue
to ask me for the root solution.
Do you have
such an important thing?
So,
you'd better do something
that you can do.
Wenjin,
remove the ring from the fourth prince's ring.
Continue to be the chief of the imperial examination.
Your Majesty,
you asked the third prince
to be the chief of the imperial examination with the fourth prince.
Now you want two chiefs to be the ministers.
I forgot.
Two chiefs in the imperial examination.
If the crown prince is to be the teacher,
it will be troublesome.
Father, don't worry.
I am willing to withdraw from this imperial examination.
Withdraw?
It's a good job
that many people can't expect.
Why?
Father,
I was too confused before.
I just
wanted to help you.
Besides, you know
I'm not here.
And the fourth brother
is a little higher than me
in both academic and financial matters.
Among many students,
he has a good reputation.
It's right for the fourth brother
to be the official.
It seems that the study is successful.
I am very glad
that the world is not in a dispute.
Father, you flatter me.
I'll leave first.
Your Highness.
Qingfeng's spirit uncle
has been sent back to the mansion.
Prime Minister has selected
the best official for him.
Prime Minister asked me to
pay him a visit.
Qingfeng's son
is also a little regretful.
Shen Zaiye,
you blocked my way today.
In the future,
I will make him
your sword.
I'll be back.
This is for you.
Qingtai left Daqi Hospital.
I don't know
if he is safe
to reach the star state of Beiyuan.
Did you find Changjue?
How is Changjue doing?
How far is it
from the star state of Beiyuan?
Not far.
Just walk out of the desert.
Is there a military camp
in Beiyuan nearby?
I don't know.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
I will find Changjue.
If there is any change
in the valley,
it will become
the backbone and the backbone of Changjue.
If we can find out
the origin of the rain,
we may be able to
return to the main place.
But now there is no source of solitude.
We need to find an assistant.
The water is boiling.
Why is Prime Minister Shen here?
The imperial examination is urgent.
If we don't pack up,
we may not make it in time.
Besides, as an examiner,
I can clean the place
and prevent people from
stealing the five coins.
Thank you, Prime Minister Shen.
It's my life's grace.
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
You shouldn't be so cold.
Gu Wu Xia,
don't just thank my brother.
This is the person
you should thank the most.
I'm relieved to see you safe and sound
Princess
You
You're still alive
Of course, Princess
I'm just pretending, okay?
But where have you been these days?
It's a long story
Don't ask so many questions here
You can't remember everything
We have something to do, right?
Let's go
Jiang Tau-hua, help my brother
How are you feeling after you went back that day?
I'm fine
Thank you for your concern
That's good
I have something to ask you to help me find out
What is it?
I overheard the Third Prince calling the Empress Lv as A'Hua
And the bracelet of the Empress Lv is also a treasure
I really don't understand the relationship between them
As far as I know, the Third Prince has never been out of the country
After the
Imperial Examination, she left the palace and moved to Shunjing Palace
I've never heard of a woman in the palace
When I was young, the Empress Lv had been in the North Court
She was in charge of the court
Since then, she should have no chance
to meet the Third Prince in the Great Qi
I sent a spy to investigate the Empress Lv secretly
Before she entered the palace in the North Court, she was so mysterious
She was a fraud
So I suspect that the Empress Lv was a member of the Great Qi Palace
I'll stay here during the Imperial Examination
But I'll send my men to investigate this matter carefully
Don't worry
No hurry. Thank you, Prime Minister Shen
After the Imperial Examination, I'll try to contact you
I'll leave now
What's going on between them?
Zi Yuan, don't listen to the court
My brother used so much effort to save you
You don't want to repay my brother
Do you have any conscience?
Do what you should do
I'll take care of the rest
I'll go back to the palace
Repay himер
warned
If this applies to one of my men,
you will have the best repayment
Prime Minister
There's a big thing to find out about Doctor Bai
Be quick
which is extremely rare, yet bombastic
In fact, in daily consumption
it will only drop poison
and perish the toxic substance in the
windows around the date down
In my opinion, if the flower is poisoned
it may deliver a new life
Okay
Before you entered the palace
you had to wearactly
and
strictly check
there must be no fraud
in this case
If you find out
that Qin Hui is being bribed
you can tell me at any time
I have asked my father for the imperial edict
and found out that
the imperial edict was rejected
I think you all know
about the leak
in the previous examination
If this happens again
I have asked my father for the imperial edict
I will be the one
to give the question
You are wise, my Lord
Your Highness, you are a good lawyer
All the students, please enter
These Hanmen students
will be the future of our Qi
There will be no more
tragic events like Brother Jiao Han
in the future
The bright future
that Mr. Wei Ming expected
will come
You think he is your brother
Did he ever be close to you?
Although he is not
very close to me
he is not bad
in his daily life
It's normal
Are you serious?
Are you a child?
You are not young anymore
You should know your place
The one who takes the enemy
will never give up
until he is dead
If you don't give the order
you will be punished
Hua, you are so cruel
You are so cruel
I will not let you down this time
Go back to your home
Father, the park you saved
that year
is now in full bloom
In the future, Hanmen
will be the most important
in the court
Your wish
I have fulfilled
for you
One day
I will help the Xie family
Please rest assured
Go
Prime Minister
During the period of the court's closing
You are so cruel
I played this song
for Mu Wu Xia
You are not qualified to listen
Shut your ears
Miss Qingying
During the period of the court's closing
You are playing music here
Is it inappropriate?
But I want to see you
You don't let me in
You have been working so hard recently
I can only play the zither outside
and let you relax
But
If you do this
you will disturb others
Okay
Wait a minute
How about this?
I will play a song with you
What do you think?
You can play the zither?
Okay
I will play a song with you
I will play the zither
Okay
Hey there
I'm here
Lord
People you asked to know
You have got some friends
was in the palace again
There was a maid by her side
Her name was Hua
Back then, the third prince
was killed by her
Princess Jinrong died of sudden illness
The servants
were unable to get close to her
Only Hua
was very different from the others
Get out
Why are you still here?
Your Highness
I'm here to take care of you
Sister takes care of me
What's your name?
My name is Hua
I don't know what that maid Hua is capable of
The third prince was unable to get close to her
But I don't know why
one day, she suddenly disappeared
There's another strange thing
When I was going to the Zongzheng Mansion
to check the records
I found that all the records about Hua
were missing
Thank you, Eunuch Wen
Shen Zaiye is so good
He's been in the dark for long
Who leaked the news about Hua?
Your Highness
I've been with you for years
I've never been betrayed by you
I can see it
These are the past between me and Hua
I've been hiding them for years
Hai Jue
Look here
Here
Thatbackground
It's not much
in the individual key
What is this?
How did Holy Master find out?
Could it be that Qing Feng told you before he died?
If Qing Feng told me about Hua before he died
Grand Master Shen wouldn't have let me quit the imperial examination.
Your Highness, do you still remember the fire at the Purple Garden?
Grand Master Shen came very quickly.
The peach blossoms haven't bloomed yet.
Does the peach blossoms know anything?
The peach blossoms...
If this peach blossom hadn't been for holding Shen Zai Yan back
I would have let him die.
Bring the peach blossoms here.
Yes.
I greet Your Highness.
Miss Mo'er, you haven't seen me in a few days.
You look so good.
With Your Highness's care,
the servants in the manor are all very good to me.
They are all very good to you.
So they let you roam around the manor.
So you know what you should know and what you shouldn't know.
You remember what you should remember and what you shouldn't remember.
Your Highness, how could you say that?
Mo'er and my brother's lives are in your hands.
Even if I remember anything, I will never betray you.
Your beautiful face is really like a ghost in my eyes.
If I slip up here and ruin your face
I will be the one who will be punished.
do you think Shen Zai Yan will still love you and protect you?
What does Shen Zai Yan have to do with me?
I only pray that Your Highness can keep Chang Que and I safe for the rest of our lives.
If you want to save your life,
then use your own values
and let Shen Zai Yan be at ease.
Yes. I will go right now.
Your Highness, do you still believe him?
As long as the antidote and Jiang Chang Que are in my and A'Hua's hands,
then Jiang Tao Hua will never be able to turn into a wave.
He will always be Shen Zai Yan's weakness.
To avoid causing a disturbance, please stop investigating.
Does Third Prince suspect you?
Third Prince trusts me a lot now.
By the way, did you receive the letter from Qingtai?
Qingtai? Didn't he go back to the North Campus to find his wife?
Why would he send a letter to the Prime Minister?
If he sent me a letter, he would only send it here.
He has already left Yue Yu, but there is no news of him.
I can take the letter for you, but you have to answer one question.
What is it?
What exactly did you ask Qingtai to do in the North Campus?
If you send her there to kill someone and set the fire,
I am not afraid of being implicated, but I need to be prepared.
I just asked Qingtai to help me go to the North Campus to find the whereabouts of Chang Que.
Please rest assured, Prime Minister.
Where is Chang Que?
This has nothing to do with you, right?
Speaking of Chang Que, I found a letter that he wrote to you.
I have put it back in its original place.
Do you still remember Ange?
It was Qingtai. Qingtai told me about it.
I am sorry.
If you want to find Chang Que,
maybe I can help you.
Dr. Bai is developing a method to reduce the number of bullets.
Once it succeeds, you will no longer be controlled by the bullet.
Thank you for your help, Prime Minister.
What do you want to write?
As the left prime minister,
I have all the wealth and fame.
What can I do?
How about we share a meal together?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I just suddenly remembered
that we have never had a meal together without any thoughts.
Zhang Luo.
Prime Minister.
Inform the kitchen to prepare the ingredients.
I want to have some shrimps.
Prime Minister, do you want to steam them or sweet and sour?
I will inform them.
I will cook them myself.
I understand.
You did this for me.
I will taste it.
You are willing to cook with me?
You and I...
Prime Minister.
I can't smell the smoke.
Okay.
Wait for me here.
The leaves are in full bloom.
The flowers are blooming.
When the wind blows,
the flowers will be gone.
If so,
what will happen?
I don't know.
I will
send you out of the Bureau.
I will feel your love.
The moon and the sky are like a movie.
I want to be free.
No one can stop me.
Every year, you are by my side.
Time is short.
A momentary memory is like a long distance.
Your eyes.
The ink is like a knife.
It can cut through the black and white.
Even if it's a golden flower,
if you are by my side.
Zhang Lu.
Go to the Northern Plains and Xingzhou.
Find Qingtai and Changjue.
Qingtai is in the Northern Plains and Xingzhou?
Tao Hua sent Qingtai to find Changjue.
They are the two most important people.
There must be no accident.
But Prime Minister.
You have done so much for the princess.
She will not understand.
I don't need her to understand.
I will set out now.
Go.
Doctor Bai.
There is a miracle.
Prime Minister.
I use the acupuncture to reduce the toxicity.
I am taking the medicine to help with the blood.
One of the patients has not died for a month.
Where is it?
Take me to see.
Follow me.
The time is only the amount of the poison.
If you control the amount, you can use it to replenish the gas.
It seems that the acupuncture can only stop the time of the toxic gas.
Where is the toxic root of the peach-flavored elixir?
I will try another way.
I will go to the Northern Plains and Xingzhou.
Doctor Bai.
I am developing the root of the peach-flavored elixir for you.
Once you succeed.
You will not be controlled by the peach-flavored elixir.
I can't give her hope and let her down.
I am sorry.
Good.
He is indeed a talented man.
What is your order?
Now the course is only waiting for the wind to come.
I am going to the Northern Plains.
If you go to the Northern Plains, it will take a long time.
What about your work?
I have asked His Majesty to give the work to the Minister's Office.
You have been in the court for many years and never asked for leave.
This time you are going to find the medicine for the princess.
I also want to see the future of Lv Hou.
The ups and downs that I and the science bureau have experienced are also related to her.
With her character.
She has experienced such a big mistake.
She will never give up.
Take care of Wu Xia while I am away.
Don't worry, I will always be on guard.
Don't worry, Tao Hua.
I will bring the antidote back from the Northern Plains.
The flowers bloom, you know nothing.
The beauty of the flowers can't be ignored.
The flowers fall, the north wind blows.
The city is in a state of panic.
The petals are wet with the rain.
My heart is with the knot.
The flowers fall, the tears are in the heart.
The eyes are full of tears.
The heart is full of thoughts.
There is nowhere to tell.
The wish is struggling in the mud.
Regret is killing in despair.
I still hope that she can hold the flowers in her arms.
Even if I have to give the flowers to the song.
Who can take away the heart of the flowers?
Love and hate can only be taken away.
The flowers wither, the heart is broken.
There is no need to tell.
How can I still be crazy about him?
I'm not afraid to be underestimated
I'm just looking at what he said
It turns out that he has the answer to his curiosity