[English subtitles are available]
F-a-v-o-u-r-i-t-e.
Favourite.
Hello?
What are you doing?
I'm reviewing English.
Why are you talking like a thief?
Aren't you sick of me bothering you?
Oh c'mon.
You already called.
Can you stop pretending to be polite?
Aren't you gilding the lily?
Can you save the proverb
for your writing?
I'll hang up if you have nothing to say.
Hang on.
The college entrance exam is coming soon.
Are you nervous?
I would be lying if I say I am not nervous.
But
I think I have no regrets in my senior year.
I'll just do my best.
I believe you can make it.
I have a question for you.
What is it?
Well...
Nothing.
Why are you so hesitant?
So weird.
I'll tell you after the exam.
Isn't it just a few days away from the exam?
Why can't you tell me now?
Yes.
It's only a few days away.
Don't study too hard.
Go to bed early.
Good night.
What do you mean?
Check if my head is square shaped.
No.
Fine.
At the beginning of high school,
I took a photo here.
I thought
I'd taken another photo after graduation,
but I didn't expect
this day arrived so early.
It's really unreal to me.
After taking this photo,
we will drift apart.
Take it easy.
Sun Yat-Sen University
is not far from Yunhai University.
It's only two or three hours by car.
If you miss me,
come to see me there.
Why won’t you come to see me?
Haven't you been admitted by
Yunhai University?
Sun Yat-Sen University?
Come on.
Stand in the middle.
Everybody, are you ready?
Look at me.
Look at the camera.
Three.
Two.
One.
Cheese.
Why are you crying?
What are you crying for?
Attention, everyone.
Xu Linglong's crying
is quite brilliant.
After 10 or 20 years,
when you look at this photo,
you may not remember
the names of your classmates.
But you will always remember
the ugliest student who is crying
is Xu Linglong.
It is ugly indeed.
It's ugly. Don't cry.
In writing,
what is this method called?
Foreshadowing.
Exactly.
Come on. Let's take a photo.
Smile, everyone.
Is your head teacher handsome?
No.
Rabbit.
Did you sleep well?
Our student comes out.
Good.
So good.
Look at Rabbit.
Dad, mom.
I'm back.
Ling Chao, why are you back?
Your godmother is worried.
She asked Ling Chao to take two days off
to accompany you for the exam.
There's no need to take a leave.
Can Ling Chao take the exam for Rabbit?
Xiao Haishan, how can you say that?
Do you know many students
wear Chao's photos
as an amulet?
Pray for God's blessing.
We have a living God in our family.
Of course we need to pray for his blessing.
Am I right?
With the accompany of our living God,
you will definitely make it.
-Right, Rabbit? -Yes.
Have you got everything with you?
Okay, check it quickly.
Identity card, admission card, sign pen,
pencil, eraser.
Yes.
Okay, yes. Let's check it again.
Yes. Check it.
Okay.
Yes.
Did you wear the purple underwear
I bought for you?
Mom, that's too ugly.
How can you say that?
I bought it for you.
There's a check mark on it.
It brings good luck. You must wear it.
Let's go. I'll wear it.
Don't you know that underwear is so popular?
Many moms bought them.
Have you guys
worn it?
Yes, of course.
Certainly we have worn it.
Yes, definitely.
Have you all worn it?
Yes.
No matter what we do,
we stay
and work together
and strive for the best.
Strive for the best!
Strive for the best.
Let's have breakfast.
Yes. Come on.
My dear daughter, have a seat.
Try the breakfast I made for you. 100 marks.
-100-mark breakfast! -Yes.
100 marks. Try it.
Is it good?
Fine.
You guys try it.
Don't look at me like this.
We've already eaten. You...
Yes, enjoy your breakfast.
Yes, eat them all.
Dad.
The score of each Liberal Arts exam is 100,
but it's 150 for Chinese, Maths and English.
One.
The number five is missing.
Five is missing. Xiao.
Go looking for it. Five is missing.
Do you have any food that sounds like five?
Turtle!
Steamed turtle?
It can be steamed with soft-shelled turtle.
Do you have wax apple?
Wax apple, how about five-kernel mooncake?
Exactly, five kernel.
It's not five kernel. How about these...
Not five kernel. They're not here.
Five-kernel mooncake is not here.
Not here.
What should we do?
Got it.
Let's dance.
Dance?
Yeah, I'm good at dancing.
Let's dance together.
Let's dance. Come on.
Why don't we ride a bike?
With your luck,
on such an important day,
your bike will have a flat tire
or fall into a manhole cover
which couldn't be pulled out.
So it's safer to walk.
My luck is not that bad.
I think you're right.
It's not surprising
that this happened to you.
Sit here.
This dog has a bad stomach.
Maybe you should just wear my shoes.
Don't tell me you have athlete's foot.
Yes I have.
Ten-year athlete's foot.
Dogshit or athlete's foot.
It's up to you.
Okay.
Try walking a few steps.
Let's go.
Okay, give me my bag.
Wait.
What?
Be sure to read the questions carefully.
Sometimes you know how to solve a problem,
but you're careless.
You must be careful.
Besides,
if you can't solve a problem,
just skip it first.
Don't get stuck there.
Maybe when analyzing for the second time,
you'll have new ideas.
Okay.
What else?
By the way,
the most important thing is
that check your answer card carefully.
Last year, there is someone in our class...
Stop it.
You've said it too many times.
I've said it many times.
I don't know if you've listened to me.
But you must remember,
don't be nervous.
Also,
you've taken so many exams.
The college entrance exam
is just one of them.
I think you're the one who's nervous.
You've become so talkative all of a sudden.
Don't worry.
I'm not nervous at all.
Just wait for me outside.
I'm leaving.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Hello.
We are from Yidong Event Program Team.
I have a few simple questions for you.
I saw you seeing off a girl to the exam.
You look very close to each other.
Is she your sister?
No.
Today is the first day
of the college entrance exam.
Do you have any good wishes
for all the candidates?
Good luck everyone.
What a simple and powerful blessing.
The exam is finally over.
The last question is too difficult.
So difficult.
The college entrance exam is over.
Another school year has passed.
Everything in front of me
is familiar but also unfamiliar.
I seem to have
a very long dream.
A dream like a TV series.
Teacher.
In my dream,
I still remember
those math problems that I can't understand
no matter how hard I try.
And those inseparable friends.
Those gossips we talk
when we gather together.
Those first prizes that I can't get
no matter how hard I study.
Of course,
in my dream there are also delicious snacks
that we share with classmates.
Everything seems to have happened yesterday.
I finally understand,
the youthful time
is really like a one-way train.
It takes us all the way to the future.
We have enjoyed the tenderest spring breeze.
And we have seen
the most spectacular views in life.
However, this train can never
carry us back.
At this moment, I suddenly realized
this may be the last time for some people
to see each other in their lives.
After today,
I can no longer run down the corridor
in this school uniform.
And I can never enjoy
the sunset on the way home from school.
We will never be 16 or 17 years old anymore.
I know
that no matter how long a TV series is,
there will be an ending.
No matter how real a dream is,
it'll be waken up by the morning alarm.
I've only just left
but I'm already missing
those days
which are once-in-a-lifetime.
Is that her?
Rabbit.
How was the exam?
Not bad.
I think it's good.
If you come out later,
the ice cream's gonna melt.
Everyone else gives flowers.
Why are you giving ice cream?
You can't eat flowers.
You're right. You know me best.
Why did you come out so late?
How was the last exam?
Not bad.
The exam is over.
No more questions.
Yes.
Xiao, how about this?
I've booked a private room in restaurant.
Let's celebrate together tonight.
Mom.
Look at that tall and handsome boy there.
He was a senior in my school last year.
He's always the best.
Really exceptional.
Really? He's so amazing.
I didn't even notice
that you've grown so tall.
The look on your face
is idiotic.
By the way, let's take a photo together.
We didn't take when Ling Chao was graduated.
I've brought the camera here.
Okay, let's take a photo.
Get someone.
Come on, mate.
Could take a photo for us?
Of course, auntie .
Thank you.
-You're welcome. -Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Stand closer.
Three, two, one.
Cheese.
Dad, mom.
My ass is turning purple.
Take it easy.
Why are you making a fuss?
That's the color fading.
-Take it easy. -You...
You are wearing it too?
Did the colour fade?
Why is that window open?
Yes, go and take a look.
Okay.
Godfather, godmother.
I can't take too much time off from school.
I'm leaving now.
-Don't leave. -Okay.
You're wearing it too, aren't you?
Let me see.
Let me see your underwear.
What are you doing?
Let me see.
Hey, what are you touching?
Are you crazy?
Let me see if your ass is purple.
-What are you doing? -Let me see.
-Are you crazy? -Let me see.
What's wrong?
Don't move.
No. We're not wearing it.
You're the only one wearing it.
Well,
we're going to have a meeting?
I'll be there soon.
Xiao, let's play it next time.
Okay. Bye.
Next time. Okay.
What a pity.
You liars!
Yes.
Yes, that...
I'm not the only liar.
You're the only one I've told about this.
How did she know?
Well, when you called me just now,
I was already at your door.
I laughed too loudly
and she heard it.
How did he know that my ass turned purple?
Won't I be embarrassed?
I don't know.
I just knew it.
I've stepped into your home after that.
I didn't have time to commit the crime.
By the way, why are you here?
I’m here to give out wedding candies.
Wedding candies?
Are you getting married?
It's not me.
It's Mr. Xue.
Mr. Xue and Ms. Xiao are getting engaged.
Mr. Xue?
Yes.
He said
by the time he gets married,
his students can't get together.
So he asked me
to give out candies to the students nearby
to share the good news in advance.
I didn't expect Xue to win Ms. Xiao's heart.
Of course.
They were childhood sweethearts.
I heard
that in order to win Ms. Xiao's heart,
Xue went to the same university with her
in spite of the objections of his family.
But Ms. Xiao is one year older than him.
So what?
There is no such a rule
that a girl can't marry
the boy who is one year younger than her.
Xue Xiaoxiao. Xiao Xiaoxue.
It sounds like couple names.
Ling Chao and I
were childhood sweethearts too.
We share couple names.
It doesn't sound like couple names.
You are not good at Chinese, right?
We both have "Ling" in our names.
Ling...
Ling Chao and Xiao Tu...
They both have two characters in names.
One is "rabbit" and one is "grass".
Rabbits eat grass by their nest.
Perfect match.
You two can argue.
Why do you mention me?
You...
596.
Rabbit, you're amazing.
Look.
Purple underwear brought good luck, right?
Yes.
Good girl.
You are the first college student
in Xiao's family.
Yes. Great.
20 points higher than I expected.
What was the minimum passing score
of Yunhai University last year?
601.
How about
considering other universities?
Yes.
Medical University.
Medical University is good.
It's good for girls to study medicine.
Yes.
Let me think about it.
It's good.
Hello.
Did you check the exam results?
Is it bad?
596.
Isn't it nice?
The exam this year is quite difficult.
Your already did very well.
My score is five points behind
the minimum passing score of last year.
Ling Chao,
I can't go to Yunhai University, can I?
Take it easy.
Yunhai offered a journalism major this year
and it expanded enrollment.
The minimum passing score
is not very likely to rise this year.
You could apply for journalism major
be subject to professional adjustment.
You have a good chance of being admitted.
I don't agree.
Choosing university
is the most important in her life.
This time,
I can't let you mess things up.
How can you say that?
With her score,
if she wants to go to a better university,
she must go further away from home.
Don't you worry about her?
That's right.
Give it a try.
Maybe she could be admitted.
Besides,
these two kids will have companions
when they're together.
Yeah.
Ling Chao can take care of Little Rabbit.
Right?
Yes.
Xiao.
We are not familiar with
the university application process,
but the kids are familiar with it.
I think
we should let them make their own decisions.
Let her decide it.
Our Xiao Tu
has been following
Ling Chao's step since she was a child.
She will do whatever Ling Chao says.
I don't care
if it's anything else,
but applying for unversity is different.
I couldn't let her mess it up.
If we make a mistake on this,
who will regret for her?
Xiao Tu.
Let me ask you.
What do you think?
Don't be disturbed.
I want to apply for Yunhai University.
I did listen to
Ling Chao's analysis and advice,
but I didn't make this decision
under his influence.
The decision was made through consideration.
I can fill in several applications anyway.
I want to take Yunhai as my first choice.
Also, Journalism is my favourite major.
Dad.
This is the first time
I've made a big decision on my own.
I want to give it a try.
Okay?
Why are you in such a hurry?
Are you in a hurry to go home?
Are you really going back home?
Yes.
The train is in two hours.
No wonder you handed in exam paper early.
Master.
You made me anxious.
I didn't get the last question right.
Where is Guanjiu?
He won't come out
until the last minute.
Master is in a hurry to see his child bride.
What are you doing?
Are you in a hurry to reincarnate?
Child bride?
A beauty brings misfortune.
Beauty is overstated,
but misfortune is true.
I'm not at home.
I don't know if she can handle it herself.
I'm leaving.
See you next semester.
Okay.
Bye.
Execuse me.
Where is Master going?
Where is he going?
Come here, Sha.
Master was taken away by a demon.
Taken away?
So how's your application?
Just so so.
What is so so?
Well,
my dad didn't agree.
Didn't agree.
Have you argued with him?
Didn't you apply for Yunhai University?
Why are you yelling suddenly?
Did you apply for other university in Yunhai City?
Even if it’s not Yunhai University,
you could apply for another college there.
Why do you insist
to let me go to Yunhai?
Because...
Because I want to see you every day.
Didn't we used to see each other every day?
Because we used to see each other every day,
I've already taken your accompany
as granted.
The past dozen years
have been wasted by us.
I want to cherish every moment from now on.
Rabbit.
Do you understand what I mean?
You're really weird.
To avoid me in high school,
you skipped a grade.
Now you want me
to go to the same university with you.
Didn't you say we are gonna be together?
Even if we're not in the same university,
we can still meet during festivals.
Why festivals?
What if I say
I want to see you every day?
You...
I can't swim.
The water is shallow.
You can stand up.
You know this place too?
This place is really good.
What do you want to eat?
Help yourself. My treat.
Thank you so much.
The tiramisu is yummy.
The Dark Forest Cake looks good too.
Which one do you want?
You can order them both.
Both.
This is for you.
How do you know today is my birthday?
Isn't your birthday over?
June 20.
Today is my lunar birthday.
How do you know that?
Let me see.
You give me a ball.
What do you mean?
This is the graduation gift for you.
I see.
You mean
although Yunhai and Qingbei are far away,
but as the earth is a ball,
we will finally meet again someday.
Yes.
One of my other friends
said that too.
I think it's so romantic.
Jia Siwen,
you're so thoughtful.
I didn't get admitted by
Sun Yat-Sen University,
but Yunhai is also good.
I can be together with Xiao Tu.
You don't need to comfort me.
I'm not sad at all.
This ball is really cute.
Thank you.
I like it so much.
Xiao.
Congratulations.
Congratulations. Why do you bring me gifts?
Just bring your mouth is fine.
Don't say that.
Rabbit is the prospective journalism student
at Yunhai University.
We must celebrate it.
To be admitted.
The admission letter hasn't arrived yet.
What's the difference?
It's already released online.
Who dares not to admit our Little Rabbit?
Exactly.
Xiao,
Wenhui said
she wanted to hold a roadside banquet
in our community,
but I think
this is too ostentatious.
Too ostentatious.
There are many candidates in the community.
If you hold a roadside banquet,
won't you make a fool of yourself?
Change your shoes.
Okay.
Godfather, godmother.
Where is Ling Chao?
He caught a cold. I didn't ask him to come.
He didn't want to infect us.
Hasn't he had a cold for a while?
Exactly.
It's summer now.
How can he catch a cold?
But he's getting better.
At the end of a cold,
it is most contagious.
Don't worry about him.
Let's eat and drink.
When we go back home,
we'll bring him some leftovers.
That's it.
What are you talking about?
Here, the last dish. Come on.
Great! Wonderful!
I'll sit next to Rabbit. Sit here.
Have a seat.
Everything is so delicious.
Everything you cook
is delicious.
Yes.
Cheers!
Come on. Let's celebrate.
Yeah.
Together.
Come on. Together.
How about
giving him a call?
It's me pushing him into the lake.
But if he hadn't come closer,
how could I have done it?
How can a normal person
have a cold for two weeks?
How about
visiting him to see if he's fine.
Cheers. Another drink.
Another one. Come on.
Okay. Bottoms up.
Dad, mom, I need to go out.
Where are you going so late?
You...
Be careful.
Ling Chao.
Are you home?
Why he is not here?
Ling Chao.
I can't believe the book is here.
Here it is.
The cold and fiery atmosphere of the night
is gradually approaching.
The wall behind her is cold.
There's no turning back.
No.
Why should I hide?
Bath towel?
Clothes?
There's...
Oh no.
How long are you going to stay under my bed?
How did you know I was under the bed?
Next time when you act like a thief,
remember to hide your slippers.
Why did you take off your clothes?
Are you a pervert?
Who took off clothes?
I was going to wash them.
Are you kidding me?
Can you be reasonable?
You attacked me
but don't allow me to take revenge on you?
That's because
you were acting weird that day.
I felt a little guilty,
so I came to see if you've recovered.
You're pretending to be sick.
What are you tallking about?
I go into the water every day,
so I haven't recovered from the cold.
Why did you go into the water?
I'm learning swimming.
If
you throw me into the lake again,
what should I do?
Are you crazy?
Get up, you two.
We have to set off.
Can't get out of bed.
Dad, mom,
I don't want you to see me off.
I decided to go there myself.
It is my first time
to go on a long journey alone.
Xiao, your daughter ran away.
But don't worry.
I have paddles of happiness and wisdom.
I'll call you when I get there.
Love you.
Xiao Tu.
Today is the first day
of the college entrance exam.
Do you have any good wishes
for all the candidates?
Good luck everyone.
What a simple and powerful blessing.
What do you expect
from that girl?
I hope she can be admitted by my university.