[English subtitles are available]
How is the story going?
At least give us, the viewers,
an ending.
I'll follow this post.
Yes.
I can't believe I'm watching a drama on the Tieba forum.
Will you be together?
Family, I'm here to update.
After you said I like him last time,
I've been confused.
I was nervous and shy.
So,
I've been avoiding him these days.
I dare not answer his calls.
What should I do now?
I don't know if I've been too reckless lately.
I was able to ask her out,
but now she just disappeared.
How long has madam been like this?
72 hours.
That means our tricks
won't work on her.
If what you said is useful,
it won't be this useless.
But why did she hide?
If she doesn't like you,
she could just say it.
I know.
At this point,
you have no choice.
Just go to her
and ask her why she's avoiding you.
What if I scared her away?
I think
she blocking you
is the worst result.
But as long as she's still at school,
she won't cancel her account.
Sha,
you're really good at comparing.
But I think
since we can't act rashly,
let's boil the frog in warm water.
Let's boil the rabbit.
I'll meet first
and then boil the rabbit.
Thank you for today.
Not at all.
I'm just a freshman.
I am happy that
I can attend this kind of big event.
Your camera is heavy, right?
Give it to me.
No, I can do it myself.
Your camera was borrowed by the student council.
It's my duty to protect it.
Plus, your tripod is quite heavy.
Let me take it.
Here.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hello.
Who is the girl next to Jianghu?
Why is he helping her?
Senior.
I didn't expect you to be so popular.
It feels like everyone passing by knows you.
They are juniors from the student council.
Sometimes, it's a big trouble
memorizing names while attending all the events.
But you are different.
Your name is special
and unforgettable.
I'll get going then.
Bye.
Okay.
How is it?
She hung up.
Why didn't you answer my call?
Is your phone broken?
Yes.
Are you crazy?
This...
It's just fixed.
What do you want?
What can I do?
If you're here for your birthday present,
let me tell you,
I don't have much money left this month.
I advise you not to pick too expensive ones.
I want nothing.
I just want...
As long as you are not avoiding me...
Who is that?
Stole my line.
Doesn't he look like Jianghu?
This is boring.
Put your double chin back.
What are you doing?
I'm looking for a book.
Are you sure it's this book?
Is anyone sitting here?
Yes.
Study hard.
Do you often use this sentence...
Eyelashes
are longer than mine.
Nose.
According to Jiang Juanjuan's fangirl terminology,
it shapes like a slide.
Mouth
is heart-shaped.
What?
You snored.
I never snore when I sleep.
Then why did you fall asleep while reading?
I came to take the seats at six.
Unlike someone
who sleeps until ten o'clock.
Why don't you...
get back to sleep.
Are you worried about me?
I'm not.
What are you doing?
Ling Chao is popular again.
This time, it's a love confession wall.
There is such a handsome guy in our school.
I don't believe it.
Unless you give me his WeChat.
Stop thinking about it.
I have his WeChat.
I never post it on Moments.
I was there too.
Why crop me out?
I can't shop anymore.
I've been shopping with you all day.
My feet are going to have blisters.
Hang in there.
I'll buy you milk tea later.
If you can't find a suitable gift this year,
maybe next year,
the great laboring people
will invent one.
There are birthdays every year.
You...
This shop is nice.
Let's go in and have a look.
Take a look.
This knitting wool...
Knitting wool like this...
If you are knitting socks,
this roll is enough.
You must buy two rolls.
This is very suitable.
It's beautiful.
Look.
The cerise and pink
suit you very well.
Are you
knitting a scarf
to give it to Ling Chao?
So what?
You think I can't learn?
Is that the problem?
Girl.
Your mind is very dangerous.
Miss, do you want knitting wool?
Are you knitting a scarf for your boyfriend?
The black one sells very well.
It's comfortable and won't pilling.
Many girls in your university city
buy it.
He is not my boyfriend.
He will be your boyfriend after you finish knitting.
I understand.
Me too.
How is it?
Are you happier now?
If you
are unhappy,
just tell me.
Don't be upset alone.
Got it?
Yes.
It's getting late.
Go to bed early.
Good night.
What are you laughing at?
Am I?
What about you?
You are not sleeping in the middle of the night,
and you are here knitting a scarf for your boyfriend.
Why do you all say that?
Do you think I will knit a scarf for Ling Chao
as a birthday gift?
I don't think so.
It does seem a little strange.
Then why can you do it?
Because Ling Chao and I...
Are sister
and brother?
I just don't understand
what it is to like someone.
I checked online,
but there is no standard answer.
Didn't you like
Xu Linglong's cousin?
No.
That's admiration.
Ling Chao is different.
But I can't tell what's different.
Let me ask you another question.
Do you have someone you like?
When I asked you this question,
who was in your mind?
Please answer.
Ling Chao.
That's it.
Sister,
I'll make it clear today.
You have a crush on him.
Listen to me.
You'd rather break up at the end
than miss any chance.
But if...
Don't tell me
you're afraid that you can't be friends anymore.
You need friends?
I'm going to sleep.
You just need to knit
that love nicely.
Bye.
Ling Chao.
What is it?
This is for you.
I knitted it myself.
I wanted to give it to you on your birthday.
I can't wait.
I don't wear a scarf.
You're right.
The temperature has been pretty high these days.
But the temperature will drop next week.
It will be useful.
I mean,
I can't accept it.
It's not about the weather.
It's my fault.
I thought you would understand
even if I don't say anything.
I have to tell you now.
What's wrong?
Don't cry.
Ling Chao said
he's not afraid of the cold.
He never wears a scarf.
All right.
I like...
I don't want to hear it.
What's wrong with you?
I said I don't want to hear it.
Calm down
or keep your voice down.
Then tell me,
I'm different
from other girls, right?
We grew up together.
It's different.
What?
What kind of attitude is that?
How could you say that?
Fine, I'll grant your wish.
I won't deceive myself anymore.
I won't bother you anymore.
Are you satisfied?
All right.
Dad.
This scarf is for you.
My dear daughter.
I love it.
Thank you.
Really.
My little girl is so sweet.
But at my age,
wearing white
is too plain, isn't it?
Like.
Dislike.
I'm sorry.
S-Senior.
Are you okay?
You seem strong.
I'm not...
I used to learn taekwondo.
What was that?
I was thinking about something.
I wasn't watching.
Is something bothering you?
Do you want to tell me?
He knows Ling Chao.
I might get exposed.
I should change some of the information.
I have...
A friend?
No, she's my cousin.
I should've just said friend.
And then?
And
she has a close senior
who often appears in front of her recently.
Do you think
he is seeking attention?
Objectively speaking,
Ling Chao is indeed a senior.
It depends.
Maybe it's fate.
Or maybe
your cousin
appears in a way that
made him feel
he should show up in front of her.
And this senior
is special to her.
She has a little crush on him.
But she's not sure
if he likes her or not.
So your cousin...
she has never been in a relationship, right?
I think
she should believe in her intuition.
Since she has never been in a relationship,
yet she has developed
a special feeling toward this senior.
I think
it has a special meaning.
I'll go back and think about me...
about my cousin.
Senior,
you've helped me so many times.
If I don't treat you to a meal,
I would feel sorry.
Okay, let's go.
We have to do it after I finish level 4 exam.
Okay.
Bye.
I'll tell the truth.
I fell in love with him.
But
I don't know if he likes me.
You just gave your dad the scarf?
Are you sure you are going to Ling Chao's birthday empty-handed?
He doesn't need gifts.
There are birthdays every year.
I'll give him next year.
What did you prepare?
We can't both go to the birthday dinner empty-handed.
Jia Siwen picked a computer book for me.
It's very practical.
It won't go wrong.
Jia Siwen is quite reliable.
Ling Chao is also reliable.
Didn't he reject Xu Linglong?
He didn't say he liked me.
What if he rejected me too?
How is that possible?
He was so fierce
but it turned out to be unreliable.
Don't worry.
I made mistakes twice.
The third time will never go wrong.
Trust me.
It's true this time.
Hello, Tony.
Can the hairstyle you mentioned last time
makes me shine?
Today is an important day for me.
I have to take the risk.
Why are you sitting here?
Can't I sit here?
I reserved a seat for Xia Mo.
Xia...
Xia Mo, Xia Mo will…
Hi.
Hello.
Waiter, we are ready to order.
Listen,
order whatever you want.
Tonight, all the expense
will be paid by Mr. Ling.
You are so generous.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Why are you the only two from your dorm
coming here?
Xia Mo is attending a horror party that
she can't refuse.
I don't know what Xu Linglong is doing.
Before the order is ready,
why don't we take a look
what madam prepared for master?
Right.
It's rare for Sha to make a request.
Let's satisfy him.
Satisfy him.
I didn't prepare a gift.
No way.
I came empty-handed.
I don't need gifts.
We're not kids.
It's already nice that
we sit together and have dinner.
Let me tell you.
Someone stayed up for several nights
and knitted a scarf.
I heard that
our birthday boy is particularly not afraid of cold
that he doesn't need a scarf at all.
So she gave it to her dad.
Really?
Can I ask for another one?
You never wear a scarf.
Never.
I can wear it from now on.
Me on that day
is different from me today.
I said I can wear it today.
It starts from today.
The scarf can be replenished later.
Birthday gift is a must.
Why don't
you two go shopping nearby?
Go, go, go.
I'll call you when the food is served.
Go ahead.
It's wonderful outside.
There are also acrobatics.
Go, go, go.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Doesn't it feel like New Year's Eve?
You are feeling like New Year's Eve.
I don't feel like it at all.
Why don't you bring Xia Mo here?
Then go with her.
I dare not.
Are you Ms. Jiang?
We didn't order vegetables.
Mr. Jia
called to order.
And he has already paid
for this table.
Why did you pay the bill?
Today is Ling Chao's birthday.
It should be his treat.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Please feel free to pick.
Not too free.
This is the new design of our designer.
Do you want to try your size?
No hurry. Let's take a look.
Okay. You can shop around first.
2999.
4299.
Can you get me a size bigger?
Okay, wait a moment.
Are you serious?
Aren't you going to give me a gift?
And have my pick.
The saleswoman said it.
I didn't say it.
I told you
I don't have much pocket money left this month.
You can't pick too expensive ones.
But I've asked the saleswoman
to get my size
of the cloth that I just picked.
Just try it
and say
it's not a match or
you don't like it.
Or it's too big or too small.
Whatever.
Okay.
Sir, this is the size you want.
Thank you.
Hold this for me.
How is it?
It fits perfectly.
It fits well.
This is the classic design of our shop.
And the color goes with everything.
Very practical.
Yes.
There are no shortcomings except the price.
Then this one.
We offer a special price on this one
for our anniversary.
It's only 199 yuan.
It's a good deal to buy it now.
You're sensible.
Satisfied?
You must be hungry.
I'm starving.
Eat more.
Young man.
Do you want to buy a bouquet of flowers for your girlfriend?
Do you want it?
No.
I'm not your girlfriend.
So,
is he still single?
For now.
Can I add you on WeChat?
Sorry.
I forgot my phone.
Then give me your WeChat number.
Why are you walking so fast?
Why did you catch up?
Why didn't you talk more?
You two seem to get along well.
Why don't you let her celebrate your birthday?
You gave me a gift.
Of course I have to treat you to dinner.
It's just a shirt.
I can give it to my dad.
The size is not right.
Then...then I'll give...
give...
Check your contact list
and see who you can give it to.
I'll check it now.
I'll give it to someone right away.
Can we go eat now?
Happy birthday to Ling Chao.
May all your wishes come true.
Wish all of you good health in the new year.
Enjoy it.
Wish everyone a better life.
Cheers.
It's almost time.
Countdown.
Wait.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Sir, if you can't drive,
just drop me off here.
No, I can't park here.
Wait for the next intersection.
Seven, six, five.
Girl, where did you get your hair done?
Four, three, two.
Did you ask him for compensation?
Hair.
One.
Happy New Year.
Cheers.
I'm not going.
I used to think
you could understand if I didn't tell you.
But I have to say it now.
I'm sorry.
Why?
I like...
I don't want to hear it.
I like Xiao Tu.
Dislike.
Like.
I'm sorry.
I like her very much.
Like.