[English subtitles are available]
-Godmother. -Baby.
-I miss you so much. -I miss you too.
Let's go.
Where are my parents?
They went for a checkup.
Why didn't you go?
Our department had a checkup last week.
Everything is fine for me.
Then I'm relieved.
Hello, Grandma.
Hello.
Whatever. Let's go.
Young man.
You're a son-in-law, right?
Me too.
Life
is hard.
Rabbit.
You must be tired after sitting in the car for a whole day.
Go watch TV in the living room.
I'm not tired.
Godmother, why do you always treat me like a child?
I can do this. It's not a big deal.
My baby.
You are a child.
Mom.
Take a break.
Let me help her.
Okay, I'll go.
I'll leave this place to you two.
You'd better stand aside
in case blood splatters on you.
I've never seen you in that shirt.
Which one?
It's the one on your birthday…
I know.
Are you that kind of person
who doesn't cherish it when they get it?
Who knows?
I don't know.
How about
let me get you first?
I...
Damn you!
This is aired every winter and summer vacation.
I even memorized the lines.
Left hand or right hand?
Right hand.
Are you tricking me?
Your dad and I have something to ask you.
You mean
you like Rabbit?
Yes.
What kind of feelings?
I want to raise a family with her.
Well.
Does Rabbit like you?
Right.
This is more important.
Probably.
What does it mean by "probably"?
Have you confessed your love?
Not yet.
When are you going to confess to her?
My daughter-in-law may run away.
He's so slow.
I'm so worried.
Mom.
Don't you think I'm not good enough for Xiao Tu?
Really?
It's normal.
Rabbit is so cute.
You only bully her.
Besides,
your personality is weird
and unlikeable.
I don't know who you take after.
The biggest regret
for me
is that I don't have a daughter.
So,
I always treat Rabbit as my daughter.
In the past, they were young,
so I didn't think about that.
But that day,
when that boy came to our house for dinner.
It was Yin...
Yin Zihan.
Yes, that was him.
She brought a boy back.
It felt like I'm losing her.
Also,
I met
Yin's mother
when I went to the parent-teacher conference for Rabbit.
She looked unreliable.
I can't imagine
Rabbit marring into their family in the future.
Right.
Your mother is right.
If Rabbit really gets married,
she won't come to our house often.
I'll also feel quite lonely.
Ling Chao, let me tell you.
You can do anything you want.
Be thick-skinned
and thoughtful.
If you can't do it,
you can even cry and make a scene.
I don't care.
You must marry Rabbit.
I'll try my best.
Go back first.
If you need anything,
just let us know.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I can do it.
Can he really do it?
Hello.
Yin Zihan.
What time is it now?
Don't you know I'm suffering from jet lag?
It's nine o'clock.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Please thank your mother for me.
Good night.
Ling Chao, are you crazy?
You bought so many things.
This is the special tea from Yunhai.
The local students said it's very good.
Okay.
This is dried fruit.
It's a good snack while you're watching dramas.
Try it.
And this is the sweet potato.
I've been feeling cold
around my neck lately.
Let me find something to wrap it up.
This…
A scarf, right?
Let me find it for you.
A scarf.
-Is there any? -Sure, I must have one.
This.
It's my first time knitting.
I saw my classmates knitting.
It doesn't look good.
Why did you knit?
It's tiring.
It's well knitted.
This is so fashionable.
Yes, it is.
They're designed to be ripped
for the ones being sold in the mall.
Yours is much better than that.
Put it on.
Who do your classmates
knit scarfs for?
Their boyfriends.
That means
there must a lot of girls in your class who are dating.
Yes, there are a few.
I'm not sure about that.
Is there any boy
interested in our Rabbit?
Mom.
Are you asking if I'm in a relationship?
Can't I ask?
I'm just caring about you.
No.
It's not that I don't want you to date, right?
You're in college now.
I mean
you are likely to go back to Yidong after graduating.
If you find someone who lives too far away,
you'll be married far away, right?
Yes.
You won't marry far away, right?
We don't want you to marry far away.
Right.
That means
I can find someone from our hometown?
Yeah, it's great to date someone from the same place.
You'll know each other well.
So you mean
you've already found someone from our hometown?
What does he look like?
Do you have a photo?
Right.
No, I haven't.
I've asked around.
Later,
Wenhui will come out
through the staff exit at the west gate.
We'll wait for him there then.
Okay.
I've contacted a driver.
Once he comes out,
we can catch up immediately.
Great!
Are you
going to follow his car?
None of your business.
If you like him, you can get close to him,
but don't stalk him.
You'll only make him uncomfortable.
What do you know?
We don't simply like him.
This is love.
Shouldn't you care more about him if you love him?
This stage is for his fans.
His life is for himself.
Don't hurt him
in the name of loving him.
Besides, it's dangerous to follow a car.
What if an accident occurs?
Who do you think you are?
How dare you lecture us here?
I'm also a fan of Wenhui.
You guys look about my age.
You should be able to tell right from wrong.
Can you be a rational fan?
It's none of your business.
Are you crazy?
It's none of your business. Watch your mouth.
You can't fight.
The idol has to pay for what his fans do.
I can't let my idol suffer this
because of me.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Luckily you showed up in time.
Why are you here?
I was buying glasses there.
I saw this poster.
I knew you've been fangirling him lately.
So I noticed it.
I didn't expect they…
Buying glasses?
Where are your glasses?
I ran too fast.
I lost it.
It's okay.
You look good without glasses.
You can also try contact lenses.
The one my idol endorsed.
Is it cold?
A little.
If he says we should go back,
I'll turn against him now.
Hair.
No.
I mean you're pressing my hair.
All right.
This darn sweetness.
Honey.
Come to me.
You're so sweet.
I've read your proposal.
It's well written.
Just minor changes
are needed.
Okay.
It's okay.
Answer it if you want.
What is it?
Are you still busy?
Let's have dinner together tonight.
Why do you always think about eating?
I'm in a meeting. I'm busy.
Another meeting for that seminar?
It's a psychological health seminar.
Not a random seminar.
They did a great job last year.
This year, the Psychology Department
got enough funds
to co-organize with our News Department.
I'm in charge of a handful of projects.
I also need to train the newcomers.
I'm busy.
Will you gain any credits for this?
I think so.
After all, I'm the person in charge.
Fine.
I forgave you.
Talk to you later.
Bye.
I've changed this code several times.
There's still a bug.
Master, please help me.
Master.
You're a pervert.
It just came to me
that there's a competition in Lin City next month.
We need to pick two people.
One is decided, Sun.
The other hasn't been decided yet.
Are you going?
I'm not interested.
If you don't go,
I guess it'll be Jianghu.
Let's double check it.
One second.
What is this?
What's wrong?
I think it got a virus.
Don't worry. Let me see.
What should we do? Can it be restored?
Looks like it can't be fixed.
Fortunately, we have enough time.
We can rewrite it.
Ling Chao, you're dead meat.
We both study Computer Science.
Why can't he do something serious?
What?
It's okay. Take your time. I'll accompany you.
Can you find the first draft?
I don't know where it is.
Let me do it.
My rehearsal is over.
Come over.
Let's have milk tea.
Come on.
Have you
prepared well today?
Almost. Almost.
Will there be any problems tomorrow?
No.
Don't worry, Senior.
Even if the whole school is out of power tomorrow,
I'll get a generator
to complete this event successfully.
Okay.
Let's call it a day.
Thank you, everyone.
Go back and rest.
Okay.
Xiao Tu, you stay for a while.
Let's check the manuscript.
Okay.
Dali.
It's too noisy outside.
Close the door when you go out.
Okay.
Senior.
Should we start from the beginning
or the interview part?
What's the rush?
Are you in a hurry?
I am in a hurry.
I have an appointment.
An appointment?
Is it
Ling Chao?
No, no.
You're so funny.
You're with me,
but you always want to get involved with others.
Stop pretending to be surprised.
I know
you like me.
I knew it
when you asked me for my number.
You can't fool people with your eyes.
Do you misunderstand?
I'm slow-witted sometimes.
I'll apologize to you
if I did something to mislead you.
You know,
many girls like me.
In the past,
you
were really not my type.
Now there are just two of us.
My patience is limited.
Stop playing
hard to get.
I really don't like you.
I just see you as my senior.
Hello?
Something happened.
You really don't like me?
Why did you ask me for my phone number?
I've explained it many times.
I lost a game.
I don't believe it.
Are you mad at me
because you're shy
after I said
what's in your mind?
I'm gonna go.
If you leave,
I'll take this
as you giving up on credits for this event.
Senior, what's wrong?
What took you so long?
I was bullied by the book.
My fingers got cut
and are bleeding.
Ridiculous.
How dare you say that?
What if
Madam was bullied by something,
then…
Who can bully her?
It's good that she doesn't bully others.
Suck it yourself.
Hey.
Think it over.
Are you
controlling yourself?
I know.
You can't control yourself
when you fall in love with someone.
If you don't like me,
why did you raise your hand
to sign up for this seminar?
I wasn't mean to raise my hand. It was really an accident.
Accident?
Every time you saw me,
you smiled so shyly.
Do you still want to deny that you like me?
Shy?
I smiled because I like to smile.
What does it have to do with being shy?
Then why did you treat me to dinner
and let me be your model?
Why did you give me hints
to tempt me to respond
every time you showed up in front of me?
Senior.
Don't you think too much?
Do you think you're excellent
and every woman should like you?
Isn't it reasonable
for someone to like me?
Don't be shy.
I know.
Are you the scumbag from the Computer Department
in that post?
Yes.
Since you've found out,
can you be more honest?
Who is it?
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Hold on.
When did you become so smart?
Take a guess.
I want to be as manly as my master,
so that girls would like me.
Look at my spin kick.
Ling Chao.
What are you doing?
Why did the other candidate on the competition list
become you?
Didn't you say you weren't going?
I suddenly wanted to join.
You...
What?
What do you mean by the other candidate changed into Master?
There was only me
on the list.
You were just a spare.
Ling Chao.
Have you gone too far?
Revealing the disgusting truth of the Prince Charming from the Computer Department.
We are all in the same department.
Do you really think we are stupid?
Haven't we already found
the IP address of the poster
and not made it public?
The first time, you framed me.
The second time, you harassed Xiao Tu.
You can try the third time.
I suggest
you behave yourself until you graduate.
Don't hurt other girls anymore.
Otherwise, I'll report you.
Ling Chao.
You won.
Let's go.
Sha.
Don't you think
you looked so cool just now?
But I'm on duty today.
I'm on duty. I...
Master, check this post out.
Come on.
We grew up together.
We are kind of like childhood sweethearts to each other.
Ever since you said I like him last time,
I've been confused.
I'm nervous and shy.
I think I've fallen in love with him.
You've been working hard lately.
Eat more.
It's nutritious.
There are only two of us. You ordered too much.
What a waste.
Of course not.
If we can't finish them, we can pack the leftovers
and share them with my roommates.
Thank you.
I haven't seen you eat like this for a long time.
You kept busy recently
every time I asked you out.
I won't go to that seminar anymore.
Whoever wants to go can go.
That scoundrel threatened me with credits.
I don't need it.
From now on,
I'll be free.
I have to eat three bowls of rice every day.
Eat more.
Take your time.
Don't be so excited while you're eating.
If you're not busy,
do you want to go to the competition in Lin City with me?
Lin City?
Two days and one night.
Congratulations.
It must be exciting.
A strange city.
A hotel in the midnight.
Do you think
something strange would happen?
For example,
something like…
By the way,
don’t tell Xu Linglong.
If she tells her mom
and her mom tells my dad,
Ling Chao will be dead meat.
Hurry up.
Here.
Take this.
And this.
Brush and stuff.
Bring more lipsticks.
I'll just stay there for one night.
That's too much.
It's not too much.
There you go.
Right.
It's friendly sponsorship
for your first date.
You rarely wear skirts.
Ling Chao must like it
if you wear this.
Let's meet in the hall
after we unpack
in our own room.
Let's go to the food street then.
Okay.
Let's go.
Did they forget
I'm also in the lift?
The sour smell of love
The sour smell of love.
It doesn't matter whether you dress up or not.
What matters is
I can't let my sisters down.
Does it look weird?
Hold on.
-I'll get changed. -No.
Don't.
It looks good.
Let's go.
Well...
Where's Wukong?
He said he's too tired.
He won't go.
Let's bring him some food
when we come back.
Let's go.
You are tired.
Your whole family is tired.
Do you really think I'm a monkey?
This is the best stinky tofu
in the universe.
Try it.
Is it good?
Not bad.
Your clothes are dirty.
Your face...
I'm not blushing.
I mean
your face is dirty too.
Well, I'm full.
I bought some food for Wukong.
Let's go back.
Cushion foundation.
What is this?
This…
Ling Chao must like it
if you wear this.
Jiang Juanjuan.
Coming.
The electric kettle in our room is broken.
Can I use yours to boil some water?
You're so polite.
Come in.
Let me help you.
I can do it myself.
You're
a little different today.
Is it that obvious?
I can feel
that you put some effort into it.
Let me explain.
It's not mine.
It's really not mine.
Not mine.
Why didn't you dry your hair?
It's easy to catch a cold
in this season.
It's okay. I'm inside the room...
Don't move.
Itchy.
Ling Chao.
I must talk to you.
What?
We have a big competition tomorrow.
It's not good to be so tired
the night before the competition.
Go to sleep.
We'll win first place
when we wake up.