Qingyao,
at last, you belong to me.
I
have always belonged to you.
Your Highness.
I am the real Qingyao.
She is an assassin.
Impudent assassin!
Utter nonsense!
Your Highness,
I am the true Qingyao.
You once said
you vowed to guard me forever.
Of course.
With me here,
no one can harm you in the slightest.
Your Highness, be careful!
Qingyao.
I've awaited
this moment for long.
Your Highness.
Wants to kill me?
Would you dare?
After all,
this is your own body.
Though we've exchanged bodies,
the sense we have for each other's body
remain unchanged.
Your heart must ache terribly now.
=How to Train Your Killer=
=Episode 1=
Qingyao,
it was I who proposed to the Emperor
I would only marry Gu Qingyao
from the Prime Minister's Residence.
Now you stand right before me,
it feels almost like a dream.
Your Highness,
a dream
is never this real.
Who are you?
How dare you?
Your Highness, run!
Your Highness!
(Where is this place?)
(Why can't I move?)
Speak.
Who ordered you
to attack the Crown Prince?
(Attack the Crown Prince?)
I didn't!
I didn't harm him!
(Why is that a man's voice?)
Still denying it.
Come on.
Burn a heart shape onto his chest.
Let's see how he dares
show his face again.
It really wasn't me.
I truly didn't harm him.
(Why doesn't my body feel any pain?)
Ah!
It hurts.
Your Highness.
We did not know you were coming.
Please forgive us
for not greeting you sooner.
(Her appearance...)
I came late.
Sorry for making you suffer.
Your Highness,
he tried to kill the Crown Prince...
Nonsense.
He is a shadow guard sent
by my father to protect me.
Last night, he saved both me
and the Crown Prince.
How dare you torture him?
You're awake.
Where is this place?
Want to see a mirror, right?
Well?
Are you pleased with this face?
Why have I turned into a man?
What's with that look?
I've taken on your face.
And I haven't even complained.
Why are you crying?
You don't understand.
With this look,
how could I still be Crown Princess?
Exactly.
Right now, I'm the Crown Princess.
If I wanted to harm your husband,
wouldn't it be very easy?
What?
You mean harm Ling Yu?
The task isn't done yet.
How could I give up?
You've already ruined me so badly,
and now you still want
to kill my husband.
I'll fight you to the end!
- Let go!
- I won't!
- Will you let go?
- No!
- Let go or not?
Not letting go, huh?
How's that?
Does a slap feel so pleasant?
You dare slap me?
Though our bodies have been exchanged,
the sense we have for each other's body
remains unchanged.
Since my childhood,
my father has never hit me,
yet you actually struck me.
Hold on, are you missing the point here?
I endured branding torture in prison.
What's the big deal about taking a slap?
You deserve it!
You put me in such a state
and even try to kill my husband?
I'll tell Ling Yu
and let him exterminate
your entire family.
Sure.
Go tell him right now
let's see who will be treated
as an assassin.
If I hadn't said
you were my guard,
do you think you'd still be alive?
- You...
- Me what?
Greetings, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
His Highness has come to see you.
Ling Yu, I…
Shut up!
Qingyao, are you available to meet me?
What are you doing?
Hide at once.
He's my husband.
- Why hide?
- Qingyao.
Do you still think you're Gu Qingyao?
As a guard, if you flirt with the him
and he notices,
you'll suffer.
Who is striking a pose?
Qingyao, may I come in?
I am here.
Your Highness, please allow me
to change clothes.
No time left. Hurry and hide.
Where am I supposed to hide?
On the beam, where else?
It's too high. How do I get up there?
You now possess 20 years
of my inner strength.
There's nowhere you can't reach.
Quickly.
Go.
Please come in, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Qingyao, what happened to you?
I just caught a chill from the water.
Now I've taken the medicine.
I feel much better.
Don't worry about me.
That assassin was clearly aiming for me.
If you were dragged into this,
I would truly feel uneasy.
(If not for Gu Qingyao,)
(your life would already be mine.)
Not at all.
It is my honor
to help you.
I heard
a shadow guard sent by Minister Gu
saved me.
Where he is now?
He endured some punishment.
He is now healing.
Once he is better,
I will bring him to meet you.
Get down!
How dare you!
You misunderstand, Your Highness.
This is the shadow guard
my father assigned to protect me.
Shi...
Hero Shi.
So it was you who saved me.
Quickly, pay respects to His Highness.
Hurry up.
Greetings, Your Highness.
You are quite an interesting man.
Your Highness.
And this is?
This is an imperial bodyguard
sent by the Emperor to protect me.
Eunuch Leng.
(Leng Wuchang of the Western Bureau?)
Greetings, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
I heard Hero Shi was punished,
and still carries wounds.
Perhaps allow me to take his pulse.
That won't be necessary.
Qingyao,
let Eunuch Leng
check on Hero Shi.
It's a token of my affection.
(Even if you were an immortal,)
(you would never notice)
(I've swapped bodies
with the Crown Princess.)
Your Highness,
Hero Shi's injuries are not serious.
With some rest,
he'll soon recover completely.
That puts my mind at ease.
Eunuch Leng,
take Hero Shi and step outside first.
Yes, Your Highness.
Eunuch Leng,
why do you have a beard?
The assassin from last night
must've been sent by the court factions,
unhappy about the alliance
between our two houses.
What a pity though.
The man slipped away.
But don't worry.
I will definitely drag him out
and execute him by dismemberment.
Qingyao,
are you tired?
How about this?
I will visit you again tomorrow.
Your Highness.
What is it, Qingyao?
(In a few more days...)
(Tonight, I'll end your life.)
Your Highness,
do you want me to be left alone
in an empty room
just after getting married?
I have yet to…
Your Highness, say something.
Qingyao.
Mm.
Your strength
seems to have grown lately.
Then as you wish,
see you tonight.
(This time,)
(let's see where you can run.)
♪When a breeze passes by♪
♪The sand and wind burn with longing♪
♪Fearless even when thirst
goes unquenched♪
♪Like a camel wandering
with eyes closed♪
♪When the rain quietly settles♪
♪I think of our sorrow yet unknown♪
♪No need to hum the song of the wind♪
♪Ignoring the sky darkening before us♪
♪I finally understood that truth♪
♪Yet you have already faded away♪
♪I lose my way in the night♪
♪Not knowing how to still my heart♪
♪Loving you feels like lifetimes apart♪
♪Yet longing flows back into verse♪
♪For you and me to meet again♪
♪We must cross a thousand years
of promises♪
♪In the pouring rain♪
♪As if you are still by my side♪