=How to Train Your Killer=
=Episode 15=
Don't think I don't know
that the old fox
married you to me back then
just to secure the Gu family's position.
If you truly have no feelings for me,
there's still time to change your mind.
Qingyao,
what's really troubling you?
Was it someone who bullied you,
or are you saying
you find life here too stifling?
I admit, days like these,
are dull beyond measure.
Everyone thinks the Crown Prince
will wield immense power in the future.
But I've long known
the Emperor here in the Palace
is merely the prisoner
with the longest sentence.
How about this?
Let's journey
through the world together.
That way,
wouldn't it be OK?
Of course it would.
As the Crown Prince,
it is only right
to see what kind of life the people lead
under the grandeur of our land.
Besides,
I've dreamed of the martial world
since childhood.
To uphold justice and protect the weak,
and roam the world with a sword,
is a unique charm.
Qingyao,
what do you think?
Mm.
Your Highness,
this must never be done.
If anything were to happen to you,
how should I report this to His Majesty?
This journey is merely
for leisure and sightseeing.
Where would any danger come from?
I will travel lightly with Qingyao.
We will bring no attendants.
Never make a big fuss,
or it will ruin her good mood.
But Your Highness,
the martial world is treacherous;
those people are all crude,
striking without restraint.
- If you...
- I still have you.
Remember this.
Protect us from the shadows.
Don't show up unless necessary.
I wish to see for myself
what the legendary martial world,
truly looks like.
Yes, Your Highness.
You're awake.
I'm awake.
At your level of skill,
still using an axe to chop wood?
It's not an easy task for people
in the martial world
to chop wood and cook meals.
It's just chopping wood.
How hard could it be?
Don't believe me?
Here, give it a try.
Fine, I'll try.
Here.
Well?
Not that simple, is it?
Let me try again.
You said my swordsmanship is too rigid
and thus easy to break,
but overcoming rigidity with strength
is precisely my way of the sword.
That night,
if I hadn't faced two foes alone,
I'm afraid you wouldn't be able
to beat me.
All the hidden secrets
lie within the art of chopping wood.
You feel it out.
I'll go cook us a meal.
You'll get to taste my cooking soon.
Alright, Bai.
See? I told you so.
Bai Jun was bound to return.
Who would've thought your stubborn head
finally figured it out?
End this quickly.
The Master
has long grown impatient.
If we just let him die like this,
wouldn't that be letting him off
too easily?
Shiyi,
take a rest for now.
Come, it's mealtime.
Coming.
Today I must
really savor your cooking.
Come on over.
Have a sip of water first.
Thank you.
This water is poisoned.
What?
You narrowly escaped
and became a traitor.
You actually colluded with two fugitives
wanted by the Imperial Court.
The innocent lives
lost at your hands
outnumber the bamboo in this grove.
How dare you still
twist truth and falsehood?
You stand defiant even at death's door.
Let me deal with those two first,
then I'll come for you.
Feng, run!
No, I won't leave.
If you die, I'll die with you.
- I'm not leaving.
- Go.
No.
- Hurry!
- I said no.
So devoted!
No need to rush.
I'll send you all to your deaths
right now.
Bai, you go first.
Struck by her whip,
you are already a spent force.
How about this, Shiyi?
Kneel and beg us now.
Maybe we'll consider
to spare that woman.
What do you say?
I'm not sure
if you've ever heard this saying.
What saying?
A villain
always dies from talking too much.
You're courting death.
You old eunuch,
it's you again.
You two only know how to talk tough.
You got away last time.
But this time,
you might not leave here alive.
Eunuch Leng,
I told you not to steal the spotlight.
Let me join in the fun
of saving a beauty as well.
Your Highness,
these two are ruthless and cunning.
I must strike first
to gain the upper hand.
Is that so?
You brat,
consider yourself lucky.
Forget it.
Never chase a desperate foe.
Yes.
Be careful.
Are you alright?
Hero Shi.
No need to be nervous, Hero Shi.
Your Highness.
No, I wouldn't dare.
It's always others who serve me.
You're actually the first one
who's ever refused to let me serve.
Your Highness.
This time I am traveling incognito.
My identity must not be revealed.
Just call me young master.
How are you feeling?
Don't worry.
After taking the pill
I got from the imperial physician,
you'll be fine.
Where are Bai Jun and Ruan Feng?
They're both fine.
You're the one who's more badly hurt.
You looked impressive
taking on two alone.
Still as stubborn as ever.
Why are you here?
You think I want to be here?
It's just a coincidence.
Actually, it's Qingyao...
Life in the Palace is dull,
so the Crown Prince brought me
for some travel.
Guess what?
When I passed by the bamboo grove,
I heard the sound of a fight.
What a coincidence.
It turned out to be Hero Shi,
who left without a word.
A coincidence?
No story is complete
without coincidences.
I'm venturing through the world,
and I just happen to need a guide.
Meeting like this must be fate.
I wonder if you...
Your Highness.
Sorry, I am unable to do so.
Fine.
If you can't, then you can't.
You're not much of a guide anyway.
Qingyao,
how do you know that so well?
Just a guess.
Either way,
please think it through, Hero Shi.
Both Qingyao and I
hope you'll stand guard for us.
Let's go.
Mm.
Wind and Rain Pavilion?
Yes, Your Highness.
I've looked into it quietly.
Those two are exactly
the top killers of the Pavilion.
They're known as the Serpent
and Scorpion Twin Fiends.
Then why would these killers suddenly
come looking for Hero Shi for no reason?
The owner of this bamboo grove, Bai Jun,
is a wanted criminal pursued
by the authorities.
Perhaps he is a close friend
of Hero Shi.
The two sides must have
long-held grudges.
So that's how it is.
Is this Wind and Rain Pavilion
the most deadly killer group
in the martial world?
Its name is not well-known,
but it is the most mysterious.
To the Imperial Court,
there's no such thing as mystery.
♪When a breeze passes by♪
♪The sand and wind burn with longing♪
♪Fearless even when thirst
goes unquenched♪
♪Like a camel wandering
with eyes closed♪
♪When the rain quietly settles♪
♪I think of our sorrow yet unknown♪
♪No need to hum the song of the wind♪
♪Ignoring the sky darkening before us♪
♪I finally understood that truth♪
♪Yet you have already faded away♪
♪I lose my way in the night♪
♪Not knowing how to still my heart♪
♪Loving you feels like lifetimes apart♪
♪Yet longing flows back into verse♪
♪For you and me to meet again♪
♪We must cross a thousand years
of promises♪
♪In the pouring rain♪
♪As if you are still by my side♪