=How to Train Your Killer=
=Episode 16=
Here.
Try Feng's cooking.
Qingyao, you eat first.
It's a new dish.
It really tastes like mint!
Of course.
- Smells good?
- Mm.
Cool and refreshing.
The taste's lovely.
Shiyi.
Shiyi, you're...
Leaving?
Yes.
I've troubled you for too long.
It's time I go.
But your wounds...
They're near healed.
Thank you for taking me in these days.
Acting tough again!
Farewell.
Have you given any thought
to the matter of being the guide?
I'm wounded.
I truly can't take on such a duty.
I hope you can understand.
If I have the authorities
lift their wanted notices,
and pardon their crimes,
would you grant me some courtesy?
Shiyi.
Take care.
Bai,
take care.
The sunlight feels wonderful.
(Friend's Inn)
Friend's Inn?
Isn't that obvious?
Out here in the wilderness, could it be…
(Friend's Inn)
So it really is called Friend's Inn.
What a strange name for an inn.
Waiter.
Sir, will you be grabbing a bite
or staying the night?
What do you mean by 'grabbing a bite'?
Grab a bite and stay the night.
Then what would you like to eat?
Bring us a pot of wine first.
Apologies.
We don't serve wine here.
Then… what are those people drinking?
Wine, of course.
Here.
Now we have some?
Sir,
yes, yes.
You three look unfamiliar.
Where are you from?
The Capital City.
Ah, the Capital City.
The Capital City is truly a fine place.
I've never been there.
Could you tell me about it?
Come, come, thank you.
Go on, tell us.
It really is a marvelous place.
Sadly, we have no chance to be there.
Why is that?
Since ancient times, the martial world
and the Imperial Court,
knights and officials,
are like fire and water.
Yes, that's true.
Perhaps that's just your prejudice.
From what I know,
the Imperial Court values talent.
In recent years,
they've begun recruiting
from the martial world.
Forget it.
It's merely leading the tiger
into the cage.
We're not falling for that trick.
By the way, after talking to you
for so long,
I still haven't asked your name.
I am He Zheng.
May I have your name?
I am
Lin Yu.
Good, very good.
Lin,
what a destined meeting this is.
In that case,
let's get drunk tonight, shall we?
Sure, sounds great!
- Cheers!
- Here!
Here.
To be honest,
when I first saw you,
I thought you came looking for trouble.
Ah, Lin,
you've got me all wrong.
Our inn is named Friend's Inn.
The reason
is to keep trouble far away.
What we truly seek
is to build good ties with all.
Am I right, brothers?
That's right.
So lively in here!
Lady San?
Lady San,
you've come at just the right time.
Listen,
these three here are honored guests
from the Capital City.
You must bring out
your finest wine and dishes.
From the Capital City?
Of course they deserve
the best hospitality.
Waiter!
Bring out the finest wine in the inn!
Got it.
Brothers,
take good care of Young Master Lin.
- No need.
- Sure.
Have a drink, Young Master Lin.
Here, pour another cup.
What's wrong?
The madam is pretty,
and your eyes are glued to her.
Hey!
Say something.
Have you been blinded by lust?
Sit still.
I'm afraid what I'll say
might scare you.
Go on, say it.
That man with the scar
is called He Heng.
Three years ago,
he wiped out an entire caravan alone
in Baiyun Ravine.
And that Lady Li too.
Drink well!
Also known as Lady Shisan.
I told you before.
You remember, right?
That devil who drains men's strength
to please herself?
Exactly.
This is bad.
We've in deep water.
Well,
with you and Eunuch Leng here,
we don't have to be afraid, right?
It's not as simple as you think.
They're all wanted
by the Imperial Court.
Then let's hurry up and go,
and not stay here.
Look at the Crown Prince.
Wouldn't leaving now
arouse even more suspicion?
Just now,
if I hadn't shown a little skill
in advance,
how could they be so friendly?
So it's because of you.
What should we do now?
Eat, of course.
Where's the food?
Waiter!
Why aren't you drinking?
Not interested.
What's so good about alcohol?
He drank that much!
He has stayed in the Palace
for a long time,
so naturally he needs to relax
when he comes out.
I don't get it.
Are you doing alright?
These are just small occasions.
I can handle them easily.
I'm asking
if you're living well
in the Palace now.
Well...
What about you?
I was pretty free and easy before.
Never thought
I would become your guard.
Well, it's quite the coincidence.
Coincidence?
Did you happen to pass
by that bamboo grove?
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?
If it weren't for me and His Highness,
you've been killed.
Whatever.
No one would care anyway.
I care.
What did you just say?
I...
I said...
Look at me when you say it.
Fill it up, fill it up!
Where's Qingyao?
Qingyao.
- Qingyao.
- I'm here.
Qingyao,
I think I've had too much to drink.
Help me back to my room to rest.
- Alright.
- Hurry.
Let's go.
Young Master Lin, don't leave.
Let's keep drinking.
What about you?
Not satisfied yet.
Bring out a few more jars!
My fist technique...
Would you do me the honor?
I heard from Young Master Lin
that you are highly skilled
in martial arts.
But in the martial world,
I've never heard of your name before.
Highly skilled?
I'm merely a guard, that's all.
I have no title.
True mastery hides its brilliance.
One conceals both merit and fame.
Indeed, that is the highest realm.
But this face of yours...
I think I've seen you somewhere before.
Is that so?
Not I think,
I must've truly seen you somewhere.
Perhaps,
it was a bond carried over
from a past life.
Who knows?
Why does your heart race so fast?
Why do I think
you're even more nervous than I am?
Enjoy yourself.
Hero Shi.
♪When a breeze passes by♪
♪The sand and wind burn with longing♪
♪Fearless even when thirst
goes unquenched♪
♪Like a camel wandering
with eyes closed♪
♪When the rain quietly settles♪
♪I think of our sorrow yet unknown♪
♪No need to hum the song of the wind♪
♪Ignoring the sky darkening before us♪
♪I finally understood that truth♪
♪Yet you have already faded away♪
♪I lose my way in the night♪
♪Not knowing how to still my heart♪
♪Loving you feels like lifetimes apart♪
♪Yet longing flows back into verse♪
♪For you and me to meet again♪
♪We must cross a thousand years
of promises♪
♪In the pouring rain♪
♪As if you are still by my side♪