=How to Train Your Killer=
=Episode 5=
How's that?
Pluck a blossom within ten steps.
Looks like my skill is mastered.
A promising talent.
No time to waste.
Let's set out at once.
Ah?
Set out?
Mm.
Go where?
To finish the mission.
Right now?
Strike while it's hot. Let's move.
No, no, no.
- Go.
- No.
Go.
I… I really can't right now.
A man can't admit he's incapable.
But right now, I'm hardly a man.
I am a man.
That's Butcher Wang Quan?
Isn't he just a pork seller?
Don't underestimate him.
That year, he used this knife
to kill all 13 members
of the Liu family.
13 members?
Just one knife?
Nothing to be afraid of.
Butcher Wang Quan is fierce
and quick-tempered.
Easy to spark his fury.
You can start by shaking his composure.
Wait.
My composure, or his?
I…
Aren't you a noble lady?
Can't make difficulties?
Still need me to teach you?
I'm always so gentle and refined,
so graceful and kind.
How would I know those shameless tricks?
Excuse me.
We are making wontons today.
Cut me ten jin of minced pork.
All lean,
not a speck of fat.
Alright, alright.
Good knife skills.
Here's your pork.
Wait.
I also need ten jin of fat pork,
minced the same way,
to fill meat buns.
You certainly have an appetite.
Your meat is ready.
Two copper coins.
Well then...
I'll take another ten jin
of minced meat,
half fatty
and half lean.
We'll make meatballs.
Are you trying to mess with me?
I'll turn you into meatballs.
Hurry up and give me a hand!
(The mind follows the will,)
(channeling strength through.)
Wang Quan.
You have a really good appetite.
The mission's complete.
Why wouldn't I eat?
Candied hawthorns are delicious.
I've liked it since I was a kid.
Then keep on eating.
(Assassination List)
Killer God Bai Yan.
This guy commits
every imaginable crime.
He's committed over a dozen offenses.
He only targets women.
What a vile man.
And a skilled fighter too.
You mean,
you can't beat him?
I could before.
Now I can't.
If we join forces,
that Bai Yan
will be easy to bring down.
It's because you slow me down,
that I can't win against him.
He must have a weakness, right?
Of course.
Bai Yan is fond of beauties.
He often visits the brothels.
Brothels?
I am the dignified Crown Princess.
Going to a place like that
would hardly suit me.
You're right about that.
A place of pleasure,
a crowd of women.
That wouldn't suit you much.
But right now I'm a man.
Is it fun there?
What?
You want to go?
Don't forget.
You're the dignified Crown Princess now.
As Crown Princess,
I must lead by example,
and step forward before others.
How could I tolerate someone
like Bai Yan,
bringing harm to the realm?
Tomorrow,
we'll set out for the brothel.
No, wait.
It is to eliminate harm for the people.
It's convenient for you,
but it's troublesome for me.
That's easy.
I've got a way.
Take a bite and I'll tell you.
No, I'm not eating.
Come on, come on.
Young master.
What is it?
This is your so-called plan?
You're really daring.
It's for the people's good.
To be honest…
You're beautiful.
Truly beautiful.
Young master.
My mother passed away early,
but...
She did make me rather handsome.
- Really?
- Indeed.
Feeling quite cheerful.
Happy indeed.
I can't stand those flaunting gestures.
If you like dressing up,
do it yourself.
When you tried to charm
the Crown Prince last time,
you were doing pretty well.
Do you still want
to complete the mission?
You need to show some professionalism.
Besides, you're using my body.
What are you shy about?
Come on, let's go.
Go, carry out the mission.
That won't do, sir.
How wicked.
I accidentally walked
into the wrong place.
Wait a moment.
Since you're already here,
don't ruin my mood.
Stay and keep me company.
I'm worried
other guests will grow impatient.
Rest assured.
No one dares vie with me.
May I know
what skills you possess?
I am skilled in dance.
Sir, come join us.
Catch me if you can.
Here I come.
You came alone, sir?
Alone.
Come catch me.
Young Master...
Slow down.
You're playful.
(It's taking far too long.)
(Could it be my beauty)
(has no sway over Bai Yan?)
Though your beauty is striking,
when it comes to your dancing skill…
Well, it's no big deal.
(Darn it!)
(I danced poorly on purpose,)
(to make him not look at me,)
(so that I could make my move easily.)
(Why does this fellow
keep staring at me?)
Beauty, stop dancing.
Come share a drink with me.
To win a beauty's favor tonight,
even if I perish in your gentle embrace,
that would still be my fortune.
You...
Your fortune?
How could this be?
Let go of me!
Lucky I wore chainmail beneath my robe.
I knew there was something
wrong with you.
When did this Qinyue House
have a beauty like you?
Since you've come here,
you might as well stay for good.
If I hadn't shown mercy,
you'd have been gone long ago.
Take my advice.
Do as you're told.
Get your filthy hands off!
♪When a breeze passes by♪
♪The sand and wind burn with longing♪
♪Fearless even when thirst
goes unquenched♪
♪Like a camel wandering
with eyes closed♪
♪When the rain quietly settles♪
♪I think of our sorrow yet unknown♪
♪No need to hum the song of the wind♪
♪Ignoring the sky darkening before us♪
♪I finally understood that truth♪
♪Yet you have already faded away♪
♪I lose my way in the night♪
♪Not knowing how to still my heart♪
♪Loving you feels like lifetimes apart♪
♪Yet longing flows back into verse♪
♪For you and me to meet again♪
♪We must cross a thousand years
of promises
♪In the pouring rain♪
♪As if you are still by my side♪