=How to Train Your Killer=
=Episode 20=
Sit down.
(Father?)
You couldn't catch me.
Take a seat.
What?
You're tense?
No, I'm not.
Harming her fellow members
always ends like this.
She… she…
Is she gone?
Her life and death
is up to you to decide.
No one can decide
another's life or death.
All these years,
I've raised you myself.
I know your greatest weakness
is your soft heart.
Acting this way
is a grave mistake.
The matter with Bai Jun
was meant as a lesson for you.
I do not know
what crime Bai Jun has committed.
His guilt or innocence
is for the authorities to decide.
We only carry out orders.
So some oversights are inevitable.
You can't be blamed for this.
But
when mistakes are made,
punishment must follow.
You are no exception.
I assigned you
as the Crown Princess's guard,
but
you seem to be growing closer
to Ling Yu.
I…
I only did it to hide my true identity.
That's good.
I raised you with my own hands.
To me, you are as my own child.
Never forget where you come from.
I understand.
Master,
do we have a new mission this time?
Lately, across the martial world,
in every stronghold,
spies of unknown origin
have suddenly appeared.
I suspect,
the Imperial Court has grown suspicious.
Could it be that the plot to assassinate
the Crown Prince has been exposed?
As long as you remain unharmed,
our secret will stay hidden.
So what you mean is…
To keep danger at bay,
we must act before they do.
You want me to kill the Crown Prince
right now?
No.
I want you to kill...
(Piaoyao Cloth Shop)
Well?
Your favorite candied haws.
If I hadn't seen it with my own eyes,
I would never have believed
that the one who planned all of this
was actually my biological father.
But there's one thing
I just can't figure out.
Why would he plot
to kill the Crown Prince?
By doing this,
what benefit could he possibly gain?
Now His Majesty lies gravely ill,
and the Crown Prince holds full control
of state affairs.
It has long been a foregone conclusion
that he will ascend the throne
in the future.
If there's any variable left,
it would be Noble Consort Xiao's son,
Second Prince Ling Huan.
But I heard that he's
been frail and sickly since childhood.
It's precisely because
of his poor health
that he could serve well
as a puppet emperor.
Prop up the young emperor,
and command the lords in his name.
Yet the father I remember
wasn't like that.
He was a true pillar of the Court,
always diligent and caring
for the people,
treating others with kindness.
Why then would he commit
such a grave act against all order?
This is just his surface.
In my impression,
the Master has always been
a cold-blooded and ruthless person
who would stop at nothing
to achieve his goals.
Still don't dare to make a move?
The law of the jungle
is itself the truth of the world.
Today,
you choose mercy toward him,
but tomorrow,
you may fall beneath his blade.
I have no fondness for the weak.
Today,
only one of you
can leave here.
He has always
been skilled at playing with hearts.
He's a man of deep schemes.
To clear himself of suspicion,
he specifically ordered me
to strike on your wedding night.
Who would have foreseen that?
What about this time?
Who does he want me to kill?
This time,
he plans to kill his own daughter.
I'm asking you
to kill the Crown Princess.
Why?
I suppose
that if the Crown Prince truly died
by assassination,
and he supported
the young emperor's accession
to become a prime minister,
he would ultimately
be a treacherous minister
with an illegitimate claim,
unable to silence public opinion.
But if...
But if the one to die were me instead...
He could frame the Crown Prince,
then march to conquer
with rightful pretext.
Even seizing the throne for himself,
he still seeks a proper pretext.
My father...
Still cares so much about appearances.
Now it seems
I'm just a pawn
on his path to power.
When the Master makes up his mind,
he never changes it easily.
But this mission…
How did you agree to it?
This is not right.
Gu Qingyao is pregnant now.
What?
Is that truly so?
Without a doubt.
Gu Qingyao's pulse indicates joy,
and her face shows signs of pregnancy.
I fear
she's already three months pregnant.
I'm betting
on whether he is truly so heartless,
willing to give up both his own daughter
and the grandchild in her womb.
I've won my bet.
He still has a trace of humanity left.
From this day on...
From this day on, what should I do?
I've thought it through.
From now on,
no matter what happens,
even if I have to stand
against the entire Pavilion,
and the Master,
I will stay by your side.
Your Highness.
Guard Shi is here as well.
It's so late.
Need something from me?
Noble Consort Xiao sent an invitation.
She invites you to offer incense
at the temple tomorrow.
Noble Consort Xiao?
Yeah.
♪When a breeze passes by♪
♪The sand and wind burn with longing♪
♪Fearless even when thirst
goes unquenched♪
♪Like a camel wandering
with eyes closed♪
♪When the rain quietly settles♪
♪I think of our sorrow yet unknown♪
♪No need to hum the song of the wind♪
♪Ignoring the sky darkening before us♪
♪I finally understood that truth♪
♪Yet you have already faded away♪
♪I lose my way in the night♪
♪Not knowing how to still my heart♪
♪Loving you feels like lifetimes apart♪
♪Yet longing flows back into verse♪
♪For you and me to meet again♪
♪We must cross a thousand years
of promises♪
♪In the pouring rain♪
♪As if you are still by my side♪