=Dance of the Phoenix=
(Episode 7)
If you want to fight one-on-one,
let's do it.
But, if I win,
you need to tell me
why you place a spy
around me!
Okay.
Let's see if you can really
get the chance to win.
I...
You...
How dare you!
It's you who struck the first blow.
Jun Linyuan,
you're not focused even when you're fighting.
You're looking down upon me.
If you are not serious with the fight,
you'd lose your life.
You're always thinking yourself
beautiful and talkative.
Today I'm gonna cut your face.
I wanna see how you hook up
with His Highness Jun again.
Stop!
Miss Liu, you've gone too far!
Madam,
it's your daughter who has gone too far.
She is a person of no cultivation base
and she covers up all truth
from my brother and me.
Enough.
Feng Wu, are you okay?
Feng Yiran,
stop pretending to be a good person.
If you really want to be a good person,
you should get out of here
with your idiot sister.
What did you say?
Stop it!
Get out of my way.
You like herbal medicine.
I'm gonna burn all your stuff.
I wanna see how you continue to pretend.
No.
You...
How dare you hook up with His Highness Jun!
Feng Wu.
Mom.
Mom. No.
I will fight you to the end.
Boss Jun.
You're not even in the same league as I am.
There's no point in fighting against you.
I gotta go.
Forget about that.
Something is wrong in the front courtyard.
Go check it out.
Feng Wu.
Mom.
Does it hurt?
Feng Wu.
-Feng Wu.
-My Lady.
Phoenix Sword.
What did you say?
Phoenix Sword comes out
to look for its owner.
But it chose her.
That doesn't make any sense.
Feng Liu.
My Lady.
Feng Wu and Madam both got hurt.
What do you want to do?
Both of you
are taking advantage of
a person of no cultivation base.
Don't you feel ashamed?
Your Highness Jun.
There's some misunderstanding.
I know that my sister has gone too far.
I was just about to stop her.
Remember that
if a strong person
can order a weak person to do anything,
then at this place
the only person that can determine your fate
is me.
(Simple and Incorruptible)
Mom.
How can I get you
into this dangerous situation
just because I don't believe you?
Even though you lost Phoenix Blood,
you should not put yourself
under anyone's thumb like this.
As time goes by,
you'll be looked down upon by other people.
Today Phoenix Sword chose you as its owner.
Since you don't agree on
the secular rules in this world,
you should try to be a strong person.
Are you really...
My Lady, you should get better quickly.
It belongs to Yu Mingye.
Feng Wu,
how many things about you are there
that I still don't know?
Hail to you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
His Highness Jun isn't back yet.
We don't know what's wrong with him.
It's good that Crown Prince is a devoted son.
But he's gone for so long.
I don't know
if everything is okay with him.
Your Majesty, you're kind-hearted.
If His Highness Jun knows
you're worrying about him,
(Great Spiritual Master Yan)
he will surely come back to the capital soon.
Every Great Spiritual Master here,
do you have anything to discuss?
Since March this year,
many people from villages in the south
were reported to have been
attacked by demonic beasts.
Panic immediately swept through the area,
with no businessman or traveler
willing to go there.
I hereby beg Your Majesty
to order East Governor and his cultivators
to kill the demonic beasts,
thus letting people
live a peaceful life again.
Do you have any other ideas?
Your Majesty,
I think we'd better
pick an obedient cultivator in the capital
and order him to lead everyone
to kill the demonic beasts.
I think Your Majesty's nephew Gao Wei,
who is a young and courageous
senior-rank spiritual practitioner now,
can be entrusted with this important task.
Gao Wei
is still young.
I'm afraid he might not
be trusted by everyone.
I am supportive of that proposal.
Gao Wei is the best candidate
for this job.
I agree.
Your Majesty,
what's your opinion of it?
I don't care.
Then
it's all set.
In a few days,
I will get in practice in seclusion.
But Crown Prince hasn't come back
to the capital yet.
So can you recommend someone
that we can entrust with the important job of
filling my shoes
and managing the affairs of the clan?
Your Majesty,
now all the Elders and Masters
are living at different places.
Most of the new Great Spiritual Masters
are not fully-fledged for the job.
So I suggest that
Her Majesty do the work for you.
That doesn't make sense.
I am just a woman.
I can only
perform simple tasks.
It's impossible for me
to handle the affairs of the clan.
I agree that
Her Majesty is the best candidate.
Hopefully you can share
His Majesty's heavy burden.
I agree.
Okay. Her Majesty,
since they all recommend you,
you'd better take the job.
Yes.
Since all of you have recommended me,
I cannot but take this job.
Wait a second.
I can't believe this.
Spiritual Elder Fang has come.
Hail to you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Spiritual Elder Fang,
what brought you here?
You've been living a peaceful life
in your hometown these years.
How are you?
I'm grateful for Your Majesty's blessing.
I'm very well.
I came to the capital
this time particularly to
help Your Majesty out.
Everything is okay in the clan.
What do you mean by saying...
I took the order from His Highness Jun
and was entrusted with the job of
handling different affairs in the clan.
That's great.
If you are here,
I can get in practice in seclusion
without anything to worry about.
You were entrusted by Crown Prince?
His Highness Jun
is considerate of Your Majesty.
He ordered me to come back
and help Your Majesty solve problems.
I see.
That's good.
It just worries me to think
how to handle all the affairs in the clan.
Luckily, you are back.
Now I can breathe a sigh of relief.
Mom.
My Lady.
My Lady, you are conscious.
Does your hand still hurt?
Where is mom?
Madam is fine.
She has just come back to rest.
Madam has taken medicine.
She is fine.
You should also get more rest.
My Lady.
Why are you doing this?
Goddess Zuo.
It's all my fault and I've got what I deserve.
Could you forgive me this time?
It's not related to my forgiving you.
I know that
you really admire Crown Prince.
So sometimes you're a little impatient.
You'd better have a clear picture of it.
You don't need to this.
But you've gone so far this time that
you even made such a serious attack
against Feng Wu.
Yes.
I've learned my lesson.
I'll always follow your advice from now on.
I won't cross the line again.
This time I come back,
I notice that Feng Wu is very different
from what she used to be in childhood.
I haven't seen her for a long time.
I don't know
how her life is on the border.
Mom.
Does it hurt?
It's all my fault.
You often tell me
not to act rashly.
But I never listen to your words.
I always think I can
get things done on my own.
So this time I got you in trouble.
It doesn't matter.
Feng Wu, I'm fine.
As to you,
you should thank His Highness Jun.
Jun Linyuan?
No.
But for him,
Feng Liu wouldn't have gotten me in trouble.
Feng Wu.
Listen to me.
It'd be good if you could
regain your cultivation base.
You can thus do what you want to do.
But keep in mind that
never be controlled by hatred.
Phoenix Sword
used to belong to your father.
I haven't seen it for many years.
Since the sword chose you
by a strange twist of fate,
you should keep it safe.
Your Highness,
there is some misunderstanding today.
Misunderstanding?
Even though Feng Wu is down and out now,
she shouldn't have been treated like this.
You have gone too far.
You must be punished.
Boss Jun,
why not leave them
to demonic beasts in the wilderness?
They can even increase
their cultivation base there.
Young Master Feng, I beg to differ.
Even though they both
have done something wrong,
their spirit energy is not strong enough
to protect themselves
when encountering superior demonic beasts.
The Feng family
is a distinguished family in the capital.
We should not punish them too harshly.
Women are really
soft-hearted.
Even though His Majesty
encourages cultivation,
he also promotes
equality of all living things.
You are both cultivators,
but you bullied a person of
no cultivation base before so many people
and even kept talking nonsense
in the name of His Majesty.
Your Highness.
We beg you to forgive us.
We will surely keep it in mind.
We promise that we won't do it again.
Yes, Your Highness.
Please consider the fact that
the Feng family has been working so hard
for the sake of Junwu Clan.
We should be given some credit
for hard work if not for merit.
Please forgive us this time.
Considering the fact that
it was your first offence
and little damage was caused,
I will cut you some slack.
We appreciate it very much, Your Highness.
You can stand up.
Do you mean that we're giving you
a hard time deliberately?
No. Definitely not.
But punishment cannot be spared.
I just lowered your spirit energy
as a warning this time.
Hopefully, you will learn your lesson
and correct your mistake.
Don't ever bully other people
just because you have some cultivation base.
Feng Liu.
You are too aggressive.
Thunder Spell will bring thunder
down from the sky
whenever you want to talk dirty words.
Hopefully you will know what you should do
and be kind to others.
Your Highness,
we gotta go.
Let's go.
My Lady,
this is the first time
I see Eldest Young Master
and Sixth Young Lady
so embarrassed.
It serves them right.
He gets what a bad person should get.
Come in.
Boss Jun has already known
that you are listening in.
Feng Wu.
Long time no see.
I killed Hundred Poison Beast.
After that,
if I hadn't returned to the border
to make humble efforts
to help His Highness Jun,
I wouldn't have run into you
when you are in danger.
I appreciate it very much.
You deserve to be
eldest sister of Celestial Palace.
You are not only beautiful but also kind.
I have just thought that
we have special pills in Celestial Palace,
which is greatly effective to burns.
I'll get some and give them to your mom.
How did you know that I was outside?
We all heard you chuckling at other people's
embarrassment outside the door.
You thought we wouldn't hear the sound
when you cover your mouth, didn't you?
You...
Anyway.
Since you helped me out,
I don't want to argue with you
when you're putting on a poker face.
Poker face?
Look at me.
I am very ugly,
so I don't want to get married.
Otherwise
I'd rather choose you as my partner
than Jun Linyuan,
who is always putting on a poker face.
Nor will I choose Xuan Yi,
who has two bulging eyes.
Poker face?
Is this word popular around the border area?
Yes.
The people on the border
always say this word,
don't they, Qiu Ling?
By the way,
my mom
asked me to thank you.
So could you give me the chance
to make something for you?
What are you doing, My Lady?
Today
I'm gonna see how much
spirit energy I still have.
Attention, please.
Anything happens?
Is there any fire?
No.
It's choking.
Phoenix Sword is known to set a fire.
But why can't I do anything with it now?
What's this?
My Lady says it's called Phoenix Tea.
Phoenix Tea?
It's so good.
Qiu Ling, is there anything else?
Where is Feng Wu?
I can help her.
She took some tea to Goddess Zuo.
She said that if you wanted more,
she would make it for you next time.
Okay. Okay.
Besides that,
what else can Feng Wu make?
I got to drink her Dirty Tea,
pearl milk tea and honey pomelo tea.
Each tastes really good.
Looks like there're many things
that we don't know about Feng Wu.
Your Highness,
you have business to do.
I don't want to bother you anymore.
I gotta go.
What's up, Boss Jun?
Do we have trouble in the capital again?
No.
Because of Spiritual Elder Fang,
they start to get out of the bad situation.
Xuan Yi,
thank you.
Grandfather is always
concerned with Junwu Clan.
So he must be willing to
help you out this time.
Yes. Boss Jun.
Then what are you still worrying about?
His Majesty really expects me
to take back Celestial Fruit.
But now what I can give him
is only disappointment.
If I don't guess wrong,
what's the relation
between all of this and Darknight Court?
It's good.
Thank you for the tea.
It's good that you like it.
Thank you for saving us.
Without your pills,
my mom wouldn't have recovered so soon.
You call me
Goddess Zuo?
What's wrong?
Is there any problem?
I know that they all call you Goddess Zuo.
I just follow suit.
Do I offend you?
No.
I just feel that
you're very different from
what you used to be.
Yes.
Even my mom and Qiu Ling say that
I've changed a lot.
But
the incident three years ago
was a matter of life and death.
How many people can remain the same
after experiencing that?
They might, at least, change a bit.
So
do you really
forget all of the past?
I've forgotten most of the past.
But it's not a big deal.
I come to the border with mom.
It's a new place and new life.
Every day I sell herbal medicine
and keep my mom company.
I live a full life.
And you're happy with your life.
That's good.
Oh, I haven't prepared herbal medicine yet.
I gotta go.
Enough!
Don't get so angry.
You're making such a big noise.
If His Highness Jun hears it,
he will blame you again.
It's all because of that stupid Feng Wu!
(Dwelling of Leisurely Elegance)
We really misjudged the situation this time.
It never occurred to me that
they would be partial to Feng Wu.
If we were at the capital,
even ten Feng Wus were no match for us.
Feng Wu has Phoenix Sword now.
What are we gonna do?
Goddess Zuo.
Taking Phoenix Sword away by force
doesn't make any sense.
You should think of some other ways.
These pills are from Celestial Palace.
You can recover your spirit energy
after taking them.
Do you feel that
Feng Wu is a little different?
Different?
Since childhood,
she has always been annoying like this.
It seems that
she is...
Do you mean that she seems not to know
who you are?
You left the Feng family to practice
cultivation when you were a child.
How did you know this?
I asked around the other day.
It is said that
since Feng Wu lost
cultivation base three years ago,
she seemed to have forgotten many things.
Besides, she behaved in a peculiar way.
Perhaps she got so upset that
she had a different disposition.
Looks like she didn't lie to me.
She did forget who I am.
Brother,
you seem to be really concerned with Feng Wu.
Shut up!
It's not bad that you're concerned with her.
You're her elder brother,
so you need to take care of her.
Take care of her?
I see.
Brother, do you have a plan?
What we can do now
is to marry Feng Wu off.
Marry her off?
If she gets married,
she cannot take Phoenix Sword with her.
Nor can the leader of the Feng family.
At that time,
the person who can inherit the family
is only me.
Sister,
you're my only sister.
So I will act in the best interests
of you at that time.
By doing so,
we can separate Feng Wu
with His Highness Jun.
She'll no longer be a hidden threat to us.
Feng Wu.
You also come from a distinguished family,
but you don't have Phoenix Blood.
You can just
do exactly what Zuo Qingluan tells you.
Besides,
only by trying to
get close to His Highness Jun
can you make your presence felt.
And the entrance examination to Junwu Academy
is just around the corner.
Zuo Qingluan won't stay
on the border for too long.
I promise you that
I will do my best
to bring you and His Highness Jun together.
This seems to be the only way out.
Okay.
It allows no delay.
Now I'm gonna meet aunt
and discuss with her the marriage of Feng Wu.
It is said that
the person with Phoenix Sword
is the heir to the Feng Family.
But how did the sword
get so rusted like this?
My Lady,
why not
take a grindstone to sharpen the sword?
Why is it so heavy?
Phoenix Sword is in my hands.
But if I cannot protect myself with it,
I will surely get caught in trouble.
I cannot wait anymore.
No.
I must have a try.
My Phoenix Blood...
Qingyun.
Master.
(The leader of the Celestial Palace)
I... Don't say anything.
Since you've done it,
you don't need to regret it.
If you want to achieve great success,
don't bother about trifling matters.
You seem to have been
scared out of your wits.
Don't be like that!
Master,
you have already known that Feng Wu was...
Shut up!
You should act
as if nothing has happened today,
you haven't done anything
and I don't know anything of it.
Keep this Ice Bracelet.
It can cover up the presence of Phoenix Blood
so that no one can find it.
Since you have got Phoenix Blood,
you should think about
how to use it to your advantage.
My Lady,
what do you think of Goddess Zuo?
She is a nice person.
I'm grateful to her.
I don't mean this.
I mean that
many people say
His Highness Jun and her
are a match made in heaven.
Besides, it's very possible that
she would be the new Spiritual Princess.
I don't care
whether His Highness Jun and her
are a match made in heaven.
Besides, I...
Goddess Zuo.
Feng Wu.
I
come here to give you
some pills or something.
They cannot help you
regain your cultivation base,
but they can improve your health.
Thank you very much indeed.
You
are trying out the sword?
I don't have any spirit energy
in my body.
To me,
Phoenix Sword is just like
a piece of scrap iron.
Let me teach you, okay?
♪I tried to hold back
the first drop of tears♪
♪yet ended up crying a river.♪
♪A cicada was enlightened after meditation.♪
♪Suddenly, everything became kind.♪
♪The flying fish folded its wings.♪
♪The words were written on the paper.♪
♪I stare into space with my bare eyes.♪
♪No need to constrain your youth.♪
♪Let the laughter be heard.♪
♪On my face there's a look of love.♪
♪That time can't erase.♪
♪To win your favor,♪
♪I need to get my story straight.♪
♪I'm at a loss for words
due to the chaotic world.♪
♪My stubbornness for love♪
♪is too conceited to be defeated.♪
♪Stand in the heavy frost♪
♪to wait for the blossom.♪
♪There's no better song
than the Phoenix's singing.♪
♪I'm like a beggar in love.♪
♪Wondering on love's path
and collecting your tender words.♪
♪To win your favor,♪
♪I need to get my story straight.♪
♪I'm at a loss for words
due to the chaotic world.♪
♪My stubbornness for love♪
♪is too conceited to be defeated.♪
♪Stand in the heavy frost♪
♪to wait for the blossom.♪
♪There's no better song
than the Phoenix's singing.♪
♪I'm like a beggar in love.♪
♪Wondering on love's path
and collecting your tender words.♪
♪Nothing has changed
from the beginning to the end.♪