=Dance of the Phoenix=
(Episode 30)
How do I look?
Jun Linyuan!
Come back!
I hope today we'll forget everything
and have a happy and normal day.
Forget about cultivation, the enmity
and the struggle for power.
How could you leave me like this?
Don't you know
that I still want to spend many more
such happy days with you?
Wu.
Zhao Ge.
I think Jun Linyuan is still alive.
I can feel him.
Do you trust me?
Of course, I do.
But we need to perk up
before we can go rescue him.
You gotta cheer up.
Okay?
It's the legendary Master Mu!
Don't know what kinda crime he's committed.
How can they execute him for no reason?
It's so unfair!
Be careful with what you say.
The time is different now.
The cultivators of Junwu Academy
have all disappeared.
I'm afraid the world
is about to change hands.
Stop talking.
It's not safe.
Let's go home! Come on!
Let's go! Hurry.
Come on!
Dear fellows!
Stop right there!
We know what you are going to say.
Holy Queen Gao will execute Master Mu.
He has only one day left.
You want us to help you
to get him out, right?
Dream on!
We are not their match at all!
We also want to save Master Mu,
but it's literally
a suicide mission!
Fellows,
could you please hear Feng Wu out?
Feng Wu, have you thought about us?
If we keep fighting like this,
what will happen to us?
Have you thought of that?
That's right.
Have you thought about us?
Master Mu sacrificed himself
for protecting us.
Besides, if Feng Wu hadn't
brought us all here,
we would have long been
taken by Holy Queen Gao!
She's right!
You've all seen what happened to her
and Goddess Zuo in the Illusion Mirror.
We don't want to be enslaved either!
However, even if we are going to fight back,
with your unknown identity,
how are you qualified to be our leader?
That's exactly my thought.
It makes sense!
Who gave her the right to...
Everybody, please be quiet.
What you said all makes sense.
But could you please let me say something?
Yes,
I don't belong here.
When I first got here,
I felt so depressed.
I couldn't help thinking why I should
carry the burden I shouldn't have carried,
and face the difficulties
I shouldn't have faced.
I admit
that my original purpose
was merely to awaken my Master Mu Jiuzhou
so that he could tell me the answer.
But then I met all of you,
and things have changed ever since.
Be it spirit energy, cultivation base,
the rise and fall of Qianyuan Continent,
or the duty to guard the people,
none of them was my concern before.
I was only interested in cooking,
collecting herbs,
and enjoying a carefree life.
But because I met you,
now I have friends,
family,
even my beloved.
I've fell in love with this place!
You want to know why I choose to stay here
and fight back?
Because I truly love this place.
And I'm sure
that
you love this place even more than I do!
In order not to lose more of our classmates,
friends and loved ones,
I hope
we can stick together.
It's not for me,
but for yourselves.
Let's guard and fight for our beautiful life,
our academy,
and our home we all cherish dearly.
Wu, I'll go with you!
Me, too!
I'm going with you!
-So are we!
We are going! So are we! So are we!
So am I!
Feng Xun! What are you doing here?
Xuan Yi sent me a secret letter.
I'm here to find you guys.
I can't let you guys go for a fight
without me!
Have you found any clue?
It doesn't matter.
Holy Queen Gao must think that we are not
strong enough to attack head-on,
so we'll take her by surprise
and attack Junwu Divine Hall
before dawn while she's unprepared.
Fight to the death!
Eliminate demons and uphold justice!
What's the matter?
No worry.
I know you are concerned about Boss Jun.
But I trust Feng Wu's intuition.
I'm sure he's fine.
Xuan Yi.
Do you know
who I met this time
when I was at Penglai Pavilion?
The leader of Celestial Palace.
She was there to see Old Master.
After she left,
Old Master told me
that Zhao Ge's spirit energy is blocked
not because
she has limited talent.
What do you mean?
There's a valuable treasure
in Zhao Ge's body.
Red Sacred Bead,
which is the thing
that stops Zhao Ge's spirit energy
from increasing.
As a result, her cultivation base
has been weaker than the average.
Red Sacred Bead?
Red Sacred Bead is a precious treasure
left from the ancient times.
When it takes effect,
it can greatly increase the spirit energy.
However,
as soon as the bead separates from its host,
the host will perish right away.
There's no way to keep both.
Feng Xun,
promise me
you won't tell Zhao Ge about this.
That's why I'm here to tell you only.
The leader of Celestial Palace
sent her to the capital
so that no one else
could find out about this.
She's been trying to find a cure for Zhao Ge.
She's talked to Old Master many times
to find a way to separate
the bead from Zhao Ge's body,
but had no luck yet.
Xuan Yi,
with Zhao Ge's situation...
After we finished our mission,
I'll help Zhao Ge to find a solution.
No matter what,
I'll be with her
and keep her safe.
You are so bad!
Come here.
Where's the night patrol?
The people of Darknight Court
are so unreliable!
They can't even get the most basic job right!
Oh, no!
Where's the woman
we captured from the Feng family?
Bring her to me.
Yes.
Hey! Were you sleeping?
What's going on?
People all say that you are dead.
Do you know how sad Feng Wu is hearing that?
I found
Phoenix Blood.
But Lord Damon caught me.
Phoenix Blood? Where is it?
I've sealed it inside the wall
of the secret chamber.
Please go find it,
and give it to Feng Wu,
so that she can
stand a chance to fight against
Lord Damon and Holy Queen Gao.
I'll get you out of here first.
Don't mind me.
Go help Feng Wu.
If you are dead,
Feng Wu will be miserable
for the rest of her life.
Let me get you out first.
You can tell the rest to Feng Wu yourself.
Are you out of your mind?
Neither of us can get out in this case.
Cut the crap! Let's go!
Help! Someone broke into the jail!
-Oh, no!
-You should...
It's the Invisible Pill of Darknight Court.
You can hide inside the wall
or underground for two hours.
I promise you.
I will give Phoenix Blood to Feng Wu.
You...
Do not die.
Otherwise, no one will fight with me anymore.
My Lord.
Leave me the stuff,
and I'll spare your life.
It's here! Follow me!
Let's go!
Off you go.
What's with the noise outside?
Your Majesty,
Feng Wu and the remaining cultivators
of Junwu Academy
are attacking the Divine Hall right now!
What?
She's actually bold enough
to attack me first!
Let's go.
Holy Queen Gao!
How dare you
attack Junwu Divine Hall?
You'll surely make
your Master Mu Jiuzhou proud.
Unfortunately,
today will be an end for you.
None of you can get out of here!
Feng Wu!
It's all because of you,
my Mingye
ends up like this!
Yu Mingye
could have had
a much happier life without you!
You don't deserve to be a father at all!
I'm the ruler of this continent!
Wanna kill me?
You are so ignorant!
Feng Wu!
No!
Phoenix Blood!
Stop her!
Go!
Master Mu! Master Mu!
Master Mu!
Wake up!
Come on! I'll take you out!
Don't!
Don't bother.
Just leave yourself.
Master Mu!
Let's attack Junwu Divine Hall!
Listen,
Feng Wu has brought people to save us.
Let's go!
Feng Wu...
How can she fight against
Lord Demon and Holy Queen Gao alone?
This is the only way
at this point!
Master Mu, what are you...
I can't hold it anymore!
We have to win more time for Feng Wu!
She's done so much for me.
It's time for me to do something for her.
Zhao Ge! What are you doing?
Red Sacred Bead.
How did you know?
Zhao Ge! Calm down!
We will figure out a way!
We even removed
Loveless Insect Venom from Boss Jun's body!
Zhao Ge!
Yi.
I'm so lucky
to have met you!
Don't!
Wu!
You've got to win!
-Zhao Ge! What are you going to do?
-Zhao Ge!
Zhao Ge!
Under heaven and the emperor star,
-tribulation strikes!
-Zhao Ge!
Red Sacred Bead!
Condense!
Yi!
Zhao Ge,
if this is your fate,
I'll go with you.
Zhao Ge!
Xuan Yi!
Feng Wu!
Put down your sword and stop resisting!
Mom!
Or else, I'll kill your mom!
Feng Wu! Don't mind me!
-Gao Wei!
-Mom!
Feng Wu, are you okay?
Are you alright?
Feng Xun, get my mom out of here!
Okay.
No, Feng Wu!
I can't leave you here alone!
Mom, don't worry about me.
Just go!
-No! I can't!
-Let's go, Madam. Come on.
Feng Wu!
Jun Linyuan!
Mu Jiuzhou
passed all his spirit energy
to you!
Jun Linyuan,
you win.
I guess it's destiny.
There's nothing I can do about it.
So why did you go through all the trouble?
If Mu Jiuzhou
didn't reject me back then
for his cultivation,
if I didn't
marry into this Junwu Divine Hall,
if...
There are no "ifs" in this world!
And now,
you have also left me.
For all these years,
I've never done anything for you.
This time,
I'll
go
with you.
Father,
let me take you home.
Boss Jun,
why do I have to
end up being the only single one?
Compared with Xuan Yi,
I'm really not half bad.
Yet he has Zhao Ge,
and I have no one.
The flowers are so pretty!
Where did you get them?
I wasn't sure
what to get for Feng Wu's wedding.
Giving her flowers is not a bad idea.
But would they look too cheesy
to match my identity?
What do you think I should give her?
Boss Jun,
why did they leave?
Stop complaining!
If you talk less,
the ladies would appreciate and hang out
with you more.
What do you mean?
You are so much trouble!
Wouldn't riding your sword be better?
Why do you have to do it
in the conventional way?
And also, that Yu Mingye
said he'd come with us,
but there's still no sign of him.
I guess
he's already at the Feng family
and hanging out with Feng Wu.
(Tongqi Pavilion)
Wu,
you are so beautiful today!
So will you one day!
Xuan Yi,
shouldn't you join the wedding procession?
What are you doing here?
Don't address me like that.
Boss Jun has Feng Xun to keep him company.
Plus,
I count myself as a member
of the Feng family now.
Alright.
We should thank Master Mu for securing
our nascent souls
with Dragon Phoenix Spirit Ring.
Wu and His Highness Jun
have also been helping us
find spiritual herbs.
Today is your wedding day.
We'll for sure
arrange everything well for you!
Got you!
And I'm wondering
when our wedding day will be.
Alright, you two.
Don't just stand there watching me.
You can wait outside.
Okay.
Then we'll go to the front gate
and welcome the procession.
Let's go.
Can't believe
my Feng Wu will get married soon!
Time really files.
Mom!
I feel sad about your leaving.
I really do.
Mom!
Madam,
it's a happy day.
We should be happy for Young Lady.
That's right.
We should be happy.
I won't cry.
I won't cry anymore.
Mom.
Now,
let's put the bridal veil on for her.
Come here.
Mom.
Qiu Ling.
Master,
you scared me.
What are you doing here?
Would you like to take a rest
in the front hall?
The wedding procession will be here soon.
Feng Wu.
I'm here to pick you up.
This is the story of my second life.
Don't care too much about how it ends.
The most important thing
is that we've experienced,
grown up,
and loved.
♪I tried to hold back
the first drop of tears♪
♪yet ended up crying a river.♪
♪A cicada was enlightened after meditation.♪
♪Suddenly, everything became kind.♪
♪The flying fish folded its wings.♪
♪The words were written on the paper.♪
♪I stare into space with my bare eyes.♪
♪No need to constrain your youth.♪
♪Let the laughter be heard.♪
♪On my face there's a look of love.♪
♪That time can't erase.♪
♪To win your favor,♪
♪I need to get my story straight.♪
♪I'm at a loss for words
due to the chaotic world.♪
♪My stubbornness for love♪
♪is too conceited to be defeated.♪
♪Stand in the heavy frost♪
♪to wait for the blossom.♪
♪There's no better song
than the Phoenix's singing.♪
♪I'm like a beggar in love.♪
♪Wondering on love's path
and collecting your tender words.♪
♪To win your favor,♪
♪I need to get my story straight.♪
♪I'm at a loss for words
due to the chaotic world.♪
♪My stubbornness for love♪
♪is too conceited to be defeated.♪
♪Stand in the heavy frost♪
♪to wait for the blossom.♪
♪There's no better song
than the Phoenix's singing.♪
♪I'm like a beggar in love.♪
♪Wondering on love's path
and collecting your tender words.♪
♪Nothing has changed
from the beginning to the end.♪