=Dance of the Phoenix=
(Episode 28)
I have been unable to come to the academy
to pay you a visit
in your dwelling all along.
I am finally here today.
I know you have nobody to look after you
and you handle
these medicinal herbs every day.
Don't tire your eyes.
Mom.
I am already a spiritual elder.
Right.
I forgot it.
You are no longer the girl
that you used to be
and don't need my protection any longer.
Mom.
No.
Madam.
I am sorry.
I don't know why
I look exactly like your daughter.
But I really can't indulge myself
in your motherly love
with this face resembling hers.
Also, I should return this Phoenix Sword
to your Feng family.
I have always known that
you are not my daughter Feng Wu.
After all, she has been
in my womb for ten months
and I have brought her up painstakingly.
How could I not see the difference
between you and Feng Wu?
But I lost my husband first.
Then I lost my daughter.
I have nobody to care about.
I still remember
when I saw you for the first time,
you were covered in blood
and looked exactly like my daughter.
How could I close the door on you?
As time passed,
I got used to having you around me.
I saw you as a gift from god.
Mom.
No.
Madam.
No matter what it is,
I know
you have been kind to me.
You have been treating me
as your biological daughter.
I cherish your love a lot.
However, from now on,
I will feel ashamed to continue...
You need not,
kid.
I should thank you.
After Feng Wu's father passed away,
as she grew day by day,
it was harder and harder for her to smile.
She wanted to protect me from being bullied.
She wanted to shoulder the load
of the whole Feng family like her father.
When she felt hurt,
she put up with the pain.
When she felt aggrieved,
she endured in silence.
However, you are not like her.
You laugh and cry when you want to.
When I saw you,
I recalled what Feng Wu was like in the past.
My Feng Wu can't come back again.
But you are still here.
The Phoenix Sword belongs to you.
Jun Linyuan is yours, too.
You need not mind who you are.
You are who you are.
People stay with you
for who you are.
I gotta go now.
I have to return to our Feng family.
It is getting cold.
I made an article of thick clothing for you.
I will ask Qiu Ling to bring it
to you some other day.
Mom.
I dreamed of Feng Wu.
She asked me to tell you
to eat more and cover yourself
with quilts while sleeping.
Mom.
No more words.
I got it.
You should also
eat more and cover yourself
with quilts while sleeping.
Are you still feeling sad
for your senior sister?
Yi.
I am fine.
Maybe this is
a kind of relief for my senior sister.
What about the relationship
between you and Feng Wu?
Overnight,
my senior sister passed away
and my best friend
turned out to be another person.
My thoughts are in a mess now.
I don't know what to do.
People have to go through things
to grow up gradually.
Since you are concerned about her,
just go to see her.
It will be fine
if you two bare your soul to each other.
I know she had no choice.
But, every time I think of
getting close to her,
I feel I am betraying the real Wu.
Flowers remain the same every year.
But people come and go year after year.
Miss Zhao Ge,
since
the original Feng Wu has left,
which is cut and dried
and the present Feng Wu is your good friend,
which is also fact,
you need to face her,
accept her,
keep the former Feng Wu in your memory
and value the days
you spent with this Feng Wu.
I believe
she will definitely understand you.
What you said makes sense.
Nonetheless,
I shouldn't have said
that about Wu yesterday.
She treated me so nicely.
She also removed the poison from me.
and cooked delicious food for me.
What should I do?
Go apologize to her sincerely.
Since you are good friends,
she will certainly forgive you.
You are right.
If I cook some palatable food for Feng Wu,
she will forgive me for sure.
Xuan Yi. Xuan Yi.
It is surprising
that you can also console a girl.
If the other female disciples
of Junwu Academy
get to know this,
their hearts will be broken.
You are a young fellow
without a female partner,
so you don't understand.
How could you!
Xuan Yi!
Colored Phoenix.
Silly bird.
Why are you calling me silly bird again?
You are more and more impolite.
You finally showed yourself.
I want to ask you about something.
Since my master woke up,
there have always been people around him.
So I got no chance to ask him
where I come from and who I am.
Did he tell you about this?
No.
You must find a chance to ask him yourself.
You have waited for so long
and made so many efforts
only to make clear of these things.
Why don't you hurry to ask him?
Besides,
though my master came to himself,
be honest with me,
his spirit energy
has declined substantially, right?
How could that happen?
He is the great ruler of this continent,
and the founder of Junwu Academy.
Among all the cultivators
across Qianyuan Continent,
he is most likely to become an immortal.
Don't talk nonsense.
Why are you looking at me this way?
Are you doubting my words?
In terms of seniority,
I am a senior to you.
How can you doubt my words?
Master Mu!
I will give you another chance.
If you don't tell me the truth,
I will cook you.
I will tell.
(Library Pavilion)
According to what you said,
back then, my master has
used half a drop of phoenix blood
to prolong my life.
Thus, he is in such conditions now.
If we compare spirit energy to
the blood running in Mu Jiuzhou's body,
the Phoenix Blood is like his heart.
No matter how much blood he has,
without a heart,
he will be a living dead.
To put it simply,
he is like a machine
losing the core component.
Com...component?
Master,
why are you up?
Hurry to go back to rest.
Don't worry.
Go have a walk with me.
Master,
you have sacrificed
such important stuff for me.
Why didn't you tell me?
You failed to keep the secret.
We are destined to cross paths.
Since I am your master,
I am obliged to do so.
A teacher for a day
is a father for a lifetime.
Don't you remember?
Yes, I do.
Now our Qianyuan Continent is in chaos.
Holy Queen Gao
takes the chance to stir up trouble.
I am useless.
Relying on my own strength,
I can't reverse the situation at all.
But you are different, Master.
If you still have your past spirit energy,
on your own,
you can turn the tide.
But I...
I am always thinking that it is a waste
for me to have the Phoenix Blood.
Do you still remember what I taught you?
Don't be arrogant and conceited.
Don't belittle yourself.
Master,
when did you teach me these?
You taught these
to another Feng Wu.
Anyway, am I right or not?
Yes, you are right.
But under the current circumstances,
what should we do?
All these arose out of me.
So I am meant to
bring it to an end.
Master,
what do you mean?
Don't be too worried.
When the proper time comes,
I will surely send you back
where you come from.
Are you sure
you can apologize by making this?
Of course.
Feng Wu once taught me to cook this.
It is
the Master Feng's instant noodles.
She said that when she was unhappy,
felt sad and depressed
and was up to her eyes in work,
a bowl of steaming instant noodles
would be the best thing
to cheer her up.
However, it requires a lot of work.
The noodles have to be fried.
Well,
let me help you.
Really?
Yi.
Didn't you say that even if we cultivators
weren't abstinent from food,
we couldn't indulge ourselves in eating?
It doesn't matter.
After eating so much of your food,
I should repay your kindness.
What should we do for the next?
Cut the noodles.
OK.
Look carefully.
Feng Wu.
We are very sorry.
We believed the rumors and misunderstood you.
Never mind.
I know that Feng Wu is magnanimous
and won't blame us for what we did.
Feng Wu.
Since you are the disciple of Master Mu,
you must have learned his real skills.
It is said that
he once became a Spirit Immortal
and was very close to immortal ascension.
Please tell us
how he taught you.
Please. Please.
If we can learn
one or two superior skills of him,
there will be hope for us
to become Great Spiritual Masters.
Zhao Ge.
What is that?
Did you prepare it for me?
It is the instant noodle.
The instant noodle?
What is that?
I never heard of that.
But how could Zhao Ge do this?
We are cultivators.
It is necessary for us
to fast for physical cultivation.
But she
just eats as she likes.
She also tries to drag others
into her indolence.
Zhao Ge and Feng Wu
are still young,
so I guess they just like trying new things.
I have
many immortal grass and spirit pills.
After taking them,
our cultivation will be improved.
Feng Wu,
would you like me to fetch some for you?
I have them, too.
Feng Wu.
Please give me a detailed account
about how Master Mu taught you
to enable you to progress so fast.
I will give my spirit pills to you.
Me too.
Feng Wu, please tell me, too.
I will give all my spirit pills to you.
Zhao Ge.
Wu.
I will leave you to your business.
I will be off.
Why need you leave?
All fellow cultivators,
I know that
you are all curious about
and admire Master Mu.
But even if you asked me,
I don't know what to say.
How about this?
I will go back to ask my master
whether he is willing
to give lectures in the academy.
Really?
Can we really attend Master Mu's lectures?
But you have to wait
till this crisis is over.
I guess my master won't refuse.
You'd better go back to make preparations.
-Let's go.
Why are you standing there dumbly?
Come here quickly.
It is yummy.
Zhao Ge.
I decide to stop calling you
the incompetent chef.
Wu,
I am sorry.
I shouldn't have said that about you.
If you don't eat,
I will finish them all.
Hurry! Hurry!
Yi, I...
I...
I hope he didn't notice it.
Have you made up with Feng Wu?
Luckily, he didn't sense it.
Yes, I have.
The method you taught me helped a lot.
So I came to thank you.
You really came here only to thank me?
Of course.
I will be off if there is nothing else.
Eh.
It is really haw cake.
Miss Zhao Ge,
now the situation is getting
more and more complicated,
which is unexpected to all people.
But you need not worry.
No matter what happens,
I will stand by your side,
protect you
and be with you.
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Why are you allowing this to happen?
Junwu Clan and the Darknight Court
have been on opposing sides.
Your Majesty, you will put
the whole Qianyuan Continent
in jeopardy by doing this.
It is a fact that the Crown Prince
attempted to overthrow the Junwu Clan.
Is there anyone else who wants to defend him?
Come forward.
Nonsense!
You claimed His Highness
plotted against Junwu Clan.
What evidence do you have?
All courtiers.
Look!
Is the man sitting on the throne
still our Holy Sovereign?
He is obviously a puppet.
Spiritual Elder Fang,
please mind what you say.
You can vilify me,
but can't insult His Majesty.
You are not thinking that
by manipulating His Majesty,
you can bring everything
under control, are you?
All cultivators in the world have eyes to tell.
You talked so much nonsense.
Come on.
Kill me now.
If my death can
awaken all courtiers here.
I have nothing to fear.
Stop!
Spiritual Elder Fang
is the senior statesman of Junwu Clan
and has contributed a lot
to Qianyuan Continent over all these years.
At such a time,
you are still acting hypocritically
and shedding crocodile's tears.
Your life can be spared,
but you must be punished.
Attendants!
Take him away.
Have him remanded in custody and tried later.
Don't touch me.
Great Spiritual Master Yan,
why don't you say a word?
Do you have any unspeakable reason?
Your Majesty's doing is reasonable and fair.
I have no objection,
so I didn't say anything.
Very good!
All fellow spiritual masters,
allow me to say goodbye to you.
-Great Spiritual Master Yan, see you.
-See you.
Master.
Listen.
Now nobody is watching.
So, go hand over this letter
to Feng Wu herself.
Hurry up.
Yes, sir.
The Holy Queen Gao
is doing things so blatantly.
If this is the case,
we will imperil the lives
of all people of Junwu Academy
and implicate all of you
by staying here.
Well, if we don't stay here.
where can we go?
The Holy Queen Gao
has taken control of the whole capital.
Even if we manage to escape by luck,
tens of thousands of minions
of the Darknight Court
will definitely hunt down us.
Penglai Pavilion can't rival them
and can't protect us.
In this world,
can't we find a shelter anywhere?
You are all students of Junwu Academy.
The academy is your shelter.
None of you needs to leave.
You just stay here.
If the Holy Queen Gao
has Junwu Academy stormed,
we will fight with all our might.
We mustn't allow this to happen.
We can't put so many students here in danger
for our own sake.
Moreover,
even if we mobilize the whole academy,
we can't defeat the Holy Queen Gao's forces.
Now we can only choose
to leave.
You are all my students
and the fellow cultivators
of hundreds of disciples of Junwu Academy.
As cultivators,
confronted with the current disaster,
if we don't uphold justice with our swords,
how can we live up
to the reputation of our academy?
Your Highness,
I am not so capable
and only good at teaching.
But if I can do my bit
for the peace of Qianyuan Continent,
I will charge at the head
even if I may be smashed into pieces.
Your Majesty,
Master Mu is still waiting outside.
Did he say anything?
He just waited for several hours
and presented an old item to you.
But you lost your composure and wavered.
Master Mu Jiuzhou
is really a resourceful man.
He achieved his goal easily
without resorting to force.
It is a pity that
he didn't care about your feelings back then.
As a result, he broke your heart
and you tried to kill him
while he was weak.
If he gets to know that
what caused his beloved woman
to die at that time,
do you think...
Enough!
Stop saying more.
Under the current circumstances,
nobody
can stop me from carrying out my plan.
Go give it back to him
and ask him to leave.
I won't see him.
Master Mu.
It has been a long time.
Your evil-foreboding air
hasn't weakened at all.
After so many years,
have you got rid of the doubts in your mind
and been aware of what you want exactly?
My aspirations have never changed.
You need not trouble yourself with this.
Ziyan said that
she would put the past behind her.
She won't see you again.
You can leave now.
With your current cultivation base,
you can't rival me.
You'd better find a place
to enjoy some more happy days.
It won't be long before
I send you to the other world.
All disciples of Junwu Academy,
emergency muster!
All disciples,
I guess you all heard about
what is going on at present.
Now the wicked queen is in power
and she is manipulating His Majesty.
Many years ago,
Master Mu founded Junwu Academy
to eradicate the evil and defend the right.
As a member of Junwu Academy,
how can you shrink back and do nothing?
But, in the present situation,
it is undoubtedly a hopeless battle
if we fight against
the Darknight Court and Holy Queen Gao.
Master Zhao.
Do we really have a good chance of winning?
Yes, do we?
Don't talk about eradicating the evil
and defending the right.
To be honest,
we came here for cultivation back then
only for the centennial reputation
of the academy.
Is it really necessary for us
to die for
the intangible lofty ideals?
How come Junwu Academy
have students like you?
If Qianyuan Continent falls into disorder,
what will you do?
Staying aloof from trouble
can only keep you safe temporarily.
Have you conducted cultivation
only to satisfy your personal desires?
Master Mu.
Forget it.
If some disciples don't want to stay,
they can leave now.
Feng Wu.
Don't worry too much about me.
My spiritual cognition has been damaged.
It is natural for me to be unable
to do things as I wish.
I have lived for so many years.
It is a great blessing.
Master.
I am worthless.
I can't share your burden.
I can't help Jun Linyuan out, either.
I didn't expect
the present Junwu Academy
is like a heap of loose sand.
I guess all sects
also only try to secure their own safety.
Such being the case,
we won't be able to fight against
the Darknight Lord Demon and the Holy Queen.
Master,
what should we do, then?
The only way out for us now
is to fight a decisive battle
relying on your power.
My power?
Yes.
I need you to return to where you come from
to find the power
and to do it all over again.
In this way,
we can go back in time
and stop all this
before it happens.
Master.
Is this the only way?
If changes occur after I go back,
what should I do?
Everything is predestined.
You only need to let nature take its course.
OK.
Now go prepare for it.
I will have a rest for a while.
When the day after tomorrow comes,
I will see you off.
Jun Linyuan,
I promise I will come back
to face all this with you.
You must wait for me.
Come out.
Master Mu.
What power do you want
Feng Wu to find exactly
after she returns to where she comes from?
♪I tried to hold back
the first drop of tears♪
♪yet ended up crying a river.♪
♪A cicada was enlightened after meditation.♪
♪Suddenly, everything became kind.♪
♪The flying fish folded its wings.♪
♪The words were written on the paper.♪
♪I stare into space with my bare eyes.♪
♪No need to constrain your youth.♪
♪Let the laughter be heard.♪
♪On my face there's a look of love.♪
♪That time can't erase.♪
♪To win your favor,♪
♪I need to get my story straight.♪
♪I'm at a loss for words
due to the chaotic world.♪
♪My stubbornness for love♪
♪is too conceited to be defeated.♪
♪Stand in the heavy frost♪
♪to wait for the blossom.♪
♪There's no better song
than the Phoenix's singing.♪
♪I'm like a beggar in love.♪
♪Wondering on love's path
and collecting your tender words.♪
♪To win your favor,♪
♪I need to get my story straight.♪
♪I'm at a loss for words
due to the chaotic world.♪
♪My stubbornness for love♪
♪is too conceited to be defeated.♪
♪Stand in the heavy frost♪
♪to wait for the blossom.♪
♪There's no better song
than the Phoenix's singing.♪
♪I'm like a beggar in love.♪
♪Wondering on love's path
and collecting your tender words.♪
♪Nothing has changed
from the beginning to the end.♪