=Dance of the Phoenix=
(Episode 18)
The second floor of the Library
is off-limits.
This floor
is open to all disciples to borrow books.
I've noticed you for a while.
Though I've never said anything,
I feel there's a connection of some sort
between you and me.
I'm sure you've also sensed the same thing.
And from your eyes, I can see
that you are looking for something.
I can't tell you the answer.
But they might be able to.
This is the key
to the side door of the Library.
You can have the run of this place
in the future if you'd like.
But don't tell
anybody else about this,
including His Highness Jun.
Why do you mention him in particular?
Junior Sister.
Feng Wu is being punished.
Her spirit energy
must have decreased a lot.
Take this.
This...
This is the Celestial Pill
from Celestial Palace.
Yes.
I knew you'd recognize it.
Senior Sister...
Goddess Zuo,
please don't call me Junior Sister anymore.
I've never been admitted
into Celestial Palace
and taught by the leader.
So it doesn't count.
Zhao Ge.
We should treat each other
like we used to.
Don't let the others
affect you.
Anyway,
you have the pill now.
Hope it can help you.
Boss Jun,
are you alright?
Where's Feng Wu?
Wu said she needed to go back
to take care of something.
She should be back to her room.
After all, it's Junwu Academy.
She'll be fine.
The relationship between you
and His Highness Jun
is destined to be tough.
If you two are determined to be together,
it'll bring you endless mishaps.
Supervisor Wu,
isn't what you said a little extreme?
Why are we destined to have a tough relationship?
I don't follow.
You are not you.
Yet he is he.
Based on what your horoscope signs suggest,
your destiny has long been predetermined.
You've got to know clearly
what you really want.
Don't forget your initial purpose
just because of affection.
I'm telling you this
from my own experience.
Supervisor Wu!
Remember.
Don't step into the off-limits.
I am not I.
Yet he is he.
I'm your Master Mu Jiuzhou.
I know you don't belong here.
But, remember,
from now on,
you'll be Feng Wu.
If you want to find out who you really are
and why you got here,
you gotta live your life well.
(Feng's Mansion)
Your Highness.
What brought you here?
Please come in.
No need.
I'm only here to ask
if Feng Wu is back.
My Lady?
She's not back yet.
What happened?
Don't worry.
She's probably taking a walk somewhere.
I'll go keep looking for her.
Okay. If there's anything,
please let us know, Your Highness.
I will.
Don't tell Mrs. Feng that I came by.
Wait for my news.
(Feng's Mansion)
It's so late.
Zhao Ge must be worried sick.
And I haven't heard anything
from that poker face!
He's gone to the Divine Hall
for a whole day now.
Who is it?
Hey!
You almost burned my hair!
It's you!
(Auspicious Clouds)
So, what were you doing over there?
The second floor of the Library
is a forbidden zone of Junwu Academy.
In that case,
what were you doing there at this hour?
I...
I was studying
in case I'd fall behind.
So, I'm also allowed
to study there.
It's your excuse!
Okay! Alright!
You've seen that
there's energy barrier in the forbidden zone.
We have no way to break in.
How about this?
Let's keep it a secret
and pretend that we've never been here.
What do you say?
Okay.
You've studied for long.
You must be hungry.
Shall we go out and eat something?
No.
As cultivators,
we can't always think about
satisfying our taste buds.
I know you too well.
Don't make yourself become a fogey
like those people.
We are different
from Jun Linyuan and the others.
Let's go!
No! I'm not going!
Zhao Ge.
Wake up.
Don't sleep here.
Wu.
Where have you been this late?
His Highness Jun has been looking for you.
Jun Linyuan
came here to look for me?
Not only that,
he almost turned the entire
Junwu Academy upside down!
He's left for the Feng's Mansion.
So...
So my mom knows already?
Oh, no! I have to go back.
Don't bother.
He was just here.
He told me you'd be back soon
and asked me not to worry.
Then he went to the Feng's Mansion to inform them.
That's good to know.
Then have a good night's sleep.
Don't forget to explain it
to His Highness Jun tomorrow.
He was really worried about you.
I will.
Now, go to bed.
You silly bird!
What's the relationship
between Wu Youdao and Master?
Why does he seem
so familiar to me?
Well...
I have no idea.
But it may be an opportunity for you.
And Wu Youdao could be the key.
Since you've already entered Junwu Academy,
just focus on cultivation
and don't be distracted by other things.
Always remember your purpose of being here.
Which is to awaken Master
and then leave.
What?
You don't wanna leave anymore?
Are you in love with that...
I'm not!
I'm not in love with Jun Linyuan!
Did I say his name?
You just gave yourself away!
You can fool others
but you can't fool yourself.
Just think about it.
After all, you are different
from the people here.
Though you spend all the time together
and nothing's happened yet,
no one can guarantee that your body
won't change eventually.
Stop talking!
I know it.
-Feng Wu.
-Your Highness.
I still have things to do.
I've got to go now.
Our relationship is destined to be tough.
If so, I can't put him in trouble.
I know it is the right thing to do.
But...
Hurry! We'll be late!
Come on! Hurry!
Where are you going?
You don't know?
Holy Queen Gao came
to the academy for inspection.
We don't have classes this afternoon.
Stop talking to her! Let's go!
I heard that Her Majesty
asked Zuo Qingluan to accompany her.
People say that Her Majesty
has already seen her as daughter-in-law.
She'll most likely be the Spiritual Princess.
So it's not just a rumor!
To be honest,
she and His Highness Jun
are really a perfect match.
Whatever! I'm not that lucky anyway.
Let's go take a look.
Come on! Let's go.
Feng Wu! Feng Wu!
Why does he always follow me?
Where are you going?
We don't have classes this afternoon.
So I come to the Library to study.
You've been acting mysteriously.
Now, confess.
Are you hiding something from us?
Not at all.
What could I possibly hide from you?
Oh, by the way. Holy Queen Gao is here.
Don't you wanna go take a look?
I came here to get you
so that we can go together.
To be fair, Holy Queen Gao
is quite amiable.
She loves Boss Jun so much,
and she cares a lot about me and Xuan Yi.
Even so, I just don't like her.
I like a nagging person like my mom,
or someone like your mom.
What's special about my mom?
It's hard to explain.
But you can see so much joy in her eyes
when she looks at you.
You know what?
Holy Queen Gao came to Junwu Academy
for her birthday celebration.
So how's that related to me?
I haven't finished.
On her birthday,
she will pick one male and one female
from the newly-recruited disciples
to perform Double Swordsmanship
that was created by Master Mu.
The male disciple
will certainly be His Highness Jun.
As for the female disciple...
Needless to say,
it must be Zuo Qingluan.
Due to the limited cultivation base,
none of the other disciples is her match.
Who else could it be?
You!
I'm not interested at all.
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Think about it.
Won't you be jealous
if she performs Double Swordsmanship
with Jun Linyuan?
Why would I be jealous?
Hey...
You were just fine a couple of days ago.
It's so hard to understand you girls!
Greetings to you, Your Majesty!
Rise.
I'm so impressed
by your energy
and your thirst for righteousness.
You represent the disciples of Junwu Academy.
You are also the future
of Qianyuan Continent.
Two paragons of virtue will be picked
from our disciples to perform
Double Swordsmanship
on Your Majesty's birthday.
It's not only an honor to them,
but also an honor to Junwu Academy.
I actually wasn't going
to have a celebration.
It's just a birthday.
There's no need to make it a big deal.
But His Majesty
enjoys a blast,
and he also wants to see
the abilities of the new recruits.
His Majesty and Your Majesty love people,
and care a great deal of the young disciples,
which is indeed a blessing
for our Junwu Clan!
I think the male representative
should be His Highness Jun.
As for the female representative...
It should be Senior Sister Qingluan!
No one is more qualified than her
to perform together
with His Highness Jun.
Mu Yao!
Behave yourself in front of Her Majesty!
Qingluan is a good girl.
I do like her.
His Majesty will also be happy
to see her performing with Linyuan.
They are such a perfect match.
Your Majesty, you will certainly
enjoy a lovely birthday this year.
Your Majesty,
I have a suggestion.
Linyuan, what's on your mind?
We can hold a challenge.
From today till your birthday,
all the female disciples
can participate into the challenge,
which is like a "wheel battle."
Whoever stands to the end
will be selected for the performance.
Linyuan, your suggestion is good.
Which female disciple do you prefer?
I don't have
a particular recommendation.
I just think that a rash decision
won't be convincing.
Whoever is capable the most
should be the ultimate choice.
What Linyuan said makes sense.
Then let's do it.
If nobody makes to the end of the challenge,
then you'll still team up
with Qingluan.
I'm really looking forward to this!
If Feng Wu
misbehaves again,
I'll report it to Dean Ning
and expel her from Junwu Academy!
Supervisor Wu,
please say something!
Master Zhao,
calm down!
Please calm down!
This is the quiz of this time, right?
You haven't got a chance
to check the disciples' names
after grading the papers, have you?
I haven't.
Now, take a look at this paper.
I remember this one.
It's the most insightful answer
I've ever seen.
But I haven't got a chance to check the name.
I don't know whose paper it is.
Look closer, then.
Which disciple is it?
I've never noticed
there's such an
outstanding disciple in my class,
who even learned the Cultivation Method
and Spiritual Cognition ahead of time.
Actually, this disciple
is that trouble-maker Feng Wu
you just mentioned.
But...
You want to ask
how she managed
to learn the things you taught
when she was constantly
driven out of the class by you
and punished with standing outside.
Am I right?
Yes! Exactly!
Although she was punished
by standing outside every time,
she still learned everything
you taught by heart
and reflected her hard work on her paper.
Moreover, she studied late
every day in the Library
to look through the books
and digest what she has learned.
That's why she felt tired and sleepy
during the day.
So,
you still want to expel
such an excellent disciple from the academy?
Boss Jun.
You are still up?
It's okay. You can go to bed first.
You've been absent-minded
since you met His Majesty and Her Majesty.
What's wrong?
No worry.
I know he is a big mouth.
But he's asleep now.
You can trust me.
I won't tell anybody else.
I'm nervous.
I hope Feng Wu can perform
the swordsmanship with me
in front of His Majesty and Her Majesty.
In that case,
it'll be much easier for me
to recommend her as my Spiritual Princess.
But I find her
quite cold and distant these days.
And I don't know why.
You won't be able
to find an answer to that in books.
Why don't you
just go ask her?
Ask her?
Yes.
It's very hard to read
a girl's mind.
Senior Sister, congratulations
to you in advance!
When His Majesty and Her Majesty see
what a perfect match you
and His Highness Jun are,
they may issue an edict right on site
and make you the Spiritual Princess.
That's right!
Senior Sister and His Highness Jun
are a match made in heaven.
No one deserves His Highness Jun
more than our Senior Sister.
Feng Wu is just a broken-winged phoenix now.
How can she compare to our Senior Sister?
But that Zhao Ge,
as a disciple of Celestial Palace,
is actually on Feng Wu's side,
which is so hateful!
No matter what,
Zhao Ge is my Master's daughter,
as well as my Junior Sister!
If you say those nonsense
to hurt our sisterhood again,
I'll punish you severely!
I heard you, Senior Sister!
The most important thing right now
is to earn a reputation
for our Celestial Palace.
Senior Sister always protects Zhao Ge.
I will let Zhao Ge pay big time
for being an ungrateful traitor!
Zhao Ge.
Why don't you go to bed?
Wu.
I wanna know
what you are going to do
about the challenge this time.
I don't have a plan.
It's irrelevant to me.
But I think
you should fight for it!
Give me a break.
I don't think so.
Listen to me.
Though Zuo Qingluan is my Senior Sister,
it's
a celebration for Her Majesty's birthday,
if you can perform on that day,
it must be so amazing,
and
no one would say Feng Wu
doesn't deserve His Highness Jun anymore.
Just let them talk.
I don't care.
The one who's meant to leave cannot be kept.
It's better that nothing has ever happened.
Everybody can see
that His Highness Jun is into you.
Wu, don't you wanna fight for him?
Look at you!
You always concern about others!
Stop worrying. Just go to sleep.
Feng Wu,
you really don't care about my feelings?
I just don't believe it!
Why can't I have
what Feng Wu has?
Master is about to be here.
I need to go to class.
Nobody will protect you
while Feng Wu isn't around, right?
You and Feng Wu
are both pathetic losers!
You'll be sorry
if you talk about Feng Wu like that again!
Here's a reminder for you.
I've got a bunch of witnesses here.
You attacked me first.
What? You are going
to disobey your Senior Sister?
Go back and tell Feng Wu
to put her tail between her legs
just like you do,
so that I can spare your life!
Dream on!
I'll tell my mom on you.
She won't forgive you!
You are the one who's dreaming!
Your mom has long abandoned you!
That's bullshit!
How dare you to fight back?!
Mu Yao!
Zhao Ge! Zhao Ge!
Zhao Ge!
Mu Yao! What are you doing?
How could you do such a thing
to your classmate?
I did nothing wrong.
Zhao Ge attacked me first.
They've all seen it!
Even so,
you must have provoked her first!
Zhao Ge's cultivation base is not your match.
She wouldn't challenge you for no reason!
You...
She seems a little slow,
but she's not a fool at all!
If anything happens to her,
I won't let you off easily!
Zhao Ge.
I'm sorry!
I failed in protecting you!
You don't usually go to class.
What are you doing here today?
I found a pond
on the top of the back hill.
Would you like to go fishing with me?
Why do you always go to the back hill?
Master said the back hill was quite steep
and asked us to stay away from it.
I'm there for fun.
So, are you going or not?
I don't have time.
And I'm not in the mood.
I haven't found what I need yet.
I'm not going.
There's never an end to cultivation.
You gotta learn how to balance your life.
Let's go.
You are not you.
Yet he is he.
Based on what your horoscope signs suggest,
your destiny has long been predetermined.
You've got to know clearly
what you really want.
Yu Mingye,
if you want to take me to go fishing,
let's go!
Feng Wu! Feng Wu!
Bad news! Zhao Ge is hurt!
What happened?
It's ridiculous!
The school has just opened for a few days,
you already made such a big mistake!
Luckily, she was sent
to the doctor in time and saved.
Dean Ning.
Zhao Ge attacked me first.
It's the truth!
Really?
Then let's hear what others will say.
You two,
be honest and tell us
what you saw.
Dean and Supervisor,
we don't know why they argued with Zhao Ge.
But when we arrived at the scene,
they've already begun to hurt her.
That's a lie!
Dean, Supervisor,
please investigate carefully!
We really...
Enough!
You seriously hurt your classmate,
yet you are still making excuses
and showing no sign of repentance!
I'm so disappointed in you!
Supervisor Wu.
According to the article 28
of the Rules of Junwu Academy,
"One who bullies classmate
and shows no repentance
shall be held
in confinement for seven days."
Guards,
take her away.
Senior Sister! Senior Sister! Senior Sister!
Senior Sister! Senior Sister!
Senior Sister!
I failed in disciplining my Junior Sister.
Dean, Supervisor,
I'd like to accept your punishment.
Zuo Qingluan.
Although you weren't involved,
you are after all their Senior Sister.
How are you going
to deal with this problem?
Zhao Ge is a Junior Sister of my sect.
I hope you can allow me
to take care of her in person
until she's recovered,
so that I can make up
for my mistake of negligence.
Zhao Ge has been heavily hurt.
You think this is all you can do
to make up for your mistake?
That's something you are obligated to do!
In my opinion,
Celestial Palace encouraged its people
to hurt a disciple,
which will discredit our academy
if word gets out.
We can't let them off so easily.
If we do,
who can guarantee that Zhao Ge
won't get hurt again?
I will strictly discipline them.
If someone dares to do it again,
I will ask our sect leader to kick her
out of our palace to warn the others.
It's a fact that Zhao Ge
has been severely hurt.
I have to seek justice for her!
As far as I'm concerned,
the one who hurt her has been punished,
and Zuo Qingluan has made a promise.
Let's put this thing to an end.
You are all classmates.
You should try to be forgiving.
Dean Ning, I'm sorry!
I'm never a broad-minded person.
Since you all want to end this thing,
it'll be improper if I don't let go.
So, I've made my decision.
I'll participate into the challenge
to fight for the performer
spot on Her Majesty's birthday!
Zuo Qingluan seems to be the only one
who has signed up for the challenge so far.
In this case,
you mean you want to compete with her?
Yes.
Why do you do this?
Your people all bully Zhao Ge
and accuse her of being a traitor.
What will make them proud the most
would be for you
to perform on Her Majesty's birthday.
So, I won't let you get your way!
Besides, it's an open and fair competition.
Everybody can attend, right?
Of course!
I sincerely apologize again.
And I accept your challenge.
Good.
In this case,
I'll grant you two this opportunity.
The challenge
will take place in three days.
Whoever wins the challenge
will perform Double Swordsmanship.
(Righteous Teaching Hall)
"A challenge will take place in three days.
These disciples will have a battle over
the performer spot on Her Majesty's birthday."
Feng Wu and Zuo Qingluan?
Yeah.
A Senior-rank Spiritual Practitioner is going
to challenge a Great Spiritual Master?
She's literally looking for trouble.
Tell me about it!
Is she crazy?
It's going to be quite a show!
I extended a challenge on impulse!
Now what should I do?
Feng Wu,
I tell you, you should just go for it.
I'll figure out a way to take her down.
I assure you that in three days,
she won't even be able to stand straight!
(Be Humble)
Don't do something foolish.
If anything bad
happened to her at this point,
people would naturally think
Feng Wu were behind it.
But...
Who put up
the notice this quickly?
What a busybody!
Now,
come with me.
I'll take you to a place.
You guys left without me again!
This place is breathtaking!
What is this place?
I named this place "Skyland."
I found this place by accident
when I was little.
I enjoyed flying around
with my sword back then.
"Skyland."
What a lovely name!
It's an ancient relic,
which
has already been formed
even before the establishment of Junwu Clan.
But there's no way to know
how long it's been in existence.
It's been that long?
I come here to cultivate
and enjoy the view
when I'm free.
And now, aside from me,
you are the only one who's visited here.
So,
you brought me here to...
There are only a couple of days left.
Your cultivation base for now
is far weaker than Zuo Qingyuan's.
I certainly know that.
So, you have to rely
on techniques to win her.
Junwu Clan features gold.
Our swordsmanship is invincible.
So incredible!
These skills have never been
showed to outsiders.
The key of the skills
lies in step moves instead of strength.
If you can master these skills,
you'll have a chance to win Zuo Qingyuan.
It's your turn now.
My turn?
You just demonstrated once.
It's so complicated.
I don't know how to do it.
For Zhao Ge,
and for you,
I've got to win the competition!
Senior Sister.
How is it going?
I've made a deal with the guard.
He will let you in.
Don't stay for too long.
Senior Sister! Senior Sister!
There are spells everywhere in this room.
My spirit energy
has been fully suppressed.
I'm in so much pain, Senior Sister!
Who gave you the right to do that?
I've told you,
no matter what,
you are not allowed to hurt Zhao Ge!
I made a mistake, Senior Sister!
I just don't understand.
Zhao Ge betrayed you,
but why do you still protect her?
You can have this.
Go ahead.
Don't cry!
Is it hurt?
♪I tried to hold back
the first drop of tears♪
♪yet ended up crying a river.♪
♪A cicada was enlightened after meditation.♪
♪Suddenly, everything became kind.♪
♪The flying fish folded its wings.♪
♪The words were written on the paper.♪
♪I stare into space with my bare eyes.♪
♪No need to constrain your youth.♪
♪Let the laughter be heard.♪
♪On my face there's a look of love.♪
♪That time can't erase.♪
♪To win your favor,♪
♪I need to get my story straight.♪
♪I'm at a loss for words
due to the chaotic world.♪
♪My stubbornness for love♪
♪is too conceited to be defeated.♪
♪Stand in the heavy frost♪
♪to wait for the blossom.♪
♪There's no better song
than the Phoenix's singing.♪
♪I'm like a beggar in love.♪
♪Wondering on love's path
and collecting your tender words.♪
♪To win your favor,♪
♪I need to get my story straight.♪
♪I'm at a loss for words
due to the chaotic world.♪
♪My stubbornness for love♪
♪is too conceited to be defeated.♪
♪Stand in the heavy frost♪
♪to wait for the blossom.♪
♪There's no better song
than the Phoenix's singing.♪
♪I'm like a beggar in love.♪
♪Wondering on love's path
and collecting your tender words.♪
♪Nothing has changed
from the beginning to the end.♪