=Love in A Dream=
=Episode 24=
What do you like
about Prince of Ning An?
He's not a good person.
Says who?
In my eyes,
he's the best.
You love me,
don't you?
You are
God's gift for me.
Su Qin.
Marry me.
I'm just an ordinary girl.
Since I was a child,
I have dreamed
to be with someone
that I love.
A loving couple
lives a simple life together.
The truth is,
I have been lying to you.
I know.
Chun,
I will marry you formally,
no longer as a concubine.
I give you my promise.
(Su Qin.)
(Don't be afraid.)
(Wait for me.)
(Lu Huan.)
(I'm still here.)
(You're home.)
♪Rolling mountains
and vast lake♪
♪Who sees the river of stars♪
♪Time is cruel♪
♪Wander in the rain♪
♪The night ripples♪
♪Who am I waiting for♪
♪No right or wrong♪
♪It's God's prank♪
♪Fall into thousands of stars♪
♪Just to look you in the eyes♪
♪Pause again and again♪
♪Something is on the tip
of the tongue♪
♪I thought
I caught the promise♪
♪You're the one who said♪
♪No worries in life♪
♪No result for love♪
♪Life is but a dream♪
♪Love is a deceiver♪
♪Who made me lost♪
(The right of network communication
of this work)
(is exclusively owned by Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)