=Love in A Dream=
=Episode 16=
- Sir.
- Hi.
- A bowl of wontons.
- Sure.
Sit here, please.
Wait a moment.
OK.
We traveled all the way
from Guazhou.
We deserve a good meal.
No worries.
The prince
wants to capture
the emperor's concubine.
I've got the message
that she just got out
of the palace.
And now
she's in Yun Town.
I've heard
Prince of Ning An is near.
That jerk
fought us all the time.
Humph.
I've prepared
the knock-out drug.
I'll make sure he's killed.
Yeah.
This time,
he's dead for sure.
Yeah, he's
a dead man walking.
Humph.
Catch her.
Uncle.
You're spruced up, Uncle.
You arrive early,
Your Majesty.
As of now,
we are both sticking
to the plan.
It's for the future of Dacheng.
We must be synchronized.
You still
make excellent speeches
like you did
when we were little.
You're better than me
at knowledge and martial arts.
Mother raised me,
so I had no power.
I had to put on a mask.
But you returned,
I have seen that
you do everything
for the good of Dacheng,
so I declared my stance.
Over the years,
you didn't have trust in me,
and I get it.
But as I'm looking at you,
I don't see any difference.
Uncle,
on my way here,
I saw the grim reality.
The enemy's invasion
and the natural disaster
are making
people homeless.
Uncle, we must do something.
Someone is sending
information to the enemy
from inside the palace.
They're likely to have
control of everything.
After all these years,
I've finally known
more of you.
With you at my side,
I feel secure.
Your Majesty, Your Highness.
Lady Su has been taken
by bad people from Guazhou.
Where are we?
Doesn't matter.
I don't think
it's a good place.
Yo, you're awake,
my prince.
Have mercy, my lord!
Have mercy!
- My lord, please!
- So annoying.
Kill her.
Have mercy, my lord!
Please don't!
My prince,
you'll be the emperor
who rules a country.
You need to learn
anger management.
What do you know?
Bah!
De Quan didn't
send money over this month?
Oh.
I'll see to it.
You are
from Dacheng Kingdom.
You, too?
So weak.
Bah!
Remove her blindfold.
Get her over here.
Teach me how to
write your characters.
Quickly.
Kill the man!
- Move.
- My lord!
My lord!
My lord, I can write, too!
I do carving!
I can do carving,
my lord!
Wooden figurines!
I carve wooden figurines!
Wait!
My lord.
Hmm?
Do you like it?
Pretty good.
Who taught you?
I taught myself.
Oh.
You're gifted.
Yeah.
Good.
This is good.
I like it.
I didn't ask you to write.
You teach me to write.
Quickly!
How do I write?
Release me!
Hmm?
Sister?
Lady Su?
♪Rolling mountains
and vast lake♪
♪Who sees the river of stars♪
♪Time is cruel♪
♪Wander in the rain♪
♪The night ripples♪
♪Who am I waiting for♪
♪No right or wrong♪
♪It's God's prank♪
♪Fall into thousands of stars♪
♪Just to look you in the eyes♪
♪Pause again and again♪
♪Something is on the tip
of the tongue♪
♪I thought
I caught the promise♪
♪You're the one who said♪
♪No worries in life♪
♪No result for love♪
♪Life is but a dream♪
♪Love is a deceiver♪
♪Who made me lost♪
(The right of network communication
of this work)
(is exclusively owned by Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)