[Episode 43]
Hey! Let go! What are you doing?
Why?
Why are you doing this?
What?
What did I do?
Getting all cozy with another man.
So what? Why can't I?
What are you to me anyway?
Why would you say that?
Because I'm just a player.
I'm just a promiscuous gay man.
Do you still want to be with me now?
-Are you saying
-You want to date that amateur?
-That guy is just a weakling.
-He can't satisfy you.
-Only I
-Can fulfill your needs.
-Is that all
-You think about?
Don't assume everyone is like you.
Obsessed with sex all day long.
I'm not overthinking. I'm just stating
what happened between us.
You know what?
A relationship between two people
isn't based on sex.
Try to understand that
love should be involved.
Are you saying
what we have is just sex
and what you have with that nobody is love?
Hey, what's wrong? Why aren't you sleeping?
Nothing. It's nothing.
When you're with him
he's only thinking
about other women.
Because you know
Fuzhi isn't attracted to men.
-Are you okay?
-Did that guy do anything to you?
I think you should stop seeing him.
It'll only make things worse for you.
He's just being pointlessly jealous.
It's meaningless.
[To Be Continued]