Wataru?
[tense music playing]
[Yudai] What's going on?
Why are they here together?
Is he a friend of yours?
Yeah.
He's the son of a friend
who was in a club with me in college.
Right?
Uh...
yes.
Oh, this is my wife and my son.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Minori, his wife.
I'm Wataru Miyake.
This is a surprise. It's been a long time.
Yes, it's been a while.
Is your father well?
[Wataru] Yes.
This must mean you came for advice
on something you can't ask your dad.
Yes.
Kind of.
Sorry, I want to have a man-to-man
talk in private. Go on home.
Okay.
Let's go.
[tense music fades]
Yes.
Daddy's friends come over a lot
these days, don't they?
Friends?
Yeah. A lady stopped by
when we were playing in the park.
A lady?
A pretty lady with long hair.
Are you friends with her, too?
[Minori] That woman...
met Tsubasa?
No.
I don't think I do.
She gave me candy.
[ominous music playing]
[cracks]
[gasps]
What did you do with it?
- I ate it.
- [gasps]
Why did you eat candy from a stranger?
I'm sorry.
[gasps]
[Minori] If she harms Tsubasa...
I'll kill her.
What are you doing?
I told you not to come near this house.
I didn't think
I would bump into your wife.
Why didn't you text me?
You know better than to do this.
Your wife...
she's beautiful.
What? What are you saying all of a sudden?
Mom and your wife
are different types, I noticed.
Never mind that.
What's so important for you
to have come all the way here?
Well...
[Yudai] I've got to fake it somehow.
I can never let Minori find out
that I have another family.
[theme music playing]
UNTIL I DESTROYED
MY HUSBAND'S OTHER FAMILY
[Minori and Tsubasa] Squeeze.
[gasps] Finished!
Wow, you drew such a cute cat!
Next one's Daddy's.
You should draw a heart for him, Mommy.
Me?
Daddy drew one for you before, remember?
[Tsubasa] There.
I'm done. Now it's your turn
to draw a heart.
- Hmm?
- A heart.
[chuckles]
Okay.
[somber music playing]
[indistinct whispering]
[indistinct whispering continues]
That's... a lot of ketchup.
Sorry. I squeezed a little too much.
Mommy drew a heart for you, Daddy.
It just didn't work out today.
Uh... oh, okay.
- [Tsubasa] Mm.
- [chuckles]
That's nice of you.
Thank you for the meal.
[Minori] How can he keep smiling?
What did Wataru come here to say?
Did he come
to tell Yudai about me?
That boy who came...
What was his name? Miyake?
What was such an emergency
that he had to come see you?
Well, he...
Um... [clears throat]
...he had questions
about which college to go to.
He has a college he wants to go to
but his parents are against it.
I see.
Which college does he want to go to?
Huh?
What was it... Oh, an art university.
He says he likes art.
Keiho, the Faculty of Education.
[uneasy music playing]
Mommy, I want milk.
Just a second.
[Tsubasa humming]
[sighs]
Sorry, Tsubasa, we're out of milk.
But I want to drink milk.
Okay, then I'll go buy some milk.
- Watch Tsubasa for me.
- Sure.
Wataru.
Ms. Kume.
I...
[breathing heavily]
Why did you come to our house?
Is it because I used you?
Did you come to reveal everything?
That's not it.
I wanted to see you.
I...
I've been thinking
since the last time we met.
That day we went to the sea.
Ms. Kume...
Minori, you said to me that day...
You are plunging
the family of your lover into hell!
You made me think about...
why I was okay with infidelity.
I realized...
I was running away from it
this whole time.
If Mom was happy,
then it was fine for me, too.
So...
I was just looking away
from the reality of their affair.
I was trying not to think about it.
That's why
I wanted to see you in person
and apologize to you.
I know my apology won't solve anything.
It's not for you to apologize.
But...
it was also my fault
it got awkward just now.
Tell me.
What did you talk about
with Yudai just now?
I asked him if he was serious
about getting married to Mom.
And?
Yudai said...
You don't have to worry about it.
But...
didn't you marry your wife
because you loved her?
- Then why--
- The one I love is...
Your mother is the only one I love.
[Minori] I already knew the answer, but...
[Wataru] I'm sorry.
But...
I don't want to lie anymore.
Minori.
[somber music playing]
Hey, Wataru.
Are you on my side?
Huh?
Would you do anything I say?
Anything?
Yes.
Anything.
[somber music continues]
I'm home.
Tsubasa, I got milk.
[Yudai] What is going on?
[uneasy music playing]
[Yudai] Mm-hmm.
Yeah, and?
Uh-huh.
I already know that.
But if we're found out,
everything will be in vain.
How long do we have to wait for the money?
We don't have much time. My marriage
to Minori would become pointless!
[phone buzzes]
KANON MUTO
COME TO THE CRAM SCHOOL RIGHT NOW!
MOM MISSED CALL
[sighs]
[sighs deeply]
[door opens]
- It's hot, isn't it?
- This never happened before, Teacher.
It's fine.
The kids are in their sensitive years.
He's probably letting off steam somewhere.
I'm so sorry.
You don't have to worry, Ms. Miyake.
Wataru is doing very well recently.
- Really?
- Look at this.
It's his study plan sheet.
Mom.
Wataru. Where were you?
I just had to go get something
I left at school.
You know you should have
contacted your teacher.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right. [chuckles]
But don't worry your mother so much.
Sorry.
- Wataru?
- I'll come home after studying.
- You can go home without me.
- Hey, Wataru.
[sighs]
I'm really sorry for all this trouble.
No worries. Please take a look.
Keiho University?
His scores for English
are improving rapidly
so if he keeps it up, it's not impossible
for him to be admitted.
[gasps]
Is that so?
[Riko] I didn't know.
FIRST CHOICE: KEIHO UNIVERSITY
FACULTY OF EDUCATION TUTOR: KUME
Were you okay?
Uh... Yeah.
- Give it to me.
- Huh?
I want that.
Huh? This?
- Why?
- You owe me, don't you?
Here.
[chuckles]
Thank you.
Where were you really?
I bet you went to see Ms. Kume.
- I seriously think you shouldn't.
- It's nothing like that.
What's it to you?
[uneasy music playing]
My marriage to Minori
would become pointless!
[Minori] Why did he say
there wasn't much time?
Wait for what money?
Why would marrying me be pointless?
Hey.
Hmm?
Who were you talking to on the phone?
What?
Um...
You were
raising your voice, so...
Oh.
It was about work.
Kusunoki messed up again.
I see.
It must be hard working late.
[Yudai] It is.
I'm going to take a bath.
[door opens]
[knocking on door]
[Riko] Can I come in for a second?
- What?
- [door opens]
[chuckles softly]
Guess what?
Your teacher said getting into Keiho
is possible if you work hard.
[chuckles]
- I was pleasantly surprised.
- Mom.
Hmm?
Do you...
really believe
you could get married to Yudai?
Why all of a sudden?
You know...
he has his real family over there.
[chuckles]
Why are you bringing
something like that up now?
I believe in Yudai.
I see.
You're acting strange lately. [chuckles]
Did something happen?
Not really.
Are you done?
I have to study.
Oh. Okay.
Try your best.
[Yudai] It's only a matter of time
before Minori finds out.
Wataru?
Who were you talking to on the phone?
I've got to do something.
[door opens]
Hey, are you free on Friday?
- Friday?
- Isn't it our first date anniversary?
I'll take off work,
how about we eat out together?
[Minori] What's gotten into him?
Huh?
Wow. You remembered?
Of course.
[chuckles]
I'm glad you did.
We can let my mother babysit Tsubasa
and spend some time alone together.
Do you have a restaurant in mind?
I'd go anywhere you choose.
Okay, then I'll search for one.
I can't wait.
[pensive music playing]
[Sara] It sure is suspicious.
Right?
Wataru's visit made him nervous.
He's trying to get on my good side.
Yeah.
And that phone call is concerning.
Not having much time
could be about the baby being born.
But marriage to you being pointless?
What is he plotting?
[Ichiro] Fancy!
- A date with your wife?
- You've got to once in a while.
I've never eaten anywhere like this.
You're loaded.
It's just like our chief
to take good care of his wife.
That's why he's married.
That looks like a nice place.
I want to go there with you someday.
What?
I've never been to a restaurant like this.
Right. Someday.
[woman] Really? All right!
[boy] It went that way.
[Hiromi] I'm sorry to make you come by
after work when you're tired.
No, I don't mind. What do you want?
I made a lot of chikuwa salad
that Tsubasa likes, so take some home.
You can still eat it tomorrow
if you store it in the fridge.
You called me for this?
Don't be silly.
Just wait a second.
[children laughing, screaming]
[woman] Sorry.
[indistinct whispering]
[indistinct whispering continues]
Yu-chan!
[Hiromi] Take this.
- This is the main reason I called you.
- Oh.
[Yudai] What is it?
This is what's in it.
[Yudai] Expensive!
- It's an anniversary gift for her.
- Huh?
You have to take special care of Minori.
Only then can we be happy, right?
[indistinct whispering]
I know.
[Minori] Do you remember...
our first first-date anniversary?
Of course I do.
- You wanted to go to Disneyland so badly.
- [chuckles]
My dream was to take a picture with you
wearing Mickey Mouse ears.
I took so many part time jobs
to pay for it.
We ate churros for the first time
that day, remember?
Hmm? What's that?
They're those long,
stick-like things that have ridges--
- Ah, those donuts.
- Yeah. That's it.
[both chuckle]
That was 17 years ago, huh...
Does that feel long ago?
Or does it feel recent?
[sighs]
I don't know.
My marriage to Minori
would become pointless!
This bracelet.
This was what started it all.
Tonight...
let's start by making a toast
to our first encounter.
Yes.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
- [glasses clink]
[tender music playing]
Hey.
I've been wanting to ask you.
How do you feel about me?
Why do you ask?
We've had 17 years together.
During this time...
have you really...
loved me?
[light music playing]
I...
Mm?
[phone buzzing]
- [chuckles]
- [phone buzzing]
Sorry.
Just a minute.
Hello?
Yes.
What?
[gasps] I see. I'll be right there.
- What's the matter?
- Grandpa got taken to the hospital.
- What?
- I have to go.
I'll go too.
I need you to go pick up Tsubasa.
[uneasy music playing]
Hello? It's me.
Grandpa.
[Minori] The cancer is spreading?
[doctor] Unfortunately,
it's advanced further.
With it spreading to this level,
treatment by surgery is difficult.
[Minori] I didn't realize it at all.
I'm sorry.
Grandpa.
Oh.
Minori, it's you.
You must have been surprised.
Sorry.
Have you been suffering for a long time?
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want to worry you.
Were you doing something special today?
Oh? Ah.
It was my anniversary with Yudai.
I see.
I feel bad for ruining it.
It's okay.
I seems I don't have long to live.
Minori.
There's something I want to tell you
before I die.
Stop it.
Don't say something like that.
That bracelet...
- This?
- Yes.
Do you know where it's from?
Where it's from?
Tsukishiro Jewelry, right?
Yes.
That was given...
by Susumu Tsukishiro
to Miyuki.
Tsukishiro...
Susumu...
He's the chairman of Tsukishiro Group.
[Minori] This man?
SUSUMU TSUKISHIRO
Yes.
Why did this prominent man
give this to Mom?
That man...
is your father.
[somber music playing]
Forgive me for not telling you until now.
Really?
Why?
Why didn't you tell me?
Minori.
You probably were aware
of why you didn't have a father.
[woman] Karma got her
for having an affair.
What Miyuki did...
was unacceptable.
But the same can be said
about Susumu Tsukishiro.
In spite of that...
the moment he knew
that Miyuki was pregnant
he abruptly left Miyuki.
But...
after Miyuki died in an accident
he came to see me.
On the day
of the accident
he and Miyuki saw each other.
[young Minori] What happened, Mom?
You look pretty today.
So that's why.
He tried...
to settle everything with money.
I couldn't forgive him.
That kind of man...
wasn't worthy of being called a father.
That's why I never told you
the true identity of your father.
I'm sorry.
Minori.
Can you hand me my bag?
There's a passbook inside.
That passbook
is what he gave me
as child support for you, Minori.
So much...
He also gave me stocks.
I have it arranged
so that when I die,
you will get all of them.
Don't talk about dying.
[sobs] What am I going to do
without you, Grandpa?
You have your beloved family,
don't you, Minori?
You should live happily
with Yudai...
and Tsubasa.
[Minori] I can't let my grandfather
worry about me.
Yes.
I will.
[chuckles]
[Minori sobbing]
[somber music playing]
[Minori] Susumu Tsukishiro left my mother
as soon as he found out
my mother was pregnant.
On the other hand
Yudai said....
He says he can't wait to meet the baby.
Why?
Grandpa...
no matter how much money you give me
my happy home is no more.
How long do we have to wait for the money?
TSUKISHIRO ANNOUNCES
THEIR FIRST EUROPEAN STORE
[indistinct whispering]
[foreboding music playing]
[Minori] Could it be?
But...
how would Yudai know about
a secret that's unknown to me?
[munches, laughs]
[Minori panting]
[Hiromi] Coming!
- [door opens]
- [gasps]
I'm so sorry I'm late.
Haven't you heard from Yudai?
He took Tsubasa home a while ago.
I forgot.
I'm the one who told him to,
but I got confused.
Don't worry, it can't be helped.
So, how is your grandfather doing?
The cancer is spreading?
[Minori] They can only delay
the spread with medication.
Nothing else they can do.
But with the recent advancements
in medicine...
I'm sure he'll be all right.
Minori.
Try to stay strong.
Thank you.
Yudai told me you didn't have time to eat.
Oh. I guess so.
I wish I had some sweets in the house.
I know, I'll go get some
at the convenience store.
- It'll only be a minute.
- Don't worry about it.
Okay. Huh?
- Where did I put my wallet?
- [phone chimes]
I keep putting it somewhere
but I forget where.
YUDAI KISARAGI
YOU MUST HAVE HEARD FROM MINORI.
WHEN I RECEIVE THE MONEY,
WE SHOULD GET MOVING.
[closing theme music playing]
Minori.
Yes.
I'll be right back. [chuckles]
- Be careful.
- [Hiromi] I will.
[door opens, closes]
[chimes]
TALK
[computer voice in English] Talk.
KISARAGI NEW FAMILY (3)
Kisaragi...
New family.
KISARAGI NEW FAMILY (3)
YUDAI KISARAGI
YOU MUST HAVE HEARD FROM MINORI.
WHEN I RECEIVE THE MONEY,
WE SHOULD GET MOVING.
IT SOUNDED BAD.
MAYBE HE ONLY HAS A FEW MONTHS.
[indistinct whispering]
[foreboding music playing]
[indistinct whispering continues]
THANK YOU. I HOPE WE CAN
LIVE TOGETHER AS A NEW FAMILY SOON.
[indistinct whispering continues]
[somber music playing]
RIKO GOOD NIGHT. THANK YOU AS ALWAYS.
I'LL SEND YOU PHOTOS FROM OUR DINNER
TOGETHER THE OTHER DAY.
KISARAGI NEW FAMILY (3)
[gasps]
[closing theme music playing]
[Minori in Japanese] How can even
my mother-in-law betray me?
How can they be hoping
to make a new family?
I won't let them.
I can't let them.
[laughing]
I won't let them.
[Minori] It's our family's big project.
They were all involved in a plot
to steal your assets?
[Minori]
You'll catch a cold like that.
[Wataru]
I'm on your side, Minori.