[Mirror : A Tale of Twin Cities]
[Episode 37]
What do I need to do then?
It's better that you remain here at Quanxian camp.
When we go to the enemy's camp, it is better if fewer people go.
What's more, you also have the power of Heaven with you.
We can't put you at risk for Princess Bai's sake.
Na Sheng, we are going to the camp to rescue Yan Xi.
Someone must remain here to prepare for Yan Xi's arrival.
Okay. Ning Liang, your rescue of Yan Xi must go smoothly.
It will.
Young Master, the pallor of your face...
I'm fine.
Then I'll go contact Xiang about Yan Xi's rescue.
I'll go take care of Older Sister Bai Ying, then.
I'll go find Xi Jing and head towards Taoyuan Province later.
All right.
- Emperor of the Sea.
- Master, I can feel an extremely
powerful force about to give me a backlash.
It's getting serious. You mustn't force it.
Princess Bai's injury isn't that serious. Regaining consciousness is just a matter of time.
You must stay in seclusion to heal your injury
and control the reaction to the backlash. I will help you.
Thank you, Master.
Brother Crown Prince, don't worry.
Leave this to me. I will take good care of Older Sister Bai Ying.
I'm at ease, then.
Then, when you go to Taoyuan Province, you must succeed.
Your Highness.
- You're finally here.
- How's Na Sheng, A'Ying, and the others?
- They're fine. It is just that A'Ying...
- What's wrong with her?
She is staying at Quanxian camp to recover from her injuries. Fortunately, her life is not in danger.
In order to treat her injury, Su Mo lost a lot of his magic.
Right now, he is in seclusion in order to recuperate.
A'Ying is in a coma. Su Mo is in seclusion.
What should we do next, then?
I called you here to tell you about what's next.
This is a good solution. We can try it.
Yes. This is urgent and must not be delayed.
We are going to look for Gao Shunzhao tonight.
All right. I will go make the arrangements.
Your Highness. Zhen Lan. General Xi Jing.
It's been a long time since we met.
After we last said our farewells here, I wondered how everyone was doing.
I'm fine.
You should know our motive for coming here.
In this campaign, Cangliu has been injuring and killing people.
After going through the battle with the Wind Falcons, Taoyuan Province
has been badly damaged.
[Gao Shunzhao - Cangliu - Taoyuan Province Governer]
This is the time that many things are waiting to be done.
Can you show me the way?
I don't dare prescribe a way.
We merely would like to collaborate with you.
Are you saying we should
submit to Kongsang and Quanxian
and become an affiliated province of theirs?
If that's the case,
what's the difference if we do the same thing with Cangliu right now?
This isn't what I meant.
I'm saying...
We should create a new and peaceful Yunhuang together.
Just like how Quanxian and Kongsang formed the Land-Sea Alliance.
It's definitely not to surrender to another to create an alliance.
But it's an alliance for the sake of stabilizing each other's lives.
I know that you are diligent in government affairs and love your people,
and that they're everything to you.
It's the same for us. Kongsang hopes that our 100,000 people can see the sun again.
Quanxian also hopes to be able to return to Bilou Sea.
We are all doing this for our people,
fighting for peace for them.
When we returned to Taoyuan Province, I had wanted to convince you to serve the Young Master as well,
but I know that you have always wanted the people to live in peace.
And not be someone who depends on power.
Based on my understanding of Young Master, he doesn't want more power either.
He only wants us to live a peaceful and happy life.
We all understand each other; this is what people yearn for.
It's generally the same thing that you wish for them as well.
Let Taoyuan Province become a new Taoyuan.
That's right.
All these years, Cangliu has abused its military power in fierce wars
turning Taoyuan Province into ruins.
After experiencing this campaign and suffering heavy and terrible losses,
it's like sitting on pins and needles.
If you can give the people a peaceful life,
I will definitely help you.
I won't give up
on giving the people of Taoyuan Province this opportunity.
Governor Gao, don't worry.
We won't disappoint you.
All right.
Then... how do we arrange this? What do you want to do?
We need you to...
[Command Token]
[Taoyuan Province]
[Taoyuan Province Government Office]
Bad news, the lord was attacked by an assassin!
My Lord, there was an assassination at Governor Gao's council office in Taoyuan Province.
Gao Shunzhao encountered an assassination attempt. It's not clear if he's dead or alive.
I understand.
What do you think of this?
It's very obvious that it was done by the Kongsang.
Their motive is also obvious. It is to take control of Taoyuan Province.
If Gao Shunzhao had an unexpected accident,
they will have taken control of his Gold Two-Headed Green Finch command token.
Then...
Taoyuan Province will belong to the Kongsang.
I request to lead an army to Taoyuan Province to suppress the rebellion.
To suppress the rebellion...
Naturally, I will send someone.
I'm going to hand you an even more important mission.
Young Master is in seclusion. Keep a tight watch.
Don't let anyone go near him. Understand?
- Yes.
Ning Liang, I guessed you would be here.
Of course, I would be here. Young Master is in seclusion. I'm worried.
What are you worried about?
You wouldn't understand.
Right Commissioner, there's news from Taoyuan Province.
His Highness and General Xi Jing have already taken control of Gao Shunzhao
and have succeeded in attracting the attention of Cangliu.
- You can leave.
- Yes.
Crown Prince Zhen Lan and the others have succeeded.
Xiang should be starting to make her move as well.
What about Yan Xi?
Young Master and the rest have already developed a plan. I'm going to meet up with Xiang.
Nothing dangerous will happen.
Then... Then you must take care of your safety.
- Set out on an expedition to Taoyuan Province!
- Yes, Sir!
Bai Ying, are you awake?
You've slept for such a long time.
Have you dreamed a lot?
I wonder...
if I'm in your dreams.
Bai Ying.
Who are you?
I'm here to bring you out of here.
Who are you? Where are you?
What is this?
- Tears.
- Tears?
- Whose tears?
- They're mine.
Why is this with me?
Because my beloved one refuses to wake up.
I'm afraid to lose her.
Who's your beloved one? Where are you?
Follow me.
Bai Ying... come with me.
You're awake.
Emperor of the Sea, you've crossed the line.
What is this place?
This is Quanxian's main camp.
You've forgotten. After you were injured, I brought you here to heal.
Don't you remember?
I am Su Mo.
I know that you are Su Mo.
Unless you forcefully open her five rhythms and six senses and then infuse magic power.
But if you do this forcefully,
it'll cause damage to Princess Bai.
Is it because of this that Bai Ying is keeping her distance from me?
Other than remembering that I'm the Emperor of the Sea, what else do you remember?
I remember... the Land-Sea Alliance.
We went to undo the seal together.
Undo the seal...
Where is His Highness?
He isn't here.
Where did he go?
He went to Taoyuan Province. He'll return soon.
Don't worry just yet.
It's probably because you just woke up,
so you're feeling a little confused.
Rest for a while first. I'll go prepare medicine for you.
What is this?
A tear.
Young Master.
Prepare medicine for Bai Ying.
Princess Bai is awake?
Now that she's awake, is Princess Bai all right?
Her body still needs to recover. Also...
Also what?
She doesn't seem to totally recognize me.
"Doesn't totally recognize you." What does that mean?
She knows that I'm Emperor of the Sea.
But she... doesn't know Su Mo.
Maybe her body is weak after
recovering from a severe injury?
Yes. Let's wait until she recovers.
Young Master, you don't need to worry too much.
At least Princess Bai has awakened. Everything will be fine.
Yes, at least she has awakened.
- Young Master.
- Emperor of the Sea, His Highness the Crown Prince asked me to come to take care of A'Ying.
You'll still be free in the future. You can go wherever you want.
Choose someone you love and stay together for a lifetime.
A merperson...
can only love one person in their whole lifetime.
A'Yuan,
it's been a long time.
It's been a long time, Zhi Xiu.
How is A'Ying right now?
She just woke up.
That's great. Then, I'll go see her right away
Follow me.
Sister Hong Yuan, you've come.
Thankfully, Su Mo saved you again.
What happened to you when you were in the Stranded Dragon Abyss?
Saved me again? Did he save me before?
Don't you remember?
I remember going to the Ruyi Gambling House.
I was looking for Na Sheng.
Do you remember someone named Su Mo?
Why are you asking this, too?
Has something happened?
Nothing. You just woke up and need to recuperate.
You should take it slow until you've completely recovered.
I'll go pour a cup of water for you. First, get some rest.
Young Master.
Deliver it later.
Yes.
You two... haven't seen each other for a hundred years.
After we bid farewell a hundred years ago, we never saw each other again.
To be able to meet again after a hundred years, it's truly fated.
Brother Ice Cube! Brother Ice Cube, you're out of seclusion?
How are you? Are you better now?
- How about Sister Bai Ying?
- She's awake.
This is wonderful. Wonderful.
Oh right, Brother Ice Cube.
What's the matter?
News just came from Taoyuan Province. We can go rescue Yan Xi.
The news was sent to you?
Ning Liang received the news.
- Why didn't she tell me?
- You were still in seclusion.
Ning Liang went ahead and left to rescue Yan Xi.
- How could she go by herself?
- Ning Liang is so strong,
Xiang is also helping. They should be able to bring back Yan Xi successfully, right?
Young Master, we just got news from Xiang asking for help.
Xiang? Could Yan Xi and Ning Liang be in trouble?
Thank you for the medicine you gave.
I didn't expect... to see you again here.
It's been 100 years since we parted.
I thought we wouldn't see each other ever again.
That's right.
Things are unpredictable in the world.
A'Yuan.
Have you endured hardship over the past 100 years?
- Master!
- Master! We've finished our homework.
Master, this is...
This is Kongsang's Princess Chi, Hong Yuan.
She came specifically to take care of Princess Bai.
Hong Yuan? This name sounds a bit familiar.
- Do you know me?
- We've only heard about it once before. Master...
Che, the wounded Quanxian soldiers are gradually returning and need medicine.
You and Han should go to the pharmacy to prepare the medicinal ingredients.
- Yes.
Once Master was calling out from his dream. It sounded like A'Yuan.
Hurry.
- What's going on?
- Ning Liang, take Yan Xi away first.
We've already sent a sound pearl back to the camp for help.
Someone should be coming to meet you on your way back. I'll head back first.
All right.
- Can you get away?
- Nan Zhao!
- Capture these people!
- You go first. I'll cover the rear.
It's not my style to abandon comrades. We go together!
Hurry!
Ning Liang.
- Ning Liang?
- How are you?
I didn't do well. Please punish me, Young Master.
You fought by yourself. It's not easy to have endured for this long.
Don't waste anymore effort on me.
I know it's useless.
Young Master, can you agree to do me a favor?
Tell me.
After I die, bury me in the sea.
I want to forever stay where I started.
You are warriors in the Quanxian Army.
If you die, your names will be written with your blood
and forever remembered by the dragon deity and Quanxian's people.
From Heaven, you will see the Quanxian return to Biluo Sea.
Ning Liang!
Ning Liang, rest assured.
All of this will be over very soon.
Please... watch us from Heaven.
That's the place where the Emperor of the Sea cultivates and recuperates. It's at the end of the corridor.
Intruders will be punished by the elders.
This will belong to me someday.
A'Ying.
What are you doing here?
What's this place?
I don't know, either. But it's best that we don't linger here.
But I just saw someone who resembles Su Mo go inside.
That can't be. Zhi Xiu just told me that he went to rescue Yan Xi and the others.
He isn't in the main camp.
Was I mistaken?
You've only just recovered. It's likely that you were mistaken.
A'Ying, what's the matter?
It's nothing. You were saying... they went to find Yan Xi?
Yan Xi was captured at the Stranded Dragon Abyss. Su Mo went to rescue him.
Let's go then.
Princess Bai. Princess Chi. This is Emperor of the Sea's ice chamber.
Please don't enter without permission.
Sorry, we came the wrong way.
Let's go.
You actually survived that sword strike at the Stranded Dragon Abyss.
In order to save you, Su Mo was willing to suffer from the backlash.
Even I had to suffer as well.
By then, you can just die with Su Mo.
Why hasn't Brother Ice Cube returned after such a long time?
It's my fault. I shouldn't have let Yu Huan take Yan Xi away.
Where was Yan Xi taken by Yu Huan?
At the Stranded Dragon Abyss.
You and Brother Ice Cube were going to the Stranded Dragon Abyss to undo the seal on the dragon deity.
Sister Bai Ying, you don't remember anymore?
I remember going to the Stranded Dragon Abyss.
But everything else... I can't seem to remember clearly.
It's fine. You suffered such a severe injury this time
and have only just recovered, it's normal not to remember.
But I definitely won't forget Yan Xi.
I remember everything about Yan Xi very clearly. He has to come back safely.
They're back! They're back!
- Hurry!
- Where?
Are they back?
Sister Bai Ying, let's go. Let's go take a look!
Hurry! Let's go!
Hang on.
- Hang on.
- Yan Xi? Where is Yan Xi?
Yan Xi?
Yan Xi! How is Yan Xi?
He should be all right.
Take Ning Liang back to her room.
Let Zhi Xiu inspect Yan Xi's injury.
Yes.
Ning Liang, she...
I didn't protect everyone well.
Why did you come out here?
Na Sheng was worried about Yan Xi. I was keeping her company, waiting for your return.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
But... Han Zhou,
Ning Liang, Ting, and the others,
all fell one by one on the way back.
I've been thinking sometimes.
If only I was a little stronger, could they have survived?
Could I have taken them home? Home to Biluo Sea?
Don't blame yourself too much.
No one can save everyone.
Don't bear all the responsibilities on your own shoulders.
It's fine now.
Go back and rest.
Oh, right! I saw someone enter the ice chamber today. I thought it was you.
But once I entered, I didn't see anyone inside.
Could outsiders have intruded into Quanxian's main camp?
Are you sure? Were you perhaps mistaken?
No, I wouldn't be mistaken.
They say no one would dare to intrude into Quanxian's ice chamber, but I'm still worried.
Don't worry. I'll have someone look into it.
Perhaps you really were mistaken.
Is anything else the matter?
Have I been to the ice chamber before?
Do you remember something?
I just feel...
that it seems a little familiar.
No matter what happens in the future, I won't let you disappear again.
I will always stay by your side.
Are you willing to believe me?
Don't think about it anymore.
Maybe after you are fully recovered, you'll naturally remember.
Go back and rest early.
Yan Xi.
Zhi Xiu said that you're all right.
But why aren't you awake yet?
You... Whenever you leave, you always return full of wounds.
In the future, I'll always stay with you no matter what. You won't be able to get rid of me.
I don't want a next time. I'm so afraid.
Those Cangliu people are so vicious.
How many more of our people will they kill?
I've completed what you assigned me to do. Master Peng, please don't worry.
I deliberately dragged out the time
and kept waiting until Su Mo appeared.
- He rescued the person from you?
- Yes.
In the battle at the Stranded Dragon Abyss, Yu Huan suffered heavy casualties.
But Su Mo wasn't harmed at all.
It would appear that abandoning that child, Yu Huan,
wasn't wrong at all.
A'Huan, you're awake?
Sister.
A'Huan, does it hurt anywhere?
Sister,
how are things outside?
Why am I here?
Who saved me?
It was Fei Lian.
He not only brought you back,
we also schemed together to force Master Lang to send a physician to treat you.
- Where is he now?
- Ever since Master Lang took him back,
we haven't had any contact.
Where is the prisoner Yan Xi that I caught?
Yan Xi was taken back to Jing City and was guarded under Master Peng.
Quanxian had help from the inside,
and the Emperor of the Sea personally came to rescue Yan Xi.
Cangliu's troops suffered heavy casualties at the Stranded Dragon Abyss this time.
Yan Xi was also rescued.
The Five Masters won't have any reason to let me go this time.
Master Peng, what are you doing?
Yu Huan, as the commander in the battle at the Stranded Dragon Abyss,
you caused great losses for Cangliu's troops.
By military rule, you should be executed right away.
However, I've pleaded mercy for you in front of the other four masters.
As long as you provide a full explanation of the loss,
I'm sure we'll give you a fair punishment.
Take him!
- What are you doing?
- Sister. It's fine.
You... You... Let go of him!
A'Huan!
How is it? Are you all right now?
Yan Xi has returned.
But... Ning Liang has died.
How did it turn out like this?
How are things over at Taoyuan Province?
Just as you expected, with Gao Shunzhao's cooperation,
we easily took Taoyuan Province.
Taoyuan Province's Commander Guo Yanyun has received the governor's secret order.
[Taoyuan Province]
All of the troops in Taoyuan Province will follow General Xi Jing's command.
Where did these two people come from?
Who are they? Why do the generals have to listen to them?
I heard that Governor Gao was assassinated. Are they here to take the opportunity to take over Taoyuan Province?
The Cangliu people won't let this go that easily.
When that time comes, we will be the ones to get injured and die.
Taoyuan Province's soldiers swear to defend Taoyuan County.
We won't so easily surrender!
[Command Token]
[Taoyuan Province]
The Gold Two-Headed Green Finch command token!
The holder shall command Taoyuan Province.
[Command token]
A hundred years ago,
the Cangliu made it difficult for the people in Taoyuan Province.
A few months ago, they even dispatched the Wind Falcons
to burn Taoyuan Province to the ground.
If you are willing to follow the Kongsang,
we will bring peace back to Taoyuan Province
and let the people live in comfort again!
It's time to safeguard Taoyuan Province for your own sake!
I, Gu Yanyun, will follow Crown Prince Zhen Lan and General Xi Jing.
I hope everyone
will be united and fight against our common enemy!
Our Kongsang's several thousand troops are waiting right outside the city gates.
They are waiting to safeguard your homeland with you!
To bring peace back to Taoyuan Province!
I had Xi Jing stay in Taoyuan Province to plan and organize our next steps. Don't worry.
By the way, how is A'Ying? Has she woken up yet?
- She's already awake.
- She's awake?
Then... Then can I go see her?
Of course, you can.
Her injuries have been completely healed.
It's just that...
"It's just" what?
Her memory is a bit messy.
She only remembers that I'm the Emperor of the Sea.
But as for everything else... she doesn't remember anymore.
What about other people?
Just go and see her for yourself.
- A'Ying.
- Your Highness.
How are you doing? Are you well?
- I'm all right now.
- That's good.
Did you just come back from Taoyuan Province?
Yes. Xi Jing and I took over Taoyuan Province together.
He's staying there and will return after a few days.
Your Highness, do you know what this is?
This doesn't look like anything from Kongsang.
Why do I have this?
This is...
Bai Ying will suffer a terrible headache if she tries to recall the past.
Perhaps, by forgetting the feelings between us,
she might live more at ease.
Your Highness?
A'Ying, you've just recovered.
Just pay attention to your health, don't think about anything else.
Your Highness, I seem to have...
forgotten a lot of important things.
What things?
I don't know either.
But in my mind, all the memories about the Emperor of the Sea are fuzzy.
What exactly happened between him and me?
A'Ying, whatever happened between you and the Emperor of the Sea,
I think it's best that you ask him yourself.
A'Ying, is there anything you want me to do?
I'll do it for you.
A'Ying, I've wished for many things.
But not everything can be perfect.
I like you,
but I won't take advantage of someone's trouble.
However, if you were to make a different choice,
I don't want to let go so easily either.
You're awake. You're really awake.
What exactly happened between us?
Emperor of the Sea.
It's late. Why aren't you asleep yet?
I've bothered the Quanxian during this time.
It's all thanks to you that my body is able to recover.
I'd like to ask you about something.
Go ahead.
I know I've forgotten some things.
But these things seem to be related to you.
Sister Hong Yuan and His Highness the Crown Prince both hesitate in telling me.
So I can only come and ask you.
Did something happen to me?
Also, does this pearl have something to do with you?
Those things that you can't remember,
do they bother you?
I've been trying hard to reassemble those scattered memories in my head.
But no matter what, I really can't remember.
Even if I were to tell you,
it would only be just a story.
Why obsess over it?
Perhaps... these memories are very important to me.
Are they not important?
As long as you are alive, that's more important than anything else.
I plan on leaving Quanxian camp tomorrow.
Wanting to Return by Zhou Shen
♫ Among the frosty clouds is the cold moon ♫
♫ A strange light in the night ♫
♫ In the dream, there is longing and fear ♫
♫ The layers of waves build up ♫
♫ Repeating the promise ♫
♫ Yet they disappear in the end ♫
♫ We've met several times ♫
♫ Yet it is hard to mention our fated relationship from the past ♫
♫ Sighing over the past is as frivolous as smoke ♫
♫ Split open the cocoon in my heart ♫
♫ You live in there ♫
♫ and have never been discovered by anyone ♫
♫ Ask time to borrow a chapter ♫
♫ The unforgettable memories ♫
♫ have disappeared, disappeared ♫
♫ I once thought there was a deep bond ♫
♫ Using ten fingers to painstakingly ♫
♫ play the ancient chords ♫
♫ In exchange for only a moment of your smile ♫
♫ Use a lifetime to love only one person ♫
♫ How do you calculate the debt between each other? ♫
♫ Yet unwilling, unwilling ♫
♫ to make an exchange for a promise and apology ♫
♫ Our next lives are too far away ♫
♫ I would rather turn into ash and be lost in a reverie ♫
♫ When I want to return,
it will be time for my dream to come true ♫