[Mirror: A Tale of Twin Cities]
[Episode 7]
Can you now tell me, why is the Heavenly Ring on your finger?
I didn't expect to see a Heavenly Temple in this wilderness.
Let's go in and take a break.
Trying to escape?
You just mentioned Heavenly Ring. What Heavenly Ring?
I found this thing on Snow Mountain.
Also, I don't know what happened. It just ended up on my finger.
Also, no matter what I do, I can't take it off. How would I know what it was.
Since you don't know, why did you use it to make me help you?
Su Mo?
Who's there?
General!
General, news came that two people crossed over into Tianque.
They've escaped.
One was a merperson dressed in blue clothes. The other was a girl who seemed to be from the Central Plains.
Bai Ying?
Bai Ying? You're Bai Ying?
- One night, when Brother Ice Cube was dreaming, he—
- Na Sheng.
Quickly tell me why the Heavenly Ring is on your finger.
Why is the Heavenly Ring on your finger?
Has the seal been broken?
I have no idea. I picked this up in a cave on Tianque Snow Mountain.
Why was the ring on Snow Mountain?
A hundred years ago, Kongsang fell to the enemy.
Zhen Lan's spiritual consciousness was sealed.
He's been in a deep sleep for a hundred years already.
General, they should be inside there.
I'm General Yu Huan from Cangliu,
with orders to arrest the suspects.
Those in the temple, open the door immediately.
Otherwise, I'll burn this temple down!
What's going on? Are they looking for you?
Is this related to the ring?
It's a long story.
I didn't want to wear this ring either.
Anyway, after I crossed into Tianque,
there have been so many people after me, trying to kill me.
I'm innocent.
You crossed into Tianque with this ring on your finger?
You're the one I'm looking for!
Take her and leave first.
I can go against them.
You must listen to her.
If you cause her harm, I'll take your life.
You crossed into Tianque.
Are there others in there?
Immortal Brother, quickly come out.
Hurry and help me.
A'Ying.
Immortal Brother, you're finally here.
You know her, too?
What's your relationship with her?
Her Earth Ring and my Heavenly Ring are a pair.
You two are together?
I...
Na Sheng.
How is it out there?
Kill him.
Yes!
He's using the techniques of the Holy Sword Sect.
This man is quite formidable.
Let me get you somewhere safe first. Hide the ring.
No. She can't see the daylight.
Follow me.
Older Sister Bai Ying.
Hurry, go!
Na Sheng, take A'Ying into the forest!
Quickly.
- I can't, I can't.
- Hang in there.
Older sister, let's take a break. Take a break.
My goodness, I'm so tired.
Immortal Brother.
The power in the ring is depleting. I'm going to disappear.
- Hurry, tell...
- Who are you talking to?
A'Ying that I...
Hurry up! Hurry up!
There's an Immortal Brother in this ring.
He's been with me for the past two days.
He taught me how to take the hidden paths and dodge those who were pursuing me.
But he's just a shadow. No one can see or hear him.
I'm the only one who can see him.
It's His Highness, right? Where is he?
Over there.
Na Sheng, give me your hand.
What are you going to do?
Don't be afraid.
Do it with me.
Keep going.
Ancestors of Kongsang, please use the power of Heaven and Earth
to awaken His Highness who's been in a deep sleep for a hundred years. May heaven bless Kongsang.
What... What is this radiant light?
Could it be the Heavenly and Earth Rings?
Did Princess Bai find the Heavenly Ring?
The Heavenly Ring has reappeared.
The brightest star has manifested itself.
The Heavenly Ring which has been missing for a hundred years has reappeared.
The brightest star which had been dimmed for a hundred years has started to shine again.
Relay this order.
We must get the Heavenly Ring back no matter what.
Yes.
I've finally awakened.
Are you really Immortal Brother?
You look exactly like your shadow!
Of course, it's the same!
Your Highness the Crown Prince.
Your Highness, you've finally awakened.
We didn't wait in vain these one hundred years.
A'Ying, it's been tough on you these hundred years.
Rest here with Na Sheng.
The five princes should soon be on their way here.
I'm going to check on Su Mo.
He has saved me many times before.
All right. Go on.
A'Ying,
be... careful of the sunlight.
It's okay. It's getting dark soon.
No. W-What I meant is that, you should resolve it as quickly as possible.
After all, this Crown Prince who has just awakened is waiting for you.
You're a crown prince?
Yes.
I didn't expect him to have become so powerful.
Is this really the Holy Sword Sect's Sword of Light?
Is she senior sister?
Retreat.
Crown Prince Brother, did you really sleep for a hundred years?
Just about.
The Sister Bai Ying that we just saw, is she the one
who traveled all over Yunhuang and told you all sorts of stories?
Yes. That's her.
What relationship do you two have exactly?
We...
A hundred years ago,
I was the crown prince and she was the crown princess.
However, we didn't get married, so...
Oh, so she isn't your wife yet.
No, wait! I remember Su Mo and Sister Bai Ying also seemed to know each other.
Are they a couple?
Are they?
I won't ask anymore. Won't ask anymore.
Brother Crown Prince, where have you been sleeping for these past hundred years?
Wuse City.
Where's Wuse City?
Wuse City is an underwater city.
It's a mystical place.
Inside, sleeps a hundred thousand people.
A hundred thousand people?
A hundred years ago, Cangliu invaded Kongsang.
In order to avoid the massacre,
the six princes opened Wuse City.
Attack!
Cangliu has smashed into our city. We have no power to resist them.
Our people are being massacred.
Crown Prince hasn't regained the power of the emperor.
What should we do?
Open Wuse City.
This is the only way to preserve the lives of the Kongsang people in Jing City.
Wuse City, open!
When Wuse City was opened,
the Kongsang people being massacred in Jing City vanished instantly.
All of Yunhuang shook.
Countless ice spheres protecting the people fell into Jing Lake.
Since then, 100,000 Kongsang people fell into a deep sleep
and became the residents of Wuse City.
That's why the six princes can never see the sun again.
So that's why Sister Bai Ying's skin will smoke when she's in the sunlight.
Cangliu people are too horrible!
That's right. In order for the Kongsang people to see the sun again,
we can only rely on the powers of Heaven and Earth now.
Now we've already found the Heavenly Ring.
That's right.
All thanks to you.
However,
in the battle a hundred years ago,
my powers have been sealed throughout Yunhuang.
I may have been awakened,
but only this right hand's gained some power back.
I have very little ability to do anything right now.
So, we still need you
to rely on the Heavenly Ring to guide us to find the other seals.
Are you willing to help us?
Brother Crown Prince, I'm sorry.
Although the old grandpa in the village told me I must repay kindness
and you did save me on Snow Mountain,
you also led the way for me.
I should repay the favor.
However, breaking seals is too heavy of a burden for me.
I don't know if I have the ability to do it...
Na Sheng,
I know that this matter really is difficult for you.
Actually...
my greatest wish was to come to Yunhuang to find the legendary peaceful home.
When I was in the Central Plains, I had no family.
I didn't want to lead a life of hiding and wandering,
one of homelessness and being miserable.
H-However, once I go with you to break seals,
a-after all, I'm just a normal person who doesn't understand anything at all...
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- There's no need to apologize.
How about this? Think about it some more.
During this time,
let's maintain contact so that we can at least protect you
and take you to the place you want to go.
Let's see if it's over there.
Be careful.
There!
Greetings, Your Highness.
Hurry. Hurry and get up.
Your Highness, I've waited for a hundred years
[Xuan Yu - Prince Xuan of Kongsang ]
and finally you're awake.
That's right. Also, our search for the Heavenly Ring hasn't been in vain.
[Zi Mang - Kongsang Prince Zi]
Prince Zi and Prince Xuan, I've made you worry.
- Your Highness the Crown Prince.
Qing Yuan, you've matured a lot.
Lan Xia, you've grown taller, too.
Your Highness,
you must be joking. How have they changed that much?
Princess Chi, you're still the same. You always tell the truth to expose me.
By the way,
where's A'Ying, Your Highness?
Everyone, let me introduce a young lady to you all.
This young lady is from the Central Plains and is named Na Sheng.
The Heavenly Ring is with her now so everyone needs to protect her.
I'm going to go look for A'Ying, okay?
Why did His Highness leave?
Since you've decided to come back,
why would you leave again?
If it was anyone else, I would've still come back.
Am I just anybody to you?
Yes.
I know you're concerned about me.
The Heavenly Ring has been on Tianque Snow Mountain this whole time.
Zhen Lan has been asleep for a hundred years.
You can't possibly be Kongsang's crown princess.
If you were the crown princess,
you wouldn't have dared answered yes.
A hundred years' time has changed too many things.
Whether it is or not, is no longer important.
That's right.
A hundred years ago, that moment you jumped off Jing Pagoda,
many things changed.
However, on this day on Tianque Snow Mountain, we've gone around and run into each other several times.
Isn't that important when it comes to us?
Just forget all of that.
Everything that happened a hundred years ago, to me, was only a mistake.
The current me just wants to make up for that mistake.
Make up?
How are you going to make it up?
Make it up by forgetting me?
What I've been waiting for a hundred years,
is to be able to awaken the 100,000 Kongsang people in Wuse City.
Have you thought about me during these past hundred years?
I thought that if I had never met you,
this entire tragedy wouldn't have happened.
For these hundred years, I've never missed you.
I've never hoped you'd appear before me.
I've never thought...
that I would see you again.
I don't believe you.
You're lying.
♫ Cool my cheeks ♫
♫ Yet I cannot bear to wipe them away ♫
♫ Somehow, this intoxicated me is silently worried ♫
♫ I once walked over waves to borrow a bit of starlight ♫
♫ Yet, no matter what I do, I cannot see you clearly ♫
♫ I thought that closing my eyes would make my heart clear ♫
♫ Yet I'm just lost in a reverie ♫
♫ All beginnings comes at the expense of having endings ♫
♫ However, love makes even breathing so difficult to do ♫
♫ So let love be silent ♫
♫ Help each other expand our horizons ♫
A'Ying.
Let's go.
Aren't you tired?
We always do things at night.
Why aren't they back yet?
They should be fine, right?
They're here. They're here.
Older Sister Bai Ying!
A'Ying, since you're back,
let's return to Wuse City together.
Do I need to go to Wuse City, too?
Let's see if I can remove this ring.
W-Why can't I remove it?
Isn't this ring yours?
You're awake. Why doesn't it come off?
Na Sheng, I can't do anything either.
This Heavenly Ring has its own will.
Crown Prince Brother, you must be joking. Right?
Ever since I came to Yunhuang, I've been so unlucky.
I even almost lost my life!
Hurry and take the ring back.
Lord Ring, I-I, Na Sheng,
I-I can't carry things in my hands, nor on my shoulders.
I-I even covet money and sensual desires.
I beg you, please hurry and leave.
Let me tell you! You're really mistaken about me.
Your owner is over there. Hurry and go back. Hurry and go back.
Na Sheng.
It's useless.
Then... what will work then?
In your Wuse City, is there anyone stronger than he is?
I can go back to Wuse City with you and take off the ring.
You can't go to Wuse City. You're not a person of Kongsang.
No, wait! This won't work and that won't work?
Na Sheng.
Don't panic. We will definitely keep you completely safe.
It's fine. It's fine. Forget about it.
Every time you say you'll protect me,
in the end, Su Mo is the one that fights them off.
Su Mo? Which Su Mo?
Can there be another Su Mo?
Isn't he the one who doesn't ever say anything
and exudes an aura from his whole body that causes people chills? That Su Mo.
But he really seems to have magical powers!
If he weren't at the Heavenly Temple just now,
Sister Bai Ying and I might not have been able to escape.
A'Ying, you've seen Su Mo?
A'Ying, did you go to see Su Mo just now?
Ridiculous!
- Prince Xuan, what are you doing?
- I'll kill him!
It's been a hundred years; he's actually not dead and continues to bother A'Ying!
That's right. We should've killed him a long time ago.
You all don't seem to be strong enough to beat him.
Prince Xuan. Prince Zi.
I've already seen Su Mo.
At the Tianque Heavenly Temple, he was the one who saved A'Ying and Na Sheng.
Your Highness, you're actually speaking up for Su Mo?
Prince Xuan, since His Highness already knows about this matter,
he must have thought about it already.
Let's follow His Highness's plan.
Your Highness, this old subject was impulsive.
A'Ying, don't get confused again.
Sister Bai Ying, they don't seem to like Su Mo.
Can you ask Su Mo to protect me?
It's useless if I ask him. He'll do it if you ask him though.
He's already left.
Then... what about me then?
I... Will I die here?
Na Sheng, come. Come here.
What do I do? Will people be chasing and trying to kill me the whole way?
Na Sheng, listen to me.
Follow this road and keep going straight ahead. That place is called Taoyuan Province.
It's a rich and prosperous place where visitors and merchants frequently come to do business.
See? The sun is about to rise.
Why don't you go there today and find a safe place to hide first?
I promise that I'll come and pick you up as soon as the sun sets.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
What are you scared about?
The Heavenly Ring has already acknowledged its master. It'll protect you.
Have you forgotten? When you were in danger on Tianque Snow Mountain,
it protected you. Right?
Will it still listen to me?
Will it listen to you?
Let me tell you a mantra to say when you need to use the ring.
Want to hear it?
This mantra is,
"Zhen Lan is the most, very most, handsome person in the world."
You-You-You're lying to me!
Enough then. I was kidding you.
I was teasing you to make you happy.
Either way, this ring is a divine object.
As long as you're careful, it'll be your protection charm.
All right then.
I'll be leaving then. You must remember to come and find me. I'm going. I'm going.
- Hurry and go then.
- I'm leaving now.
Has the Heavenly Ring really acknowledged a master?
But she's not from Kongsang.
The Heavenly Ring allowed her to put it on.
It will definitely protect her. All right, we should go too.
Let's hurry back and get some rest.
Then come back quickly to pick her up.
Yes.
A'Ying.
Let's go.
A hundred years ago, the moment I jumped from Jing Pagoda,
my heart already died and I never hoped that you'd reappear.
Whether it is or not, is no longer important.
Everything that happened a hundred years ago, to me, was only a mistake.
Just treat it as if you've never met me before.
Forget everything.
You're alive. That's already the best blessing from Heaven.
What more can I ask for?
Aunt Ru, I'm back.
I'll come meet up with everyone.
It's time for the Quanxian Tribe's suffering to end.
A'Ying, something seems wrong with you.
It's probably because my body is a bit weak from the sunburn.
Sit.
You ran into Su Mo? Did he save you and Na Sheng?
Yes.
But, Sister Hong Yuan, don't worry.
He and I... won't see each other again.
Since he saved you, why wouldn't he want to see you again?
I'm the one who doesn't want to see him.
I told him,
I've forgotten everything from 100 years ago.
That I never thought about him.
That I never missed him.
That I never... longed for him to reappear.
This old minister respectfully welcomes Your Highness the Crown Prince.
Your Highness.
High Priest, we haven't seen each other in a hundred years. Are you well?
I'm well. I'm well, Your Highness.
I prayed day and night, hoping you would return to us soon.
Today, it's really become a reality.
Your Highness, allow me to introduce the changes that have occurred in the last 100 years.
No need.
I know about everything here in Wuse City already.
Although I've been asleep this whole time,
but this ear of mine never took any time off.
Your Highness, w-where's your Heavenly Ring?
I gifted it to someone.
Gifted it to someone?
I'm the crown prince. When someone took the effort to bring me back, I should show some appreciation. Right?
Your Highness, how could you gift such an important item to someone?
High Priest.
A hundred years have passed.
You're still so easily tricked!
The Heavenly Ring is in the hands of a Central Plains girl named Na Sheng.
She's not a Kongsang person so she can't enter Wuse City.
I've arranged to have her stay in Taoyuan Province.
Once we've rested and organized, we'll bring her back.
Then... why is the ring in her hands?
The Heavenly Ring recognized her as its master.
This Heavenly Ring is connected with my imperial energy and strength.
Since she can wear the Heavenly Ring,
it means, through the Heavenly Ring,
she can sense the power of the other seals.
Does that girl have the power to break the seals for us?
She's very weak and has no strength at all.
Therefore, we have to clear the path for her.
By the way, I saw Su Mo on Tianque.
That Su Mo?
Yes.
He seems different from who he was a hundred years ago.
I have a feeling we'll meet again in the future.
I've awakened!
It'll take time to figure out how to break the seals.
I also want to regain all that
was lost from 100 years ago.
[Nan Zhao - Cangliu Vice General]
I respectfully greet General Fei Lian.
You're Yu Huan's Vice General, Nan Zhao?
Exactly.
By the order of Master Peng, I'm transferring this prisoner to Jing City's prison.
How did Master Peng know about this prisoner?
Whatever Master Peng wants to know about, he'll know.
Thank you, General, for escorting the prisoner from Banbu City. Goodbye.
Wait!
It's best to wait for General Yu Huan to come and personally do the interrogation.
I've promised him that.
What happens later on, Master Peng has already made arrangements for.
I won't bother the General with them.
Take her away!
Were those who passed through Tianque killed?
It was my incompetence.
Go ahead and rise.
It wasted my efforts to find a special opportunity for you to return with military honors.
Who would have known that you would return having failed?
When we searched the mountain today, we ran into two highly skilled fighters.
There are people that you can't defeat?
One is a male merperson who was manipulating silk threads with his hands.
That thread was weird like a spirit snake.
My entire Cangliu small squadron wasn't a match for him.
There was also a woman.
It was my martial arts skills that were lacking.
It's a great mistake to miss anyone trying to enter over Tianque.
You must hurry and amend the mistake quickly.
The prisoner you caught in Banbu City is of high status.
Yes.
That person was ordered to assassinate me, highly skilled in martial arts.
She must have had some power in the Quanxian army.
I have a plan.
I'll certainly do my best and not disappoint you, My Lord.
You don't need to go on this mission.
Quickly tell me. Who's your accomplice?
I don't have any accomplices.
Still won't admit it?
Even if you don't admit it, it's useless.
Come in.
What are you doing?
Since you won't confess honestly,
we can only use the mind control technique then.
Right now, she's resisting really hard.
If we force the mind control technique, she'll lose her memory.
At worst, she'll lose her senses and go mad.
She's just a captured prisoner. So what?
Continue.
Lord Nan Zhao, here's an order from Master Peng.
Go back and report to Master Peng, I'll definitely carry it out.
Yes.
You can stop.
She keeps resisting. The mind-control technique didn't work.
It's not important anymore.
We can put her to good use in another way now.
Why does Xiao want to meet me in Jing City?
Xiao!
Wanting to Return by Zhou Shen
♫ Among the frosty clouds is the cold moon ♫
♫ A strange light in the night ♫
♫ In the dream, there is longing and fear ♫
♫ The layers of waves build up ♫
♫ Repeating the promise ♫
♫ Yet they disappear in the end ♫
♫ We've met several times ♫
♫ Yet it is hard to mention our fated relationship from the past ♫
♫ Sighing over the past is as frivolous as smoke ♫
♫ Split open the cocoon in my heart ♫
♫ You live in there ♫
♫ and have never been discovered by anyone ♫
♫ Ask time to borrow a chapter ♫
♫ The unforgettable memories ♫
♫ have disappeared, disappeared ♫
♫ I once thought there was a deep bond ♫
♫ Using ten fingers to painstakingly ♫
♫ play the ancient chords ♫
♫ In exchange for only a moment of your smile ♫
♫ Use a lifetime to love only one person ♫
♫ How do you calculate the debt between each other? ♫
♫ Yet unwilling, unwilling ♫
♫ to make an exchange for a promise and apology ♫
♫ Our next lives are too far away ♫
♫ I would rather turn into ash and be lost in a reverie ♫
♫ When I want to return,
it will be time for my dream to come true ♫