[Mirror: A Tale of Twin Cities]
[Episode 41]
Your Highness, what is this?
It's Yu Huan's Sword of Light.
Watch mine!
Rest for a bit first.
Why is the Water Mirror open again?
High Priest.
Your Highness, what's happened?
I was next to Jing Lake and could feel the shaking from Wuse City.
What's wrong?
I'm fine. It's just this Water Mirror—
What's wrong with the Water Mirror?
It's Yu Huan. He appeared in the Water Mirror.
He attacked just now.
I'm afraid we can't use the Water Mirror anymore.
Your Highness.
Yu Huan broke through the Spirit Mirror Stage's enchantment under the Monument of Fallen Tears.
Hong Yuan, hurry and take the High Priest to get some rest.
Also, summon Prince Xuan and Prince Zi back. We will fight to our death to defend Wuse City.
Yes.
Yu Huan might take this information back to Jing City.
If the entrance to Wuse City is discovered, we'll be in a weakened position.
I understand.
Your Highness, I'd like to request
to remove the last seal.
But... you'll turn into ash.
A hundred years ago we already made our decision.
Now, it's Your Highness' turn to decide.
I can't decide.
We are in danger right now!
If Cangliu's army is upon us, we really won't have a chance.
A'Ying...
You're my family, not a tool for me to use.
Give me more time. I will find a solution!
- Your Highness!
- Don't say anymore.
Don't say anymore.
Your Highness, I have something to report.
Is it related to the Water Mirror?
It definitely is.
After Yu Huan was forced out of the passage way,
I found that the Water Mirror can't be opened anymore.
Actually, I saw Zhi Zhe in the Water Mirror again.
What!
What's wrong?
When?
When you pushed back Yu Huan.
Oh no! That's bad. Bad.
Previously, I only had suspicions.
Your Highness, when all of you were at the Stranded Dragon Abyss
I realized that I couldn't open the Water Mirror then either.
But then soon after it returned to normal.
I originally thought it was because I was old and losing my mind,
that my magic wasn't enough.
Could it be...
related to the Water Mirror in the Heavenly Temple?
I-I-I've checked the ancient books before.
I discovered that the Water Mirror in Wuse City and that of Heavenly Temple
are internally connected.
If ours can't be opened,
then the Heavenly Temple one can open.
But, Your Highness, without my skills
they can't open theirs at will.
Maybe they opened it and then immediately closed it.
But we can't determine
exactly when they opened it or what they saw, right?
Right.
Your Highness, Kongsang is in danger.
How did my royal father... make the choice back then?
His Majesty hesitated at that time.
In the evening, before he issued the command to Lord Xi Jing,
His Majesty... didn't sleep at all.
He personally told me that he wanted you to be happy and carefree,
to grow up in the prairies and away from conflicts.
He told me... the way to become king
was a lonely path.
He was willing to face the consequences,
he didn't want you to have to bear it.
But then...
he still brought me back.
That's right. Between being a father and a king,
His Majesty chose the way of the king.
The way of the king has always been a lonely path.
This guilty subject, Yu Huan, greets Lord Zhi Zhe.
There is a reason for me to cross the line this time.
I've discovered something; consider it a gift.
You went to Wuse City.
How did you know?
Because the Water Mirror has been opened.
Now, I want you to enter one more time.
I have an important mission for you.
Turning into ash,
Wuse City is broken, the Water Mirror is open.
What should I do
so I can solve this dilemma?
[Dark Golden Classics]
What's this?
[Six Star Reversal Formation]
"Six Star Reversal Formation"?
I've never seen this before.
Could this Six Star Reversal Formation
be the solution to the six princes turning into ash?
Great!
Did Yan Xi come back last night?
No. Before he left, some soldiers heard him say
he was going to take Na Sheng to the capital for a few days.
Okay. If he comes back, tell him to come and see me.
- You may go.
- Yes
Su Mo, I found a solution!
I found the solution to avoid turning into ash.
- What's the solution?
- The Six Star Reversal Formation.
- Six Star Reversal Formation?
- That's right.
Tell me. How is it done?
You can change the course of life by offering up power on the Spirit Mirror Stage.
It's another method to reverse life and death.
But I know that you didn't discover this method in the Dark Golden Classics previously.
Perhaps... I saw it wrong?
Su Mo, I found the solution.
A'Ying can be saved! How come you're unhappy?
This came too suddenly. I also think this Dark Golden Classics...
I'm just wondering whether we can find a safer method.
We don't have the time anymore.
The Wuse City has been invaded and the Water Mirror has been opened.
More than anyone else, I know I have to undo the last seal.
I know better than anyone that the last barrier must be broken.
I'm the last person who wants to see A'Ying and the others die.
We don't have time for a better solution.
So you came to find me for...
Obsidian.
Okay. Come with me.
What are you doing?
Give me the Dark Golden Classics.
What is this?
Just as I thought. Awhile ago, I saw this
black smoke on Su Nuo's body.
I think it's Zhi Zhe's spell. It's a good thing we discovered it early.
At the Stranded Dragon Abyss,
the real history was also different from what was recorded in the Dark Golden Classics.
The Six Star Reversal Formation was also a trap, wasn't it?
I'm afraid Zhi Zhe wants to take in your power
with the Six Star Reversal Formation. As for the Dark Golden Classics,
you can't believe all of it since you can't discern its authenticity.
The hope that just appeared... turned out to be fake.
Do Bai Ying and the others know about this?
I think... they should know by now.
I'll go explain to them.
Let me deal with the problem of turning into ash.
You have a solution?
When I'm certain, I will tell everyone.
All right.
I heard that Wuse City was invaded.
And the Water Mirror had been opened.
Yes. Yu Huan broke into the passage way
between the Spirit Mirror Stage and Wuse City.
He was forced out by High Priest.
The Six Star Reversal Formation was sent over shortly after.
Looks like their goal is Wuse City.
It really is killing two birds with one stone.
What's going on with the Water Mirror?
We think the Heavenly Temple Water Mirror has been opened.
- How many times has it been opened?
- Twice
Once at the Stranded Dragon Abyss, and then this time.
The important thing is we don't know when it'll be opened again.
This is problematic.
These past few days, His Highness has gone through all Wuse City's books.
For us, His Highness has bags under his eyes.
Sister Hong Yuan, if we don't turn into ash,
I want to ask if you'll have candied annatto fruit and roast pork with me in Ye City in a few days.
Where did you learn about these?
His Highness' private scrolls!
Just looking at these words makes me drool!
Your Highness.
Your Highness, we heard from the High Priest that you found a solution?
Yes, I did.
Everyone get ready. We'll head for the Spirit Mirror Stage tomorrow.
- Spirit Mirror Stage?
- I found a formation method in the Dark Golden Classics.
The formation can only be opened at a certain hour in each period.
I observed the astronomical events and found that the time is tomorrow at noon.
Tomorrow at noon?
There is little time then. What should we prepare, Your Highness?
Prepare some snow crystals.
Yes.
Your Highness, did the Dark Golden Classics mention the cost in this formation?
There's definitely a risk.
But no matter what happens, I will protect you all
regardless... of the cost.
Then, what did Su Mo say?
Su Mo gave me the obsidian needed for the formation.
Will he go with us?
A'Ying, this is Kongsang's affair.
I hope you can trust me in the same way that you trust Su Mo.
By taking this chance,
I hope we'll succeed.
Yan Xi, we've been through a lot lately.
I feel that I've matured a lot, too.
You are right. We should cherish each other even more in the future.
I won't be willful anymore.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Immediately bring the Heavenly Ring to Jing City.
Yan Xi? What's wrong?
Yan Xi.
What's wrong with you?
Has the Nine-headed Bird been released?
Yes, Your Lordship has thought through everything.
They'll never imagine that
the Yan Xi they painstakingly rescued is already under our mind control technique.
He's ours to use now.
When I get the Heavenly Ring,
what can Lord Zhi Zhe do?
The Spirit Mirror Stage is just ahead. Everyone, be careful.
Each time the Water Mirror opens,
it consumes more of my power than I expected.
Your Highness, you've looked worried the whole way here.
Are you looking for someone?
I'm checking to see if Yu Huan has been following us.
The Qing Clan's army has already checked Jiuyi Mountain. They didn't find Yu Huan.
- What about Su Mo?
- Bai Ying.
When we go inside, follow me closely.
All right.
Then, will Su Mo come to help us?
He won't be coming.
The Spirit Mirror Stage will open
and I'll kill the six princes.
At that time, the Wuse City barrier will lose its support.
Seize the opportunity to destroy Wuse City.
Once we win this battle, I'll give you the position as the commander-in-chief,
as commander of the Five Masters.
Everyone, stand in your own positions.
We'll begin.
Bai Ying, don't worry. I'm here.
Spirit Mirror Stage. Open up.
Your Highness, what's going on?
Sister Bai Ying, what's the matter with His Highness?
There's something wrong with the formation. We should all leave!
- Yes.
- Yes!
Don't waste your effort.
I finally have you, A'Wei.
Lord Zhi Zhe, so it was you!
Everything has its cracks.
Who can escape?
If he didn't want to try and save you all,
when would I have gotten the opportunity?
The Six Star Reversal Formation is a trap!
Your Highness!
Your Highness, what's the matter with you?
He is already under my control.
Also, it's just that old man left
in Wuse City, right?
Su Mo...
Su Mo?
Su Mo!
Su Mo...
won't be coming.
The obsidian is finally done releasing.
What?
Su Mo! You!
I'd like to see how you can withstand so much force.
You can break Wuse City's Water Mirror
if you fill the Sword of Light with the obsidian.
This is bad! Someone is attacking Wuse City's barrier!
If Su Mo is here,
is His Highness in Wuse City?
The Splitting Sword.
Did you really think your plan was flawless?
Su Mo saw through it a long time ago!
A'Ying!
Your Lord Zhi Zhe is going to use your life to open Wuse City!
What are you saying?
Once Wuse City's barrier is broken,
the passageway that you are in, will disappear immediately.
Stop with your scare tactics!
A'Ying!
Take care of her.
Su Mo, you want to push me to my limits
and kill me.
A'Ying.
You should go back to Wuse City. I'll take her to treat her injuries.
What happened on the top of Jing Pagoda?
Could it be... that Lord Zhi Zhe is in trouble?
If that's true, then Heaven is helping me.
My body…
has already decayed to such an extent.
Why is Bai Ying's spiritual consciousness so unstable?
Zhi Zhe didn't attack us.
Why have we all been injured?
This is bad! Someone is attacking Wuse City's barrier!
It turns out that the lives of the six princes
are tied together with the Wuse City's barrier.
Lin'er. Lin'er.
You have me. I'm right here.
What happened to me?
You just had a dream.
I dreamed of Lin'er and Royal Father.
Lin'er's greatest wish was to be buried in the Valley of the Ancestral Kings.
When you're better,
I'll go with you to see them.
Is the Sea Oath of the Star Soul spell the phrase on the tomb?
What's the matter with you?
Are you hiding something from me again?
I'm not keeping anything from you.
Whatever you want to know, I'll tell you.
Then, what was the deal with the Six Star Reversal Formation?
I didn't expect that Zhi Zhe would design so many obstacles for us.
I'm thinking...
could we use the Six Star Reversal Formation to severely injure Zhi Zhe?
What you mean is for us to continue with the Six Star Reversal Formation?
But my seal hasn't been removed completely yet.
That's why I need you to keep guard at Wuse City while I go to the Spirit Mirror Stage.
I've already obtained the power of the dragon deity. I'll leave the Splitting Sword with you.
We all saw the tragedy from 7,000 years ago at the Stranded Dragon Abyss.
Also, you were almost injured by it.
So now, why are you...
I don't believe in fate.
I trust you.
I've always wanted to tell you,
but never found a good time.
Actually, from the very beginning, I had already guessed.
Along the way to Jiuyi, even though you took the appearance of Zhen Lan,
but you didn't talk or behave like him.
I knew that you were always by my side.
Also, you made a big mistake.
You call me Bai Ying.
However, His Highness always calls me A'Ying.
Didn't you say, you would listen to everything I say?
Then call me A'Ying.
Forget it. I know you two had your reasons.
I have at least this tacit understanding.
So from that moment I knew,
this had to be a trap.
The so-called Six Star Reversal Formation
really couldn't reverse anything.
Should I tell her that I've found a solution?
But if she knew, she'd definitely not let me do it.
Don't worry.
A... A'Ying
[Master Peng's Residence - Cangliu]
[Master Peng's Residence]
My Lord.
You all may step out.
Today... I invited all of you to my residence
because I'm sure you've heard.
A lot has happened at the top of Jing Pagoda.
Yet Lord Zhi Zhe still hasn't given us
any instructions.
Master Peng, what do you mean?
Do you still not understand?
Back then, Lord Zhi Zhe promoted the five of us
and bestowed us with immortality.
He even brought magic and weapons to Cangliu.
Now...
Are you planning to betray Lord Zhi Zhe?
Haven't you also wanted to?
First, it was Yu Huan.
Then, it was Quanxian's Su Nuo.
Has Zhi Zhe given us any further orders?
Lord Zhi Zhe already abandoned us a while ago.
Still, you don't understand that yet?
Before we become abandoned pawns in a chess game,
let's get rid of the chess player first.
It is Master Xian who can see it most clearly.
Then, Master Peng, do you have a plan?
Yu Huan is nothing to fear.
As soon as he appears,
we'll send him to jail.
Everyone, my chess piece has already arrived.
What I want from everyone
is to cooperate with my plan.
[Arrest Order]
Has Lord Zhi Zhe really abandoned me?
Was Zhen Lan telling the truth?
Who am I even working for?
There are disloyal people...
in Cangliu.
Yu Huan is still alive.
He's now wanted all over the city.
If he falls into the hands of the Five Masters,
only I...
can protect him.
Lord Zhi Zhe,
I, Saintess Yu Zhu,
am pleading with you,
once this matter concludes,
set Yu Huan free.
Are you sure you don't need to rest more before you go back?
I'm still worried about His Highness, Sister Hong Yuan, and the others.
I want to go back and check on them.
Tell Zhen Lan for me.
Based on my understanding of the splitting technique,
Lord Zhi Zhe is now probably suffering severe backlash.
This is the best time to counterattack. Tell him to be prepared.
The Flower God Festival is the day after next.
I want to hang Lin'er a wishing plaque on the Flower Deity Tree.
Pray for peace for our uncertain future.
All right. I'll go with you.
♫ Suddenly far, suddenly near, swaying in the wind unsteadily ♫
♫ Your silhouette is like those clouds ♫
♫ I want to be your rain ♫
♫ Tapping on your heart ♫
♫ It's too uncertain whether the world will be cloudy or sunny ♫
♫ Taking advantage of this light drizzle to caress you softly ♫
♫ I train repeatedly ♫
♫ Afraid that the strong winds
will suddenly blow you away, losing you ♫
Wanting to Return by Zhou Shen
♫ Among the frosty clouds is the cold moon ♫
♫ A strange light in the night ♫
♫ In the dream, there is longing and fear ♫
♫ The layers of waves build up ♫
♫ Repeating the promise ♫
♫ Yet they disappear in the end ♫
♫ We've met several times ♫
♫ Yet it is hard to mention our fated relationship from the past ♫
♫ Sighing over the past is as frivolous as smoke ♫
♫ Split open the cocoon in my heart ♫
♫ You live in there ♫
♫ and have never been discovered by anyone ♫
♫ Ask time to borrow a chapter ♫
♫ The unforgettable memories ♫
♫ have disappeared, disappeared ♫
♫ I once thought there was a deep bond ♫
♫ Using ten fingers to painstakingly ♫
♫ play the ancient chords ♫
♫ In exchange for only a moment of your smile ♫
♫ Use a lifetime to love only one person ♫
♫ How do you calculate the debt between each other? ♫
♫ Yet unwilling, unwilling ♫
♫ to make an exchange for a promise and apology ♫
♫ Our next lives are too far away ♫
♫ I would rather turn into ash and be lost in a reverie ♫
♫ When I want to return,
it will be time for my dream to come true ♫