[Mirror : A Tale of Twin Cities]
[Episode 22]
Look over there. There should be cassava.
Go dig up some cassava.
I only want to eat meat.
- What are you muttering about?
- Nothing.
I was just saying, in this wild place there isn't even a tea stall to rest at.
At the tea stalls in the Central Plains, there would be food and drinks.
Even if there was a tea stall, we don't have any money.
You really are too poor of a crown prince, aren't you?
I...
- Oh, right! We have Yan Xi.
- Hey!
You're not thinking of selling Yan Xi for money, are you?
No, no. Yan Xi's tears can turn into pearls. We can sell them for money.
We warriors of Quanxian would rather shed blood than tears.
Really?
Yes.
Unless we suffer a great pain.
We don't otherwise randomly cry.
Look at how pitiful Na Sheng looks when she's starving.
Why don't you suffer just a bit?
Forget it. I'll look for something to eat on my own.
Come with me then.
I...
- I'll go get some firewood.
- Hey!
I'll dig by myself then.
This girl really does love to eat.
Your Highness, you must be hungry.
I'll go catch a pheasant.
Sure. Thank you, General.
Did you think I liked you?
I wouldn't have torn apart our marriage agreement back then.
Such a big cassava.
Why is it so hard to dig out?
Even a stupid cassava is hard to dig out.
Loosen the soil. Loosen the soil.
Cangliu's new weapon!
Na Sheng.
Na Sheng! Na Sheng!
Na Sheng, wake up!
Na Sheng!
- Why did it explode?
- Na Sheng.
Sorry, I shouldn't have let you dig cassavas out alone.
Can you wake up?
Na Sheng. Na Sheng!
Yan Xi, let me take a look.
How is she?
She's doomed. We can't save her.
Yan Xi, let's dig a hole and bury her.
- Were you about to cry?
- You were pretending to be dead?
Not totally.
- I got–
- You're still lying!
What happened exactly?
I found it hard to dig out the cassava,
so I wanted to use magic to blow it loose a bit.
But I didn't expect to pass out.
Since Yan Xi was so worried about me,
I didn't know if I should wake up sooner or later.
Sooner, of course! How could you joke about your life?
Look at you.
Go.
Yan Xi! Yan Xi!
You've already grown up so much.
Back then your mother Yu Ji, Madam Ru Yi, and I
were as close as sisters.
Later on,
Yu Ji lost touch with you due to the war.
She got depressed and passed away.
Fortunately, Madam Ru Yi found you.
Who would've thought, in the blink of an eye, so many years have passed.
Madam, you're my elder.
Thank you for taking care of my mother back in the day.
Young Master, please don't do that.
Young Master. Young Master, please don't do that.
I just got emotional for a moment.
Back then you were just a baby swaddled in cloth,
but now you've become the powerful Emperor of the Sea.
It's just a shame that Su Nuo...
I did a terrible job back then. I didn't take care of her.
Let's not mention it anymore. It's nothing but sadness.
I believe your mother's spirit in Heaven has nothing to worry about anymore.
The future is hopeful.
Young Master. Princess Bai Ying.
Cheers.
Cheers, Madam.
If you keep drinking, you'll get drunk. This wine is strong.
I'm fine. This wine isn't strong.
What a great kid.
Am I right, Young Master?
Yan Xi. Yan Xi, can you not be mad at me?
How could I not be mad?
I just wanted to see if you'd be worried about me.
Of course, I was worried about you!
Really?
Are you telling the truth?
The mission the Young Master gave me was to protect you.
If anything were to happen to you, how could I explain it to Young Master?
That aside, if Brother Ice Cube hadn't told you to protect me,
- would you have been worried about me?
- I...
So can you joke about your life?
Is it because your life in the Central Plains was so comfortable that you don't care about your life?
No, I...
I just wanted to see if you were worried about me.
Of course, I was worried!
They're back here again. They haven't even gotten out and I'm already done roasting my chicken.
These two silly kids. Na Sheng just wants to know if Yan Xi likes her.
If Yan Xi didn't like her, he wouldn't have been mad this long.
Yan Xi is unbelievable. Na Sheng follows him all day long, makes him laugh,
and acts silly with him all the time. If she doesn't like him, I don't know what this is.
They can't even tell.
Why are you looking at me?
You're good at talking about others.
Stop fighting. Come over and eat chicken.
- I'm not eating.
We're going to the left peak of Jiuyi Mountain tomorrow.
- I'm not going.
All right. You and I can eat.
Yan Xi. Yan Xi. Yan Xi.
Keep me company.
Actually, I envy them sometimes.
What do you envy?
It's difficult indeed...
to confess your love.
You're here.
I've been behind you this whole time.
Why did you come here alone?
I...
This.
Bai Ying, do you know that you're already drunk?
I know I'm drunk,
but I've never been drunk before.
I don't ever get drunk!
A hundred years ago, you only got drunk once.
What are you saying?
You can't hold my hand.
Why?
Because... Su Mo would be unhappy.
He's often unhappy,
but he never tells me.
You're not allowed to hold my hand.
So you know everything.
So... who can hold your hand?
Su Mo.
Who am I then?
You... are as good-looking as Su Mo.
Do you know, if you do this, Su Mo will be angry, too?
But this is a trivial matter.
Trivial matter?
Are there bigger things that will make Su Mo angry?
I'm not telling.
It looks like you really are hiding something from him.
I'm not hiding anything from him.
I just want...
♫ Using up all my fortune just to touch you ♫
♫ Even crying sounds so beautiful ♫
♫ Listening to the soft whisper of the rain from that day ♫
♫ That is the sound of my heart, so please listen ♫
Bai Ying.
I'm sleepy.
Su Mo.
If...
If I disappear someday, am not around anymore,
and you can't find me anymore,
don't be sad.
You just need to know that
you're the best, best, best person in this world.
I'll always...
Don't worry.
I said that I'd always be safeguarding you from behind.
I won't let you disappear.
♫ That is me using my tears to breathe with you ♫
♫ Using up all my fortune just to touch you ♫
♫ Even crying sounds so beautiful ♫
♫ Listening to the soft whisper of the rain from that day ♫
♫ That is the sound of my heart, so please listen ♫
♫ Because when it becomes sunny ♫
♫ I will leave quietly ♫
Young Master. Young Master.
Why don't you rest a little longer? After Princess Bai Ying wakes up,
- you can then go to Jiuyi Mountain.
- No need.
We've already been delayed too long.
There's still a long distance before reaching Jiuyi Mountain.
By the time we reach Jiuyi Mountain, she should be awake.
This is the recipe for the Drunken Essence of Lilac Daphne.
When the princess is awake,
please give it to her.
If the princess doesn't understand something,
she can use the Sound Pearl to ask me anytime.
Madam, you're so thoughtful.
I really like Princess Bai Ying.
Even though the situation in Yunhuang is in dire straits,
I still wish that she could relax occasionally.
She's thoughtful in handling things, dignified, and prudent,
but... but she's very restrained, too.
It looks like she's really suffering.
If Bai Ying were to know how much you care about her,
she'd definitely be pleased.
That's good then. That's good then.
We'll be leaving now.
I respectfully bid farewell to Young Master.
[Tianxiang Tavern]
I hope my master's wish will be fulfilled.
Awake now?
The fruit wine was sweet. I didn't know it would be so intoxicating.
I won't drink anymore so that we won't delay our trip.
It's fine. You were quite adorable when you were drunk.
You... Put me down first.
All right.
This is the entrance to the right peak of Jiuyi Mountain?
[Jiuyi Mountain - Right Peak]
Will Jiuyi's barrier bother you?
We still have to barge in.
[Misty Forest]
How are you feeling?
The barrier is truly powerful here.
I can already sense that my power is decreasing.
Any other discomfort?
No.
Are these fireflies?
Why doesn't it look like what Madam Tianxiang described?
Don't be charmed by the surface.
Be careful.
I wonder what else is in the deep parts of the forest.
Let's go.
The time has arrived.
The star that has been suppressing the Puojun Star's light
has finally fallen.
(T/N: Puojun is the easternmost star in the Big Dipper. It symbolizes a death-defying warrior that will break through the enemy.)
Lord Zhi Zhe, is Puojun going to shine?
That's right.
When the greedy wolf escapes from the trap, chaos shall rise.
When the bright star appears, disorder brings calamity.
If the greedy wolf represents Su Mo,
his return to Yunhuang will lead to turbulence.
Then the bright star represents Zhen Lan.
When Zhen Lan awakens, Kongsang is restored, the Land-Sea Alliance
will gradually form a confrontation with Cangliu.
In that case, Cangliu is in danger.
Pojun...
is the star that will breakthrough this situation.
Yu Huan. Yu Huan.
Who's calling me?
Do you want to obtain a strong force?
Who are you?
You don't need to know who I am.
You only need to know that I can give you what you want.
What do you want from me?
Follow me. Obey my command.
I'm not going to follow anyone.
I understand everything about you:
all of your fears, ambition, and desires.
You want to get ride of them.
You want to really win for once
and truly be in control of your fate!
If I follow you,
how can I truly control my fate?
I will give you freedom and everything else you want.
What I really want, I'll get myself.
I hope you won't regret it.
I will come to you again.
The mist is really vast in the forest.
We can't even see what direction we're going in. I think we're lost.
Pojun appears.
Pojun?
Pojun, a star of exhaustion. It's hard to say if it'll lead to loss or success.
The Pojun Star hasn't appeared in Yunhuang for many years. It's faintly glowing now.
I don't know what that represents.
Even the stars have disappeared. It's even harder to distinguish the direction now.
Let's go.
What's wrong? Are you feeling unwell?
I feel a little...
Su Mo, I'll go with you.
I'm not going back to the Jing Pagoda.
A'Ying.
Su Mo, I don't want to disappear.
I want to stay alive longer.
This is... This is my own desire.
Because I want... to always be with you.
That's wonderful then.
- How are you feeling?
We were affected by the miasma just now. You said a lot to me.
What did I say?
You said
that you want to be a sword master to fight for justice.
You also said...
What else did I say?
You also said that you didn't want to disappear.
You wanted to stay alive longer.
I told you my innermost thoughts.
I really envy your people, to be able to live 1,000 years.
If I would also live that long,
I could do so much.
Is this really all you meant?
What else did you think I meant?
I was talking nonsense. Don't make fun of me anymore.
What's wrong? Feeling bad again?
Maybe... Maybe I inhaled too much of the miasma.
I don't know how much longer I can endure it.
It may happen again.
Let's find an exit quickly.
But the misty is so heavy now, and the stars are covered up.
There's no way to discern the direction.
Everything in the world is mutually reinforcing and conquering.
Some of the most dangerous places are also where one finds a way to survive.
Look. All the fireflies are flying towards that direction.
Let's go that way and take a look.
Let's go.
I didn't expect them to pass through the miasmic forest and ascend Jiuyu Mountain.
Then, we should...
It's been a hundred years. He really is like a ghost that won't go away.
I've already sent a message to Jing City.
I'm sure Lord Zhi Zhe will help us.
This time, I'll thoroughly destroy him.
Let's rest for a bit.
All right.
Did you say to take a rest because you saw how tired I was?
We've walked a long way already.
I didn't hear you say you were tired before.
To me, the most important thing is to protect everyone's safety.
Also, to protect you. Whether I'm tired or not isn't worth mentioning.
But you can...
You can tell a friend.
You should care more about yourself, too.
Because of the Land-Sea Nation Alliance, you should get used to having people help you.
All right.
This is the King of Jiuyi's Nine-headed Bird.
When the Nine-headed Bird comes,
it's when the King of Jiuyi wants medicine.
But why is it earlier this year than in the past?
The Nine-headed Bird has sent a message,
saying Su Mo and Bai Ying have reached Jiuyi Mountain's right peak.
They're looking for the Splitting Sword.
Summon Yu Huan here.
Yes.
We've walked so far, but haven't seen a water source.
Are you thirsty? I'll go look for some water.
There's no rush. I'll see if I can use a spell
to condense the water here.
Why would it do that?
Jiuyi Mountain is indeed sinister.
Let's look elsewhere to see if there's another water source.
Let's go.
A pool of stagnant water.
I think we're really in the Misty Forest that Madam Tianxiang described.
Everything in this forest, on the surface looks like other forests,
but actually everything is dead.
This scenery really looks like it came from a nightmare.
Jiuyi Mountain was originally Prince Qing's domain.
Unfortunately, Prince Qing betrayed Kongsang a hundred years ago,
so it became Cangliu's territory.
They say Prince Qing Chen has already died.
I'm still doubtful about Prince Qing Chen's death.
After I came back from Yunhuang, I asked Aunt Ru to check into it.
But there's still no news.
Why do you doubt his death?
Back then in the Jing Pagoda, he said Quanxian's blood pact
was ineffective against him.
I immediately used it.
But he indeed wasn't harmed at all.
How could that be?
I suspect that the black-robed person on the Jing Pagoda was helping him.
The black-robed person?
We also sent people to look into it.
There hasn't been any news about Prince Qing Chen in the past hundred years.
That's why Jiuyi Mountain
has been stationed by the secondary branches of the Qing clan.
It's unlikely that he's still alive.
No matter what, if Prince Qing Chen
is dead, I want to see the corpse. If he's alive, I want to see him.
A'Huan, what's the matter?
Why do you seem so unsettled?
Older Sister, don't worry. I probably just didn't rest well.
When I get back, I'll tell people to prepare a medicinal soup to supplement you.
Older Sister, I'm fine.
I'm just worried about you.
A'Huan, you must be careful when you see Lord Zhi Zhe this time.
Older Sister, you seem to fear Lord Zhi Zhe.
Lord Zhi Zhe has strong powers and his temper is unpredictable,
especially during this time.
Anyway, you must be cautious about everything.
I know.
Go ahead.
Yu Huan greets Lord Zhi Zhe.
I'm grateful for Lord Zhi Zhe saving my life.
Did your older sister tell you?
Older Sister told me that the real ruler of Cangliu
is you, Lord Zhi Zhe.
Also, Lord Zhi Zhe removed my Quanxian blood pact.
That's right.
Smart.
Stoic.
Ambitious.
As expected of the person I've chosen.
From now on, you'll report directly to me.
I shall not disappoint your command.
- I will do my best.
- Good.
I have an important mission...
to assign to you.
Yu Zhu.
Master Peng.
Lord Zhi Zhen summoned Yu Huan.
You've done a lot behind my back.
I wouldn't dare. It's Lord Zhi Zhe—
Lord Zhi Zhe?
That night, who was it that you took up the Jing Pagoda?
It was the person that Lord Zhi Zhe invited to a meeting at Jing Pagoda.
Someone that Lord Zhi Zhe invited. Who was he?
Didn't Master Peng engage in a fight with him in the library before?
Are talking in riddles with me?
Why did Lord Zhi Zhe want to meet a Kongsang person?
I don't dare question him.
If I have any intentions of prying,
Lord Zhi Zhe will surely punish me.
Please forgive me, Master Peng.
I really don't know who Lord Zhi Zhe invited.
Don't think that just because Lord Zhi Zhe summoned Yu Huan
that you have a new person to rely on.
Don't forget back then how you two crawled step by step to where you are now.
I don't dare.
I'm ordering you to immediately go to Jiuyi Mountain
to kill the Emperor of the Sea.
Am I going alone?
There's a Qing clan's barrier at Jiuyi Mountain.
Anyone who is not from Kongsang
will have his power reduced by half.
But half of the blood in your body is Kongsang blood.
You're the best person to go to Jiuyi.
It's also the best time
to get rid of the Emperor of the Sea.
I don't dare deceive Lord Zhi Zhe,
but I've been defeated by the Emperor of the Sea, Su Mo, many times.
You... fear him?
I have no fear.
But I also have to admit
that I cannot defeat him in my current state.
It's good to acknowledge defeat.
But you shouldn't be shackled by it.
Thank you for the teaching, Lord Zhi Zhe.
I'll teach you a fighting formation.
It's called the Fire Formation.
Used especially to overcome the Quanxian.
You only need to lure him into the formation.
Thank you, Lord Zhi Zhe.
Over there.
[Jiuyi Mountain - Left Peak]
We've arrived.
Yan Xi, you've achieved your mission by sending us here.
You can go back.
I'll be going into Jiuyi soon.
I probably won't see you for many days.
Can you calm down and not be angry anymore?
I heard the old granddad in the village say,
it's not good for your health to stay angry.
Then-Then I'll explain it one last time, just once more.
I-I really didn't mean to trick pearls out of you.
I didn't do it on purpose.
Forget it. It'll be good as long as you aren't angry.
When you go into the mountain, don't run around.
Don't stray too far from Crown Prince Zhen Lan and General Xi Jing.
You must listen to them. Be careful.
Enough now. The mission is more important.
Be careful on your way back.
I'll trouble the two of you to please take care of Na Sheng.
Let's go, Miss Na Sheng.
Let's go.
Na Sheng!
Yan Xi!
I just wanted to tell you.
I...
I'm not going back to the main camp.
I'll wait here to support you.
Really?
This is great. Then I'll go unseal the seal right away.
You must be careful by yourself here. Wait for me.
I'm going to go right now. Let's go!
- Slowly. Slowly.
- I'm going to unseal the seal now!
- Slowly.
- Let's unseal the seal.
- Go! Go!
- Don't trip and fall!
- Be careful!
- Let's go!
Wait for us!
Ever since the fall of Kongsang, the Jiuyi Mountain has been covered by the barrier.
Ting and I've passed by here many times.
But right now who the King of Jiuyi is, no one knows.
There probably aren't many people in the Jiuyi palace.
It's so gloomy and spooky, it's too scary.
That's why you can't run around. Stay close to Xi Jing.
Your Highness, later will we go directly up the mountain
to the Jiuyi Palace and meet the King of Jiuyi?
Yes. When the time comes, pretend you're Kongsang refugees.
Don't reveal our identities.
The Heavenly Ring is lighting up.
Is something happening with A'Ying?
- No, it's not.
- Why were you shouting for nothing then?
We're probably not far from the other seal.
Wait a moment.
No?
Na Sheng, are you sure about this?
We've been walking with you for two hours in the forest already.
No, it should be right over there.
That should be Queen Bai Wei's tomb.
She seems to be luring us here on purpose.
- This singing—
- Be careful.
It could be a trap.
What is it?
Maybe it's Tu Luo?
Hurry and go.
It should be here.
That's not right.
This doesn't look like a tomb.
Let's go in to take a look.
[Be Wei's Former Home]
Queen Bai Wei was Kongsang's first queen.
Her tomb is a place for later generations to revere.
How could it be like this?
That's right. Isn't a tomb a grave?
But this is clearly a bamboo hut.
So strange.
Look. A mark of the rose.
Even if it's not a tomb,
I think it is still related to Queen Bai Wei.
Why don't we go in and take a look?
Your Highness.
You step back. I'll take a look.
Na Sheng, come here.
You bold treasure thieves!
How dare you barge into Queen Bai Wei's tomb!
Who are you?
[Li Zhu - Qing Clan's servant - Kongsang]
How dare you trespass here?
You're from Kongsang?
This girl isn't from Kongsang.
Miss, we're Kongsang people who rushed here from the Central Plains.
We came especially to pay respects to our ancestors.
To pay respect to the ancestors?
Kongsang fell a hundred years ago.
Why would there be anyone paying respects?
Wanting to Return by Zhou Shen
♫ Among the frosty clouds is the cold moon ♫
♫ A strange light in the night ♫
♫ In the dream, there is longing and fear ♫
♫ The layers of waves build up ♫
♫ Repeating the promise ♫
♫ Yet they disappear in the end ♫
♫ We've met several times ♫
♫ Yet it is hard to mention our fated relationship from the past ♫
♫ Sighing over the past is as frivolous as smoke ♫
♫ Split open the cocoon in my heart ♫
♫ You live in there ♫
♫ and have never been discovered by anyone ♫
♫ Ask time to borrow a chapter ♫
♫ The unforgettable memories ♫
♫ have disappeared, disappeared ♫
♫ I once thought there was a deep bond ♫
♫ Using ten fingers to painstakingly ♫
♫ play the ancient chords ♫
♫ In exchange for only a moment of your smile ♫
♫ Use a lifetime to love only one person ♫
♫ How do you calculate the debt between each other? ♫
♫ Yet unwilling, unwilling ♫
♫ to make an exchange for a promise and apology ♫
♫ Our next lives are too far away ♫
♫ I would rather turn into ash and be lost in a reverie ♫
♫ When I want to return,
it will be time for my dream to come true ♫