[Mirror: A Tale of Twin Cities]
[Episode 8]
Xiao!
- After him! Hurry!
- Yes!
- This way!
- Stop right there!
Capture him!
Hurry!
- Split up!
- Yes!
- This way!
- After him!
Escaped again!
We searched every river channel but found no traces of him.
We can't find him when he's alive or his corpse when he's dead.
- Did he vanish into the air?
- We didn't come back completely empty-handed.
Someone recognized the culprit who broke the prisoner out of prison from a portrait.
He is Yan Xi, the Quanxian army's Commissioner of the Left.
- I—
- That Commissioner of the Left
was injured when he escaped.
The channel between Ye City and Jing City has always been under our control.
I don't think he could have passed through the blockade. He can't have escaped far.
There is another possibility.
Taoyuan Province.
I will immediately inform the Cangliu soldiers
to assist the investigation.
We'll leave the search for the Commissioner of the Left
to Nan Zhao.
Governor Gao Shunzhao of Taoyuan Province is very powerful.
I heard he has an intimate, Quanxian friend.
That's why the entire Taoyuan Province is tolerant of merpeople.
Taoyuan Province soldiers
may give them a way out.
Yes.
You should still
kill that person who crossed Tianque.
Remember.
I want to see that person, dead or alive.
Yes.
You two may leave.
[Taoyuan Province]
Wait. Go ahead.
- What is this?
- A sachet.
Go ahead.
Wait. What is inside your bag?
Clothes
Let's play.
Come, come.
Slow down.
This is so fun.
I'm not waiting for you.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Miss, do you want some buns?
Shopkeeper,
can I use these to exchange for some buns?
What is that? Do you think I'm stupid?
You want to exchange these weeds for food?
Go away.
No, wait. How is this weed?
This is valuable fairy grass. You can sell it for money.
Hurry and leave.
Miss! Miss!
Miss, buns.
You're hungry, right? Eat them while they're hot.
I was careless just now and bumped into you.
So embarrassing. I'm sorry.
It's fine. You didn't do it on purpose.
You don't look like you're from here.
Where are you from?
I came from Central Plains.
Central Plains?
All by yourself?
Yes.
I don't know much about Central Plains.
But here, life isn't easy when you don't have money.
Just now, I saw you try to exchange your fairy grass for buns.
That shopkeeper really doesn't have an eye.
One fairy grass
can exchange for 10 buns and plenty more!
That's right.
By the way, Uncle, do you know where there is an apothecary?
I want to sell these fairy grass for some money.
Because you called me uncle,
I'll take care of this matter.
There's a merchant I know very well who specifically buys valuable medicinal herbs.
I guarantee that he can give you the best price in Yunhuang.
Really?
This is great!
Oh, right, Uncle.
I don't have much to repay you with
I have some of these to give you.
If it's not enough, I have more.
This... This fairy plant is too precious.
I can't take it. We have a rule in Taoyuan Province.
When we pass by and if we can help, we must lend a hand.
We cannot ask for compensation.
How about it? Follow me then?
All right, all right.
Let's go.
The assassination attempt failed today. You're no longer useful.
I'll make it fast and pain-free.
Wait.
General,
what are you doing here instead of carrying out Lord Peng's order?
It's not up to you, to kill the person that I bought here.
Regular prisoners would have already confessed when they'd encountered the branding irons.
You're bones are quite hard.
(T/N: unyielding person)
Who are you?
What trick are you playing now?
You know me?
When I woke up,
I couldn't remember anything.
Did you interrogate her before?
She's very tough, and wouldn't confess anything.
I had the priest use the mind-control technique on her.
However, she resisted very strongly.
Maybe something happened to her brain.
Then she's really lost her memory.
Then you are useless to Cangliu now.
I can give you a way to live. Be my weapon.
Partner with me to help me drive the Wind Falcon.
What do you think?
General,
she is just a prisoner captured for treason.
You want her to drive the Wind Falcon?
Isn't that against military rules?
Answer me.
I don't remember anything.
But I know you saved me.
A Quanxian person will always repay kindness.
Then, starting today,
your life is mine.
Guards.
Release her. Take her.
General, you mustn't.
Nan Zhao, don't forget that you're my vice general in the military camp!
You do not have the authority to interfere with my decisions.
Didn't Lord Peng give you an assignment?
You can go to Taoyuan Province to carry it out now.
Yu Huan.
Take her back to the training field, and get the best medical officer to treat her.
- Yes.
What are you doing?
Agile, strong-willed, and loyal.
Also, a natural-born acuity.
She will be a good driver of Wind Falcon.
You should know better than I do.
Since she dares enter Banbu City to assassinate you, she must be a powerful figure.
- Is there anything she can't do?
- I know.
- Thank you for this time.
- Why thank me?
I should apologize to you.
If I had been personally on guard this time,
then everything that happened later on wouldn't have happened.
Also, you should give Lord Peng
a proper explanation about keeping this prisoner.
I've brought good merchandise.
Go on in.
You're here.
This young girl comes from the Central Plains.
All alone by herself.
Looking at her appearance, she's worth a good price. Right?
I can make the purchase.
But I must...
inspect the merchandise first.
That... The fairy grass is in here.
I brought them from the Central Plains.
What is this?
This... Boss, is an inspection really necessary?
Look at how good of a condition she's in.
Her birthplace is the Central Plains.
We've been friends for so many years, I wouldn't cheat you.
Young girl, you're all by yourself anyway.
When the time comes, I'll find a good husband for you.
I'll make sure you live a good life.
Aren't we selling fairy grass? Why sell me?
Save me!
High Priest. Your Highness. There's a reaction from the Heaven and Earth rings.
- What's the matter?
- Na Sheng is most likely in danger.
Na Sheng is wearing the Heavenly Ring.
We should be able to see her in the Water Mirror.
- Let go of me!
- Wait.
Su Mo.
Brother Ice Cube! Brother Ice Cube, how did you know I was in there?
I didn't expect him to be in Taoyuan Province, too.
With him there, he can protect Na Sheng.
Brother Ice Cub! Brother Ice Cube, how did you know I was in there?
You knew I was in danger? Good thing you were there to save me.
Brother Ice Cube, you are so good-looking. Why do you always have a stern face?
Look, you should smile more.
Don't follow me.
It's you who is following me.
How is it that I'm following you?
If it weren't so, how could you have saved me?
There is only this one road in Tianque Mountain.
Since there is only one road, why won't you let me follow you?
Don't you want to see Sister Bai Ying?
There are many bad people in the city. You should leave the city.
Brother Ice Cube!
I think it's better if you practice smiling more.
Come inside, guests.
[Ruyi Gambling House]
Aunt Ru, greetings.
- Be careful.
- Yes.
- Let's gamble two more rounds.
- Sure, we can.
- Aunt Ru is really pretty today.
- Thank you much.
- Your complexion looks great.
- Aunt Ru is wearing new clothes today. So pretty.
Have fun.
- Aunt Ru.
Hello, everyone.
Aunt Ru, you've come down.
I've kept an eye out for half a day. Nothing has happened.
Rest assured. I'm here, right?
Quickly! Quickly! Come on!
Place your bets and let go of your hands. Don't touch it.
Aunt Ru, I have a lucky streak today.
Your reward.
Thank you, boss. I hope you earn enough to overfill your pot today.
[Madam Ru Yi - Quanxian Merperson]
Okay.
Come on, come on, come on!
Take care.
Let's continue! Let's continue!
Bet either big or small! Bet either big or small!
Anyone else? Anyone?
Place your bet and then hands off!
- Big! Big!
- Open it!
- Boss.
I'm having a lucky steak. You better not say anything that brings bad luck.
Someone came to sell merchandise earlier.
Not only was it fake merchandise,
- they even smashed our courtyard.
- What?
Let's roll again.
It's him! The cheat!
- Catch him!
- You bastard.
- Stop!
- Thanks.
- Scram.
Some customers in the back are fighting.
Him!
Young Master, please.
Young Master, we received the news you sent through the sound pearls.
We've waited a long time, and you've finally appeared.
I should have met up with you all back then.
But a lot happened afterward.
I didn't expect our parting
to be 100 years long.
Back then, you only left one sound pearl.
You said you were going to search for strength.
There was no more news from you for 100 years.
Where did you go during all these years?
- Have you been living well?
- I've caused you to worry.
In the past 100 years, I was away from Yunhuang
to search for great powers.
Now, even though my power as the Emperor of the Sea have not awakened,
I'm different from 100 years ago.
I'll no longer let anyone slaughter us.
Young Master is even more mature and steady now.
You must have gone through a lot of hardship.
My hardship is nothing.
On the other hand, you have operated this gambling house
to raise money for Quanxian and to collect intel.
You've worked hard.
Don't say that.
In order to return to Biluo Sea as soon as possible,
this is all a part of my duty.
By the way, back then, I had you and Yan Xi
take those we saved away from Jing City.
I wonder what happened to them.
Most of our tribe people under Prince Qing's control
got away successfully.
It's just that, right before they left,
they were still backstabbed by that despicable Prince Qing.
Prince Qing has issued an order. Kill everyone without mercy!
Yes!
How is Prince Qing now?
We looked for Prince Qing.
In the past 100 years, we haven't heard any news about him.
Maybe he really is dead.
Will you help or not?
Su Mo, in this world,
there is still someone who can break your blood pact.
Aunt Ru, do you know something?
Back then, at the top of the Jing Pagoda,
I activated the blood pact,
but Prince Qing was not harmed at all.
How is that possible?
Quanxian's blood pact is drawn on life.
Unless it's extremely great powers,
the pact is very difficult to break.
Someone must have helped him behind the scenes.
Unless I see his corpse,
- I'll continue to doubt his death.
- Young Master is wise.
I will send people to keep searching for Prince Qing.
All right.
How is our Quanxian Great Camp?
The elders are already at the Quanxian Great Camp
waiting for Young Master.
Young Master, please.
We placed the Great Camp at the bottom of Jing Lake, in a very hidden place.
Jing Lake isn't far from Jing City.
The elders used their power to create an enchantment.
They hid the Great Camp beyond the common people's vision.
It's been safe, hidden from everyone.
It's just that the elders are old now and their powers are declining.
I'm afraid that they won't last much longer.
Don't worry about the enchantment.
I will reinforce it.
Aside from the spies placed in various places to collect intel,
we've done our best to conserve our strength.
Just recently, we sent a small unit to Banbu City
intending to assassinate Cangliu's General Yu Huan.
But we failed.
Yan Xi was able to escape, but Xiao got captured.
But Yan Xi sent good news just recently,
saying Xiao should have successfully escaped also.
Someone has gone to receive them early this morning. Rest assured, Young Master.
In the next few days, contact the others in Taoyuan Province first.
After Xiao and Yan Xi return, we will go back to the Great Camp in Jing Lake together.
Yes.
What do you have planned for later?
I'm going to the Entrapped Dragon Abyss to unseal the dragon deity's seal.
With the power of the dragon deity, I'll break the seal of the Sea Soul Plain in the Bilou Sea
and take everyone home.
But it's not easy to break the dragon deity's seal.
You need to go to Jiuyi Mountain to retrieve the Splitting Sword first.
It is indeed not easy.
The road back to Biluo Sea is full of difficulties.
We need sufficient manpower.
How many of our people are in Taoyuan Province?
About 1,000 in Taoyuan Province.
About eighty percent are adults though.
But Taoyuan Province's topography is very complex.
Plus, Cangliu has stationed many troops here.
To take away so many people, I'm afraid we need to think of another way.
All right. Aunt Ru, first contact the others in Taoyuan Province.
Yes, Young Master.
A few days ago, I also heard that
Cangliu people sent many soldiers
to Tianque to capture someone. I kept inquiring
but don't know who exactly they are trying to capture.
They want to capture those who passed through Tianque.
It's me and another girl.
That girl is carrying the Heavenly Ring.
The Heavenly Ring has reappeared?
What exactly has happened during the 100 years I was away from Yunhuang?
Cangliu invaded en masse.
They had magical weapons on the outside and spies cooperating from the inside.
They conquered Ye City very quickly.
Kongsang's Crown Prince Zhen Lan used the Heavenly Ring's power to lead troops against Cangliu,
but he still suffered a terrible defeat. Young Master?
Previously, I saw Bai Ying and Zhen Lan on Tianque Mountain.
If the Heaven and Earth rings reunite,
then the Kongsang people will surely want to take back Jing City.
Young Master, during this time, you should stay here at the gambling house.
This secret chamber is very safe. No one will disturb you.
All right.
Young Master, please rest for now.
I will prepare some food for you.
Thank you, Aunt Ru.
To me, what happened 100 years ago was a mistake.
Right now, I just want to make up for that mistake.
I've thought that if I never met you,
none of the tragedies would have happened.
During these hundred years, I never missed you.
I never longed for your return.
Even more so, I never thought I would see you again.
After I woke up, I sensed my other powers by using my monarchy powers.
They are separately sealed at Ghost and Deity Abyss,
Jiuyi Mountain, and also
Jing City's Jing Tower.
Good. Good.
We've wandered everywhere for the past 100 years.
Those places are all known to be dangerous.
Ghost and Deity Abyss is in the south of Yunhuang. Legend has it that it's difficult for even ghosts and deities to enter.
That's why it's named Ghost and Deity Abyss.
[Ghost and Deity Abyss]
Jiuyi was originally our Qing clan's domain.
[Jiuyi Mountain]
It's been shrouded in mist for a hundred years. It's once again haunted by ghostly creatures and isolated.
The Jing Pagoda is the center of Jing City.
[Kongsang Imperial City - Jing Citiy]
It's heavily guarded and very difficult to get close to.
The Cangliu people are really ruthless.
Given the current power of the heavenly ring,
I'm afraid it'll be very difficult to protect Na Sheng, to break through Cangliu's obstacles,
and to unseal the remaining seals.
This Earth ring can sense the Heavenly ring.
I should be the one who goes.
No way, no way.
Right now, none of the Kongsang people
can leave Wuse City during the day.
The six princes and princesses can only travel at night.
How can we safeguard Miss Na Sheng?
There won't be any sunlight under the water of the Ghost and Deity Abyss.
That's good because we can escort her there.
But Jiuyi Mountain is a long-distance away. Besides, along the way,
there aren't any places to hide from the sunlight during the day.
We have to think of a way to get someone else to escort her.
Do we have anyone else?
Who says Kongsang's 100,000 people are all in Wuse City?
Isn't there still a person in Yunhuang?
Senior Brother.
It is Xi Jing,
Kongsang's Great General.
[Xi Jing - Successor of the Holy Sword - Kongsang]
General, we are lucky today.
I caught a wild hare.
[Ting - Former Leader of Quanxian]
After we cross over the snow mountain in front of us, we'll arrive at the Central Plains.
We'll be away from Yunhuang.
To me, whether it's the Central Plains or Yunhuang,
it's fine as long as I can follow you, General.
But to you, as long as there's wine to drink
and money to gamble, it's fine.
There's no more wine.
There's still this much left?
Did you tell me yesterday that we were out of wine?
It will still take some time before we reach Taoyuan Province.
If you finish it all, General, you'll be miserable at night.
But can't you go a day without drinking, General?
Don't call me "General" anymore. I've stopped being one long ago.
I'll go clean the hare, and we'll have something to eat tonight.
Ting.
I've let you leave every year, but you never would.
A 100 years have flown by. You haven't seen your older sister in a long time, right?
Yes. It's indeed been a long time since I've received news about my sister.
You've suffered a lot following me.
You should leave. You are a free person.
Go find your family and reunite with your older sister.
General, during these 100 years, I've already said this over 100 times.
If I'm not around when you get drunk and lie on the road, who will drag you back.
If I'm not around, will you eat raw fish and uncooked vegetables every day?
If I'm not around when you gamble and lose all your money, who will bail you out?
What's the use in bailing me out?
I am no longer the Xi Jing from 100 years ago.
In my eyes, you are the same as 100 years ago.
Nothing has changed at all.
Konsang has become Cangliu.
How could I have not changed?
General, if we hurry,
we'll reach Taoyuan Province in half a day's time. There is a Ruyi Gambling House there.
The owner has good wine.
All right.
Brother Ice Cube is a good person, right?
He told me to go hide outside of the city.
It is quite safe.
But I'm so hungry.
I'm tired and hungry and hungry and tired.
No way.
What's going on with this girl now?
High Priest.
Hurry and activate the Water Mirror.
All right.
My goodness!. Are you hurt?
What should I do?
Wake up. Wake up.
What should I do? There is only grass around here, no medicinal herbs.
So cold.
What should I do?
Are you awake?
What are you doing?
You're hurt. I'm trying to help you.
There's poison.
What's your name?
I'm...
I'm Na Sheng. I'm from the Central Plains.
Na Sheng, please help me with something.
Please take this necklace to Aunt Ru at the Ruyi Gambling House in Taoyuan Province.
Tell her I failed my mission and was killed in action.
No, you are not dead yet. Don't rush to conclusions.
I brought some medicinal herbs from the Central Plains. There is still hope.
Don't waste your time.
The troops that are after me will surely come. I don't want to implicate you.
No, just wait a moment.
That's right, I have a snow poppy. This precious snow poppy must be able to save your life.
- Let's go.
- Where are we going?
To save your life.
Your Highness, why didn't Na Sheng protect herself with the Heavenly Ring
when she was in danger?
I don't know either. The Heavenly ring has clearly already recognized her as its master.
I will go to Taoyuan Province to bring Na Sheng back.
Before we find Senior Brother, I will protect her.
A'Ying, it's too dangerous for you to go alone.
Have Hong Yuan and Lan Xia go with you.
Your Highness, I often wandered the land over the years. I know how to avoid the sun.
Besides, it'll be dark soon.
But you were injured by the sunlight recently and haven't recovered yet.
What? Do you no longer listen to me?
Your Highness, are you afraid
I'll run into Su Mo on this trip?
I'll lose face if you expose me like this.
But all I care about now
is letting the people of Kongsang see the sun again.
I will not get involved with Su Mo anymore.
Very well, since you've said that.
However, you must be very careful on this trip.
So good looking.
If you weren't that good-looking, I wouldn't have wasted the snow poppy.
Are you awake?
This snow poppy can really save lives. He didn't trick me.
[Yan Xi - Quanxian Commissioner of the Left]
Did you use the snow poppy to save me?
Yes. You didn't expect I would have a snow poppy, right?
I'm surprised that those people who took the fairy grass didn't discover you.
Could it be that you really do have a spirit in you and hid yourself?
Na Sheng,
you're from the Central Plains so you might not know.
The snow poppy is Yunhuang's treasure and is priceless.
I know that. Someone told me that.
Yet you still used it to save a stranger's life?
It'll be extremely difficult for me to find another one to repay you.
It's fine, you are more valuable.
What?
I-I meant you don't have to return a snow poppy to me.
You can give yourself to me. That's fine, too.
W-What's wrong?
Us merpeople won't be slaves to anyone.
No, no! You've misunderstood.
That's not what I meant.
I wasn't asking you to be my slave. I want you to be my...
Wait! Did you just say merpeople?
My goodness. I thought that was only a legend.
According to the legend, there is a kind of fish...
No, no. A kind of people, people...
No, a type of fish. No, no. A type of people
who can sing and weave. The tears they shed become pearls.
Looking at you, aside from being a bit more good-looking than me,
there's not much difference between us.
Are those gills?
Wow, so interesting!
Stay still, don't move. I won't touch you anymore.
Although I used the snow poppy to stop the bleeding,
your wounds are still healing.
If your wound opens again, we won't have enough herbs.
Miss Na Sheng,
thank you.
If you want to cry, then just let it out.
It won't be as painful if you let it out.
You must be hoping that if I shed tears,
you can get pearls.
You can tell?
I see bloodstains.
The Quanxian Commissioner of the Left must have come here by going down stream.
Everyone, listen up. Starting from here,
search along the stream until we reach the border of Taoyuan Province.
Do not miss anything!
- Yes!
We must be in danger.
I have wasted too much time. I need to return to Taoyuan Province right away.
Miss Na Sheng, we'll part ways here. One day, I will surely repay you for saving my life.
No, no. There's no need to part ways.
You might not believe me, but I'm heading to Taoyuan Province as well.
You will run into a lot of danger if you travel with me.
It seems you only know how to say you'll repay me.
Yunhuang is big. Once we've parted ways, how will you find me to repay my favor?
You are not sincere at all.
Fine.
Notify Gao Shunzhao, telling him to send troops from Taoyuan Province to assist us.
Yes.
Bastard.
What are you doing?
I'm carving a sign unique to Quanxian.
My comrades will then know that I have been here and use this to find me.
[Taoyuan Province]
Hold on for a little longer.
Stop right there!
D-Don't capture me. Don't capture me.
Please don't capture me! Don't capture me.
Don't capture me! Don't capture me!
[Ending OST: Wanting to Return by Zhou Shen]
♫ Among the frosty clouds is the cold moon ♫
♫ A strange light in the night ♫
♫ In the dream, there is longing and fear ♫
♫ The layers of waves build up ♫
♫ Repeating the promise ♫
♫ Yet they disappear in the end ♫
♫ We've met several times ♫
♫ Yet it is hard to mention our fated relationship from the past ♫
♫ Sighing over the past is as frivolous as smoke ♫
♫ Split open the cocoon in my heart ♫
♫ You live in there ♫
♫ and have never been discovered by anyone ♫
♫ Ask time to borrow a chapter ♫
♫ The unforgettable memories ♫
♫ have disappeared, disappeared ♫
♫ I once thought there was a deep bond ♫
♫ Using ten fingers to painstakingly ♫
♫ play the ancient chords ♫
♫ In exchange for only a moment of your smile ♫
♫ Use a lifetime to love only one person ♫
♫ How do you calculate the debt between each other? ♫
♫ Yet unwilling, unwilling ♫
♫ to make an exchange for a promise and apology ♫
♫ Our next lives are too far away ♫
♫ I would rather turn into ash and be lost in a reverie ♫
♫ When I want to return,
it will be time for my dream to come true ♫