[Mirror: A Tale of Twin Cities]
[Episode 5]
Why did you leave the pagoda? Did anyone notice?
Why didn't you say goodbye? Why did you keep my sachet?
No one saw me leave the pagoda.
What about you? Are you leaving?
That's good.
I wish you happiness. May all our wishes come true.
Can you...
not return to the Jing Pagoda?
I...
If...
If you don't become the crown princess
and just be A'Lin, what would happen?
There!
- There! After them!
- Let's go.
Don't run! Stop right there!
Stop right there!
They disappeared.
- Search carefully!
- Yes!
Let's look up ahead.
♫ Listen ♫
♫ Using up all my fortune just to touch you ♫
♫ Even crying sounds so beautiful ♫
Let's go.
♫ Listening to the soft whisper of the rain from that day ♫
♫ That is the sound of my heart, so please listen ♫
♫ Because when it becomes sunny ♫
♫ I will leave quietly ♫
I can't go back.
That's right.
You can't go back.
I'm giving this to you, as a keepsake.
♫ We've met several times ♫
Must... you go back?
♫ Sighing over the past that's as frivolous as smoke ♫
♫ Split open the cocoon in my heart ♫
♫ You live in there ♫
Since that's the case...
♫ and have never been discovered by anyone ♫
...in regards to everything else...
♫ Ask time to borrow a chapter ♫
♫ The unforgettable memories ♫
...just forget all of it.
♫ I once thought there was a deep bond ♫
♫ Using ten fingers to painstakingly ♫
♫ play the ancient chords ♫
♫ In exchange for only a moment of your smile ♫
♫ Use a lifetime to love only one person ♫
♫ How do you calculate the debt between each other? ♫
♫ Yet unwilling, unwilling ♫
♫ to make an exchange for a promise and apology ♫
♫ Our next lives are too far away ♫
♫ I would rather turn into ash and be lost in a reverie ♫
♫ When I want to return,
it will be time for my dream to come true ♫
All right.
We must forget.
Your seal...
The crown princess' seal
has been broken!
♫ Using ten fingers to painstakingly ♫
♫ play the ancient chords ♫
Come with me.
I can't.
I have to go back.
Over there! Capture them!
Hurry and leave.
Hurry and leave!
Go! Hurry and leave.
No.
If I'm to leave, we must leave together. You must leave with me.
♫ Our next lives are too far away ♫
Princess!
Let them go. I'll return with you.
Why isn't Su Mo back yet? Do you know where he went?
It seems that he went back to the Jing Pagoda.
Why did he return to the Jing Pagoda again?
Perhaps he's worried about that Princess Bai.
Aunt Ru, take the other clan people back with you to the Great Camp of Jing Lake,
I'll go and make inquiries to find him.
- Then you must be extra careful.
- All right.
What exactly do you want to do to Bai Ying?
What else would happen to an impure crown princess?
Stop!
If you don't want to die, then help her.
Threatening me? Going to kill me?
You can try.
I only wish that she will live.
However, I only want her to die.
If she dies, you won't be able to stay alive either.
Will you help or not?
Unexpected, right? You're very surprised, right?
How is that possible?
Su Mo, in this world
there are people who can break your blood pact.
I didn't do anything outside of the ordinary.
Why would this happen?
I wonder
how Su Mo is doing right now.
Is he okay?
Your Majesty, the crown princess' seal
has been broken.
The crown princess is no longer pure.
Prince Bai, why don't you ask your precious daughter
who broke her seal?
Like mother, like daughter.
Have you forgotten that her mother abandoned you both
to elope with a Cangliu person?
What kind of person was my mother?
She was the bravest and kindest person I've ever met.
- Shut your mouth.
- She's the most responsible woman.
- Don't pay attention to him.
- Tell the truth.
- She was also the best mother in the world.
I'm afraid the crown princess doesn't dare tell the truth.
Not only was her seal broken, she even went down the pagoda without permission.
When she was caught, she was in the midst of planning to elope with a man!
Her crime deserves the death penalty, Your Majesty.
Who dares?
Prince Bai!
If there's no one to inherit the power of Earth,
you're also guilty of not disciplining her strictly.
- Men! Arrest Prince Bai!
- You!
Stop!
The defensive line has fallen and you haven't supplied any army provisions.
Ye City's soldiers are invincible!
What are all of you doing!
You cut off the army provisions for Ye City's garrisons.
You even burned all the remaining army provisions. I'll settle that with you later.
The priority is to defend Ye City.
High Priest, I don't need to tell you what to do, right?
His Majesty hopes that the powers of Heaven and Earth come together soon to protect Kongsang.
However, the crown princess's seal has already been broken.
This is the future queen of Kongsang. What are you trying to do?
The crown princess undertook the heavy responsibility of inheriting the power of Earth.
If the crown prince insists on marrying her
and she's unable to inherit the power of Earth, bringing bad luck to Kongsang,
- will you be able to bear the consequences?
- You!
The fate of Kongsang is critical.
Your Royal Highness.
The fate of Kongsang is absolutely not a trifling matter.
If Princess Bai Ying can't inherit the power of Earth,
how will you explain it to the people of Kongsang?
If she can't inherit the power of Earth,
my Bai Clan shall bear that consequences!
Your Majesty, please make the final decision.
During the grand wedding,
if Princess Bai Ying is unable to inherit the power of Earth,
then the whole Bai Clan shall be executed.
This has been decided.
Prince Bai and Prince Qing, immediately mobilize troops to support Ye City.
Royal Father.
Royal Father, there must be a hidden scheme behind this.
Bring Su Mo here.
This is the innocence you claim?
Outside the Jing Pagoda, the crown princess was about to elope with this person.
They were caught in the act!
Elope?
In the pagoda, your precious daughter couldn't stand the loneliness
- and had relations with this man so the seal broke.
- Shut your mouth!
I haven't transformed so how could I have seduced the crown princess?
This was all planned by you!
You forced me to enter the Jing Pagoda
to break Her Highness' seal.
Since the beginning, Her Highness has treated me the same as others.
There were never any deviant behaviors.
You're quite good at making up stories.
Continue. Let's see who would believe you.
I haven't made anything up!
If you, Prince Qing, hadn't assisted me,
how could I have possibly entered the Jing Pagoda?
Turns out it was you, you despicable evildoer!
Cangliu's great army is pushing at our borders, yet you're up to such trickery.
You're the one who's ruining the fate of Kongsang!
Later on, I will surely report this to His Majesty.
They sure are singing the same tune.
From what I see, this person was sent by Prince Bai to frame me.
Guards!
Drag this merperson out to be beheaded!
Wait!
Prince Qing, are you trying to kill him to silence him?
This person tainted the crown princess' purity.
Yet the crown prince wants to help him?
So benevolent.
All right.
Then I'll wait for the day you and the crown princess get married.
Let's see how you two will inherit the power of Earth.
All of this was arranged by Prince Qing?
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Before coming to the pagoda, did you know it would be me?
No, I didn't.
Su Mo,
we shouldn't have met.
Can I still inherit the power of Earth even though the seal has been broken?
There's no precedent for this.
I dare not make any assertions.
Everyone thinks that the seal seals the physical body.
In actuality, it seals the crown princess' heart.
If the crown princess sincerely falls in love with someone,
the seal will break.
Now that my seal is broken,
we don't know if I can inherit the power of Earth.
[Ye City]
Cangliu is striking.
There cannot be any mistake in joining the powers of Heaven and Earth.
The seal has been broken. Immediately attack the city.
Live and die with Ye City!
- Live and die with Ye City!
Only if I die,
can other women in my Bai family
inherit the power of Earth.
Su Mo, I'm to blame for everything.
You're not at fault.
No!
♫ When I want to return, it will be time for my dream to come true ♫
Bai Ying!
Su Mo.
Remember to forget.
You must forget.
♫ Ask time to borrow a chapter ♫
♫ The unforgettable memories ♫
Even if you die, you won't be able to see Bai Ying.
If every day you're alive,
you can be tortured by your pain,
then that's the greatest punishment for you!
I'm going to exile you from Tianque, so that for the rest of your life,
you can suffer the pain of losing Bai Ying.
In any case, she asked that of me
so I must keep my promise, isn't that right?
In addition, High Priest, relay the order
to spread the word that the crown princess was originally a goddess of Heaven
who came to the mortal world.
She cannot marry a mortal,
so during the grand wedding,
another goddess came to take her back.
Crown Prince,
why would you spend so much effort to protect her?
Aren't I doing this to protect the dignity of the Kongsang royal family
and the reputation of the Bai family?
Enough, High Priest. Just do as I say.
The Cangliu army
is about to attack Jing City's city walls.
I'm going to take soldiers into battle and
live or die with Kongsang.
Hurry, catch up.
Hurry! Hurry!
Keep up! Hurry!
Prince Qing has sent orders, kill them all!
[Kongsang - Ye City]
Remember to forget.
♫ Until the very last moment ♫
♫ The world's most precious tears ♫
♫ Cool my cheeks ♫
♫ Yet I cannot bear to wipe them away ♫
♫ Somehow, this intoxicated me is silently worried ♫
♫ I once walked over waves to borrow a bit of starlight ♫
♫ Yet, no matter what I do, I cannot see you clearly ♫
♫ I thought that closing my eyes would make my heart clear ♫
♫ Yet I'm just lost in a reverie ♫
♫ All beginnings comes at the expense of having endings ♫
♫ However, love makes even breathing so difficult to do ♫
♫ So let love be silent ♫
♫ Help each other expand our horizons ♫
♫ All beginnings comes at the expense of having endings ♫
♫ I once walked over waves to borrow a bit of starlight ♫
♫ Yet, no matter what I do, I cannot see you clearly ♫
♫ I thought that closing my eyes would make my heart clear ♫
♫ Yet I'm just lost in reverie ♫
♫ All beginnings comes at the expense of having endings ♫
♫ However, love makes even breathing so difficult to do ♫
♫ So let love be silent ♫
♫ Help each other expand our horizons ♫
In what seems like a moment, a hundred years have passed.
Yunhuang, even though it's said to be thousands of years old,
[Yunfu City]
but actually, it changed to a new era a long time ago.
[Goddess Huijia - Goddess in Yunfu City]
Goddess, I didn't think that after all the battles,
Kongsang would be defeated and Cangliu would rise.
Goddess, I've recorded all the things that have happened in Yunhuang in the past hundred years.
Cangliu is good in battles and war,
the people of Yunhuang are suffering terribly.
This kind of life... when will it end?
Yunfu cannot interfere with mortal lives.
But are we really going to watch these mortals suffer?
The mortal world should be decided by the mortals.
We also have to believe they can change their own fates with their own powers.
Although Cangliu has replaced Kongsang,
they still possess the seeds of hope.
Are you talking about the people in Wuse City who can't see the daylight?'
Not only those people,
but also the person who's returning from traveling the world.
[One hundred years later]
[Tianque Snow Mountain]
Goddess in Heaven, please tell me this person's past, present, and future.
Please write down your prophecy on the ground.
Tell me this person's past, present, and future.
I'm done.
Hurry, go take a look and see if the answer you seek is on the ground.
I can't read it just like how I cannot read my own fortune.
Hurry and take a look. After you're done, I'll wipe it away.
Every beginning starts with an end.
The only way to fight the void
is through creation and protection.
- Hold onto it.
- Thank you
Little girl, this was all thanks to your food.
Now everyone can have a meal.
You're welcome.
You cooked it so we can enjoy it together.
- That's right.
- After we get over this snow mountain, we should be at Tianque. Right?
Yes, we're almost there.
I'm afraid that it won't be that easy to get to Yunhuang.
- Why?
- Look at us and you can tell.
Compared to when we left the Central Plains, half of the people are already gone.
If we want to get to Yunhuang, who knows how many will make it there alive.
We couldn't find anywhere to make money in the Central Plains.
If we stayed there, we'd still be poor. We might as well go to Yunhuang.
In the legends, Yunhuang is peaceful and beautiful.
When we get there, we can live better.
Isn't that right?
Hurry, eat some food. We'll be going over the mountain soon.
Otherwise, you won't have any energy.
Here. The winds are so intense, you'll catch a cold.
Eat it while it is still hot, hurry.
Hurry, eat it. Here.
Why are your hands so cold?
Hurry, eat some food; otherwise, you really will catch a cold.
You aren't eating?
You...
Strange.
Does he only need heat and not to eat food?
After crossing over this snow mountain, it will be Yunhuang. We should be really close.
Don't get excited too soon.
Do you know how many corpses are buried on that mountain?
But a lot of people survived as well.
I want to be one of them.
In the future, I will tell my children and grandchildren about how I went through such dangers.
- What's wrong?
- Elder.
Elder, are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- Just hold on a bit longer. Over that mountain should be Yunhuang.
Thank you.
[Snow Poppy]
What flower is that?
- Snow poppy!
- It's quite pretty.
- Get out of my way!
- It's mine.
- You...
- Mine.
- Mine!
I found it first. Don't you know first come, first serve?
Why did they push me?
This isn't good. Avalanche!
- It's mine!
- Out of my way!
- Quickly, go.
- Go!
Avalanche! Stop fighting over it!
You'll die, hurry and run!
Stop fighting!
Stop fighting! Quick—
[Jing Pagoda - Heavenly Temple]
There's a strange change in the Greedy Wolf Star.
[Zhi Zhe - Cangliu Hierarch]
It's that person.
He's returned.
This avalanche really comes fast and goes fast.
Where are the other people? What happened to everyone?
A greedy heart will cause them to leave their bones here.
That's the legendary Jing Pagoda of Yunhuang, isn't it?
I heard elders in my village say that it's about 64,000 feet tall.
(T/N: Chinese feet, one Chinese foot = 1/3 meter)
It was built by Kongsang's Heavenly King.
But... it's so tall.
How hard would it be to climb it?
The legends say that the taller Jing Pagoda is,
the more likely the prayers of the High Priest and ministers will be heard.
- I also heard that...
- Laughable.
Who can hear whose prayers?
It's a legend.
Hey, Brother Ice Cube!
Brother Ice Cube, where are you going?
You must be really powerful, right?
I heard the village elders say that some people have divine powers and are very powerful.
You have divine powers, right? Take me there.
Then, can I give you some of my fairy grass?
Take me there. I promise that I won't talk to you and I won't annoy you.
Yunhuang is a mythical place. There are never any battles there, I must go.
There's no such place like that in the world.
I don't believe it. I'll only know once I see it for myself.
Aren't you going as well? We can go together.
I... I'll just follow you from afar.
There. In between the mountains. Once you get past Tianque.
If you can get down the mountain alive
and go west along the stream,
when you see a place where people are living, that's Taoyuan province.
That's Yunhuang.
Taoyuan Province.
It sounds like a great place, just by the name!
You must get down the mountain before it gets dark.
Hey, Brother Ice Cube! Brother Ice Cube, what is your name?
Su Mo.
Su Mo？
There's no precedent for this.
I dare not make any assertions.
Everyone thinks that the seal seals the physical body.
In actuality, it seals the crown princess' heart.
If the crown princess sincerely falls in love with someone,
the seal will break.
[Bai Ying - Reigning Princess Bai of Kongsang]
One hundred years ago, when I fell off the pagoda,
I was rescued by the Earth Ring.
Prince Zhen Lan fought to the death against Cangliu alone.
By the time I woke from the Still Meditation and rushed to the battlefield,
Prince Zhen Lan's power of Heaven
had been sealed by a mysterious Cangliu person.
There was no trace of it anywhere.
Maybe... this is my fate.
[Earth Ring]
After Zhen Lan fell into a deep sleep, in order to protect the Kongsang people,
the six princes sacrificed half of their spiritual powers to open up Wuse City.
[Kongsang - Wuse City]
Never again can we walk in daylight.
[Zhen Lan - Crown Prince of Kongsang]
Your Highness, you've already slept for a hundred years.
In this hundred years, I've gone across the whole of Yunhuang.
But I still haven't found the Heavenly Ring.
Or the sealed power of Heaven.
But I've told you all about Yunhuang's land and culture.
This time, I went to Banbu City in Kangping Province.
Banbu City is a desert city. The houses there are made of rocks.
Although I went at night,
the sand there was warm at night.
That's the feeling of sunlight.
Are you done with today's news?
I told him about Banbu City.
The High Priest told us to talk to His Highness more,
saying that he might be able to hear our calls.
But it's already been a hundred years. There hasn't been any movement whatsoever.
His Highness will wake up one day.
A'Ying, it's been a hundred years already.
[Hong Yuan - Reiging Princess Chi of Kongsang]
can you still not forget that person?
It's been a hundred years. What I needed to forget, is long forgotten.
What you should've forgotten? All these years, you've gone all over Yunhuang.
Is it really to find the Heavenly Ring
and the sealed power of Heaven?
A hundred years ago, he left Tianque Mountain.
In these hundred years, how many times have you gone there?
What are you waiting for?
Right now, I only want to find the Heavenly Ring,
undo the seal on His Highness, and find the power of Heaven.
And let the hundred thousand citizens of Kongsang see the daylight once more.
We'll definitely accomplish this.
High Priest, why have you called me here so urgently?
A'Ying, there's a change in the Greedy Wolf Star.
A huge misfortune will fall upon the world soon.
The invader will enter through Tianque into Yunhuang.
I fear it will bring turmoil to all of Yunhuang.
Turmoil to all of Yunhuang?
I wonder if it's good or bad.
But this person will definitely break the situation we're in now.
Maybe we'll have an opportunity to see the sun again.
That's right. But we need to stay ahead of Cangliu
and find this person who can change Yunhuang.
Cangliu won't easily let them go.
In that case, after dark
I'll go to Tianque and find this invader.
Maybe I can help them avoid the crisis.
Reigning Princess, please be safe.
No matter who it is, I hope this person
can bring hope to Kongsang and Yunhuang.
May I ask...
Wanting to Return by Zhou Shen
♫ Among the frosty clouds is the cold moon ♫
♫ A strange light in the night ♫
♫ In the dream, there is longing and fear ♫
♫ The layers of waves build up ♫
♫ Repeating the promise ♫
♫ Yet they disappear in the end ♫
♫ We've met several times ♫
♫ Yet it is hard to mention our fated relationship from the past ♫
♫ Sighing over the past is as frivolous as smoke ♫
♫ Split open the cocoon in my heart ♫
♫ You live in there ♫
♫ and have never been discovered by anyone ♫
♫ Ask time to borrow a chapter ♫
♫ The unforgettable memories ♫
♫ have disappeared, disappeared ♫
♫ I once thought there was a deep bond ♫
♫ Using ten fingers to painstakingly ♫
♫ play the ancient chords ♫
♫ In exchange for only a moment of your smile ♫
♫ Use a lifetime to love only one person ♫
♫ How do you calculate the debt between each other? ♫
♫ Yet unwilling, unwilling ♫
♫ to make an exchange for a promise and apology ♫
♫ Our next lives are too far away ♫
♫ I would rather turn into ash and be lost in a reverie ♫
♫ When I want to return,
it will be time for my dream to come true ♫