[Mirror: A Tale of Twin Cities]
[Episode 14]
Kongsang is willing to help us unlock the dragon deity's seal.
To us, it's really all that we can wish for.
Their proposal to collaborate is not a bad idea, but—
Aunt Ru, there's no harm in saying what you think.
The grievances between the Kongsang and Quanxian tribes for the past several thousand years,
how can they be eliminated so easily?
You haven't agreed to it and have come to discuss it with me.
I guess that your thoughts are similar to mine, right?
Ning Liang and the others' resentment against the Kongsang
has exceeded my expectation.
For the past few years, Kongsang's treatment towards our Quanxian people
has not fostered resentment. Right?
Now our common enemy is Cangliu.
Young Master, do you want to accept Crown Prince Zhen Lan's offer?
The collaboration that I want
isn't to exchange one seal for another.
Then, what?
Brother Ice Cube. Brother Ice Cube.
Can you tell me how to help the Quanxian Tribe return to the Biluo Sea?
It's none of your business.
Is there anything I can help with? Tell me. I'll go do it.
The matters of our Quanxian Tribe, do not need other people's help.
I'm serious. I sincerely want to help you.
No. It's the whole Quanxian Tribe.
As long as I can do it, I'm willing to do anything—
You're a little girl from the Central Plains.
What can you do?
Since it chose me, that means I'm a little different from ordinary people. Right?
After all, I have the power to defeat Cangliu's Wind Falcons.
You're just an accessory holder.
That's the power of the heavenly ring, not yours.
But you need me, in order to use the power of the heavenly ring.
When Cangliu wanted to set the city on fire, it was me.
I was the one who unleashed the divine power of the heavenly ring.
I even defeated a Wind Falcon.
Don't always think I'm messing around.
Although my power is small, you can't ignore my good intentions.
You've done so much, it's all for Yan Xi. Right?
N-Not entirely.
Miss Na Sheng,
we're about to leave.
Go bid a proper farewell to Yan Xi.
What?
Sister Bai Ying! Sister Bai Ying!
Na Sheng, what's wrong?
Su Mo wants to leave with Yan Xi now, and he won't let me go with them.
Na Sheng, you're wearing the Heavenly Ring. Of course, you should come with us.
A'Ying and His Highness went to Taoyuan Province in order to get you.
I know.
Since I'm wearing the Heavenly Ring, I'll definitely complete the mission.
But if I go with Yan Xi, I'll delay your matters.
If I go with you, I won't be able to see Yan Xi ever again.
My mind is not very smart.
Brother Crown Prince, do you have any way that I can satisfy both sides?
Help me think of a way.
There is a way.
But whether it'll succeed or not, I can't say.
Who says you can't say? I'll go scold the person!
Why must the Kongsang people and Merpeople be separated?
What reasoning is there for that?
I-I know that with just the few of you, we might not be able to break the seals.
Su Mo is bringing along his tribe people, which will be even more dangerous, too.
Yan Xi. Yan Xi.
Also, since all of you knew each other from before,
why can't you all fight Cangliu together?
They're so bad!
Younger Sister Na Sheng,
there are some matters between Kongsang and Quanxian that you do not know of.
But I know Brother Ice Cube!
Although he appears cold all the time,
he saved us all in Taoyuan Province.
In my heart, I know he's a good person. Can you all not hate him?
Na Sheng, we don't hate him.
- Then, come with me to go see Brother Ice Cube, Sister Bai Ying.
- Na Sheng.
- A'Ying.
- Hong Yuan.
The Heavenly Ring chose Na Sheng for its own reason.
Young Master, no matter what you decide,
I'll support you.
You are Quanxian's hope.
I certainly won't disappoint everyone.
The elders are eagerly waiting for you to return to the great camp.
About sending spies to inquire for news,
you must do that first once you return to Taoyuan Province.
Although our people are all over the place, we are not connected.
After we obtain the information, it will be more convenient to carry out matters.
Yes, Young Master.
I'll definitely get it done.
The danger from the battle in Taoyuan Province hasn't subsided.
If you return alone,
you should be extra cautious.
Young Master, take care. I'll take my leave now.
Hurry.
I'm looking for Su Mo. We want to go fight Cangliu together.
Young Master needs to rest now. He's not—
It's fine.
Young Master.
Aunt Ru, be careful on your way there.
Yes.
Brother Ice Cube, I have lots of important things to talk about with you.
You can't just leave like this.
If you just leave like this, we'll never see each other again.
If we don't see each other again, there will be many, many problems.
Also, it'll be very dangerous to break that seal. Anyway, we need you.
- Brother Ice Cube—
- Na Sheng.
What's wrong, Sister Bai Ying?
Let me chat with Su Mo alone.
Okay, okay. It's better if you speak to him. That'll be better.
Brother Ice Cube only listens to you.
Don't say nonsense.
Let's talk inside.
Sister Bai Ying, you must convince him.
The sun is so bright today. Why are you out again?
You two spoke already?
About what?
The collaboration between Kongsang and Quanxian.
He's probably told you that I still haven't agreed to it.
If you don't collaborate with Kongsang,
how do you plan on bringing Quanxian back to the Biluo Sea
and breaking the seal in the Entrapped Dragon Abyss?
You will encounter various difficulties along the way. Then you—
Are you concerned about me?
When we were in the hidden chamber,
did you have a backlash?
In order to take Quanxian back to the Biluo Sea,
what exact magic did you cultivate?
What exactly did you experience?
You still care about me.
Right?
♫ In the dream, there is longing and fear ♫
I care about you.
I also care about the 100,000 sleeping people of Kongsang.
I also hope Quanxian can return to the Biluo Sea.
You still don't understand.
What I want to know...
is your truest thoughts.
I want Wuse City to open.
I want the 100,000 people of Kongsang to wake up.
I hope Quanxian can return to the Biluo Sea.
Those are my thoughts.
Can't we go back to how it was before?
We can't go back.
We can't...
go back to the past.
Then let's not go back to the past.
How about a future with just you and me?
Su Mo,
don't say anymore.
♫ Use a lifetime to love only one person ♫
♫ How do you calculate the debt between each other? ♫
I'm very happy to have met you again.
But between us,
it's impossible.
♫ When I want to return, it will be time for my dream to come true ♫
I understand.
Cangliu soldiers are powerful.
On top of that, there are the Wind Falcons.
Kongsang and Quanxian collaborating
will indeed lead to a better chance of winning.
But the grudge from a century ago,
even with an agreement,
we'll encounter various
betrayals and misunderstandings.
Even if that's the case,
♫ I once thought there was a deep bond ♫
do you want to collaborate?
♫ ...play the ancient chords ♫
I understand.
Everything will be as you wish.
♫ Use a lifetime to love only one person ♫
♫ How do you calculate the debt between each other? ♫
Greetings, General.
- Xiang, ready?
- Yes.
But, General, how will we find them?
[Xiang - Quanxian Merperson]
The one who possesses the heavenly ring went with the Quanxian people.
That means they must have taken a water route.
Based on the direction they left the city, look for water routes and underground rivers
outside of Taoyuan Province. We can definitely find them this way.
Yes.
I wonder how the discussion between Su Mo and A'Ying is going.
Sister Hong Yuan, do you approve of a collaboration with Quanxian, too?
Setting aside prejudices, what His Highness said makes sense.
Collaborating is indeed the most beneficial decision for us.
But Su Mo and Princess Bai...
What about Su Mo and A'Ying?
A Kongsang person and a merperson together,
in the end, would...
I'm talking nonsense, Older Sister Hong Yuan, don't take it to heart.
Yes. A hundred years have already passed.
Many things have changed.
We are the only ones who are still waiting in our original places.
We were able to wait for the crown prince's awakening.
Next, whatever we are waiting for, will arrive.
Hong Yuan... Older Sister.
A'Ying, what did he say?
He didn't reject the offer.
Really?
That's great.
He's agreed.
But he didn't fully agree.
If he didn't reject the offer, that means he's agreed to it. Let's take it that he agreed.
Then let's discuss this at length.
Everyone, go back to your rooms and rest for now.
Your Highness.
Yes, that's right.
A'Ying, go and rest now.
A'Ying, what exactly is Su Mo thinking?
Su Mo is not against a collaboration
but he's worried that if Kongsang and Quanxian collaborate, there will still be feelings of animosity.
I'm afraid such a collaboration won't last long.
Even more so, we won't unsettle Cangliu.
His apprehensions are reasonable.
Then we must let him see that
we let go of any resentments long ago.
Go and rest.
- Let me walk on my own.
- All right.
Why is Young Master looking for us?
No idea.
Before Aunt Ru left, she told us to assist Young Master.
Young Master must have his reasons for the decisions he makes.
- Could it be that Young Master...
- What?
Xiang, what are you doing?
General, the map shows an underground river in a Taoyuan village.
They must be there. Everyone, listen to my order.
Reverse direction, ready the crossbows, and advance to the underground river.
Yes!
Young Master, Aunt Ru has left for Taoyuan Province.
Did you want to see us to discuss our return to the camp?
Yan Xi's injuries have improved. We can set out anytime.
Young Master, my injuries have improved.
I called you here to discuss some other matters.
I wonder what urgent matters you have.
My humble opinion is that our priority should be returning to camp as soon as possible.
- Ning Liang.
- Young Master, please forgive us.
Ning Liang is merely eager to return to camp.
The soldiers of the Quanxian camp all look forward to seeing you soon.
Naturally, we will return to the great camp.
I called you here because I want to know, in regards to breaking the Dragon Deity Seal,
defeating Cangliu, and returning to the Bilou Sea,
what different suggestions do you have?
I will follow your lead, Young Master.
The generals and soldiers of Quanxian will listen to your commands, Young Master.
What about you, Ning Liang?
I am the same as them.
If I want to collaborate with Kongsang,
what are your thoughts?
I wonder why you said this. The generals and soldiers of Quanxian have bitterly waited for a hundred years.
This outcome is not what we want to see.
What do the soldiers of Quanxian want to see?
They want to see the Emperor of the Sea lead us into battle,
break the Dragon Deity Seal, and defeat Cangliu.
How many generals and soldiers are there in Quanxian camp?
- More than 3,000.
- What weapons are there to use?
But now that you are back, everything will be different.
You are our hope.
Even though Young Master has divine powers, it'll still be hard to resist tens to hundreds of Wind Falcons attacking together.
In terms of military power, Quanxian indeed cannot match Cangliu.
The priority now is to break the Dragon Deity Seal in order to protect Quanxian with the power of
the dragon deity.
If we want to break the Dragon Deity Seal, we need to go to Jiuyu Mountain
to retrieve the Splitting Sword and cut off the chains trapping the dragon.
Only Kongsang people may enter Jiuyi Mountain.
If we have help from the Kongsang people, it may be easier.
Why would the Kongsang people help us?
What if they do?
Young Master, they will only use us,
just like what Prince Qing did a hundred years ago.
They need our help to obtain the Six Directions Seal in the Ghost and Deity Abyss.
- As expected.
- Even so, this is beneficial to us.
You want to collaborate with Kongsang?
I just think this is a way.
This is a way...
but it's not the best.
Of course, it's not a good idea to collaborate with Kongsang.
Trading a seal for another seal,
this is called making a deal.
The best kind of collaboration is to form an alliance with Kongsang.
- Alliance?
- An alliance with Kongsang?
Based on the current strengths of Quanxian and Kongsang,
neither one, fighting alone, is a match for Cangliu.
Only an alliance to gain more power will give us a chance to defeat Cangliu
and return peace to Yunhuang.
But how do you form an alliance with resentments towards each other at heart?
That's why I called you here to discuss this.
Even if we don't mention the grievances from a century ago,
won't the people of Kongsang bring it up?
Go take a look.
Listen to my order. Strike the barrier. Release the arrows.
- What's going on?
- It must be Cangliu troops attacking the barrier.
How long can this barrier last?
If they're using the Wind Falcons to attack, it won't last for long.
This won't do. We have insufficient armed forces, and there are some who are injured.
I fear we can't resist them.
Notify the soldiers of Quanxian to use the water route to evacuate.
- Yes.
We can use the water route, but what will you do?
Us?
We can only fight to the death.
Look! The barrier is cracking.
Everyone, follow me.
Su Mo, Cangliu is menacingly bearing down on us.
- You all are weak against fire so leave first.
- Hurry and leave!
You can't see sunlight so you won't be able to hang on for long either.
Before, you said Kongsang and Quanxian going against Cangliu together will result in a better chance of winning.
Why not use this battle as an example
and see what our odds of winning are?
I'll protect Na Sheng and His Highness.
Su Mo, no matter what, you must protect Na Sheng and His Highness.
No, we can't leave you here.
- Your Highness, leave now.
- No.
- Leave now.
- Leave with His Highness now.
- A'Ying!
This way.
General, they seemed to have escaped.
Don't worry. They won't be able to escape.
I have placed barriers over all the water routes in Taoyuan Province.
- What's wrong?
- There's a barrier here. It must have been placed by the Cangliu people.
Let's go.
- What's going on?
- This barrier is specifically designed for merpeople.
What do you mean?
- This is Kongsang's spell.
- Kongsang?
If they can't get in from here,
why don't we go back to chase the Cangliu people away with Sister Bai Ying?
We have you and the Heavenly Ring in my hands. We might be able to.
Those below, listen. If you continue to not disarm and surrender,
I will burn down the entire mountain.
I found a way to break the barrier,
but I don't have sufficient powers yet. I fear it'll be hard for me to do it.
Su Mo, can you share some of your powers with me?
No, Young Master! If you supply your magic power to him,
- what if—
- As I already said, our current common enemy is Cangliu.
I won't treat the lives of my tribe as child's play.
You also won't betray the 100,000 people of your Kongsang.
- Give it a try.
- Thank you.
Na Sheng, come here.
- Me?
- Come here!
Don't move.
The barrier has been broken.
- What's going on?
- Be careful.
Be careful.
- Go on.
- Let's go.
Go on.
But I can't swim. Won't I drown if I go in?
Come here.
It's done.
Hurry and go.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going to retrieve them.
You...
- Young Master.
- Yan Xi, take care of them.
Yes.
- Come on.
- No, Su Mo.
Let's go.
Withdraw! Withdraw!
Xiang!
Didn't you already leave?
I won't leave you behind.
Everyone, follow me.
Let's quickly leave.
Lord Zhi Zhe.
This game is getting more interesting.
Look, there's no water.
Yan Xi, the Water Avoidance spell Su Mo cast on me was quite amazing.
Older Brother Crown Prince, is this Jing Lake?
Do you really live down there?
Yes. This is Jing Lake.
For thousands of miles, boats cannot pass through and birds will sink if they fly over it.
Then if we hide in there, we won't be afraid of the Cangliu people coming.
That is how it works. However, you are not a Kongsang person,
so you can't enter Wuse City.
I do know a very secretive place.
If you stay there alone, I'm worried...
Na Sheng, come with me, I will protect you.
I don't want to.
You can't go to Wuse City or the Quanxian camp. You can only come with me.
Na Sheng, the view at that place is especially great.
Moreover, General Xi Jing can go hunting for wild chickens for you.
- Wild chickens are very tasty.
- Wild chickens?
Okay, okay.
Yan Xi. Yan Xi.
I will leave a mark along the way. Remember to come and look for me.
What's wrong with your hands?
It's nothing.
Wait here for me.
Your Highness.
Su Mo, I will ask you directly.
Do you have your response to a collaboration between Kongsang and Quanxian?
I decline.
Since that is the case, we shall part ways.
- A'Ying, let's go.
- Hold on.
I decline a collaboration where we use one seal to trade for another seal.
- Then you're saying...
- I hope Kongsang and Quanxian can form an alliance.
Are you saying that you're willing to not only help us obtain the seal from the Ghost and Deity Abyss,
but also obtain the other seal and go against Cangliu together?
That's right.
Fine. Kongsong will not break our promise.
We will surely help you release the dragon deity.
Then the powers of the dragon deity, heavenly ring, and earth ring will unite
to destroy Cangliu together,
allowing Kongsang to see the sunlight once again
and allowing Quanxian to return to the Bilou Sea.
Let's clasp our hands as our pledge.
In the future, throw three stones into the Jing Lake
and a guard will take you into our camp.
Get some good rest.
A'Ying, you go back first.
Does Your Highness still have other matters?
I still need to go settle Xi Jing and Na Sheng.
Don't worry. I'm here.
Thank you for the trouble, Your Highness.
The Twin Stars are about to rise.
Lord Zhi Zhe, what did you see?
The meeting of the Greedy Wolf Star and Bright Star.
The balance of Yunhuang is about to break.
I'm ignorant. Please explain.
Kongsang and Qianxuan are about to form an alliance.
I will inform the five masters now!
Lord Zhi Zhe?
No need...
to tell them.
Yes.
[Cabin by the Water]
This is not far from Jing Lake and is relatively hidden.
You should be safe living here.
Great General, I will leave Na Sheng in your care.
Cangliu will definitely not give us any rest.
Rest assured. Those Cangliu evildoers won't be able to deal with me.
What are you doing?
I need to see whether this place is good or not.
I'm afraid of this wild and mountainous countryside.
Whether you do your divination or not, there's just this one place.
T-Then I won't do it.
If the barrier is not strong, then I will be more afraid.
But wouldn't that be great, if I learned to suddenly become invisible or travel thousands of miles a day?
Come here.
[Book of Harmony]
Is this a divine book that only fairies of the ninth heaven can have?
- Yes.
This is really a divine book?
In here, the spells are written in
the ancient characters of Yunhuang.
If you can understand it, then you can see ghosts.
(T/N: be miraculous)
I will translate it for you.
This book is illusory.
You change it however you like with magic.
As for the contents, there are also some enlightenment spells. You can read it.
If there's anything you don't understand, ask me when I return.
If I practice a lot, would I be able to travel thousands of miles in a day and be invisible, too?
You can probably travel ten meters in a day.
Only ten meters?
Great General.
- I'm going back to Wuse City now.
- How is it like this?
Don't worry. Leave this to me.
Na Sheng, watch carefully.
Where did he go?
[Quanxian Great Camp]
Welcome back, Young Master.
We haven't seen each other in a hundred years.
Elders, please rise.
It has been tough for you for these hundred years.
It wasn't tough at all. Fortunately, in my lifetime,
[Du, Quan, Yu, Gong - Quanxian Elders]
I can witness the return of Young Master.
Whatever hardship there was, I don't remember them at all.
We have hope now!
From now on,
I will be responsible for the barrier.
Take a look.
[Names of Heroic Souls of Quanxian]
[Records of Heroic Souls]
For thousands of years, the Emperor of the Sea that we have waited for, has finally returned.
There's hope in Quanxian now.
We can finally go back to the Bilou Sea.
What will lead us back to the Bilou Sea
is the power of the dragon deity.
This is also the wish of everyone in the Quanxian army.
Countless Quanxian soldiers
willingly bled and died for that wish. We have
engraved their names on this Records of Heroic Souls
to let them personally witness
the day we return to the Bilou Sea.
Young Master, please.
Welcome back, Emperor of the Sea.
- Welcome back, Emperor of the Sea.
Rise.
Seven thousand years ago, Master Ming Huo left a divination.
A man with a mark of a dragon on his back will bring back the power of the dragon deity.
Now, we had finally awaited your return.
Then I shall hand this to you.
This is?
This is the ice crystal left by Master Ming Huo.
You can use this to summon the master
and ask her
to interpret fate and determine the future of Quanxian.
Young Master, you must take revenge for Quanxian.
We currently have little manpower and are weak.
What can we use to go against the powerful Cangliu?
That's why I want to break the dragon deity's seal.
I have already decided to form an alliance with Kongsang.
They can help us to unlock the dragon deity's seal.
We will help them to retrieve the Six Directions Seal.
Then we'll join forces to oppose Cangliu.
Young Master, you want to join forces with Kongsang?
Only a hundred years ago, we witnessed the people of Kongsang breaking their promise.
If we don't defeat Cangliu now,
it will be very hard for both Kongsang and Quanxian to regain our peaceful lives.
Do we still want to live like this, resigned to these circumstances?
How could we be willing to live like this?
- But—
- Elder Yu, I did consider the concerns you have.
But if we don't join forces now,
we will miss the best opportunity to oppose Cangliu for no reason.
To Quanxian, Kongsang, and even Yunhuang,
this alliance is a good thing.
Since Young Master has already thought this through,
we won't say any more.
I just hope when we join forces,
Young Master will make more preparations for Quanxian
so we have no regrets in the future.
Thank you, Elder Yu, for your advice.
[Quanxian Great Camp - Water Chamber]
Emperor of the Sea, you have finally shown up.
Master Huo Ming greets Emperor of the Sea.
Master? You know me?
On the eve of the destruction of Quanxian,
[Ming Huo - Quanxian Rituals Master]
I performed a divination.
The next Emperor of the Sea would appear 7,000 years later.
That would be the beginning of all your pains.
However, for you, everything begins
after the end.
[Every beginning starts with an end. The only way to fight the void is through creation and protection.]
So, Na Sheng's divination wasn't a child's game.
7,000 years ago,
my fate had already been engraved on the Wheel of Life.
Wanting to Return by Zhou Shen
♫ Among the frosty clouds is the cold moon ♫
♫ A strange light in the night ♫
♫ In the dream, there is longing and fear ♫
♫ The layers of waves build up ♫
♫ Repeating the promise ♫
♫ Yet they disappear in the end ♫
♫ We've met several times ♫
♫ Yet it is hard to mention our fated relationship from the past ♫
♫ Sighing over the past is as frivolous as smoke ♫
♫ Split open the cocoon in my heart ♫
♫ You live in there ♫
♫ and have never been discovered by anyone ♫
♫ Ask time to borrow a chapter ♫
♫ The unforgettable memories ♫
♫ have disappeared, disappeared ♫
♫ I once thought there was a deep bond ♫
♫ Using ten fingers to painstakingly ♫
♫ play the ancient chords ♫
♫ In exchange for only a moment of your smile ♫
♫ Use a lifetime to love only one person ♫
♫ How do you calculate the debt between each other? ♫
♫ Yet unwilling, unwilling ♫
♫ to make an exchange for a promise and apology ♫
♫ Our next lives are too far away ♫
♫ I would rather turn into ash and be lost in a reverie ♫
♫ When I want to return,
it will be time for my dream to come true ♫