Another new day.
How wonderful.
Time for breakfast.
I'm not hungry.
But...
Skipping breakfast is bad for you.
I know.
I'm perfectly healthy, aren't I?
Fine. Food's in the pot.
Heat it up when you're hungry.
You're heading out?
Yeah.
Uncle Cripple's crutch is broken.
Needs fixing.
Brother Fool's candy is gone too.
Grandpa An's made up a new story.
I want to go see them all.
Such drama queens.
No going out for a while.
Why?
I'm the boss.
I pay the wages.
So no skipping work.
Fine.
No going out on weekends either.
You're working overtime.
I'll pay overtime.
Is it my condition?
Has it gotten worse again?
How much longer do I have?
A long time.
Mom used to say...
everyone dies eventually.
And according to the doctors,
I shouldn't have lived this long.
So every day I'm still alive,
I'm truly grateful.
So can Brother Su Yang tell me...
how much longer I have?
I told you.
You'll keep living.
Three months.
That's plenty.
That gives me enough time
to fix Uncle Cripple's crutch,
buy candy for Brother Fool,
and hear Grandpa An's story.
Oh, right.
Sister Qiu Ge's remote needs new batteries too.
What does any of this have to do with you?
Can't you do something for yourself?
I've already done what I need to.
Doing something for others
is the last meaning of my existence.
Grandpa An's show...
if I don't go,
he won't have an audience.
Also...
I'll go buy you more medicine tomorrow.
And...
as long as I don't let you go,
you're not going to die.
Not even Death himself can take you.
Every immortal has their own Artifact.
And after long-term nurturing,
they leave their Will upon the Artifact.
Do you know what that means?
Spit it out.
It means the Artifact gets a patina.
Try saying something useful.
What, you polishing prayer beads?
What it means is,
aside from the immortals themselves,
their Artifacts
can also use their lingering Will
to seek out a suitable Blessed One.
Do you get it now?
Nope, don't get it.
Let me put it this way.
If you found Zhurong's Artifact
and absorbed the Will inside it,
your power would skyrocket.
This is huge information.
Wang Qiusheng,
you're practically my benefactor!
An Artifact can nourish those of the same origin.
Isn't that exactly what only Immortal Seeds can do?
So then, the Artifacts—
where would one find them?
I'm sure our benefactor Wang Qiusheng
is wondering the same thing.
The museum.
It's gotta be the museum.
Just think about it.
Artifacts left over from ancient times—
those are antiques.
So,
they might be kept in a museum.
If I can think of this,
our benefactor Wang Qiusheng,
who's been planning this for so long,
must have figured it out too.
He's not the indecisive type.
So tonight,
he just might
go test his luck.
Give it here.
I want a map.
I don't buy it.
No way Wang Qiusheng has only this one ancient text.
So we can find him,
shake him down for a second one,
then let him go,
and we'll get a third,
and a fourth.
He's basically a treasure-hunting rat.
Send a few of your top men
to this museum
to lie in wait
for our benefactor.
Wait, something's off.
If Liu Chengfeng was so sure he could catch me,
why would he give me a chance to escape?
He's bluffing me.
If I go to Qiushui City now,
or Chuncao City,
or even the Imperial Capital,
I can still start over.
But before I leave,
the Shanhai Scripture Vault—
if I could find an Artifact here,
even a broken one...
Call the young master.
Move.
Hello there, benefactor.
Didn't expect us to meet again
so soon.
Got any more ancient texts?
Toss me one,
and I'll still let you go.
Oh, right—
just a heads-up:
if you run out of stock,
you'll have to go find more.
One ancient text,
one life.
I'm very reasonable.
Off you go.
Hold on.
Leave the bag too.
Very good.
Bye-bye.
Well, that really wasn't hard at all.
Sure,
I lost an ancient text,
but you all overlooked
that I got an Artifact.
A museum...
...replica.
This thing...
Even this thing is a fake!
Shameless Shanhai City!
If Shanhai City won't have me,
then I'll go to the Imperial Capital!
One day,
I'll rise again!
I will...
I will personally avenge this!
Personally avenge this!
Can we talk?
Who are you?
Past-With-The-Wind.
Right.
I'm Liu from Shanhai City.
I am...
Past-With-The-Wind.
Right.
Last night I read an ancient text.
It had information about Tongtong's illness.
I've been curious for a while now.
About Tongtong's illness.
Three years ago, shouldn't it have...
Sorry.
Let me finish, all right?
According to the ancient records,
Tongtong's constitution
is called a Celestial Blight Body.
It instinctively rejects Immortal Energy,
yet is severely deficient in it.
Ultimately, it causes blood disorders.
So the only way is through external means,
forcibly injecting Immortal Energy,
to keep all the organs in her body
functioning.
But as time goes on,
her demand for the quality of Immortal Energy
will only grow higher.
So if I'm not mistaken,
up until now,
you've been using items with trace Immortal Energy
to keep Tongtong alive, right?
And now,
items of that level,
of that quality,
no longer work on her condition.
Go on.
So the perfect solution right now
would be to kill a true Immortal.
That way,
Tongtong's complications over the next few years
wouldn't get any worse.
But from the looks of it now,
that doesn't seem realistic.
Of course,
I have a second option.
Next time in front of me,
if you leave a sentence half-finished,
it'll be your windpipe I slit.
Artifact. An Artifact.
According to the ancient records,
Artifacts are treasures left behind by Immortals.
They contain the purest Immortal Energy.
So even with the passage of time,
and a bit of depletion,
using one to heal Tongtong
would still be more than enough.
Now then, let's talk
about the Artifact in your hands.
I...
Brother Su Yang is a really nice guy.
He's just joking with you.
Right.
Let me patch you up.
Just kidding.
The wound isn't serious.
Rest a couple of days and you'll be fine.
It won't leave a scar.
Thank you.
Now, where were we?
The Artifact.
Right.
Next month,
the Imperial Capital will hold a Blessed Ones Tournament.
First prize is an Artifact...
...fragment.
Even though it's just a fragment,
it still contains a Will within it.
That alone is extraordinary.
Blessed Ones Tournament.
Right.
Anything else?
Aren't you...
planning to enter?
I am entering.
Now that I know,
I'll go on my own.
I think I forgot to mention,
only the most powerful teams from each city
are eligible to compete.
I just tested it for you.
The water temperature is just right.
You must be thirsty.
Not really.
That thing you asked me to join...
Captain of whatever team...
I agree to do it.
You're not going to resign
the moment the tournament ends, are you?
No.
The first thing I'll do
is treat Tongtong's illness.
Resigning will be the second thing.
Okay, okay, okay.
Even so,
I still need to explain something to you.
In Shanhai City,
though the Liu family has some influence,
there's still the Council of Elders above us,
which creates chains of vested interests.
So,
the Council won't let me handle it all alone.
They'll definitely plant some people
they want to push forward.
Then they'll stage what looks like
a perfectly fair qualifying match.
As for the people they're pushing,
I don't know their exact strength yet.
So the only one you can rely on is yourself.
What are you doing...
Is there something else?
Stirring-Up-Trouble.
Weren't you just Past-With-The-...
Before the qualifying match begins,
I'll send someone to notify you, okay?
Have a safe trip.
Safe trip.
By the way.
Actually, my name is Liu Cheng—
Never mind, you don't care anyway.
You're going to be cured!