It's all taken care of.
Let's go.
Go.
Move.
Monkey's been buried.
Your medicine.
The upgraded version.
The medicine you give me is always so bitter.
Didn't Qiu Ge give you some candy?
Take them together.
In all of Black Street,
you're the only one who dares eat Qiu Ge's candy.
Sister Qiu Ge is really nice.
You know what?
In all of Shanhai City,
you matter the most to me.
Have a seat.
Okay.
Would you like some coffee?
Sure.
The best coffee in Qiushui City.
From Qiushui.
Go brew some.
Are you sure?
Of course.
It's just a cup of coffee.
Careful, it's hot.
Drink it slowly.
I think
you still need more experience.
Take this operation, for example.
Qiushui coffee
has always been rich and smooth.
Yours tastes a bit different
from what I usually drink.
It's a little sour.
Could it be expired?
Let's skip this topic
and talk about Black Street.
I've decided
to send you to Black Street for a while.
I believe
you'll gain a lot
from your time on Black Street.
In one month,
come back and report to me.
By then,
you'll surely be the most capable
captain in the Celestial Vanguard.
Are you confident?
I'll definitely do my best.
Good.
Then I hope on Black Street,
you'll bring out the Celestial Vanguard's—
Do you have a restroom?
A... a restroom?
I... excuse me for a moment.
What the—
A young man's heart
can surpass even the immortals,
let alone a mere Black Street.
My future
is the stars and the sea.
You're sick.
Let me introduce myself.
Xu Kai.
A big shot from Central Street.
Madman is my business partner.
Hello.
I'm fine.
But you're not.
You're sick.
I... I'm sick?
Hesitating when trouble comes,
lacking courage—
it's a sickness of the heart.
Kid,
do you know the Madman of Central Street?
Yes.
He even kicked me once.
It really hurt.
How did he kick you?
Like this.
He kicked me flying.
I didn't die, though.
Sorry about that.
You're not sick.
I have things to do.
Goodbye.
Senior,
my boss sent me to Black Street for training.
Who should I look for?
I understand.
Who's the toughest on this street?
I've got money.
Lots of money.
Who's the toughest on this street?
I've got money.
Lots of money.
Who's the toughest on this street?
What a rich mark.
I've got money.
Know Madman, Cripple, and Fool?
I do.
They're all formidable.
All of them rose to power from here.
So that would make them
your senior disciples too.
If it weren't for your rare talent,
forget ten thousand a day,
I wouldn't take you for a million.
Understood.
We're here.
Today, your first lesson from me is
force control.
Can you do it?
Probably not.
Force is easy to exert, hard to control.
The day you can
make the stone slab
crack but not shatter,
that's when you've truly begun.
Right.
I still can't control my strength,
like you do, Master,
making the cracks so clear and even.
Decent talent.
Pity, though.
Too rigid and forceful.
Take your time practicing.
Oh, right.
Don't forget to transfer the money.
Tomorrow,
give this courtyard a full cleaning.
Tempering the mind matters too.
Force control.
Mind tempering.
Such profound wisdom.
Truly Black Street's top-secret camp.
Just what kind of monster did I swindle?
That was specially made marble!
If he ever finds out I conned him,
what if he tears me to pieces too?
No.
I'm Black Street's top con artist.
Fortune favors the bold.
Is the Liu family that desperate for cash?
Thank goodness,
the ancient text on immortal spirits is still here.
Just as I thought,
the most dangerous place
is the safest place.
Setting up the liaison post here again,
even the Liu family would never guess
that two shells
would land in the same crater.
Still, within the Liu family,
I should recruit a few members.
Otherwise I'd never feel at ease.
Over here.
Here, right here.
Sorry, World's Strongest,
mind if I interrupt?
What made you think
the Liu family are all fools
who don't know how to stake out a place?
What was that you just dug up?
I...
I don't have anything.
Then just kill him.
He's of no more use.
Got it.
Wait, wait, wait!
Let me go.
The ancient text is yours.
A wise choice.
Looking forward to our next meeting.
Bye-bye.
He actually did come back.
Hey,
bring the stuff back here quickly.
Also,
the most important thing
is this:
He probably won't come back here again.
Just leave one camera.
Dismantle all the rest.
Take them to Digital Street.
Sell them to anyone who pays.
Then bring the money to my office.
You hear me?
Got it.
It's really important.
Really important.
You two, go dismantle them.
Awesome!
Next month's allowance
is sorted now.
Wang Qiusheng, oh Wang Qiusheng.
I can always count on you.
What would I do without you?
Where you going?
I'm heading out
for a little walk.
Alright.
I heard
there's cash from the scrapped cameras
that'll end up in your hands.
Remember to bring it back tomorrow.
Father.
Father,
are we short on money?
Short on money?
How could our family be short on money?
Look at our family's big company.
It's not short on cash.
So why do you keep shortchanging me?
Other people
get to drink Qiushui coffee freely.
But when it comes to me...
This guy's incredible.
We won!
What did you just say?
I said,
I just remembered.
Raise boys poor, raise girls rich.
That old man from Qiushui City
told me that very seriously.
Look at us now.
It proves he was right.
The pro agreed to add me as a friend!
I'll send you a few skins first.
So you can carry me.
Bro, you're amazing!
That old geezer is quite something too.
Dresses his own son in gold and silver,
fattens him up like a pig,
then tricks my dad into mistreating me?
What a scumbag.
Tongtong.
Do you need help?
In her current condition,
even the Rat's celestial seed
can only ease the symptoms now?
Time is running out.
Where can I find another immortal?
A true immortal.
Watch over her for me.
Why
is your celestial seed withered?
Speak!
Where on earth can I find a good celestial seed?