He's here.
Oh my god, the gorilla is here.
Finished
It's over.
Why don't I try something else?
In order to see my old mother as soon as possible,
Go for it.
Sleep with him tonight.
I
I really really like him.
What does he want?
To tell you the truth,
It's hard to disobey the imperial order.
You deserve to marry into the General's Mansion.
What a conceited man.
Since you married into the General's Mansion,
You must learn to behave yourself.
She's the wife of the general's mansion.
Take care of yourself.
I was rejected by the gorilla.
I'm pretty, right?
I want to see what is in your brain.
dang!
This is so cool.
God is so kind to me.
I can reach the peak of my life by sleeping with him.
And thank you for throwing a bottle at me.
So that I can achieve great achievement ahead of time.
today
I will forgive you.
You need to find the man you really like.
After getting married with her lover,
And return to the real world.
It's you.
Finish the task and let me go home.
This beautiful man won't waste my time travelling.
What are you doing?
You can move to another courtyard tomorrow morning.
I don't want to see your face again.
What does he mean?
According to modern terms,
It's you, Goddess Su, who was abandoned by Gao Fu Shuai.
It seems that this task is very difficult.
mom
You must wait for me.
I should have found a boyfriend.
Did you finish my mom's wish?
Nothing
With my wisdom,
And my beauty.
And my cooking skills,
I'm sure I can get this ice face.
Based on my years of experience,
I'm in the cold palace.
You can't see the ice face.
How can I complete my task?
The general said
Madam, don't go out of the yard.
Miss
Did you not serve the general well last night?
I'll take care of you.
Look at this.
Isn't that
garden
A villa.
I'm telling you,
From now on,
This is our base.
Miss, I can't understand you.
Are you possessed again?
I'm on your body.
Just follow me and see how I lead you.
And kicked Miss Second.
I slept with Ice Face.
general
Old Madam is coming.
Would you like me to prepare it?
The treatment
I want to lie down.
Remember, remember.
We must not go to corruption because of these materials.
If the old lady wants to come, let me dress up to welcome her.
This ice face.
Can't it be Nanny Bao?
Whatever.
The transfer is coming.
You must take down my mother-in-law.
I can only go back if I sleep on ice face.
Your Highness.
I want to see how Ice Face pleases me now.
Please.
If Mother hadn't come,
I'm too lazy to look at you.
When my mother was here,
Just do your duty.
What does the general mean by duty?
He won't force me, right?
When my mother was around,
You have to pretend to be in love with me.
To reassure her.
You're so overbearing and selfish.
Move your sister out when you use her.
When you're not using it, you should leave me alone.
What do you take her for?
I'm telling you,
If you want me to pretend love in front of your mother,
Unless you kneel down and beg me,
Oh, my God.
You can play back this cute little face.
Su Shen.
Please help me.
The boy's soft voice.
To my bone marrow.
Is this the feeling of being in love?
I will be your horse.
Please.
That's more like it.
Sister, think about it.
Even if you are wild inside,
And be gentle as a sheep.
Otherwise, I might not survive this episode.
OK
Is there anything else?
Also
When my mother was away,
Don't let me see your face.
Don't you want to see it?
It ticks me off
How could there be such a person?
If I slapped you, I'll slap you.
Look, give him what he can.
Calm down.
Don't be angry. It's important to protect yourself.
Not angry.
I'm not angry at all.
Brother Junyao.
Jingruo.
With my years of watching TV,
This is the opposite.
wow
You're really handsome.
Golden boy and jade girl -- immortal boy and girl in waiting of a divine house
Mother!
And made the task more difficult for me.
Well
Where's my mother-in-law?