♪Peach blossoms fall,
yesterday's trace fades away♪
♪Ahead lie storms and winds,
our fates like drifting clouds sway♪
♪Alas, I roam through what remains,
fate's grip won't set me free♪
♪If time would spare me
just one breath to stay♪
♪If you could see
the depth of my belief♪
♪Alone I enter the game,
every move made with no regret in me♪
♪Though shackles bind my soul
and chain my form♪
♪I've walked
through life and death before♪
♪I fear not fate's cruel temptations,
I've severed every cause♪
♪In this life our threads entwined,
in love and pain we crossed♪
♪But I'll keep my word
no matter the cost♪
♪Forged in stardust and flame♪
♪I rise with an unyielding frame♪
=The Princess's Gambit=
(Adapted from the novel "Peach Blossoms
Reflecting the River and Mountains")
(by Bai Lu Cheng Shuang)
=Episode 23=
Stop!
Let go of me!
I don't know you.
I'm not the one you're after.
You got the wrong person.
How unfortunate for you.
♪The flower bloomed,
knowing nothing at all♪
♪In splendor, proud and tall♪
♪The flower weeps, burdened by thoughts♪
♪With no one it can be brought♪
♪Wishes struggle through the mire♪
♪Regrets clash in hopeless fire♪
♪Still I hope she'll pick
the flower kissed by dew♪
(Thank you for being alive.)
♪I must gift the flower to another♪
♪Yet I still long for her in madness♪
♪Unafraid of judgment or sadness♪
♪Remembering the words
she spoke of flowers and skies♪
♪They were her gentle heart's reply♪
(Meng Residence)
Master, I have news.
After we got to the cremation ground,
Shen Zaiye rushed in and took her away.
That confirms it.
The woman must be Jiang Taohua.
But if she's still alive,
why has she been staying
with Prince Wuyin?
Unless...
there's bad blood between
Prince Wuyin and Shen Zaiye?
Should I look into it?
No.
The enemy of my enemy is my friend.
Let's just sit back and watch the show.
That man might be one of my enemies.
I'll get to the bottom of it.
No.
I'll just treat it as a false alarm.
Chancellor Shen,
how did you know I was in trouble?
His Majesty's attendant
said he saw you
at Prince Wuyin's Residence.
His Majesty wanted to summon you
and see you.
Luckily,
Prince Wuyin arranged for another woman
to take your place.
You really do have
eyes and ears everywhere.
Nothing seems to escape you.
I just happen to care about someone.
The physician said
you should go somewhere familiar.
It might help restore your memory.
I must stay at Prince Wuyin's
residence to find Qingtai.
I understand.
(Shen Zaiye.)
(Thank you for saving me.)
(Wedding)
(But no matter what we once had,)
(I have to go back and figure out)
(the link between)
(Empress Lv and Prince Wuyin.)
(Empress Lv really is something else.)
(Did she even manage to
bring Prince Wuyin over to her side?)
It's Jiangtao poison.
Quick, get Eunuch Ren.
He's already dead.
The only antidote is probably
in Prince Wuyin's residence.
Zhan Lu, hurry!
Yes, sir!
Hyah!
(Shunjing Residence)
I'll walk on my own.
I don't feel safe letting you go.
Prince Wuyin's been lying to you.
Going back is like walking into a trap.
If he's still lying to me,
it means one thing.
I'm still useful to him.
But if I leave with you now,
then to him,
I'm nothing but a discarded piece.
Take care.
(Jiang Taohua.)
(I swear I'll find a cure for you,)
(and help you save Changjue,)
(so you won't have to live in fear)
(and terror,)
(or always bracing yourself
for the worst.)
(I promise.)
Meng, hang in there.
The physician will be here soon.
It won't help.
I've had this ailment
since I was a child.
Only the special medicine from Beiyuan
can treat it.
Otherwise,
not even a miracle doctor
could save me.
I only ask one thing of Your Highness.
Go ahead.
After I die...
Your Highness,
please do not tell anyone.
Why not?
My younger brother, Changjue,
is at the Beiyuan military camp.
I want him
to always believe
that I am living well
here in Qi.
So the bond between you two
runs deep.
Yes.
For Changjue,
I am willing to do anything.
Take it.
(So Prince Wuyin
really has the antidote.)
(He and Empress Lv)
(really are working together.)
Your Highness,
how do you have
the antidote to Jiangtao pill?
I am the real master
behind Lan Boutique.
(Lan Boutique?)
(Lan Boutique)
(Lv)
(Whatever happened between us,)
(is not something a eunuch
should be poking into.)
(It was him.)
From now on, your life
and your brother's life
are both in your hands.
Yes, Your Highness.
I will do as you say.
In the future,
when Lan Boutique is rebuilt,
you will be very useful.
(Shen Residence)
(Chancellor, we did everything we could
to get the three ingredients.)
(We were ambushed in Beiyuan.
To avoid exposing ourselves,)
(I had to send a message by pigeon.)
(Final words from Zengtu.)
Chancellor,
our men were attacked by
Empress Lv's soldier while retreating.
To avoid getting compromised,
they took their own lives.
The families of our fallen brothers
will be supported by us.
Yes, sir.
Chancellor,
we do not have the antidote.
What about the Princess?
I will not approach her for now.
It might put her in danger.
(Jiang Taohua, don't worry.)
(Once I handle all of this,)
(I'll bring you home.)
(Serenity and Elegance)
As long as I'm here,
your meals will always be just right.
But...
I do sometimes cook
at His Highness's annex.
Enough chatter.
(I lost a day yesterday.)
(I must find Qingtai today.)
(But the question is,)
(how do I get to that annex?)
Miss Meng, time to eat.
(Got it.)
I am not eating.
We're going out.
Go out?
Where are we going?
I dreamed of a giant snake
falling from the sky last night.
I heard as a child
that it is a sign of unrest at home.
I want to visit a nearby temple
and pray for a protective charm
for Prince Wuyin
to keep his household safe.
But Lord Qingfeng said
you are not allowed to leave.
Who has more authority?
Lord Qingfeng
or Prince Wuyin?
Prince Wuyin does.
And you know full well
that Prince Wuyin believes
in karma and fate.
Heaven sent me a dream,
and you're trying to stop me.
Then, I'll go to Prince Wuyin
and tell him myself.
If this ruins everything
he has worked so hard to build,
then the consequences
will be too great
for either of us to bear.
Please, Miss Meng.
If you wish to pray at the temple,
I will go with you.
After you.
Sturdy bamboo baskets!
Built to last!
Traditional medicinal wine,
good for whatever ails you!
You two really have an eye for quality.
These are all new fabrics I just got in.
(Yunshang Fabric Store)
(A fabric store.)
(This is the place.)
Miss Meng?
Weren't we going to the temple?
Why stop by a fabric store?
You silly boy.
You really don't understand women.
What woman goes out without
picking up some rouge or powder,
or getting a new dress made?
(Yunshang Fabric Store)
Whose daughter is this?
You're absolutely radiant.
You light up my humble little shop.
Take your time, miss.
See if anything catches your eye.
Listen to me rambling...
With that fair skin and noble air,
you wouldn't settle
for anything ordinary.
Right this way.
This is Wuling brocade.
Take a look.
This is it.
Sure.
Miss, please come inside.
I need her measurements
for a new dress.
Why are you following her in?
I...
You have no sense at all.
Wait outside.
Miss.
Shopkeeper, do you have any tea here?
I have the finest Longjing.
Just give me a moment,
I'll bring some right over.
Miss, here's the tea I just brewed.
Miss?
Where did she go?
I don't know!
I'm from Prince Wuyin's residence.
If I don't find her today,
you're dead to me.
(He didn't go home.)
(He must've gone to the annex
for Prince Wuyin.)
Chancellor, a report came in.
The Princess left with a servant.
But later,
she ditched the servant
and headed for the outskirts.
Prince Wuyin has never let
Jiang Taohua leave alone.
Zhan Lu, come with me.
I lost track of Miss Meng.
Please punish me.
You're a disappointment and a failure.
Scram!
Monster! Go ahead and kill me!
(Qingtai!)
I can insult you all I want!
If I weren't tied up,
I'd kill you myself.
Slap her.
(Empress Lv.)
(What is she doing here in Qi?)
(And Prince Wuyin is with her.)
(They really are in it together.)
Sharp tongue, yet no manners.
You should've been sent
to the underworld ages ago.
You'll die the worst death!
Keep going.
(If this keeps up,)
(Qingtai will be beaten to death.)
(No.)
(I need to think of something fast.)
Oh no, there's a fire!
Someone help!
Help!
It's bad. The fire's too strong!
Report to the master!
Your Highness,
the courtyard is on fire!
The guards say
it's too intense.
It won't be put out anytime soon.
This is unusual.
It might expose us.
Kill her.
Yes.
Tell everyone to evacuate.
Make sure there's no trace.
(Qingtai!)
Jiang Taohua...
I prayed for you.
You will not die.
You cannot die.
Jiang Taohua, wake up.
Wake up.
You wicked scoundrel!
I'm from Beiyuan.
I follow who I marry.
I live with who I marry.
(So what if I'm just a concubine?)
(I don't feel wronged.)
(But in the Chancellor's garden,)
(I'm just another flower.)
(If I could stay here forever,)
(far from all the court's chaos,)
(how wonderful that'd be.)
(It was you.)
(You hurt me,)
(set me up,)
(and tried to kill me.)
(But it was also you)
(who protected me,)
(saved me, and worried about me.)
(Shen Zaiye...)
(I never imagined that you and I)
(had such a complicated past.)
Jiang Taohua!
Qingtai?
Where is Qingtai?
Zhan Lu is looking after her.
Qingtai, hang in there.
Qingtai!
Qingtai, stay with me!
You have to survive!
Qingtai!
Princess...
It hurts...
I know, I know.
Don't worry.
I swear I'll make Empress Lv pay.
I'll kill her!
No.
She must have the plan flawless.
If anything happens to her,
you,
His Highness Changjue,
and many others will all die.
Promise me.
Don't go.
Yes.
I promise.
Don't go.
Qingtai, hang in there, please.
You're going to be fine.
You'll be alright.
Chancellor.
Everyone in the courtyard has escaped.
Help the wounded.
I'll ready the carriage.
Qingtai.
Don't fall asleep, Qingtai.
Qingtai!
(Shen Residence)
Please be a little gentler, physician.
Qingtai...
Could you please be gentler?
Just a bit gentler.
This is a piercing wound.
I need to stitch her internal organs.
How am I supposed to treat her gently?
Please calm down.
I'll assist you.
Just let me know what you need.
Another basin of hot water.
Sir, will she make it?
The blade did pierce a vital organ.
But luckily, you found her in time.
I'll stitch up her organs first.
She lost a lot of blood,
so we'll have to use medicine
to keep her in a dormant state for now.
She'll need rest and recovery in time.
But she should survive.
Thank you, sir. Thank you!
You'll be alright, Qingtai.
Zhan Lu.
Could you look after Qingtai for now?
Chancellor Shen.
Thank you for saving my life.
No need to thank me.
I have no status or power.
The only thing I can offer is gratitude.
I wonder how we can catch Empress Lv
without endangering you or your brother?
Changjue's life and mine
are in her hands.
If there isn't a perfect plan,
I hope you can hold back for now.
Even now,
you still don't believe
what we once had?
If it were you, Chancellor Shen,
would you trust someone that easily?
I told you I was saving a life,
but you locked me
in the interrogation room.
(Is that what you call trust?)
(I never truly trusted you at all...)
They came after Qingtai.
If you go back to Prince Wuyin,
how will you explain this to him?
The longer I'm gone,
the harder it is to explain.
If Qingtai wakes up,
please find a way to let me know.
Farewell.
(If he finds out my memory is back,)
(he will surely try to keep me.)
(Then, it'll be impossible)
(to get close to Prince Wuyin again.)
(Shen Zaiye,)
(it's better if you and I)
(never knew each other.)
(Shunjing Residence)
Gone all night...
And looking a mess.
Your Highness, I...
Don't say anything you do not mean.
I don't want to hear it.
You need to remember
that your life and your brother's
are both in my hands.
Ms. Meng...
Everyone makes one or two mistakes.
But never more than that.
Do you understand?
I will remember that.
We hereby summon
Chancellor Shen
and Prince Wuxia to the court.
I have finished
reading your policy paper.
You two always claim
to be well-read and wise.
Then tell me,
what do you think of this essay?
Father.
These nine proposals are indeed
solid strategies for national peace.
But it feels like something is missing.
And the writing style...
He is clearly
holding something back from me
to get a promotion.
That part feels like
the Left Chancellor.
Left Chancellor, what do you think?
It is an excellent essay.
And as Prince Wuxia said,
it does seem to be missing something.
However...
Your calligraphy
needs serious improvement.
Thank you for the advice, Chancellor.
I will work hard to improve.
Did you really write this yourself?
I'm but an unworthy scholar
with arrogant ideas.
I hope Your Highness will forgive me.
From where I sit...
Meng Huairui.
His Majesty is a wise ruler
who won't overlook talent.
If your essay is incomplete,
revise it and submit it again.
We will discuss your placement then.
What do you think, Your Majesty?
Well said, Left Chancellor.
Revise and organize it,
then show me again.
I look forward to your completed work.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I will give it my utmost effort
and polish it well.
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Wuxia.
Consort Lan is hosting
a family feast today.
Stay.
I take my leave.
(Meng Residence)
Uncle.
I here for a visit.
I thought the family head
needed something from me.
How bold of you
to sit at the head of the table?
Why should I not sit there?
My uncle let you
take charge temporarily,
but I heard things didn't go well.
Prince Wuyin left halfway
through your conversation.
You sure have your sources.
I told my uncle so.
What can a woman ever accomplish?
I still don't get it.
How did he fall for your tricks?
Whether a woman can succeed
depends on the long game.
Let me ask you this.
Did you present someone else's
essay to His Majesty again?
What do you mean someone else's?
I wrote every single word myself.
But Li Jiaohan is very close
to Prince Wuyin.
Do you think Prince Wuyin would let you
get away with tricks like that?
I did make some edits while copying it.
Prince Wuyin...
The style reveals character.
Do you think a fake would fool him?
When the heir was alive,
the Meng family was the top
noble house in the court.
Now that we have lost that support,
if anything goes wrong,
the other families will
jump at the chance to finish us.
And the consequences
is too great for one like you!
You have two options now.
One, the Meng family turns you in
to clear our name,
and you agree to be exiled
3,000 li away.
My lady.
My lady, please don't!
I won't survive that punishment!
My lady.
I still have aging parents to care for.
Then, clean up this mess.
But let me be clear.
If anything goes wrong,
the Meng family will be the first
to denounce you.
It's a death sentence.
I will handle it myself.
From now on, you do or say
according to my orders.
Can you do that?
From this day forward,
I am at your command.
(Shen Residence)
(There was something odd
about today's essay.)
(It seemed very similar)
(to the one Prince Wuyin
once showed to the ministers.)
(Though the content
slightly differed between the two,)
(the style clearly came
from the same hand.)
(Could it be)
(that Meng Huairui
plagiarized Li Jiaohan?)
Did you really write this yourself?
Zhan Lu, prepare a horse.
Li Jiaohan?
Chancellor, there are signs
of struggle on the wrist,
flesh under the nails,
and a fine mark beneath
the strangulation bruise.
Li Jiaohan.
You had a brilliant mind.
He held no official rank or title,
yet his talent even surpassed mine.
If someone like him is wasted,
how can our nation
ever rise to greater heights?
Are you questioning
the Nine-Rank System?
That system had its place back then.
It suited the times.
But times have changed.
Our nation now values
both civil and military excellence.
We are strong in arms,
but our civil strength
suffers under this system.
(Young Meng Zhongyan)
It undermined the careers
of poor but talented scholars.
(Young Meng Zhongyan)
If this keeps up,
(Minister of Personnel Xie Guanyu)
those scholars may flee to Beiyuan,
and we will be guilty
of aiding our enemies.
So what are you proposing?
Ignore the divide between classes?
Start with subject-based nominations,
then promote by merit?
So we can win the hearts
of scholars across the land?
But if commoners
can easily enter officialdom,
(Young Prince Qi)
the entire nation will see chaos!
What is
your true agenda?
Why you...
Your Majesty.
My loyalty is as clear
as the sun and moon.
I am doing this
for the people of the realm.
For the everlasting prosperity of Qi.
Minister Xie...
No need to get worked up.
This is a serious matter.
It is indeed just as Minister Meng said.
It concerns the very foundation.
We need to think it through carefully.
Allow me some time to consider it.
I will give you my answer.
Your Majesty!
You may leave for now.
Yes.
Father.
An?
Why are you here?
Father, are you all right just now?
Well...
Father.
Are you thinking of giving up?
No.
I will never stop
fighting for the imperial examination.
I must find a way out
for scholars from poor families.
I will never let the noble clans
dominate the court forever.
Chancellor.
This clearly looks like
someone staged a suicide.
I'll inform the Yujing Magistrate
and have them investigate it.
No.
Tell the coroner
to confirm it as a suicide.
But...
Mr. Li.
I know who did this to you.
I assure you
I'll make sure justice is served.
However,
we still need to wait a bit longer.
Chancellor, what are you...
Using his death to reinstate
the imperial exam.
Zhan Lu.
Take my letter
to the Yujing coroner.
He will know what to do.
(Examination Hall)
This was murder, right?
How can you tell?
That archway is so tall.
It's hard to tie a rope up there.
I bet it's exhausting to die this way.
Hey, move back.
Alright.
The coroner will sort it out anyway.
Get him down.
Sir, please have a look.
Upon examination,
this man had no signs
of struggle or restraint.
It seems he tied a brick to a rope,
threw it over the archway,
then used the rope
to hang himself.
Such a complicated way to hang oneself.
Wouldn't any old crooked tree
be a lot easier?
According to this letter,
his name was Li Jiaohan.
A commoner and scholar,
who only wished to serve the court.
But because noble clans
blocked his path,
he died in despair.
His dying wish was that one day,
the imperial exam would be reinstated.
He died for the people!
He sacrificed for us!
He acted for the greater good!
The poor are treated like dirt.
He was killed by the noble families.
Reinstate the exam!
Or we will end up like him!
- Reinstate the exam!
- No more nobles! Reinstate the exam!
(Li...)
(Did you see this?)
(It's the future of poor scholars.)
(Learning and Virtue)
(You made it possible.)
- No more nobles! Reinstate the exam!
♪The flower bloomed,
knowing nothing at all♪
♪In splendor, proud and tall♪
♪The flower fell, lashed by the wind♪
♪In a daze,
it felt like lifetimes had thinned♪
♪Petals soaked in rain♪
♪Heartbreak follows again and again♪
♪The flower weeps, burdened by thoughts♪
♪With no one it can be brought♪
♪Wishes struggle through the mire♪
♪Regrets clash in hopeless fire♪
♪Still I hope she'll pick the flower
kissed by dew♪
♪Even if it means this flower♪
♪Will be hers to give to someone new♪
♪Whose eyes
did the flower's heart meet?♪
♪Love and hate held back, discreet♪
♪The flower withers, feelings in decay♪
♪No longer needing to say♪
♪Yet I still long for her in madness♪
♪Unafraid of judgment or sadness♪
♪Remembering the words
she spoke of flowers and skies♪
♪And finding♪
♪They were her gentle heart's reply♪