♪Peach blossoms fall,
yesterday's trace fades away♪
♪Ahead lie storms and winds,
our fates like drifting clouds sway♪
♪Alas, I roam through what remains,
fate's grip won't set me free♪
♪If time would spare me
just one breath to stay♪
♪If you could see
the depth of my belief♪
♪Alone I enter the game,
every move made with no regret in me♪
♪Though shackles bind my soul
and chain my form♪
♪I've walked
through life and death before♪
♪I fear not fate's cruel temptations,
I've severed every cause♪
♪In this life our threads entwined,
in love and pain we crossed♪
♪But I'll keep my word
no matter the cost♪
♪Forged in stardust and flame♪
♪I rise with an unyielding frame♪
=The Princess's Gambit=
(Adapted from the novel "Peach Blossoms
Reflecting the River and Mountains")
(by Bai Lu Cheng Shuang)
=Episode 25=
(Examination Hall)
Easy, easy.
Be careful with that.
Put it over there.
Yes, that's the spot.
Put
three tables on that side.
That one. Turn it sideways.
Yes, like that.
Wang Xi.
- Hey, Wang Xi.
- That's right.
Yes, Your Highness.
Go prepare some rations.
These candidates have come
from all over the country.
Especially those from poor families,
some might not have eaten a thing.
I'll also set up a barrel
of spring water.
They can drink with a ladle
if they're thirsty,
and take food as needed.
That sounds like a good plan.
Go on and get everything ready.
Yes, Your Highness.
I'll see to it right away.
Come with me.
Make sure there's enough food
for all the examinees.
You go ahead.
Stick to the plan.
Don't stop me.
Hu, think this through.
I said, don't stop me!
If I don't stand up,
who will?
Hu, what about your family?
It's because of them
that I can no longer keep this quiet.
Li,
if you stop me again,
don't blame me for forsaking
our years of friendship.
What are you two doing?
Why are you arguing
in front of the exam hall?
You two barely study to begin with,
and now you're spreading rumors?
You're just afraid of failing.
So you're stirring up trouble
and bringing others down with you.
What did you say?
What do you think you're doing,
shouting in the examination hall?
Just leave.
I...
Just go.
Excuse me, mister.
Your Highness.
What were you arguing about just now?
Lately, there have been rumors
about Prince Wuhen selling
exam questions.
But there's no proof.
It's taken years to reopen
the imperial examination.
We can't let it all fall apart
over hearsay.
How about this?
Then do your best to prepare.
I'll look into
this matter.
(Chunyue Pavilion)
Little lady, are you drunk already?
Come on, drink more.
Your friend isn't here yet.
Forget about him.
If you don't like the food or wine,
I will replace everything for you.
Money's not a problem for me.
Your Highness,
you're so dashing and generous.
Wuhen.
Your Highness.
Oh, Wuxia.
What brings you here?
Ladies, could you give us a moment?
Why should they leave?
There's nothing here to hide.
Besides,
with a beauty like this in my arms,
I can even put up
with your pompous talk.
You two, leave us.
I need to talk to my brother.
Mu Wuhen,
do you know what crime you've committed
for selling the exam questions?
Mu Wuxia, who do you think you are?
- Let's go.
- Coming in here to throw your weight around?
Someone's messing
with the integrity of the exams.
Of course, I'll step in.
(Examination Hall)
Next.
Sir,
I'm Li Dian, styled Kui'an.
From Qufu.
Words alone are no evidence.
Where's the travel slip issued
by your commanding official?
Next.
Only half a slip?
I can't even read the writing.
It's invalid.
Move along.
(Li Dian, Scholar of Humble Origins)
Sir, I was robbed on the road.
They took everything.
I risked my life
to grab back my slip.
That's how it was torn in half.
I'm not afraid of being laughed at.
- But I begged all the way here.
- Next.
I don't care
if you flew here on a crane.
I only care if you have your slip.
One that is not torn, get it?
It has been twenty years.
I finally have the opportunity
to retake the exam.
The people in my village
are counting on me.
If I can't sit the exam,
how will I ever face them again, sir?
That's your problem,
not mine.
I'm only a clerk.
Don't call me "sir."
Move along now.
Sir...
Don't waste time.
Sir, is there a way...
Next.
This slip is not fake, sir.
I...
Excuse me, mister.
Could you explain
what Laozi meant
by "Heaven and Earth show no mercy,
treating everything as insignificant"?
What do you think it means?
This is from the Dao De Jing,
Chapter Five.
It means that the world is abiding
by natural law,
favoring no one
and letting things grow freely.
Though it sounds merciless,
it reflects the truth of nature.
The Dao follows its course
without interference.
Well said.
You're too kind.
I'm only a poor scholar
from the countryside
with little learning.
And now I can't even take the exam.
Who says you can't?
But my slip...
This exam is to select talent,
not to chase slips of paper.
Wang Xi.
Yes?
Someone,
take him away.
Have mercy, Your Highness.
Make sure Li Dian's name
- is registered.
- Your Highness.
Yes, Prince Wuxia.
You haven't taken the exam,
nor earned a title.
I can't accept such a formal bow.
Prince Wuxia.
Even if I fail this time,
I'll return to retake the exam.
From this day on,
I consider you my patron.
You...
Then it's a promise.
If you all truly have talent,
I, Mu Wuxia,
will be your patron.
All I ask is that, when you enter court,
you remain upright, loyal,
serve the country with all your heart,
and bring peace and prosperity to Qi.
Prince Wuxia.
If I'm ever appointed,
I'll be a beacon of integrity.
I won't let you down.
- We will do the same.
Imperial Guards! Make way!
Prince Wuxia.
What brings the Imperial Guards here?
By His Majesty's order,
you are to return to the residence
and refrain from receiving visitors.
Father?
Last night, Prince Wuhen was found dead.
A report claims you were involved.
Your Majesty,
Prince Wuhen
was my sister's only remaining son.
For the sake
of the Qin family's loyalty,
I beg Your Majesty
to punish Prince Wuxia.
Look at me.
Tell me.
Did you see Wuxia kill him?
The matter is under investigation.
Your Majesty,
multiple witnesses confirm
that the two princes had an argument.
Wuhen was found dead
in a tavern soon after.
Your Majesty,
please seek justice for Wuhen
and punish Prince Wuxia.
May Your Majesty see this
with clear judgment.
- May Your Majesty issue an edict
- and bring the culprit to justice.
I've already lost one son.
Now, you're asking me
to give up another?
Get out. All of you.
If you don't leave,
I'll see you executed first!
Your Majesty.
Quick. Bring my pills!
The pills.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Wuhen.
Wuhen...
Your Majesty.
Wuhen
may not have been the most capable.
But he was still my son.
First, it was Wugou.
Now,
it's Wuhen.
One by one, they're all gone.
I call myself "the lonely king"
every day.
Will I end up truly alone,
with no one left to call my own?
How could that be?
Your Majesty,
you still have me.
Luckily, I still have you.
Your Majesty, the Left Chancellor
requests an audience.
I will not see him.
Your Majesty,
he's your most trusted official.
How can you not see him?
He must have come for Wuxia.
My dear,
this fratricide
must not go unpunished.
Or else Qi will fall.
Let him in.
Go on ahead.
Then I'll take my leave first.
Bring my pills.
Here it is, Your Majesty.
You may go.
Summon the Left Chancellor.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Do you know of the tragedy
that befell the Zhao State?
I do not.
In the chaos of the Five Kingdoms,
the Zhao State was the strongest.
But their royal family destroyed itself
through infighting.
Eventually, with no heirs left,
the state was divided.
Indeed, fratricide is truly
the greatest tragedy.
But from what I know of Prince Wuxia,
he would never do such a thing.
And yet so many have testified.
Are you here trying
to protect a wolf in sheep's clothing?
I've taken many lives
of such people in my day.
I don't dare dispute Your Majesty.
But this case is riddled with suspicion.
May I interrogate Prince Wuxia myself?
I've already ordered
that no one is to enter his residence
or seek audience with him.
Then may I at least assist
with the investigation?
You can't be distracted now.
The imperial exam is near,
and Wuyin has only just been appointed.
Go and assist him.
Prince Wuyin?
I've appointed him
as the chief examiner.
Meng Zhongyan is reinstated
to his former post
and appointed as a co-examiner
to assist Wuyin in overseeing
the imperial examinations.
You may go.
Yes, Your Majesty.
(Shen Residence)
If we can't see Prince Wuxia,
we won't be able to find out the truth.
The investigation will be all
the more difficult.
We have to investigate,
however hard it gets.
There's no way
Prince Wuxia is the killer.
Should we go to the scene now
and look for clues?
No.
The Imperial Guards
have already intervened in this matter.
They are on high alert during the day.
We can go tonight.
For now, let the word out
that I'm too busy with the exam
to receive guests.
We must uncover the truth
before the exams begin.
If we don't, all our efforts
will be in vain.
Understood. I'll go now.
(Meng Residence)
Ms. Zhenzhen.
Search the place.
Zhenzhen, what's going on?
If you needed something from me,
a message would have sufficed.
Why bring your noble feet
into my lowly courtyard?
Does Prince Wuhen's death
have anything to do with you?
That was His Majesty's son.
Even if I have the courage,
I wouldn't dare do such a thing.
Then why were you sneaking
around Chunyue Pavilion
and slipping away just as quietly?
Prince Wuhen died that night.
I'm sure you've heard
it was Prince Wuxia
who barged into the tavern
and fought with Prince Wuhen that night.
In a moment of rage,
he accidentally killed Prince Wuhen.
So, was it really a gentleman's fury
that turned deadly?
What are you hiding in your hand?
Nothing.
Where did you get this?
Are you trying to ruin the Meng family?
No, I'm not.
It's only a plain jade pendant.
"Regret not the past,
take righteousness as profit."
Congratulations on your new role
as the Chief Examiner.
And to Right Chancellor Meng
for his reinstatement too.
The Mengs rise once more
to lead the noble clans.
Have a seat.
You know I prefer peace and quiet.
Your father will bear much
of the burden of this exam.
The Meng family stands ready
to serve Your Highness.
We trust you'll watch over us in return.
"A gift from heaven unclaimed
brings misfortune,
a chance ignored becomes a curse.
Miss the moment,
and you'll pay the price."
Wuhen and I
were always close.
Wuxia may be my brother too.
But he has completely lost his mind.
I won't let anyone clear his name.
As for that lowly pawn
who got caught in the crossfire,
I assume I don't need to spell out
what should be done?
Your Highness,
there's one more thing that troubles me.
Speak.
From what I've gathered,
this exam only happened
thanks to Shen Zaiye,
not Prince Wuxia.
I still suspect Li Jiaohan's case
is linked to him.
So
I believe Shen Zaiye and Prince Wuxia
have some secret connection.
A valid point.
But don't worry.
I already have someone watching him.
You planted a spy?
By Shen Zaiye's side?
Let me tell you a secret.
Jiang Taohua is currently staying
in my residence.
Princess Chengping? In your residence?
It's just as you have predicted.
Shen Zaiye came to rescue her.
Jiang Taohua,
I knew you wouldn't die so easily.
What's the next step, Master?
Why would Jiang Taohua remain
at Prince Wuyin's residence?
She hit her head
when she fell from a cliff.
She is still mentally disoriented
and has lost her memories.
Now she follows my every word.
Your Highness,
why did you summon me?
Sit.
Miss Meng,
I have a task for you.
At your command, Your Highness.
You've been resting for months.
Wouldn't it be nice
to stretch your legs a little?
A major event has shaken the court.
My brother Wuxia has murdered Wuhen.
There are witnesses
and concrete evidence.
There's no turning it around.
But Shen Zaiye will not let it go.
He'll look into it.
I want to know what he finds.
So I need you
to get close to him.
If there's any sign of movement,
report back to me immediately.
(Prince Wuxia would never kill
his own brother.)
(But why is Prince Wuyin so sure)
(Shen Zaiye will try to clear his name?)
What? You can't do it?
No, it's not that.
I was just thinking
it's been months since we last met.
Getting close to him now
without raising suspicion won't be easy.
His sister, Xiang Qingying,
is simple-minded.
And she's grown quite close to Wuxia.
I suppose
she might be the key.
Thank you for the guidance,
Your Highness.
Mu Wuxia, I swear I'll get you out.
Qingying.
Jiang Taohua? What are you doing here?
I want to visit Qingtai
at the Chancellor's residence.
Are...
Are you crying?
Jiang Taohua,
do you know
Mu Wuxia has been wrongly accused
of killing Prince Wuhen?
He's now locked up in his residence,
completely cut off
from the outside world.
Prince Wuxia?
You know him, Qingying?
Not just me.
You knew him too.
But you don't remember anymore.
Mu Wuxia always looked out for you
and helped you more than once.
After you fell off the cliff,
he even stood up for you
and had a big argument
with my brother over it.
I've heard
that Prince Wuxia is a man of honor.
It turns out to be true.
Since I have received kindness from him,
I cannot stand by and do nothing.
Wherever you're going,
I'm coming with you.
Jiang Taohua,
I didn't expect you to be so loyal.
I was on my way to see him.
Where?
Zaiye said
His Majesty gave strict orders.
No one is allowed to see Mu Wuxia.
But
no one can stop me and my sword.
Qingying,
barging into Prince Wuxia's residence
will only make things worse for him.
How about this?
We go and check the scene of the crime.
Maybe we'll find something useful.
What matters now
is to clear Prince Wuxia's name.
You have a point. Let's go.
I know where it happened.
- Come.
- Let's go.
(Chunyue Pavilion)
Who's there?
(What are they doing here?)
There's a noise by the river.
You two, check it out.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Let's use the back entrance.
Stop right there.
Zaiye?
Have you been following us?
Zaiye, say something.
Didn't I tell you to stay home
and stay out of this?
Mu Wuxia's still locked up.
How am I supposed to sit still?
And
what are you two doing here?
I just snuck out of the residence
and hadn't gone far
when I ran into her looking for Qingtai.
I told her what happened.
Zaiye, the moment she heard
Prince Wuxia was in trouble,
she insisted on helping.
So, how could I back out?
Besides, we came here
to look for evidence.
It can help to clear Mu Wuxia's name.
We're not here to cause trouble.
Even the Princess knew
to dress in disguise.
But you?
Just strutting around like this?
Zaiye, are you taking us with you?
Then wait for me.
I'll go with you.
Miss Meng.
Greetings, Chancellor Shen.
It's been a while.
Miss Meng,
have you remembered something?
Why do you say that, Chancellor Shen?
Do you remember
Prince Wuxia?
Qingying told me
Prince Wuxia helped me many times.
Of course, I'd want to return the favor.
But you're willing to help
just based on what you heard?
Chancellor Shen,
are you interrogating me?
Of course not.
Then I don't see the need
to explain myself.
Go home.
You shouldn't get involved in this mess.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
I don't need you to tell me
what I should or shouldn't do.
We clearly can't see eye to eye.
So there's no point in talking.
Very well.
In that case,
I'll go ahead first.
Where is he?
He has already left.
We're splitting up.
Did you two argue?
Qingying.
Whatever happened between me
and the Chancellor in the past
is already in the past.
We're just strangers now.
How did you two end up like this?
Let's go.
(Prince Wuhen must've hit his head.)
(That's why there's so much blood.)
(These are...)
(Fingernail scratches.)
(He struggled before he died.)
(Prince Wuxia
has never been good at fighting,)
(and Prince Wuhen was much bigger.)
(If they fought, Wuxia would've lost.)
My brother must be inside.
Let's go in.
Zaiye, did you leave this door open
for us on purpose?
So, is this where Prince Wuhen was killed?
Mu Wuxia is not even strong enough.
So he couldn't have killed Prince Wuhen.
(There's blood.)
(But no signs of a fight.)
(Prince Wuhen)
(must have been attacked)
(when he wasn't expecting it.)
(These footprints)
(must be from the killer escaping.)
(The dancer from that night said)
(Prince Wuxia left through
the front door.)
Who's inside?
There's a light upstairs.
Go and check it out.
You, over there.
Yes, sir.
Bring more men.
Follow me.
- Yes, sir.
(Shunjing Residence)
Your Highness,
I followed Shen Zaiye to the scene,
and I found a broken piece
of a jade pendant.
A broken jade piece?
What kind?
Something about this size.
All right.
Thank you for your hard work.
You should return and get some rest.
Yes, Your Highness.
(Hua,)
(once I've cleared the path for you,)
(you'll come back to me.)
(Right?)
(Happiness)
♪The flower bloomed,
knowing nothing at all♪
♪In splendor, proud and tall♪
♪The flower fell, lashed by the wind♪
♪In a daze,
it felt like lifetimes had thinned♪
♪Petals soaked in rain♪
♪Heartbreak follows again and again♪
♪The flower weeps, burdened by thoughts♪
♪With no one it can be brought♪
♪Wishes struggle through the mire♪
♪Regrets clash in hopeless fire♪
♪Still I hope she'll pick the flower
kissed by dew♪
♪Even if it means this flower♪
♪Will be hers to give to someone new♪
♪Whose eyes
did the flower's heart meet?♪
♪Love and hate held back, discreet♪
♪The flower withers, feelings in decay♪
♪No longer needing to say♪
♪Yet I still long for her in madness♪
♪Unafraid of judgment or sadness♪
♪Remembering the words
she spoke of flowers and skies♪
♪And finding♪
♪They were her gentle heart's reply♪