♪Peach blossoms fall,
yesterday's trace fades away♪
♪Ahead lie storms and winds,
our fates like drifting clouds sway♪
♪Alas, I roam through what remains,
fate's grip won't set me free♪
♪If time would spare me
just one breath to stay♪
♪If you could see
the depth of my belief♪
♪Alone I enter the game,
every move made with no regret in me♪
♪Though shackles bind my soul
and chain my form♪
♪I've walked
through life and death before♪
♪I fear not fate's cruel temptations,
I've severed every cause♪
♪In this life our threads entwined,
in love and pain we crossed♪
♪But I'll keep my word
no matter the cost♪
♪Forged in stardust and flame♪
♪I rise with an unyielding frame♪
=The Princess's Gambit=
(Adapted from the novel "Peach Blossoms
Reflecting the River and Mountains")
(by Bai Lu Cheng Shuang)
=Episode 34=
Here's the confession letter you want
(Confession Letter)
and
the petition Xie Guanyu wrote back then.
Father said
it was hidden behind the plaque
in his study.
I hope you will keep your word
and spare the women and children
of the Meng family.
I may do what it takes
to get what I want.
But I won't go back on my word
like your father did.
(Meng Residence)
(Humility)
(Petition)
I will present this petition
to His Majesty.
He will see the truth
and clear my name.
(Respectfully, Xie Guanyu)
(Father,)
(I will restore our family's honor.)
(Shen Residence)
Today, not only did
Meng Zhongyan confess,
but I also found the petition
my father wrote back then.
Taohua,
I'm sorry.
I...
You don't need to apologize to me.
If you had not stood with Prince Wuxia
to fight for your family for my sake,
I wouldn't have fallen for you.
You knew?
Don't worry.
I already sent Zhan Lu ahead
with the shadow guards
to Beiyuan to search for the antidote.
Once I've finished this,
I'll ride
to Beiyuan with you.
Chancellor,
just focus on clearing
your father's name.
Don't worry about me.
I'll head off with Zhan Lu tomorrow.
But how can I not worry
when you go back alone?
I have Zhan Lu, Qingtai,
and the shadow guards with me.
I won't be alone.
Besides, Changjue sent a letter today.
He said he has already gathered support
from many officials
in Hao City.
Even Qian Mochen?
Changjue did try reaching out.
But Qian Mochen turned him away.
Luckily, we had warned Changjue.
So he stayed cautious.
So Qian Mochen doesn't know where he is.
Good.
So
don't worry.
Once I reach Hao City,
Changjue will help me look
for the antidote.
What worries me is
that you always protect Changjue
and don't let him worry about you.
He's my brother.
Now that I need his help,
I'll tell him everything.
So don't worry.
Then promise me
to take care of yourself.
When this is over,
I'll come and find you right away.
I promise.
Do you have confidence
in tomorrow's court session?
Don't worry.
Everything's in place.
Court is in session!
His Majesty arrives!
You may all leave.
- Greetings, Your Majesty.
- Greetings, Father.
Rise.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
I'm feeling unwell today.
Present only urgent matters.
Your Majesty,
I have an important matter to report.
Proceed.
Your Majesty,
over several days of questioning,
I've learned that in addition
to treason,
Meng Zhongyan committed
another crime 18 years ago.
He has written a full confession.
I ask Your Majesty to allow me
to present the details.
I'm not well.
We'll discuss it another day.
Summon the imperial physician.
Father,
the physician will be here shortly.
Please rest.
Allow me to hear the report
on your behalf.
Chancellor Shen,
please proceed with Meng's confession.
According to Meng Zhongyan's confession,
he orchestrated the witchcraft case
eighteen years ago.
He planted cursed objects
to frame Consort Shu
and hid the petition written
by her brother, Xie Guanyu,
the head of the Xie family.
He then falsely claimed resistance
and ordered the slaughter
of the entire Xie family.
Why?
Because Xie Guanyu had proposed
an imperial exam reform
that threatened the interests
of powerful noble families like his.
I found
both Xie Guanyu's petition
and Meng Zhongyan's confession
at the Meng residence.
I shall present both to Your Majesty.
Father,
Meng Zhongyan deceived the throne,
formed private factions,
and murdered loyal subjects.
His crimes cry out for justice.
Please order a retrial of the case.
- Please order a retrial, Your Majesty.
Are you trying to drive me to my grave?
What difference is there
between this and the treason
of Mu Wuyin and Meng Zhongyan?
Meng Zhongyan's crimes
are unforgivable.
All we ask
is to right what was wrong.
How is that the same?
Mu Wuxia,
it looks like
I truly underestimated you.
You're better at winning hearts
than your three brothers ever were.
Even Left Chancellor
now speaks up for you.
Fine.
Why don't I just hand my throne
to you now?
So you can decide
which case for retrials!
Father, please wait.
What now? Do you want to rebel too?
I dare not.
I only speak
from reason.
The witchcraft charges have failed
to convince the public.
Fine.
You
and you!
Stay!
Everyone else is dismissed!
You want to reopen the case
for your mother.
And you,
Left Chancellor.
What's your reason?
I am
Xie Guanyu's son,
Xie Jing'an.
Xie Jing'an?
You're still alive?
Your entire clan
was executed.
Yet
you've hidden at my side
for over a decade.
What's your motive?
By law,
I should have you executed
for deceiving your ruler!
Father,
Jing'an must have suffered greatly
to survive.
He has served
the court loyally for ten years.
He deserves recognition
for both his service and his effort.
Silence!
So long as I live,
that witchcraft case
will never be overturned!
When Meng Zhongyan lied to you,
you did nothing.
When noble clans schemed for power,
you looked the other way.
I have suffered a grave injustice.
All I ask now is
to clear my clan's name.
Is it that Your Majesty
can't tell right from wrong,
or that you simply refuse to admit
that Meng Zhongyan was only the blade
that killed my family,
and you were the one
who wielded it?
You dare speak to me like that?
Your Majesty.
I've served you loyally
for ten years.
I rooted out traitors
and went against noble families.
But I am not my father.
I won't let myself become
your pawn in a political game.
The truth
of the witchcraft case is already known.
History won't lie for your sake.
A hundred years from now,
do you want to be remembered
as a stubborn tyrant
who destroyed the loyal
or
a wise ruler
who could admit his mistakes
and cherish his loyal ministers?
Father,
Mr. Li Dian is currently drafting
your royal chronicle.
What?
Are you threatening me now?
Aren't you afraid I'll execute you both?
Your Majesty,
what I've said today
may be bold.
But this will be
my final counsel to the throne.
What are you up to now?
I will resign my post
as Left Chancellor
to live among the common people.
As I take my leave,
I beg Your Majesty
to retry the witchcraft case
and clear the Xie family
and Consort Shu,
the mother
of the future Crown Prince Wuxia's
name.
(Xie Residence)
(Imperial Edict)
(A nation's strength lies)
(in the clarity of its laws.)
(When justice is clouded,)
(evil thrives,)
(and the loyal suffer.)
(Now that the truth is revealed,)
(I hereby decree.)
(Xie Guanyu and his kin)
(were indeed wrongfully accused)
(and framed.)
(Xie Guanyu's former ranks
and titles are restored.)
(Consort Shu
shall be posthumously titled "Yi",)
(to honor her virtue.)
(Xie Residence)
(Let this be proclaimed)
(across the land.)
(Father. Mother.)
(I have cleared our family's name.)
(May your spirits)
(finally rest in peace.)
(Xie Residence)
Have you paid your respects?
I think Uncle's spirit
can rest in peace now.
Zaiye, are you really leaving?
I don't want you to go.
Wuxia doesn't want you to go either.
Right?
Say something, you block of wood.
Qingying, don't make a scene.
Taohua has already gone to Beiyuan.
She's waiting for me.
Then promise you'll come visit often.
Or better yet, we'll come visit you.
Mu Wuxia, will you go with me?
Wuxia's going
to be the Crown Prince soon.
He can't just enter
another state like that.
As for you, Qingying,
you need to grow up.
You're about to become
the Crown Princess.
Then you need to settle down too.
You're about to be a Prince Consort.
Wuxia, Qingying lost her father
at a young age, and I've spoiled her.
You'll need to keep her in check.
There's no need to hold back.
I understand, Jing'an.
You wouldn't dare.
Jing'an, there will always be a place
for you in Qi.
I've lived under a false name
and endured humiliation all these years
for two reasons.
First, to clear the Xie family's name
from the witchcraft case,
and to help you grow strong enough
to rule.
For ten years,
I gave everything
as a subject,
a son,
and an elder brother.
I have no regrets.
Now that justice has been done,
and
you are soon to become Crown Prince,
my only wish
is to keep Taohua safe,
find a quiet place away from the world,
and grow old with her.
Then
I hope you and Taohua will take care
and live the life you deserve.
The road ahead is long.
Qi will depend on you now.
(Beiyuan Palace)
Cui Wei,
your efforts were key
to my safe return.
You're too kind, Your Highness.
After Your Highness met
with Mu Wuyin that day,
we lost all trace of you
in Luocheng.
So I sent riders
to Qi State to search for you.
Thankfully,
they succeeded
and found you.
Everyone thought
I perished in that fire.
But there was a hidden passage
beneath my chamber.
That's how I escaped
the capital of Qi State back then
without anyone noticing.
And now,
that same passage saved my life again.
Your Highness is blessed by the heavens.
Naturally, no danger can harm you.
While I've been away,
what has happened in Hao City?
Your Highness,
Jiang Changjue has arrived in the city.
Our spies found
he has been in secret contact
with the State Preceptor
and Deputy Chief Yue.
They plan to install a new ruler
at tomorrow's court session.
Jiang Changjue
is staying at a residence arranged
by Deputy Chief Yue.
Take men and eliminate
Jiang Changjue immediately.
Bring me his head.
Yes, Your Highness.
The news from Qi says
Empress Lv and Mu Wuyin
both perished in the fire.
I've already requested Deputy Chief Yue
to summon the officials who support us.
We'll change the tides of this state
at tomorrow's court session.
Your Highness,
there's a group of strangers outside.
The one leading them looks like Cui Wei.
Your Highness,
this place is no longer safe.
We'll leave through the back.
Quick.
Commander Cui, they've escaped.
Here's what we'll do.
You all go hide in the secret chamber.
I'll head out to alert Deputy Chief Yue.
Your Highness, let me come with you.
You're attending court tomorrow.
We can't risk anything happening to you.
All right, that works.
The rest of you, follow me!
Let's go.
Why did you betray me?
Men die for wealth,
just as birds die for food.
Hurry! Don't let him get away!
Commander Cui, the spy we planted
with Jiang Changjue, is dead.
Useless fool.
Commander Cui,
he seems to have gone that way.
After him.
If we lose him, how am I supposed to
explain to Her Highness?
Send some men to stake out
Deputy Chief Yue's residence.
If Jiang Changjue shows up,
seize him immediately.
Split up and go after him.
(Empress Lv is still alive?)
Her Highness arrives!
- Peace and blessings, Your Highness.
I'm here to attend to His Majesty.
You may leave.
- Yes, Your Highness.
Stay.
I'm ordering you to stay.
Stay...
You were once
a charismatic, charming,
and commanding ruler.
Now look at how you have fallen
to such a disgrace,
it's hard to even bear the sight.
I...
(Emperor of Beiyuan)
I have treated you well.
Don't forget
that
you were just a dancer
from Liufang Court.
You're right, Your Majesty.
You did treat me well.
I came from humble origins.
I was humiliated in Qi.
Then I fled to Beiyuan,
where I ended up as a dancer.
I twisted my ankle
and couldn't perform one night.
A distinguished guest ordered me
to stand barefoot on ice to heal.
From that night on,
I could never dance again
and lost my livelihood.
My body was ruined by the cold,
and I could never bear children.
Even my last hope of marrying into
a decent family was shattered
by the cruelty of Beiyuan.
I searched far and wide
and finally discovered
that distinguished guest that night
was you,
Your Majesty.
I
don't remember.
Medicine...
Medicine.
Your Majesty,
savor this despair.
It's what I felt back then.
Are...
Are you out of your mind?
To get revenge,
I got close to you.
I flattered and schemed without shame
until you gave me status.
Wasn't
that enough?
How is that enough?
Then I took hold of court affairs
and ruled from behind the curtain.
I never thought
it would bring me the joy
I had never known before.
Life and death hang on
the stroke of a brush.
I, Lv Yuanhua,
no longer had to be trampled on.
They dread me and fear me.
For nearly a decade, I've held power.
This throne
should have been mine long ago.
You...
You vile woman.
Someone...
Help...
Save me.
Once I take the throne,
I'll wipe out
every last one of your Jiang clan.
Not a single one shall remain.
(Hao City, Beiyuan Capital City)
(Hao City)
Miss, come and take a look.
Let's go.
Zhan Lu, look.
That's our famous Hao City wine.
And over there.
I said, look.
(Hao City's streets and alleys)
(- look just as I remembered.)
- That's it.
Push him.
(Empress Lv,)
(this was the freedom I dreamt of)
(when you locked me up back then.)
(But now,)
(your ambition and cruelty)
(have all been burned to ashes.)
(This time,)
(nothing will stop Changjue and me)
(from reclaiming what's ours.)
(Postal Inn)
Her Highness has arrived!
My dear ministers, it's been a while.
How have you all been?
- Peace and blessings, Your Highness.
I have returned safe and sound.
What's with
the long faces?
Don't tell me
(Yue Xingming, Deputy Chief Censor)
you're disappointed.
I heard that when Jiang Changjue
first arrived in Hao City,
the first person he approached
was you, State Preceptor.
(Qian Mochen, Beiyuan State Preceptor)
The messenger he sent was beaten out
of my residence
by my orders.
At that time,
Commander Cui happened to be present.
He can vouch for me.
Since today's assembly is
to determine the new ruler,
who would like to speak first?
Your Highness.
Since no one else steps forward,
allow me.
Commander Cui, please speak.
Your Highness.
For over a decade,
His Majesty had been gravely ill.
The affairs of state have rested
on your shoulders.
Now, for the stability of the court
and the will of the people,
you should follow the will
of heaven and the people
and take the reins.
This is outrageous.
It's usurping the throne!
Your Highness, not once in history
has a woman taken the throne.
His Majesty would never give
the throne to you.
I request to see His Majesty.
- I request to see His Majesty.
Oh, did I forget to mention?
His Majesty passed away last night.
What?
The Crown Prince, Jiang Changjue,
died in unfortunate circumstances.
Your Highness,
without an official decree of succession,
we will never recognize you as ruler.
Commander Cui,
I've grown tired
of Deputy Chief Yue's endless prattle.
He's annoyingly loud.
Deputy Chief Yue has insulted
Her Highness.
Take him away and have him executed!
This...
If my death can uphold justice,
then let it be so!
You evil empress,
you will not die a good death!
As for the rest of you,
any more objections?
- Please show mercy, Your Highness!
I suggest you all know your place.
Do not play with fire,
or your future will suffer.
You're all dismissed.
- Thank you, Your Highness.
State Preceptor, stay.
Step forward.
Yes, Your Highness.
If I recall correctly,
your poison is about to flare up.
So I trust you know time is short.
Choose an auspicious date
for my coronation immediately.
Yes, I'll do all I can.
(Postal Inn)
Word just came from the palace.
They say the Emperor of Beiyuan
passed away last night.
What do we do now?
The Emperor is now dead,
and the Crown Prince is also missing.
Beiyuan has truly descended into chaos.
Zhan Lu,
have they verified it?
Could there have been a mistake?
No, there's no mistake.
We were all fooled
by Empress Lv's decoy.
No one knows
how she made it back to Beiyuan.
How am I supposed to break this
to the Princess?
Your Highness...
Your Highness.
I've heard everything.
Right now,
the priority is to locate Changjue.
Let's go and speak to Qian Mochen.
We've located Qian Mochen's whereabouts.
So we're here to report it to you.
All right. You can leave now.
Yes, Your Highness.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Thanks to you, State Preceptor,
I was cast out of my homeland
and forced into a political marriage.
I'm hardly worthy
of the title "Princess" anymore.
Did you return home
just to condemn your master's betrayal?
If you want to eat, you should pay up.
You should be grateful
I even bothered
to take this lousy silver lock.
Hand it over!
Mother gave this lock to Taohua!
Let go!
Give it to me, brat!
Changjue,
are you all right?
Taohua,
why isn't Father protecting us?
What did we do wrong?
I'll be good, I promise.
I got your longevity lock back.
It's yours again.
Who are you?
I'm Qian
Mochen.
I'm just a wanderer
who once received Empress Helan's favor.
Now I return to repay her.
My mother...
She's gone.
Then let me stay by your side
until you're strong enough
to protect yourselves.
But this is the palace.
It won't be easy for you to get back in.
Though my knowledge of the scriptures
and ancient astronomy is limited,
I've been appointed State Preceptor.
Then may we take you as our teacher?
Just what I had in mind.
I came to find you for Changjue.
I've searched the city for days,
but he's nowhere to be found.
Does this have anything to do with you?
Do you know
Empress Lv is still alive?
She intends to take the throne.
Then that makes it all the more urgent
to find Changjue.
Tell me where he is.
I don't know.
But
I've already sent people out
to search for him.
Didn't know you had such a good heart.
Have you heard about His Majesty?
I know he has passed.
Since you already know,
there's something important
I must give you.
What is it?
The late Emperor's edict
to pass the throne to Changjue
is in my residence.
♪The flower bloomed,
knowing nothing at all♪
♪In splendor, proud and tall♪
♪The flower fell, lashed by the wind♪
♪In a daze,
it felt like lifetimes had thinned♪
♪Petals soaked in rain♪
♪Heartbreak follows again and again♪
♪The flower weeps, burdened by thoughts♪
♪With no one it can be brought♪
♪Wishes struggle through the mire♪
♪Regrets clash in hopeless fire♪
♪Still I hope she'll pick the flower
kissed by dew♪
♪Even if it means this flower♪
♪Will be hers to give to someone new♪
♪Whose eyes
did the flower's heart meet?♪
♪Love and hate held back, discreet♪
♪The flower withers, feelings in decay♪
♪No longer needing to say♪
♪Yet I still long for her in madness♪
♪Unafraid of judgment or sadness♪
♪Remembering the words
she spoke of flowers and skies♪
♪And finding♪
♪They were her gentle heart's reply♪