Sparkle Love
EP24
Why do you have a raincoat on?
It'll rain today according to the weather forecast,
so I put on a raincoat.
You're cute.
Come on.
Let me show you something.
Surprise.
I prepared these.
These are foods.
Here are the chairs.
You can eat food when hungry.
You can sit in the chair when tired.
This is a fishing rod.
This is a telescope.
You can use them for fishing and stargazing.
You can't stand the cold,
so I also prepared a thick tent for you.
I see.
You are so nice.
Dad
Mom
Hello. Aunt and Uncle.
Take care of yourselves.
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of Weiwei.
Dad, mom, we gotta go.
Goodbye.
Bye.
We gotta go.
Goodbye.
-Take care. -Ok.
Hello.
Sichong
Let me tell you about the arrangement after that.
OK.
You must step up training after you return to the team tomorrow.
I plan to arrange for you to participate in this year's tournament.
In addition,
I suggest you
find a place where there are fewer people
to stay for half a year.
Tomorrow
we'll go to school
to get you suspended.
Have you figured out how to tell him?
Why is there rustling on your side?
Mai Sichong, this is our last meet.
I'm at the lake with my girlfriend.
So great?
A girlfriend?
If it weren't for your great grades,
I'd have forbidden you to fall in love.
I got it.
I assure you
it will certainly not interfere with later training.
Will you have a lot of training afterwards?
And the training must be stricter
after entering the provincial team.
Don't think too much.
Let's have a fun day.
Let's go.
Go for a visit.
Here are alpacas.
We can feed them.
It'll spit.
It won't. Look.
Let's go.
How cute they are.
All right.
Your turn.
Come on.
Take it.
Feed it.
That's right.
You...
It's static electricity.
I just touched my hair.
Weiwei
You're really a Pikachu.
Your static electricity is stronger than others.
But be careful next time.
Luckily it's me.
If it's someone else it will be...
I'll see
the peacocks.
What's wrong?
It's okay.
My hands just got dirty on the floor earlier.
Come and sit here.
In fact,
I envy you sometimes.
Envy what?
You can meet me
at just 19 years old.
I don't like to answer you.
So
if I didn't shock you,
would you still like me?
At that time, I really thought I liked you
because I was shocked by you.
But
to be honest,
it's not that.
Do you remember
our first meeting
at the mobilization meeting?
Yes.
At that time, I thought
this girl
was troublesome
but interesting.
I tried to get close to you.
So I kept letting you shock me.
Who would have thought
that I, a big star on campus,
pursued you
after all kinds of hardships?
Will you regret it?
I never regret anything.
I won't regret
liking you.
Why don't you cover up?
Come on.
If you still feel cold,
there are quilts in the car,
I'll get them for you.
That's enough.
What's wrong?
Can't fall asleep?
A little bit.
Something on your mind?
Mai Sichong
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You'll always be the Pikachu I want to protect.
I like you.
Good night.
I gotta go.
Or I can't catch the provincial team's bus.
What's wrong with you?
You miss me now?
You won't stop coming
because you can't get tickets
to the tournament at the end of next month, will you?
I won't.
I'll be there.
That's good.
Goodbye.
I gotta run.
Take care.
Mai Sichong
Goodbye.
Many times
we don't wanna say goodbye.
Because we don't know if goodbye is meeting again
or never again.
I'll start training soon.
Because I can't see you,
I can only miss you with the stuff.
It's time
to turn in your cell phones.
Please,
can I make one more call?
No way.
It's a rule set by the coach.
I can't help it.
Please hand in your phone.
Just a minute.
Still calling someone.
Chong
Long time no see.
Where's Weiwei?
Something happened at her family, so she couldn't come.
But she asked me to tell you
to fight for the game.
Don't let her down.
Chong
The competition is on. Let's go.
Let's go.
Athletics can only get better.
Mai Sichong on track 7 from Southern Sport University is far ahead.
It seems that the outcome of the match is no longer in doubt.
Congratulations to winner Mai Sichong
from Southern Sport University.
This is the seventh championship in his career.
Bless him to keep this level.
Wish him Phelps of China one day.
Mom
You've been in closed training for so long.
After that,
will you go home first, or go home first?
Of course.
But
please take me somewhere before going home.
OK.
What happened to my son?
He trained for so long.
He hasn't been home for months.
After that, his girlfriend comes to his mind first.
You are so heartless.
Mom
That's because I haven't seen Weiwei for a long time.
The management of the provincial team is very strict.
I can't get my phone.
She didn't answer even when I called her.
So I have to...
All right. Hurry up.
Put your luggage in that trunk.
Hurry up.
Sorry.
The number you dialed is power off.
Mom
She...
Her phone is off.
Off?
Could she
be angry with you?
No.
Right.
It's impossible for them to close the bookstore.
Is something wrong?
Mom, take it.
You drive, and I'll go back by myself.
Take care.
Chong, you're back?
What happened to Mei Weiwei?
Tell me.
Weiwei...
What happened?
Where is she?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
She didn't even tell me she was moving away with her parents.
I'm worried about her, too.
This is
the last message she sent me when she left.
She told me to pay attention to your emotions.
What did you say to him?
I...
In fact, before you went to the provincial team,
there was something wrong with Weiwei's health.
She didn't say anything.
She chose to endure it alone.
She didn't send me a farewell message
until she left.
Remember
to tell Mai Sichong
not to look for me.
Please tell me
that she must have been here later, right?
Right.
But I don't know where they live.
Can you
contact them for me?
I must find her.
They did come here
the other day.
Look.
These flowers are from them.
They won't come any time soon.
So it's no use
staying here,
isn't it?
In fact,
before you went to the provincial team,
there was something wrong with Weiwei's health.
Why do you have a raincoat on?
It's static electricity.
I just touched my hair.
Weiwei
You're really a Pikachu.
Your static electricity is stronger than others.
Mai Sichong
Goodbye.
I visited my aunt in Nanxiao Road today.
I'm so sad
that my aunt's flower shop can't continue to open.
These flowers are from them.
Weiwei
Look, how beautiful the flowers are.
Yes.
The recent flowers are of good quality.
There're just a few orders. I'll deliver them later.
You? Can you?
Mom, dad, don't worry.
(Wait for meet again.)
Mei Weiwei, open the door.
I don't wanna see you.
Just leave.
You don't open the door?
So I'll break the door.
I'll shock you if you don't leave.
Come on.
It's not the first time anyway.
I don't like you anymore.
You only know swimming in the provincial team.
Where were you when my electricity lost control?
I'm sorry.
It doesn't make sense.
Mai Sichong, do you know
that I left quietly to make you feel better?
I don't need a boyfriend
who can't be with me at all.
Do you understand?
Mai Sichong
Let's break up.
Please leave.
Mai Sichong
Why are you still so disobedient after entering the provincial team?
They all call me now to look for you.
Do you know that you are going back to training in advance?
You already have a bad record.
Who can help you if you're late now?
They have all set off.
You take a taxi back
right now.
I got it, Ms. Peipei.
It's my fault.
Sorry.
You...
Weiwei
Do you remember
the night we were at the resort?
You said to me
that no matter how imperfect I am,
you can accept,
understand
and tolerate me.
I know
I
still have many shortcomings.
But I promise you
that I will be there for you
as long as you need me.
But even doctor
can't diagnose my constitution.
We can't be together at all.
I'm like a bomb.
I've had enough bad luck.
I don't want you to be unlucky with me.
You still have your own life.
What if
my electricity gets more and more out of control
and one day it hurts you?
And what if
my electricity can't disappear all my life?
Don't think too much.
(Three years later.)
All right.
This is what we'll talk about in class today.
Let's turn the textbook to page 82.
Is Mr. Lin here, please?
Here is you takeout.
Please preview the textbook.
Hello.
Why are you here?
To deliver to you something.
No sugar and less milk.
Thanks.
That's Mai Sichong, right?
Mai Sichong
May I ask you a question?
What do you wanna do most next?
Most wanna do...
Propose.
I heard you and your girlfriend have a very good relationship.
Wish you a successful proposal.
That must be.
After all, I have never failed.
Well, thank you for accepting our interview.
That's all for today's interview.
I'm reporter Li Daixi.
Please sort out the materials when you go back.
What's wrong?
I gave you my first exclusive interview.
But you do this to me?
You changed the outline of the interview for no reason.
She may not wanna go public.
But I want.
Do you know how many girls in the school like me?
I do this to protect her, you know?
All right.
You're lovey-dovey.
You'd better prepare more gift money for me.
By the way.
You must remember
to give her this.
What's this?
It's not your business and just give it to her.
Five.
Three, two, one.
Zero point nine.
Chong
You're the winner again. Congratulations.
Daixi
The parents
who pick up their children today are late.
As a coach, I can't leave first.
Don't be angry.
Again?
Please.
OK.
Let's go.
Bye.
Take care.
Don't worry.
Don't forget to give her that.
OK.
Don't be so unreliable.
Don't move.
Chong
We gotta go.
Goodbye.
Take care.
Let's go.
Mai Sichong
Long time no see.
How are you?
I was going to watch your play today.
But because of the lecture, I didn't go.
What's the result?
As usual.
Still the first.
By the way, I forgot to tell you that I am now
studying medicine.
Then you'll be a schoolboy for a long time.
And
didn't Junjun come to see you play?
What's up?
You didn't contact her?
Junjun will be in charge of the company.
She's quite busy and she doesn't have time to watch me play.
Cell phone.
What?
I'm gonna see Weiwei. Goodbye.
Hello.
I'm Xia Rui.
Mai Sichong
Why do you ask me to be here?
Stop asking.
I will instruct you to meet me remotely.
OK.
This place is so beautiful.
Don't be distracted from anything else.
Don't you even ask me about the ranking?
I'll prepare for postgraduate entrance exam.
Anyway,
you won't get any other ranking except the first one.
I'm just so perfect that you don't even have a sense of crisis.
How about the reexamine?
The first one.
You'll be my exclusive rehabilitator after graduating. I'll hang up.
(See you later.)
So childish.
Mai Sichong?
You...
This is the one you have prepared in the water.
Open it.
I know
this may come as a surprise to you
when you see this.
But I've figured it out.
I've made many decisions.
I think
the most correct decision
is that I choose you.
I've wondered countless times
if it's too early
or too soon.
But I think
I'll always choose you
as long as you are by my side.
I...
If you think it's too soon,
that's okay.
No matter it is one year,
three years,
or ten years,
I'll always wait for you.
Do you wanna make me wait so long?
Mai Sichong
I do.
You're my one
in my life.
Pikachu
The end.