=Sparkle Love
EP07=
Fan Zengxiang, the former chairman of
Students' Association Union of our school,
embezzled the public funds of the union.
The circumstances were bad
and he was relieved
of his post as chairman
of the Students' Association Union.
A fine was imposed...
It's ok.
I know about the thing about
chairman of Students' Association Union.
You have done a good job.
Come on in the future!
Thanks.
Okay, I still have classes.
I'm leaving.
Thanks, Mr. Peng.
Why didn't she give me the message?
According to this inspection report,
he is recovering well.
But it is still somewhat difficult
to recover to the state before the injury.
Don't worry, auntie.
I can do it myself.
Is this Junjun?
Yes.
She has grown up.
I remember her as a little girl.
By the way,
perhaps you do not know that
Mai Sichong and Junjun
are in the same university.
Which class are you in?
I'm
in the Class of Rehabilitation.
Then
you and Mei Weiwei are in
the same dormitory, right?
Yes.
When you were kids,
you two played together every day.
Since you moved,
Junjun
didn't have a playmate anymore.
Why don't I remember?
When did it happen?
What can you remember?
You only remember some funny things.
Then,
mom, auntie,
I'll go back to school first.
Don't you go back to school, Mai?
You can go together!
OK, let's go.
Be careful on the road.
OK.
Be careful.
Bye!
Junjun,
your phone is upside down.
Thanks.
By the way, Junjun,
are you supposed to
have class at this time?
You
want to know Weiwei's
class schedule, right?
Are you two familiar?
I
I am completely not familiar with her.
How can I be familiar
with her?
What's this?
This is
for you.
For me?
Thanks.
Pretty cool.
It looks like me,
right?
I make it!
Why are you here?
To return your gloves.
Thanks.
Great!
Weiwei,
I heard that the misappropriation
of public funds by Fan was exposed.
Did you do it?
No.
This is a long story.
I'll tell you next time.
Now tell him
who helped you deal with that man.
Well,
it's Mr. Peng.
Thanks to him, our club can
apply successfully this time.
Really?
What?
Who?
Mr. Peng
OK, stop talking about that.
Let's talk about the club activities.
I have ideas!
Mei Weiwei
What's wrong?
Weiwei,
what's up with him?
He is crazy.
Come,
come on!
Let me show you.
I wrote 3941 words.
Look!
This is the first one.
OK.
That's all for today.
Class is over.
Don't miss it when you pass by.
Please have a look.
The first Massage Club
Impart professional skills selflessly.
You can learn it well.
Look,
have a look!
Weiwei,
We're almost done.
Let's go outside.
Hi
Have a look at the first
Physical Massage Club.
We impart professional skills for free.
Hi,
please give me a flyer.
Here you are.
Mr. Peng
You can't call on others here.
You should go to the gym.
There are more people.
Weiwei,
I bought you milk tea.
Thank you.
Mr. Peng,
milk tea is bad for health
because there is too much sugar in it.
Mr. Peng,
I haven't thanked you for
helping us with the club last time.
What?
You're Mr. Peng?
Hello, Mr. Peng.
We'll move to the gym and hand out flyers.
Thanks.
Mr. Peng,
thanks.
Be careful.
It's free!
Have a look!
Have a look at the Physical Massage Club.
It's free.
Free!
You don't reply to my message
but to distribute the flyer here.
You look busy.
I was too busy in class just now,
so I forgot to reply.
You won't get angry
because of this, will you?
How could I?
You don't know how to send out flyers.
Why are you so stupid?
It's like you have a way.
It is easy for you to say!
In your way,
it can be finished after graduation.
Look at me!
Hurry up!
250 people
Mai,
thank you very much!
If I can be like you,
the recovery of Massage Club
will be around the corner.
It's a piece of cake.
I just don't want her
to delay my training.
Weiwei,
are you going to train with Mr. Mai?
Can you swim?
No. Ding Yi has something else recently.
I help him about the timekeeping.
OK,
stop talking about this.
Let's think about the
club activities first.
Yes.
Club activities?
What can a Massage Club do?
About this,
I have already thought about it.
You'd better come down.
Let me think about the
content of the activity.
That's ok.
Weiwei,
Mr. Peng has helped us
with the club application.
Stop it.
What's the relationship between
Peng Pai and club application?
He exposed Fan Zengxiang,
which made our club run smoothly.
He exposed?
It was he who exposed Fan Zengxiang.
Actually...
Also,
our classmate Mai Sichong
helped us a lot today.
He is the second hero.
Do it by yourselves!
I have something else. I'll go.
Mr. Mai,
I'll give you some massage tickets later.
I don't need.
Yuxin,
is there any strawberry cake?
I'm sorry.
He bought the last piece.
It's you again!
You bought my strawberry cake!
Your strawberry cake?
You call it
and see it responds to you or not.
You...
What's wrong? In a bad mood again?
Are you still having trouble
with my brother's girlfriend?
Don't talk nonsense here.
She's not your brother's girlfriend.
Do you mind?
I advise you to give up Chong.
You are homely.
There is no chance.
You're ugly!
Your body looks like a frog,
and you look like a squirrel!
You...
So what?
I tell you,
I'm not interested in Mai
Sichong for a long time.
Weiwei doesn't like being gossip outside,
so you'd better not talk nonsense here.
She'll be upset.
You haven't used the fork, have you?
It's used by you.
How can I use it?
I reward it to you.
What time is your activity?
I'll come to have a look after work.
Ok.
What are you doing?
How can this be conductive?
So what?
Do you want to hold hands again?
Do you want to hold my hands?
Who want to hold your hands?
You asked me to come and help you.
Well...
Do what others ask you to do?
Someone asks you to set up
a club, and you set up a club?
Someone gives you
milk tea, then you drink it?
Can you have your own opinion?
You ask me to help you,
but you're blaming me.
Forget it.
I'm not in the mood.
Why are you angry?
Why am I angry?
Mei Weiwei, I tell you
that the club is actually...
what's the matter with you?
Don't worry.
It's just the days that all girls have.
Come on!
Hurry up!
What's up?
Put me down.
I'm not feeling well.
Be careful.
I don't seem to
feel that bad anymore.
Weiwei
Daixi
What are you doing?
She
is not feeling well.
I send her back.
Thanks.
Weiwei,
sit down.
I'll make some brown sugar water for you.
Daixi,
are you back?
Why did you even change
the style of the sheets?
I think it's pretty cute recently.
So I change it.
Come on.
Drink the brown sugar water.
Thanks.
It's hot.
The affections you get by
electrifying are not reliable.
Falling in love at first electrifying
is really...
Junjun, you're back.
She just...
Did she hear me?
It's OK. I don't think she heard you.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Don't worry.
It can't be true?
I was electrified by her again?
Whatever. Sleep.
Weiwei,
You haven't told me
what our theme is today?
Isn't this clear?
Disco dancing in a healthy way!
Disco dancing in a healthy way?
But we can't drink wines.
Soda water...
Why are you here?
I'm here to see if I can help.
Isn't this syrup?
I tell you
this is very bad for health.
It contains food flavors
and food colorants.
I'm going to hang
up the fairy lights first.
Mr. Mai,
have a try.
Add some wolfberry.
Wolfberry?
Why hadn't I thought about it?
Give it to me.
Thanks.
You are not tall enough to hang it.
Who is short?
You really...
Li Daixi,
I wonder why you move things with me?
You just want to exploit me.
No.
It's your honor
to help me carry things.
You...
You can see clearly now
that's me.
So,
don't fall in love with me.
I fall in love with you?
Do you know the name
of Zhang Ziyi's daughter?
What?
Xingxing,
please wake up!
You...
It's not bad.
No, thanks.
Everybody,
next,
we are going to welcome
the most important activity
of our health-preserving party,
health-preserving lecture.
Next I need a volunteer.
If you are interested,
please step forward.
Who would like to be the volunteer?
He!
Let's welcome Ding Yi!
Great!
Well.
Please lie here.
Today I will tell you about
an acupuncture point called Shenshu.
It is between the ribs.
Find this position,
and see if his kidney is healthy.
Press it.
Mr. Lin now presses
Shenshu Point for this student.
He screams so violently.
It can be seen that
the kidney is not good.
What?
Li Daixi, are you on purpose?
Relax.
Pay attention to this technique,
and the strength.
Mr. Peng, why do you come here?
You can share it later.
I'm going back to work overtime.
Thanks.
Actually, you don't have to come here.
You're so busy.
Your things are important for me.
If it wasn't for my internship,
I would play with you until dawn.
By the way,
I didn't thank you for
your help with the club.
Thank you.
It doesn't matter.
That's what I should do.
I'm leaving.
OK.
Bye!
I have something to
tell you. Come with me.
What are you doing?
What do you want to say?
You have to come out to say?
I ask you,
is there anything between
you and Peng Pai?
What's the matter?
Answer my question directly.
Answer what?
What are you doing?
Chong,
we don't see anything.
Go on,
go on.
Not in your right mind.
In such a flurry,
she must like Peng Pai.
Okay, Ding Yi.
Thank you all for participating
in our lecture today.
Then let's continue our activities.
Come on!
Good.
Your massage skill is good.
Thank you.
OK.
Then you continue to
play. I'm going over there.
Li Daixi,
let me give you a massage.
I don't need.
Hi,
let me help you.
Are you in Class of Rehabilitation, too?
Hello, I'm Xia Rui.
Thank you.
The Class of Rehabilitation is
dancing for health preservation.
I want to join them, too.
Come on!
Hurry up!
You're the only one left. Come along, too!
OK.
You are not busy at all.
You still have time to
steal things of home.
How did your mother teach
you when she was alive?
Wang Meiyun,
don't mention my mother.
I'm back. Anything to eat?
Where's the table?
Is the house robbed?
Thanks to your sweetheart,
the mahogany table I just bought
was thrown away.
I think she wants to tear down this home.
Zhang Yuxin,
what do you want to do?
She threw the table
left by my mother first.
If you want to protect her,
then
throw me away.
Weiwei,
trouble you to clean up.
Weiwei, we'll go first.
OK. Bye!
Be careful.
See you, Weiwei.
Go back.
Mr. Mai
Weiwei
Why don't you get up?
It's done!
There are still people inside.
What's wrong with your leg?
What's wrong with the door?
The door is locked.
What to do then?
I'll call Daixi.
I gave Daixi my cell phone.
How about yours?
Mine
is at Ding Yi's hand.
what should we do then?
Wait a minute.
Maybe someone will come soon.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Li Daixi,
You're not hungry, are you?
Why do you eat so much?
I'm here to supervise you.
As an athlete, you should
pay attention to your diet.
Can you stop talking about me?
I plan to bring many dishes for Chong.
Are they going to be okay?
Is your knee
okay?
Almost well.
There should be no problem.
Where you've been injured before
is in the knee, right?
No.
I just knocked here.
Don't cheat me.
You want me to electrify you,
because you want your knee
injury to recover soon, right?
How did you know?
Anyway,
I know it.
You haven't said how your knee hurt.
I'll tell you,
but don't tell anyone else.
OK.
Before,
I had an accident
to save a child.
I fainted at the time.
Later, it's said that
someone saved me.
My knee was sprained at the time.
I didn't expect you to be so brave.
Do you have any secrets?
It's not a secret in fact.
But you know that
my electrified physique is so special
that it is impossible to
talk to others everywhere.
Since I was a child, I thought
this physique was a troublesome thing
because it never brought me good luck.
But you know what?
I saved a person with my electricity,
and since then I've felt that
electrified physique is cool.
You used to
babble around me
about my electrified physique.
I was a little nervous at that time,
so I yelled at you.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.