If you're hurt this much,
we should do something
to put them in a difficult situation.
What’s your idea?
Keep it safe. Someday,
it will come in handy for you.
HYDRANGEA PLANTING GUIDE
You can't run away from me.
I'm the father of your child after all.
It's just a matter of time
before the secret is out.
Where did you keep the rings, Dao?
Please show them to my mom.
Wow.
They're really lovely.
You have a good eye.
I won't lose
my girlfriend and my child to him.
I don't want him as my son-in-law either!
If the groom is gone,
there will be no wedding.
Wow.
Can I come in?
Please come in.
Oh, I'll change the bedsheets for you.
I already did that.
Who gave this to you?
It was Miang.
Does it look good?
What were you signaling to me
earlier today?
Is there more to your marriage
with Dao than it seems?
Yes.
Can you tell me about it?
I'm not the father of Dao's child.
I thought so.
And are you going to marry her
just because you feel bad
that the child will be fatherless?
Hey. Don't you think
you're sacrificing too much?
That child actually has a father.
- You know him?
- Yes.
And you've just met him.
It's the man named Puwin, who we were
eating with at Aunt Ploy's house.
And I was certain this wedding
would never happen, so I didn't tell you.
I'm so sorry.
And does Ms. Ploy know about that?
Aunt Ploy didn't believe me and Miang
because now
she's dating Puwin.
I heard about it,
but I don't think I'll go.
Why, Lee?
The reunion wouldn't be fun without you.
What about the best female entrepreneur?
Did she respond to the invitation?
She did.
That's why I'm asking you
if you really won't go.
Why? What are you trying to say?
Ploysaeng noted that
she'd bring a plus one.
Insiders say that she might
introduce her young boyfriend to everyone.
Lee. Are you listening?
What are you going to do?
Did you change your mind and will come?
Since you just promoted
the event highlights like that,
I would go even if I was sick
and had to carry an oxygen tank with me.
See you there.
How dare you treat me
like I’m nothing, Pu.
You'll get what you wish for.
Yes, Mr. Pu. No problem at all.
I'll tell him to stand by at the spot.
Can I give him your number?
This number, right?
Got it.
Do you want me to get it done today?
Today is our best shot.
When you're done eating,
go wait for him at Camellia.
Let's add more beans.
Go ahead.
- More lime?
- The smell of fermented fish…
It's mouthwatering.
Wait, let me add the crabs first.
- Do you eat this?
- You can add all of it. Don't worry.
I won't hold back anymore.
- Another one?
- Let's add another for the rich taste.
I wouldn't trade this for a steak.
Keep the fermented fish coming.
- Come on.
- Here.
Give me another spoonful.
I'll give you two.
What’s all the excitement about?
Do you want to join
our Som Tum party, Dao?
I shouldn't.
I could have an upset stomach later.
I forgot that you're pregnant.
I bought these for nothing then.
It's alright. You can join us with those.
I'll put them on the dishes.
I didn't buy any for you.
I didn't know you were here.
That's okay.
I want to have teacher's Som Tum so bad.
I'm sure you'll ask for more.
I'll wait there then.
HBD, PARIT
MY HEART IS RIGHT HERE
What? Where did the heart go?
You don’t look as fresh as usual today.
I had something on my mind last night,
so I didn’t get much sleep.
Then, please let me drive you to the event
and drop you off right there.
That way, you can sit back and relax.
- Thank you.
- Please.
HUMAN RESOURCE MANAGER
PARKING SPOT
How long was I asleep?
Just a while.
Where are we?
The parking lot of my condo.
There is still some time left,
so I decided to park here
for you to get some rest.
Thank you so much. I feel better now.
Would you like to go have some coffee
in my room before going to the event?
We still have time.
That would be nice. But I'm not
bothering you too much, right?
I'm glad to do it.
Next time,
please let me cook something for you.
Do you cook?
Well, if I didn't work at Tharnthong,
I would have been a chef.
If you put it that way,
I might have to find
some time to try your food.
Thank you.
With pleasure.
If you want to try anything,
you can put it on a list for me.
Thanks.
You seem more lively now.
Maybe that's because I've taken a nap.
Can I ask you
what was on your mind?
I've made a decision.
I'm going to call off
Dao and Parit's wedding.
Why?
I had a chance to talk to Ms. Maratee,
Parit's mother. She wasn’t entirely
on board with their marriage.
She doesn't believe
that Parit is the father?
She wants us to take a DNA test first,
to make sure it's fair to everyone.
This might be a bit insulting to Miss Dao.
Anyone would suspect it.
They weren't even dating,
and she suddenly got pregnant.
We're shocked.
Ms. Maratee doesn't live here,
so she must be even more shocked.
That's true.
- Oh, sorry. I'm sorry.
- Uh…
But to be honest,
I somehow agree with that decision.
Sometimes we can't trust people we know.
He might not be the father,
but pretend to be for his own benefit.
There are so many cases
like that on the news.
Well, didn't Miss Dao
prepare many things for the wedding?
I heard that she's made
an appointment with a tailor.
That's right. I should tell Dao
to cancel the appointment.
You can't backtrack that easily!
I won't listen to any of that!
Why do we have to take the test
when Parit has confirmed
that he's the father?
What more do you want?
I've spent a day with her today.
If she didn't want me to marry Parit,
she would have told me directly!
I'll go ask her right now.
How was it?
Did she take it well?
She insists she'll have a wedding.
Please don't worry.
You did what you thought was best.
Let's go to the event.
I won't be able to stay long.
Right.
Hello.
Where are you?
Gas station. I'm about to do it.
- No need to do it anymore.
- Why?
It won't be necessary. Come back.
It's easy for you to say.
What about my payment?
I'll pay you half of it, okay?
It's not your time to die yet,
you lucky bastard.
What's up.
Did Miss Dao call you?
She didn't. Why?
Ms. Ploy called her and said that
she wanted to call off the wedding.
Really?
Wait. Why so? Do you know?
I couldn't hear it clearly.
But Miss Dao sounded really angry.
She's going to talk to your mom.
Weird. Why would Aunt Ploy want to cancel
it if she was the one organizing it?
Then, the plan
to expose Puwin would be ruined.
Let's talk when I'm home. Please go
take a look at Dao and Mom for me.
Right.
Why didn't you tell me to my face?
You don't want me to marry Parit?
Dao, calm down and listen to me.
If you're certain Parit is the father,
then there's no need to worry.
It's just a matter of time.
You will marry him anyway.
Then why would we have to wait?!
Or do you believe
that I didn't have only Parit?
Did someone
falsely accuse me behind my back?
If you're talking about me,
then the answer is no.
I don't believe you.
I don't believe that Parit is the father
either, but I didn't want to say it.
- Miang!
- Stop, Dao!
Don't use violence in here.
I don't like it!
You love her more than me.
Everyone loves Miang!
Not a single person wants me to be happy!
I… That's not it, Dao.
No one is stopping you
from marrying Parit.
We just have to wait
for a DNA test result. That's it.
I've prepared everything for the wedding!
It can all be postponed, right?
There's nothing to fear.
Or do you already know who the father is?
Fine. If this is what you want,
just don’t cry over it later.
Did you ask Ms. Ploy
to call off the wedding, teacher?
I didn't.
It was Ms. Ploy who asked me
to postpone the wedding.
You can't do this to me!
I feel guilty towards Ms. Maratee.
I don't understand.
I've been thinking about this.
I have to say that I'm not happy at all.
I was worried about you.
I wanted to help you.
But it's like we're just exploiting Parit.
How are we exploiting him
if he's willing to marry me?!
That's because he felt bad for you!
But he's the father of my child.
Stop lying to everyone!
Parit told me everything.
What's really going on?
Ms. Ploy told Miss Dao that teacher
isn't on board with this marriage.
But teacher said
Ms. Ploy told her to say that.
Who started this? I'm confused now.
Could it be that
Aunt Ploy suspects something,
so she wants to
postpone the wedding until it's clear.
If only that were true.
Um.
Why do you seem to doubt it?
I don't know.
Ms. Ploy and Puwin
are inseparable right now.
It's basically them announcing
they're officially dating.
She must trust him more than us.
But if Aunt Ploy actually likes him,
there's nothing we can do about it.
But know that it's better than letting it
happen without telling her anything.
Yes.
Miang. I'm stuffed.
Why did you have to eat that much?
But you were the one
who wanted Ice cream, right?
Watch out, Miang!
I don't know what she plans to do next.
I'm sure she'll go back to Puwin.
Get inside.
Why are you here?
Don't you care if anyone sees you?
Let them see me. Why would I care?
No need to hide anymore.
Relax. What happened to you?
Aunt Ploy canceled my wedding.
How am I supposed to react to that?
Everything is proceeding
as per our original plan.
In the end,
no one is truly sincere with you
except me.
We're made for each other.
What? I forgot my medicine?
We'll do it on the reunion night.
Do you think you can do your part in time?
Are you scared?
What the hell are you playing at?
Why did you go through my stuff?
I was just looking for some painkillers.
And who'll carry it out?
Will you?
The last assignment
before the job is done.
We can't mess it up.
Oh, Miss Dao?
Are you here
to pick up the dress for Ms. Ploy?
It's not my job.
Here you are, Miss Dao.
We have a lot of beautiful
maternity dress designs for events.
I'll just browse for ideas then.
Please feel free.
I'm here to pick up Ms. Ploysaeng's dress.
Ah. Ms. Ploysaeng informed us.
Are you Miss Mirin?
- Yes.
- Over here please.
Aoy, can you get Ms. Ploy's dress for me?
‪-Good evening.
‪-Long time no see.
Ploy. Come and register here.
Please.
- Aom. How are you doing?
- I'm doing well.
Ah, right here?
- Don't forget to update your phone number.
- Right.
Okay.
Are you doing well?
Hanging in there.
- Let's talk later, Aom.
- Alright.
Fon?
Fon. Are you here too?
How could you do this?!
What did I do?
You're fooling my friend!
You can charm any woman all you want,
but not Ploysaeng, my best friend!
Wait, Fon.
You took it too far, Pu.
When will your ambition stop?!
You were just a poor country boy
who Lee took in.
Now you have a job and a high position.
Isn't that enough for you?
Why do you have to
trick my friend for more money?!
Fon…
Are you drunk?
Whoa. All I can smell is alcohol.
Hey, if you can't quit drinking,
you shouldn't come to an event like this
and embarrass yourself.
Please forgive us. Sorry.
Let's cool down outside with me.
- Please forgive us. I'm so sorry.
- Pu.
- I'm not drunk.
- Sorry.
- Excuse us.
- Let go of me, Pu.
- I'm not drunk.
- Excuse me.
What's the commotion?
I can hear it from inside the room.
Are you the one who staged it?
Do you like Pu that much?
Why do I need to tell you?
No matter how good you are,
you can easily be ruined because of a man.
I can give him to you, at a cost.
Pu already told me.
Good. So I don't have to say it again.
Meet me at my house after the party,
alone.
Pu, let go. It hurts.
Why did you do that?
You were humiliating me.
Pu, I'm sorry. I did it for you.
For me?
It's like you were burying me alive.
Did Ms. Lee tell you to do it?
Did she?
Tell me the truth
if you still want the money from me.
Lee…
Lee threatened me,
saying that if I didn't do it,
she'd fire you.
Even if you didn't do it,
she would do anything
to get rid of me anyway!
Ploy.
Long time no see.
Ploy, I… I'm sorry.
Forget it, Fon.
I knew
that Panalee
would do something
to humiliate me in front of people.
You knew, yet you brought Pu here.
Some things are worth the sacrifice.
Do you really like my brother?
And would you mind
having me as your sister-in-law?
Ploy. You are my best friend.
How am I your best friend?
You left and cut off all contact with me.
When you were in trouble,
you didn't even ask me for help.
Don't feel bad for me,
and stop letting Lee abuse you.
When are you going back home?
Tomorrow.
Then, before you go back,
let's have a meal.
I want to get to know your brother better.
What's with you?
Why do you have to call repeatedly?
I'm talking to my friends.
This is not what we talked about.
I thought you liked surprises.
I paved the way for you
to buy Ms. Ploy's land easily.
Where did Fon come from?
Don't tell me she came by herself.
I told her to come.
I missed my friend.
Don't you miss your sister at all?
You were trying to humiliate me.
Yes. That's because
you were challenging me.
Do you think I'm not the vengeful kind?
You chose the wrong woman to mess with.
You'll be reminded
that we're built differently.
If I can groom you,
I can destroy you as well.
Be prepared for it.
Enjoy it while you can.
Tonight, you'll smile for the last time.
You finally showed up.
Are you drunk?
I thought we were going to talk
while you were sober and fully conscious.
What I'm going to say to you
is short, and easy.
There's no need to be that sober.
Good.
Tell me about your offer.
Are you in a rush?
You want a man as soon as possible?
But the price Pu offered
is quite interesting.
When it's that much higher
than the evaluated price,
you'd be stupid
if you were not interested.
If I sell the land
connected to Tharnthong market to you,
how can I know for sure
that you would never
mess with the two of us again?
The two of you?
You were really born
to be my nemesis, weren't you?
You took Aran from me before.
Now you're taking Pu from me!
In the end, I don't get to
have my men with me.
Everyone leaves me for you.
I didn't take Puwin from you.
Even if he has me,
he'll still be your brother.
If you let him live the life he wants,
he would come back to
take care of you like he did before.
Pu? Take care of me?
I have no one. Don't you understand?
I'm all alone.
I'll die alone.
My sister and my friends
all have their families.
I'm all on my own.
Nobody wants me in their life!
I saw you were drinking a lot
since you were at the party.
Let's talk later then.
You can't go anywhere.
Don't think you can trade a piece of land
just to keep Pu for yourself that easily.
I raised him.
I gave him his future.
I gave him his education.
All of that can't be bought with money!
Pu would never be able to repay me.
He belongs to me. Don't you get it?!
You're too drunk!
We can't understand each other like this.
Hey. I think…
we should talk about a deal next time.
I said you can't go anywhere!
It's all because of you,
that I have to be alone
for the rest of my life.
You took my fiancé from me!
You destroyed my life!
I'll kill you, Ploysaeng!
It ended a long time ago!
Why can't you move on from the past?!
Panalee.
How could you do this to me?!
Don't.
Stop! Don't!
Stop the ceremony!
Ms. Lee.
Puwin is the boy I took in
and I won't allow him
to marry the person I didn't choose.
Mark my words. I own your life.
You have everything because of me.
You have to serve me
until the day I die, not another woman.
His family is poor and I felt bad.
He likes to tell
the girls he met that he's my brother.
He probably wants to
upgrade his social status.
Are you ashamed that I called you out
in front of everyone?
Why would you? If it wasn't for me,
would you be able to
be the manager by yourself?
You've completely destroyed
the reputation of my market!
You ungrateful bastard!
Miss Dao?
Are you on duty or something?
Why aren't you sleeping?
A sound woke me up,
so I'm just here to take a look.
Where are you going?
Can you drive for me?
What did you say?
A threatened miscarriage is a possibility
Is there a chance of miscarriage?
From the pelvic exam and ultrasound,
it appears the bleeding has stopped.
Other than bleeding,
do you feel any lower abdominal pain?
Just a little bit.
Please don't worry too much,
as stress may have an effect on the baby.
Please wait for the doctor's
prescription for a moment.
Yes.
What did the doctor say?
The baby is safe.
I'm happy for you.
I thought you'd be disappointed.
You must want me to miscarry so bad.
Why would I want that?
The baby didn't do anything wrong.
I'm glad
that you care about your child
and didn't drive here yourself.
You even asked me for help.
It doesn't matter who the father is.
What’s important is that
the baby is your flesh and blood.
If I were you, I'd do my best
to take care of the baby.
I wouldn’t let them grow up
without a complete family, like we did.
Don’t associate me with you.
What smells so bad?
Ms. Lee! Ms. Lee!
Ms. Lee!
KHAOSUAY
Mr. Pu! Where are you?
I'm at my condo. What do you want?
Ms. Lee has been shot dead.
How is that possible? What happened?
What should I do, Mr. Pu?
Call the police.
Could you please do that for me?
No. I'm not home.
And you're the one who
discovered the body. You need to do it.
Right.
Miang. Why is the police here?
To charge Ms. Ploy with
murdering Ms. Lee by gunshot.
How is that possible?
Ms. Ploy went to
Ms. Lee's house last night
and they got into an argument
that escalated into a fight.
Do they have the evidence
that Aunt Ploy shot Ms. Panalee dead?
They said that the CCTV footage
captured the murder.
When I was able to escape,
I immediately drove home
and didn't go back in.
But the CCTV footage
covered the area
and showed that
you went back in to shoot Ms. Panalee.
That's not true. That can't have been me.
If that's the case,
can I look at the footage?
Yes. Then, I'd like to have you
come to the station
for questioning as well.
No problem.
But I'll have to contact my lawyer first.
Please feel free.
If I were home,
this wouldn't have happened.
No need to blame yourself, Pu.
No one wants
something like this to happen.
Mom.
I think this house is cursed.
Two people have died in it.
We should sell it.
Are you crazy? Who would want to buy it?
We would be forced to sell it cheap.
How about this?
Let Pu stay here.
Think of it as a perk of your position.
Alright, Pu?
Pu. Are you scared?
I'm not.
I'll help take good care of this house.
Stay and help our business for
a long time, and I'll give you this house.
Thank you.
We're relatives anyway.
Letting you stay
is far better than selling it cheap.
What you said is right.
Pu.
Help our company, and don't leave us.
Right.
- Mom…
- Your sister is gone.
Thanks.
Is the police done with the questioning?
Yes, sir.
Did you go on a trip again?
Can we really count on you to
look after the house? Should we fire you?
I've got a two-night
hotel voucher in Pattaya.
Do you want a vacation?
Me?
Are you allowing me to go on a trip?
But you should tell Ms. Lee in advance,
since the voucher might be date-specific.
What day is it?
I was the one who allowed
Khaosuay to go on vacation.
From this CCTV footage,
can you confirm
that it’s really you, Ms. Ployseang?
Yes.
Then let's look at the next clip.
Stop! Don't!
This shocking murder
happened inside the home of Ms. Panalee,
a major entrepreneur who owns
Tharnthong Market. It's the second murder
that's happened inside this house,
not long after the first.
The news doesn't seem to talk about
Ms. Ploy being a suspect.
But I don't think it'll take long.
A famous businesswoman
murdering a competitor
would make headlines for weeks.
What did I just say?
Whoa.
The angle of this CCTV footage
isn't clearly showing her.
It’s just that
the dress is the same color,
and the design is similar.
This type of dress
isn't really hard to find.
And it's a high-angle view.
Those who don't know me
would think it was the same person.
But I'm the accused.
I knew at first glance that it wasn’t me.
The physique is not even similar to me,
and the movements are off.
Anyone could dress like this,
and claim that they're Ms. Ploysaeng.
Are you suggesting that
this murder was staged
to frame Ms. Ploysaeng?
Yes.
And the dress you wore in the clip,
was it purchased or tailor-made?
It was tailor-made.
Then It's very unlikely
someone else has the same dress.
Well, we'll have to
look further at the evidence.
CCTV footage
doesn't really show the fabric,
materials, and design details.
Right. I'll have the experts
look further into this.
Before the incident, had you two
had any arguments?
We had.
You came up with all these plans
just to get your inheritance back?
That's it?
Dad gave it to me
but Aunt Ploy took it from me,
so I had to take it back!
I think there's something fishy
about Mr. Aran's construction company.
INCOME OF 2020
Have you found something?
I had to adjust my plans quickly.
Did you wear gloves when you held the gun?
Very thoughtful of you. That way,
we'll have the clear fingerprints
of the murderer.
The general meeting of Tharnthong Group
reached a unanimous decision to appoint me
as the chief executive officer,
effective today.
A scumbag like you
won't be happy for long.
Choose the right time to be born.
Subtitle translation by: Anan Pratchayakul