MARIA CLARA AND IBARRA
THIS PROGRAM, WHICH IS ADAPTED
FROM THE NOVELS OF DR. JOSE P. RIZAL,
IS PRESENTED USING DRAMATIC ELEMENTS
TO CONNECT THE PRESENT AND THE PAST
IN A SPECIAL REIMAGINING OF THE NATIONAL
LITERATURE FILIPINOS ARE PROUD OF.
Forgive me, Uncle,
for dragging you into this problem.
But once the excommunication
punishment is lifted,
even the friars won't be able to stop me
and Maria from being together.
I have been telling you to try
and get along with them.
How else do you want me
to get along with them?
I seem to sense rage in your words.
If you really want
to be married to my daughter,
do not destroy your future
by rebelling against the friars.
We want to introduce you to
a young peninsulares…
A more deserving man for Maria Clara.
I would like you to meet our nephew,
Señor Alfonso Linares.
But I don't think it's right
to promise Maria to a man
you do not know full well.
Do you think I will put Maria at risk?
She is like a daughter to you.
Maria Clara is Tiago's only child.
And who do you think will
benefit from all of that?
Doña Maria Clara, for sure!
And her soon-to-be husband.
You are one big disaster!
Qualities that will only
bring trouble and shame to my life!
What did you say?
But those qualities
are also what I love about you.
I will not give up until I have proven
that I am worthy of your love.
This can't be, Klay.
The main characters of this story
are none other than Maria Clara and…
Sir Ibarra!
How did your conversation
with the Captain General go?
The outcome was very good.
I am Lucas, the brother of the man
killed by the derrick at your school.
PREVIOUSLY…
My condolences for your loss.
Mister, this is not enough compensation
for the death of my brother.
Is that so?
What about your brother's attempt
to murder Sir Ibarra?
What was that?
I am deeply saddened
by the death of your brother, mister.
But…
I already gave you a huge sum
as a donation.
Now, if you do not have a livelihood,
I can hire you in my school
or maybe I can…
I don't need a job, señor.
What I need is money as payment
for the life of my brother!
How demanding…
Mister, I don't mean any disrespect,
but I am aware
of your brother's motive to kill me.
So I should not even be obligated
to extend help to you.
It is best if you leave now…
and never come back.
I will never forget this night.
You have the nerve to be angry.
This is your brother's fault.
My gosh, sir.
Some people can be really opportunistic.
You can't blame him.
Desperate times
call for desperate measures,
especially when those in power continue
to enslave you and hinder your progress.
Thank you, Father.
Thank God your appetite is back.
I wonder what helped you get better.
Was it the medicine
prescribed by your doctor
or your confession and communion
with Father Salvi?
All right then.
I'll have them bring you
more food, all right?
Thank you, Father.
Lord…
I thank your kind heart
for letting Crisostomo and I
see each other again.
Please guide him
and give him enough strength
to get through all the challenges
that he is facing right now.
Amen.
I heard that the Captain General
did not stay long
at Captain Tiago's house.
He left yesterday to get back to Manila.
I'm sure that Father Damaso will be glad
that he won't have
to pay tribute to officials
who don't even like him.
What if he will make good
on his promise to Señor Ibarra
to lift his excommunication?
I'm sure that you and Father Damaso
will be put to shame
in front of the people.
Good morning, Curate.
And what are you doing here, Lucas?
Didn't I tell you that you are not allowed
to come here?
Your Reverence,
I came here to report Mr. Ibarra.
Leave us, Renato.
And what is it that you want
to tell me, Indio?
Instead of paying for damages
for my brother's death,
he only gave me a small amount
as a donation.
You should be thankful
he even gave you anything at all.
You Indios
are very opportunistic.
Forgive me, Curate.
I don't understand what you're saying.
All I want is to get justice
for what happened to my brother.
To what extent are you willing to go
to get the justice you want?
I will do anything
just to make that arrogant gentleman pay.
I think the Lord has heard my prayers.
Well then, I will support you.
Because I believe
that Crisostomo Ibarra needs to pay
for everything he did.
That will only happen
if we break his connection
to the Captain General
and to the other powerful officials
who support him.
It's not enough
that he is seen as a heretic.
He needs to go to prison
because he is a filibuster!
I want you to do something.
Arnis was already popular in this era?
Cool.
Impressive.
Ms. Klay.
Have you been there long?
A bit.
Sir, have you seen Sir Fidel lately?
Were you able to talk to him?
Did he tell you something about me?
My friend and I haven't seen
each other again.
Maybe he is busy with his business.
Why?
What does he need to tell me about you?
Señor, there are people looking for you.
Good morning, señor.
Good morning too.
This is a letter for you.
It came from the office
of the Captain General.
It has the signature
of His Highness, the Archbishop.
From the Archbishop?
What does it say?
Good news, Ms. Klay.
The Archbishop has already
lifted my excommunication
because of the Captain General's request.
I am no longer an outcast.
I can now marry Maria.
Thank you very much, señor.
Please tell the Captain General
that he is indeed a true friend.
I will.
Goodbye, señor and señorita.
Goodbye.
Father…
Maria!
What your auntie said was true.
-You are no longer sick.
-Yes, father.
That is why we are going to the church
to pray the novena and give Him thanks.
As you should. Very good.
Isabel, please take good care
of my daughter, all right?
I always do, my cousin.
Very well, dear. Let's go.
Maria, my angel!
Godfather.
Good morning, señor and señora.
It is truly a beautiful day.
Because today,
you are destined to meet someone
who will truly save you
from a cursed fate.
What is the señora
talking about, Godfather?
We have another companion
that I would like you all
and my goddaughter to meet.
Tiburcio, let him in.
There he is.
Doña Isabel, Captain Tiago, Maria Clara,
I want you all to meet
our relative from Spain!
Good morning, everyone.
Especially to you, Doña Maria Clara.
Here's your change, miss.
Can you really not love me back, miss?
Whatever! I don't have time for this!
I said, here's your change.
Thank you.
Apologies. I just spaced out.
Klay, let's focus on the real story,
which is Project Happy Ending
for Maria Clara and Ibarra.
Not for you.
You keep on seeing things.
Be careful next time you do
something again.
Once you are bound,
it's difficult to break free.
But if there is a reasonable price
in return,
is there anything else to lose?
I really am in a wet market.
Good morning, Sacristan Mayor.
Why were you talking to that man?
It's you again, you meddlesome woman.
You have a real temper.
I was just asking.
I'm just worried because that man
tried to extort money from us last night.
I was thinking
that he might do the same to you.
Maybe you had something to do
with the trouble he caused?
We should be the ones
asking you questions, miss.
Beloved Curate.
I was just asking
if you're up to something again.
If not, then that's good.
Bye.
Because honestly,
I don't want any trouble.
I will go ahead.
What demon possessed you
to have the audacity
to interrogate a disciple of God?
Forgive me.
We were not able to prepare anything.
We were not informed that you were coming.
Father, forgive me.
Señora, señores.
No need to ask forgiveness, Tiago,
because your families
will soon become one.
Because I want to pair up Alfonso
with Maria Clara.
Pair us up, Godfather?
Yes, my love.
You know, I saw in this bachelor
the character of a man deserving to be
with a princess like you.
And I want Alfonso to be your husband
instead of Crisostomo Ibarra.
Maria, why did you drop that?
You will have bad luck.
That is just a proverbial saying
of the Indios, señora.
So don't worry about it.
Can we talk in private, Godfather? Please.
Forgive me.
Godfather, forgive me,
but I cannot marry a man I do not know.
Maria,
why are you acting
as if this is new to you?
You are aware that many people
who get married
only meet for the first time
on the day of their wedding.
You are actually in a better situation
with Señor Linares
because you have a chance to talk
and get to know each other.
You will soon realize
that he is worthy to be your husband
instead of a violent mestizo
who hurts friars.
With all due respect, Godfather.
You cannot blame Crisostomo,
because you also angered him.
My goodness, Maria!
Did I not teach you
not to talk back to your elders?
Apologize to your godfather right away.
There's no need.
I understand Maria's hesitation.
But if she will give
Señor Linares a chance--
My decision is final.
I will only get married to Crisostomo.
Father, Auntie,
I will leave it up to you
to show our guests out.
Goodbye, Godfather.
Wait, Maria.
I will not allow your future
to be destroyed
by ending up with that man.
I'm sure your future will be dark
if you marry him.
You will have a better future
if you will marry Señor Linares.
You really never learn, woman.
What are you doing here near the church?
Were you spying on us?
It is obvious that I am just here
to buy things, right?
It just so happened that I saw your helper
escorting out the brother
of the yellow man.
Is there anything wrong
with a bereaved Indio asking for help
because of your good friend?
You are malicious!
Well, there you go.
It is clear then.
Why are you getting defensive?
Now, let go of me
because everyone is already
looking at you, Father.
Do you think these Indios scare me?
You are no longer under Maria's care.
She can no longer protect you.
And I will no longer let
your defamatory words pass!
Look at this woman!
She is worse than an animal.
She is a minion of the devil
who has done nothing
but disrespect the ways of this town
and prosecute the messengers of God!
And you, Father,
who should be making the decision for me.
What is your decision on this matter?
Why don't you get to know
Mr. Linares first?
Talk to each other so that
you two will get along.
Very good. Very good, Santiago!
Isabel, escort Maria Clara
and Mr. Linares to the balcony
so they can talk.
Yes, Father.
Let's go, my child.
Let's go.
Bring those to the home of the Chinese
and please make sure
that nothing gets broken.
Yes, señor.
My friend!
My suspicion was right.
You are busy and that's why
you are no longer able to see
how your good friend is doing.
Is there anything new with you, my friend?
Good news, my friend.
The archbishop
has lifted my excommunication.
This means that I can now
marry Maria Clara.
That's why I am going
to their home right now,
to share this news.
My friend…
Do you really love Maria?
Or perhaps…
you love another woman?
Like Ms. Klay, for example.
And what made you think that Ms. Klay is…
Yes, you are right.
It is true that she is lovely.
But she is just a good friend
who I treat like a younger sister.
So you better stop your teasing
because there is no other woman
I want to marry other than Maria Clara.
My goodness!
Why did you have to embrace me, my friend?
I am just happy, my friend,
that you are no longer
excommunicated, right?
-Yes.
-That's really good news, my friend!
That's true.
You better thank God
that I still have some forgiveness
and patience left.
May you all emulate my good nature
and not this woman's!
Just be thankful
that I don't have time
for people like you.
If you try to question my disciples again,
if you tell your friends about this,
your dear curate will do much worse things
to all of you.
Your dear curate
is more valuable than your life
and the lives of your loved ones
in this town.
Miss…
Thank you.
What I heard is true.
You are truly very beautiful.
I understand what you're trying to say
with your fan.
I know that you have a fiancé.
But he will not get in my way
because I am ready
to prove myself to you, señorita.
You do not mean anything to her,
young man.
I will not force you
to like me now, señorita.
Yes, I may not mean anything to you yet.
But the time will come
when you will see my worth.
My Maria Clara is not interested, son.
Now that we have met
and I have shown you how I feel…
You may go now, señor.
Again, good day to you, and goodbye.
Good morning, mister.
Good morning to you too.
Do we know each other?
You don't know me, but I know you.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Pedro.
Sisa is my wife.
I'm the father of Crispin and Basilio.
How come you only introduced yourself now?
Are you aware of what happened
to your wife and sons?
I only found out recently
because I just came back
from another province.
I was so surprised when I didn't
see my family in our house.
If I had not bumped into Pilosopo Tasyo,
I would not have found out
what happened to them.
Do not fret, mister.
I am looking for your sons.
Meanwhile, I had Ms. Sisa
taken to the hospice
to help her mind get better.
You may visit her there.
And if you want, I can have
my coachman take you there.
What else can she possibly do
if she's already crazy?
You will be able to help me better
if you buy our small farmland.
I can use the money to start a new life.
What kind of father and husband are you
if you only think about yourself
instead of your family?
Is there anything I can do
to bring back my wife's sanity?
Or to bring back my sons?
What do you want me to do?
To just cry about it?
Apologies, mister.
But I wish for you to get out of my sight.
Who do you think you are?
The world is round.
Your downfall will come.
That's right.
And if you want that to happen sooner,
why don't we work together?
In exchange for this blessed money
that will help you start anew.
Ensure that that woman will not be able
to set foot in this church.
You should be careful too.
That little demon is onto us.
Good thing she did not find
any evidence against us.
She only has her suspicions.
But everyone saw how you humiliated her.
Of course, for her to learn her lesson.
I am aware that I'm not like Father Damaso
who uses that way to discipline others.
But now, I feel the relief
he feels when he does it.
Now, she should be thankful
that I have more important
things to attend to.
Dear Curate,
is there anything else you need?
Keep an eye on Klay.
If she needs to be followed,
have someone do it.
She must not get in the way of my plans
for Ibarra and Maria Clara.
My dearest Ms. Klay, good afternoon.
Where have you been?
I have been waiting for you.
Don't ask.
I'm not in the mood.
I don't know.
Asking questions seems to be
forbidden in this place.
If you do, you will just get in trouble.
As for me, I have been staying
here for so long now,
and yet I still don't get it!
Ms. Klay, wait.
Ms. Klay, you're shaking.
No.
I can do this.
I just need to calm myself down.
-Hold on.
-I can…
Are you making fun of me again?
No, Ms. Klay.
It looks like what you're doing
is helping you, right?
So maybe it will help me too.
Because I also want to calm myself down
from being too worried about you.
Ms. Klay, I won't ask you
about what happened to you
if you don't want me to.
But I hope…
it will be of help
if you let me stay here with you.
So that, somehow, it will make
whatever you're going through
right now disappear.
If you think about it…
Señor Linares is a first-class gentleman.
That is why he is
perfect for you, my dear.
Auntie…
That never even crossed my mind.
So I beg you.
Let us not talk about him anymore, please.
They said you did not talk
to Señor Linares that much.
Maria,
since when did you become ill-mannered
in welcoming your special guests?
Forgive me, Father.
But Maria tried to be respectful
toward Mr. Linares.
But maybe we really cannot dictate
one's heart to--
This is not about the heart.
This is about common sense.
Maria…
I think it would be better
for you to come out,
and ask forgiveness
for the way you welcomed them.
No.
I will not do it, Godfather.
Please, Maria.
Do not make your godfather angry.
Face Mr. Linares again.
Be nice to them.
Do it for me, my child.
I beg you, please.
Let me. Thank you.
Why do you have that?
I should be the one doing that
because you are the guest here.
Ms. Klay, you need to quench your thirst
to help you feel relieved.
Thank you.
Ms. Klay.
Maria.
Thank you for facing us.
I just want to grant the request
of my father and godfather.
But I also do not want
to give you false hopes.
You know that I already have a fiancé.
Maria?
That is all right, Father.
My dear, Maria Clara,
just think of Ibarra
as a sick person who is dying.
Dear, what can
an excommunicated man offer you?
Yes! That is true.
You are also going to destroy
yourself because of him.
You heard what I said earlier.
I already have a fiancé.
I choose to get married only to Crisostomo
and not to anyone else.
Why did you bring me flowers?
That's really my present for you, right?
That was before you made me worry earlier.
Ms. Klay, you don't like it?
I'm sorry. I think I'm allergic.
Allergic?
Oh, right. They don't use the word
"allergic" in this era yet.
It's…
What I mean is…
It's like a person's
hypersensitive reaction
to a substance or a thing
in an environment.
This may be harmless to ordinary people.
But the reaction may
be from flowers or dust.
You don't get it?
What you mean is that…
you are allergic…
to my gift?
And to my love for you?
Are you the one who's hypersensitive?
That's not what I meant.
Ms. Klay, if you don't like
what I gave you,
just tell me directly.
Don't beat around the bush
with your words and terms
that I don't even understand.
Give me that.
Why are you angry? I'm sorry.
-Sorry.
-Sorry?
-Give it to me. Never mind.
-You already gave it to me, right?
I apologize for the unkind words
uttered by my goddaughter.
But my decision will still prevail…
So, Tiburcio,
prepare to ask
for Maria's hand in marriage.
Father…
Perhaps we should discuss this
at another time.
Maria has just recovered from her illness.
That is right, Father.
Maria might relapse…
Let us grant Maria's request, Father.
Maria Clara might need to rest.
All right then.
Fine.
Rest well, my child.
And weigh your options well
for your future's sake.
A good future you cannot get
from someone who is ill-mannered
but you will likely only get
from Mr. Linares.
Let's go, Alfonso.
Until next time, friends!
How dare you come here!
Crisostomo?
Yuck!
Why did you kiss me?
I didn't give you my consent.
I'm sorry.
But, Ms. Klay,
you saw what happened, right?
I did not mean to do it.
But because of what happened,
you have no choice but to marry me.
Don't worry.
Because I am sure
that once we are married,
Mrs. Fidel de los Reyes,
you will eventually learn to love me.
Really?
Why don't you marry this bouquet instead?
But…
Why don't you go home? It's okay.
I'm all right now. Yes, I'm fine.
You may go home.
You've reached your quota.
Bye.
What a fool!
He did comfort me.
But he also stole a kiss from me.
I think he's planning to trick me
into marrying him.
Don't forget your things!
Oh, right. Thank you.
This is your fault.
I'm here to visit Maria, Father.
But since you are here,
I would like to take this opportunity
to reconcile with you.
You should not have come here.
Someone who is excommunicated like you
has no right to face
my goddaughter or face me.
Let's go, Crisostomo,
I will accompany you out.
No, Uncle.
Because I have some important news
for you and for Maria.
I did not expect
that the friar would be here.
Even Don Tiburcio.
This is my nephew, señor,
Don Alfonso Linares,
whom we have arranged with the friar
to be Maria Clara's husband.
What are you saying, señora?
You heard what they said, didn't you?
Maria…
What is this?
Are they telling the truth?
Do you think we are kidding?
Do you think
I will allow you to marry
my goddaughter Maria Clara?
It cannot be!
That will never happen!
I will never allow someone excommunicated
to destroy Maria's future.
But I am no longer excommunicated
like what you are saying.
Here. Read it.
This letter came from
the honorable Archbishop himself.
He has lifted the excommunication
that you imposed on me
so I no longer see any reason
for you to keep Maria away
and marry her off to someone else!
Perhaps the Archbishop spoke
with the Captain General
when he came to Manila
and that's why he changed the decision.
That is indeed what happened, Uncle.
I don't care!
I will still not allow you
to marry my goddaughter!
My apologies, Father.
I do not want to embarrass you,
but what gives you the right to dictate
to Maria what she should do
as if you are her father
when her real father is right here?
That is enough!
You really have no manners, Ibarra!
You have no respect for our priest!
Look, Maria!
Is that the kind of man you want to marry?
Crisostomo, come on.
Please leave.
Get out!
He will not leave, Godfather.
I still need to speak to my fiancé.
Did you hear that?
So perhaps it is them you should
see out of your home, Uncle.
You have no shame!
-Father!
-Enough!
Crisostomo!
COMING UP…
Ms. Klay, it seems that my friend
is serenading you.
And I think my wish has come true.
Here is the one who loves you.
We have made a decision.
We will no longer delay it.
I will ask for Maria Clara's hand
so that we can already get married.
I think what you are asking
is impossible, my son.
I don't want to put you at risk
but it's important that I talk to you.
It is time for me to use this.
Father, what do we need to talk about?
Godfather?
Why are you crying?
Don't attempt to lie to me, Father.
Especially since we are
in the house of God.
You know the truth.
So you better start confessing, Father.
Subtitle translation by
Nehemiarey Dallego, Norman Baguisa