MARIA CLARA AND IBARRA
THIS PROGRAM, WHICH IS ADAPTED
FROM THE NOVELS OF DR. JOSE P. RIZAL,
IS PRESENTED USING DRAMATIC ELEMENTS
TO CONNECT THE PRESENT AND THE PAST
IN A SPECIAL REIMAGINING OF THE NATIONAL
LITERATURE FILIPINOS ARE PROUD OF.
I am only wondering…
what a jeweler like you
would need from a nun--
Curiosity.
It was my curiosity
that pushed me to visit her
but I was forbidden to enter
by one of the sisters.
So, I did not pursue it.
Maria Clara Infantes.
-Klay?
-It doesn't say here where you're from.
I'm from San Diego.
I live with my relatives.
Maria Clara de los Santos y Alba.
Not only that.
I'm also a close friend
of the wealthy jeweler.
Señor Simoun.
Is he really your friend
or are you just using his name
to escape punishment?
Ask Señor Simoun to come here.
Tell him that Miss Klay is here.
And you, Father?
Why are you here?
Why don't you go up
to where your eminence belongs?
Because my uncle is not like
others who are self-conceited.
People who think of themselves
as gods who came down from heaven.
Apologies, señor.
Apologize, Isagani.
No need, Father.
I was not offended.
What's the matter with you?
Why do you seem so angry at that person?
I do not know, but…
I have a bad feeling about him.
Don't you know that he's known
as the Brown Cardinal
because the Captain General listens
and does everything he says?
To be honest, Captain…
Isagani also has a point.
There is something unusual
about Señor Simoun.
Is there anything
I can help you with, señor?
Señor Ibarra?
Who is this woman from my town
who was arrested by civil guards?
She said she is the cousin of
Maria Clara de los Santos y Alba.
Who is this cousin of hers?
She said she is Miss Klay.
Forgive me, señor…
if I scared you.
I am only glad to see you again.
Thirteen years have passed
since we last saw each other here.
And who do you think I am?
You are the gentleman…
from my youth…
whom we respected very much.
Me, my late mother, and brother.
You, señor…
Everyone thought you were already dead.
But…
I'm the only one who knows the truth.
Don't tell anyone that we know each other
and that I am still alive.
You hold the secret to my true identity.
A secret that no one else can know.
Especially my enemies.
You are the hero from my childhood.
Señor Crisostomo Ibarra.
That is why…
you embraced me earlier today.
Don't worry, señor.
I will keep your secret
as long as you want me to.
Eat, woman.
What time is it?
Is there no news yet?
Do you think the man you sent
to fetch Señor Simoun already reached him?
Do not be impatient.
My comrade may already be
talking to him right now.
That's good.
Thank you.
You never failed me, Mister Adong.
May your soul rest in peace.
What's inside, señor?
Have a look.
My God.
Who knew that the riches
of the Ibarras are here?
Riches that we will use
to get this country back
from the foreigners
who ruined me and Maria.
We… will use them, señor?
Yes, Basilio…
because you and I are one.
Just like you, the Spaniards
also defiled my family.
They're the reason why
your brother and mother are dead.
But don't worry…
the time for our revenge has come.
Together, we will plan their downfall,
and drive them out
of the Philippine islands.
I cannot believe that you
and Señor Simoun are the same person.
Based on the stories
that Father Florentino
and Captain Basilio told us today…
you are the one advising
the Captain General
to push for forced labor.
And that you're also advocating
to increase the tax that people must pay.
All of that is true.
Then…
what happened to the man I once admired?
I'm using my head now.
Compared to Ibarra
who didn't use his head…
who thought that it is enough
to help his countrymen
and to have a good heart.
Is this the reason why instead of helping
alleviate the lives of us Indios,
you are making our lives more miserable?
So that you will suffer more!
So that you will be oppressed!
So you will learn to rebel.
Sir?
Can you hand me the book?
It's important to me.
I'm already bored here inside.
I've been doing nothing.
I want to read.
Didn't my officer inform you earlier
that you can't touch any of your things
while you're still detained?
Come on.
It's just a book.
There's nothing dangerous about that.
All right, you can have
the other contents of my bag.
The canned goods, food…
They are all yours.
But the book, I must have that book.
I cannot lose it.
It will not disappear from our care.
So, please…
will you shut up and stop disturbing me?
What are you doing anyway?
This wasn't part of the plan.
What will I do?
Miss Klay?
What does she look like?
How tall is she?
Can you describe her?
She's a beautiful woman.
Slim, short, and has a fair complexion.
I think she has the blood of a…
Chinese!
Yes, right.
Wait…
if that's the case,
do you really know who this woman is?
Fidel…
are we thinking of the same person?
I will never forget that woman.
Hernando…
Where did the civil guards take Miss Klay?
Take us there.
Elias, please…
Help me.
Yes, my friend.
I'll never forsake you.
Comrades!
Prepare your weapons!
We are going to save…
the woman that I've been waiting for.
Hernando, let us go.
Comrades…
Let's hurry.
Let's go!
The curate of San Diego is not here now.
Why?
What do you need?
My superior ordered me to come here.
We caught a woman.
She said she's from San Diego.
Do you know who this person is, Father?
I know this woman.
Where is she?
I can feel that it will happen very soon.
I saw your friend, Isagani…
I can feel his hatred towards me.
I know that his eyes are open…
to the sufferings of this country.
So, perhaps with just a bit more push…
he will be among the first ones to fight.
But, señor…
Isagani and I want something else.
Señor…
I will soon be a certified doctor.
My other friends…
just like Isagani…
also want to reach their dreams.
Just like the school that we aim to build
that will teach Spanish to our countrymen.
Why would you promote Hispanism?
Don't you know that
this is a form of suicide?
Speaking Spanish is not the basis
for the advancement of a person's ability.
The people who do not know how
to love their own language…
they are also the ones helping
destroy their national identity.
We will become a country with no identity!
A race…
with no dignity.
You already witnessed that.
The cruelty that your mother
and brother experienced.
But what did you do…
to seek justice for them?
Señor…
I cannot do anything to obtain justice.
Because the truth is…
I am not wealthy.
I am just a poor person…
who needs to work and serve others
just to get an education.
And one more thing…
Will I be able to bring back
the lives of my mother and Crispin?
So what's the use for me to avenge them?
What's the use…
if I join you with your plans?
What is the death of a man
in the presence of the death of society?
A life lost is useless
if it is not consecrated to a great idea.
And you, sir…
will soon become a doctor.
Someday…
you will perhaps be a famous
and great physician…
If they allow you
to practice medicine in peace.
But what you're doing now is far greater…
in giving life to this ailing country.
You may not be able
to bring back their lives…
but you will be able to stop
anyone from being sick
and from losing a loved one
due to the colonizers' cruelty to them.
Think carefully about what I said…
Doctor Basilio.
There is a gathering I must go to.
No one can hinder and stop
the children of our motherland
from waking up…
and revolting.
Someone is coming. Hide!
At this very moment,
the civil guards are already
searching the mountains…
to find and bring before justice…
the bandits who killed
our two civil guards.
Are we certain that they are
the ones who did it, General?
And who would do such a thing
if not those damned bandits!
So it is just right to hunt them…
and annihilate them!
Fidel…
there are many more of them
compared to our numbers.
So I will give the order to retreat.
I am sure they will follow us.
So I must praise you, my friend…
because you are a ruler with an iron fist.
Which is just right, so that
the people will fear you…
and will simply follow.
Especially since no one is helping
to make this country progressive
other than the most honorable Spain.
There is still someone you must save.
Am I right?
Cheers!
We will continue to exchange fire
for a few minutes
to give you time to escape.
And when you return…
in case we are no longer at our hideout…
I will leave a note and put it
at the guava tree,
so that you will know where we are.
You are a brave leader…
and you have concern for others.
Thank you, my friend.
I pray that you will find
and save the one you love.
Until our resurrection, my friend.
You count up to three, and then leave.
Thank you.
Basilio…
What took you so long?
-Good evening.
-I have been waiting for you.
I just dropped by some place, Miss Etta.
It seems that this place
does not get cleaned often.
Oh my, Miss Etta,
you will be scolded by
Captain Tiago and Madam Isabel.
What if they suddenly come home
and find out that their house
has been neglected?
The Captain will not be coming home.
There is no public smoking room here.
He also cannot bear to not smoke opium.
Come on, Miss Etta.
Captain Tiago's condition is improving.
That's because I'm watching over him.
But what about now
that you are not with him?
Come on, Miss Etta…
please have the house cleaned.
I want Captain Tiago to stay here.
I will take care of him
and watch over him here.
I will go ahead.
Wait, one moment.
Have you heard what happened
to your fiancee's father?
Her father?
What happened to Chief Tales?
He was abducted by the bandits yesterday,
and I heard that Juli is inconsolable.
She does not even know what to do.
We are near the road, Hernando.
I am sorry, but we cannot walk
on the road.
It's easy for the civil guards on patrol
to see us.
We will walk here.
We can hide in trees and shrubs
and they will barely notice us.
Or better yet, why don't we rest for now?
Let's just continue our journey tomorrow.
Hernando, how can I rest
if it is indeed Miss Klay that you met…
and she is in jail now?
Because I know her demeanor very well…
I will be worried even more.
She might already have argued
with the civil guards…
especially since she can't keep
her mouth shut.
So, Hernando…
let's take advantage of the dark of night,
so that we can reach the town
and the prison cells right away.
Let's go.
It is very beautiful!
But it is very expensive.
But I am not charging you for it, Father.
Instead, I will charge it to
the richest Indio of your parish.
Just tell me his name
and I will be the one to talk to him.
I am sure he cannot refuse.
Don't worry, Father…
no one else will know.
All right.
I will write his name later
and I will give it to you.
That's excellent, Father.
It seems that Father Salvi is not here.
He did not come because
he's not feeling well again.
I am telling you, señor, it seems that…
he will not live long because
he easily gets sick.
What did you say?
I said my apologies, but I must rest now.
Good evening and Merry Christmas
to you, Father.
And to you as well, señor.
Officer…
Here is the former curate of San Diego.
Good evening.
My name is Bernardo Salvi.
I am one of the counsels of
the current curate of San Diego.
An honor to meet you, Father.
I came here because of a woman
who is currently in the care
of your prison.
Are you also wondering about this?
You will be wondering even more
about the contents of her bag.
Even before, that woman has always been
different and acted strange.
What is this?
El Filibusterismo?
How interesting.
Have you read the contents of this book?
Not yet, Father.
But based on the title--
It might contain subversive text
if we base it on the title of the novel.
It's not surprising
that you found this book on her.
Well then, where is she?
Take me to her. I wish to see her.
Yes, Father.
Let's go.
Really, Auntie?
Klay is missing again?
She's been gone the whole day.
She's not even responding
to my calls and texts.
What could have happened
to your friend, Stacy?
Did she go to another cosplay thing?
Elias said that she was too busy
reading a book.
She even mentioned something
about research.
What was it?
She mentioned a different world
which I don't even understand.
Last time I saw her was yesterday, Auntie.
When she stole…
I mean, when she borrowed
the book from our professor.
Book?
Yes, the El Fili book.
Because your crazy daughter said
that she needs the book to…
Hold on. What else did she say?
I really hope this is the key
that could help me go back.
Go back where?
This is crazy. You only needed a book?
I could have lent you mine.
Gosh, girl…
This is not just a book.
I need this with me when I go back there.
So when they tell me
that what I am saying is not true…
I'll give this to them.
"Here, ma'am, sir. Read this."
All the evidence is in there.
The story of what will happen
to you is written there."
Wait. Read by who?
My new friends.
Because they don't believe
that Noli and El Fili are just stories.
It's all made-up.
At least if I bring this,
they will easily believe me.
It will be easier for me to save
the lives of Maria Clara and Ibarra.
Girl, are you okay?
Do I need to bring you
to a psychiatrist, huh?
Let's just talk when I get back, okay?
-All right. Bye!
-Why…
Wait, where are you going?
Hey! She really ignored me.
But your daughter never
responded to me, Auntie.
That was the last time I spoke with her.
I want to help…
my friends.
But in my current situation,
I'm so helpless.
My God.
Is this the same thing
that my daughter told me about?
The friends that she needs to help?
What did my daughter get into?
Where could she be right now?
Father Salvi?
Amazing…
Miss Klay…
You don't seem to have aged a day.
Wait…
Do you need water, Hernando? Water?
That's what happens to people
who don't exercise.
You have a weak body
and you seem to be clumsy.
Clumsy?
Señor, we've been running for hours.
I'm only human.
How long will you rest?
I'm only thinking
about the time we're losing.
How far away are we from
the prison that you told me about?
We're near.
In about thirty minutes,
we will reach the center
where the prison is located.
Thirty minutes…
It will be sunrise by then.
I need to see her now.
I cannot wait any longer.
I'll go ahead.
Wait, my friend…
Really?
He really left me.
My God…
A tree monster might be lurking nearby.
I'll catch up with him.
What magic do you possess
that prevents you from aging
and allows you to remain young?
You're really concerned about
my skincare right now, Father?
I'm not even surprised.
Facial cream.
Cream that you put on your face
to prevent wrinkles and eye bags.
You want some, Father?
-I have it in my bag--
-Silence.
I never imagined we would see
each other again.
In that case…
you may be the woman
that the nun told me about
who wanted to visit Maria Clara.
Why did you come back?
What trouble do you bring
to Maria Clara's life this time?
Trouble?
What did you say?
From which depth of hell did you
come from, you devil woman?
You will regret returning here.
Because I assure you…
that you will rot in prison.
For what case, Father?
For many cases, miss.
Whatever I could think of.
The first one is of you
being a filibuster!
Especially since you possess
this kind of book…
which I presume contains subversive text.
Give me that.
Give me that!
It's nothing! Everything in there
is nonsense, Father!
Give it!
I said give it back!
With the way you're acting…
looking pale and so scared…
I think this book contains
something important.
Sir…
Where is that civil guard that
you sent to fetch Señor Simoun?
Why did he come here instead?
Where is señor Si…
You and the Brown Cardinal
know each other?
I just want to talk to the Brown Cardinal…
so I can sue this friar!
You are so gutsy.
Let us see…
if the kind gentleman will help you.
After he finds out what kind
of woman you are.
Señor…
tell the civil guards who will
come with us to get ready…
because we are returning
to the town of San Diego.
I want to put…
this woman…
in a prison near where I am.
So that I can always keep an eye on her.
Consider it done, Father.
De Paz, call your companions!
Quick!
Right away, sir.
Where are you, Crisostomo?
Where are you, my love?
Come back.
Come back here.
Save me. Save me, my love.
Where are you?
Come back here.
Come back here, my love, and save me.
Save me.
Save me, Crisostomo.
Maria!
Señor…
Beloved curate…
what are you doing in my room?
The Captain General asked me
to wake you up.
We need to go hunting in the forest early.
Were you having a nightmare, señor?
Who is this Maria you are referring to?
Please tell the Captain General…
that I will just get dressed.
Thank you very much.
There…
That is the town prison.
But we can't just go near that prison.
There are civil guards.
How strange…
There are many civil guards tonight
compared to the last time I was here.
Hernando…
we cannot go near that prison right away.
We need to leave our guns here.
We must pretend to be ordinary citizens
and that we went there
to seek help for a problem.
Let me take care of it.
Come on.
Here.
It's Father Salvi…
If so…
he already saw…
Hey! Block her!
-Hey!
-Where are you going?
Let go of me!
My heart flutters…
and…
I lose my breath…
my Miss Klay…
Hurry!
Hurry…
Wait…
You can't go near them.
The friar will recognize you
and I am sure that he will
have you arrested.
Listen to me…
we can't save the lady
if you will also be imprisoned.
Hurry!
We can go now.
Go on! Walk!
Wait.
Fidel…
Fidel.
Let go of me, Hernando!
Listen!
Miss Klay needs me.
I know.
But will you really
expose yourself to danger?
You have been out of sight
of the enemies for many years.
And now…
you want to be reckless?
You want to expose yourself to them now?
I had to endure thirteen years
of being apart from the woman I love…
and now that she's back…
I won't let the two of us be apart again.
I understand, but…
Fidel, stay calm.
Wait!
Forgive me, Grandfather…
if I have to leave you alone here.
What is important is that…
father will finally go home.
I pray everyday…
that I can pay my debt
to Sister Penchang soon.
So that we can all be together again.
And I can once again
be with the one I love.
Juli…
Basilio?
Grandfather Selo…
may I please speak with Juli?
My love…
I heard about what happened
to Mister Tales.
Did you recognize the bandits
who abducted him?
Did they ask for ransom?
My God, Juli…
are they aware that the court
and the corporation have
decimated your properties?
And now they have abducted him!
What is this?
You seem to be packing your things, Juli?
The bandits are asking
for ransom for Father
in the sum of five hundred pesos.
I don't know where to get
that amount of money!
So I was forced to go to Sister Penchang,
and she lent me money.
But she wanted something in return.
In return, I will be her servant.
I am hoping and praying to God…
and to all the saints!
Now that I have paid the bandits, Basilio…
they will bring Father home
any moment now.
But I don't think I will get
to see that moment
because I need to go.
I need to become a servant
to the one I owed money from.
Wait…
the pendant that I gave you as a gift.
It will stay here.
Why did you not pawn this?
You don't need to be a slave
to Sister Penchang.
That cannot be.
Isn't this a gift from a kind woman
to a man with leprosy?
The leper said…
that this was a gift
from Señorita Maria Clara.
It is a symbol of a kind heart…
which is invaluable.
Plus the leper gave this to you
when you helped him on the road.
Which I then gifted to you…
as a symbol…
of my heart that loves you.
Fool!
If you keep walking slowly,
I will make the horse run
so you will be dragged!
Jose Rizal?
Who is he?
And where did this creature
get the strength to publish…
a book about filibusterism?
The title is in Spanish, but the…
contents are in the
language of the Indios.
First chapter.
One morning in December,
the dipper-shaped ship was traversing
the circuitous path
of the Pasig River.
Doña Victorina was very disgusted that day
because the passengers were ignoring her.
Those Indios are slowing down our journey,
and the progress of the Philippines.
The Indios are not the problem.
The river is the problem.
The solution to your argument is easy!
Amazing!
That's a great idea!
But a huge amount is needed for that.
Who will pay for it and how
will we pay the laborers?
We do not need to pay the Indios,
especially if the prisoners
will become laborers.
And it will be better
if the government imposes forced labor
on men who are aged sixteen to sixty.
How terrifying!
How did he…
Halt!
Stop!
Come here!
What kind of book is this?
Who is Jose Rizal?
And how did he know
the exact events on the ship?
Even our discussion…
he predicted and he even printed?
I knew it.
Look at me.
Answer my question.
Is Rizal a member…
of your group of witches?
I knew it.
You are a demon!
You are a devil!
Am I really the devil?
You are the one who tied me up.
All the evil things you did in this town…
it is you, Father, who is the real devil!
Shameless!
You will really regret coming back here!
Give me that!
Introduce yourself!
You are Satan concealed in a human body!
What is happening to you, Pablito?
You seem to be blinded by anger and power!
You are also oppressing the oppressed?
You better pray…
to whomever you worship, woman.
I will make sure…
that you will return to the hell
you came from.
The villain is already reading the story.
He will find out about Simoun.
I think it is better
if we leave this place.
Hernando, I know to which town
they brought Miss Klay.
Who are you?
Why do you need to bring me food
as if I am sick or a prisoner?
Señor, come with us right away!
The carriage is waiting!
I am just making sure that
you will be away from danger.
Subtitle translation by
Nehemiarey Dallego &amp; Norman Baguisa