(Yukiya) There's no way in my life I'll ever be able to forgive you.
(Nobuo) What happened? Today we are two people again
(Male) Yukiya Ise
9:19 p.m. Arrested on suspicion of violating the Specified Secrets Protection Act
(Reo) It's my own fault.
(Sound of door opening and closing)
(sekibarai)
(Nobuo) Yukiya-kun, it’s been a while.
(Nobuo) Do you remember uncle?
The last time we met...
Are you sure that was Masa-kun's wedding?
7 years ago
Where is this?
Yeah? Aoyama Police Station
(laughter)
Don't make that face
Don't worry, I'm here.
If there's nothing, I can give it to you right away.
There is no way
What is it?
(Nobuo) Indeed...
Yukiya-kun from a long time ago⸺
I was good at computers.
Sei-chan also said so.
They say you have talent in that area.
…I’m sure⸺
Last year I was with Sei-chan...
Even though I quit because I was angry⸺
State secrets was too much.
State secret?
It makes some sense...
Even my uncle is sad
The youngest son of the Ise family is a dangerous person who threatens the nation.
Please be careful
In short, you should never touch someone⸺
That I made you angry
You know what? He's a good adult
(Masayuki) As expected, Nobuo-san
(Masayuki) The next Prime Minister
(Erika) It's true.
(Masayuki) This guy is an idiot.
Fufufufu…
you were good
A member of the Ise family
(Officer) Come in.
(Sound of door closing) (Sound of locking)
‪♪～
‪～♪
(Officer) Breakfast.
take it
eat quickly
Are you feeling unwell?
(Masayuki) Oh, you drink a lot.
This is my first time trying German-made powdered milk, but I think I like it.
Hey?
What about your father today?
(Fuyu) I haven't seen you since this morning.
(mobile phone vibrator)
knock)
(Seiichiro) Yes.
(sound of door opening)
- (Masayuki) Excuse me - (Erika) Excuse me
(sound of door closing)
what happened?
I received a call from the Ise Medical Center this morning.
It seems that Kaho has woken up.
Found while trying to escape from the facility
It seems like it was tough, he went wild.
-(Nurse) Hanaho-san-(Nurse) It's okay.
(Nurse) Please calm down.
(Nurse) It's okay to take it slow.
-(Nurse) It's okay.-(Nurse) It's okay.
- (Nurse) It's okay, Hanaho-san - (Nurse) It's okay, it's okay.
He says he almost got killed.
To you guys
footsteps)
Answer!
haven't done anything
Masayuki-san found Hanaho-san collapsed...
I can't think of anything but suicide.
It's impossible for us to try to kill you, right?
Is that so?
yes
What do you think?
Hanaho is now...
I'm sleeping
What I'm asking is the truth or falsity of Hanaho's statement.
Masayuki
We are...
haven't done anything
Got it
No matter what she says in the future, don't be upset.
Okay?
Don't change your words no matter what
yes
(Seiichiro) Too bad, it's over now.
-(Fuyu) No, I'll take it down.-(Seiichiro) Yeah, thank you.
Hey
Do you understand?
(sound of door closing)
Huh! Ha ha...
Ha ha...
(Yukiya in childhood) ♪ Twinkle Hikaru
(Yukiya) ♪ The star of the sky
(Saori/Yukiya) ♪ If you blink,
♪ I'm watching everyone
♪ Twinkle Hikaru
♪ The star of the sky
-(Saori) Yukiya-(Yukiya) Yeah?
Even if this factory becomes part of the Ise Group⸺
The time and memories spent here will remain in my heart forever.
So... it's okay
Hanaho-sama
(Yukiya) You might not betray me.
Maybe I won't bully you
but…
not on your side
After all, he is a servant of the Ise family.
(birds chirping)
footsteps)
(Officer) It's food. Open it.
It's decided, open it.
How long are you planning on not eating?
Eat carefully!
(footsteps leaving)
I have transferred the money, please check it.
(Reo) Thank you
But I was saved, thanks for your cooperation.
Of course
I have been indebted to Erika before.
And⸺
Yukiya Ise only feels betrayed.
Thank you for telling me the truth
you're tough being you
Bring the members along to make your dreams come true
You can't live without money
(Reo) Yes.
It's me⸺
I don't trust people who don't care about money.
You can live in a daze, right?
I get irritated when I see things like that
Huh...
That's why I'm trying to rebuild the team somehow.
I'm rooting for Satake-san.
I think I suffered badly in that incident.
But don't blame yourself
It's his fault for taking advantage of people's dreams.
yes
I wish I could be punished for this incident.
Can you help me again if something happens?
Yeah
Thank you, of course I will add the reward.
I...
I trust Erika.
Huh?
(Reo) For giving me a job⸺
He promises a commensurate reward
thank you
footsteps)
(Officer) Number 31, I'm meeting you.
(sound of lock opening)
knock)
(Officer) Sit down.
It's kind of cold here
What do you mean?
(Erika) I had no intention of doing anything...
Yukiya was the one who betrayed me first, right?
(Yukiya) Huh?
As long as you behave like a member of the Ise family⸺
I didn't have to do this either.
feel ill
Why are you so obsessed with us?
Forget about this⸺
I wish I could just live my life
Because it doesn't matter anymore
what?
but…
We were once a couple
(Erika) Hehehehe...
Huh...
I agree
For letting me into the Ise family⸺
I'm grateful
Sorry
My name is Yukiya Ise.
He was from the Ise family.
Would you like to talk to us a little more?
please hang out with me
(Erika) My purpose is only one
I was to become a member of the Ise family.
But...
I love those people⸺
I never thought of them as family⸺
Eventually, I will cut ties with the Ise family⸺
I want to live with you
If you promise never to seek revenge again⸺
May you be released⸺
You can ask your father-in-law, though.
If you can't do that, why don't you just stay there for the rest of your life?
in exchange for my pride
Erika is...
Did you really want that?
this way of life
Degrading other people's lives and clinging to the Ise family like this.
of course
Me and Masayuki-san⸺
Miyabi was also achieved.
As president, I have been given the opportunity to take on many challenges.
It's me⸺
Every day is so fulfilling now.
You and me⸺
It's different from when I lived in that small house.
that's why…
Don't interfere with my happiness anymore
I don't want you to get involved
So why...
(Erika) Huh?
So why did you come?
(Sound of door opening and closing)
(sigh)
- (Girl) It's delicious - (Girl) It's delicious.
- (Girl) It's delicious. - (Girl) It's delicious.
(Girl) Cute clothes
(Girl) Thank you, I bought you a new one.
-(Girl) Is that so? -(Girl) Oh, that's a rabbit.
(Girl) Fluffy and cute
(Sound of knocking on the door) (Male) Mr. Sato!
Please give me back the money
(Male) I also have a loan book today.
Please give me back the 3 million yen!
(Male) Open it! Hey!
(Nobuo) Good.
Ah...
-(Nobuo) Too bad, always-(Seiichiro) Good, good, good.
(Nobuo) Hehe... I also heard about Hanaho-san.
If something happens, I'll be your strength
thank you
...Taku Masayuki has always been like this.
So-so So-so
Sei-chan and I are close, so when we have a problem, we're both there. Yeah.
Helpful
(Nobuo) Hmm... What should we do over there?
That Aoyama Police Station
Why did you do that kind of harassment again?
Isn't it deeply rooted in the fact that your wife was taken away?
(Seiichiro) Huh...
(Juna) What happened?
(Kotoko) I heard you're taking a break for a while.
(Kina) Huh? why?
(Kotoko) I wonder why?
(Kina) I guess Yukini caught a cold.
(Kotoko) Huh?
Kina worried
(Kotoko) That's right.
Shall we come again tomorrow?
-(Kina) Yeah-(Kotoko) I'm sure it'll be okay.
-(Kina) Yeah! -(Kotoko) Yeah, hehehehe...
Okay
- (Girl) Ah! Kina-chan-(Girl) Ah Kina-chan
(Girl) What were you doing just now?
(Erika) Ah... I was back.
Ah... yeah
Welcome back
I'm home
(Masayuki) Work?
Yeah, a little bit
(Masayuki) Yeah
Today is? Were you busy?
Maybe not so
(Masayuki) Yeah
Have you heard anything since then?
No, especially
What about your father-in-law?
We only met this morning
(Erika) Yeah.
Is it okay?
What?
(Masayuki) No, we
Isn't it okay?
If something happens, don't make that face
(sigh)
Are you still jumpy?
Why don't you just get fed up?
When I'm moving around a lot⸺
Masayuki is always at home⸺
It's depressing to think that you were thinking like that.
What is it?
Yukiya-san, who I went to see today.
Why did you bother to talk to him?
Stop it, I'm not inexperienced
I told you not to get involved with me again.
Stay strong
You are the heir of the Ise family, right?
Can't you do anything without your father-in-law protecting you?
If you swear you'll never seek revenge again⸺
May you be released⸺
You can ask your father-in-law, though.
Master
I'll bring you a hot drink
(sound of door opening)
please
That you can do anything⸺
I think it's okay to do anything.
I don't want to see anyone unhappy anymore.
surely⸺
I think that person will be the most sad.
I'm sorry for acting too much.
(Masayuki) Erika
Huh?
What are you doing! ?
what?
What... Huh?
Why stop?
Something like this⸺
Miyabi would feel bad if she found him when she grew up, right?
(Masayuki) Huh?
what?
Any problem?
No, it's not a problem...
(Erika) Pull this out!
What do you want?
feel ill
Huh?
(Erika) “Everyone from the Ise family”
“I write this letter hoping that it will arrive safely.”
“This time it was my thoughtless idea⸺”
“I harassed everyone in the Ise family⸺”
“I am really sorry”
“I deeply regret it.”
“I promise I will never seek revenge again⸺”
“Please get me out of here”
“Please me”…
Enough is enough
This is definitely a lie
get carried away
I also agree with Masayuki-san.
Excuse me
footsteps)
(policeman) number 31
Released.
‪♪～
Well then
‪～♪
(Erika) There's no way you can destroy the Ise family.
my Ise family
(Seiichiro) Could you cut ties with the Ise family now?
Why are you so obsessed with us?
(Masayuki as a child) The very fact that you were born into this world was an accident.
- (Male) It's dangerous, it's dangerous - (Yukiya as a child) Mother!
-(Male) No-(Yukiya) Mom!
(Yukiya) What about your mother?
give me back my mom
Get out.
Yukiya can't do anything anyway.
Look aside
I...
I will never forgive you
(Yukiya) I'm different from you⸺
I have nothing to lose
(Seiichiro) I thought I had to talk to you someday.
Don't be silly!
(Erika) Maybe it's best to take it easy.
About your father-in-law
You will continue to be punished until you die.