Daughter
It's your mother who has let you down.
The body of Liu Zhaodi's father, Liu Qingsong
was sent over from Shanyin County.
The cases have already been merged.
After Liu Zhaodi,
there were two more victims: Daoist Feng
and Liu Qingsong.
Is it possible that the mountain god really killed them?
There's another clue.
Liu Zhaodi
married a wealthy merchant's son years ago.
Su Heng
In the name of the Yuezhou Governor's Office,
contact all the prefectural offices and regional authorities.
Check the household registrations.
Find this Su Heng.
Yes.
Huan'er
Come inside for dinner.
Time to eat.
Mother
Let's go.
Eat.
Huan'er, eat a bit more.
Here.
How much rice do we have left at home?
About
enough for three or four more days.
Got it.
Let's eat first.
Who is it?
Is this Su Heng's residence?
Why are you looking for me?
We’re your new neighbors.
We’d like to invite you to perform an opera tonight.
Carrying a black umbrella in broad daylight—
Are you a ghost or something?
You just said
to perform at night.
That’s a ghost opera.
I won’t do it.
To be honest with you,
our family just moved into this village a couple of days ago.
After we moved in,
my son has been acting as if
he’s possessed by something.
There’s no feng shui master in the village.
But I heard
you’ve performed as Lord Guan at the temple fair.
We’d like you to sing a piece
to scare away the spirits.
This custom has existed since the time of the former emperor.
Dressing as Guan Gong and performing at temple fairs to drive away evil spirits.
But the fee—
But I’m afraid of the dark.
How about this:
bring your son here to this courtyard,
and we’ll perform here.
Alright.
Let’s do it your way.
I’ll bring my son over after dark.
Husband,
you didn’t even say you’d be back for dinner.
Is there any food left?
Yes.
Xiaocui,
go to the kitchen and bring the food.
Yes.
Eat slowly.
We still have to work on the case after eating.
Even so, we should eat well.
I asked Xiaocui to make a fish for you.
I'll go take a look.
Okay.
That gold
Is it real?
I used to deal with gold a lot.
I wouldn't mistake it.
Su Lang
Every time you put on that costume,
I always remember the day I was harassed by those thugs.
You happened to be passing by, dressed as Guan Gong for the temple fair.
And you chased them away.
That day, I didn't mean anything by it.
But I always feel
that Lord Guan was watching over me on purpose.
What was that sound?
Go take a look.
What is it?
A crow.
It flew into the window and died.
How unlucky.
Just throw it away.
Get lost.
Su Lang
Go tell Third and Fourth Brother
to perform the opera about Impermanence in the courtyard.
Alright.
Wait.
About the gold,
don't tell them yet.
If they ask,
just say each gets fifty coins.
Okay.
According to what the registrar indicated,
Su Heng should be just ahead.
Let's go ahead and see if there are any houses.
Yes.
I didn't expect this.
The Su family, once a household of merchants,
has actually fallen to living in such a rundown place.
Thirty years on the east bank,
thirty years on the west bank.
That's how life goes.
Sir Si,
you and Su Heng are old rivals, aren't you?
You won't get into a fight later, will you?
Maybe I'll deal with you first.
As long as you don't start anything, I'm relieved.
There's a house up ahead with people living in it.
Let's go.
Third and Fourth Brother,
Sister Huang,
What brings you here?
Third Brother, call Fourth Brother too.
Come to my house in half an hour.
Sing the song of the Martial Sage.
Fifty coins per person, is that alright?
Alright, we'll get ready right away.
Deal.
Huan'er,
why did you come out?
Your father has earned some money.
Now we have food to eat.
Come here.
Sirs,
visiting so late at night,
what brings you here?
We're looking for Su Heng.
That's me.
We're from the Yuezhou Governor's Office.
Let me ask you,
have there been any strange occurrences lately?
For example,
crows,
strange dreams,
or someone in a wedding dress acting oddly.
Su Lang,
Huan'er,
Where is Huan'er?
Huan'er is sleeping inside.
What's wrong?
Sirs,
That was my wife just now, please forgive her.
We are officials from the prefectural government.
What happened?
What's wrong with you?
Say something!
On my way back,
I think I saw a ghost.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Please forgive her, sirs.
My wife is a bit out of her mind.
No need to pay attention to her.
Su Heng.
Liu Zhaodi is dead.
We are here because of her murder.
Liu Zhaodi?
I...
I don't know this person.
She was once your first wife.
You dare say you don't know her?
Sir.
I know her.
Liu Zhaodi is dead.
But it has nothing to do with me.
I haven't seen her in many years.
She married you when she was twenty.
You tell the rest yourself.