That's all.
I understand.
The mark on my hand
means you want to kill me.
Is that right?
A life for a life.
I should be arrested.
Leaving you the mark
was because I wanted you to catch me.
I knew you could solve the case.
Why?
Because I was waiting
to see you again.
As for those children,
they were misled by me.
They are accomplices.
I hope the authorities will show them leniency.
Don't worry.
Once I settle things for Huahua today,
I will turn myself in to the authorities.
Give it a name.
Call it
Huahua.
How about that?
Okay.
We'll call you Huahua.
Siwen,
do you know?
The first half of my life was bleak and miserable.
It was on the verge of collapse.
Until you appeared in my world like a ray of light.
I hope
to spend my remaining years in peace here.
There were times
when I truly thought I was heading toward a happy ending.
But later I understood
that love
was just a longing in my heart,
and a stubbornness I blindly held onto all my life.
Siwen
Goodbye
Zhaodi
Sigong
Thank you for your hard work
Wenzhao
Siwen
Now everyone knows you've been tainted by spirits
You'll die within seven days
Today is the perfect day for you to die
So it was you
To Yuezhou City and its people
You spread the rumor that I was haunted by spirits
Let me tell you
The information I know
The mark on the girl's chest
was drawn by you on purpose.
You've been lying all along.
Maybe it's karma.
Zheng Yuenü
My wife
I once deceived her.
I've never told anyone this secret.
The tavern
Young lady
The tavern is full of all sorts of people.
It's not a place you should go.
I'll go wherever I want.
It's none of your business.
You are Lord Zheng's daughter.
There are rumors at court
that your father will be promoted next month.
There are several people gambling and drinking in the tavern right now.
If you go in,
and something happens,
it won't look good if word gets to the court.
Go.
You two are just low-ranking officers.
To put it bluntly, you're just temporary workers.
You haven't even entered the prefecture and you're already bossing me around.
Let her go.
We can't stop her anyway.
Go ahead.
We'll wait for you here.
You think I don't dare?
Place your bets, place your bets!
Reveal, reveal, reveal!
Reveal!
Count me in!
Come on, place your bets!
Place your bets!
The young lady is bold!
Of course I am.
Reveal!
They're all mine!
Keep going, keep going!
This is a robbery!
Put all your money on the table!
No one put anything in your pockets!
Hurry up!
Looking for trouble?
Put all the money on the table!
How dare you!
You dare commit a crime in Yuezhou City?
I didn't expect this.
A woman with a sword gambling in a tavern.
Who are you?
Then listen up, all of you.
I am the daughter of Lord Zheng from the Ministry of Justice.
I advise you to surrender now.
Otherwise,
my father will not let you off.
Do you know who we three brothers are?
We're fugitives from Yue Prefecture.
Big brother.
Kill her.
Teach those rotten officials a lesson.
Big brother.
Kill her.
On your way to the underworld,
blame your own loose tongue.