"The Emotion"
Wake up and get some food first?
You're heavy.
I thought we were going to eat.
Hold on.
Can't I get a morning kiss first?
Please?
How many times have I told you
to let me brush my teeth first?
Wow.
You're so touchy.
Hey, what are you putting on me?
It's CK cream.
The one I use every day.
Let me try putting it on you.
Don't use too much.
Not too much.
- Just a little bit.
- That's enough, that's enough.
Enough, that's way too much.
- It's too much.
- Let's see. Where?
See that? Go.
- Wait, wait.
- Don't put it there.
Enough, I already applied it.
- Okay.
- Put more later. Let me breathe.
It's a waste, that's enough.
What are you doing standing here?
Where did you go?
Why didn't you come home last night?
And why didn't you call me at all?
Why are you questioning me?
I was out making money for you.
Stop being so jealous.
Jealousy doesn't feed us,
you know?
Let's go home.
Wait.
Since when do you use this perfume?
You left me waiting all night.
Or were you
sleeping around?
We'll talk about this at home.
This man
is my comfort,
my safe zone.
He gives freely without me asking.
Since the first day we moved in,
until today, Nat's love
is still at one hundred percent.
But why is my love for Nat
fading a little more every day?
We've been together a long time.
Wow.
So many orders today.
I'll give you a boost.
You can take over.
I'll go deliver the orders myself.
Hey, hold on, Shane.
Why tire yourself out?
Stay here, I'll go instead.
Your good intentions...
if they're too much,
they just become a burden.
Get it?
Shane.
- I can really just go myself.
- It's okay.
Hey, wait, Shane.
Give me a sec.
Wait for me, Shane.
Shane!
Shane, hold on!
Safety first, okay?
Stay safe out there.
Let me know when you arrive.
Okay?
I'm sick of how clingy you are.
Bye.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Bye.
Hi.
Is the ring I ordered ready?
Oh, it's ready?
Okay, I'll go pick it up
this evening.
Thank you so much.
Where did he go?
I saw him yelling out front
this morning.
He's asleep.
I'd be tired too.
You never seem to find
any good love.
Honestly,
you're great at everything.
Even better than Nat.
But the one thing I can't stand
is how jealous you get.
I've always believed that
between two people in love,
one will always love the other less.
If you don't want to get hurt,
you should be that person.
Remember that.
Just let it go,
trust me.
What are you doing?
Your face is covered in dirt.
Hey Nai.
Remember where we...
Uh,
Oh,
Of course I do.
Want to go again?
Sit tight.
Fuck.
You know,
you're the person
I want to be with all the time.
But if that day,
you hadn't broken up with me
to date Nat,
I wouldn't have to put up with Sak.
Well, you were too jealous.
It annoyed me.
But whatever.
No matter what,
you're still my type.
I...
I think about you all the time.
Seriously,
do you...
do you still really love me?
Of course I do.
I love you a lot.
What is this?
What is it?
You said you broke up with him.
Why are you still seeing him?
I'm sorry.
Shane, I'm begging you.
If you really love me,
you shouldn't cheat on me.
Huh?
Nat.
The truth is...
I don't love you.
Hey, don't do this.
Shane.
I'm not mad at you anymore, okay?
I'll forget about today.
But I just ask for one thing.
Just love me like before, Shane.
Shane!
Love me just like before.
- Shane.
- Listen to me.
I could say it a hundred
or a thousand times...
I really don't love you.