Darn, Am, listen to me.
Panon took Lomnaw.
He sent me a pic.
Huh! What the hell?
I want Lomnaw back.
So what's it gonna be?
You wanna fight me?
If you're gonna be a crybaby
who's stopped by your friends...
then just go back to where you're from.
I can't take this anymore!
I'll kill him!
Tatch! You need to chill!
Listen to me.
If the judges find out about this,
you won't be able to participate.
Then what am I supposed to do?
Leave all this to me.
Are you gonna fight me, Rak?
Right.
Yeah!
Let's celebrate!
Our faculty spares no expense.
We booked the whole bar just to celebrate for Tatch.
Well, he's our faculty's pride.
The seniors must really went all in.
Remember when Lom participated?
That time, it was a party at Am's room.
Like a consoling private party.
That's right.
A very sad party, was it?
And the contestant was drunk like hell?
We gossiped so loud.
Wouldn't you care to look at us?
Lom!
Huh? Yeah?
You didn't have to look that hard,
Tatch hasn't arrived yet.
If he had, the crowd would go...
Here he comes!
So handsome.
Wait, he'll be right back.
Can we have a talk?
Mmm.
Guys, may I have a talk with Lomnaw for a while?
You had to announce that we're gonna talk?
Announce what?
If I didn't tell them,
I wouldn't have a chance to talk to you.
So, now you know, right? I didn't lose.
You could've told me last night.
Well, you assumed I lost...
So I didn't want to interrupt.
Thanks.
For what?
Thank you for putting effort.
Thank you for trying this hard.
I intended to say it last night.
Even if you'd lost, I would've thanked you anyway.
But you won. Everyone would be so proud of you.
Honestly, Lom...
I didn't do it for the faculty.
I didn't do it for the uni.
I did it for you.
The prize I got is also yours.
I just represented you.
Nonsense.
You won this by yourself.
That's not true.
I was there because you gave up your position for me.
You pushed me.
You supported me.
I couldn't have done it without you.
For my beloved.
The true Ambassador in my heart.
I love you.
I love you too.
What are we doing here?
Well, Pha didn't reply to my text.
Wait, calm down.
You can't expect him to stay with you all day like
when he was a freshman or a sophomore.
He's a grown up now and he's got more responsibilities.
You of all people should know that.
You work for your Dad's company.
I think I'm reasonable.
But this is too much, man.
He just didn't change a bit. He changed a lot.
And have you talked to him about this?
Well, not exactly.
But I said something, so he could think,
Mmm.
Something like, aren't you gonna stay for a meal?
Aren't you gonna sleep with me again?
And...
That's enough.
Even a fool knows that you're mad now.
And I think he does too.
I guess.
What if he found a pretty doctor and changed his mind?
You're being nonsense.
He's very busy.
And you two have been together for so long,
and you still don't know each other well?
Stop being so dramatic.
Let's go.
Let's spy on him.
Like how we spied on him at the faculty.
Back then, you spied on him, and I spied on my guy.
C'mon.
You're just too much.
Too much?
Buddy, why are you wearing shades and a hat?
Why don't you go back and change?
But even if you take those off, you still stand out.
Just do whatever you need to do.
Hello, Mr. Yo, would you like any help?
Er...
Right now, the doctor is in the examine room.
And there are full of patients now.
Oh, you can remember me?
Of course, Mr. Yo.
Thank you, then may I be excused?
Please.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
How do you know him?
Why are you hiding?
Everyone saw you.
Shhh.
What?
Do you think Pha is in the room?
I guess so.
He wouldn't be flirting with any girls outside.
Darn you.
What?
Seriously, he doesn't seem like
he's gonna change his mind.
You think too much.
C'mon, let's go.
Hey, c'mon, stay.
It's a waste of time, let's go.
Don't jump to conclusion.
What?
Wait.
We've been waiting for long. Let's go.
C'mon, a bit more.
Oh.
Oh, it's on you, then.
Can we go now?
No.
Alright, don't forget to take the medicine on time.
Alright.
Goodbye.
Doctor, a guest is here to see you.
Mmm, if it's a pretty girl with great figure...
please tell her that I'm busy.
Er...if it's pretty girls, then, there are plenty.
But I told them that you're busy, so they left.
But there are two more coming.
One of them is Mr. Yo.
The other one is quite handsome and stylish.
C'mon, you've seen this handsome doctor everyday...
Are you not used to it yet?
Oh, why didn't you tell me sooner that they're here?
Well, you're busy.
Mmm, it's fine.
So, which guest should I invite in first?
This is the next patient's folder.
And...
Mr. Wayo.
I told you they could recognize you.
Please go see the doctor in the examine room.
Pha.
Sit down.
Are you here to see me?
Yeah.
I saw a lot of girls coming to see you.
I don't know them.
They were hitting on me.
Then...
I'll leave.
I have less than 30-minute break.
Please stay for a talk.
I have nothing to talk about.
Yo.
I'm a little mad.
Do you love me less?
Or have you changed your mind?
Yo.
It's not like that.
Answer me.
Why are you quiet?
Why did it take you so long to answer?
Yo.
It's not like that.
I have my reasons.
I got a lot of work.
You know that.
You've always had lots of work.
You said you studied hard.
When you work, you have lots of work to do.
You don't care about me.
Then can I ask you something?
If I'm still like this, can you put up with it?
I don't sleep at the time that you do.
Some days, I won't be able to go home.
I won't have time to take you out,
to have a meal together...
to watch a movie together...
to listen to music together...
like we used to when I was a freshman or a sophomore.
If I keep being like this, will you be okay with that?
Why are you asking that?
Then, I'll go home first.
Yo.
If you can't endure it,
do you know what we both will be like?
No.
Where is Ming?
Wake him up to talk to me.
Where is Yo?
Don't think that we're grown ups,
and I won't dare fight you.
Mingkwan.
Really?
He hasn't come home.
Where could Yo be?
Instagram?
Alright, that's it.
Pha.
What's up, little brat?
Is it like before?
How?
Well, you liked to sit here and watch me play basketball.
Right here. It's your favorite spot, isn't it?
And you used to bring me water.
And you never paid attention to me.
Right over there.
You found a cat, didn't you?
How did you know that?
Of course, I knew.
I'd always noticed you.
I got eyes on you.
C'mon.
This is late. Let's head back.
What? I came here to sit alone.
If you'd like to go back, then go.
Are you crazy?
I came here to pick you up.
Let's head back together, alright?
C'mon.
You peeked at me and you got me at last.
And still, you're overthinking?
How could I not?
You don't pay attention to me, Pha.
I do.
I was just testing you.
What?
I just pretended that I didn't care about you.
But about the time that I don't have, that's for real.
I'm afraid that one day...
you won't be okay with it.
And it wouldn't be too late,
if you have a new start.
What are you thinking?
Hey, wait, chill, chill, chill.
I've been mad since when you asked me
if I could endure it.
You being a doctor...seriously, c'mon,
what were you thinking? Are you nuts?
How many years have we been together?
How could I not know how you're like?
How could I not endure it?
Er...
Don't start.
I'm mad that you don't pay attention to me.
Honestly, why would you do such a thing?
It's a waste of time.
I'm okay with you not having time.
But I'm not okay with you not paying attention to me.
Are we clear?
Yes.
I love you, Yo.
C'mon, let's go home.
No.
C'mon.
Hurry up, give me a hug, little brat.
Come here, don't be stubborn.
Little brat.
Don't tease me again.
I know that already.
Are you back, darling?
Mmm. I'm tired.
Oh, I miss you!
Oh, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
Well, I got something for you.
What is it?
Can I take a rest for today?
I'm exhausted.
Why do you close your eyes? Open them!
What's HKT?
It's Phuket.
Huh?
You booked a flight to Phuket?
Mmm.
Don't tell me that your parents booked it but can't make it.
Are you crazy? I bought it for you.
It's the present for finishing the exam.
Since when?
Since our pool villa trip.
Really?
And when are we going?
Tonight.
Huh?
Tonight!
Mmm.
Then, we should hurry and pack our bags.
And we'll continue our sweet moment together in Phuket.
Why do you make that face?
Go pack your bags!
Or we'll miss the flight!
Hurry up!
I think this Hawaiian shirt is kinda cute.
Would you like to take it?
Thanks.
Let's take that too.
And the games too.
Take them all.
And...RC cars too, so we could play it by the sea, okay?
And, guitar too.
And what else should we bring?
Ming, how could they all fit in a bag?
That's quite big. You could take them all.
Take them.
Why'd you bring a teddy bear?
So I can hug him.
Let's take this car here. Take the teddy bear out.
It's pretty nice.
Keep it out.
Why?
I'll continue.
Good?
Mmm.
It's gonna be runied.
What should I do?
I guess I will be like that too.
What's that?
Pha!
Pha has a key to you room?
Right, my Mom gave him another copy.
Darn!
Pha!
I...I'll head back.
No need to.
It's my cousin's room.
You can stay.
Alright.
I came by to see you.
Auntie Prow is worried.
I thought you were gonna be crying and all that.
For getting The Ambassador taken away.
Mom—
Next time you come over, knock on the door first.
I didn't hear anything from outside.
Do you guys moan at all?
Huh?
If you never moaned so loud that next door can hear you,
that means you're not doing it well, Tatch.
Please consider it your homework.
Alright.
Okay, okay, I'm fine, don't worry.
You can go home now.
Alright, alright, I won't be a bother anymore.
Do whatever you need to.
Alright, so to you, am I alright?
What's alright and what's not?
Am I good enough to take care of you bro here?
I'm good-looking, I'm rich
and I'm the uni's ambassador.
You already had him.
Why would you show off your qualities now?
If my bro loves someone,
do I have the right to stop him?
Then, you, take a good care of my bro. I count on you.
Why so happy?
I've gained your cousin's trust.
And it's been the thing I've always wanting to prove.
But...
we still have a mission to do.
What mission?
To make you scream so loud the next door can hear you.
Hey!
Are you crazy?
Come here.
Hey, don't, he'll come back!
Relax.
Pha, what's with the cruise in all of a sudden?
Because I have something I need to
ask a permission from you, Yo.
A permission?
And you had to go through all this?
Of course.
Hey, Lom!
Why are you so late?
We're about to leave now.
Oh, hello, Pha and Yo.
Hello, hello.
Hello.
Why did you call us here?
You'll find out.
Really.
Oh, you're keeping secrets now?
You had us all dressed up...
You complained so much.
You could jump off the river and go home.
Alright, you, crazy cousin!
Right, I am crazy.
I was just playing.
Come here, sit down and eat.
Yo, give him the glass.
So, what do you have in mind?
It's a long term thing, Yo.
I must wait until you graduate.
What are you up to?
Are you gonna study abroad?
No.
Yo.
When you graduate,
will you marry me?
Yo!
Don't be quiet.
I'm scared.
Yo.
I love you, Wayo.
I love you, Pha.
Let's stay together forever.
That's so romantic.
What's wrong with you, Tatch?
What is it, Tatch?
Normally, I'm not a romantic person.
And you know that.
I only got sincerity for you.
What's wrong with you?
I have a gift for you.
But you need to promise me first,
that you'll say you like it;
though you may not like it...
Why wouldn't I like it?
I'll like it for sure.
Anything that comes from you, I always like it.
I hope you'll like it.
What's gotten into you?
Don't be romantic.
I'm shy.
Man, you're ruining the moment.
I thought I could be romantic.
C'mon, give me your hand.
Now, it's your turn.
Wear it for me.
You'll wear it often, right?
Forever.
And you? Will you wear it often?
I might...wear it for the rest of my life.
Could you do that? There's only one ring
and you'll have to wear it for the rest of your life?
Then you buy me a lot more.
Lom, I love you.
Very much.
I love you too.
Right, what's with Panon now?
Do you know?
Why do you ask?
Nothing, I just feel for Parak.
No matter what, they're twin brothers.
Mmm. Rak told me that after what happened...
Panon apologized to Parak.
I think they've made things up.
Parak told Panon to stay out of our business.
Mmm, that's the way to end it.
Why are you smiling?
Can I not look at my boyfriend and smile?
Tatch.
Yes?
Can I ask you for one thing?
You can ask me for anything.
I can give them all to you.
If one day, you get bored of me and wanna leave me,
please let me know.
So I can handle it.
Why did you say that?
Honestly, you're stuck to me.
But I really like the way you are, like this.
But what if one day you change,
what am I supposed to do?
I can't leave you, my boyfriend.
My boyfriend is super sweet.
Anyone could say that.
Hold on, Lom.
Hey, what is that?
Clearly, it's a pocket knife.
I know that, but why are you taking it out?
Don't tell me that you're gonna cut yourself
and do the blood swear.
I'm not gonna do that. It hurts.
Hey, Tatch, don't, don't.
Are you crazy?
Have you watched too much of Kwan-Riam?
You, look that way.
Take a look at your Instagram,
I've already tagged you.
Hmm?
See? I wasn't just saying,
I posted it on Instagram too.
Crazy!
Are you really Lomnaw (Cold wind)?
You're not cold.
You're warm.