So you're here alone?
Then can I spend a night here?
Chill, Ming.
It just made me think.
Think about what?
That you have someone else.
I didn't see you at the dorm.
You didn't answer any of my calls.
He's with me.
He asked me to go with him.
Don't do it next time.
Tarntatch, do you know that Uni's Moon?
He stares so intensely.
A little but we're not that close.
Lom and I are a couple.
We like each other.
Tatch.
Tatch, how long are you gonna avoid me?
We haven't cleared things up.
We have.
I don't have any feelings for you, Marn.
That's not true. You just don't know what you feel.
Marn, the thing is...
Lom and I are a couple.
We like each other.
That's not true. You're joking, right?
Huh?
Lom.
You like Tatch?
You like him even though that day
you were there for me.
You took me out for a meal.
And you listened to every story I told you about Tatch?
Well, I didn't...
Lom, how could you be such a jerk?
Marn.
Don't talk to Lom like that.
Why, Tatch?
He really is a jerk.
But not only Lom, who is a jerk...
you, Tatch, is also a jerk.
Marn, calm down.
I've never liked you, Marn.
I've liked guys all my life.
And when you dumped Parak to talk to me,...
that made everyone in the school hate me.
That makes you a jerk too.
Oh, so you're telling me that you're not wrong at all?
I am, for not clearing things up with you, Marn.
That I don't like girls.
But you can't talk to Lom like that.
Mmm. I get it now.
Then you should enjoy your love.
Because a jerk deserves to be with a jerk.
This happens so many times already.
Everytime Marnfah came to me,
it always ended up like this.
But this time, she won't come back anymore.
At least, if Marnfah had listened to you,
she would've known what the reason was.
You have a football practice, right?
I wanna go watch it.
Don't, you need to go practice
answering questions with the seniors.
Alright, I know that.
I don't like these shoes.
Can I throw them away?
Those are expensive.
I'll return them.
How? His feet are way bigger than yours.
Just throw them away.
We could give them to the charity.
There's no problem with the shoes.
At least, they could still be useful.
Alright.
Can I ask you something?
What if I don't win...
and the whole faculty scolds me,
will the world come to an end?
Aren't you overthinking about that?
What are you worried about?
I just wanna win
because I wanna see you smile.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Just do you best, that's all.
I understand your cousin's feelings now.
How much pressure do I have to carry?
Well, how about this?
Just do your best and be yourself.
And don't mind the rest.
Okay?
Let's go!
Let's get some sleep!
Are you really gonna sleep?
"Louknam is calling..."
Hello.
Something happened, Lom!
What happened?
We've been played.
Tarntatch needs to be ready before 9 a.m.
They just informed me that all the Moons contestants
need to do an activity with the dean.
Darn!
At 9 a.m.?
I'll handle it.
Okay, hurry up and get to the faculty. I'm waiting.
Got it.
Tatch, Tatch, wake up!
Something's up.
You need to be at the faculty by 9 a.m.
Huh?
What?
Get up!
You need to be there before 9 a.m.
Then when will I see you today?
This afternoon. I'll be at the booth all day.
So I wouldn't get to spend my morning with you.
C'mon, you need to go take a shower.
It's late now.
Go!
Shower!
Hurry up!
Hey!
Could you shave for me?
Huh?
Please shave for me.
You want me to shave for you?
Is this the booth of Faculty of Agriculture?
Yes, it is.
What's up, Lom?
Oh, isn't this Tarntatch's imaginary pair on Instagram?
Don't you remember?
Oh, you're Lomnaw, right?
You look better than on Instagram.
So you're Parak, Panon's twin brother?
Mmm.
Are you here to see Tatch?
In what way?
Just coming by
to say...I miss him.
Hey, if you're gonna talk that way,
you need to ask his boyfriend first..
His boyfriend?
There, there. As I thought.
Panon fooled me.
Huh? What about? I don't know what you're talking about.
I think we'll come back later.
By then, everything will be cleared up already.
Er...
Can I ask you something?
Yes?
Are you still mad at Tatch?
I guess you could say, I've stopped being a fool.
Can I talk to you?
Guys, please take care of this for me.
Why, what's up?
What's there to talk about?
About you, actually.
But can we go somewhere else?
So we can have a long talk.
Is there any good place to eat around here?
A place that sells beer too.
Yeah, there is.
Take me there.
Of course.
Then I'll see you this evening.
Come on. I'll help you pack.
Are you tired?
So how do you know Lom?
I briefly saw his Instagram.
We just had a first talk at the booth.
He's kinda cute.
I understand now why Non likes him.
You're bugging me now, Rak.
Just kidding.
No matter how much he likes him,
he'll get heart-broken someday.
So why did you come here?
Can't I come to see my friend?
That's bold of you to say.
You're such...
I don't know if love blinded you.
No.
You only listened to what Panon expressed
and what Marnfah said.
But you never listened to me.
Never believed me that this friend wouldn't hurt you.
You really make me feel guilty.
Why don't you just stab me?
I'd love to.
Hey, Tatch?!
Your friend's just...
I already have someone.
If I go to jail, how would that person live?
Is that right?
Darn! Were you joking?
Your joke is good.
Of course.
But it's unbelievable.
I thought you like girls all this time.
I think I've never flirted a girl for you to see.
But many girls like you.
I can't help with that 'cause I'm super hot.
Your jokes are always good.
So, where's your bottle?
Let's clink the glasses.
Cheers.
Really?
Can you do one thing for me?
What's it?
Can you not stop being my friend?
What a drama?
Who would do that?
Is that right, guys?
Absolutely.
Darn, how did you get here?
Rak texted me that he found you.
He told us to come here.
Actually, we came to see you since the afternoon,
but your boyfriend said you're free in the evening.
So we went back to our uni first.
Darn, I feel like I haven't met you for a long time.
I'm being sentimental.
No, no, no. Don't cry.
If you cry, you have to finish your drink.
But first, you have to order.
Excuse me...
I'll order it for you.
Alright, thank you.
So, how are you?
Same old, same old. Still don't get what I study.
Same here. So confused.
Me too.
"I'm sitting outside." "It's sentimental. I don't want your friends
to see my tears." "Just spend time with your friends. "
Why are you sitting alone?
I want you guys to reminisce.
You can join us.
Everyone's okay with that.
Man, you guys are heavy drinkers.
Come on, you won't get drunk.
It's only 2 crates.
2 crates!
Tarntatch can drink a lot.
That's true.
Anyway, why did you make up with Tatch?
You two were mad at each other before.
I heard that Non was about to
attack Tatch in front of the clinic.
I thought it was kinda strange.
And things between Marnfah and I ended long time ago.
I don't know why he picked a fight with Tatch.
So I started to follow Tatch's Instagram again.
I saw he's dating you.
And I checked Marnfah's timeline.
And it got suspicious.
Because Tatch didn't do anything with Marnfah.
I was...like a worthless person.
I blindly kept chasing the person who didn't love me.
It isn't just not loving my friends, it's not loving myself as well.
But you came to realization.
After I started to love myself, I had to solve the matter
about Tatch, which was still bothering me.
What are you doing?
I'm consoling your friend.
What's wrong? Why do you need to console him?
I told your boyfriend about the time
when I was in the hospital.
Ah, the time you almost committed suicide?
Yeah.
I understand.
But talking alone with boyfriend, isn't it too much?
You're so jealous.
Of course.
Tatch, keep this boyfriend of yours.
I'll go drink beer with the guys.
Hurry up and join us.
Okay.
Are you not joining your friends?
I am. But only with you.
Recently, I just texted you to spend time with your friends.
My friends are your friends, aren't they?
That's right, but...
You got too sentimental?
Yeah, I did.
Love and friendship are very heartwarming.
Parak is so right.
I have to keep you.
I'm a rare stuff, right?
Teaser.
Do I look great?
I'll wear this in the competition tomorrow.
Are you having a football match
or fitting for a model shoot?
You haven't seen the good part yet.
Here.
What about it?
What's about 17?
It's your birthday.
Speechless, aren't you?
Are you that happy?
Extremely.
But I'm just a substitute.
I don't know if I'd get to play.
I don't care about that.
I only care about the number on your shirt.
It's said if you have sex before the competition,
you'll look better.
Who said that?
I did.
You're such a...
I'll do it gently.
Please.
Please, dear.
Panon.
Here, I'll answer it.
Hey, wait!
What the heck do you want?
Man, you're so cool.
Hello.
What's your business?
Huh?!
What are you talking about?
Can you speak human language?
What are you babbling about?
Lom, come see me down here!
Lomnaw!
Lom!
Lom, come see me down here!
Lomnaw!
Lom!
I...Tatch...Tatch, he...
What the heck is wrong with him?
I think he's drunk.
He dares come to the dorm?
Does he think I'm gonna let it be that easily?
Stay here. I'll go down.
Tatch, don't. I'll go.
Are you crazy?
I'll clear things up with him.
If you're concerned, you can come with me.
It won't settle.
Not to you. But to me, it will.
How do you know?
Because I already have a boyfriend.
Then I'll watch from around the elevator.
Answer my call, Lom.
Lom, you come to see me.
What do you want?
I just...
I just want to try to change your mind.
One last time.
Tatch is a jerk, you know.
He's the cause why Rak hates me.
I think you made that up.
Rak is your brother.
He knows you well.
If he's to hate you, it won't involve Tatch.
That's not true.
Tatch is a liar.
I think you should go home and carefully think about it.
I've thought this through.
Judging from how you look, you haven't thought at all.
That's my business.
What about you, Lom?
What do you say?
I've come to see you here, and you still like Tatch?
I don't like him.
Are you serious?
I am.
I don't like him.
But I love him.
Tatch and I are a couple.
So stop bothering me.
My boyfriend doesn't like it.
Darn, he's such a stealer.
Huh?
What did he steal?
I met you before him.
You know what, you're such a loser.
Lom.
I don't have anything else to talk to you.
Just go back.
And just stop...
messing with people's minds.
Be reasonable.
Don't judge anything by your hatred.
Somehow, your life may be better.
Lom.
Lomnaw!
Lom!
Come back to me!
You're so cool.
How was it cool?
I'm so upset.
That jerk didn't listen to anything.
The things you said hit him pretty hard.
If he'd only listened,...
Now it's your turn.
Find sometime to clear things up with him.
I've been thinking about what to do.
Let's go to the room.
Wanna continue?
To hell with continue. I'm upset.
Alright, alright.
Let's wait after the contest, deal?
"What are you doing?"
"Putting on make-up."
"Almost ready for fitting."
"Wanna see what you wear."
"I'll practice answering the question."
"Alright. Do your best."
"You've got this."
Alright, Tarntatch, next is the question from the judges.
Say, if you were the university ambassador,
what would you do for the university?
Prepare your answer, okay?
Alright.
So, mainly, the question is about this, right?
That's right.
The first pair, come forward.
Walk, greet.
Beautifully.
Back to your post.
Next.
1 hour before the Ambassador Contest
Oh! The rehearsal is finished?
Already.
I'll be right back.
I'll take care of your make-up but I need restroom first.
Alright.
"We won the football match."
"Darn, that's great."
"Let's celebrate."
"Hey, hey, easy, easy."
"Wait for the result of the Ambassador."
"We're counting on you, Tarntatch."
"Right, Tatch, the football team is counting on you."
"Just wait and see."
"How's Lom?"
"Darn, they're flirting in the group chat."
"Woooo."
Tarntatch!
Have you heard? We won the football tournament.
I have.
The group chat keeps ringing.
So happy about that.
Do you know how Lomnaw is?
Lomnaw...?
As far as I know, Lomnaw twisted his ankle during the match.
Now he's in the infirmary.
No need to worry.
But he might not be able to see the contest.
I'll check on Lomnaw quickly.
Hey, hey, wait, wait.
The contest starts in 1 hour.
I'll be quick.
If it still bothers me, I can't focus on the contest.
Okay, okay.
Alright, I'll let you go. But...
Promise me.
You have to come back for a stand-by
half an hour before, okay?
Okay.
Thank you so much.
You're okay, but I'm not.
What's going on today?
It's so messy. My hair is messy too.
Hello, Am, where are you?
I'm at the canteen. What are you calling for?
I'm worried about Lom. Are you with him?
I said I am at the canteen. Lom is still sleeping.
Don't worry.
No one is with Lom?
No. He fell asleep right after taking the medicine.
Which room is Lom in?
At the pharmacy. Wait.
Are you going to look for him?
The contest starts in an hour, Tat.
"Panon is calling."
You saw the pic I sent you, right?
Non, what do you want?
Whoa, whoa, take it easy, man.
You want your boyfriend back, right?
Am! Listen to me.
Panon took Lomnaw.
He sent me a pic.
Huh!
What the heck?
It's me, it's me, it's me.
Tatch!
Return Lomnaw to me!
So what you want?
Wanna have a brawl?
Take it easy.
Tatch!
Help Tatch.