Lom, are you close to Tatch?
Recently, I feel like that he's changed.
Lom, do you happen to know why?
He seemed so troubled that
you disappeared in all of a sudden.
Really?
So do you like girls or guys?
Answer me.
So I'd know whether I should continue or stop.
What's up?
Tatch, since I've been with you,
today, you look like a fool.
I went to bed quite late last night.
Yeah, forget it. No matter how foolish you look,
you still look so freakin' handsome.
Should we kick him into a poop pile?
I wanna know if you'd still look this handsome.
If I'm in a poop pile,
I'll drag you both in too.
But I'm certain that even if I dive into the pile,
I'd still look handsome.
Whatever, handsome.
He's not here yet.
What?
You don't have to act all innocent.
I know that you were looking for Lom.
Tatch, take a look.
Your followers are 25K.
And Lom's are 66K.
Darn, why is there a huge gap?
It's better this way.
We're wondering about one thing.
Yesterday, what did you talk to Lom in front of the class?
Oh.
Well...
I...
I asked Lom if he liked girls or guys...
Darn!
Well, so I'd know if I should stop
what I'm doing or continue.
I think he knows now how you feel about him.
If he doesn't, then he's really stupid.
But that may be the case, Lom is really stupid.
That's true.
Well, what you're saying is reasonable.
Look. There he is...
Lom!
My friend likes you.
There's no signal from the number you've dialed...
So, I got turned down?
Who's turned down?
Look at him.
He's blushing and he doesn't know what to do now.
I think there's hope for you, buddy.
Really?
Alright, let's go.
So, so, so...
Got teased since early in the morning.
Calm down.
They were only teasing you a little bit.
Don't get so shocked.
Yeah, what would you do if it were you?
What? I'd say no.
Huh?
Well, I only like handsome guys
because I look at them as idols.
That's it.
Understood?
So what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna let Tatch hit on you?
I don't know. The problem now
is that he's my competitor.
Hmm, I think the real problem for you now is...
why the hell are you shy now?
Or you don't see him as your competitor?
You don't seem to reject him.
You're holding back.
Or maybe you hold back
because you want to take advantage of him.
You let him give you rides.
And rip him off 20,000-30,000 Baht.
I don't know.
I'll just...
think about it first.
Only the pretty ones get to choose.
It's always like that.
Can you use the word "handsome"?
The handsome ones get to choose.
How can I use that word?
He's not handsome.
Well, that's true.
Sompoch, help Papa.
What? Take a look at other unis's Agriculture's Moon,
so darn hot!
Let me see the pics!
They're all your type, girlie.
No, you're Girlie.
Well, they're fabulous.
If other uni's Moons would be this hot, our uni
should send Tarntatch only for The Ambassador contest.
I agree.
We gotta send Tarntatch, no matter what.
If we send Lom, then we would...
What will happen if we send Lomnaw?
definitely lose!
When did you get here?
You popped here just like in a movie.
Why do you think if we send Lom and we will lose?
Because Lomnaw's style is kinda cute,
compared to the representatives from other unis.
Right?
Yeah, I think the cute style won't work. If we send
the handsome and cool one would do us more good.
Right, gal?
Yeah, gal.
Take a look at numbers of the followers on Instagram.
Oh.
Today, your make-up is so gorgeous.
See? I told you.
Can you teach me how to do it?
Your friends are playing a game now.
Are you lost or something?
I'm not lost.
But I'm lost in...
Stop it!
Don't be so cheesy.
Why didn't you look that way
when you were studying?
It's my neck and my eyes.
Why do you have to be so bossy about it?
Because if you didn't look that way,
then I wouldn't be able to see your face.
You didn't look up at all.
Why are you staring at me?
The reason I'm staring at you is....
because...
I want you to see my face clearly.
Happy now?
Mmm.
Now, I'm motivated to study.
Alright, guys, stop chatting.
Are you gonna study or what?
Let's start our lesson.
The scent of love is in the air.
Stop teasing me and start focusing on your studies.
Okay.
Yeah! The number of Tarntatch's followers are up!
What a relief.
But yours are way too far apart.
Do you think Tatch can catch up?
Of course.
Or if not, I have to do everything
in order for him to catch up.
He must be our faculty's representative.
Hey, Lom!
My friend sent me to tell you
that he missed you.
Yeah!
Yeah, my ass, jerks!
They teased you as if you were a high school girl.
Tarntatch seems to be obsessed with you.
Tarntatchtachtach: I've photoshopped a photo.
Take a look.
Whoa, he spent time doing this?
I guess I'll post it.
I haven't updated my Instagram for a while now.
Chill, Lom, your Instagram? Not updated?
Lomnawwwww: The sun is bright but I'm cuter than the sun!
Photo credit: @eyes_wan and @Tarntatchtatchtatch
Whoa, you tagged him too?
That's so sweet!
Darn!
What?
Take a look at Tarntatch's Instagram.
Tarntatch: I'm allergic to the cute one.
Photo credit: @eyes_wan
They're flirting with their captions.
Whoa, I guess I gotta press like unstoppingly.
Lomnawwww: Do you need an anti-histamine?
Wow, wow, wow.
Our friend here is pretty flirty too.
You're no ordinary...huh?
I'm not flirting. I'm just getting on his nerves.
He said he was allergic.
So he needed an anti-histamine.
Oh, really?
Tarntatchtatchtatch: Bring it to my room tonight.
That's it. I'm done playing.
Seriously, you won't be able to keep up with Tatch.
Mmm.
Oh, and where are you going?
I'm going to the Engineering's parking lot.
Why don't you take the bus?
No. I'll just walk there.
See you tomorrow, bye!
What's gotten into him?
I think he's not being active;
he just doesn't know what to do.
He has no idea what to do.
C'mon, let's go.
Right.
"Tarntatch is calling..."
Darn! It's Tatch calling.
Why is he calling?
Hello.
Where are you?
I'm at the uni. What's up?
And where are you?
I'm in my room, about to change into sports clothes.
I think I'm gonna go play soccer.
Oh, okay.
After I'm done, I'm coming back to change again.
Tomorrow, I got no class
so I think I'm gonna go hang out tonight.
So?
So, what?
Am I allowed?
If you wanna go, then go.
Why are you asking me this?
I have to.
If I don't have your permission, I won't go.
Then you can go.
I must do everything that you're okay with,
so you'll like me.
Do whatever you want.
You don't have to ask me.
I have to.
You can go anywhere you want.
Why are you asking me?
Are you sure?
You won't get all dramatic after that, right?
Are you my boyfriend?
If you wanna go somewhere, just go.
You don't need to ask me.
Well, it's because I want to be your boyfriend,
that's why I have to ask.
So you'll know that
I behave well and listen to you.
So you'll easily give in.
So, cutie...do you give in now?
Cutie, my ass!
I guess not.
Can you hear me?
From now on, if you got something on your mind,
you can call me.
I have no businesses to call you.
Well, if you got no one
to pick you up or drop you off,
no friends to have a meal with,...
no one to accompany you,
you can always call me.
And if you miss me, you must call me.
Really? Who would have such a thought?
Alright, alright, I give up now.
That's all, bye.
What?
So he hung up just like that?
Or did he really give up earlier?
Hello.
What's up?
Nothing.
So you called me but you got nothing to say?
Well, can I not?
I haven't said anything.
Then, that'd be all.
Lom.
Huh? Yeah?
"I miss you," isn't so hard to say.
Are you crazy?
We just met during the day.
You're a chicken.
Just an "I miss you".
Alright, alright.
Well, if you were here in front of me right now,
I would tell you face to face.
Right, you said it yourself.
Let's hear it.
Er...I give up.
I'm a chicken.
Why are you following me?
You don't have to follow me.
I'm sending you off to your car.
I know where my car is.
Where are you going?
Your car is right here.
Get in the car first.
If you don't leave now, I'll think of it as if
you wanna spend more time with me.
Tatch.
Yes?
Tonight, if you're gonna go out for a drink,
don't look at other people.
Whoa, why do you go to such a classy place?
Look, man. That's the 5th one.
He's darn hot.
Why is he so hot?
Tarntatch: Are you not asleep yet?
Lomnaw: This is an auto-message.
Lomnaw: Hottie...
Tarntatch: Who's a hottie?
Tarntatch: I have no interest in anyone else but you.
Tarntatch: Did you just trick me to speak the truth?
Lomnaw: You're silly.
Tarntatch: If you like it,
I can keep telling you this.
Tarntatch: The reason my friend said that
because there were five people asking for my number.
Lomnaw: Right, handsome guy.
Tarntatch: I didn't give it to anyone.
Tarntatch: So my friends were teasing me about it.
Tatch, when you're done, follow us.
Mmm.
Let's go.
Hello.
Are you alright?
You read the text but you didn't reply.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Are you thinking about something too much?
No, I'm not thinking about anything too much.
Are you sure?
Mmm.
If you're upset, I can go to your place right now.
Hey, are you crazy?
About other people asking for my number,
I don't think you should think about it too much.
Because I'd turned them down completely.
You should be proud that the one
who likes you are very much wanted.
What should I feel now?
You're complimenting yourself for me to listen...
You just focus on the part that I like you.
Hello?
Did I make you stunned?
Give me some time to be shy a little bit.
Oh?
I wanna see that.
There's no way.
Tatch.
How come we both have become like this?
I've...
liked you since you were drinking at Am's.
On the day that you lost in the Moon contest.
I've gotten some more beer.
Did you drink that night?
I was there after you'd already been drunk.
You took that advantage to like me.
Well, if I approach you directly,
you wouldn't like me.
Because at that time,
I was running away from what I was supposed to get.
And I let you get into the contest instead.
Anyhow, I still think
that you're more suitable than I am.
Don't underestimate yourself.
Mmm.
And if I didn't get on your nerves,
then you wouldn't talk to me.
If I didn't scold you,
you wouldn't scold me back.
I was so afraid you weren't even gonna look at me.
So I had to do it my way.
And one more thing, you liked Manfah.
Manfah.
Although I placed second from the bottom,
but my love from you is at the top, Manfah.
No!
Not since I met you.
It's just like I've been more interested
in you than any other people.
Really?
Mmm.
Because I'm handsome?
Whatever, hottie.
So are you still thinking about that?
Not anymore.
If I didn't call you,
there would be a drama, wouldn't it?
I don't think so.
Don't think about it too much.
About this kind of stuff,
I always have my guard up.
I've faced it all my life.
Hey, Tatch, what are you doing?
The senior asked me to come get you to drink.
Huh? What senior?
What? Our seniors.
Right, they just got here.
And...whom...are you talking to?
Oh, a person I'm seeing.
Hey!
You're quite something.
Who is it?
Is it the one I'm thinking about?
Am, just leave him alone.
Let's go. You should hang up soon
and come drink with us.
Alright, I'll be right there.
Then, I'll go drink now.
Mmm.
So if the seniors are there,
this could last till dawn, right?
I don't think so.
I'm afraid that you'll be worried.
Mmm, text me when you're back, alright?
Mmm.
Gotta go now. Bye.
Bye.
"Gotta go now."
"Louknam is calling..."
Hello.
Hello, Lom!
I don't think he's gonna make it.
Just only two days left, Lom.
Tarntatch still needs 35k followers
in order to beat you.
Huh? 35k?
How about this? I got an idea.
Well, it might be a little dumb.
But I'll go ask for the pic of Tarntatch
from Glasses and post it on my Instagram.
Are you here for the pics?
Glasses is not here so I already took it.
Huh? Why would you come here and take my pics?
So I could do a photoshop for you.
I came here to take his pics.
But he came here to take my pics.
Darn! Why is it so weird?
Are you talking to yourself?
Huh? No, no, no.
But you seem like you're fighting with yourself.
Nevermind. Have you called Glasses?
What?
He cut me off.
"I'm at my idols' concert. Not available
to answer the call from a maggot like you."
He's at the concert.
Mmm...then, would you like to go grab some coffee?
Are you inviting me?
Yes, I'm asking you out on a date.
I think your number of followers seems to be stable.
Don't you want to do anything with it?
It's fine with whatever it may be.
But you were the one who told me
to post lots of pics and stories often.
Can you send me a pic?
Why?
Well, people seem to like it when you're with me.
So I think I'm gonna post your pic.
This way, I'm also helping you get more followers.
Then, I'll go live.
Hey, really?
On one condition.
What's that?
After the live, you have to video call me.
For what?
I want to see your face before going to bed.
Alright.
But I haven't got my pics from Glasses.
Then, give me your phone.
I'll take a selfie.
Lomnawwwww: Occupied.
All done.
Hey!
You posted it yourself?
Well, it's my pic.
"Am: Bonehead, Tatch, did you occupy
the space or Lom's Instagram?"
"Tarntatchtatchtatch: Whatever,
but I've occupied everything here."
I got quite a lot of followers.
"Tarntatch is calling..."
You're so quick. Aren't you gonna go to
the restroom or drink something first?
You're already sleepy?
Well, a little bit.
Mmm, then I'm not gonna bother you.
I'll let you go to bed.
Er...then I'm off to bed.
Okay, sweet dreams, Lom.
Sweet dreams, Tatch.
Oh, right, tomorrow, we got a morning class.
The teacher just texted us in the chat group.
When?
When you went live.
Mmm, and are you going anywhere in the afternoon?
I don't know. What do you suggest?
I'll be waiting for someone to post a story, I guess.
Chome? Lerdluck? Karat? Kalaya? Or...
Sompoch, of course.
You!
Tatch!
Does it freeze?
Darn!
What's wrong with you, Lom?
Just a frozen screen, and you're shocked?
Bonehead Tatch, are you getting on my nerves?
Well, you did that first.
But when I get on your nerves, you seem cute.
Are we gonna get some sleep, you and I?
So why don't we skip the sleep
and keep video calling all night?
Go to bed already, I'm gonna do that too.
I'm melting.
Alright, sweet dreams, Lom.
Mmm, sweet dreams, Tatch.
Bye.
My gosh, how can he be this cute?
"Panon: Why don't we meet up?"
"Panon: It's been a while."
"Panon: Don't turn me down this time."
Here, I got the movie tickets.
Why do you look so stressed?
Well, I've got something on my mind.
About the Ambassador contest?
Hey, how do you know that?
Oh, well, I'm also a representative.
Let's go shopping.
Before the movie starts.
Hold these for me.
I'm happy that I'll get to do
this kind of activity with you.
It must be pretty fun.
I may not be the representative.
Because the one who's gonna be is Tatch.
He's way more handsome than me.
So you're really close to him, aren't you?
Well, yeah.
I don't want you and him to be close.
Why not?
He stole my brother's girlfriend.
Hey! Are you serious?
Yeah. Manfah studies at the same uni as you.
She's a uni's Star too.
I liked Tatch
even though I already had a boyfriend.
So I broke up with Parak
to begin a relationship with Tatch.
Is your brother Parak?
Yes, Parak.
The one who steals other people's girlfriend
wouldn't be a good person, would it?
"Tarntatchtatchtatch: Where are you?"
"Tarntatchtatchtatch: You haven't posted a story yet."
Here, this is yours.
Huh? Wait, you bought these for me?
Well, they got your size, not mine.
Oh? And why would you buy them?
C'mon, just take them.
I saw you posted a story
saying that you wanted these.
"Lomnawwwww: Wait for me, my babies."
Wait, you took a screenshot of my story?
I saw them and I wanted them too.
Actually, I can buy these myself, you know.
It's alright. Take them as
your birthday present in advance.
That's like eight more months before my birthday.
It's okay. I wanted to buy them for you.
Why are you being so nice to me?
I'll pay you back when I have the chance.
Alright, if you want to pay me back,
you just have to beat Tatch.
And join The Ambassador contest with me.
Thanks for buying me the shoes today.
It's alright, man.
Mmm.
Okay, I'll see you later.
See ya. Bye.
Bye.
Lomnawwwww: Sorry, I was at the movie.
Tarntatchtatchtatch: Was it fun?
Lomnawwwww: Yeah.
Tarntatchtatchtatch: You went there alone?
Lomnawwwww: With a friend.
Tarntatchtatchtatch: Which one?
Lomnawwwww: Panon.
Lomnawwwww: Actually, I have something to ask you.
"Pha: Let's play soccer.
Happy Buffalo Field. 7:30 p.m."
"Pha: You must come."
"Lomnawwwww: I can't..."
"Pha: There's not enough people.
Bring your friends too."
"Lomnawwwww: Okay."
Hello, guys.
Hey.
Oh? Why are there so few of you?
Someone's boyfriend went to a camp again.
That's why we don't have enough people.
It's like you're mentioning me and Beam.
Well, yeah.
Well, there will be more people coming.
Let's join them, I guess.
And...isn't Wayo here too?
Yo's reading comics at the dorm.
Oh, right, I told you to bring some friends.
Did you invite them?
Oh, I already texted them.
They're on their way.
Alright, good. Then, should we go jogging for a warm up?
That's good so we won't get muscle cramps.
What's muscle camp-camp?
Well, cramps.
Oh, that's how doctors say it.
Yeah, let's go.
C'mon, follow us.
Pha, Pha.
What's up?
Right, did you invite the silverware guy?
You mean Tatch?
If he's the one who wears
lots of silver accessories, then yeah.
Well, I invited my friends
but I don't know if he'll come too or not.
Mmm.
Right, are you fighting?
He ditched you?
No.
So you ditched him?
What? Then what happened?
Well, I don't really have guts to talk to him.
But in order to fix it,
you need to talk, don't you?
I don't know.
Do you want me to help clear things up?
Are you nuts?
If you can't do it, then I have to help you.
I'm like your brother.
Hey, are those your friends, Lom?
They're finally here.
Hello.
You remember when Yo and I had a big problem, right?
The one that you haven't told me yet?
Well, I'll tell you now.
Let's go.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm here to see Yo.
Yo, Yo!
Hey!
Yo!
Let me go!
What are you guys doing?