As I male and batter
you
Are in
Three days ago, I found this thread here.
This thread has no color, no taste, and is also called the shadowless thread.
It can not only control the shadow, but also kill people.
When I was doing the autopsy, I found a scratch on the owner's finger.
It is exactly the same as the shadowless thread.
When the murder took place, the owner had multiple shadowless threads.
Really?
The only person who could use this thread that night was Ah Cai from the shadowless building.
Ah Cai, do you have anything else to say?
Do you think your theory is right?
Why would I kill the owner?
Your theory is not true.
One shadowless person can only control one shadowless person.
And I have good memory, and two hands can control two different shadows.
Then the question arises, how can I kill people with two hands?
That's not easy. Use your feet.
Blood? How can I explain the blood?
If the owner had been strangled to death, why would he bleed?
This blood proofed that you are the murderer.
Did you notice anything different about today's scene?
I remember when I watched the shadow drama, the light was on the left. Why is it on the right today?
The light of the scene was on the left.
But when I was checking the scene, I found the blood on the back.
The truth is that someone moved the tomb on the day of the murder.
Ah Cai, do you have anything else to say?
Ah Cai, is it really you? Why did you do that?
Ah Cai, why is it you?
Ah Cai, you killed the owner.
I didn't mean to kill him.
At that time, the salary of the troupe was getting lower and lower.
I wanted to make a new film, and to play a new character.
But the troupe owner didn't agree with my plan.
Impossible! My troupe can't be in the same situation.
Isn't it great to play a character like Chu Han? Why can't we continue to play?
Troupe owner, troupe owner.
The salary of the troupe is getting lower and lower.
You know that.
It's not good to be a regular.
We should do what the audience likes.
Now the audience likes to watch the love drama.
Let's do the love drama.
Okay, I said it. I'm the troupe owner. I said it.
My troupe can only play the old troupe owner.
Troupe owner, troupe owner.
I was rejected several times.
I made a new film and needed a donkey skin.
But the donkey skin is expensive and I have no money.
So I pretended to be a fool.
I took the opportunity to fix the donkey skin.
I secretly transferred the donkey skin in the script.
I was rejected several times.
I took the opportunity to fix the donkey skin.
I secretly transferred the donkey skin in the script.
I used it to make a new film.
But the troupe couldn't keep the fire.
He still found out.
The first half hour of the opening of the drama.
In his room, he saw me.
Ah Cai, what are you doing?
Troupe owner, the drama is about to start.
I'll go prepare.
Stop.
How long have you been doing this?
It's really you.
I've been burning your body for years.
You're stupid.
How dare you steal my money?
Troupe owner, listen to me.
I stole the donkey skin not for others.
I did it for the life of the troupe.
What explanation?
You just want to use your new film.
Okay, I promise you.
Get out of here now.
Go get your food.
Don't come back again.
Troupe owner.
Troupe owner, no.
Troupe owner, you can't drive me away.
Troupe owner, master.
I only know how to make a film.
I can't live without this.
The drama is about to start.
Go prepare.
Stealing your money.
Is that your money?
That's the whole troupe's money.
Forget him, forget him
Forget the flowers in the wound
Forget the little boat going home
Forget, forget him, forget him
Forget the summer of that year
How silly the love song is
Forget the
face that can't be seen again
Forget the three lifetimes
A kiss sealed the past
Forget the black night
Your white clothes
The gray summer
Never dare to say goodbye
I see you again
Forget everything
Forget, forget him, forget him
Forget the flowers in the wound
Forget the boat going home
Forget, forget him, forget him
Forget the summer of that year
How silly the love song is