BEHIND EVERY STAR
EPISODE 7
I heard you two became the hosts
of a new variety show.
It's a musical audition program
called Love Love Musical.
So-hyun and I will both be the hosts
and judges on the show.
Then you two must continue
to see each other at home and work.
You get sick of each other, don't you?
"Get sick of each other"?
I've never felt such a thing with So-hyun.
Gosh, I've got goosebumps.
It must be tough for our agent here
to watch this.
Anyway,
isn't it uncomfortable
sharing the same agent?
You might end up saying something
you probably shouldn't.
Not at all.
We don't keep any secrets between us.
It's already the last question.
What do you think it means to be married?
To be married is
to be with your life's companion
who loves and trusts you.
You came thoroughly prepared.
What about you, Jun-ho?
On a stage called life,
a partner whom you can
trust the most.
Oh, my.
Oh, my, you two are far too sweet.
It's time to let you two go.
When will the program air?
This Saturday at 9 p.m., on tvX.
-Please tune in!
-Thank you.
-Great work--
Inhale.
Exhale.
You're breathing is becoming
more and more comfortable.
ACTRESS KIM SO-HYUN
-Hello?
-Director Ma, what do I do?
Why? What's going on?
I was in my car with a friend,
and I think someone took a picture of us.
What? Is your friend a man?
Did you do something inappropriate?
No, he's a friend from university,
and we were just chatting.
Then what's to worry about?
Well…
Jun-ho thinks I went to my parents' house.
-What?
-You can't tell him no matter what.
He hates it when I meet him.
Goodness. Calm down.
It's late, so go home.
-Go tell Jun-ho the truth.
-What?
Be honest and tell him the truth.
He'll be angrier
if he later finds out that you lied.
Thinking it over,
I may have been mistaken.
They could have taken a selfie
as they walked by, right?
-What?
-Gosh.
That must be it.
I got overly conscious
and took it the wrong way.
Nothing will happen, so don't worry.
-I'm hanging up.
-So-hyun, hello?
Jeez.
Sang-uk?
What is it?
It's what you asked me to do.
I singled out Ko Eun-gyul's scenes
and put them together.
-How's Eun-gyul doing?
-Sorry?
How is he on set?
I thought… Yes.
Everyone compliments him
for doing his best.
He should unless he wants to hear
talk of nepotism.
You don't have to worry about that.
The actors and production crew said
they wanted to work with him again
for his diligence and good character.
Then you can take Ko Eun-gyul from now on.
Sorry?
Well, there aren't a lot of scenes left,
but go to the ones that are left
for some field experience.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Really?
Yes, a director saw you
at your last audition
and he must have liked you a lot.
He's invited you for a different audition.
What's the role?
It's not decided yet.
First, he wants to see you again,
and if there's a fit,
match you with a role.
This happens from time to time.
A director can even create a new role
for an actor they really like.
Let's see.
You can leave after lunch around 1 p.m.
I told Won-jae about it, so go with him.
You aren't coming with me?
I'm swamped with work today.
A callback is a great opportunity,
so make sure to do well.
Okay?
Yes.
I'm going on set from tomorrow
as Eun-gyul's agent.
But don't worry.
I'll be there only as an agent,
and I know best about his strengths
and weaknesses as an actor.
Okay.
Good luck.
It must be tough for him,
so look after him on set.
And I feel bad for you.
It must be tough for you too.
It's okay.
So while we're at it,
I want to try
to set things right from here.
But you already told your wife.
I want to be honest at work too,
and tell them that you're my daughter.
If you say I'm your daughter now,
they'll all feel betrayed by me,
thinking I hid it from them
the whole time.
And there's Eun-gyul too.
I'm fine with how things are,
so please keep it a secret at work
just as it is now.
Okay.
-Should we head out now?
-Okay.
Thank you for the food.
ACTRESS KIM SO-HYUN
MISSED CALLS
Isn't that the president of Star Media?
And our president's wife next to him…
-"Is he a musical actor too?"
-This is just awful.
-She usually doesn't upload this stuff.
-When did this happen?
I can't believe it.
-What's wrong?
-Look.
Someone uploaded this on social media,
then deleted it right away,
but it already got around.
I'm starting to see articles too.
This wasn't edited, was it?
You knew?
I talked to So-hyun yesterday.
He's a school friend.
They were chatting in the car.
They're hugging each other.
-Look.
-Having fun?
No, it's just that the photo…
His belt wouldn't come off.
She went to help him,
and it was taken then.
It looks like that because it's dark.
So it wasn't an affair?
Seriously.
I was just worried. I'm sorry.
The Love Love Musical staff
is going to complain.
They were cast as hosts
since they're a happy couple,
but they're in this mess now.
This week is the premiere,
so they have lots of promotions booked.
So let's patch this up.
We have to be honest about these things.
If things don't add up later, it blows up.
It won't become a bigger problem
as long as we play the media right.
There's a bigger problem.
President Wang's wife is
in contact with Cho Gi-bong of Star Media.
Why?
-Will she sell us off to them?
-Maybe.
Cho Gi-bong would do that and much more.
He lived his entire life
trying to bring President Wang down.
And everyone, listen up.
The agency is really struggling.
We lost a lot of income
when films got canceled due to COVID-19,
and our additional taxes…
were a lot more than we expected.
What? Are you saying that's my fault?
You said you'd handle it.
Director Ma, you said
you'd buy the company.
All right, now.
Anyway, I gave this some thought.
We'll have to reduce our salaries
for a couple of months.
What? Whose salary?
Our salaries.
All of us.
Once we're back on track,
you'll get all your deferred pay.
How can you be so sure?
We don't know
when we'll get back on track.
Who knows if it'll be two months,
three months, or six? No one knows.
I can't believe you, Director Ma.
Me neither.
It's very tough for me…
to believe you, Director Ma.
Goodness.
Why'd you come here
when there are so many prying eyes?
Don't try to fool me. Be honest.
You knew, didn't you?
You know why she met that jerk.
-I'm sure they chatted as friends.
-Friend, my ass.
A man and a woman can't be friends.
This is so unfair.
When one of his girl friends calls,
he runs out right away to meet them.
Ever since I got married,
all I've ever known was work and home.
Don't you know why So-hyun would
go so far as to make up such a lie?
I wasn't going to tell you this, but…
Jun-ho is downstairs.
He gets that he was mistaken
and feels bad for overreacting.
So accept his apology.
It's just as you said.
Just as you hid your affair from your wife
to avoid hurting her,
-So-hyun lied in case I got hurt.
-Take this.
Take this, tell her you're sorry,
apologize, and make up. Okay?
I'll let her off this time.
Okay.
Darn it.
-One second.
-What now?
Let me check the dashcam.
UNABLE TO USE VIDEO SAVE FUNCTION
SAVED VIDEOS: 0
So why did you delete the footage?
My friend asked me
not to share his story with anyone.
How can I believe her?
She dated so many guys
before we got married.
I once went to her house
and found a stash of matching rings.
What about him?
He clung to a single woman for years.
And even now, every single day,
he watches IU's videos on repeat!
That is my only means of comfort.
Last Valentine's Day,
she got me cheap,
convenience store chocolate.
He only acts sweet on TV. So pretentious.
She may be my senior out here,
but she patronizes me at home
and nags at me all the time!
-You have no idea how much
-I've been enduring it all this time!
Enough. Stop!
You want me to manage So-hyun?
Yes, just for a short while.
Go with Mr. Kim for a few days.
You and Jun-ho have
the same schedule right now,
and you two will only fight.
Gosh.
So you're choosing Jun-ho over me.
It's not that.
You're probably mentally drained.
I thought it'd be nice
to have Mr. Kim around.
He's deeply caring and calm.
He's the most trusted agent
among the actors in our agency.
And also, Mr. Kim, didn't you say
you wanted to work with her?
Me?
Yes, I did.
If being separated from Jun-ho is ideal,
I'd rather look
for another agency at this point--
-No.
Yes, hello?
I'm calling from Shark Entertainment.
Is this Agent Choi Jin-hyeok?
Yes, that's me.
You recently applied to our job opening
as an experienced agent, right?
I called after seeing your résumé.
Yes, that's right.
We're in a bit of a rush.
Can you start next week?
What?
That soon?
One of our managers suddenly had to quit.
Please consider it soon.
Next week is a bit of a rush…
Did you just say…
it was a manager position?
Yes.
Mr. Choi Jin-hyeok,
we'd like you to join us as a manager.
Well, this is a very sudden offer.
Can you tell me about the
compensation package?
That would aid in considering the offer.
Your coffee is ready.
Yes, right.
-Did you do what I asked?
-Yes.
You'll see the reservation in the app.
You depart tomorrow at 7 a.m.
Are you going somewhere?
Haenam. My parent's place.
All of a sudden?
She's receiving an award
as a youth who's honored her hometown.
That's just an excuse.
The district provided a filming site
for Han Ji-min's new film.
I'm stopping by to thank them
and show my face around.
Use the opportunity to get some fresh air.
And clear your mind.
What fresh air?
I run into my parent's friends
at every corner,
so it's more like a prison.
Why am I returning the next day?
I wanted to return right away.
Well, that was the only viable time
because you wanted to stop by
Han Ji-min's film location.
Man, this is driving me insane.
Won-jae.
What's Ji-min's schedule like on set?
She doesn't have any time off?
Goodness.
She doesn't even want to spend a night
in her hometown.
I guess not.
Hee-sun.
I heard your second audition is today.
Won-jae told me
that you got another callback.
-Yes.
-I'm glad.
Anyway, what's with them?
If they want to cast you,
they should do it straight away.
Right?
Hee-sun, you'll get busier soon.
We'll need a new receptionist soon.
Good luck later.
Hello, Director.
Yes, right.
Have you been well?
Yes, I've been well.
I'm sorry.
The company cars were all booked.
It's all right.
I go around like this often.
The bus is probably faster at this hour.
But still.
I wanted you to relax on your way there.
You need to focus on your script too.
I only have one line today.
That's true.
Anyway, Hyun-joo.
You're really pretty today.
You're a great actor.
-I am?
-Yes.
-You practiced a lot.
-Was that good?
Totally.
It's a lot of pressure
since it's just one line.
Yes, and that one line
should be memorable too.
-Yes.
-You did really well.
-Let me try again.
-No.
-Just once more.
-Anyway, you're really pretty today.
-No, stop that.
-So pretty.
-You're a good actor.
-So dazzling.
-Enough.
-My eyes.
-Stop overreacting.
The star lovebirds special?
Yes, we'd love to have them there,
but both Kim So-hyun and Son Jun-ho
are completely booked right now.
I'm sorry. Bye.
We're getting so many casting calls
after the scandal.
Why is Hyun-joo on set on a day like this?
This is Method Entertainment.
You left this on the copier.
And once you're done using it,
can you refill the paper?
It's not like we have a guy
just for refilling the copier.
Won-jae, can you go downstairs
and get some coffee?
A reporter is coming in for an interview.
We didn't join this company
to fetch coffee and run errands.
Not at all.
Jin-hyeok, is something going on?
Listen up, Won-jae.
Putting up with such mistreatment
and staying loyal to the agency?
I'm not sure.
This agency won't protect you forever.
But figures.
My advice to you ends
right about here.
-Three cups?
-Yes, Americanos.
Okay.
You're the joint host
for Love Love Musical with Son Jun-ho.
Do you ever get into fights?
All the time.
How can a married couple not fight?
Life every day is a climax.
And it ends in tragedy.
Could you stick to questions
about the program?
-Sure.
-Thanks.
Then what do you think is
most important between a couple?
I'm sorry,
but no questions about her private life.
I'm asking
about the contents of the program.
If you keep this up,
it's slightly uncomfortable.
I've been mentally worn out lately,
so he's concerned I might make a mistake.
Then let me ask you
about your future plans.
Do you have any other musicals in line
after Anna Karenina?
I don't have any plans right now.
I want to abandon everything.
No, she doesn't mean
abandoning everything.
She just said…
-she wants to abandon everything.
-No.
That's not what she means.
Well, it's… Anyway, no.
Considering retiring…
"Considering retiring"?
No, she hasn't considered that.
Q. FUTURE PLANS?
A. NO PLANS, I WANT TO ABANDON…
What are you doing right now?
I want to ensure
the interview is accurate.
I shouldn't have. I'm sorry.
Sure.
Wait, I…
Wait, I mean.
-Forget it.
-Let me…
I'll give you a call.
HAENAM CITIZENS' DAY
MAKE OUR HOMETOWN SHINE AWARD
-Why did he leave her with me?
-I wonder.
Director Ma manages
all the musical actors himself.
He normally doesn't like it
when others intervene.
Precisely.
It's really odd.
Did he put So-hyun with me
thinking she'll cause trouble?
He doesn't want to be responsible.
He's doing this to get rid of me,
his strongest rival.
That's it.
It must be a scheme
to get rid of me for good, right?
That must be it. You're in deep trouble.
Hey, I'll call you later.
-Hello.
-Well,
look who it is.
It's the eldest of the Chun family.
Wow, you've become a young lady already.
What young lady? She's about to be 40--
She'll be older tomorrow
than she is today,
but she won't get married.
Do I go up when I'm called?
No.
There was a bit of a change.
You haven't heard?
What are you talking about?
Isn't my kid getting an award?
Will you stop shouting?
You'll make me go deaf.
Now, don't worry about that.
We just have a surprise guest.
We're awarding him too,
so we just switched
the order of the ceremony. Just the order.
You know him too, right?
The second son of the mill, Hae-jun.
Oh, my.
The one who became
a big success in America?
He made some dating app or something
-and made a fortune, right?
-Yes.
I wonder if he's still single.
Do you remember him?
You two used to be best friends
when you were young.
-Goodness.
-Look at that cool car.
Oh, my. Speak of the devil.
There he is.
-What's that car?
-That looks impressive.
Is that him?
Well…
He's quite handsome.
Look who this is. It's my son.
-Goodness, welcome back.
-Hello.
-How was your trip?
-How are you?
How long has it been?
-He's my son. Isn't he good-looking?
-He's quite tall.
He made a fortune.
My gosh.
We are here to commemorate
the 49th Haenam Citizens' Day.
I'd like to thank our residents
and distinguished guests
for traveling a long way and coming here
to honor the Make Our Hometown Shine Award
despite your busy schedules.
Well, you already know that
Ms. Han Ji-min, the actress,
is here at Haenam right now
filming a movie, right?
The agent of Actress Han Ji-min is
Ms. Chun Jane,
who is sitting with us right now.
She is the daughter of Chun Bong-su,
the representative of the Livestock Co-op.
This young lady who now works
with such a global star
was proudly brought up in our hometown.
Please give her a big hand.
MAKE OUR HOMETOWN SHINE AWARD
Do we know each other?
Class 6-2, Haenam Elementary.
It was you, Chun Je-suk.
Why does everyone call you Chun Jane?
I changed my name in middle school.
I see.
Je-suk suits you better.
Following this young lady's example,
we'll continue to cooperate actively…
ME + U
SERVER DOWNTIME NOTICE
…to help K-dramas
and K-movies expand worldwide.
I made that app.
And now, let me introduce Mr. Koo Hae-jun.
He developed a dating app
that became a big hit
in over 40 countries worldwide.
He is also a famous businessman
as an M&A specialist,
and he was chosen
as the tenth most noteworthy
young businessman by the LA Times.
Anyway, I have a question for you.
May I ask you?
Sure, please.
I hear you'll begin
a new business in Korea.
I'm quite curious about that.
I'm still thinking about it.
Please make a good recommendation.
Our district is
in need of a new soccer field.
What do you think about that?
He's such a funny man, isn't he?
I'd like to donate a natural grass field
for every school in our district.
Who knows? Our hometown
may have the next Son Heung-min.
-Koo Hae-jun!
-He's so cool!
What's going on?
We put out a press release saying
the couple will come,
but only So-hyun showed up!
I'm sorry.
Jun-ho isn't feeling well lately.
You know how hard it was
to get on We Quiz, don't you?
I do. And that's why I'm sorry.
But why don't we let So-hyun
promote Love Love Musical alone?
Are you kidding me?
Forget it. They have to be there
for the live talk show tomorrow.
If they don't show up there either,
then I won't let this slide!
I will sue you for breach of contract
and cut them both off from the program!
Good grief.
RECENT CALLS
ACTOR SON HO-JUN
The device is turned off.
Please leave a message…
They're driving me nuts.
Have you heard?
Is So-hyun still upset?
Yes, she's barely
getting through her schedule.
But she has to do
that live talk show tomorrow.
Anyway, about asking me to manage So-hyun.
Why did you do that?
I mean, it's all very sudden.
To be honest, you've never transferred
one of your clients to me before.
I found it odd.
So-hyun needs you right now
more than she needs me.
Someone she can lean on
during her troubles.
If it hadn't been for you,
she wouldn't have done any work right now.
Do you really think so?
Why? Don't you believe me?
I mean, you've never said
anything like that to me before.
Ever since you and your wife parted,
strangely enough,
you've become more considerate.
We haven't parted.
We're temporarily separated.
The two will make up soon, right?
Of course.
We won't break up that easily.
Don't worry.
I meant So-hyun and Jun-ho.
This seemed a little too serious
to simply call it a lover's quarrel.
What if they--
What do you know, Mr. Kim?
A couple doesn't break up over a fight.
Right?
Right.
And they won't get divorced
unless one of them is hugely at fault.
Darn.
Who's that?
Jang Myung-aeh!
What have you done? Hey!
Darn it. Have you gone senile?
Oh, my.
You got me.
Damn it, I just got this two months ago!
You got all four sides.
Hey, do you want to get arrested
for damaging property?
No, you better be careful
if you don't want to be arrested.
You put up this building
with bribes you took behind your actors.
Do your actors know?
How funny.
What now? Do you have any evidence?
Of course.
Do you think I came here with nothing?
When Tae-ja and I were
betrayed and kicked out by you,
do you think we left empty-handed?
Method Entertainment isn't an agency
for some hoodlum like you.
Don't you dare lurk around us again.
This won't be the end of it.
It's not too late to join us.
Your dearly beloved Wang Tae-ja
is now dead and long gone.
Method will go down soon.
Hey!
This is my final warning.
If you mess with Method,
Star Media will also…
Got it?
What? Hey.
Not the hood. You!
No! Not the bumper! Damn it, that woman.
He sold the dating app
to Jacebook for 80 million dollars.
-Are you listening?
-Yes.
But would he invest in us?
I heard he divorced his wife in America
and returned to Korea for good.
He's looking for a new investment,
I'm going to try to win him over.
How will you do that?
He used to like me as a kid.
It's our last chance
to protect our agency…
Hey, stop!
Hey, Chun Je-suk. What's up?
It's our reunion,
so it's a shame to leave so early.
Let's grab a meal.
If you're busy,
can you drop me off at my set?
One of our clients is on set nearby.
Han Ji-min.
Give her the address.
Yes, okay. Go now. Go!
Go now! Go far away!
Don't come home!
I can't believe we met again like this.
Seems like fate brought us together.
Do you remember how I saved you
when you transferred in and got bullied?
That Koo Hae-jun grew up
into such a magnificent guy.
Well, I knew it back then too.
That you were different from other kids.
How can I put this?
You had this aura about you.
Cut to the chase.
After I became rich,
lots of people come looking for a handout.
So? What is it? What do you want?
Your mother said
you're looking for a husband.
-I'm just joking, Je-suk.
-Gosh.
Goodness, you wouldn't
try anything with me.
You were really nice to me
when we were kids.
And…
you know I had a crush on you, right?
Jeez.
That's embarrassing.
I always told myself
I would pay you back for that
if we ever meet again.
Let me know if I can help in any way.
Good.
Then I'll be frank with you,
although this may seem sudden.
Actually, our agency is a great company.
We have great clients and great agents.
But we've been in trouble
after our president
suddenly passed away in an accident.
There are many agencies
that want to buy us out,
but we don't want it to be just anybody.
We're looking for a good investor
who can appreciate our value.
An investment?
All of a sudden?
Yes.
Okay.
Aren't you getting out?
Yeah.
Right. I should go.
Je-suk, show me around the set.
Our agency
partially invested in this film.
Directed by Seo Ju-hwan.
Written by Lee Jeong-eun.
You know them, right?
They won awards at Cannes.
Are they famous?
I've been living abroad,
so I'm not familiar.
They're famous in the US too.
Anyway, the lead role is Han Ji-min.
Watch out for the cable.
The project budget is 20 billion won.
There are four different crews…
Twenty billion?
We have scenes abroad,
with lots of computer graphics.
There's Ji-min. Ji-min!
ACTRESS HAN JI-MIN
Hello.
-Hello.
-Han Ji-min?
-She's the script supervisor.
Where's Ji-min?
She went back to her lodging.
Her day shoot ended.
-She isn't coming?
-No.
-I see.
Okay, thanks.
Right. I see.
So this is worth 20 billion won?
You're throwing away money.
Do you have to do this?
I need time to think.
I want to reflect on my marriage.
You have to go
to the live talk show tomorrow.
You know, right?
If you don't show up for that,
you'll be kicked off Love Love Musical.
My faith in So-hyun is shaken.
How can we do a talk show
as if nothing has happened?
Okay, in that case,
why don't you show up alone instead?
That's okay, right?
Are you telling me to go out
and have a good laugh?
Impossible.
Hey, Jun-ho, You can't do this to me.
When you lost your money in stocks,
didn't I let you
take an advance on your fee?
Man, Tae-oh.
You can't say that to me.
I got into trading because of you!
You had to do musicals back-to-back
to make up for that,
but I let the news say
it was out of goodwill.
Should I expose the truth?
Jeez.
Hey.
Jun-ho.
Just one last talk show, okay?
Fine.
I'll do that talk show. Happy?
Good. I'm glad you made that decision.
Tae-oh.
You have to keep it a secret.
She's going to kill me. Okay?
Don't worry about it. Don't you trust me?
Don't worry.
Goodness.
It rained until yesterday,
we haven't shot any outdoor scenes.
And now the car broke down,
so the schedule has to be pushed.
Man, what a mess.
Sets are always like this,
full of accidents and mishaps.
So the car broke?
You can use my car.
-What?
-It's better to use a Korean car anyway.
Well, may we do that?
-I can talk to the insurance agency…
-You can tell them and use it.
And why don't you
let her drive too?
She's an amazing driver.
-Right?
-No, it's too dangerous.
Of course not.
There is a set of moves for car scenes,
so it must be a stunt performer.
I'm letting you use my car,
so is it wrong to have my driver drive it?
Who cares if anybody does it?
It's not just for anybody.
This is a part of acting too.
And there's the problem
with insurance too.
I see.
If there's an accident,
I'll take responsibility. Use it.
Sunny, you'll make your film debut.
Hey, let's call it off.
Do you think filmmaking is a joke?
Damn you.
"Damn…"
-"Damn you"?
-No.
-What?
-Come on.
No, nothing.
-How dare you swear at me?
-Stop.
-You said it to me first, punk.
-No.
-Punk?
-Stunt Director.
-You swore at me first.
-Don't you point at me.
Stunt Director, please.
-I'm sorry.
-Hey, you!
I'm sorry.
Man.
Who the heck is that punk?
What a total psycho.
-Man.
-Hey, Hae-jun!
Hae-jun, wait! Stop!
Hae-jun!
Watch out!
The second time.
I should ask.
The stylist. In.
Oh, man.
Goodness, look who this is.
If this isn't Mr. Kang
of Number One Entertainment.
Is your agency in trouble?
What kind of sudden nonsense is this?
One of my rookies went to an audition,
and one of your actors was there
reciting lines.
I think her name was Kang Hee-sun.
I felt bad to hear
she was reciting lines all day
although she wasn't cast.
You never allow your clients to do that.
What happened?
Hey, I need to hang up.
She made me promise not to tell you.
I mean, even so. Look at the time.
I had no idea.
I'm sorry. I still should have called you.
No, it's not your fault. Where's the car?
Over there.
-Can you bring it over?
-Okay.
Mr. Kim.
Hee-sun.
I didn't know about this.
You should've told me.
It's all going under my belt.
This helped me out
much more than I expected.
And I could see the strengths
and weaknesses of those being auditioned.
I'm okay. I feel completely fine.
But you should've told me.
I'm someone who must know
everything about you.
After all, I'm your agent.
I'm sorry, Hee-sun.
Why?
I feel like
I haven't paid a lot of attention to you.
As an agent?
Sorry?
Mr. Kim.
Hey.
Hop in, Hee-sun.
Are you coming?
On my way.
The agency explained everything,
and most people don't believe it,
so it'll be fine.
If I had known,
I should have listened to you
and been honest from the start.
It's because I made up a lie
about visiting my parents.
After this incident,
I reflected on our relationship.
Everything we held back and piled up
blew up all at once.
Jun-ho says
he sacrificed a lot
for the sake of our family.
I thought I was the one
who sacrificed and held back more.
Why should we live together
if we must both hold back and sacrifice?
Because you're a family.
And you have a kid.
You each hold back for the other.
That's just life.
I made up a lie because
I didn't want him to be concerned.
Do you think I can get Jun-ho
to trust me again?
Of course, Jun-ho will be there
at the talk show tomorrow.
His anger will slowly subside too.
Don't worry about it.
Je-suk, come and eat!
Wake up already!
Goodness.
Are you all right?
Can you take me to the dentist later?
You should've stayed out,
why did you come back with a broken tooth?
Go to a big dentist's office in Seoul.
It's better to go
to a big and famous hospital.
The same goes for jobs too.
I heard your agency is about to go down
after what happened to your president.
It's not too late,
so you should take the state exam.
The agency isn't going down.
How about marrying a civil servant?
You don't know any, do you?
Should I find someone? Should I?
Try this one too.
Okay.
Goodness.
She's not a daughter,
but our greatest enemy.
You're going to Shark Entertainment?
So that's why
you made that ridiculous scene.
-You're so quick.
-Despite how you look,
you're the daughter of a rich farmer,
but contrary to my looks,
I must make a living for myself
and survive on my own.
You're going to stick around anyway.
You adore Director Ma.
Goodness.
Don't be so sad.
I prepared a goodbye present.
I left a handwritten
resignation letter for Mr. Kim.
I also included some killer advice on
the mess of a system this agency runs on!
You lunatic.
Shark. It's Shark Entertainment.
They're already looking for me.
Pick it up.
Hello? Choi Jin-hyeok speaking.
Hello, this is Shark Entertainment.
Yes, hello. I was going to call you.
I'm so sorry.
I thought you were the Choi Jin-hyeok
our president mentioned.
But I called the wrong person.
The Mr. Choi Jin-hyeok we were after
started work today.
I'm sorry, but what do you mean?
I'm so sorry about that. Goodbye.
Excuse me. Hello?
Hey. What…
What do I do?
-No! Oh, my gosh!
-Run!
Go!
-Eat it!
-Eat it?
Say hi to him.
Swallow it.
Coffee smells great. May I have some?
Coffee, my ass.
What's wrong?
You wanted to talk.
Isn't that why you called?
Change your address.
And take your stuff since you're here.
Otherwise,
I'll get someone to throw it all out.
Let's stop this, Eun-ha.
Stop this? Stop what?
I'm sorry.
But it was 24 years ago.
How much longer do I have to beg?
I'll be sorry for the rest of my life.
I really thought we were done.
It was just that one time.
And since then,
I never even looked at another woman.
You know that already.
What's this?
Who sent this to you?
An employee of my restaurant
lives in that apartment.
She said she saw you yesterday
going to another woman's house.
Another woman? Look, it's So-hyun.
So-hyun is a woman too!
Jun-ho and So-hyun had a fight,
so he's staying with me.
That's why I stopped by,
to discuss something.
So you went in alone
to her house without Jun-ho?
Well after midnight?
Stop that. What's with you?
You made me like this!
Eun-ha, one second.
Let's…
get a divorce.
LOVE LOVE MUSICAL HOST KIM SO-HYUN
ADMITS WANTING TO "ABANDON EVERYTHING"
Who are you?
Yes, well…
STAR MEDIA
PRESIDENT CHO GI-BONG
We've met a few times in passing.
I'm waiting for someone.
President Kim Mi-hye of Sam Musical?
She'll be late.
I asked her to set this up
because I wanted to meet you.
Your bag.
How much do you trust Director Ma?
What do you think you're doing?
Do you know that Director Ma
and Son Jun-ho are on the same team?
What are you talking about?
I'd like to order.
Do you know that Jun-ho keeps
some money of his own hidden from you?
We're about an hour into
the live talk show
celebrating the premiere
of Love Love Musical.
Ms. Kim So-hyun was supposed to join us,
but she became quite ill,
so I only have Mr. Son Jun-ho with me.
Some questions are coming in right now.
ID Snorlaxative sent this question.
"What's the secret to maintaining
a marriage without losing your spark?"
It must be
my deep generosity like the sea.
Is that so?
I wonder what this person will think
about your answer.
We have a surprise guest
at the studio right now.
-A surprise guest?
-Yes.
-Do you want to find out?
Then let's meet her.
Let's welcome the guest into the studio.
Come on out!
-Hello.
Yes, please take a seat.
-All right. Welcome.
-Hello.
-Did you know about this?
-What?
-I was quite worried.
-No.
I heard you were ill.
Are you feeling better?
-Yes, I'm all right.
-I see.
I wanted to surprise Jun-ho.
I'm not sure if it worked.
After living together for a long time,
I find that
we must tell lies like this at times.
She's right.
Marriage…
is a series of lies
and perpetual surprises.
Love Love Musical will
premiere tomorrow at 9 p.m.
Let's watch the highlights together.
You lying crook.
Who? Me?
-Yes.
-That should be my line.
Shut up.
You lost all your money in trading.
And you got an advance on your pay?
Why? Why didn't you
just take out a private loan?
Right.
That's why you did
five musicals in a row last year.
-No, I--
-Be honest.
How much did you lose?
-It's…
-How much?
Hey!
Excuse me, the clip is about to end.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know it would plummet.
It was supposed to go up for sure.
-I just--
-I can't believe it.
I told you time and time again
not to get into that.
Wait, where did you
get the money for that?
I know where all the money comes from.
What?
We're back in ten seconds. Okay.
It was all for you.
What?
You lost money because of me?
I did it to see you smile.
What?
Last year,
on our tenth wedding anniversary,
you couldn't take a break from work.
That's why
I wanted to send you on a vacation
to the US for a few months.
I knew you wouldn't want it.
I'm certain you'd have said
you didn't need the rest.
That's why I wanted
to prepare it in secret and let you go.
You've worked tirelessly.
So I wanted to let you rest.
I never had a chance
to do anything good for you.
What do you mean?
I'm here today because you're with me.
I could hold out until this day
thanks to your support.
Looking at the highlight clip
already got me excited for the show.
So-hyun, when you evaluate,
do you have anything you look for?
Excuse me, So-hyun?
So-hyun?
-Yes.
-Yes, right.
Of course,
one's skills and techniques are important.
But above all, it's important
to be considerate of one another.
And…
Love.
Love that embraces each other's mistakes
or even faults.
How much you are in love
when you're on the stage.
That's what we'll look for.
Yes, he's right.
When you sing a duet,
it's most important
to listen to one another.
So I'll keep my eyes out to see
how considerate you are of one another.
Goodness, this is so lovely.
It's great to see you two together.
Love Love Musical premieres tomorrow.
Are you all excited?
Please tune in tomorrow!
Mr. Kim.
Yes?
I like you.
Hee-sun.
I like you, Mr. Kim.
You already know that, Mr. Kim.
I'm not asking you for anything,
so don't be pressured.
-Hello.
LOVE LOVE MUSICAL
IS OFF TO A GOOD START
HOSTED BY KIM SO-HYUN AND SON JUN-HO,
LOVE LOVE MUSICAL IS A HIT…
-Tae-oh.
-Hey.
Hello.
It's been a while
since the three of us met.
You're right.
You two look great.
Let's order. Here's the menu.
What? Do you have something to say?
Wait.
You aren't in another fight, are you?
No, that's not it.
We had a talk.
Here's our thought.
For a relationship to last long,
trust is essential.
Yes, of course.
As you know, we went through
a big incident recently.
That's why we want to bring some change.
-So I'm saying--
-We're moving agencies.
You and Jun-ho worked together to fool me,
but it's all in the past,
and he's reflecting on himself,
so I won't bring that up.
However,
someone must be responsible.
-What do you mean?
-She found out.
About the trading
and the advance payments.
-So-hyun, that's…
-Yes.
He was trying to help me out.
But you were the one
that told me to buy that stock.
I didn't care about stock trading before.
-Right?
-Jun-ho.
Jun-ho and I want a fresh start
through this incident,
without any lies, in honesty.
Let me leave you with this just in case.
Don't try to hold us back
with the period left in our contract.
You know what you've done.
I mean,
you can't suddenly switch agencies…
You aren't looking
for another agency, are you?
I am.
Star Media.
I've already talked with their president.
And he's giving us a hefty advance.
-All we need to do is sign and relax.
-Come on.
-Tae-oh, I'll be in touch.
-Goodbye, then.
Hey.
Are you ill? You don't look well.
No, I'm okay.
Hello, Ms. Chun Jane. Director Ma.
I've been waiting for you.
Hello.
Ms. Chun.
Thank you for introducing our agency
to President Koo Hae-jun.
Thanks to you, we finally found
a savior for Method Entertainment.
Yes.
Well, we've made introductions
to almost everyone.
The de facto leader
of Method Entertainment.
Please meet Director Ma Tae-oh.
He'll be of great help from now on.
Nice to meet you. My name is Koo Hae-jun.
Director Ma?
Mr. Koo Hae-jun is
the new president of Method Entertainment.
What's wrong with him?
-Director Ma!
-Oh, my!
BEHIND EVERY STAR
Kim Ji-hoon.
Let's poach him from Star Media.
Ten million won to the person
making the biggest contribution.
Not even Star Media could do it,
what are you going to do about it?
Kim Ji-hoon had no idea.
What if we don't tell them directly?
I realized clearly that there's
something more important than money.
-Don't mess it up by making it personal.
-Gosh.
But not her.
What are you talking about?
-Can we just talk casually?
-I guess when it's just the two of us.
I'm not sure why I should keep you here.
What happened was just ludicrous.
Don't even think of stealing our actors.
Pack your stuff.