=The Dangerous Lover=
=Episode 4=
(Hu Mansion)
Why do you
have so many scars?
They're from years ago.
It seems everyone
has their own secrets.
(Good thing my secret)
(is resolved.)
I almost died just now.
Why do you seem so happy?
Do I?
Since you're out of the palace now,
let's treat your wounds here first.
You did this to help me,
I'll take responsibility for you.
Thank you then, Miss Hu.
My problem has finally been resolved.
But what if the Seventh Prince
comes back to life?
How could a dead man come back to life?
If he does,
I'll poison him again.
Tianba.
Hu Tiantian, what trouble
did you cause again?
Greetings, Your Highness.
(You are)
(the Seventh Prince?)
I'm Xia Jiu.
Xia Jiu, listen to me,
don't have any pity
for your enemies.
Why?
The Hu family
no longer means anything to me.
What are you doing here?
To take you away.
(Su Yanli,)
(long time no see.)
(General Hu,)
(nice to meet you again.)
(Happiness)
Miss Hu,
I am your husband.
Why would you want to harm me?
Xia Jiu,
what's going on?
Call me Su Yanli!
Su Yanli!
I hate you!
What?
You are calling the name of
the Seventh Prince even in your dream?
Where is he?
What's wrong with you again?
Tianlin,
kill him!
Do you know what you're saying?
This man is very cunning.
He is using the Hu Family to climb up.
Our entire family will die miserably
by his hands.
Tiantian, the Seventh Prince
is just a commoner now.
What storm can he stir up?
Besides, Tianba forbids us from
meddling in court affairs.
Stop overthinking.
Tiantian has been self-willed,
she must have caused trouble
for Your Highness.
It's okay,
this commotion she caused
actually helped me.
You must have suffered
in the past years.
Tiantian! Tiantian!
What... What are you doing?
- Hu Tiantian! Where are your manners?
- Tiantian.
Su Yanli,
you're quite dramatic.
Tiantian,
I'm sorry I lied to you.
I just didn't want you
to get involved in trouble.
Tiantian, are you crazy?
Put down the sword.
Tianba, don't believe him.
He will only harm the Hu Family.
I never meant to harm you
or the Hu Family.
♪Lightly arranging the phoenix hairpin♪
♪Smiling as we watch the fish swim♪
♪In the courtyard, flowers fall
without desire♪
♪It's difficult to find kindred spirits♪
♪I dare not look into your eyes♪
♪Are the zither and the lute in harmony?♪
♪Plucking a bunch of red beans♪
♪Old friends standing on the jade tower♪
♪Drunkenly watching the bustling lights
with sorrow♪
♪But heaven does not cease♪
Tiantian,
I don't know why you hate me so much
♪For how long?♪
that you want to kill me.
My fate
should be decided by myself!
Your Highness!
♪Snow adorns the branches♪
♪Geese pass through leaving wind behind♪
♪I don't care if this path has an end♪
♪I'm just glad you are with me♪
♪If all love and enmity should fade away♪
♪I wish we could quietly wait together♪
♪Stepping into the mortal world♪
♪No need to inquire about the future♪
♪We know who we have missed♪
♪Let's dispel any tenderness♪
♪Lightly arranging the phoenix hairpin♪
♪Smiling as we watch the fish swim♪
♪In the courtyard, flowers fall
without desire♪
♪It's difficult to find kindred spirits♪
♪I dare not look into your eyes♪
♪Are the zither and the lute in harmony?♪
♪Plucking a bunch of red beans♪
♪Old friends standing on the jade tower♪
♪Drunkenly watching the bustling lights
with sorrow♪
♪But heaven does not cease♪
♪Emotions may slash at our sleeves♪
♪One person, one sword,
can we stand together?♪
♪For how long?♪
♪Make wine with green plums♪
♪Unaware of the passage of time♪
♪Respecting the night as if it were day♪
♪Love never stops, never ceases♪
♪If all love and enmity should fade away♪
♪I wish we could quietly wait together♪
♪Stepping into the mortal world♪
♪No need to inquire about the future♪
♪We know who we have missed♪
♪Let's dispel any tenderness♪
(The right of network communication
of this work)
(is exclusively owned by Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)