Chief Detective 1958
This series is unrelated to any places,
persons, settings or events.
Scenes involving animals were filmed in
compliance with animal welfare guidelines.
Episode 3
Jungil Bank
Closed temporarily
Freeze! Don't move!
Hey, you!
Put the phone down!
Get down on the floor!
Move!
Come on, move!
Get down.
Get down now!
Who's in charge here?
Who's the manager?
It's… It's me.
Come on, hurry.
Out of the way!
Episode 3
Highwaymen
How'd you get him to join?
Chief Crap allowed it?
He said he was afraid
keeping him would be disastrous,
so he eagerly let us have him.
With Zhuge Liang joining our unit,
I feel like I have an army now.
Your parents must be proud of you.
Well, they actually kicked me out, sir.
My father strongly objected
to me becoming a cop.
Get out.
Please don't do this, honey.
How dare you defy me,
just to be some lowly cop?
I will stick to the path I chose, Father.
Why did he object?
He has a negative view of the police.
Let's do our best to change his mind then.
That's right, Detective Seo.
Let your actions change his mind.
Yes, sir.
My goodness, Detective Jo.
It still amazes me how big you are.
I feel such a strong sense of patriotism,
being with you all here.
Well, I've got nothing to worry about.
I trust you all immensely.
You can trust us, sir.
They say trust is the mother of deceit.
Speak of the devil.
Now that Unit 1 is complete,
it's time I give you your first mission.
This is of utmost importance.
Operation Jongnam Market,
"Get rid of all the bums."
Now, move!
Yes, sir.
I can't believe
my first mission is getting rid of bums.
My first-ever mission
was fishing an assemblyman's wife's ring
out of a crapper.
Hey, boys.
Does anyone have toothpaste?
What for?
This is such a good idea.
Why didn't I think of it?
What's this even for?
It stings.
You'll find out later.
As cops,
shouldn't we be training
for arrests and shootings?
I'm also excited
to learn how to shoot guns.
You can learn basic stuff like that
on your own time.
You can only learn how to be a real cop
by tussling on the streets, all right?
Still, aren't they necessary skills
as cops?
You're right, but…
only one thing should matter
to a detective.
"If I don't solve this case,
someone's life could be destroyed."
With that in mind,
you could get whooped
and not feel an ounce of pain.
You could stay up for days
and feel as fresh as the morning dew.
That's not all.
Even the heavens above
will be on our side!
- Got it?
- Yes, sir.
- Remember this, all right?
- All right.
- Make sure you do!
- Yes, sir.
Let's go then.
There's definitely
something wrong with him.
♪ Hurray, here we all go! ♪
♪ The beggar who came last year ♪
♪ Is alive and here again ♪
♪ The beggar who came last year… ♪
Go away, you bums!
No!
♪ The beggar who came last year ♪
♪ Is alive and here again ♪
♪ Hurray! ♪
Hey, bums. Freeze!
Run!
Come on, run! Move!
I guess we'll have to run too.
Oh, come on.
Hands up!
I get why we have toothpaste
under our noses.
How can they smell so bad?
You punks.
You have to beg fair and square,
not steal from others.
You see,
people are so heartless and cold
these days
that they don't give us anything
even if we sing.
Then you should blame your singing.
You better practice more!
I'm pretty good at it already.
Just because you're a bum
doesn't mean you can't have a conscience.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive us.
Hands down.
Since the weather's gloomy and damp today,
I'll let you off the hook.
Do you mean it?
But you need to return
what you stole back to their owners.
And bow down and apologize to them, okay?
Yes, sir.
Thank you!
But don't bow twice.
What are you all doing?
Thank him right now!
- Thank you!
That's enough. Go.
Aren't we going to arrest them?
Criminals worse than them
don't get arrested.
So why would we take them?
Senior Superintendent Choi
will be furious though.
That's too bad. Let's go.
Selling chocolates!
- Should we go in?
- It looks exciting.
Let's watch a film.
Okay.
I still smell the toothpaste.
You're a saint, Detective.
They're all just poor beggars.
But if they steal again,
you better lock them all up!
I'm sure they'll keep their word
and won't get into trouble.
The thing is,
beggars have no one on their side.
So once people like us stand up for them,
they pledge their absolute loyalty.
You know who helped me catch
all those cow thieves?
Beggars.
Did they act as your informants?
That's right. They were my eyes and ears.
No one is better at noticing
and remembering things than beggars.
As expected,
you had a reason for what you did.
Hey, freeze.
Are you a wild boar or something?
You eat way too much.
What's so good about this?
Wait, there's rice in this?
This tastes delicious.
It does, doesn't it?
Eat to your heart's content.
Wait a minute.
If you were kicked out,
where are you staying now?
My mother had a place
prepared for me just in case.
He'd be homeless by now
if it weren't for his mother.
He's right. Be nice to her.
So, what made you want to be a cop
so badly?
What's that?
Let me see.
Is this a throwing star?
No, it's not.
This is a badge,
just like the one
the legendary sheriff Frank Hamer had.
Is he a big deal or something?
Of course.
There was once
a couple called Bonnie and Clyde,
who were infamous bank robbers in America.
The two were extremely elusive
and no one could catch them.
You see, Frank Hamer is the one
who finally caught them.
Frank Hamer?
But… Bonnie and Clark? Who were they?
Here's the thing.
Bonnie and Clyde happened to be lovers.
Why didn't they just get coffee?
What sort of lovers would rob banks?
That's nonsense.
I bet they couldn't break up.
Keep going.
Anyway, they stole cars,
robbed banks,
and even attacked a prison.
What happened next?
Now Showing
The Man Who Never Returned
Thank you for the food, ma'am!
Frank truly sounds like an amazing guy.
So he did all that
after coming back from retirement?
My dream is to serve like he did.
You will.
Bad things need to happen
to do great things, so forget it.
I guarantee the tears will flow.
Watch The Man Who Never Returned.
It's about a pathetic scumbag
who betrays an innocent woman.
I hear that one is fun.
Showing now at Dansungsa Theater!
Boys, I need to go.
Now Showing
The Man Who Never Returned
Goodness.
Damn it.
Jongnam Bookstore
Hyeju.
You're here.
Is The Criminal's Shadow in?
Yes, it is.
Here.
- It's finally here.
- It is.
Did something happen today?
No.
You're wearing such a pretty dress,
yet you're feeling down.
You got stood up, didn't you?
How did you know that?
Well, this is what you call
logical inference.
But by who?
Someone who's no good.
- Hey, Nansil.
- Yes?
Does this make any sense to you?
- No.
- He wanted to repay my kindness.
I never asked him to repay me…
Jeez.
Papers! Get your papers!
Another bank was robbed!
Papers!
Get your papers here!
Hey, kid, I'll buy one.
Suwon becomes the fourth target
of the five armed bank robbers
- Here.
- Thank you.
Look at all this.
One last job,
and we're leaving the country.
Are you all ready?
- Yes.
Where will be our last target?
At 15:00 tomorrow,
Sergeant Kim will let us know
at the Hwaseong underpass.
Suwon was our last practice run.
It's time for the real operation.
Yes, sir.
Those worthless scumbags.
Why couldn't they just steal money?
Why kill the innocent security guard?
I wonder that too.
Wait, what if they hit Seoul next?
There's no way they'll do that.
But what if they do?
Huh?
Look.
"After the robbery,
they traveled through Daegu,
Daejeon, and Suwon."
What do you think, Detective?
Jeez, seriously.
They can come all they want,
because I'll catch all of them.
Hmm. They actually shoot people.
Would you be okay?
Well, I wouldn't just sit by.
I'd shoot back.
By the way, Detective,
when will you show me your gun?
Well…
If the bank robbers come to Seoul,
I'll show you my gun then.
Okay.
Suwon becomes the fourth target
of the five armed bank robbers
Seoul is next.
Exactly.
After Busan, Daegu, Daejeon, and Suwon,
Seoul is likely to be next.
Well, it's obviously not Pyongyang.
So they're coming here for certain,
but where will they target?
Are you thinking it'll be Jongnam?
There's no way.
They wouldn't dare come here.
It's easier to escape in the country,
where there's less police presence.
But Jongnam is packed with cars and cops,
so they wouldn't be able
to run away easily.
Take a look at the paper, sir.
The robbers are a five-man group
wearing military boots and field jackets
and they are using carbines.
What does this imply, sir?
It means the perps are former military.
All four robberies happened the same way,
with no mistakes.
They also made sure
to kill the guards as a warning.
- Are you one of them?
- What?
How do you know all of this?
I was invested in the case
since their first robbery in Busan.
You're really like that Frank guy.
A key detail here is that the robbers
moved around in a four-door Jeep.
How are the four doors important?
Did you not go to the army?
Jeeps are made with two doors.
Four doors mean they modified it
for the five of them.
- I see.
- All right.
So to summarize,
the robbers are trained,
former military men
fully equipped with a car and firearms?
This could be a big problem.
What if they go to another district
that isn't Jongnam?
Then all districts need to be prepared.
Wait a minute.
What's critical for a military operation?
Guts.
Aside from guts.
It's training.
Repeated training.
What if…
all the previous robberies
were all part of their training?
That would mean Seoul is the real thing.
Shouldn't we report this
to Senior Superintendent Choi?
Not him again.
Senior Superintendent Choi
has called an emergency meeting.
Attention, everyone!
I have important news.
Dongdaemun's Lee Jungjae
and Myeong-dong's Lee Hwaryong
are having a meeting at Jongnam Hall
next Wednesday at 11:00 a.m.
They'll be discussing accountability
for the Jongno ax case,
so we're expecting a conflict.
Therefore, every single officer
in this station
will be protecting Chairman Lee that day.
- You should all think about ways…
- Chief Yu.
- …to better protect him.
Shouldn't we tell him
about the bank robbery now?
- Senior Superintendent Choi.
- What is it? Got something to say?
It's about the bank robbery in Suwon.
What about it?
As you may all be thinking,
Seoul may be the next target.
The circumstances suggest
that the perps are former military
and will go for a bigger target next.
So, what are you trying to get at?
Districts with large banks like ours,
Jongno-gu and Jung-gu must be prepared.
Are you suggesting those punks
will attack the heart of Seoul,
knowing they'll get caught?
It's obvious they'll target the outskirts.
They wouldn't dare come here.
Well, that would be a relief,
but what if they do?
Why get worried about something
you don't have grounds for?
Even if no cow thief exists,
there's no harm in fixing up the stable.
Will you ever stop talking
about the damn cow thieves?
We don't need a whole lot of men, sir.
Just let my unit handle it.
Shut that mouth of yours!
I know what this is really about.
You guys are just sick to your stomachs
about protecting Chairman Lee.
- That's not true.
- Not true, my foot.
You better not mention
the bank robbers again.
Everyone else,
if you see these guys scheming,
report to me immediately.
- Got it?
- Yes, sir.
Dismissed!
Armed bank robbers
who targeted Daejeon and other cities
have now even attacked Suwon.
The armed men took over
Jungil Bank in Suwon
and escaped with cash and checks
worth 1.8 million won.
In the process,
the security guard at the bank
was shot and killed.
As a result of the robbery,
corporations and merchants in the area
have not been able to pay salaries
and other business costs,
suffering much hardship.
Dongdaemun-gu
Saessak Bank
Jongnam-gu
Goryeo Bank
Lee Jungjae and Lee Hwaryong will meet
on Wednesday at 11:00 a.m.
The heavens must be on our side
for things to be in our favor.
Where will we hit then?
Which of the three banks should we rob?
We can't be caught discussing this,
so be careful for the time being.
- Yes, sir.
Detective Seo, gather the case files
for the bank robberies.
I already have, sir.
I'll report them to you soon.
- Very good.
- Detectives Kim and Jo,
scan the banks in Seoul
that might be a target.
- How do we scan banks?
- Lower your voice, man.
We'll see where security is weak
and which ones have a lot of cash--
They're coming.
We don't know when they'll attack,
so let's all hurry.
You're right.
Shall we go eat?
- Sounds good.
- Let's go!
Detective Park.
- Go pick up your suit.
- My suit?
Oh, right, my suit!
Hey, what's up with them?
I'm not sure.
What's wrong with them?
My goodness,
you could be an actor.
I bet all the ladies
fall for you instantly.
Are you seeing anyone, by any chance?
No, of course not.
But I guess there is…
someone I need to apologize to.
Is that so?
If you go apologize to her
while looking this sharp,
I'm sure she'll forgive you.
Do you really think so?
I see you bought new clothes.
Is it your payday?
Well, I'm actually here to apologize.
You don't have to.
I enjoyed the film by myself.
The one titled
The Punk Who Never Returned.
Or was it The Prick Who Never Returned?
I'm truly sorry.
It's just that an urgent case
came up that day.
You should get back to work
since you're so busy.
And let's never see each other again.
I sincerely beg for your leniency.
Isn't that something criminals say?
Yes, you're right.
I just feel like I've committed a crime.
Goodness.
This shelf is nearly falling apart.
Could I help you with this?
Just leave it.
Let me see.
Do you have a hammer
and some nails lying around?
I said you didn't have to.
We'll never see each other again anyway.
You don't have to forgive me,
but let me at least fix this.
I've been so worried about you
ever since I stood you up that day.
I'll just fix this quietly and leave.
Why won't this fit?
There.
There we go.
Have some water.
Thank you.
Thank you for fixing it.
Don't mention it.
I had to use a stopgap measure today.
I'll make sure to come over the weekend
to fix it properly.
You're thinking of coming here again?
What I meant was…
You see…
I mean I'll take responsibility
for fixing the shelf.
I didn't mean anything else.
I shouldn't mean anything else.
All right, then.
What are you going to do
about your ruined shirt?
Getting my shirt dirty
isn't a big deal to me.
What matters is that I hurt you.
After everything you've said,
it would be horrible of me
not to forgive you.
Does that mean…
that you'll accept my apology?
Did you always want to be a detective?
It all started when I was 11.
I started catching cow thieves then.
How?
I could just look into my neighbors' eyes
and tell who was up to no good.
Maybe you should've been a shaman,
not a detective.
But I wouldn't have met you then.
Excuse me?
The thing is,
I never run away from anything.
It's just that I ended up
taking a step back while making arrests
and happened to run away
into your bookstore.
It's embarrassing to admit it,
but I'm glad I did.
Right.
What did you want to become?
What did I want to become?
Yes.
I'm embarrassed to say.
That makes me all the more curious.
I'll tell you some other time.
- Can't you tell me now?
- No, I don't want to.
I told you mine.
Please?
An actress.
Really?
I could see you as one.
I was the best at playing the role
of a crazy, abandoned woman.
Well, why didn't you become an actress?
My mother threatened to send me
to a temple somewhere far away.
If things had turned out differently,
we could've met as a shaman and a nun.
I saw your wound
while you were fixing the shelf.
Did you get hurt in the line of duty?
Oh, well…
I got the wound
while I was a student soldier.
You were a student soldier?
Yes.
Hmm.
Just a moment.
- Hello.
- Hello, miss.
I'll take this.
This one, please.
Thank you.
- Give me your hand.
- Sorry?
It's not really made for men,
but it looks good on you.
Do keep it on.
Okay.
I'll… make sure to keep it on.
- Shall we go?
- Yes.
The stars are beautiful tonight.
You're right.
Good job.
Goryeo Bank
Their modus operandi
has been identical for all banks.
First, they use a "closed" sign
to prevent anyone from entering.
Closed temporarily
On average,
they're out within eight minutes.
- Guards, get up.
- Okay.
And they kill the guards before leaving.
What about robbery times?
Changdo Bank in Busan was at 10:00 a.m.,
Chilsung Bank in Daegu was at 1:00 p.m.,
Myungdo Bank in Daejeon was at 1:15 p.m.,
and Jungil Bank in Suwon was at 2:30 p.m.
What about the banks?
Over there.
Right.
The banks in Seoul with the most cash
are Korea Bank,
Saessak Bank's main branch,
Gyeorye Bank's main branch,
and the Jongnam Branch of Goryeo Bank.
Why is Goryeo Bank so flush with cash?
Jongnam-gu is full of corporations,
so the bank handles all the salaries.
Wait a minute.
- What day is it?
- It's September 18.
Office workers usually get paid
on the 25th,
so if they were to strike Goryeo Bank…
they'll strike within a week.
I guess the workers in Jongnam-gu
won't be getting paid this month.
Don't you think they'd go for Korea Bank?
No, that would be nearly impossible
with all the heavy security
and soldiers on guard.
Saessak Bank is in front of a station
and wouldn't be an easy target either.
And the mall across from Gyeorye Bank
is always crowded,
so they won't strike there either.
In that case…
…it's Goryeo Bank.
Right here.
Do you think the robbers would have
all of this information?
They're former military.
I'm sure they have
an informant of some sort.
Stop playing with that.
I've… made up my mind.
I'm going to become a legal official
who properly punishes
all the criminals you catch.
We get it, so put that down.
What's wrong with him?
There is one rule we must commit to.
We must not let the citizens get hurt.
And we must not let a single penny
get stolen from the bank.
Are we not allowed to use guns then?
Only if absolutely necessary,
but there can't be a shootout in the bank.
We'll have to stop the robbers
from even entering the bank.
Won't that be too difficult to do?
Yes, of course.
So we'll have to be all the more prepared.
First, let's get our eyes on the street.
Listen to me carefully.
Eyes? Do you mean the bums?
That's right.
Our pals, who will be our eyes and ears
on the streets.
Alms, please.
Have each of them
go to every bank in Jongnam-gu tomorrow.
♪ The beggar who came last year ♪
♪ Is alive and here again ♪
♪ And he makes a pretty penny ♪
Tell the pals
exactly what to do, Detective Jo.
Jongnam Branch of Goryeo Bank
Alms, please.
Thank you!
There's something
you all need to watch out for.
You all know what this is, right?
What is it?
It's a Jeep. Haven't you seen this before?
- Right.
- Yes.
Jeeps usually only have
a door on each side.
But look here. How many do you see?
One, two. That's two on one side.
- Right.
- Multiply that for two sides.
What's two plus two?
- Five.
- Are you sure it's five?
Two plus two makes…
Just memorize it. It's four.
Two plus two makes four.
If you see a four-door Jeep,
tell me where you saw it immediately.
- Got it?
- Got it.
- And you, Detective Kim.
- Here you go.
Closely observe the inside
of Goryeo Bank with Eundong.
Try to figure out what could be done
in the case of a robbery.
Welcome.
So how is the safe opened?
First, you turn the lock
with the correct numbers,
and then a key is needed.
Who knows the numbers?
Only the branch manager knows it.
So only he can open the safe.
That's right.
Detective Seo, I need you
to go over the past case files again.
All criminals have
their own quirks and habits.
- So it was 1:00 p.m.…
- By figuring them out,
we can guess what patterns are used
in the planning of the crimes.
10:00 a.m., 1:00 p.m., 1:15 p.m.
And 2:30 p.m. in the afternoon.
"Celebrating the arrival
of USS Franklin in Busan"?
Hold it.
Relax your arm, man.
Keep your shoulder loose.
Keep still like this.
And fire. Got it?
Relax your arm.
Relax.
- Relax.
- Fire.
Hey! Who told you to shoot?
♪ Here comes the beggar dancing again ♪
Alms, please.
Jongnam Branch of Goryeo Bank
I saw a car just like this pull over here.
It had one, two, three…
F-Five? No, four doors!
Are you sure it had four doors?
- Yes!
- Detective Park, we got them.
You, tell us more.
I saw it earlier in front of Goryeo Bank.
Damn it, Goryeo Bank?
How many were there?
One, two.
Two.
How tall? What did they look like?
They were both…
about this tall.
They had caps on,
so I couldn't see their faces that well.
Good job.
Go share these potatoes with the others.
Thank you.
And here, go buy yourselves some soup.
Play rock, paper, scissors.
Why on earth would we do that?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Damn it.
I have a bad feeling.
You'll go undercover
as a Goryeo Bank guard tomorrow.
But the guard always dies at the end.
Don't worry. You'll have a gun too.
There's a lot more of them.
It's okay. Shoot at them with both hands.
You little punk.
- Should I?
- I trust you.
Is that true?
It's still a speculation,
but we're informing you as a precaution.
This is a great problem,
and yet Senior Superintendent Choi
hasn't even notified me.
I hear that the bank holds cash
for high-ranking officials
and famous actors.
As such, the Senior Superintendent
has asked us to operate in secrecy.
He is a very thoughtful man, as expected.
Of course.
No one is more thoughtful than he is.
Oh, and this is Detective Kim Sangsun,
who will go undercover as a guard.
I'll do my best.
But from what I've read in the papers,
it seems those robbers
always kill the guards.
I know. That's why I…
Thank you so much, Detective.
You're risking your life.
I'm making a huge sacrifice.
Yeonghan!
I think I know what time they'll strike.
Goodness, your feet stink.
I'm sorry,
but could you take a bath first?
No, I need to show you all this now.
All right, h-hurry.
- What?
- The light's gone out again.
Jeez. Come on.
- Talk to us.
- All right.
On the day
Changdo Bank in Busan was robbed,
there was a docking ceremony
for the USS Franklin
at the Port of Busan at 10:00 a.m.
On the day
Chilsung Bank in Daegu was robbed,
the Liberal Party had a campaign rally
at a nearby square at 1:00 p.m.
On the day
Myeongdo Bank in Daejeon was robbed,
there was a protest at the nearby
Jowon University at 1:15 p.m.
And when Jungil Bank in Suwon was robbed,
there was a false espionage report
at 2:30 p.m.
Hey, hey.
What these four days had in common was…
Ah. The police
were all occupied elsewhere.
Yes, that's right.
Wait a minute.
Lee Jungjae and Lee Hwaryong
are meeting at 11:00 a.m. tomorrow.
That's when they'll strike.
Hey, I told you two
not to dig into the bank robberies!
Sir, the robbers will strike
at 11:00 a.m. tomorrow
when Lee Jungjae and Lee Hwaryong
are scheduled to meet.
We're sure of it.
Our basis for this is…
Damn you.
Please let us at least prepare for it.
I'll accept whatever punishment
you give me later.
All right, fine.
Let's say the robbers will strike.
Even still, the meeting at Jongnam Hall
is a bigger deal to us, understand?
Sir, people's possessions are at risk!
- At least let us Unit 1…
- Sir?
Assemblyman Kim is looking for you.
All right, let's go. Go.
Sir, please!
If you two bring up
the bank robbers one more time,
I'm locking up your entire unit
in the holding cell, got it?
Now, get lost.
But…
What's such a big deal
about some thugs meeting up?
This is what we expected.
Let's just stick to our plan, sir.
I'll take this.
Here you go.
Herbal medicine
- Have a nice day.
- You too.
- Make the floor shine.
- Yes, sir.
Two hours from now at 11:00 a.m.,
Chairman Lee Jungjae
and Chairman Lee Hwaryong
will be meeting at Jongnam Hall.
All personnel will mobilize.
Bring your guns with you
in case of an emergency.
Most importantly,
only intervene
if Lee Hwaryong's side starts a fight.
If Chairman Lee Jungjae starts one,
stand by and wait for orders.
- Understood?
- Yes, sir!
Now, let's move!
- Bring your guns.
- Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
- Hurry!
- Let's move!
- Let's go.
- Everybody, move out!
Here we go.
Move out now! Hurry!
Wait. Where are your guys?
They'll be out soon.
They must be in the can.
Aren't you going?
Okay. I'll go ahead.
All right.
We stick to the plan.
Got it.
Move out! Let's go!
Where are you all off to?
Are you going to war or something?
What are you doing here, Hwang?
Senior Superintendent Choi had us
make sure you don't cause trouble.
Who says we're causing trouble?
Hey, that's enough.
Just listen to us, okay?
Well, we were just on our way
to protect Chairman Lee too.
- Isn't that right?
- That's right.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
Oh. Wait a minute.
Man, it looks like I forgot something.
You all go ahead.
Freeze.
Senior Superintendent Choi gave us
permission to shoot if you disobey.
He also did tell us not to kill you.
We really don't have time left.
Hey, Officer Kim.
Officer Kim.
Officer Kim!
Come on, Officer Kim.
Senior Superintendent Choi
ordered me not to respond.
Jeez.
But you just responded.
Doesn't that mean you disobeyed orders?
You might as well just let us go too.
I can't do that.
Goryeo Bank will get robbed
if we're stuck here.
People will die!
Officer Kim.
The thing about that bank is,
not only does it hold money
for rich people,
but it also holds money for old ladies
who sell vegetables every day
and for fathers who work to the bone
to educate their children.
Hear me out.
Let's say those rich people
won't really be affected
even if their money gets stolen.
But you see,
people who live hand to mouth
will have their dreams and lives
taken from them.
Some kids out there won't be able
to afford education,
and some families will become homeless.
Listen.
We're not trying to protect
the rich people's money.
We're trying to do it for all the people
whose lives are at stake.
You boys are true policemen.
Yeonghan.
You coldhearted punk.
You need to learn how to be human first!
A human, all right?
Mother…
That's what my mother did for me.
She earned what she could
working as a seamstress
to help me become a policeman.
Mother.
Officer Kim.
You're a good son. You really are.
Could you let us out now?
Police
Detective Park.
Look who it is. Officer Kim!
I'll lead the way.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Why aren't they here yet?
We'll stand by
and subdue the robbers
as soon as they get out of the car.
In the case that they end up
entering the bank,
we'll lure them outside and grab them.
Stand firm, Sangsun.
Here you go, sir.
Take care.
Damn it.
I'd like to transfer this amount
to the Kitazawa Bookstore in Tokyo.
Uh, Tokyo?
Is there any chance
you could come in another day?
This might take a while today.
I'm sorry, but I need it sent today.
Goryeo Bank
- Stand watch.
- All right.
Jongnam Branch of Goryeo Bank
Closed temporarily
Thank you.
- Take care.
- Thanks.
Everybody down!
Get out of the way!
Employees come forward and stand down!
Listen to them. Come on!
Hurry! Move it!
Get down!
Try anything and you're dead.
Get down.
Where are you going?
Where's the manager's office?
It's that way!
- Heads down.
- Stay still.
What on earth?
What?
Hey, come on. Wake up.
Wake up!
Seoul police
Yeonghan.
They must be inside.
Damn it.
Looks like we don't have a choice.
We start now.
Hey, wake up.
Wake up. Come on.
What is it? Is he dead?
He's still breathing,
but he won't wake up.
Excuse me.
Our manager has a chronic disease.
Once he falls asleep, he can't wake up.
What kind of disease is that?
It's true! It's true!
You better wake him up now.
- How am I supposed to--
- Wake him up!
He just needs to fall into a deep sleep
nobody can wake him up from.
Branch Manager
What's this?
It's premium tea
from my brother back home, sir.
What a surprise.
I wasn't expecting this from you.
It tastes lovely.
I'm very sorry, sir.
Sir.
Sir!
Excuse me.
- What is it?
- Do you have a light?
I don't smoke. Get lost.
Wait, in that case…
Yeonghan.
Senior Superintendent Choi's radio
is down.
Damn it.
You go tell him in person, Officer Kim.
All right.
Are we going with Plan B then?
Yes. Let's stand by for now.
- All right.
- Yeonghan.
I'm ready.
I'm so sorry, sir!
We're out of time! We need to leave!
Heads down!
Take the money out here.
Okay. Come on, take the money.
Everybody, move out.
- Everybody, move out!
- Hurry, hurry! Let's go!
Let's go.
We're taking the girl.
Please spare me.
- Move out.
- Yes, sir.
Wait, wait! Hold on, stop.
I'm the guard here. Take me instead.
Back off!
Let's go!
Freeze! Stay where you are!
- Huh?
- Stand still!
Stay away, or I'll shoot!
Don't do it!
Damn it.
No, no, no!
- You prick!
- Freeze!
Move, and I'll shoot.
Don't move! Drop your guns!
Damn it.
Drop your guns!
Do you want her dead?
- That sounded like a pistol.
- Damn it.
Drop your guns!
- Do we shoot?
- No, don't.
Shoot him if he tries anything.
Okay.
Those pricks.
- Where's the car?
- Right there.
Let's go!
Where are they going?
I know.
It's not the escape route we anticipated.
Anticipated escape route, my foot.
They're heading for the main gates.
- Come on, stealthily close in.
- Yes, sir.
Jeez.
Get closer. Closer!
They're on us.
Get rid of them.
-
That little…
- Get out of the way!
- Come on!
- Hurry.
- Come on.
Shouldn't we shoot at them?
They got a hostage! Make a turn here!
Yes, sir!
Pathetic pigs.
Is this the right way?
Wait, why are you keeping so quiet?
What's wrong with you?
Are you sure we're going the right way?
It's more crowded here!
Take off your mask.
Take it off now!
- What's wrong?
- What is it?
I can't die like this.
I can't die like this, I really can't!
Let go!
Are you going to kill me?
I know you're going to kill me!
I know you are!
What's wrong with her?
Are you out of your mind?
If I die,
my widowed mother is going to die too.
Then I won't even get a funeral!
Hold her down!
- Let go!
- Let's die together.
- Stop it.
- Let's all die
and wander the afterlife.
Where are you taking us?
What on earth?
To jail.
- You prick!
- Shoot!
I'm going to kill you!
Let go!
You crazy prick!
- No!
- Damn you!
- What are those punks doing?
- What?
- Over there.
- Who's that?
Are you all right?
Yeonghan!
- Get him.
- Don't move!
Stop resisting!
Are you okay, Yeonghan?
Chief Yu!
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
Let me go!
Why are you just watching?
What's wrong with Chief Yu?
Get over here!
He's calling. Get over there.
Go on!
I'll go, sir.
Hyeju.
Are you all right?
I am.
You worthless, thieving punks.
A bunch of good-for-nothings.
- You no-good punks!
- Eyes down!
Lock them up.
Hyeju.
You're bleeding.
Are you really all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
You saved me from the worst.
Don't mention it.
By the way, Hyeju.
Are you back to your normal self again?
Did you actually think I went mad?
No, what I meant was…
This?
- Exactly.
- How did I do?
Even top actresses would envy
your godlike acting.
- That's a little too…
- Yeonghan.
Please ask the heavens
for some easier cases next time.
It's not easy to be like Frank Hamer.
I'm sorry I underestimated you,
Frank Hamer.
I want to fight with fists, not guns.
I'm better with fists.
Mm.
Watch out for tomorrow.
I bet your faces will be
all over the papers.
It looks like
someone else will make the headlines.
Hey, get these punks locked up.
And go tell Chairman Lee what happened.
Gosh, I haven't seen him so excited.
I'll take you to the hospital
to get your wound treated.
We don't need to do that,
but I'd like something sweet.
Something sweet?
Don't you need to see a doctor?
I'm low on sugar.
Ah. In that case…
Would you like to get some rice cakes
at an old lady's place?
Ah. Do you mean Ms. Ho's shop?
- Yes, that's right.
- I'd love that.
Are you in a special relationship
with Yeonghan,
Jongnam Bookstore lady?
I-Is it true?
Hey, don't put Hyeju in a tight spot.
I just have a crush on her.
Let's go.
Shall we?
I'll leave the rest up to you, sir.
Sure, Yeonghan.
Let's go. I don't even want to see them.
Wait, you need to wrap things up.
Come on, Chief Yu.
You take care of that, sir.
That's what chiefs do, right?
- Let's go.
- Hey, hey, hey! Stop right…
Jongnam Police Station!
One more time.
Don't pat yourselves on the back
for catching some petty thieves!
You all
disobeyed your superior's orders
and engaged in mutiny.
This is grounds for severe punishment.
- Are you aware of that?
- Yes, sir!
But I'll let you off the hook
just this once,
and you can thank
my merciful and generous spirit for that.
- Is it not because of your commendation?
- What?
How could you say that, Detective Kim?
Will you share
the reward you received, sir?
What reward? Did you see a reward?
That's just a rumor!
Right, I heard you donated the full amount
- for orphans of the war, sir.
- Orphans?
- Did he really do that?
- What?
- I learn a lot from you, sir.
- Learn what?
- Get some journalists in here! Applause!
- Wait a minute.
Senior Superintendent Choi!
- Senior Superintendent Choi!
- Get out.
Stop clapping and leave!
Stop it!
You're disobeying my orders!
Goodness.
Those punks can't make me
donate the fat reward I got.
I thought police work would be boring,
but it's like being in a battlefield.
I had another nightmare today.
One about Frank Hamer scolding me.
So, do you regret it?
- Definitely not. I don't regret it.
- No.
It's just that it's tougher than expected.
Right, Hojeong?
No, it's not tough for me at all.
I did almost wet my pants a few times.
Was it the same for you too, Yeonghan?
I'm no exception.
Just wet your pants if you need to.
I'll change your diapers for you,
with extra starchy ones.
A no-good scumbag
mends his ways in this tear-jerker,
The Man Who Returned!
Right.
- What is it?
- No.
- What's wrong?
- I need to go, boys.
- You can go home now!
- Take care.
Damn it.
No way.
I almost lost my mind waiting for you.
I'm so sorry for being late.
Someone once told me,
"Cops will never come in time for a date."
Who told you that?
This girl called Nansil.
I see.
I'll assume you've forgiven me.
- Shall we head in?
- Okay.
Wait.
Someone once told me,
"If a cop doesn't want to get dumped,
he should hold her hand tightly."
Who told you that?
Gyeonghwan.
Is he the man that's like a wild boar?
It didn't look like
he'd ever dated anyone.
I shouldn't have listened to him.
Let's go.
Okay.
How's your injury?
I'm all right now.
The Man Who Returned,
now showing in theaters!
The Man Who Returned
Halt what you're doing and return to base!
Yes, sir!
Platoon commander!
You need to come see this, sir.
Yes, this is Hoyang Police Station.
At Hoak Mountain?
I apologize
for not keeping the promise to date,
but next time,
I'll make sure
to send a well-screened candidate.
You can deposit the balance
after that happens, okay?
What happened
to the child I was supposed to receive?
Oh, yes, we've already placed him
in another good home.
Chief Detective 1958
Please find my dear Jongwoo.
Is there anyone suspicious close to you?
- Who did you just say?
Audrey. Audrey Ko.
Isn't this enough evidence
to lock her up, sir?
Let's start over
from when they went missing.
- Move!
I need to ask you a favor.
You accuse me of such evil?
- Stop!
What's going on here?
Senior Superintendent Choi has ordered us
to beg you for forgiveness, ma'am.
There's no need for an apology.
Just sack all of them.
Translated by Jihun Lee