Chief Detective 1958
This series is unrelated to any places,
persons, settings or events.
Scenes involving animals were filmed in
compliance with animal welfare guidelines.
"Episode 5"
Why are you all white as ghosts?
What's with the makeup?
These guys threw ash at us
as they ran away.
Why don't you all hit the shower first?
You all look nasty.
Well, let me shake this off
before I go shower.
- Let me join in.
- Go away!
Hey, stop!
Come on, seriously.
- I told you to stop!
- Mister.
Geumok.
Sungchil…
Is it really Sungchil?
Take her with you.
Sungchil…
Any witnesses?
No one claims to have seen anything
before his grandmother
discovered the body.
No one, my foot.
They're just afraid to talk.
We'll help you if anything happens.
So please trust us
and tell us what you know.
I really wish I could,
but you know how things are.
And I have Geumok to take care of.
Please come out and talk to us.
Sir, please.
Help us catch whoever killed Sungchil.
What on earth happened?
I don't know.
Just have a bowl of noodles and go.
Do you really not know anything?
I don't.
Don't ask me again.
Sungchil is dead!
He was stabbed to death by a random punk!
You need to speak up,
so I can go catch or kill that prick!
Detective Park.
I'm begging you.
Please stop.
Why won't anyone talk to us?
How could they be like this?
They're fearing for their lives.
Fearing who, exactly?
Who do you think
the market merchants are most afraid of?
You're right.
I'm sure he did it.
If one of his thugs
hadn't stopped him then,
he would've killed Sungchil
then and there.
Please don't resent
the market merchants too much.
They want to tell you what they know,
but they're just too afraid.
You're right.
It's not their fault.
Episode 5
There's No Criminal That Can't Be Caught!
What was that?
Go out and check.
Move it, move it! Hurry!
What kind of crazy punk
dares to come here?
Come on! Go and get them!
- Go and tell him now!
- Yes, sir.
- The cops from Hwangchun are here.
- Who?
The Hwangchun cops, boss.
Does that Hwangchun prick
have a death wish?
- Let go!
- Damn it!
You're dead to me!
Yeonghan, are you all right?
Yeah.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you even here?
Hey, I have a favor to ask.
Punch me.
Are you out of your mind?
I just want to know
how strong your punch is.
So go ahead.
Why? You think I won't hit you?
Do it then.
You better hit hard.
I don't want you to regret it.
Clench your jaw
if you don't want to lose a tooth.
Happy?
- Look, you punched first, all right?
- What?
Now, this is self-defense.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Where's the knife?
What knife?
The one you guys used to kill Sungchil.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
There's nothing.
Search their pockets.
Yes, sir.
What's this?
Since when do thugs listen
to fortune tellers?
No, I'll suffer bad luck!
I mean…
p-please give it back.
Suffer bad luck?
You're nothing but bad luck, you snake.
- Let's take Viper with us.
- All right.
Get him up.
I apologize, Chairman Lee.
I warned you all
not to cause trouble again.
Tell me straight.
Did Viper do it?
Well…
Now,
who did you say arrested him?
Hey, hey, hey. You should take him
to the hospital, not bring him here.
You mind your own business, Hwang.
What?
Mind your own business, you prick!
That's enough!
What's going on here?
We're investigating.
Go on.
Why did you kill him?
Who?
Why did you kill Sungchil?
Who even is Sungchil?
I can't kill someone I don't know.
Sungchil was a poor kid
who was orphaned in the war.
He just recently learned how to read
and helped his grandma read the papers.
All he wanted was to live his life.
Why would you kill such a kid?
Why? Why?
Who gives a damn about that kid?
- Wait.
- Wait, stop, Detective Park.
Tell me. Why did you kill him?
I know you killed him.
It was you, wasn't it?
I killed him, all right?
Just put the gun down.
So why? Why did you kill him?
Detective Park, put down the gun first.
Tell me, you prick. Why did you kill him?
Tell me, you damn prick. Say it!
You cops can't just take people like this!
Our boss was with us drinking all night!
This is an abuse of power.
You cops can't just arrest people
like this without evidence.
Boss, you drank with us all night!
You beat up an innocent man
and held a gun to his head.
You guys are all hopeless, aren't you?
An innocent man, sir?
He's the culprit who killed Sungchil.
Do you have proof?
He has 20 witnesses.
I've had it up to here with you all.
Chief Yu, I'm docking your pay
for two months.
The rest of you
are relieved of your duties.
Dismissed.
Sir?
Give us a moment.
What's with all the long faces?
Don't worry. You all aren't fired.
What about the case, sir?
We can investigate,
but just not the Dongdaemun guys.
That means we can't then.
You're not going to listen to him,
are you?
Listen to him? No, I want you
to arrest everyone responsible.
How do we get the damn prick?
We need to find evidence first.
Let's start from the top.
And where's that?
The crime scene.
What is it?
It's caustic soda.
The scene is such a mess.
Would there still be evidence?
Detective.
Thank you so much.
Let's go.
♪ The seagulls cry so sorrowfully ♪
♪ At the Incheon port of farewell ♪
- You sound great.
- I love it.
♪ The sailors in love shed their tears ♪
♪ At every port ♪
♪ Just as they have fallen in love ♪
♪ The boat horn of farewell cries out ♪
Isn't that nice!
Come on, stop crying.
I promise you
I'll arrest Viper within three days.
You don't have any evidence.
You don't even have the murder weapon.
Then we'll go find the weapon, right?
It'll be hard to find
if they hid it really well.
Come on, you…
All we have left is Sungchil.
We have to stay on high alert.
At this rate, we'll lose Viper.
But can't Sungchil…
Can't he have an autopsy done on him?
I read about it
in American mystery novels.
We could do it,
but it's not like the books.
It won't directly tell us who killed him.
I observed an autopsy once,
and it wasn't that helpful.
Should we still have it done just in case?
Never mind it.
It'll just hurt his grandmother even more.
Let's convince her
and have it done.
- What?
- Like I said,
all we have left is Sungchil's body.
Ma'am.
There's this thing called an autopsy.
It may help us find out…
It may help find out how Sungchil died.
And to do that,
we'll have to look inside his body.
You don't need to agree if it's too much.
We won't do it if you say no.
You don't have to agree to it
if it upsets you, ma'am.
Get it done.
If it'll help catch his killer,
it must be done.
Thank you.
I promise you I'll catch his murderer.
That's a promise.
Thank you for telling me
that you'll stop at nothing.
I cannot thank you enough.
National Forensic Service
The body reveals the truth
We found a total of eight stab wounds.
The cause of death is likely
excessive bleeding from the wounds.
I must say, I've never seen
a more brutal death in my career.
Whoever stabbed him
must have suffered injuries on their hand.
No, I'll suffer bad luck!
You're nothing but bad luck, you snake.
The width and depth
of the blade are worth noting
as the wounds are very narrow and long.
This suggests
that the weapon wasn't an ordinary knife.
Look here.
And here.
There are also bruises.
Those bruises
can't have been caused by impact.
Those are what you see in wrestling
when the thigh bands are too tight.
- Stand still, Detective Kim.
- All right.
Grab his arm and pull,
Detective Jo.
Okay.
There were at least three.
One guy stabbed him,
and two held him still.
Do you see this reddish part?
It's some sort of rash.
It looks like a burn wound
but not an ordinary one.
Perhaps from chemicals?
Wait, we found caustic soda
in the water at the crime scene.
Caustic soda could cause a burn like this.
We'll end the external examination here
and proceed with the internal examination.
I'll pray for you…
that you be born into…
a good, wealthy family…
in your next life, Sungchil.
Don't even pretend to know me…
all right?
Ma'am…
You won't have to care about spelling
where you are now.
I hope you're free and happy there.
Elementary Korean
I brought you new shoes…
for your journey.
Sungchil!
Viper.
Rattlesnake.
White Snake.
If there were three,
it's obvious they were the ones.
Can't we just interrogate them?
Since Viper's stuck at the hospital,
let's grill the other two first.
You saw how those thugs
all barged in here to rescue their boss.
We need a foolproof plan.
- Finding the murder weapon is crucial.
- You're right, sir.
It says that without a murder weapon,
the prosecution becomes unlikely
and leads to a lighter sentence.
Did the autopsy reveal
anything about the weapon?
Right.
The depth and width of the wounds
suggest the knife wasn't an ordinary one.
They said the blade
is likely narrow and long.
Then it's Viper.
The knife you described
was Lee Jungjae's gift to him.
When he was divvying up territories,
Lee Jungjae gave his closest men
knives inscribed with the word "hwarang."
Viper always carried that knife with him.
So he used it for the murder and hid it.
He hid it, not got rid of it?
It's not easy to get rid of weapons.
You'd have to go out to the sea
to throw it out there.
If you throw it into a stream,
people will find it in daylight.
Then he just may have buried it somewhere.
I wish we could just lock those snakes up
and beat them to death.
Tsk.
Wait. It's raining.
Wait, Yeonghan!
I'll get you an umbrella.
Let him be.
I just hope…
the rain can wash away
what he's feeling inside.
- What's wrong?
- Shush!
Take a look.
Black, black, black, white, white, white.
May you be moved by Yin and Yang
and bring us all prosperity!
Black, black, black.
White, white, white.
- What's he doing right now?
- May you be moved by Yin and Yang…
And you call yourself a cop?
It's all the rage these days.
The entire neighborhood is offering
their savings and property deeds.
So you're telling me…
The people at the market
and even boarders are offering their money
to the Church of Black and White?
People are out of their minds these days.
So how are you
going to take advantage of that?
It doesn't make any sense to me,
but based on their logic…
they'd retrieve the hidden knife
if their god told them to, no?
Uh…
But how?
You could use the cult leader.
But I have no idea
what kind of person it could be.
I remember
Detective Oh was trying to dig dirt
- on that cult before.
- Really?
Who's Detective Oh?
Is it just me or am I being interrogated?
Detective Oh.
Yes?
What have you found out about this church?
The Church of Black and White?
Let's see, the Church…
I did dig into it,
but I found nothing.
How is that possible?
The thing is…
its leader came from heaven, so…
You're a detective!
It's actually miraculous.
That church can fix anything.
I witnessed it with my own two eyes.
Do your two eyes need some fixing?
What did you just say?
Get out. Move.
- Hey, get out.
- Unbelievable.
Come on, out of my way.
I told you to get out!
I might as well tell you one more thing
if you are going to dig.
- Some say he rose from the ground.
- Are you kidding me?
- You punk.
- That's what I heard.
- The rumors say so.
- This Church of Black and White…
Where is it?
Damn, that's a big one.
I really don't know!
Well…
Police
Black, black, black, white, white, white.
Simply believe in me.
- With your firm faith in me…
- May you be moved by Yin and Yang
- and bring us all prosperity!
- …I shall perform miracles upon you!
Black, black, black, black, black, black.
White, white, white.
May you be moved by Yin and Yang
and bring us all prosperity!
Black, black, black, and, and, and
white, white, white.
May you be moved by Yin and Yang
and bring us all prosperity!
Black, black, black, and, and, and
white, white, white.
May you be moved by Yin and Yang
and bring us all prosperity!
Black, black, black, and, and, and
white, white, white.
May you be moved by Yin and Yang
and bring us all prosperity!
Look over there. It's Rattlesnake.
Now, with his power to heal,
our leader shall perform a miracle
upon this man who was born a cripple!
I shall set you free from your suffering.
Ward off, illness.
It worked!
It worked! He has healed!
That's 500.
A 100, and another 100.
Hey, cripple.
You better work on your acting.
It doesn't feel…
Goodness. You're here, Your Eminence.
Jeez.
That pillow was too hard.
I've got a cramp.
Could you fix this for me? Ow.
Who keeps money in a chamber pot?
That's got to smell.
Last week, this "blind woman" made 30 hwan
and the "cripple" made 50 hwan today.
Who are you all?
Who do you think?
We're people seeking miracles.
You're sure
you can actually perform miracles, right?
You of little faith!
How dare you doubt god's messenger?
You will die a sudden death.
No, that's not what I meant.
It's just really odd
how dirty the cripple's feet are
when he can't even stand.
I thought maybe it was a scam.
Your Eminence.
This man has been possessed by a dog.
Do you think
you could exorcize it from him?
He just keeps biting people.
I'll give you five seconds to do it.
I am much too exhausted today
to perform any more miracles.
There is a time for everything.
You can't just barge in here.
What?
- What's going on?
- Don't move.
You talk too much.
Listen.
We're looking for a particular knife.
And I need you to find that for me.
Yes!
Ouch!
Damn it!
Daesong Barbershop
Hey!
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey, stop!
Damn it.
DONGBU JAAE HOSPITAL
Is that you, Great Leader?
You deserve to have your limbs torn off…
…to get hit by lightning…
…and to have all your organs strewn out!
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me!
Beware of water, fire, dogs,
cars, alcohol, knives, guns, horses,
diseases and natural disasters!
Are… Are those the only things
I need to be wary of?
There's one more thing.
Beware of the wrath
of the innocent soul that has passed.
If you fail to obey
the command I've written here,
you will suffer a greater ordeal.
"The grudge of an innocent soul
is contained within you."
"Find the source of the grudge…"
Damn it.
- Is this the right spot?
- Yes.
I found it.
- I found it!
- Really?
You punk. Are you blind?
Who's there?
Damn it. All right then.
- Goodness.
- Hey, you.
You little punk.
Keep digging.
You better find the knife.
I found it.
Really?
Hwarang
I hope
I'm not causing any trouble here.
Trouble? Don't say that.
With the election drawing near,
it's best to get rid of any problems.
Of course.
Since issuing warrants is the remit
of the Prosecution Service,
I will keep things in check.
I feel such a sense of relief
hearing you say that.
What do you mean
a warrant won't be issued, sir?
The Prosecution Service won't be issuing
any warrants whatsoever
against the Dongdaemun gang,
so don't waste your energy.
But Viper is a suspect in a murder case!
Listen. If things go wrong,
you and your whole unit
could lose your lives, understand?
Dongbu Jaae Hospital
Emergency Room
What? Where on earth are these guys?
- Hey.
- Ouch.
What's with the crutch?
You don't even need it.
Not you bunch again.
Did you think we wouldn't find it?
We have evidence, Chief.
It took us ages to dig it out.
- Chief Yu.
- What?
Where are you going, sir?
As long as you're in this country,
you won't be getting any warrants
against the Dongdaemun gang.
What kind of bullcrap is that?
- What did you say?
- Calm down, Chief.
It's all measures to protect Chairman Lee
from slanderers like you two.
No need to say more. Let him go.
No, we're not letting him go.
You do it then, Detective Hwang.
Yes, sir.
Goodness.
I hear Chairman Lee…
recently won a contract
to supply the Armed Forces Command.
Everyone connected to our boss
is going to make a killing now.
What a load of crap.
Sangsun.
Hey.
What kind of a pathetic cop
can't get a warrant, huh?
It's too bad for you…
because I killed him.
- Hey.
- Why?
Are you going to beat me up again?
Go ahead.
Do it. Come on.
I'm telling you
- I'm going to get you no matter what.
- Whatever you say, man.
But do bring a warrant next time.
Let's go.
Yes, boss.
Have a nice day.
Jongnam Bookstore
Why didn't you come in?
I'll bring you warm water.
You should dry yourself.
All I wanted…
was to keep the people closest to me
from dying in vain.
I wanted criminals to be punished,
no matter what.
That's why I joined the police.
And those are rules
I've never broken until now.
But…
a friend I held dear died.
I know who killed him…
…but there's nothing I can do.
I shouldn't have been reckless
when I first arrested him.
I should have…
approached it more rationally.
You couldn't…
because it was Sungchil.
I should've found out
where the knife was hidden first.
I call myself a detective,
and all I did
was dive head first like a fool.
You can't account for everything
just because you're a detective.
Maybe I should turn in my badge
and kill all of them.
Or I should just eliminate all of them
without anyone knowing.
That's all I can think about these days.
Have you even eaten today?
Come on, let's head out.
Let's go get some food first.
Even when I spent sleepless nights
trying to catch cow thieves,
I didn't feel this way.
I know I need to catch the killer…
but I don't know
where to start or what to do.
Jeez.
Come on in.
We're having a drink.
- Would you like to join?
- No, thanks. Not today.
Please join us, Detective Park.
He failed the exam. Come on.
I offered up
three months' worth of rent to that cult.
I deserve to die.
See, you should've told me
you had all that money.
I could've opened a savings account
at the bank for you.
Stop talking about dying, all right?
You can take the exam again next year!
At least you get another chance.
But me?
I can't get a warrant,
so I won't get a chance.
Warrants aren't a big deal.
Why don't you just ask for one?
You see,
this country is rotten to the bone.
No prosecutor is willing to issue
a warrant for the prick.
Well, that's easy.
Then ask another country for a warrant.
They'll want to catch bad guys too.
Gukjin.
What did you just say?
Another country?
What's with the American flag?
I found a way
to catch that damned snake, sir.
We make him commit an international crime.
Lee Jungjae will be helpless
in such a case.
How would we do that?
Viper's turf is no bigger than Jongnam.
There's a way. Gather up.
That's good.
Jongnam Market Merchants' Association
Annex Groundbreaking Ceremony
- Is everything ready?
- You're here, boss.
It looks terrific, boss.
You notice how peaceful it is
without that Park Yeonghan meddling?
- You're right.
- Yes, boss.
Now that those annoying punks
are out of the way,
we just have to focus on the ceremony.
Boys, let's go! Head out, move!
Where are you off to, sir?
I'm your chief. I can't let you go alone.
Just stay here. You're getting up in age.
Come on, I told you I was
the Steel Hammer of Mapo back in the day.
Will you fight with a hammer today, sir?
All right, let's go.
All right. Let's go!
Move out!
Jongnam Police Station
The groundbreaking ceremony
for the annex building
of the Jongnam Market
Merchants' Association will begin now.
Please welcome the regional director,
Ou Samryong, on stage.
Give him a big hand!
Clap harder!
That's enough. Enough.
Thank you all for coming here
despite your busy schedules
with the construction of...
I heard
the construction is all screwed up!
- Hello.
Today's ceremony is over,
- so you may now leave.
- You can go.
Feel free to leave.
Go home now.
Hey, why didn't we get
an invite to the party?
Why are you all here?
You don't even have a warrant.
We're not here as cops today.
All badges off,
- let's just fight this out.
- Sounds good to me.
But give me an hour, will you?
This is an important event.
You see, we're a little busy.
So I'll just go ahead.
Hey.
Stop him. Stop him!
Deal with him! Go!
These damn pricks must have a death wish.
Damn it. Get off me!
- Rescue… Help.
- US Army, please.
- Uh, soldier… attack.
- Yeah.
You little leech.
- Let go.
- Stop hanging on to me!
It's the American soldiers, boss!
Why on earth would they be here?
Hands up!
You're attacking American soldiers.
- What did he say?
- The US Army.
You attacked an American soldier.
What bullcrap is that?
I see no Americans here.
Here.
I'm an American, you punk.
Who's this prick?
It can't be done.
We can't just detain
a South Korean citizen
and discriminate
within the US military police.
This would violate
the South Korea and US agreement
and could lead to diplomatic issues.
He says it violates the Korea-US agreement
We're not asking the American forces
to punish Viper.
We just need you
to buy us a little bit of time
before we can take him away.
We are asking only for some time
until we can bring him.
Just… three hours.
Uh…
Two hours.
Lieutenant.
A soldier who keeps his word
is a truly honorable soldier,
wouldn't you agree?
I was helping my friends
and these gangsters just attacked me.
Understood. We'll contact you later.
Okay.
Steve, thank you from the Steel Hammer!
We get it, Chief Yu.
You don't have to bring it up so much.
Thank you!
We couldn't have done this
without you, Lieutenant.
Thank you so much.
We couldn't make it
if Lieutenant didn't help us. Thank you.
Korean gangsters…
…are no big deal.
Hey, Steve!
Let's do it again another time?
No. Our friendship ends here.
Good luck, okay?
Bye, Steve.
- Goodbye!
- Bye!
Battalion Commander's Office
May we enter, Commander?
I understand. All right.
Salute.
My apologies.
That was an urgent call.
Here I am
with our country's preeminent war hero.
It's an honor.
You flatter me too much.
I'm simply just a humble soldier.
You are too kind.
Just a humble soldier?
I hear that you are a star on the rise
with your patriotism,
youth, and formidable leadership.
My expectations are high
for you, Commander.
Thank you.
I myself had been searching
for an army contractor.
Meeting you like this, Chairman Lee,
I feel a sense of relief in my heart.
Thanks to your cooperation
with the contract,
preparations for my nomination
have gone smoothly.
You can trust me to handle
any military affairs.
Anything outside of the military,
I'll trust you to handle for me.
I will certainly make sure
to repay my gratitude to you
so you are not disappointed.
Thank you, sir.
Now, if you'll sign the contract…
Just a moment.
Sir,
there's been a clash
between an American soldier
and the Dongdaemun gang.
Get out.
Yes, sir.
I'm sure it's a trivial matter.
I'll take good care of it.
Uh…
Do remember.
Please do keep in mind…
that both of our fates…
hang on this contract.
Understood.
Good.
Hey, do you even know who I am?
I'm Chairman Lee Jungjae's right-hand man!
This is Korea.
I'll be out soon, and when I do,
you pricks are all dead to me.
- I know your faces.
- Shut up!
What do you mean?
How is it impossible to get him out?
He was unaware. Perhaps you could explain…
This is no small matter.
Your man assaulted an American soldier.
There's nothing you can do
but wait for their decision.
And that's that.
- Sir.
- What is it?
A Jongnam detective is here to see you.
Your reputation precedes you.
I could say the same for you.
Judging by the look in your eyes…
I can see why my men suffered hardship.
Hardship is what one experiences
when life is much too hard.
What you mean is punishment
you thugs deserved for your crimes.
Should I call this rashness or bravery?
I'm not here to be rash or brave.
Chairman Lee,
ruler of the heavens and the earth,
I'm here to humbly offer you a proposal.
A proposal?
What could an ordinary detective
possibly offer me?
What if I do?
Then I'll eagerly accept it.
But if you don't,
you won't leave this place in one piece.
You rule over the heavens and the earth,
but there is one thing
you're not capable of ruling over.
The Daechang Daily.
I've acquired their draft
for tomorrow's headlines.
You've shut down
any mention of the ceremony,
except for that one.
Right-hand man of Dongdaemun's Lee Jungjae
arrested after assaulting American soldier
What is it that you want?
Does that mean
I leave this place in one piece?
I'm going to kill that prick
from Hwangchun for good this time.
Will you really?
Ou Samryong.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Kim Sungchil.
You know how this works.
Put them on yourself.
You got a warrant?
Show it to him, Hojeong.
Do you see your name?
Ou for "fish,"
Sam for "three," and ryong for "ant."
You're no Viper of Yongmoon Mountain.
You're just a damn ant!
It's yours, isn't it?
D-Do you have proof?
More than enough.
This wound on your cheek.
Hey, you rebel!
It is you. What are you up to?
Why are you here?
Get lost, Triangle Head.
I just missed you too much, kid.
How have you been?
What's wrong?
Get him. Go get him!
The bruises you left on his body
when your men grabbed Sungchil's arms
to hold him still.
And…
this cut on your hand
from when you stabbed him.
It's not that we didn't have proof.
It just took us time
to get a prick like you locked up.
There's something I've learned
while dealing with you.
There's no punk in this world
that can't be caught.
"The men who murdered Kim
at Jongnam Market have been arrested,
namely the Dongdaemun gang's
number two Ou, Bang, and Chu.
Investigation revealed that the men used
a lethal weapon for the murder.
An autopsy conducted
by the National Forensic Service,
an institute founded in 1955
under the Ministry of Home Affairs,
revealed that Mr. Ou was not alone
in committing the crime.
Based on this information,
Unit 1 of the Jongnam Police Station
was finally able to apprehend Mr. Ou."
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
Everything is fine now,
now that they've been caught.
Drink up, Sungchil.
Goodness.
Hey, why are you always so happy?
My father was a slave.
Back in the day, I would've been one too,
but that's all history now.
I couldn't be happier
making money selling rice cakes.
If the world changes for the better,
who's to say
someone like me can't become rich?
I'm going to learn how to read and write,
read a lot of books,
and expand Grandma's rice cake shop.
I wish I could live in a world
where people like you gain riches
instead of those who steal from others.
But you'll catch all those scumbags,
won't you?
Of course. I'll beat them all up.
Then a simple boy like me
could become rich soon
and let Grandma live comfortably.
Life would be so exciting
if only that could happen, wouldn't it?
Yes, I'm sure such a day will come.
It will.
- I'll pour you a drink.
- All right.
Thank you.
I'll go now.
That military contract wasn't easy to win.
You can't mess this up
like you did with the smuggling.
You may rest easy, sir.
There won't be any problems this time.
Any problems that could arise
would get in the way
of Commander Baek's career.
And he's an essential figure
we need on our side.
Understood, sir.
I'll handle it without a hitch.
Damn, what's this bum doing?
Hey, get out of the way.
Out of the way, you bum.
Are you deaf?
- Me?
- Who else is there?
Hey!
Let's go!
What's going on?
Get off, you bums!
Get off me, you punk!
There you go.
Get off me!
Good job. Let's go.
Let me go, you scumbags!
Step aside.
Get on!
Here we go.
Yes?
What? Beggars?
Here is today's headline news.
Military supplies
meant for the Armed Forces Command
are being secretly traded in Seoul.
The supplies include
items such as expensive liquor
and premium nylon socks.
The military authorities
have announced severe measures
- against those responsible.
- Get out.
Here is the next news item.
Large amounts have recently been donated
to orphanages in Seoul
under the name Hong Gildong.
President Rhee Syngman has promised
to reward the mystery figure when found.
- Let's drink.
- Cheers!
Wait, I've brought some more rice wine!
Did you walk the storeowner home?
Yes, and Hyeju even bought us
two more kettles.
Did you ever take a bullet
for Senior Superintendent Choi, sir?
That's what I'm wondering.
You've always been on Dongdaemun's case.
How are you still employed?
What's your secret, sir?
Senior Superintendent Choi…
has a secret only I know.
What is it?
Have you boys heard of Sinkwang Society?
Sinkwang? Is that
a book club or something?
Remember the pro-Japanese orphanage
that Audrey Ko used to run
was also once Sinkwang Academy.
Well, this society
is also a pro-Japanese group.
The members all help each other
get into high positions.
Senior Superintendent Choi
happens to be one of them.
Did you find this out
when you were special police?
That man can't ever touch me.
The moment he does,
I'm going to spill everything I know.
Unit 2 might have
Senior Superintendent Choi,
but we have Chief Yu on our side!
Chief Yu is on our side!
We'll entrust you, Chief Yu!
- Cheers to that!
- Cheers!
Jongnam Bookstore
Jeez.
Are you down for round two, sir?
I've seen enough of your faces.
I'm heading home first.
- See you all.
- Take care, sir.
Goodbye, sir.
I was hoping he'd buy the second round.
Let's go to the rice wine shop
so I can see Soonnam. Woof, woof!
Soonnam is so adorable.
What's this?
Is this the day I die?
I'll give you a choice.
Either die or work for me
and chase fortune and glory.
Those are some extreme choices.
It's all or nothing for us.
Then I choose death.
And you won't regret it?
I could ask you the same question,
Chairman Lee.
The thing about punches is
that the stronger you let fly,
the more likely you'll hit yourself
with an errant fist.
You'll soon pay with your life
for refusing this opportunity.
We'll see.
Ooh.
- Those punks.
- Jeez.
Goodness, I was so scared.
If you die,
who would we get rice wine with?
Will you guys protect me then?
- Of course.
- Yes.
Let's go.
I wish I could end those Dongdaemun punks.
Damn those guys.
Yeonghan.
Women always love big and fancy gestures.
That's ridiculous.
You don't know a thing about women.
I know more than you.
What kind of
big and fancy gestures, exactly?
Propose to her
with a huge bouquet this big
or a shiny ring,
and she'll go crazy with joy.
Then ask her to marry you
in a romantic way.
Well…
give me an example.
"I'd like to swim in your eyes
for the rest of my life."
Her eyeballs are going to fall out
if he does that, man!
I swear it works.
- Really?
- Yes.
I wonder why you're still single.
- What?
- Huh.
I wonder so too.
What's going on with Hojeong?
Did you eat chili? Yes, you did.
You're making me lose my appetite.
Yeonghan, remember to use
the line I taught you.
Okay.
"I'd like to swim in your eyes
- for the rest of my life."
- Mm.
"Hyeju.
I'd like to swim in your eyes
for the rest of my life."
Here I go.
Welcome.
Detective Park!
I guess you're not too busy today.
I was wondering
if I should wait at the rice wine shop.
Your…
- eyes…
- My eyes?
Your eyes…
Is there something I need to see?
There's nothing worth seeing outside.
By the way, why are your clothes so light?
It's freezing out there.
It looks good on you.
It's warm, isn't it?
Wear this from now on, okay?
I like you.
That was out of the blue.
I always want to be with you.
I'm sorry for making you wait
all the time.
Making a woman wait is a crime…
but I can let you off the hook
since you're a detective.
This might sound like an excuse…
and it may sound too selfish of me…
but in the days to come,
I'll have to make you wait for me
all too many times.
I may find myself in danger.
And I may never return,
without even getting to say goodbye.
But if you'll
forgive me then…
And if you could trust me…
let's get married.
Just promise me one thing.
You can be late,
but make sure you come back to me.
Okay, I promise.
Yeonghan!
I'll be good to her!
Could the father
of the groom smile a bit more?
One, two, three!
Two, three, smile!
On April 19 in the year 1960,
incessant protests broke out
denouncing rigged elections
and the autocratic government's crimes
against its own people for 12 years.
The police opened fire on the protesters,
leading to countless casualties
and flooding the streets of Seoul
with the blood of martyrs.
Second Half of 1960
Open Recruitment for Policewomen
- She's 5 ft 5 in.
- 5 ft 5 in.
Next.
Ready.
I won't let you down. I'll do my best!
You got this.
I'll give the job my best!
What?
Grab him!
Who are you punks?
You little…
Who are you?
Who are you punks?
Hey!
Chief Detective 1958
Look how much the world has changed,
but it's like we're stuck.
Nothing has changed.
We're always the same!
And we'll do this until we retire.
Congratulations on your promotion.
Hey, where's Chief Yu?
Yeonghan, Chief Yu…
What kind of scum would do this?
This has to be
the Dongdaemun gang's doing.
You're barking up the wrong tree!
We finally have
a new senior superintendent at Jongnam!
He is a former military officer,
in keeping up with the times.
The times may change easily,
but people don't, sir.
Translated by Jihun Lee