Production investment: Jin Yuzhe
Investment Coordinator: Jin Zaimin Producer: Li Junze Zhang Zhen sheng
"Happy Country" South Korea
The film is based on the 1979 assassination of the president.
All characters and events in the film are fictional and may differ from reality.
Safe House in Gung jeong-dong, Jongno-gu, Seoul
Kill the guy today.
Did he kill the president too?
Act when you are ready
There are too many guards. Maybe next time?
No.
Just do your own thing.
This is for liberal democracy
Nothing will happen.
The assassination of the president occurred on October 26, 1979
Honey
Beautiful Mom
I'm not going in.
What happened?
I'm going back now
Take good care
Children
I'm leaving
Good Dad
The assassination attempt on the president took place on October 26, 1979
The Central Intelligence Minister and seven others were arrested. Petitions calling for their release continue to appear.
Therefore, a legal team was organized around the opposition party.
In this case, the Minister of Central Intelligence has great power.
Based on huge organizational strength
If we have control over the martial law troops, we can handle it.
So I conceived this plan
Related to the military and other forces
External forces involved
Killed the President
It's a very speechless action.
It's a murder case of treason.
Office of the Presidential Assassination Counsel
He's a very active guy.
The case was handled within six hours.
It's not daybreak yet
The Minister of Central Intelligence was arrested as a murderer.
Stronger intelligence capabilities
Less than two hours later, we knew the president was dead.
That's true.
Yeah, I'm back.
How’s it going?
Deliberately hiding from me
Don't answer the phone at all
Didn't you see it?
Yes
Less than ten days until the trial
How come they don't even have a team of lawyers?
The bigger problem is Park Dae-ryung
Because he's a soldier
No one wants to defend him.
It was a military court ruling.
It is the final word
This way we can only surrender
Do you guys want to keep watching the fun?
Are you here for a spring outing?
Get out, get out
Whether it's threats or lies
Get a lawyer.
Really
Why don't you go out?
Change your position.
What
Seats?
Yes
Hurry up
Straighten your legs
Not straight forward
Straighten it like this
Have you memorized all the lines?
Yes
Say it again
OK
The bracket fell off.
Collapse on top of head
tube
Fall down this way
I thought I was going to die.
We tried our best to stop
I was dizzy from being hit
This can't happen, then...
Thinking of my wife who ran away from home, I can't stop crying
That's pretty cool.
...
Hand Position
Very impressive
Can be an actor
A few pipes fell off
There should be five or six.
Well
More than that
Eight
nine
Hello, really
Not those
A few pipes fell off
Twenty, twenty
Twenty, yes.
This guy is not a lawyer, he is clearly a gangster
No one anyway
How is the strength
Very impressive
Very good at defense and principled
No one is better suited for dog-eat-dog battles than him.
Do lawyers really have to go to this extent?
All are colleagues
I also need to make a fake plaster
Sr.
You listen to me.
The courts are not for distinguishing right from wrong.
It distinguishes between winning and losing
Got it?
All rise!
Let you come over for dinner
Why don't you come?
What's this?
I want to be your headhunter
Presidential Office Case?
The whole country is in chaos
Just put on your shroud and worship it.
This is a trial you will hardly encounter again in your lifetime.
It will be published in the newspaper every day
Try to get a reduced sentence.
There will be endless cases in the future.
That's your idea
How much will you give?
Do you want me to work for nothing?
Aren't you a human rights lawyer?
Why don't you talk about human rights?
Bring cash
Three hundred thousand per person
Then I'll take it
I visited the prison yesterday.
You don't know your father's condition yet.
It's really bad.
Shut up
Otherwise, sew your mouth shut.
Take it out immediately
If we let it go, something terrible will happen.
If you take this case
We will also be more attentive
If you leave your uncle alone, something bad will happen to your father.
How come you are here?
I heard you were sick.
It won't be so hard to stamp a seal
Hide the students who were being hunted
Then go to the parade
Will there be any changes?
Speak
They are all very cute
I can't live for myself.
Let them become criminals
Yeah
You are right, you have a clear conscience
Just live like this
Small buttocks paint
Scare me
How come you came back so late and didn't hear me calling you?
Don't do this
Shenzhen
I want to take a case. What do you think?
South Korea's biggest political scandal
Presidential Office Case?
Wait a moment
What's going on?
You're not that type.
I think this is a God-given opportunity.
Will offer good conditions
Oh my god
If I can plead not guilty
You can become the protagonist in an instant
To be successful?
How can you say that?
Okay, that's true.
Worrying for nothing
That's all I have to say.
The atmosphere is so good at night
How about it
Tonight, in the dead of night
She is the daughter of the boarding house.
You guy
What's wrong?
Handprint here
Take off your shirt
I am lawyer Jung In-ho
我是朴泰柱
November 14th Your Wife Ok Jung-ae
Hire me as your lawyer
I'm just saying the main point
Among the eight people involved in this case
Only if you are an active military member
That is to say
You will be the only one to go to court-martial.
You know a military tribunal is the final word, right?
The judge picked up the gavel
One blow of the hammer will determine your sentence
But it's different if it's a normal trial.
There will be three trials.
Second and third instance
Can delay time
Slowly create public opinion
Avoiding a military court
As long as you create public opinion, you will have a chance of winning
Mr. Lawyer
I see you have something to say. Please speak up.
Soldiers have rules to follow
I am a soldier
Soldiers should abide by military law
So what do you want to say?
I have no intention of avoiding the military.
Colonel Park
Here are the rules
There are no rules in court.
The winner is the strong one
I guess I'll have to reconsider hiring a lawyer.
Military police
I said the court is not the place to distinguish between good and bad people
Only wins and losses
I go
The crime of civil sedition is an act that undermines the democratic order.
Minister Kim Young, who led these three cases
Claims that the president was not assassinated
But to take up the gun for national restoration
The focus of the debate
Doesn't it depend on the crime of civil sedition?
Shooting the president in an attempt to launch a military coup?
Still wearing the mask of a dictator and longing for democratization
Will the court recognize Park Jong as a dictator?
I can only try it.
All right
Hello, Lawyer Zheng
I heard you went to meet Colonel Park
Any questions?
I haven't received a lawyer's notice yet.
Why
He said he would not accept trial unless it was done by military court.
He insisted on a military trial against him
It is said that Colonel Park is a very capable soldier.
Everyone is regretting the loss of a pitiful person
It seems that he is not a flashy political soldier.
He is not only honest
It is still the fastest in the same period.
Everyone says he has the ability to be promoted to Chief of General Staff
No, that's why
Do you want me to ask him to hire me as his lawyer?
What I mean is
It's hard for a man like him to escape military law.
It's really depressing.
What did you say?
To put it bluntly, isn't he digging his own grave?
How dare you shoot the president?
You really are
Okay, okay.
I think everyone's opinions are fully expressed.
The court meeting is scheduled for three o'clock.
We should go
It's too late if you don't leave now.
Yongsan Army Headquarters - Office of the Chief of Staff
No public hearings
Otherwise, it's not just reporters.
Even ordinary people will squeeze in.
I said that now that things have come to this, how can we not proceed in public?
Neither the ruling party nor the opposition party will sit idly by.
I'm afraid I'll have other intentions
We must nip the problem in the bud
You
They were from the government.
In case, your private life is leaked
Isn't the result obvious?
Stop talking
Sr.
Yes.
They've all arrived
Not available in private
The Prime Minister is determined to do this.
There's been a lot of gossip in the military lately.
Are you being led by the nose?
You were not like this when your Excellency was still alive.
Hey, Major General Quan
You don't think the power comes from the General Administration?
The Chief of Staff has arrived.
Loyalty
Okay, everyone, please take a seat.
All we can do is keep the secrets with guns.
I am very awkward with politics and other areas.
There's nothing wrong with the front line.
We are doing our best
Oh, I forgot to introduce you.
This is the security commander, Major General Jeon Sang-doo.
The bad things that happened recently are all due to his careless management.
I am Jeon Sang-doo, who is in charge of the Joint Investigation Headquarters.
The court and military prosecutors present
Not only must we protect the personal safety of the defense lawyer,
We will ensure that nothing goes wrong during the trial.
Okay, okay.
Major General Quan, please be brief.
Sr.
Speak
The defendants are all unconvicted prisoners.
Please treat him as a political prisoner.
Have you heard any other bad comments?
I'm just saying this just in case.
I will keep it in mind
Take good measures
Thick is which thickness?
The Thickness of Virtue
Jung In-hoo
This is the name my father gave me.
He must be regretting it now.
You are in charge of Colonel Park's case, right?
-loyalty
I am Private First Class Kim Shin-woo
Yes, I understand
Loyalty
What's so funny?
I don't understand why people do this.
I mean report your rank and name.
You mean it's wrong to report the official rank and name?
There's no need to speak so loudly.
It's all a manifestation of authoritarianism
Your idea is interesting
Let's take a walk
- Can you save Colonel Park?
- Are you kidding me?
Do you think so?
At least ten to fifteen
years, no less.
After all, he assassinated the president and plunged the country into panic
It should be considered a rebellion.
He was acting under instructions.
And he's not the main culprit.
I don't understand the law
But I heard that the principal and the accessory to the crime of civil sedition are of the same nature.
No
The same thing happened in the 515 incident of assassinating the Japanese cabinet.
The principal offender was sentenced to death but his subordinates were acquitted
Really?
What do you think of soldiers?
Oh, I forgot you don't like to be told your rank and name.
Well, let me ask you this.
What do you think of the soldiers?
Defending the country
Besides that, what are your thoughts?
Real thoughts
I don't understand what you mean
It seems you are more timid than I thought.
Staying in power for too long
And what else?
I also think that the military is beyond the necessary role
Arresting innocent people and framing them as communists
I don't think this is patriotic.
You should pay attention to it.
Since you told me your thoughts on soldiers
Then I will tell you what I think about lawyers.
You are garbage.
A piece of trash who only knows how to talk about the law and collect commission fees
- You said too much.
- What's wrong?
Why am I wrong?
Soldiers are different from you.
The soldiers don't even have a quarter of what you earn.
I will defend my country to the death.
You think it's funny to give out your rank and name?
You think it's funny to be polite to your superior who works hard for you, right?
I heard your father is a priest in the church.
I don't even know my body is rotting.
And help those who clamor for democracy
A bunch of idiots
Ten years at most
Just wait and see
You can't even wear the nameplate properly
How to save Colonel Park is very interesting.
Wait and see
Major General Jeon Sang-doo, who directed the assassination, was able to take power
The head of the joint investigation headquarters has more power than the commander
Japanese public opinion
Major General Jeon Sang-doo, who directed the assassination, was able to take power
The head of the joint investigation headquarters has more power than the commander
Jeon Sang-doo and the hardliners in the military, who control the combat forces
Expected to be at the forefront of power
Just follow military law
But I can't give up the third trial
Why did you kill him?
I have to know the cause and effect before I can help you
Head of the Intelligence Service of the Republic of Korea
Leading his men to assassinate the president in the center of Seoul
The investigation record says you were following orders, right?
Military prosecutors would laugh.
To defend
Patriotism or political and social awareness should be shown.
Yes.
In my eyes, this is just a meaningless struggle for interests.
That's good
Do you want to follow military law?
Didn't you say we should follow the principles?
How much do you know about the military?
I dislike
You can't like
But
To be responsible for defense
You are a complicated person.
All rise.
Army Headquarters Court-Martial
Public trial preparations completed
Take a seat
First public hearing of the first trial
The general meeting of the Army Headquarters on martial law will now begin
Public trial of Kim Young-il and seven others begins
Prosecutor please read the indictment
Defendant Kim Young-il
As the Minister of Central Intelligence, he repeatedly failed to stabilize the political situation.
Dismissed for incompetence
Plan to kill the president and seize power
After personally killing the president and the chief of security
Instructing the confidant defendant
That is, Park Tae-joo and others handled
After killing the president, he plotted to overthrow the country
Kim Young-il, the defendant, please, come forward
Defense attorney, please make your opening statement.
First
Thanks to the Ministry of Justice for making the trial public
Early morning of October 11
Kim Young-il, the head of the Central Intelligence Agency, accompanied his secretary Park Tae-joo
Taking a helicopter to look around the situation in Kamama
Witness the resistance to the Restoration dictatorship
General Kim Young-il is struggle spreads to a democratic environment
In a state of urgency to prevent further bloodshed
I have objections
Please don't use the title of General.
He is a criminal who has been prosecuted for breaking the law.
Prosecutor
You are now following the principle of presumption of guilt
presiding judge
Inappropriate names idolize the defendant
Could be used maliciously
Please make this statement
Expungement from the testimony record
Respect the defendant's position and human rights until proven guilty
Presiding judge
Defender
The title of General is not a good one.
Assassinated the President
The defendant also admitted the fact
Please don't use the title of General Minister.
Called the defendant
Fifteen-minute recess
Continue the court session
Among the defendants implicated in this case
Only Park Tae-joo was accused
The sentencing was determined at the first instance
Just because he's a soldier
The heavy sentence was determined in the first trial instead of the third trial.
Is it appropriate?
I want to find out more about this
Military law applies to soldiers
Are you saying this is wrong?
The Constitution states
In an emergency such as a war, the first instance decision
It only says this exception
This is a petition for unconstitutionality of the first instance system
Presiding judge
The defense is using unorthodox methods to delay the trial.
I am requesting that this also apply to defendant Park.
The three-tier review system for citizens’ basic rights
Citizens want a speedy trial
It cannot be used to check whether it is unconstitutional
Waste of time
Citizens don't want a speedy trial
A fair trial
Defender
Don't force it.
The one-trial system under emergency martial law cannot be considered unconstitutional
It cannot be an obstacle to the trial.
Is it unconstitutional?
It is determined by the committee and is not under the jurisdiction of the Trial Department.
And
The three-trial system is a basic right of citizens
For defendant Park, it was a matter of life and death.
The court that avoids the most basic right of defense
Is there a will for a fair trial?
I doubt it.
Hey!
Trial is the definition of procedure
Democratic Society
Reasons for not accepting people's trial
Because the procedure is not correct.
That trial cannot be considered legitimate.
Therefore
The defense attorney
To all judges
Request for refutation
Please be quiet.
Defender.
Do you mean to replace all the judges?
That's right.
We cannot accept a trial that violates the Constitution.
Before that
Why did the Trial Department respond so quickly and decisively?
Please explain first
The defense is now threatening the court
I am warning you
If you continue to say something that disregards the judgment department
I will never ignore it.
Temporary adjournment.
So sweet!
Good.
You won't treat us casually anymore, right?
Of course
The small note was delivered in real time.
Maybe near the court?
After all, the variable is still the army.
The younger generation is right
Although Park Chung-hee fell, the army is still there
If the court finds, you are resisting dictatorship
Who will be hit?
Everyone should be aware
We are following the Korean ship now.
It's really rigid
What kind of position is it other than the Secretary of the Central Intelligence Department?
Right below Minister Kim.
But
Living in a 16-ping-sized board house
The total assets are only 4 million won
Are you asking me to believe this?
Hide quickly, I want to see you
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Ten
Kid?
Elder sister
Why are you here again?
Didn't I translate it myself?
Please save his life.
I am sorry
I only know this method.
He won't beg for mercy or plead.
And very strict with himself
Will not betray others or break their trust
Please
I know the Colonel.
As long as I'm clean
As long as I am open and honest, it's fine
No matter what the family is like
I said something I shouldn't have said
Go ahead
Pull the trigger
Keep shooting until you run out of bullets.
Because in preparation
No difficulty
Here
In preparation
It means you already knew it
Although I didn't say I would kill you.
But anyone will understand
Just say you don't know
Because it's not stated
Let you shoot the president
Just say it's an emergency.
Are you asking me to lie?
In court
I've said this several times before. This is not the place to tell the real from the fake.
People all lie in life.
I lie as if it's my daily routine
We have to speak with one voice to put on a show.
It's so depressing.
Okay, you have to convince me first that you know you have to kill the president.
Then assisted
Not assisting
- I'm following orders.
- Come on, come on, come on
I'm so depressed.
Anyway, you soldiers are really...
It's such an obvious character.
How much younger are you?
I'll punch you.
Just kidding
Good
Not assistance but command
The so-called command
What is?
Disobedience means death
Soldiers must obey orders in all circumstances
What if the order is unreasonable?
Commands cannot distinguish right from wrong
Why?
Because soldiers are on war missions
If you judge the order based on your personal thoughts
The chain of command will collapse
Will eventually be defeated
Yes
You cannot judge orders based on your personal thoughts.
Because orders should be rational and legal
Especially the intelligence department where the defendant worked
It is a special organization that deals with state secrets.
Highly demanding and obedient
The superior orders the subordinate to obey
Army officer Park Tae-joo followed his superior's orders according to military discipline
The defendant's actions did not violate any law
No furthermore.
The prosecutor asks you to interrogate.
How is this situation?
There
If your superior orders you to shoot that comrade
This question has nothing to do with this case.
Let's listen.
Sir Judge?
I will obey
As long as the order is given
I'll shoot anyone who does order it.
Silence, silence, silence
Did the defendant think it was justified to shoot an innocent comrade?
I'm not saying this is justified.
For soldiers, the standard for distinguishing things is orders.
As long as the order is given
I will obey
Defendant
Who has the power to command the army?
Who has the highest command authority for the Republic of Korea's military?
Is the President
When defendant Jin gave instructions
Don't you know it's an assassination of the president?
Did You Know?
I knew.
No furthermore;
What does it mean? Not be able to go down?
What happened to you?
Just run away like a coward.
Look up!
Is there anyone here who hasn't received a threatening phone call?
Whenever the phone rings, my wife's heart beats faster
Let's go after eating.
Damn....Anyway
Life is a matter of doing things one way or another
Just go when you have to.
Go home and sleep when you have time
Damn why can't you be honest?
Everyone knows we are just a name
Does anyone here think they can win?
Is there?
Are you done yet, damn it?
Damn it, go away
Hey you guy
Do you think I don't know you came in here to be famous?
You shit...
Did you drink carbon monoxide?
Come on
You have to be beaten
Let go
Damn
Damn the dog
Yesterday was my daughter's birthday
This is what my wife gave me.
I can't say it, so I open it and see
She hasn't been to school for a week.
She said she wanted to see her friends and cried at home every day.
She is only in the first grade of elementary school
These dogs are really
Jung In-hoo Sr...
Don't say anything
It solved today
Including you?
When you hear gunshots, start moving.
This is for liberal democracy
Did you already know this?
No, I didn't know
It's death anyway
I will follow the minister.
Retreat.
What?
Canceled the battle
It’s over.
Block it
What happened?
Minister?
His Excellency has passed away
What?
Who did it?
Secretary Park
Where to go?
Intelligence Department?
Army Headquarters?
Namsan Art Cave
The Minister behind asked the Intelligence Department Army Headquarters
I said the Army Headquarters is suitable.
After the Minister agrees
We drove to Yongsan where the Army Headquarters was.
Do you remember this sentence?
During the joint investigation
Why did you transfer to the Army Headquarters?
After the President's Death
Looking for dozens of officers
Compared to going to the Intelligence Department
I think it's better to go to the Army Headquarters.
Minister Kim has a huge intelligence organization
If you want to overthrow the country
He will definitely go to Nanshan
But I went to the Army Headquarters.
In the tiger's den guarded by more than a hundred generals
Only three people
This can't be civil unrest.
At the decisive moment the colonel turned the car around
Minister, let me see the intelligence.
I turned to the Army Headquarters to prevent civil unrest.
That's it!
There is a way to survive.
All I need is to prove that it was the colonel who said he wanted to leave.
Are you betraying the minister in order to keep me alive?
The Colonel was the one who pushed the priest away.
Who is this because of?
I just followed my boss's orders.
No chaos appeared one after another
I thought maybe I could prevent more sacrifices
It's what I chose
Should I tell the truth?
Minister Jin is going to die anyway.
Hey!
I understand.
I'll see to it.
That's it.
I'm giving up
Damn Minister.
I told you now is not the time to worry about others
Not because of the minister.
I see my sinful colleagues every night.
The screams in my head
I will take responsibility for my sins
Don't say such irresponsible words
If a person ends
Do you think you can just be happy?
Three people were killed by the colonel's gun.
You don't have that qualification.
If you want to atone your sins
Standing on the judgment floor
The due blame
You should be judged.
That's the rule.
I'm going to pee
Where is this
Hey!
I am a lawyer
Something seems to be wrong
Write a letter of guarantee.
Write as I said
If you give me your fingerprints,
I'll let you out.
What's wrong with you?
Who are you?
Who ordered you guys?
Who is it?
Call your boss over.
If it weren't for your dad,
You would be useless.
Severe abdominal damage due to intestinal obstruction
Cancer cells have spread to the liver
There is really no time for treatment.
Uncle
Put your hand out
I used to think that defending soldiers was particularly incompatible with my brother.
But I knew it just by looking at the kids.
Almost like my brother
I was sad when I thought of my dad.
I was thinking while being beaten
Was my father also beaten like me?
He was caught and beaten like a dog.
Why are you laughing like that?
If you laugh like that
Do you think others will feel sorry?
I'll sleep for a while
Set off
Witness?
What is the destination of the vehicle?
No specific direction.
Of course I thought it was the Intelligence Department, so I drove to Nanshan.
The car turned towards Longshan
What is that reason?
Yes, it is the minister's instruction.
Can you elaborate on this?
The President has passed away.
What?
Who did it?
Secretary Park...
Where to go?
Intelligence Department Army Headquarters?
How did defendant Park react?
The secretary looked very flustered.
I was troubled for a while
Let's go to the Army Headquarters.
It should be better there.
Yes.
At that time, I received the order to turn the car around.
Turned to the direction of the Army Headquarters
Article 87 of the Criminal Law
The crime of civil sedition is
to investigate the law for the purpose of resisting the chaos
a crime committed by a majority of people through rioting
What does this sentence mean?
It means that only six people cannot overthrow the country.
If civil unrest is really the goal
Of course, it is natural to go to the central government, which has its own support.
Of course
But
Park Tae-joo defendant did not choose the Intelligence Department
Instead, he chose the Army Headquarters.
Kim Young-il follows Park Tae-joo's lead
Turning to Army Headquarters
So this incident
But Kim Young-il, who was originally the head of the Central Intelligence Agency
The personal escapade that killed the president
It has absolutely nothing to do with the civil unrest.
It's just a murder case.
Really?
Is this to bring down Minister Kim and save Park Tae-joo?
Have you discussed it together?
Prosecutors’ request cross-examination
Was there any vehicle operation the day before the witness incident?
Yes, every day.
With the defendants?
The two have been together
Strange Places
Didn't you find it?
They were talking to each other in weird ways.
You mean the day before the incident?
Just as you can remember
Please be more detailed.
That was the day before
I don't remember
Yeah
Focus on driving
Difficulty remembering exactly what was said
Look at the content of your statement on the day of the incident
At a speed of 80 kilometers per hour
Even remember every word of the conversation while driving
But the conversation the day before
But you can't remember
Lee Tae-moon
Perjury
It will be a great sin
The presiding prosecutor is now threatening the witness.
Ok very good
Even if the witness is right
So
What kind of person is the defendant Jin?
The man who advocated taking up arms for democratic revolution
No plans or goals
A word from an impulsive subordinate
At most, he is just a foolish person who looks around.
How else can I describe him?
This is the head of the Intelligence Department of the Republic of Korea.
And
When defendant Jin gave the order to kill
Park Tae-joo was accused of: Why didn't you assert your own opinion?
If I hadn't thought about killing someone,
You should be like in the car
Just express your opinions confidently
Presiding judge...
If you want your testimony to be valuable
First of all, the witness must be a person who thinks without prejudice.
Witness Lee Tae-moon and the defendants are like a family
There is a high possibility of giving biased testimony
The evidence is also
Very insufficient.
I apply to have his testimony expunged from the record.
The defendants advocated a democratic revolution
Just an excuse
Ultimately they want state power.
They committed
The anti-state crime of brutally killing the president and his bodyguard
-That is to say,
-Lawyer Zheng
What's this?
- What are you doing?
- What is this trial all about?
The small note was passed several times during the trial.
Please go back to your seat.
If that's the case, why is there a court hearing?
-Drag him out.
-What are you doing?
Damn, a bunch of guys who eat the government's food
Put the camera down
How dare you drag the lawyer out?
Please have a fair trial
Are you listening?
How long are you going to hide like rats?
These bastards
I asked you guys if you heard the asshole
Is this democracy?
Everyone, be quiet. Everyone, be quiet.
Silence.
The next hearing will be at 10 am on the 3rd.
Hearing in the same court
And the testimony of witness Lee Tae-moon
Will not be adopted.
Is it cool?
Don't you know their purpose?
They can judge it however they want.
How could you fall into their trap?
I am sorry.
Is the court a place for you to play heroism?
Why cause this commotion?
You have to know when to stop.
Get out.
What is chaos?
Are you pretending not to know?
If Colonel Park meant to go to Army Headquarters,
What kind of situation will Minister Jin be in?
What's your attitude?
Are you acting like this because I brought shame upon Minister Kim?
What?
Do I have to cut off the tail to keep the body?
Who cuts whose tail?
Don't I have eyes?
Don't you just want your men
to be your helpers?
And then turn Minister Kim into a democracy fighter?
Democracy?
Okay, that's OK
Dictatorship is the essence but the manifestation is social revolution
Okay, but
Shouldn't we rescue those who should survive first?
Who is this because of?
All his men rushed into the fire with oil drums.
You actually did this
What is a mere democracy fighter?
Why is everyone so damned?
What are you doing in
front of your seniors?
Besides
If this continues,
Colonel Park will die.
The trial was screwed.
You say something that makes me breathless.
It's not torture.
You're
really chilling
Sometimes I feel colder than you
Really?
Let's chat today
Chatting about the kind of things that can help us understand each other.
My father was a pastor.
Help students who escape,
give the women workers transportation fare
His wife and children are starving to death.
But he always thinking about others
I studied very hard
This disgusting poverty
I will return all of them when I become a prosecutor.
I was eliminated during recruitment
Is it because of your father?
Do you think that children are the only ones who are worrying?
Parents are also worrying
Although I am not qualified to give you advice
But don't hate your father too much
Some people are not able to live differently from others.
Just open one eye and close one eye
But he just couldn't do it
Eat it
Vice-Captain
I met the Minister for the first time.
It was a tough time.
But he takes good care of me.
That night
I wanted to ask him several times.
Is it necessary to do this?
But I couldn't ask
It's the orange Huishan gave me.
My children
They think I'm doing okay?
I want to see them in my dreams.
But they rarely show up
No time
Find someone who can prove that Colonel Park is right
Make sure to put that person on the witness stand.
The four people who were in the car that went to the Army Headquarters that day
Driver Li Taiwen is no longer useful in court
Minister Kim and Colonel Park
Because we are both defendants, so no.
Only one person left
Do you want Chief Zheng to take the witness stand?
Is there anything wrong with that?
That's easy to say.
He's the martial law commander.
What's the problem with him being in the witness chair?
Is there any other way?
It's useless for someone who has no lethality to serve as a witness.
A bomb is needed
As long as Chief Zheng can stand there
Public opinion will also cause a sensation
The judge couldn't do anything to him.
I understand your desire to not miss any opportunity.
What?
What's your plan?
Just first...
just do it with gritted teeth
Minister Kim said
Colonel Park may not have the luck of a superior, but he has the luck of a lawyer.
You're right, fuck democracy.
Let's rescue the people first.
Sr.
You can't act on impulse on this matter.
This is a procedure.
Let's go head-on three or four times
At most, it's just a drizzle that wets my clothes.
Try your best to see
Sr. Sr...
Hey, first...
Official documents
Hey, Lawyer Jin
Intermediary Application
We need your testimony.
Do you remember the day of the incident?
Colonel Park said in the car that he was going to the Army Headquarters.
You know this isn't okay, right?
This is the only testimony you can give.
Please take the witness stand.
I am the martial law commander.
The Commandant appeared in the martial law trial
Is this reasonable?
Because you were there
So you have an obligation to testify.
I'm talking about you
Do you think I can testify for just one side?
Go back.
Contact the Deputy Headmaster
What is the real reason for not being able to do this?
Hey?
What are you afraid of?
Why are you all whining like a dog holding its pee?
Why are you still standing there, you disrespectful boy?
Chief, please
Please go out.
The chief's testimony is the only
Am I going to drag you out by force?
If you are confident...
Sir?
Let me go, sir?
Wait a moment.
Damn!
If it were me, I would do the same as Colonel Park.
If you are a soldier
There is no choice.
Is there no room for persuasion?
Be careful on the road.
Damn, it's cold.
Loyalty.
Hey wake him up.
Loyalty
Sr... Sr...
for a fair trial, please be a witness.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
It's me, sir. Please help me once.
For the sake of a fair trial, please just say one word.
- Go
- Sir? Sir? Sir?
Chief...you bastard!
Lawyer Zheng
Let’s go eat
Another lawyer left.
I don't know how many people will remain here after the trial.
These guys are really...
What should Chief Zheng do?
The day after tomorrow is the last day to apply
I know you've been tired recently.
But no, it's not possible.
Where is Colonel Park?
Do you have any solution?
Do you have any way to convince Chief Zheng?
We have tried our best
There's less than a week left until trial.
Let's focus on the trial
Cheer up.
That's it
Running at full speed
One, two. One, two.
Run!
Where to run to.
Let's go.
What's going on?
Stop.
You can't go in anymore.
Catch him, catch him.
Get out of the way! Get out of the way!
You stop.
Really.
Get out of the way
Get out of the way.
Don't move.
What's wrong with you?
Catch him, catch him.
Catch him now.
If the trial is carried out
must be conducted in private.
Isn't this already discussed?
This time it doesn't feel good.
Get control before you waver.
I'll do my best if you let me do it.
Major General Quan
I heard recently that the Joint Investigation Department has exceeded its authority.
Is it your decision whether the government controls the audit of politicians?
These are all unfounded words.
It's a rumor.
So...
The Deputy Ministers' Meeting is also...
Is that also a rumor?
I'm going to say something to you.
It has been 18 years since we risked our lives to complete the revolution
You know this regime.
How did we get it?
Your legacy was thrown away like a rotten shoe.
We are always left behind.
Are we going to be led by the nose like this forever?
Who is being led by the nose?
Hey, Major General Quan
If you want to get involved in politics
If you want to do it, take off your uniform and do it.
You go out.
Hey?
Haven't you ever learned to salute?
There will be absolutely nothing for you to worry about.
That's right.
Deputy District Chief Zheng said he has something to report to you.
Can he visit?
Today?
I heard it was a joint response.
It won't take up too much of your time.
I have to go to my parents-in-law's house to celebrate my birthday tonight.
That's it.
Then I'll ask him to come over at 19 o'clock.
Birthday?
Get rid of Chief Zheng.
Adjutant
Check the family, wife and property of that guy.
All of it.
We will report back to you after investigation.
I'll let you answer the phone.
A call from the Director's Office.
What happened to your arm?
Nothing.
Simple boy!
Apply for a witness.
Can you keep my list confidential before I submit it?
Do you agree?
But
Need to use recording.
Can't...
If you don't agree, it's over.
must attend the trail.
I lost, I lost, I lost...
But
The list must not be leaked before it is submitted and must be kept confidential.
Although it's a bit rude, can I hug you?
You are.....oh
Court opens at 8:30
You must protect the general manager by half past eight.
Definitely.
I am the chief judge.
Be careful when you go back.
Are you really okay?
Why?
Are we going to pretend we didn't see the corruption case of Executive Director Jeon?
If you want to strangle him, someone needs to grab his tail.
The lawyer is a good fit.
The scene looks good too.
We might get burned.
If you want to catch Nichu, you have to be prepared to miss it.
It shouldn't be that easy
to convince him.
I said I can do it, okay?
If I take this seriously, I'm screwed.
Really?
Hey!
It is now 18:30 on December 12
They have 62 people
Arresting the Chief
Departure completed
Say it again
Current time: 18:30 on December 12
They have 62 people
Arresting the Chief
Departure completed
Expected to arrive at General Residence in Hannam-dong at 18:00
It is five kilometers away from the destination
The leading convoy will arrive in eight minutes.
Say it again
It is five kilometers away from the destination
The leading convoy will arrive in eight minutes.
Hannam-dong Army Chief of Staff Residence
Loyalty!
Deputy Director...
I have something to report to the chief.
Loyalty!
Pass.
Be prepared.
Come in.
You...
Guard? Guard?
Deal with them all.
Sorry to bother you so late.
Sit down.
We came here because we need the chief's confession.
Confession?
Between the Director General and Minister Kim
Testimony states that money was traded.
What?
Please also help
The order was given to the chief to assist
Instructions for making a statement,
Please.
Who gave this order?
Subordinates are terrified.
You know you're going to take me
It requires an order from the President.
Did the president give the order?
Yes.
Adjutant Luo
Come in.
Contact Cheong Wa Dae
Check if there is this command
Put down the phone.
Put it down, you little bastard.
What?
Put it down now...
What are you doing?
Sir.
Just go and take the survey together.
You have to think about it
Don't go wrong
Put it down quickly
I'll let you put your hands down, you little bastard.
Put it down for me
Hand, Hand, Hand
Bring it to the front
Raise your hands above your shoulders
Take the Sir
hurry up
Block
Come over here
Come here, boy.
Walk
Set off
Accelerate
Lawyer Zheng Renhou is here
Contact the Joint Investigation Headquarters
What is going on?
As long as Chief Zheng is here, everything will be settled.
Loyalty!
On December 12, 1979, the New Army Mutiny
Everyone raise your glasses
Cheers to the general's long life
Cheers
- Congratulations.
- Thank you for your hard work.
Thanks for your hard work
Last night, Chief of Staff Zheng Zhenyu
Indicted for aiding the rebellion
On October 26, the President was assassinated.
Even though we knew that the head of the Central Intelligence Agency was a criminal
What's going on?
From now on
The trial will be closed to the public
And said it's all over
Said no one would show up
Why?
There's just some damn stuff.
Damn!
Why can't I get this damn plaster off?
Oh shit!
- Can't enter.
- Damn it.
I came here to say something.
Said no.
Come back after you get permission.
Why not?
Is this Japanese territory?
Civilians are not allowed to enter here.
You can't go in.
Let go, Let go.
Hey, let him in.
Why?
Do I have to take off my underwear for you to see?
Let him in right away.
Please spare my life
I won't be an eyesore to you anymore.
Are you trying to trick me into letting him go?
Um?
You should save people in court.
Colonel Park
He is a soldier who has dedicated his life to his country.
It is not a crime to obey orders
Please give him a way out.
This No. 3 club is just not very useful.
The golf ball can't run back by itself.
Can you help me pick up the ball?
I think
obeying orders is not punishable by death.
You think the crime is not punishable by death?
Yes
Do your thoughts matter?
Thoughts of a mere lawyer.
It would have been nice if you had come earlier.
Colonel Park didn't do it.
Even if you make a plan
Minister Kim also acted alone.
Even if it is reported
Minister Jin was the only one who did this.
Don't you understand this?
Just a head on the neck
I can pick it up right away
Do you understand?
I keep it here so you can see what the country looks like.
Look around
Overwhelmed
Indecisive
The guy who didn't know what to do was running around
Messy
It's a mess.
Order must be established
Who?
Come and lift this big stick
In military uniform
Persisted for 25 years
I should be qualified.
But yeah
If someone holds me back
If someone blocks
If you were me
What will you do?
No matter what you do
Colonel Park
Death
Got it?
Section Chief Jin
Dig into this guy's background
There must be a lot of unclean places.
You go back
When things calm down, let's go have a bowl of rice cake soup
What the hell?
I am a stinky person indeed.
Because I am a guy without connections or background
I want to create my own life
So study hard
Money
That power
Will anyone hate it?
Of course I would think
Those who are rich and prosperous but still live in poverty are mentally ill
No matter if there is sin or not, no matter if there is taste or not
I'm going to steal and cheat
To lick the stinky feet of powerful people
Let the powerless shed tears of blood
How about it?
I'm bad enough already.
Yeah
But
It's really disgusting.
It's fucking disgusting.
A guy like you
I won't kill for money.
I won't kill to get ahead.
Do you understand, you bastard?
Killing because of one's desire
Is this something a human can do?
Hear me out
If you want to be king, then be the king.
If you want to get rich
Then take all the money of the Republic of Korea
But
Sincere advice
Don't kill people
Do you understand?
I asked you if you heard me, brat.
If you are told to turn right, then you must turn right
What?
Pronunciation: woo
An ignorant reporter.
Hanging on newspaper
I think you'll be interested
Let me have a few drinks with you.
I found that Minister Jin
There's a lot of hidden property.
corruption
Bribery
There are still many things that can be found.
I was under a lot of pressure because of this incident.
Do you play golf?
Very interesting, right?
Must accept...
Don't feel burdened
Just say a few words to me.
Do you think this trial will go smoothly?
There are dozens of tanks parked at Gwanghwamun.
Colonel
Do you know what real
civil unrest is?
The tanks parked on the streets of Seoul
That's the real civil unrest.
I know
Because that's the only way to survive
Only you survive
Only Lee Ye Jin can survive
Only if Li Huishan can survive can her family live.
Don't think too complicated
Never mind conscience and belief
Just turn a blind eye.
The world will be different
Anyway
The Republic of Korea will go the way of arming
Whether a traitor or a revolutionary
They won't remember the name Park Tae-joo
5-year fixed deposit and 16-square-meter fully rented bungalow
The total amount is less than 4 million won
His eldest brother has worked in a coal mine for 20 years.
His younger brother worked as a welder on construction sites to make a living
Born into a poor family
The defendant graduated with honors from the Army Academy
Always committed to serving on the front line
He is a model military officer.
On duty in the Army Division
He was once transferred away from the front line by his boss, Kim Young-il
He applied to return to the field team more than a dozen times.
This transfer application
This is information that proves that he does not want to become a political soldier.
The defendant pointed the gun at his teammate and took his life
Killing can never be justified under any circumstances
Should be severely punished
But
Absolutely cannot agree
Park Tae-joo's actions are an act of supporting civil unrest
Soldiers who obey orders cannot be held accountable
Half an hour
The order was given only half an hour ago.
This is done intentionally by the boss to hinder the judgment of his subordinates.
Article 12 of the Criminal Law
No punishment for forced behavior
The defendant was in a position of power
Cleaner than anyone else
But for the sake of the country
A true soldier who always takes the lead in fighting the enemy
Dreaming of becoming a proud military attaché
I would like to ask you
For this person who wants to be buried in the national cemetery
Foolish principleists are exonerated
Did the defendant know that this was a final judgment?
Yes.
On October 26, 1979, the defendant
Participated in the assassination plan of the president on the orders of his superiors
Yes.
I mean if
If you only have one practice in life
so
If you could go back in time
What choice will you make?
I'm asking if you'll participate.
The act of overthrowing a country and usurping power
Will you follow your boss's instructions?
If I could go back in time
In the Army Division
I want to go back to the old officers' quarters.
There is the smell of my wife's cooking
And the laughter of children
The Defendant
Please give a brief answer
I am a soldier from the Republic of Korea
Soldiers must obey orders
Because I believe
This will protect my children, my family, and my country.
I am...
The choice on October 26th
There will be no changes.
Defendants Kim Young-il, Kim Ji-won, and Han Ho-seok
Park Tae-joo Lee Ki-suk Yoo Tae-woo Kim Tae-woo
Applicable to killing for the purpose of civil unrest
And the death penalty for crimes such as aiding and abetting sedition
All rise!
For you
Don't bother.
Yeah, but I understand one thing.
You are a real lawyer.
Grateful!
March 6, 1980 Colonel Park was executed.
The trial of Captain Park, who was intervened by the new military, was concluded in a quick manner within 16 days.
It is unusual that the death penalty was hastily executed after the first instance verdict was announced while the trials of other defendants were ongoing.
Happy Country