You a stalker?
I'm not.
Don't pretend to be out
of your house.
You really are a stalker, then.
Something happened between
you and Takagi?
I told you before that my weakness
is a woman and a child, right?
By 'woman', I meant her, and by
'child', I meant our child.
What?
"Our child"?
Takagi is married.
Well, her husband is
my ex-boyfriend.
What?!
I mean, roughly speaking,
Mieko and I worked part-time
together during 1st year in highschool,
and that's where we met Eiji who
was 6 years older than us,
and the three of us got along well.
And then, Eiji and I started
going out with each other.
But, about 3 years later,
his dad was against our relationship.
And that's when Mieko said,
"I'll give birth to your child,"
"so you guys don't have
to break-up" or something.
The three of us did it.
How bizarre.
Bizarre, isn't it?
Now that I'm thinking about it,
it really was weird,
but we were all desperate back then,
and we assumed that
that was the only way.
So, Mieko got pregnant.
Your child?
No, it was Eiji's.
As I look at Eiji's heart change and
is filled with affection for Mieko,
I just couldn't take it anymore.
Well, Mieko is Mieko,
but the way it looked to me,
she was lying when she
said the child was mine.
So you---
I feel so betrayed by the
two of them and it ate me.
And then, before she gave birth,
I went and started living here.
You haven't seen them
since then?
If they're married and doing well,
that's all that matters.
Sorry for telling you all these nonsense.
Thanks for waiting.
Thanks.
Welcome.
I'm meeting someone here.
Happy New Year.
I've started drinking already.
You fine with beer?
Thanks.
You've worked hard.
Your appetizer.
Thanks.
How did your volunteer at the
home facility go?
You saw grandpa?
Well, yeah.
But, he was kinda restless
so he couldn't talk much.
I see. Well, can't do anything about it.
Big bro...
How could you take such
good care of Grandpa?
He's family, after all.
What makes you think that way?
I don't feel the same way.
To be honest, when I was at
home with him, it was hard for me.
He was very strict.
I was sick of listening to mom
and dad badmouth each other.
Wasn't it that way
with you too?
But still,
I left home as soon as I could
and stayed away from them.
I feel bad for having pushed
grandpa on to you.
And then you said I'm
taking good care of him?
I only visit him sometimes,
and it doesn't amount to much.
I know it in my head.
But, even though I owe him
one for raising me,
I just don't see him the way you do.
When grandpa collapsed, I thought,
"Everything has to come to an end."
I can't say that he was
a good grandpa,
but it doesn't change the fact
that he raised us.
That's why, if we accept
the way grandpa is now,
maybe as a result, we'd also
be saving ourselves.
You may think you've done nothing,
but it's not just about
repaying a favor.
Isn't it enough that you
feel grateful?
Did grandpa seem to know you?
Not sure.
Does he recognize you?
He sometimes does or not.
It's that bad, huh?
Well, he's got dementia.
I guess we'll just keep moving forward.
One more beer, please.
Asato, the model's here.
Sure.
I've brought a girl
from my workplace.
I am in your care.
Thank you.
Well then, right this way.
I'm leaving now.
I'm sorry, can you take
care of her for me?
Takagi, wait!
Uhh... do you know "Senoo"?
What?
Well, he was my classmate
back in grade school,
and I coincidentally met
him this other day,
and when I asked him where he
went to junior high and highschool,
I remember that it was the
same school you went to.
You know where Makki
currently lives?
No, no...
His contact details?!
His email, through direct message, or
anything at all! Please tell me!
It was just a small chat
we had that day.
I see.
You're looking for Senoo?
If you get his contact details,
please let me know immediately.
Don't forget, okay?
You know what?
I saw Takagi today.
And then, I know it was bad but,
I mentioned your name.
And then, she...
Her expression changed, and
she was asking me your contact---
You didn't tell her, did you?!
I didn't.
I've been thinking about it.
Why don't you atleast go see her
one time and have a proper talk?
With who?
Takagi, and your ex-boyfriend.
Are you a demon or something?
Takagi has been wanting to see you.
I think she believes that things
between you two aren't over yet.
Isn't it about time to draw the line?
I don't want closure.
I'm scared.
I'm much more scared of seeing
them as much as I do now.
I'm the one who should apologize.
I'm the only one who abandoned the
problem that the three of us caused.
Part of me can't forgive them.
But it wasn't just one person's fault.
And yet, I'm the only one
who ran away from it.
Get a grip of yourself, Senoo.
It's none of your concern.
I'm sure they regret it as much as you do.
I don't think they want to see
you just to blame you for it all.
Hang on.
I'll also be doing my best.
Make sure you stay right there.
Yes.
If you leave, I'll throw
you around the room.
Rather, I'll excavate you.
Excavate?
Rather, if I get found,
it'd be bad.
This has nothing to do with me,
and I don't know the circumstances.
If you didn't poke your nose
where it doesn't belong,
I wouldn't be here either.
Fine.
Well then, I'm off.
It has been so long.
Right?
Take a seat.
I'm really...
... sorry.
Don't apologize.
There's nothing to apologize for.
You haven't changed at all, Eiji.
Sorry for running away.
Makki...
But the truth is, it's always been
the three of us.
Me too.
What?
I don't have the keys with me.
Why? You're the one who put it away.
It's not here. You...
What? I don't have it.
There it is.
Geez, you can't even try
to make sure.
You guys really look like
a married couple now.
Something just felt right.
I'm glad.
We finally saw each other.
Right?
Well then, I got to pick up Shiho.
Take care.
I'll also be going grocery shopping later.
Anything you want to eat?
Sukiyaki?
Okay.
Thanks.
Eichan or Ei...
What a hassle.
I'll just call you "Eiji."
Right, Eiji?
Eiji, try it!
Because you said you're good with it.
You liking me. Do you mean it...
Because Eiji's cooking is so good!
Why would you say that
to me, anyway?
Eiji.
No, don't say that, Eiji.
Thanks.
Senoo...
How are you?
It's just...
You did great.
You really did well.
Over here.
Mr. Sugimoto.
Your other grandchild has come
to visit you today.
Well then, please stop by the
reception desk again once you leave.
Thank you so much.
Have you been buying that stuff again?
I put it out in the living
room a while ago.
Should we get ready?
Grandpa, can I give you a massage?
You used to be so loud before.
And now you're so shriveled up.
You're gotten old.
You...
You're so good at massaging shoulders.
It feels good.
Thank you.
Next up...
I'll get your hair done.
What are you doing here?
Waiting for you.
I'm home.
What are you doing?
When are you going to cut it off?
My hair?
You want it short?
I mean, I'm not really
particular about it.
I can get a shampoo at the store.
You really like that, huh?
After all...
What is it?
Well, the first time you
applied shampoo on my head,
somehow,
I wonder why, but it brought
tears to my eyes.
It really did hurt, then?
No, that's not it.
Then what?
Maybe it has the power
to make me feel relaxed.
Do you still love your
ex-boyfriend to this day?
I thought, I don't ever want
to see his face again,
but now my feelings changed
to wanting to see their child.
That's it for now.
You jealous?
You care too much about me.
Somehow...
More than liking you...
You're very dear to me.
Sorry, it's nothing heavy.
Thank you.
It's Teacher Washimi.
My teacher.
Oh, really?
I see.
So, what did you do with that teacher?
Let's see, that teacher,
taught me a lot of things.
A young man is on his way to us.
Say, "it's nice to meet you."
Nice to meet you.
Pleased to see you.
You know, this looks like a big leaf.
A big leaf.
You're right. It is big.
That's right. Just a bit farther.
You know, right?
My kindergarten friends... you see...
Well...
We play all the time at the
picture book club.
In that place, I just..
You know? I play there and have fun.
So much fun, huh?
- And then they...
At the park where they fell...
And then they play, and I saw it.
I had the smaller one.
Really?
- Is that so?
You did...
- And big brother...
he got poked a lot of times, once.
He got poked.
By who?
A big brother I don't know.
Is that so?
Shiho, Shiho.
Look, it's a bird. Bird!
Where?
- Over there. Can you see it?
So high, up high.
But, I can see a bit.
Just a bit.
- Right?
You're the same as usual, Makki.
We've changed in our own ways.
Then, have you bought a car?
- Not yet.
Then, a scooter?
You're ticking me off.
Right?
It's like those are bird
droppings, the white ones.
Right?
Does Shiho like kakipi too?
I think she likes it quite a lot.
I wouldn't mind her liking
it a little more.
You think so?
That's fine. I can just buy
as many kakipi's you want.
That's very encouraging.
You know, white stones
look so hard.
Right?
Stones are hard.
Well, I'm headed this way.
We'll head straight home now.
See you.
Alright.
Bye.
See you.
- Bye-bye.
Let's go.
Okay.
Translations by FURRITSUBS
Raws: Boron (Donsubbers)
Translations: FURRITSUBS
*furritsubs.wordpress.com
Twitter: @furritsubs