Translations by FURRITSUBS
Raws: Boron (Donsubbers)
Excuse me for a while.
Check this for me.
I'm pregnant.
For real?
Your body alright?
Where are you?
An elephant?
An elephant.
Zoo?
Zoo.
Why are you at the zoo?
I just wanted to come here.
For now, I guess we have to
go to the hospital first.
I still feel a bit uneasy.
You'll come with me?
Of course.
Right?
Thank you.
Even if I take a nap, I can't
help but catch a cold.
Mom.
I'm pregnant.
What?
Congratulations.
What? What?
Hold up.
Wait, who's the guy?
Rather, you've never told me
anything all this time!
What? You actually want to know?
What are you saying?
I mean, I thought you do
have a boyfriend.
I don't have a boyfriend.
I'm pregnant, but I'm just
going to give birth.
I just wanted to let you know.
That's not just a simple
matter of, "Sure, alright."
You need to tell me
exactly what went on and---
Mom! I won't cause you
any troubles at all!
What for? When you've never
cared for me at all.
What are you saying?
Hold up.
I'll do it. Just stop the fire.
You're kinda commendable.
You're acting calm.
Nah, I panic way too much.
Something about it just surprised me
so much that I lost my appetite.
It's fine. I'm not hungry anyway.
Mieko.
Should we go to the beach?
What?
Mama, you're working hard.
- Hey! Come in!
Kaoru! Take a seat!
What? Kaoru?
You're off work today?
That's right. I brought my
daughter with me.
What? What?
I brought my daughter with me!
Your daughter? She's so damn adorable!
Sit here.
He said you're cute.
Right?
- You're sitting over there?
Have a drink with me!
Sorry. I'll be there later so
go and sing for now.
For real? That's a promise!
Yay! I'll wait!
So this is how snack bars are?
What did you expect?
Nothing much.
But, it's been a while
since I've done this.
You're always acting upset
when I'm with you.
No, I'm not.
Welcome, Kaoru.
- Mama!
Nice to meet you.
My daughter.
- She's so cute.
Thank you for always
taking care of my mom.
Sorry.
Here you go, Kaoru.
- Thank you.
No need for an ashtray.
- Right, I'll take it off.
Alright.
Yay!
Kaoru!
- What?
Come on, now. Can't you
atleast sing one song?
What?
- Just one! One song!
Can I borrow your mom for a sec?
Just one song, okay?
- Yeah! Alright!
She will sing!
- I'll be back.
Alright, alright.
You've got a great voice!
I don't wanna get in your way.
What? You mean, you don't
know which of them is the dad?
But why?
"Why?" I just explained it to you.
- No, no. I just don't get it.
I just don't understand.
Is there such an insane
thing like that?
I know you can decide for yourself,
but what were those two actually thinking---
Stop it.
You don't even know
anything about those two.
They attended my entrance ceremony,
took me back and forth from work.
They're thinking about me
more than you could ever do.
Is that so?
But, if you genuinely think that this
is a matter between you and them,
then I think you and the guys
are way too naive.
Give birth if you want to.
You'll need to talk about it
with the guy's parents.
When are you going
to the hospital?
Tomorrow.
The three of us will.
Right.
You're alright with me
giving birth?
Nothing wrong about it, of course.
Kids are adorable.
Well...
I guess, I've gotten old already
to be drinking with my daughter.
I didn't even drink anything.
It's fine!
When was the last time we
talked like this?
Be careful.
Sure.
Thank you.
What?
Let's go out again sometime.
The heck?
Your last period was on August 19.
And you haven't bled since then, right?
Yes.
Have you tried checking
with a pregnancy test?
Yes.
I just want to make certain,
are you sure you want to have the baby?
I want to.
Well then, let's first check for
pregnancy in the uterus.
Alright.
Are you Ms. Takagi's husband?
No. Wait, husband?
Just go.
What?
I'll stay here.
It's me.
- Right this way.
Right.
Okay, I'll put in the ultrasound device now.
It might feel a bit unsettling.
Okay.
Please have look at the
screen on the right.
You can see the baby in a black bag.
See?
If you look closely, you can
see his heart beating.
It's moving!
Alright, looking healthy.
Are you alright?
Doctor, how far along am I...?
You're 8 weeks in.
Want to come back
inside with Papa?
Come on.
No, mama!
Alright, come here.
Fine, come here.
Want to sit down?
The four layers of the
epidermis, from top to bottom.
Stratum corneum, stratum granulosum,
stratum spinosum, stratum basale.
How can you even remember all
these stuff that don't make sense?
I mean, the exams are near.
So, what're you going
to do about school?
I'm going to take a break from
school at the last minute.
Eiji said this himself but,
he'd like to register you
under his family name.
What? Why?
He kinda looked up a
few things online,
so if ever some kind of
emergency happens,
he's be responsible for supporting you.
What do you think about that?
Well...
In my perspective, I don't really
need that sort of responsibility.
I do have my mom.
The fact that he's willing to do that much
must mean you're really important to him.
But, if ever it really is Eiji's child,
I know it's just for formalities,
but it won't have anything
to do with me anymore, right?
No, that's not---
That's all I can think
about these days.
Am I going crazy?
Having kids, or working,
and what I want to do.
I don't have anything like those.
At the hospital, they said
I'm already 13 weeks in.
What?
My pregnancy.
That's why, this child is
probably yours.
You worked hard today.
Thank you.
How are your studies going?
Yeah, all perfect.
Perfect? You really said that?
Miechan, here's some orange juice.
You bought a lot
of that again.
Thank you.
- How are you feeling? All good?
I'm fine.
Geez.
I don't know what's going
on, and I'm worried.
You're worrying way too much.
Right?
- If so, then I'm glad.
Hey.
It states here in the book that morning
sickness comes in at 8 to 11 weeks.
Isn't yours a bit off?
What?
There's a pretty big gap between
the time period shown on this page.
But, doesn't it depend
from person to person?
Well, I'm sure you're
right to some extent.
Are you alright, Miechan?
I'm fine.
All good.
Hey, why don't you lie down?
No, I'm fine. As long as
I get to lean on something.
It'll be bad if you
push yourself.
Why don't you head to bed?
Okay?
I'll take you to bed.
Wait a bit.
Here.
You alright?
Thank you.
Hey, Mieko.
You said you're in your 13th week,
but the truth is that you're actually
still 7-8 weeks pregnant, right?
What?
If it is, then we're on track.
You're wrong.
I told you, it's your child.
But, it looks like you're having a bad
case of morning sickness so we should---
We don't have to. I'm fine.
If that's the case,
we'll know about it in time.
Is one or the other that
much of an issue?
The problem here is why you lied.
I'm not lying!
What did you need to hide it for?
I don't get it.
That's obvious.
Because she loves you.
No, that's not it.
But, isn't that so?
If not, then---
Then, if that's the case,
what do you expect me to do?
You're asking me to reciprocate that?
No, that's not how it has to be.
Even if the child is yours,
are the three of us supposed to
come together and play family?
No...
- Even if Mieko likes me?
No, I'm saying why are things
going this way--
Rather, on the other hand,
how about you?
If it were my child.
You know how Mieko truly feels,
yet you'll still register
her under your name?
No, I said that's not--
Of course, that's so unreasonable!
Be realistic!
Don't put off thinking about it!
You don't have to raise
your voice like that.
I'm not saying we should
put off thinking about it for later.
Are you even trying to
understand how Miechan feels?
You're too impatient to reach to a
conclusion and I can't keep up.
I'm the one who can't keep up!
Why would you say that
to me, anyway?
How can you ever know how I feel
when all you can think about is Mieko?
What are you saying?
It's because of us that things
have turned out this way.
It's only natural to
think about Miechan first.
Why would you say all those?
I see.
I guess I am crazy?
No...
That's not true.
But, even if Mieko had
something to give to you,
I have nothing.
Having to keep seeing you always
looking at Mieko like this...
It's heart-breaking.
I'm leaving.
I need to cool down.
Eichan, are you still up?
The way things are now,
what's going to happen if
Makki's no longer with us?
If ever that really do happens...
You know,
I've always been thinking about it.
How did things turn out this way?
What else should I have done?
But, if we're looking at
what caused this...
I don't think there was
anything like that.
I mean,
I lied to Makki about the
baby being his.
That's not the direct problem.
But still, I think it is.
Treating life like an object.
Using it as a means to an end.
That's why, we got punished.
Every bad thing we did.
We brought all these on ourselves.
That's the only thing that I
and I'm sure Makki as well
don't think so.
Even on harrowing days,
or when frustrating
things happened to us,
do you think it was wrong for us
to try to look forward?
I don't know anymore.
You know?
I think we're only being tested
to see how we would live our lives.
Where are you now?
On my way to work.
You're lying.
You're at the zoo again, right?
These elephants are always so noisy.
You see,
the child I'm carrying,
is Eichan's kid.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I lied.
Nah, it's fine.
Hurry and come home.
We're having sukiyaki today.
Makki?
Hey, Makki.
Don't hang up on me.
Don't hang up.
Hey.
Makki?
I brought oranges and
yogurt. You want some?
Translations: FURRITSUBS
*furritsubs.wordpress.com
Twitter: @furritsubs