Mr. Xu.
For our new energy vehicle,
as soon as the news got out,
we've been getting so many calls
from advertisement companies.
Some of them have worked with us
for many years.
And there are some new companies.
They all want to tender for it.
I've expected that.
The dinner that we are going to now
will be held by an advertising agency.
I've turned them down a few times.
They didn't give up.
They knew that I'm now in Shanghai
and wanted to talk and catch up.
I couldn't say no.
But I'm afraid they're up to something.
We can't let them make the first move.
I got it.
Let me introduce you, Mr. Luo.
This is Ms. Shen Ruoxin.
She's in charge of the tender.
- Hello, Ms. Shen.
- Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
You too.
Mr. Sun, look.
Isn't Ms. Shen very beautiful?
- She's very beautiful.
- She looks familiar.
Doesn't she look like a celebrity?
If so, we don't need to hire anyone
for our advertisement.
Ms. Shen is already perfect.
That's convenient.
- Mr. Xu.
- Yes?
Ms. Shen.
I would like to make a toast.
I'm so happy today. I really am.
I'm flattered.
How many years has it been?
You came over with just one call.
Ms. Shen.
You have no idea.
We used to be on the same team.
While many people
have gotten condescending,
Mr. Xu is still the same.
He's so nice and kind.
I have no idea
that he appreciates
our old friendship so much.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
You and I go way back.
I won't forget that.
I'll be there whenever you call.
- Yes.
- However,
friendship is friendship.
Business is business.
I understand.
It's the rule, right?
We are only talking
about friendship today.
Let's not talk business. Cheers.
Mr. Xu.
Ms. Shen.
I hope I won't make a fool of myself
by telling you my opinion.
I believe that in the future,
new energy cars will own the market.
In terms of performance,
a lot of new energy cars
have already surpassed gasoline cars.
You guys are experts.
You should know, right?
There are many old-fashioned
European companies.
They used to say
that they'll never make
new energy vehicles.
They wanted to keep up the tradition.
And now?
They are all doing it.
They are developing
new energy cars, right?
That's the trend.
You guys are far ahead.
Your success is coming. Congratulations.
Here.
Hello.
May I know who is the owner of the car
with license plate D17910?
That's our car. What's the matter?
You are blocking the exit.
Please move your car.
Okay, I'll call the driver.
Is everything okay?
Yes.
Mr. Luo, I'm sorry.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Take your time.
Go ahead.
Mr. Xu.
Open up. My arms are getting tired.
Sir, please don't make it hard for me.
Without Mr. Xu's permission,
I really can't let you put them
in the car.
Didn't Mr. Xu just call you?
He did call me
to move the car.
But he didn't mention this.
Hey, sir.
This is Mr. Xu's arrangement.
He asked me to put these in the car.
- Come on.
- What did Mr. Xu ask you to do?
These are from Mr. Luo.
Just some gifts for Mr. Xu.
That's all.
We really appreciate it,
but we can't accept them.
I'm sorry.
I've already brought it.
I can't just carry them back.
Just tell Mr. Luo.
This was what Mr. Xu wanted.
Mr. Luo will know what it means.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Xu.
It's done. Don't worry.
The gifts were too expensive.
It's not appropriate,
so I turned him down for you.
Good job.
You handled it well.
Because of what happened tonight,
I'm more determined to hold a tender.
Many of our old partners
never focus on
their professional skills.
Instead,
all they care about
is how to build relationships.
We are in a new industry.
It's tough to start things up.
That's why we need strong allies.
That's right.
Hey, Ruoxin.
Do you have plans for tomorrow night?
Is there anything, Mr. Xu?
There's a private party tomorrow night.
It's a very important one.
The invitation says you must bring a date.
But I just arrived in Shanghai.
I don't know anyone
who can come with me.
But I have to attend it.
This is a personal favor.
It's not about work.
You can say no,
but I hope you can
come with me.
Mr. Xu.
This is…
I don't think
it's appropriate for me to go.
Relax.
This private party
is not completely unrelated to work.
It's because there will be
technology experts at the party.
Our department is relatively new.
We still need to find some experts.
Please reconsider.
Okay then.
Thank you.
You are too kind.
- Good morning.
Ruoxin.
What's the occasion?
What do you mean?
It's not a special day.
Why are you so dressed up?
Keep it down.
Mr. Xu asked me to go to a party
with him tonight.
Dinner last night
and a party today?
No, I'm coming too.
I would like to see
if he's up to something.
Don't cause trouble.
We met with an advertiser last night.
At tonight's party,
we are meeting
potential new energy partners.
It's business.
And I'm your assistant.
If I go, it's also for work.
I've only heard of bringing a female date.
I've never heard of male dates.
If you really want to go,
I'll ask Mr. Xu
that I'm not going.
You'll take my place.
Never mind.
If you tell him that,
I don't think I'll ever pass
the probation period.
Take my car.
I'll take Mr. Xu's car today.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll drive you to work.
Ziyan.
You are here.
Xiaoxin.
Mom!
My baby!
You're different when you see your mom.
Did you miss me?
Yes.
You did?
Good boy, pack up your things.
- Okay.
- Let's go home.
Go.
Did you just wake up?
I'm really tired.
Your son is incredible.
He's indeed quite a troublemaker.
But it's because you are inexperienced.
You are just not ready to do this.
When you have a baby,
you'll get used to it.
I really can't imagine
what your everyday life is like.
Just go with it.
I go to work
and take care of him.
I'm not like you.
My brother treats you so well.
Tell me.
Are you happy having a child?
Miserable and happy.
It can be tough.
But every time Xiaoxin kisses me
or gets clingy,
I will think that it's all worth it.
Ziyan.
I know you and my brother
decided not to have kids.
But once a woman gets to a certain age,
maternity becomes a natural instinct.
If you have a child,
you'll think differently.
Okay, I'll think about it.
Are you done packing?
Yes, I am.
Give your aunt a hug and a kiss.
That's better.
You have me in your eyes.
I have you in my eyes?
That's right.
Do you have me in your eyes, Mom?
In my eyes,
you are always there.
Not just in my eyes,
also in here,
you are everywhere.
Mr. Xu.
Let's go to the store
I visited previously.
Okay.
It's a limited edition.
There's only one in each size.
I think this is your size.
- Let her try it on.
- Okay.
- And give her a belt.
- Yes, sir.
This way, miss.
Miss, the gentleman outside
has already paid for this dress.
Does it fit you?
Do you want to try another size?
There's no need.
Did you just leave it on?
There's a pair of scissors in there.
You can cut the tag.
Thank you.
Mr. Xu.
It looks good on you.
I'll wrap up your clothes.
Please wait a moment.
It looks good on you.
It's like it's custom-made.
I picked well.
But Mr. Xu,
this is too expensive.
Do me a favor.
There's no jewelry.
So you actually saved me the money.
Miss, here are your clothes.
- Give it to me.
- Yes, sir.
My baby.
Let's eat out this evening.
I want to have Japanese food.
Okay.
I'll pick you up later.
- Bye.
- You have a son?
How old is your child?
Eight years old.
I'm almost 40 years old.
My goodness.
I can't tell.
You had a baby at 32?
I was a little too old.
But it went really well.
Look at me.
I recovered pretty well.
Just keep exercising regularly.
Do you take care of him yourself?
I'll do it when I'm home.
I'll get a babysitter if I can't.
After all, men won't help.
People always say,
"A reliable husband
makes the child a diamond.
An unreliable husband
makes the child a burden."
That's nonsense.
The husband has nothing to do
with the child.
Our husbands could be someone else's too.
But the child is ours.
I raise my own child.
No one can take him away.
Yes, let's do one more set.
- Okay.
- Hurry up.
Okay.
Mr. Xu, you are late.
I'm sorry.
I was held up at work.
It has been a while, Robin.
Are Michael and the others here?
They are all over there.
They're waiting for you.
Don't you want to talk to them?
Okay, I'll be right there.
Okay.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- You are welcome.
I'll go over and say hello.
Have some champagne.
Relax.
Michael, it has been so long.
Leo.
- Hello.
- We have been waiting for you.
That's quite fast.
It has only been a week.
Do you have a new girlfriend?
This one is quite classy.
She's a lot better than those
who have had plastic surgeries.
I've never dated anyone
who had plastic surgeries.
She's my subordinate.
- Hi, Minjie.
- Hi, it has been a while.
You are finally in Shanghai.
We are just talking about it.
Wherever he goes,
he can always find a pretty and competent
female subordinate.
Did you bring Lisa?
It's not Lisa.
Over there.
Not bad.
She might be better than Lisa.
Aren't you going to ask Lisa
to come to Shanghai?
I'm considering it.
Cheers.
Hello.
I'm Mandy.
Did Minjie bring you here?
Are you his girlfriend?
No, he's my boss.
You look nice.
What's your expertise?
I studied law.
Which school did you go to?
Peking University, China University
of Political Science and Law,
Fudan University, or East China University
of Political Science and Law?
None of those.
Mandy went to Princeton University.
She has a master's degree in literature.
Look over there.
The one in the champagne-colored dress.
She went to the University of Melbourne.
She studied art and music.
She's really good at playing the cello.
In our social circle,
one's background is important.
I remember Xu Minjie studied MBA
at Columbia University.
I'm not part of this circle.
Isn't that a limited-edition Hermes?
I didn't get one in France last time.
Whose date is that?
I'm sorry.
Do you know how expensive this dress is?
Where's your manager? Go and get him.
I'm sorry.
No, go and get the manager.
I…
Hello, what's going on?
- You are the manager, right?
- Yes.
Look what your waitress did.
She spilled wine on me!
Do you know my dress is custom-made?
What should we do about this?
That's not it, sir.
She bumped into me and it fell on her.
What did you say?
Don't push the blame on me!
What a waitress.
How can she even work here?
- Sir, I really didn't--
- That's enough. Stop it.
Miss.
I'm really sorry
about what happened earlier.
How about this?
We'll pay for the dry cleaning.
Is that okay?
The dry-cleaning bill?
Can you dry-clean this?
This is imported material!
Mandy, come.
What?
Wine stains are very common.
The dry cleaners can take care of it.
If you keep doing this,
you'll make the situation more awkward.
I happen to have a scarf here.
I'll wrap this around you.
Look, it's covered.
Isn't that good?
Enjoy the evening.
You haven't said a word all evening.
Are you tired?
It's okay.
But I kept smiling earlier.
My cheeks are tired.
It's my first time hearing
such honest feelings.
Actually, these kinds of events
can't be avoided.
But don't take them too seriously.
Just relax.
Let's go.
You're taking out the trash?
Yes.
Wait.
Why did you change clothes?
He didn't like the one I wore.
So I changed.
What are you doing? Go now.
I'll wait.
I'm on it.
Ruoxin.
What kind of party did you go to?
You are all dressed up.
It was so boring.
They spent so much money,
went to nice universities,
got high degrees and diplomas,
just to be a pretty face at a party.
They talked about bags
and people's clothes.
I don't understand them.
What are you doing? This is your floor.
Get some rest.
You too.
Good night.
Why did that take you an hour?
Wait.
Were you taking out the trash
or waiting for someone?
Do you want some?
It was fine this morning.
She had to go to this party
and was purposely given a dress for it.
Are you serious?
Do you mean Ruoxin?
I think
that must be from Mr. Xu.
The party was an excuse
to give her a dress.
Isn't this common in dramas?
Why do you think he bought her that dress?
Why do you think?
He's pursuing Ruoxin.
He's not her type.
How do you know?
What type is he?
It's just impossible.
Do you like her too?
What are you saying?
Ruoxin is my boss.
And she's nice to me.
She taught me a lot.
Can't I be concerned about her?
That's the best.
She's much older than you.
You are not a good match.
Why do you always make it weird?
You are the weird one.
You look great.
You look really great.
But you will be upset
if I keep you in my closet.
But if I hang you here,
you'll be in my way.
TOTAL LUNAR ELLIPSE
- Good morning.
You look better like this.
What?
Do I not look good in better clothes?
You are still pretty,
but a little too pretty.
It looks too unreal.
Yes.
Wearing them was tiring.
SHEN RUOXIN
Mr. Xu.
I returned that dress.
The money will be returned
to your credit card.
Please check.
PRECAUTIONS FOR PREGNANT WOMEN
OF ADVANCED AGE
Honey.
Let me make a copy.
Sure.
WHAT TO PAY ATTENTION TO
IN HIGH-RISK PREGNANCIES
Honey.
What?
Are you tempted?
Tempted?
To have children!
I'm still thinking about it.
I heard that
a reliable husband
makes the baby a diamond.
An unreliable husband
makes the baby a burden.
Look at you.
You didn't help when Xiaoxin was here.
Why should I bother having a child?
If it was my own child,
I'd help you at all costs.
I'll do whatever you ask.
Honey.
I've been doing some research
about having children.
It's better to do a full prenatal checkup.
It's safer for you.
As for the hospital,
it would be better
to visit a maternity hospital.
You've planned this long ago, haven't you?
Look at you.
You are always up to something.
That's too much of an accusation.
Before this,
I didn't say a word about it.
I just saw
that you were looking into it today.
That's why I'm telling you this.
I've looked it up in advance,
so you don't have to worry.
HONORABLE AUTHORS,
COME AND HAVE A LOOK
Sijia, let's eat.
Ms. Qiao, I'll eat here.
SU YANG
These are some good positions.
You should try to contact them.
I got it. Thank you.
Ms. Shen.
Tomorrow is the monthly inventory.
It's your turn and Qi Xiao's.
Here's the inventory list.
Okay. Thank you.
A day off?
I was just informed by Mr. Xu.
I was wondering,
for this month's inventory,
can I switch it with someone else?
I'll do it in the next round.
As it's Mr. Xu's directive,
I dare not refuse.
Otherwise,
I'll be deemed disobedient.
I can't let that happen, can I?
But about the shift change,
I can't help you.
You are on your own.
If someone is willing to switch with you,
I'm okay with it.
Ms. Shen, I said no.
My kid is sick.
I can't work overtime.
Okay.
Xiaoxuan, are you busy?
Can you swap shifts with me?
Ms. Shen.
I'm actually sick now.
Look at the medicine I just took.
I want to go home early and rest.
Okay.
Ruoxin.
Why are you changing shifts?
Are you busy tomorrow?
I have to book a flight
and go on a business trip with Mr. Xu.
You can't do it without me.
It's too much work.
A business trip?
Why would he take you with him?
You are not even his secretary.
That's the issue. He has no secretary.
He's still looking for one.
I think he needs me
to handle some contracts for him
on this trip.
Why didn't he ask
for a legal officer then?
Are you stupid?
Aren't I a legal officer?
Do you want to stay here,
at the Administration Department forever?
Did you tell him you want to go back?
Now is not the time.
When is the right time then?
It's useless to rush things.
We have to get things done first
before we negotiate.
Do you understand?
All right.
If they don't want to switch,
don't bother asking them.
I can do it alone.
Will you be able to finish?
What else can I do?
I'll have to try.
I'll leave it to you then.
Honey, stop it.
The line at the hospital will be long.
Are you afraid you'll be late for work?
Go and get changed.
I'll clean this up.
Go on.
Hello?
I'm not at the office.
I took the morning off.
Wasn't it fine yesterday?
How could this happen?
Where's Mr. He?
Okay.
Keep him there.
I'll be right there.
Don't bother.
I'll join you as soon as I'm done.
"Done"?
Will you ever be done with your business?
My wife has the biggest heart
and is really considerate.
I'll call you a cab.
When you are done,
text me, okay?
Go.
OUTPATIENT
Why is it so high?
It's your fault.
You wanted me to have children.
I was quite healthy.
Now, out of nowhere, I'm diabetic.
We are married.
We have to have children.
Otherwise, your in-laws
and your husband
will have second thoughts.
Let them think as they like. It's fine.
While they're smiling at my belly,
I have to take this needle
and poke my fingers every day.
I can't eat what I want.
And the doctor said
that even after giving birth,
this gestational diabetes
might go on for the rest of my life.
I can't even have cakes in the future.
All right, stop crying.
Number 25, Song Ziyan.
BLOOD TEST REPORT
ULTRASONOGRAPHY REPORT
Doctor, is there a problem?
You need two more tests.
And the six hormone tests
have to be taken
on the second day of your period,
or the third morning
with an empty stomach,
along with thyroid function tests.
That's a lot.
I saw someone only did a few things.
It didn't take long.
You are 34 years old.
She's only 27 years old.
She's still young.
You have six more
routine inspections than her.
That's why.
I'm only a few years older.
What's the difference?
As women get older,
the ovaries start to degenerate.
We won't be as able-bodied
as young people are.
It's likely to have high blood pressure
or even diabetes too.
That's why older women
have to do so many tests.
MOM
LIKE
Mom.
I'm on a business trip with my boss
to Chengdu this week.
When I get back next weekend,
I'll come to visit you.
It seems like your calligraphy class
is full again, right?
Hey, what's wrong?
I need to talk to someone.
Do you have time?
I'm at the airport for a business trip.
I'm waiting for my flight.
I'm at the hospital.
I just did my prenatal tests.
I'm very upset now.
What happened?
Have you really decided to have a baby?
No, not yet.
I was hoping to get a doctor's opinion,
but she ended up giving me a lesson.
Listen, Ruoxin.
I met so many women
of advanced maternal age.
They have diabetes,
high blood pressure,
miscarriage problems,
or infertility.
I'm so frustrated.
I have no idea.
Listen, Song Ziyan. I'll repeat myself.
Don't listen to Zou Cheng
or other people around you.
Having a baby is a big deal.
If you give birth to a child,
you'll be responsible
for the baby and yourself.
Which path do you want to take?
It's your decision.
I know.
Whatever decision you make,
I'll support you.
I'm sure Zou Cheng will too.
Ruoxin.
Thank you.
That's enough. You can go now.
I'm hanging up.
Don't think too much. Bye.
I'm sorry, Mr. Xu.
It's my close friend.
It's okay.
Your friend is lucky
to have you as a friend.
Mr. Xu.
Would you like a window seat
or aisle seat?
Anything is fine.
Okay.
Hello.
One first-class seat.
Arrange a quiet seat for me.
- Yes. Just a second.
- Okay, thank you.
- Here.
- Thank you. Mr. Xu.
Excuse me, I'm in economy class.
Can I check in here? We are together.
Yes. It's fine.
Hello, miss.
It says here
that yours was paid for
and promoted to first-class.
Shall I put your seats next to each other?
Are you sure?
Arrange for us to sit together.
It's a trip.
Treat yourself on a business trip.
I upgraded your seat.
We are having a meeting
as soon as we land.
We have things to discuss.
It's easier if we sit together.
Thank you, Mr. Xu.
Here's the boarding pass.
Thank you.
Hello.
This is your assistant who stayed behind.
What is it?
There's a problem with the inventory.
At the Sales Department,
some computers are missing.
Their person in charge
took the monthly inventory.
They don't admit taking them.
That's common for the Sales Department.
They are busy with work.
They are always getting calls.
Sometimes, they forget to keep a record.
But it's okay.
You can check with the Finance Department.
They must have a record.
If you have evidence,
they will admit it.
And at the Legal Department,
some of the computers are missing as well.
Ruan Ye was not there.
Ms. Qiao doesn't want to be responsible.
She wouldn't sign.
Usually, things will turn up.
If you can't find them,
note them down
and go to the Finance Department.
Let them deal with the damage.
That's what I thought.
After verifying everything,
record all the fixed assets.
Go to each department.
Ask their managers to sign.
Then go to the Finance Department
and recheck the accounts.
Okay.
I…
Is there anything else?
Yes.
I…
couldn't find the stapler.
Which drawer did you put it in?
I can't find it anywhere.
The second drawer.
Look deeper.
Okay.
Ruoxin.
Can't you make it back today?
I'm so busy.
It's a lot.
I'm exhausted.
Are you out of your mind?
I haven't left. How can I be back today?
Tomorrow at the earliest.
Fine. I'll just tire myself to death.
You will definitely be tired,
but there's no way you will die.
Do it with aims for a permanent position.
Is there anything else?
I'm at the security check.
Text me if you need anything, okay?
I'm hanging up.
I…
Is everything okay?
Why do they need you back?
It's okay.
It's just some work issues. That's all.
Subtitle translation by: Liu Men Che