Ms. Zhou.
Thank you for today.
Without you, I wouldn't be able to do it.
It's a coincidence that I met you today.
Are you always this busy with work?
This is normal.
Mom, why are you here?
What happened?
You didn't even text me back.
I'm busy with work.
Yilan.
Who is he?
My son.
He's the "tiger"?
That's right.
Two tigers
They are handsome
You two know each other?
Wait. How do you know each other?
We met while traveling.
What a coincidence.
It happened so suddenly.
Now, someone wants
to invite us over for dinner.
If we eat there,
we can't go empty-handed.
We need to bring a gift.
What should we bring? My goodness.
Mom, didn't you just go
to the supermarket?
Look for something.
Mom.
Was the ancient town fun?
It was.
It has an air of antiquity
with flowing water, small bridges,
and natural oxygen.
If there's a chance,
go there to relax and have some fun.
It's so worth it.
Okay.
Is it a gift for me?
No.
Yes.
Do you like it?
I know this one.
It's very popular these days.
My colleagues were talking about it.
I wanted to buy one.
It heats fast and keeps warm, right?
On the last day of the trip,
Qi Xiao's mom insisted on going shopping.
She insisted on buying souvenirs.
I chose this for you.
Do you like it?
It's so pretty, Mom.
It's my favorite macaron green.
The weather will get cold soon.
You can use it.
Thank you, Mom.
You're welcome.
Being with her
not only made me learn to buy things,
but I also learned
to seek blessings
for my child's marriage.
Hey.
She's really quite an interesting person.
The water's boiling. Lower the heat!
Come on, I'll help you.
Mom.
Your mission today
is to just wait and eat.
That won't do.
There are many of us today.
I'm afraid you can't handle it yourself.
Mom.
You're overthinking it.
You're banned from the kitchen today.
I don't want Ruoxin to eat
bad food.
- Do you want to get beaten up?
- All right.
All right, go and watch the television.
Watch television.
By the way, my son,
Ruoxin's mom said
that Ruoxin loves spicy food.
When you're sautéing the meat,
add extra chili.
I got it.
Be good. Go and watch television.
Chili?
I don't need another scary night.
I'm coming!
Please come in, Yilan!
I could smell the food
as soon as you opened the door.
- Come in.
- Hello, Mrs. Qi.
I'm Shen Ruoxin, sorry to bother you.
I'm sorry to disturb you at this hour.
I'm sorry.
Why are you being polite? We're neighbors.
You're welcome.
I'm really sorry.
The house is too small.
Please have a seat.
- Have a seat.
- No.
I'll take a look around first.
- Look, that's so interesting.
- You…
There are so many toys.
- Feel free to look around.
- Okay.
- Have a seat.
Okay, Mrs. Qi.
You're so pretty,
even prettier than your mom.
That's for sure.
Thank you, Mrs. Qi.
I heard a lot about you from my son.
He said you're his boss
and that you're very capable.
It's much better to see you
than just hear about you.
Just by looking at you today,
I can tell that you're great.
Thank you, Mrs. Qi.
You look young and elegant.
- And you have such good taste.
- Thank you.
Look at how exquisite your accessory is.
This one?
My son made this for me.
Qi Xiao may be a boy,
but he's good with his hands.
He made
the necklaces, earrings, and bracelets
that I usually wear.
My friends are so jealous of me.
They said they are unique.
They mentioned a very trendy word, it's…
It's "customized."
You're his boss.
I'll ask him to make you one too.
- Qi--
- It's okay, Mrs. Qi.
He has made me one.
He made this necklace for me.
It's so pretty and it goes well
with a lot of clothes.
No, it's because you're beautiful.
Yilan, try these spareribs.
It's his specialty too.
By the way,
while you were traveling together,
you really didn't know
that I'm her assistant?
Of course.
I thought you two were the same age.
I even wanted to introduce you two.
I never thought
you're a dozen years younger than her.
Yilan, try this. It's good too.
Ruoxin.
Thank you for your guidance
for all this time.
Eat more meat to nourish yourself.
Ms. Zhou, try my stir-fried pork.
Mom.
Have some meat.
Here, have some meat.
You have a good son.
Look, he does things quickly.
And this food
is really delicious.
You're lucky.
This sautéed meat is so flavorful.
Qi Xiao is mature
and ambitious.
And he's so clever.
Don't even get me started.
When he was younger,
he was so silly.
If I told you about it,
you'll be laughing so much,
you won't be able to finish your meal.
How could it be?
Let me tell you.
Once, when he was a child,
he came home and said,
"Mom. You must buy me a broom."
I asked him, "Why do you need a broom?"
He said,
"We're going to sweep the tomb tomorrow.
For tomb-sweeping,
how can you not buy a broom?"
And on the next day, I asked him,
"Hey, how did the tomb-sweeping go?"
He was so down
and pouted while saying,
"People brought snacks for tomb-sweeping
and ate and drank so much there.
I brought a broom
and watched everyone eating."
Wasn't he silly?
Mom.
That was years ago!
Why are you bringing it up?
Right. This only means that
Qi Xiao is serious in what he does.
When Xinxin was young,
she was cute and silly.
Mom, why are you dragging me into this?
Have you forgotten?
When you were little, I brought you
to the Natural History Museum.
When we went in,
she saw that huge dinosaur skeleton
and kept pestering the guide and asking,
"How many people did you hire
to eat it so cleanly?"
We can only say that Ruoxin is determined.
That's why she has accomplished
so much at work.
She's not like Qi Xiao.
He's always doing stupid things.
Mrs. Qi, what stupid thing did Qi Xiao do?
- I--
- Well,
I must tell you about it.
As you know,
we had a couch in our house back then
which is foldable.
It's usually a sofa.
If you unfold it, it becomes a bed.
That sofa armrest…
- Let's sit for a while.
My son.
A while ago, you told me
that you like someone.
Today, you have to be honest with me.
Is that person
Shen Ruoxin?
No.
Ruoxin is my boss.
How is that possible?
Is it really not her?
Ruoxin is so incredible anyway.
She might not like me.
What's the matter?
My son isn't so bad either.
My son.
If you really like her,
go after her.
I support you.
Mom.
You're not against it?
Why would I be against it?
Do you want to live with me forever?
I thought you would be against it.
Ruoxin is a lot older than me.
A dozen years.
So I thought you would be against it.
My son.
Other moms might be against this.
They would think that their son
isn't thinking clearly
and being impulsive.
They are afraid that their son
will get tricked and deceived.
But I won't act that way.
Because my son
has never done anything
that disappointed me.
Mom.
You're so open-minded.
Do you love me?
Good boy.
Actually, when you were
eating besides her earlier,
from the way you looked at her,
I can see
that you really love her.
In my life,
can you guess what is the best thing
I have ever done?
I know.
It was meeting a man
who came from Shanghai to Sichuan,
following him to Shanghai,
and…
marrying him.
Suddenly…
Suddenly,
I miss him so much.
Mom.
I still remember that back then,
a lot of people didn't think
we would make it,
especially my parents.
They were so against it.
What I did
was cry to them
and fight with them.
That's why I know that
when you really fall for someone,
no matter what anyone says,
it's useless.
So let me tell you.
No matter what kind of girlfriend
you'll have in the future,
I won't interfere.
As long as you like her,
I like her.
As long as you're happy,
I'm happy.
Do you understand?
Mom.
Thank you.
You're being so courteous to me?
No.
I was struggling before.
I struggled with how I should tell you.
I knew it.
My son, who doesn't keep secrets
and tells me everything,
suddenly likes someone
and won't tell me about it.
So it's because
you were afraid that I would object.
Don't you like watching
those dramas on television?
Usually, in dramas,
the parents will be against it.
Am I that old-fashioned?
I'm so curious.
Why do you like her?
Tell me about it.
I like
that she's very capable,
rational,
incredible at work,
very experienced,
and dazzling.
Okay.
My son,
you've grown up.
You're very confident.
I read an article on social media.
"Only mature and confident men
can appreciate a capable woman."
You're amazing.
Mom.
I'm talking about Ruoxin.
Why are you praising me?
That's right.
Okay. Keep talking.
Don't think that
she only looks that strong.
When you actually get close to her,
she's like a little girl.
Her surgery…
She had surgery?
You can't tell Ruoxin's mom.
I won't tell her.
Keep talking.
She had surgery
and refused to take her medicines.
Can you guess what I did?
What did you do?
I bought her lollipops.
I still remember
when I was sick back then
and refused to take my medicines,
I used to say,
"The medicine is so bitter."
Then your dad bought me lollipops.
I didn't expect
that you learned to do it too.
I know.
I saw it all.
That's why it's called heritage.
Thank you, Mom.
Let me repeat.
As long as my son is happy,
I'm happy.
You can do it, my son.
Be happy.
Okay.
You were so funny when you were young.
If I wasn't afraid of tearing my wound,
I would be laughing so hard.
You're laughing at me?
You're not better off.
A pen name is the pen's name?
Actually,
I also got my head stuck
between the railings.
But my mom didn't mention it.
I guess she doesn't remember.
Why do moms always like talking
about their kid's embarrassing moments?
Who wasn't stupid when they were kids?
I guess this is how they chat
with each other.
I feel like
I'm being stripped off my clothes.
It's chilly.
Hello?
Hello.
If you really like
the jewelry I designed,
I'll make you a customized set too.
Considering our relationship,
it's free.
There's no need. Stop bragging.
I'm serious.
If you like designing so much,
have you ever thought
of opening your online shop again someday?
I'm still planning it.
What are you planning?
Do you need money?
How about I lend you
some starting capital?
It's not about the money.
I can't bear to part with you.
You're such a good boss.
Actually, I think
that it's so nice for you
to have something you like to do.
If what you like
happens to be your job,
isn't that great?
Look at me.
I like astronomy,
but I can only keep it a secret.
No one knows.
I'm involved in new energy now.
It's somewhat related
to my ambition.
That's why I'm happy every day.
If I leave
and quit being your assistant,
who would help you?
Relationships are fluid.
It's impossible
for a relationship
to remain the same forever, isn't it?
In our lives,
being able to meet
and accompany each other
for a period of time
is already such a happy thing.
We should just cherish the present.
I want you to do
the things you want to do.
I got it.
But I'm not planning
to part ways with you.
Even if I have to go my own path,
I'll drag you along.
All right.
Go to sleep.
Good night.
Xinxin.
Mom.
Where are you going?
Do you feel uncomfortable staying with me?
- It's all good.
- Ms. Zhou.
Hey.
But I haven't checked my own house
for a long time.
It's so close.
Go and check whenever you want to,
then come back.
Why did you pack everything?
Are you sad that I'm going home?
I'm worried about you.
Why are you worried?
We live close to each other.
When I miss you,
I'll come to visit.
Besides, I should go back to teaching
at the University for Seniors.
Mr. Zhao called and said
that the substitute teacher
is trying hard to get on the good side
of the principal.
If I don't go back,
I won't be able to keep my job.
You'll be alone.
Stop eating at the cafeteria.
Come by when you're free.
Let's eat together.
Once I'm done with my work,
I'll visit you at home
and spend more time with you.
I'll keep that in mind.
Look at you. It's getting cold.
I've already changed your blankets
into thick ones.
I also cooked two days' worth of food
and placed them in the refrigerator.
Remember.
You have a bad stomach.
Heat them up before eating.
I originally thought
that a lawyer travels around a lot,
but you can hide in an air-conditioned
office by working in the Legal Department.
I can't believe
that you have fieldwork too.
Don't worry, Ms. Zhou.
I promise I won't let Ruoxin work.
She'll just supervise.
Okay.
I'm relieved to hear that.
Remember.
Please take good care
of my kitty.
Okay.
Mom, let Qi Xiao see you off.
- Let me take it.
- There's no need.
I'll walk you to the subway station.
Your hand has just recovered.
You shouldn't lift heavy things, okay?
Mom, it's cold.
Wear extra layers. Don't catch a cold.
Don't work too hard.
Bye.
Text me when you get home.
- Don't worry.
- Go back.
UNLEASH ITS ENERGY, ENJOY ITS POWER
DRAGON FACE DESIGN LANGUAGE
What are you doing?
It's not heavy.
I told you, no heavy lifting. I'll do it.
Come and get your coffee.
I bought coffee for you guys!
- Come on.
- Hurry.
Pick what you want. This is a latte.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Hey.
What's the matter?
The doctor said
that you shouldn't have strong drinks.
I'm already discharged.
I've almost recovered.
At least a week.
That's what the doctor said.
Here.
Drink this.
I'll get to work.
Didn't I tell you to stay still?
Sit over there and rest.
Hurry up.
Don't move!
Come with me.
Have a seat.
Can you be more self-aware?
I think I'm almost fine now.
It shouldn't be a problem.
Everyone is so busy.
I'm not doing anything.
Am I really here to supervise?
So what if you supervise us?
You said it yourself.
"You're almost fine."
"Almost" means you're not completely fine.
Endure it a bit, miss.
I just had surgery
and I already became a kid
that had to be told what to do?
You must have forgotten
the pain back then.
Who was in so much pain that night
that she clenched her fists
and kept punching about?
"Qi Xiao, I am in so much pain! Qi Xiao."
You're the typical person who forgets
the pain after recovering.
I have to do something.
Sitting and watching everyone working
doesn't make me feel accomplished.
"It's easy to find 1,000 soldiers,
but it's hard to find a good general."
Know your place.
If you do all the work,
what should soldier like us do?
It's so hard to be a general now.
The soldiers now
are so full of principles.
Miss.
Just rest.
If you need anything, tell me.
Stay still.
Everyone, hurry up.
Hurry.
Rest well.
I'm going to Zhu Lin's place
to help him with something.
Okay, go.
I'm going to Zhu Lin's place.
Why are you so happy?
Zhu Lin helped us so much before.
If you help him,
isn't that like I'm helping him?
Friends should help each other out, right?
Go and come back soon.
You have to go to work early tomorrow.
Get some rest.
Bye.
Shen Ruoxin, have you left?
I finally understood
that longing feeling when you can't see
someone you're in love with.
Every minute of every day is torture.
In love?
Who are you in love with?
Hot pot, skewers,
seafood, and grilled meat
are all my lovers.
My longing for them now
is like the wildly growing weeds,
rolling tides,
and raging wind.
Shen Ruoxin.
- Cut the crap, Song Ziyan.
- I--
Order the skewers and wait for me.
I'll be right there.
What a foodie.
Don't push your luck.
I let you eat so many skewers.
I'm so nervous.
You might end up in the hospital again.
Did you forget
what a patient's meal tastes like?
It's because I eat
too many patient's meals,
so I have to eat out today.
This is just like when you eat
candied fruits when you were little.
I'm your accomplice for having cavities.
Your mom will scold me later.
You're eating such strongly-flavored food.
What if your wound doesn't heal?
I'm telling you.
Don't take everything so seriously.
Humans have evolved for millenniums
and finally reached
the top of the food chain.
They make me eat
bland food and vegetables.
Will my wound heal
if I don't eat or drink?
Besides, it has already been so long.
I can't eat spicy food
or even drink coffee.
I've lost my motivation to work.
This is when I feel
that the world is so nice.
Life is great.
Who is it?
Who won't let you eat spicy food
or drink coffee?
Who can tell you what to do?
Who can it be?
Qi Xiao.
All he says is,
"The doctor said…"
He's using the doctor's words as commands.
He's nagging me daily.
If I'm unhappy, you're happy?
I can't see that you're unhappy,
but I can see
that you're being coquettish.
Qi Xiao is quite interesting.
He can make you obey him.
He's really good.
One thing really conquers another.
Everyone has their match.
Shen Ruoxin.
I can finally see
some femininity on your face.
What are you talking about?
I'm his boss.
Of course he's concerned about me.
Yes, that's right.
You're his boss.
How dare he tell you what to do?
Yet you're so docile and obedient to him.
What does that mean?
It means you care about him.
I thought it was strange
that you two pretended
to be a couple at the hospital.
What's the matter?
Is it for real now?
You're unbelievable, Song Ziyan.
You're still laughing?
I'm sorry.
My eyebrows are gone now.
How is that possible?
First of all,
to me,
Qi Xiao is like a little brother.
Why are you laughing?
Also,
Qi Xiao cares a lot
about everyone around him.
Like Su Yang and his mom.
It's because he's afraid of losing them.
He cares a lot
about his friends and family, right?
Also, I'm his boss.
It's only natural that he treats me well.
If I die one day,
who's going to help with his career?
In terms of our working relationship,
we're definitely
getting along well, right?
We get along well.
Save it.
You keep saying
that you see Qi Xiao as a brother.
From what I know about you,
you
like Qi Xiao.
Look.
Cui Lixin was nice to you too.
He took care of you.
Why weren't you this obedient?
You even thought he was annoying.
You have double standards.
Liking someone and having feelings
are different, you know?
Yes.
I like Qi Xiao.
- Hey--
- That's because Qi Xiao
is competent, hardworking, and smart.
He's bright too.
He solved many problems for me
in the office, right?
It's not the kind of relationship
you're referring to.
Besides, we have a huge age gap.
Twelve years.
So what?
An 82-year-old
can even be with a 28-year-old.
When it comes to true love,
why does age matter?
Don't set limitations
to wiggle away from this.
Listen up.
Let me analyze you.
Shen Ruoxin.
You're like a hedgehog.
You have spines all over you.
You're in defensive mode all year round.
You look tough,
but deep down,
you're very soft and cowardly.
When love comes,
you roll up!
Roll up?
You're the one who's rolled up.
What's wrong with hedgehogs?
I think they're cute.
Cute?
Be careful not to poke yourself.
I'll poke you.
Stop eating.
Why not?
Hey, Zou Cheng! Have a seat.
Don't sit down.
Pay the bill.
Listen, she has been eating like a pig.
- Hurry, go!
- Let's eat together. Wait!
- Eat? Go!
- Wait!
Stop.
One,
two, three.
Wait. I'll have one last bite.
- You witch.
- It's so good.
Grab your bag. Let's go.
Come on.
ZHU LIN'S FASHION DESIGN STUDIO
By the way, Zhu Lin,
back then,
I remember when you opened this studio,
you got an interest-free loan, right?
Yes.
I was still in college back then.
There was a policy that supported
college students' start-ups.
You can check out the latest rules.
See if you fit the requirements.
I'm a citizen.
I buy train tickets.
I pay for my meals.
I don't have a bad credit record.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Hey. Are you sure you want
to start your own business?
You won't be Ruoxin's assistant
anymore, right?
I feel a bit reluctant to leave.
I'm happy again.
You have satisfied your craving,
but I'm scared.
Don't let your little brother
yell at me later.
Would he dare?
He doesn't know.
I'll go to bed happy when I get home.
I thought you girls
were all about dieting.
You had supper so late at night.
How many calories are in that?
Still, we can't miss good food
just because of calories.
Yes.
If I can't even eat,
then what
should I live for?
Okay.
You're both right.
I'll get going.
Drive slowly, Zou Cheng.
- Bye.
Honey.
Don't pick me up anymore.
Why?
Because I think Ruoxin is very lonely.
It would be good
if someone could take care of Ruoxin.
She looks quite strong and independent.
But I still think that in front of her,
it's not appropriate for us
to be too sweet.
You're so sentimental.
How do you know
that she would think that way?
Perhaps she doesn't feel lonely.
She also has you, her best friend.
You even abandoned your husband at night
to have supper with her.
I think she's quite lucky.
Hey.
How dare you get jealous of Ruoxin?
I can't do that.
I even have to compete with your students.
You're the boss. You call the shots.
You're his boss.
How dare he tell you what to do?
Yet you're so docile and obedient to him.
What does that mean?
It means you care about him.
From what I know about you,
you
like Qi Xiao.
This is the latest news.
Typhoon Hagupit will hit the city
at around 11 p.m. tonight.
Its landfall intensity
is of tropical storm level.
The city's western and southern sides
will experience heavy rain and downpours.
Please pay attention to this.
Close all doors and windows
and avoid going outdoors.
What about the materials then?
Hello, is this the moving company?
I would like to call a few movers.
I have something very important to move.
Just some event materials.
Can you send more people?
I would like everything moved
before the typhoon hits.
A typhoon warning.
It will hit around 11 p.m.
It's already 10:30 p.m.
Hey, don't go home tonight.
Just sleep here.
It's not safe on the road.
Put all that stuff in there.
Be careful!
Put them in.
Is your phone ringing?
- Take a look at it.
- Thank you, sir.
Don't worry about it.
Hello?
Hello, Ruoxin.
Where are you?
I'm at the venue now. I'm busy.
I'll get back to you later.
Go home now.
I'll go there, okay?
There's no need. I'm almost done.
I have to go. I'm hanging up.
Okay.
Hello?
Zhu Lin, I'm leaving now.
Hey!
You shouldn't ride a motorcycle
in a typhoon!
Miss.
Why did you keep so much stuff here?
Didn't you see the typhoon warning?
We have a three-day event.
The typhoon forecast said
it won't be intense.
So we didn't pack up anything.
Okay.
Okay. We'll do it.
- Get in the car.
- Help me move them all then.
Okay, no problem.
- Thank you, sir.
- Don't worry about it.
- Help me move them all.
- Hurry.
All right.
XIAOMA MOVERS PROFESSIONAL SERVICE
- Slowly.
- Hurry.
Hello?
Where are you, Ruoxin?
Sir, do you have a power bank?
I don't have a power bank.
I don't have one either.
Su Yang, go upstairs
and check if Ruoxin is back.
Call me right away when she's back.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Hello.
Did a cargo truck come tonight?
Do you know which company it is?
Hold on.
- I'll show you the car registration.
- Thank you.
I think they just left.
Only one cargo truck came tonight.
It's Xiaoma Movers.
Thank you.
Xiaoma Movers.
I can move these two myself.
- Hurry up and leave.
- Okay.
The typhoon is bad out there.
- Drive safely.
- Okay.
Thank you, sirs.
- No problem.
Thank you for your hard work.
You're welcome.
AUTOMATIC DOOR
Sir!
Sir, don't lock the door!
- There's someone inside.
- No way.
We just finished the rounds.
There's a typhoon.
There is no one here.
Did you see a cargo truck
unload materials earlier?
I did see a truck unloading just now.
That's the one, isn't it?
XIAOMA MOVERS PROFESSIONAL SERVICE
SHEN RUOXIN
Hi. The number you've dialed…
Hello?
Can you contact the crew
who just made a delivery?
I'm looking for my colleague.
Okay, thank you.
Hello?
Su Yang, is Ruoxin back?
No.
I'm sitting outside Ruoxin's home
with my laptop.
Hello?
Your colleague
should still be in the office.
Our crew is on their way back.
My charger.
Where's my charger?
Is there a blackout?
Why is there no electricity?
AUTOMATIC DOOR
Is anyone there?
Subtitle translation by: Coleen Chua