- Ruoxin.
- Come in.
Why so much stuff?
Your mom bought these.
She met Mr. Xu downstairs
and they're having a talk
so I brought these up.
My mom is with Mr. Xu?
Ruoxin.
Yes?
I won't bother you.
I'll get going.
Okay.
- Ruoxin.
- Yes?
If you encounter any unhappy events,
don't forget to tell me.
I might not be of help,
but I can share your frustration.
Okay. I'll do that.
Also, I…
Sijia and I would like
to treat you to dinner
as gratitude for taking care of us.
Let me know the time.
- Bye.
Qi Xiao.
You have…
to take care of yourself in Shanghai.
I'll get going now.
Mom.
What did you talk about with Mr. Xu?
I sent my car for maintenance today,
that's why Mr. Xu drove me home.
Don't overthink.
I didn't overthink.
Don't worry.
He is your boss.
We met and exchanged a few greetings.
Can I act like I don't know him?
Mom,
why did you buy so much stuff for me?
These are Shanghai specialties.
They have been your favorites
since you were a kid.
Nowadays, everything is online.
Even if it's not,
I can give you my address in Shenzhen,
and you can send them to me.
There are too many things,
my luggage can't fit all.
Express delivery takes days,
and these can be checked-in.
I don't mind buying them.
So why do you mind bringing them?
When you miss mom's cooking,
you won't mind these.
No problem at all. I'll bring them all.
I'll pack them into boxes.
What is this mess?
Everything is scattered.
Mom.
I'll be heading out for a while tonight.
Where are you going?
To say goodbye to a friend.
Lower this a bit more.
IN THE BLUE SKY, STARLIGHT IS AROUND US
That's enough.
Take a look.
What else do you want to change?
It's good.
Send it to me.
Thank you Master Su for the design.
Are you sure you want
to put this on her page?
Will Ruoxin accept this confession?
I've even found a guy to do it.
Isn't this a bit too much?
I don't know why,
but I just can't say it to her face.
Are you sure
she'll check her official page?
What if she doesn't?
Unlikely.
She posts once every three days
and has never missed.
It's about time she updates.
Did you see the post I sent you?
And the official account?
Yes, I want you to hack into the account
and replace it with the image I sent.
As soon as possible. I'll wait.
Whether I succeed or not
all depends on this.
Pinch this.
Right hand.
Have you really made up your mind?
Yes.
Actually, going to Shenzhen
is not about the raise.
You know that too.
I think the most important thing
is to broaden one's horizon.
I like new energy vehicles.
I think this industry is very promising
and very meaningful.
Looking at you in high spirits
reminds me of my youth.
Dad, when I was young,
I couldn't understand you.
But now,
I finally understand.
I think in our lives,
we should do something we like
and it should be something meaningful.
Otherwise, our life will feel empty.
What did your mom say?
She didn't say anything this time.
She bought me a lot of stuff
as though
I'm getting married
with a bunch of dowries.
I'm only married to my job.
Don't get angry at your mom.
Since her stroke two years ago,
she didn't say it,
but she's worried about you.
She hopes
to see you marry
because she wants you
to have a good husband.
She must think
if something were to happen to her,
you have someone to take care of you.
I know.
But marriage is not something
that you can rush.
I'm not a child. I'm an adult.
I know what I'm doing.
But these past few years,
Mom's temper has never changed.
She can't understand
that she has her ideals
and I have my own ambition.
Back in those years,
when I wanted to leave,
she would fight with me every day.
I thought it's because
your college entrance exams
will be affected.
So when she suggested a divorce,
I agreed and left.
But later on, I realized
she was offered
a promotion to become a director.
After I left,
she needed to care for you
and let go of the opportunity.
Years later, when I recall this,
I feel guilty.
Yes, I've achieved my ideals.
But what about her?
She gave up her own to complete mine.
But Dad, this incident,
even after so many years,
why didn't she tell me?
You know her temper
and her headstrong character.
She'll never open up.
For you,
for this family,
she has sacrificed a lot.
I can't even compete with that.
That's why her accusations
and blames towards me,
I think
I deserve them.
That's why
make sure you call and talk to her
when you reach Shenzhen.
You know her temper
and her headstrong character.
She'll never open up.
For you,
for this family,
she has sacrificed a lot.
Mom, aren't you tired
after all this packing?
Go sit and rest for a while.
Why are you back so early?
You didn't pack a down jacket with you.
I know Shenzhen is warm,
but it will turn chilly after spring.
You have to be prepared.
Who's going to take care of you
if you fall sick?
Also,
in this book
are all your favorite dishes.
I've written everything down for you.
Don't be lazy.
You need to learn how to cook.
Don't just eat takeouts.
It's oily
and unclean.
Self-cooked food is better.
At this age,
don't just rely on facial masks.
Women should consume tonics.
Why did you pack your stuff?
Are you leaving too?
When you're not around,
I will move back to my place.
It's closer to the University for Seniors.
If you plan to stay long in Shenzhen,
I suggest
you rent out this place of yours.
Mom, your place is so old
and there's no elevator.
Your legs are hurting.
It's inconvenient for you.
Stay here and help me
look after my apartment.
That's enough.
I'll trouble you by being here.
I touch your stuff.
I know,
in these two months
the both of us
could live together for so long.
I'm so happy.
Don't worry.
I will take care of myself.
I've made up my mind.
I'm not leaving.
What?
Why not?
I don't want to.
I want to stay in Shanghai.
I say, child,
what's with this fickleness?
You flip faster than turning a page.
I can get a promotion anywhere,
even in Shanghai.
Why choose not to go?
Did Mr. Xu do something again?
It has nothing to do with him.
I don't want to leave.
I can't bear to leave Shanghai.
What was that?
What do we do with all this stuff then?
You scared me.
Unpack them.
No.
You've seen it 30 times.
You've reached 5 km with that pace.
Aren't you tired?
Do you think she has read it?
If she had,
she would have come down
and talked to you.
What should I do? How do I look?
Go inside!
Quick!
You haven't slept?
Ms. Zhou?
You see, I've bought a lot of stuff today,
so our fridge can't fit all
and we can't finish them.
I brought some for you and your friend.
Xinxin decided not to go to Shenzhen.
What?
She's not going to Shenzhen?
Yes, she's not going to Shenzhen.
Are you saying she's staying in Shanghai?
She's staying in Shanghai.
That's amazing!
- She's really not?
- What are you doing?
You've deafened an old lady.
Hurry.
Put it in the fridge.
My goodness, this kid.
- Bye.
- Rest early, bye.
Congratulations.
Congratulations?
What do you mean "congratulations"?
I'm finished!
What's the matter now?
You're finished if Ruoxin is leaving.
Now that she's not,
why are you finished?
No.
I thought she's leaving,
so I gambled everything.
Now that she's not, I…
How can we work together in the future?
Weren't you the one who said,
"I must confess that I like her"?
Who said,
"I'm prepared. I've decided"?
No, I have to remove the post.
Hey, something happened.
Can you go to the account
and remove the image?
Are you insane, dude?
I just uploaded it
and now you want it removed?
You think this is a minor advert?
Removing it takes time too.
How much time do you need?
The shortest time.
At least two hours
and at double the price.
Okay, the price is not a problem.
This isn't about money.
Quick. Faster.
I'm begging you.
Ruoxin hasn't come looking for me.
That means she hasn't seen it.
So there's only one way around it.
And what is that?
Stay close and stall her.
Coming.
Ruoxin, Qi Xiao has a bad stomachache.
The medicine he took is not working.
- Do you have medicine for gastritis?
- I do.
Is it serious?
Should he go to the hospital?
I'm not sure either.
Why don't you go check on him?
Okay.
You're screaming with pain.
Are you having stomach flu?
Don't take random medicines.
It must be stomach flu
because nowhere else hurts.
How painful is it?
It's like…
It's like a spasm. It comes and goes.
We need to go to the hospital.
I'll call my dad.
He's on duty today.
No. It's fine.
It's not my first time.
I know.
But you can't keep this up.
It's my phone. Give it to me.
Give it to me.
What are you doing?
I need to pick up this call.
Ziyan.
Shen Ruoxin,
why didn't you tell me about Shenzhen?
Come to the bar tonight and explain.
I just decided not to go.
I haven't had the time to tell you.
Why are you so ambiguous?
What happened?
Come here quickly.
I can't go. I'm at Qi Xiao's.
He's quite sick.
So I want to send him to the hospital.
I'll call you later.
I--
Him over friendship?
Where does it hurt?
Your stomach hurts?
I'm okay. It doesn't hurt anymore.
Doesn't hurt anymore?
I think it's because
I haven't had dinner.
I was hungry.
What's the time now?
Neither of you has eaten yet?
What do you want? It's my treat.
Hot pot.
You like hot pot.
You can't eat hot pot in this condition.
I can. Of course I can.
Hot pot is great. I want hot pot.
I'll do the booking.
A separate mix soup.
No.
Let Sijia do the booking.
Sijia said she knows
a delicious hot pot restaurant.
We were actually going to treat you there.
Then let me call Sijia to book.
Let Su Yang contact Sijia.
Give him a chance.
I'll contact Sijia.
It hurts again.
Can you eat hot pot? Let's not eat it.
Now it doesn't hurt anymore.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you mention Sijia?
Are you going to keep hiding from her?
Keep avoiding her?
Your love life is your--
Why drag me into it?
A friend in need is a friend indeed.
You must help me.
Let me tell you.
Our little friendship
is over.
Stop.
I tell you, today it's because--
What's the matter with you two?
- Nothing.
- This is the last time.
- If it doesn't work--
Ruoxin, how is it? Tasty?
Sijia, have you been here before?
How did you find it?
This place is a five-star.
I thought to share this place
if it's tasty.
But now we're here.
Right, I haven't ordered the drinks.
Order anything you like.
Ruoxin, try this.
You should eat. Aren't you hungry?
Right,
I'm hungry.
Eat more.
Ruoxin, I heard you're no longer
going to Shenzhen.
Yes.
Actually, I can't bear to leave everyone.
I knew you'd cherish us.
Sijia.
Today…
Are you and Su Yang okay?
We're fine.
We are alumni
and Qi Xiao's friends.
Ruoxin, do you want to order more?
Let's check online comments
- and see what else is recommended.
- No need.
No need.
Ruoxin, Qi Xiao and I invited you today,
so we'll do the ordering.
Qi Xiao, you order.
Right, I'm ordering. I'll do it.
Ruoxin, help me make a shabu-shabu.
How do you do it?
Seven to eight times.
I have some.
Ruoxin, help me make it. Yours is tastier.
Seven times is enough.
Help settle the bill.
I'll transfer you the amount.
- Bill, please.
- Yes.
The total is 794 yuan.
EYES OF THE SKY
Why is it not down yet, dude?
Can you do it faster?
I'm doing it now.
Stop urging when you need it
and don't need it.
- I'm trying.
- No--
Hello?
What should I do?
Serves you right.
- Is it done, Qi Xiao?
- Yes.
It's done.
- Ruoxin.
- Yes?
I'm too full.
Let's go somewhere else.
You guys want round two?
Ruoxin, let's go sing.
You, youngsters, go. I'm not going.
I want to rest early.
I have to get up early tomorrow.
Ruoxin, let's visit Ziyan at her bar.
She invited us last time.
Yes, I have never been there.
Ruoxin.
Let me give her a call.
No need.
Let's give her a surprise.
Something's not right about you guys.
- Not right?
- Yes.
- No.
- Everything is all right.
I'm happy you're not going to Shenzhen.
I'm so happy.
- Let's go, Ruoxin.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
- I'm almost done with work.
- Thank you.
EYES OF THE SKY
What's up with you today?
Nothing.
You have something to tell me?
You've been acting a lot today.
First, stomachache.
Then, hot pot.
Now, even at the bar.
What are you thinking about?
I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
Because you're not leaving.
Why don't I feel that you're happy?
I think you're nervous.
Nervous?
I'm not nervous.
I'm happy, from within.
Happiness from within.
Don't drink so much.
This is alcohol, not water.
None of your business.
Amazing!
Ruoxin, thanks for coming.
They insist on listening to the music.
Did you change band members?
EYES OF THE SKY
The drummer from before had already quit.
We used a temporary replacement today.
We're still trying to adapt.
Why not ask Ziyan then?
She formed a band in college.
She played the drum.
Really? She didn't tell me.
Amazing.
Are you talking about me?
I'm not a professional.
I was just playing.
Why not try it out?
You know all our songs
and you're familiar with the rhythm.
- Try--
- No.
Don't listen to her. I really can't.
You can.
You were the best girl drummer
in our school.
Ziyan, you're so cool. Show us.
Show us.
- Come.
- All right.
I know you can. Come on, show me.
Okay?
EYES OF THE SKY
Good!
Here. Let's drink.
Sijia, let's drink.
Let's drink. Come.
Good!
Morning, Mr. Xu.
Morning.
Mr. Xu, Ms. Shen brought that over
this morning.
A peculiar gift.
This is handmade by a designer's friend.
He kept the patterns of the log.
Refined, but not fancy.
When I first saw it, I felt it was unique.
It reminded me of my childhood
playing tops with my friends.
Can I interpret it as
you've given me your word?
- Mr. Xu.
- You decided not to go?
When we choose to leave,
it's inevitable that we'll feel nostalgic.
Shanghai has been your home
since you were young.
I understand your hesitation.
But such nostalgia
will keep you locked up
in your comfort zone
and come in the way
of your future developments.
Isn't it a pity?
That day…
When you said
you wanted to bring me to Shenzhen,
all I could think of in my head
is that finally, there's a reason
to leave Shanghai
and run away from my mom.
But after I returned home
and saw my mom packing for me
to leave for Shenzhen,
I realized at that moment,
escape in the name of self-improvement
is just me lying to myself.
It's not so much nostalgia.
It's my hope
that every choice I make
is pure and simple.
My mom is old.
She really needs me.
That's why I've decided
to stay here with her.
Is this your final answer?
Mr. Xu,
I'm very grateful
for all the opportunities you've given me.
From now on, in Shanghai,
I will do my best to cooperate
with you at the headquarters.
My intentions,
as you already know,
are very clear.
You are a good boss.
When I was about to fall,
you reached out to me
and turned me around.
I really appreciate our teamwork
and mutual trust.
I believe
this communication
is the best for us.
I…
respect your decision.
Mr. Xu.
I'm sorry for the promise
that I broke.
Actually, I'm quite satisfied.
This is the first time
you've expressed such thoughts to me.
The first time.
Although you refused to go.
This the first time
I felt our relationship
got a bit closer.
It's good.
I hope from now on,
aside from work,
I can have the honor to be
your old acquaintance?
Your friend?
Thank you for your understanding
and tolerance.
I hope,
as you stay here,
you will continue to be
as I first met you.
An ambitious person.
I will do my best
to cooperate with you.
All the best.
IF LIFE ONLY HAS…
The success of the New Energy Department
is all thanks to everyone's support.
Thank you for your hard work.
Tomorrow, I'll return to headquarters.
For the upcoming sales and PR work,
hopefully, everyone will keep it up.
Thank you, everyone.
What's important in sailing?
Helmsman.
Mr. Xu has always been
our company's winning general.
Mr. Xu,
I'm impressed.
Good work.
As the saying goes,
"The speed of the train
depends on its engine."
To be honest,
for me to be here today
is all thanks to Mr. Liu.
That's why today,
the one who needs to thank Mr. Xu
should be Ms. Shen.
As you all know,
Ms. Shen used to be
in the Administration Department.
It's hard to achieve any results there,
am I right, Ms. Shen?
Thank you for reminding me, Mr. Ruan.
This time, I was able
to succeed in my mission
because of Ms. Shen's contribution.
From now on, for affairs related
to the New Energy Department,
I'll have to bother Ms. Shen.
In terms of work,
you can connect with me directly.
If there are any problems,
come straight to me,
I will be in charge of the discussion.
I will definitely do my best.
Ms. Shen, congratulations.
I'll finish this glass.
It's up to you to drink or not.
We all know what this is.
Actually, life
is like a top.
Some people spin to survive.
Some people spin to profit.
Some people spin to dream.
In their course of spinning,
there will be those who'd give you a push
and those
who'd push you down.
But in the end,
only you have the final control.
Mr. Xu,
this hobby of yours
is quite unique.
Given to me by a friend.
- Right. Thank you once again.
- Yes.
Zhu Lin,
where's that wooden top in your shop?
Ruoxin bought it.
That one?
Yes.
The handmade one. There's only one.
I wanted to make one
as an ornament for the shop.
Ruoxin said she likes it
so I gave it to her.
But she said she's buying it as a gift
and paid me for it.
I couldn't say no.
Okay, I get it.
I have faith
that we'll meet again soon.
ANHUA
Mr. Xu.
Have a safe journey.
Mr. Liu.
Mr. Xu, have a safe journey.
Let's go.
Subtitle translation by: Eve Teh