Good morning, there.
Fadel, Fadel, Fadel!
You suddenly live at my pace.
Morning jogging, grocery shopping,
showing up at my burger joint,
and now frequenting the same gym?
Stop following me.
Don’t say I didn’t warn you.
Don’t you think we should
just keep it casual between you and me?
I don’t want no casual.
You’ve still got a lot to prove.
Make sure he knows he really matters to you.
You have a meeting with Senator Vichai at 4.30.
Right.
Then dinner with Mr. Boonterm at 7.
I’ve got all the documents prepared.
What about our important meeting?
They’re waiting in your office.
Good.
Don’t let anyone in there
until I’m done talking to them.
Yes.
Of course.
Ms. Lilly.
We need you to sign this month’s financial report.
You want me to sign it here?
Shouldn’t you have put that on my desk?
I’m sorry.
Your new job.
Who is he, Mother?
Someone important.
He’s a big shot.
Why does he deserve this?
I see him on the news for helping poor children
and charity.
He’s never done anything bad.
Bison, dear.
You’ve always been easily deceived by appearance.
It’s all for show.
He acts like a saint.
But it’s just a facade to mask all his crimes.
He’s the man behind corruptions, drugs,
human trafficking, and so much more.
It would take me forever to list everything.
But for this kill,
you need to make it a spectacle.
They need to send a message to the other big shots.
One more thing,
this could be dangerous.
But I believe in you two.
Of course, Mother.
But it’d be better
if you let me take a little break.
Fadel!
What’s the matter, Bison?
Do you want to stop?
Do I not pay you enough for this?
Well?
Or…
Are you seeing someone?
Well, Fadel?
Is your brother seeing someone right now?
You can tell me, love.
Well?
There’s no one, Mother.
I promise we’ll take care of this thing.
Don’t worry.
Don’t quit so soon, my dear.
Work with me.
We’re all each other’s got.
Right?
Excuse us.
I guess we’ll do it.
If you think Fadel and Bison might not make it,
do you want me to help them out?
You’re already doing well at the office,
and you’re not as adept on the field as they are.
You still have so much to learn.
One beer, please.
You’re always here alone.
Why not go have fun with everyone?
I’m good.
I’m having the time of my life here.
Hello. Hi.
Cheers.
Long live rock and rolls.
Oh, hey.
To think I’d run into you here.
You like heavy metal?
You don’t look the type.
You’re supposed to have fun with your friends
at a place like this.
You can’t just sit drinking looking mysterious.
Come on.
Let’s go dance with me.
I’ve made so many new friends already, you know?
No.
I can have a good time all by myself.
How’d that even work?
You need someone to “scream” with.
Well, whatever.
I’m here all the time anyway.
This place is so my thing.
I’ll make you scream with me one of these days.
Bro, I need a double.
Coming right up.
Double, it is!
Follow me, alright?
Double, huh?
Hey, I’ll be right back.
Did you know
they use heavy metal to torture prisoners
so they confess?
If I was the warden,
I wouldn’t do that.
What if it was me?
What’d you do
to torture the truth out of me?
Would you kiss…
or choke me?
You’ll know.
You look kinda sexy tonight.
Mind if I join you?
You’ve been following me.
Me?
This is the nearest onsen around here.
I’m a regular.
Maybe it’s you
who’s been following me.
You’ve got a tattoo on your back?
I didn’t notice it that night.
I was busy with…
With what?
Can I see?
“If I be…”
What does it mean?
“If you piss me off,”
“careful of my fist.”
Really?
Where is that from?
It’s from one of Shakespeare’s books.
Babe is a fan.
I asked him to pick some cool quotes for me.
This is my favorite.
It’s about bees.
“If I be waspish,”
“best beware my sting.”
Scary.
I’m just saying that.
You know I’m actually just a baby.
You’re much scarier than I am.
I’m scary?
Look at me.
Do I look like I can hurt anyone?
But I get what you mean.
If they did me wrong,
I’d get them back.
What’d you do to them?
You want to know?
Oww, hey!
That’s what they’d get.
That’s just a sample.
But if you don’t mean me harm,
then you have nothing to be afraid of.
Stop it.
Bye.
Anything worth reporting?
Did you follow me, Cap?
Well, it’s kinda my job to follow through.
All I know right now is that
they have the same mother,
but different dads.
Continue investigating.
Better yet, get inside their house.
I’m sure there’s some leads there.
You’re asking me to enter the tigers' lair here.
You know I could get clawed to death, right?
You can do it.
Up your game and gain his trust.
He’ll lead you right into his house.
Trust me.
What about the big brother?
How are you dealing with him?
You sure he won’t get in your way again?
My friend is handling him.
Does your friend know they’re hitmen?
No.
I’ll give you a fair warning.
Don’t tell anyone about this.
The more people know,
the more dangerous it is.
Good morning.
If you’re here, it’s clearly a bad morning.
Hey.
Starting the day off on the wrong foot
makes the whole day bad, you know?
Do you like doing cardio?
I hate doing cardio after weight training.
It’s boring.
I’m looking for some other form of cardio, though.
Is that all you think about all day?
Go jerk off if it bothers you so much.
I know I can do it alone.
But it burns more calories doing it together.
Is that why you won’t leave me alone?
You want to sleep with me?
May I?
I want your body and your…
Heart.
You’re not my type.
What’s your type, then?
Tell me!
I can be that for you.
Hey!
Excuse me.
What can we get you today?
Ground pork?
We grind… the pork ourselves here.
It will sure make some good burgers.
Do you work here full-time now?
If you’re here every day,
then I’m here every day.
I’ll give you some fresh meat daily.
Oh, you don’t want it?
My meat is sweet, I tell you!
Auntie, I’ll be back.
I have to win that guy over.
Alright.
I’m rooting for you.
Do your best.
Thanks.
Welcome to Heart Burger.
Please have a seat.
Here’s the menu.
What would you like?
One cheeseburger and some water, please.
Please have a seat.
Hello.
Here’s the menu.
Come on in.
This place is a must.
- It’s cheesy and juicy.
- I’ll be back to take your order shortly.
Come on in.
It goes down easy and agrees with your stomach.
Come on over.
Can I have a photo?
Of course.
Let’s do it.
One, two, three.
Alright. Thank you.
Come on this way.
Come here for some juicy and cheesy burgers.
It’s a must.
Don’t miss it.
Come right in.
- You won’t regret it—
- What the hell do you think you’re doing?
I’m spreading the word about your place.
I’m doing it for free, mind you.
Stop it.
I didn’t ask you to do this.
You didn’t have to.
It’s a great strategy to attract customers.
Don’t you know how many burger joints there are?
We gotta stand out to survive.
One more thing,
who would be able to resist
a handsome guy in a costume?
They’re here for my burgers,
not your theatrics.
Who knows?
Maybe they’re here because
the chef is so damn good-looking.
Don’t try to cozy up to me.
Why not?
Did that make you blush?
It did, didn’t it?
You’re blushing.
Take that thing off and go back to your garage.
Why?
I said take it off.
I won’t!
I said I won’t!
No!
You hungry?
That’s so cute.
Please come on in.
Welcome.
Leave my restaurant alone.
Shouldn’t you be cooking at a time like this
instead of telling me off?
Your brother isn’t even here to help.
But I am.
All I ask from you is a little decency.
No.
This is my job.
I can handle it myself.
Help me up.
I can’t get up.
Help me!
Keep it dry for the time being.
Make sure you avoid water.
Here as well…
No soap on your tattoo for the next seven days.
Of course.
Thank you.
What is this?
Are you getting lonely?
Is that why you called me over to your studio?
Well, you said I can’t go to your place.
And since Babe is home at night, I can’t have you over.
This is the only place we can meet during the day.
I don’t see an issue here.
We can just book a hotel.
Hotels are for hookups.
I want to see you every day.
Who meets their boyfriend at a hotel?
I’d prefer your place.
Jumping the gun, are we?
I’m not your boyfriend.
What are you talking about?
One more thing,
I don’t think Fadel will let you step foot inside my house.
So?
You called me over just to chat?
Look at this.
I called you over for the cat tattoo.
You left it here last time, remember?
You like it?
It’s nice.
But I don’t want a cat tattoo anymore.
I think it makes me look too cute.
I want something cool.
You can get any cuter than this?
I can barely resist you as you are.
Ow!
Do you like it rough or something?
Can you handle it?
If you like it, I can handle it.
What if I told you I’m into… bondages and whips?
Are you the S or the M?
I prefer to be in control.
You didn’t mention that the first night we met.
Who’d tell a total stranger their sexual preference?
Do you trust me now, then?
Not 100%.
What do I have to do
for you to trust me 100%?
We could be the perfect match.
Your stuff sure… fits me perfectly.