Kant.
I’m done running.
Five years behind bars…
That’s still better than running all our lives.
We have one day together.
I want to make the most out of it.
Let’s do something that will become good memories.
What you want to do, where to go, what to eat,
just let me know.
YEAR 1
What’s wrong?
No energy?
Yeah.
How’d I have any
when I barely got any sleep last night?
The guy next to me kept putting his leg on me all night.
We have to be here for five years.
Get used to it.
If he puts his leg on you,
just do the same to him.
Easier said than done.
Dude looks super scary.
Just exhaust yourself with exercises.
It’ll help you sleep at night.
Hey.
That’s my place.
Come on.
The equipment is for everyone, isn’t it?
What, pretty boy?
You wanna get in trouble?
It’s my workout time.
It’s not like you can book this in advance,
can you?
I don’t see anyone’s name on these things.
Or did your daddy book it ahead for you?
Hey, newbie.
You run your mouth.
Just watch your back.
A petite pretty boy like you is just my type.
You should be my plaything.
Let’s stay out of each other’s way.
You can exercise here all you want.
Why’d you let him have it?
It’ll just get to his head that he’s all that.
It’s not worth it.
We have to be here for another five years.
Don’t get yourself an enemy so fast.
How are you?
You have bags under your eyes.
Do you get any sleep at all?
Hardly.
I can’t really sleep much.
I’m worried about you…
Are you sure you got this?
Of course.
Don’t worry about me.
I’m just not used to it yet.
It’ll take some time.
What about you?
How are you?
I’m so-so.
Some TV star got a tattoo from me and posted it online.
People showed up at my studio after that.
So I’ve been busy lately.
But that’s good.
It’s making really good money.
You’re a celebrity tattoo artist now.
Don’t you forget me when you’re famous.
I won’t.
How could I?
You have my heart and my body…
Penguin.
Babe asked me to give you a book.
He said it’ll keep you company when you’re bored.
Thank him for me.
How are you?
I’m okay.
It’s not that bad here.
I’ll get by.
Really?
You sure you’re not saying that just to make me happy?
I’ve seen some interviews,
and the people who have been here said it was awful.
It’s not that bad.
I really miss you, though.
When you do, just come visit.
How’s the garage?
It’s been busy.
Dad’s pretty much retired,
so I’m taking over everything.
Do you know how my burger joint is?
The landlord sold the place.
But it’s still a burger joint.
Not a thing has changed.
Except the name, though.
I’ll find a way to buy it back when I’m out of here.
We can deal with that later.
If you can’t get the place back,
I’ll help you find another location.
Is there anything you want?
I’ll leave it with the warden.
I don’t want anything.
Just seeing your face will last me a whole month.
What did they feed you in there?
You’re way too sweet.
If you say such sweet things,
it’ll only make me want to hold you
and kiss you even more, you know?
Kant, I can’t do this.
Who’d be able to just watch their boyfriend go to jail, really?
The worst part is only getting a few minutes to talk to him.
I see him but I can’t touch him.
We’re so close but it feels so far.
I get your drift.
I wanna break through the bars just to get to him.
It makes me feel bad just seeing the look in his eyes.
Is there no way we could hold them in our arms again?
There’s a special visit day, but only once a year.
Once a year is hardly enough.
I think I have an idea
that will give us more than just a hug.
What are you thinking?
Hey, pretty boy.
Where are you off to?
Let’s have a little chat.
What do you wanna chat about now?
I gave you back your dumbbells, didn’t I?
They’re all yours.
I’m done lifting weights.
I want a different kind of exercise,
something strenuous and sexy.
Will you just leave me alone?
Be my baby,
and I’ll take you under my wing.
I promise you your life here will be darn comfy.
Not interested.
I have a boyfriend,
and he’s waiting for me out there.
He already takes good care of me.
How lovely.
Whatever your boyfriend can’t do,
I’ll do it.
Hey.
Let go of me!
Don’t think you can just make me your baby!
If you want a lover, then be nice and not force it on them!
I know I’m cute, but I can’t be messed with!
Hey, what’s going on here?
What are you doing?
He was trying to force me down, but I wouldn’t let him.
They’ll leave you alone from now on, I take it?
Being smashed by a dipper repeatedly did the job, I guess.
You’re lucky the warden was understanding.
Or else you’d have been locked up alone.
As if a man like me would let just anyone have me,
and he ain’t even good-looking.
Hey, you two.
I heard you worked in a restaurant when you were outside.
Yes.
I worked at a burger joint.
The kitchen is short-staffed right now.
Can you cook Thai food?
Yes.
I can make the basics like stir fried dishes and soups.
Good.
Go help out in the kitchen, then.
Of course.
Can I bring my brother with me?
I think I’ll need an extra pair of hands.
Fine.
Don’t let me see you two slacking off.
If you don’t do your job,
I’m putting you on crap-cleaning duty.
Oh, I won’t slack off at all, sir.
I’ll be the perfect sous chef.
Yes, chef!
Good.
Before you go to the kitchen,
make sure the floor’s clean.
Yes.
Of course.
Yes, chef.
Do your job.
What?
You want me to put you in jail?
Yes, Cap.
We want to go to jail.
You dimwits.
What do you want to go there for?
I wanna see my boyfriend.
You two are crazy.
Can’t you just visit them?
It’s not enough.
All we can do is talk to them through a glass window.
I want to touch him,
to feel him,
to hold him,
to kiss him.
And I want to…
You’re one crazy in love bastard.
So?
You’re gonna steal, kill, and sell drugs just to get locked up?
Think about it.
I literally just helped you wipe your slate clean.
That’s not what I have in mind.
I have a better way.
I just need you to pull some strings for us.
Do you know someone on the inside?
A few.
Don’t tell me you want me to help you reenact Prison Break?
Do you have a tattoo of a map or something?
You watch too much TV, Cap.
My plan is even better than that.
It’s so much better in the kitchen, don’t you think?
I can easily get through five years if we’re here all the time.
At least it’s something I’m good at.
You’re right.
I miss your cooking.
The last guy was too heavy-handed on the salt.
Thought I’d have to get my kidney replaced when I’m out.
Am I right?
Get your hands busy, not your mouth.
The prisoners will be here soon.
And don’t get too giddy,
’cause you won’t get to be in the kitchen all day.
You’re taking vocational training, too.
What kind of vocational training?
All sorts of kinds.
There’s carving, fortune telling, drawing, fixing cars.
All sorts of things for you to choose from.
Hurry up and finish it.
Yes.
I think I’ll go for drawing.
You wanna join me?
I don’t like drawing.
You go for it.
What will you do?
Just sit around being bored?
Don’t worry about me.
I’ll find something to do.
[VOCATIONAL TRAINING FOR PRISONERS: ART]
Hey, is this seat taken?
Nah.
You can sit.
Hey.
Where’s the teacher?
Are we allowed to just paint whatever we want?
He went to get more supply.
He’ll be back soon.
Sorry, guys.
I had to get us more supply.
Kant?
We’ll draw some flowers and vases today.
We’ll learn about light and shadow.
Has anyone taken an art course before?
So everyone has, except you.
Why did you want to study art now?
I think I’m too rough around the edges
and too brutish.
I think art might be able to soften me up.
Alright.
I guess I’ll have to pay attention to you especially
so you know all the basics.
[THE INSIDE OF AN ENGINE]
…It’s pretty exciting.
It makes you feel energetic and happy.
I’ll be teaching you the basics of auto repair today, though.
Let’s save dancing for later.
Oh, hey.
Don’t just stand there.
You wanna join this class or what?
I do want to join.
Is it okay if I don’t know the first thing about fixing cars?
It’s alright.
You’ll get to learn all about it.
If you want to, that is.
I’ll show you every nook and cranny of a car.
You’ll definitely find some use for what you learn from me.
But if you still can’t fix cars after that,
I’ll fix them for you.
You said you didn’t know the basics,
but you nailed this light and shadow lesson.
I have a gift for it, I guess.
There’s something you’re just good at without learning.
I guess I have nothing to teach you, then?
Do teach me.
I still need some advice from a pro.
Follow me.
You seriously broke your pencil?
Oh…
Yes.
I must have used too much strength when I was drawing.
It’s quite okay.
But we’re out of pencils right now.
I’ll go get some from behind the meeting room.
Sir.
I’m going to get some pencils for the students.
Yes.
Thanks.
Warden, may I go to the toilet, please?
I’ll be back to finish my drawing.
Told you I’d never stay away, didn’t I?
I thought you’d do something illegal just to get in here.
This is way better.
I get to be close to you
and to touch you just like I wanted to.
Style!
You’ll be in trouble if the guard sees you.
So?
Why would I come here if I don’t get to do anything with you at all?
I can’t help you.
You said you’d be patient,
and you’re already losing it?
A guy has wants and needs, you know?
Guys.
Do you mind putting the tools back in place when you’re done?
That’s all for today.
I’ll see you again next week.
I’ll make sure you can all run a garage one day.
Kant.
How’d you get here?
Let’s say I have some strings I could pull.
But you won’t get into any trouble for this, will you?
I’m worried about you.
Don’t be.
Captain talked to some people for me.
We just can’t be too obvious about this.
I’ll be coming here to teach from now on.
But.. won’t it be a waste of time for you?
Seeing you will make me happy.
I’ll get to meet you,
and touch you just like this.
I’ve been dying to do that since the moment I saw you.
You’re crazy.
Love will make people do crazy things.
Save your sweet words.
How did you get in here?
It’s thanks to Kant’s connections.
I’ll be teaching here regularly.
So I’ll see you every week.
You know…
You don’t have to do this.
I don’t mind seeing you once a month
or once every three months.
I did everything I could to be with you, you know?
You don’t appreciate that?
Or did you already find someone here?
I’d expect it of a popular guy like you.
Come here.
No matter where I am,
you’re the only one for me.
Once you’re done cleaning that,
put it back where it comes from.
Yes, sir.
I’ll see you again next week.
I’m counting on ya.
Well, what are we doing that needs hiding?
You’re the most important thing to me.