[Characters, actions, places, agencies, occupations, and events in the series are fictional and for entertainment onl
[and events in the series are fictional
and for entertainment only.]
[They are not intended to encourage any actions shown therein. Viewer discretion is advised.]
[Viewer discretion is advised.]
[Ghost Host Ghost House]
[Happy Birthday Kevin]
[Toth, Techit Panyanaraporn]
[Boy, Nattapon Wongwanit]
[Gon, Kasidech dechwongya]
[Lina, Watcharin Anantapong]
[Guide, Chawanwit Wongpong]
[Nutty, Natamon Chantarawipard]
[Ins, Lonlada Nananukul]
[Screenplay by Osan, Pluem and Vibie Gen Team]
[Executive Producer: Jebsit Dechboon]
[Assistant Executive Producer: Pawinee Pinnares]
[Producer: VIBIE LIVE Application]
[Ghost Host Ghost House]
[Director: Kwankaow]
[Previously]
It's my first time seeing See-Nam play a guitar.
That's so cool.
Whoa, that's so beautiful.
This flower is called Tuberose,
it can hide the smell of funeral.
Thank you for all your help.
I'm sorry I bother you quite often.
You can see me now?
See-Foon, let us know what you're doing.
It's not your fault at all, dad.
The time is up?
There, there.
I promise I'll be there for you
until all these come to an end.
What's shaking?
My heart, maybe. You're so cute.
If it is shaking this hard,
you should see the doctor.
Your phone is ringing.
Hello.
Yes, it's me.
Huh? What did you just say?
Oh… Oh…
Sure, I'm free to do that.
Alright, sir. Sure.
You can contact me through this number.
Alright, alright.
Bye.
You…
What's that? Who called you?
I'm so happy. I've never expected that.
Tell me about it first.
I don't know how to react now.
Well…
I was reached out to for a commercial.
And it's not even an extra role.
This is a main supporting role.
Seriously? What commercial is that?
Prawn crackers.
Are you going to be the prawn?
I'm willing to be the cracker.
I'm so glad.
This is my first gig ever.
I'm so happy for you.
You'll do a good job.
I'll take you there if they allow me to.
Am I going to be famous now?
I'm getting goosebumps.
Should I practice answering
interview questions now?
Are you for real?
Hello, it's Pluem Pitipong.
If you want to take pics with me,
please turn off the flash.
I've heard that you became well-known
after taking a prawn cracker role?
That's correct. I've done my best
for every opportunity.
On the day I got the prawn cracker role,
I did my best like in any other role.
So it's not surprising that
this handsome, talented guy
has come this far.
Wow…
You're not giving time
for others to compliment you.
I'm afraid no one will do that.
Oh, you have to go to the audition first
to know if you get that role, right?
Yes.
They asked me to go next Monday.
If I get this gig, I'll get to go to the beach.
But they haven't told me where it is.
If I get this gig, come with me, alright?
Please…
But it's a shooting set, isn't it?
Wouldn't I get in the way?
Well, you can just wait for me there.
And… You've never been
to a Thailand's beach, right?
You'll be so in love with it, I promise.
You won't want to return to the States.
But if I don't get this gig,
I'll save up so we can travel together.
You're not going back soon, right?
Umm…
So it's settled then. You'll be
there with me if I get this gig, right?
The beach?
If you really get it,
can I take someone with me, too?
This is Auntie Jeab when she was young.
So beautiful.
Of course. My painting skill never fails.
No, he referred to me.
Compliment your wife, sometimes.
You painted this when you were at the beach?
No, the twins were born
before we could make the trip.
Yes, the trip failed completely.
We had to handle with all the chaos then.
Then I'm pretty sure now
that my thought is right.
Would you like to go to the beach
for your honeymoon?
Maybe, that's your last mission.
What made you think a
honeymoon is our last mission?
I think I understand what Kevin thinks.
Kevin thinks that both of you
only focus on taking care of others
and forget to live like a couple.
And once you had kids, you
had to be a mother and a father
and forgot your roles as spouses.
I think the kids are right.
Since we had See-Nam and See-Foon,
we forgot to take care of our relationship.
We were busy fighting one another.
Actually, reminiscing some old memories
isn't a bad idea.
Honeymoon now? As ghosts?
Why not?
That way, even death can't do us part.
Okay. I'm in.
But we'll all have to go together.
Both of us will exchange our points
for the last day,
so both of you can see us there.
Is it really a good idea?
What if it isn't your last mission?
You're going to lose all of your points.
No worries.
Even if it's not our last mission,
at least we can spend our last moment together.
I'm okay with that.
I think so.
Since Kevin arrived,
we've not got any photo together.
Agree.
Because we don't appear in photos, right?
Yes.
So I want you… Kevin.
I want you to see our happy moments.
Keep that your last memory of us
- before we disappear forever.
- That's right.
That's great. Let's go together.
I thought it was so-so at first.
But it's great, actually. Right, honey?
Yeah. I don't know why I feel excited
all of a sudden.
Auntie Jeab, Uncle Art.
How many hours do you have left?
More than enough.
They're enough for us to
see the sunset with you.
Hold on, don't you go shooting
the commercial, Pluem?
The shooting starts tomorrow.
I came here one day earlier.
I knew you were going to get that role.
Good job, my dear.
You're a star as you have wanted, huh?
It's still a long way to go.
But how can I be unknown with
this handsome face?
Pluem, Kevin, go take a stroll.
Let's meet up here later.
Or do you want a double date?
I'm just kidding.
Look at you. I know you
want to spend time together.
I won't bother you anymore.
Right?
Let me join you, please.
I'm sick of Pluem now.
Hey.
Well.
Who asked me to call every single night?
Who asked me to be by your side
until you fall asleep?
Why did you spill that?
That's enough. Stop fighting.
Our time is short.
We'll go have fun. We can't wait.
Yes.
Don't forget to come back
this evening before the sunset.
Okay.
- We're going now.
- Okay.
See you later.
We've got to go now, bye-bye.
Want to go now?
Let's go.
Dried squid… Do you want to try it?
How much is this?
- You want take some pics?
- Okay.
Thank you.
You're done dressing up?
It's almost the time.
The sun almost sets.
You.
I don't want to go there…
Come with me.
They must want to see us there.
Let's send Auntie Jeab
and Uncle Art off together.
I'll choose a necklace for you.
This one.
Let me see.
Let's go.
Your shirt is nice.
Your necklace is also nice.
You're just missing…
a sweet smile on your face.
You're just so cute.
Come on.
Are you okay, honey?
It's the last day… Huh?
- I know, right.
- It's the last day.
Right.
I would have come here when…
Auntie Jeab, Uncle Art!
You…
We'd better stand right here from this far.
Fold it up to your knees.
Are you okay, honey?
Slowly. Don't rush, honey.
Come on.
Hold my hands. Okay.
Let go of my hand. Let's sit up there.
I'll find a way up there.
Slow down, honey. You'll slip.
Slow down.
1… 2… Alright?
- Where is it?
- Okay…
That spot is better, honey.
I told you the view looked good from here.
Here it is.
That's all fine.
Even if it's not our last mission,
at least we can spend our last moments together.
I'm okay with that.
You'll see our happy moment.
Keep your last memories of us
- before we disappear forever.
- Yes.
I already sent everyone off.
Why don't I feel good at all?
How can it feel good?
In the end, it's still a loss.
Don't pretend like you're not sad.
Just know that you've done your best all along.
Don't feel sorry about it.
Anything else you want to do?
I don't want to go back to the hotel now.
Actually, there is something I want to do.
What is that?
Well, taking a ride or two around town…
Something like that.
Just that?
I rarely go on a trip.
Taking a tour will do me some good.
And another thing is…
The sea at night has its own charm.
I think there are still some mini-buses around.
I'll ask if we can rent one.
That's a good idea. I want to
take a ride around town, too.
Let's go.
- Mister.
- Anything, sir?
- Is this available?
- Yes.
Can you take us on a tour?
Alright.
- Can I ask you something?
- Tell me.
Attach this.
Awww.
- Make it obvious. Don't be subtle.
- Choose a spot.
This is great.
Attach it. Make it obvious.
- What about over there?
- Okay.
- Sure, I got you.
- Thank you.
- Let's get on the bus.
- Alright.
The night sea hits different…
Not bad.
I've seen one more beautiful than that.
Where?
Right here.
I'll bite your finger off.
How is it? Is that kissing scene good to go?
- Ouch..
- Well.
It hurts.
So stop being a pervert.
- Pluem…
- Huh?
I still haven't thanked you.
Since I've been here,
you've always helped me out.
You pick me up and drop me off.
Come after me to dangerous places.
And you've been with me through thick and thin.
I just… I want to be the person
you'll see when you turn around.
Thank you, Pluem.
Hey, UFO…
What? Where?
[Will you be my boyfriend?]
Will you?
For all that time…
You've not felt anything?
Of course, I have.
Overwhelmingly, actually.
I just…
Can you give me some time?
What time do you need?
Time to forget him?
Or time to love me?
Jake?
You can't forget him, right?
No.
The question should be…
I still can't make you forget, right?
Are you scared?
Then just don't watch it.
I'm not scared…
If we die,
will we become ghosts?
Maybe…
if we still have worries.
If you die,
will you disappear or…
stay around as a ghost?
I might be a ghost then.
Really? What are your worries?
I'm worried about you.
I can take care of myself.
Don't treat me like a kid.
You're sure of that?
I do everything for you though.
So
if you die one day,
You'll be by my side as a ghost, right?
Well,
please take care of me until I'm 80.
Isn't that too long?
You won't let me move on?
Well, how about…
I'll be there until you find someone
who loves you and takes care of you.
My worries
will be gone by then.
Hi, Mrs. Kim.
Kevin's speaking.
Sorry to bother you.
But I cannot reach Jake.
He missed classes and… ah…
And…
Calm down, Kevin.
We've been thinking how to tell you about Jake.
Listen.
He passed away.
The doctor diagnosed
that he had acute heart failure.
We've never thought about this before.
However,
I know Jake wants you to be strong
and don't worry about him anymore.
Take care.
♫ Oh Susanna, don't cry for me ♫
♫ We had some good years, so
let me be ♫
♫ The world goes on I sing my song ♫
♫ I gave my own true love for you to see ♫
♫ Oh Susanna, don't you cry ♫
You told me…
♫ Hold the tears back ♫
You'll be around.
You'll never go elsewhere.
If you're still around,
I will do every single way
so we can see each other again.
♫ Dear friends and gentle hearts ♫
♫ The time has come to part ♫
♫ The jig is up now so lay me down ♫
♫ Swim when the world gets dark ♫
♫ Oh, I love you from the start ♫
♫ Listen to the words I sang to yo. ♫
- When will you be ready?
- Just a few seconds.
- Ah. This is Poom's scene?
- Yes.
The person holding a new flavor is… who?
- I'm Pluem.
- Ah, has someone given you a brief?
Yeah?
Ah, okay.
Oh, up your energy, okay?
Drowsy face won't do.
Alright, keep it going.
Okay, are you ready?
The backstage, ready?
Sound, camera, ready.
Look at the camera #4.
Alright, set.
And… action…
The old one isn't bad, why change?
Cut!
Pluem, can't you remember the script?
Do you need someone to review it with you?
I remember it. Sorry about that.
Build your emotion first.
I think you're not ready.
I'm ready. Sorry about that.
He's ready, let's continue shooting.
Don't worry, I understand.
It's not usually done in one take.
Relax and redo it, alright? Don't give up.
Alright, ready?
Let's do it all over again. Sound, camera.
Set. And… action.
The old one isn't bad, why change?
I know the old one is great.
But the new one want to take a fighting chance.
If you never open up your heart,
how can you know the new one is also great?
Latecomers also have a heart, you know?
Just like the new flavor of this cracker.
Lava Mala. Spicy, hot, delicious,
and flavorful.
I want you to try.
If you still like the old flavor, that's fine.
But please give the new one a try.
Take. Cut.
I like it. I like it. Okay.
But it's not what's in the storyboard.
- Not even close to that?
- Yes.
But his acting kills it.
I like it. Everyone likes it. It just works.
Pass. Pass. You passed…
It's okay, I got you.
You just had a fight with your partner?
When my cat died,
I secretly cried on the set like you did.
Don't give up.
Alright, okay.
Next scene, eat the Mala cracker.
Pluem, change the outfit.
Tomorrow, 7 A.M.
See me at the lobby.
The team will give us a lift to the van.
[BOARDING PASS BKK TO SEA]
It's really hot…
Please get on the bus.
- Is the shooting done?
- Yes.
Don't worry. I'll carry this for you.
Both of you get on the bus
and when you reach the destination,
get in the van there.
Okay? Follow me.
Aw.
Done?
Please get on the bus.
Don't be dramatic.
Boys, are you making room for a soccer match?
Move.
Move, there are two more.
A bit more, please.
Start the engine, bro.
[Will you be my boyfriend?]
♪ Happy birthday, Happy birthday ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Make a wish before blowing the candles.
I must have left one at the beach.
[AIEMPHON STUDIO]
[Director: Kwankaow]
[Next Episode]
During that time,
though it's been just a few month,
I've learned so many things.
He once told me that
he wanted to be the person
I'd always see when I turned around.
Thanks for keeping this for me.
It's like… finding a
precious thing I've lost.
I don't want to wait anymore.
I don't want you to wait either.
This song forever.
What song is it?
Pluem changed into this outfit.
- Because before coming here…
- Why is it so special?
Before coming here, his outfit was so lame.
A set like this…
- At that time, I believed you.
- Oh… okay.
- Take it easy.
- How are you?
Am I still not handsome? Handsome?
- You chose it yourself.
- Handsome.
- You chose it. It'd better be good.
- Good, good.
Why do you seem so unwilling?
The snacks are over there.
Boy, can you take them off
and cross your eyes?
- I can't.
- Please show me the white one.
But I'm still cool and handsome though.