[Characters, actions, places, agencies, occupations, and events in the series are fictional and for entertainment only.]
[They are not intended to encourage any actions shown therein. Viewer discretion is advised.]
[Ghost Host Ghost House]
[Happy Birthday Kevin]
[Toth, Techit Panyanaraporn]
[Boy, Nattapon Wongwanit]
[AIEMPHON]
[Gon, Kasidech dechwongya]
[Lina, Watcharin Anantapong]
[Guide, Chawanwit Wongpong]
[Nutty, Natamon Chantarawipard]
[Ins, Lonlada Nananukul]
[Screenplay by
Osan, Pluem and Vibie Gen Team]
[Executive Producer: Jebsit Dechboon]
[Assistant Executive Producer: Pawinee Pinnares]
[Producer: VIBIE LIVE Application]
[Ghost Host Ghost House]
[Director: Kwankaow]
[Previously]
Your father's car also hit my family's, didn't it?
I can tell you're dumped by your boyfriend?
Why didn't they let me die instead of Pa?
I told you not to bother Kevin now.
I happened to know that
Kevin wanted to see his best friend
when he studied aboard.
The twins already had
exchanged their points for you.
You want me to be your witness?
I'll give you this gift.
Hey!
You startled me!
Well. You flinched when you saw me?
But you smiled when you saw a ghost?
You're not rude to me anymore?
I didn't mean to do that.
What are you doing here?
Well…
I want to talk to you about something.
Just say it.
I'm so sorry that I talked
bad with you that night.
You come to my apartment, it only my fault.
So, sorry.
I accept your apology.
Are done with your business here?
Have a safe journey home.
Say it slowly, I can't quite catch up.
You know what? I had Prim's e-dictionary
say each word for me. It took days.
And you acted like you're a smart boy.
Umm.
Well…
Does an American boy here teach English?
You have to ask him if he is still mad.
You…
I'm really sorry.
I lost control that day.
And, I'm sorry for blaming you like that.
But today, I already understand
that it was no one's fault.
I was acting like a rabid dog.
What?
Yay…
Stop. Hands off.
What's wrong?
Can't I hug you? I miss you.
I'm going to collect the dry clothes.
Let the brave butler take care of the chores.
So…
where are the others?
I let them rest inside the house.
There is a big event tomorrow.
What is it?
Aiemphon family's Funeral.
Uh…
Where? Do you want me to contact
the temple for you?
It'll be held here.
Auntie Jeab told me that no one
in the family had had an official funeral.
So I wanted to hold it for them.
I'd like to make it a welfare party
in which everyone can enjoy
and doesn't cry.
I don't know when Auntie Jeab and
her family will disappear.
As all of them are present right now,
I want to hold a funeral for them.
That's true.
I'll help you with that.
Let's buy flowers tomorrow.
I remember that See-Nam likes white roses.
Are you still mad at me?
That "talked bad with you" act you pulled
made up for it.
Can I hug you now?
Up to you.
What about kissing?
Do it if you want to.
And what about the lips?
Do it then. It's your funeral?
Oops.
I'd better deal with the clothes.
- Hey. Hey.
- You'll get hit.
What kind of flower are those?
Look at my rose.
- Nice? Nice.
- Yeah. What about mine?
No.
You're the host. Go wait inside.
But I want to help.
Let me pluck the leaves for you.
Get inside now.
Get in the house.
Pluem, what's wrong with your eyes?
Hurry up.
Mom, Pluem's eyes hurt.
- Mom, do you have any eyedrops?
- That is not it.
Could've just told me
that you wanted some alone time with Kevin.
Okay, I'll wait for you inside.
Make it beautiful, guys.
This ghost kid is such a pain in the neck.
Phantom pain.
He's too young to die, do you agree?
It's fate.
That's all the time he had in this world.
When several loved ones pass at once,
it really gives you that survivor's guilt.
Don't think like that.
Do you know this flower?
No, I don't.
This flower is called Tuberose,
it can hide the smell of a funeral.
But I kind of like it.
Though it doesn't have a wonderful meaning,
used to hide the stink,
this flower reflects the reality that
pain doesn't go away.
It's just hidden
so we can move on with our lives.
Just like what you said to me,
you told me to keep my sorrow in my pocket.
Here.
Today,
I understood what dad said to me.
He said that,
in every loss,
there is something beautiful left behind.
- Ah, we started this off with the Thai BBQ.
- Umm.
- So we should end it with the BBQ.
This is my secret recipe.
BBQ pork with egg yolk dip.
I want to taste this so badly.
Umm.
Since we passed away,
I could eat normally
but we never tasted the flavors.
What can I do to make you taste it?
I have no idea.
But that's alright,
I'm just glad we can have a meal together.
Well…
Try my method.
Maybe, it'll work.
Normally, we have to ignite
incense sticks before praying.
We should try that..
Blow it gently.
Does it work?
Mom, your pork is very salty…
Oops, really? Let me try.
Very salty, honey.
And you all never told me about this.
I can't taste it,
how can I know it's this salty?
Let's eat.
Woah, I almost forgot this flavors.
Seriously? Your first choice of taste
after death is a cabbage?
Try this pork belly.
Better not. It's fatty.
Oh, right.
Wait, are you insane?
I'd better eat the cabbage.
The cabbage tastes much better.
Let's eat up.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- That's not salty, I guarantee.
Let's have the pork.
Hey.
- Is it delicious?
- Yummy.
Come on.
- Yeah.
- Cheers, kids.
(text)
Tune the guitar for me.
Okay.
I'll do it for you.
Alright.
I'm sorry, dad.
What's the matter?
After we died,
I was always aware
that I always behaved badly toward you.
It's not your fault to be mad at me.
Right?
I-I-
I was the one that…
Not like that.
It's not your fault.
I shouldn't have blamed you, dad.
I know…
You are willing to accept all the blame…
because...
you love me.
I'm sorry, dad.
Don't be mad at me, okay?
No worry.
Why are you laughing?
I laughed at you..
The last time you cried
with the running nose was
when you crashed your bicycle
and lost your teeth.
Do you remember that?
Of course.
Stop mocking me.
Why are you talking about
this stuff out of the blue?
Don't worry, dear.
At least…
I'm glad we had a talk.
Don't cry anymore, my child. Don't cry.
I love you.
You.
It's my first time seeing
See-Nam play a guitar.
That's so cool.
Ask her who the teacher is.
You taught her?
Yes.
I didn't know who she was pursuing.
She just came to me and
asked me to teach her that.
You seem very close to Auntie Jeab's family.
Yes.
But I never wanted to
come to their funeral like this.
- You.
- Hmm?
We're here to enjoy ourselves today.
I'm sorry.
See-Nam..
See-Nam.
See-Nam…
This isn't funny at all..
What's happening, See-Foon?
You two haven't
done some terrible things, right?
Leave him alone for now.
Show me your points..
Are you insane?
What have you spent them on?
They redeemed their points for me.
For what?
They wanted me to meet my dad,
so they combined their points.
Pluem, you asked them that?
How can you do this to me?
- I'm so sorry.
- Sorry?
Will See-Nam come back?
Uncle Art, Pluem's dad died…
Uncle Art.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know it would end like this.
Honey, See-Nam is our talented daughter.
She's the older sister to See-Foon.
She's a sister who loves Pluem.
I believe See-Nam was willing
to help Pluem see his dad.
I asked for See-Nam's help.
- No, it's not like that, kid.
- I was wrong.
No, it's not. Don't say that.
Don't say that… It's not like that.
See-Nam isn't here because of me.
Foon.
- It's entirely my fault.
- Foon.
- See-Foon..
- Pluem and I will look after him.
See-Foon, are you in here?
See-Foon, stop that.
What are you doing?
What are you going through her things?
See-Foon, tell us what you're doing.
I have to find out
what the last thing See-Nam
wanted to do before death.
See-Foon, calm down.
I shouldn't have asked See-Nam for her points.
If she'd had points left,
she could've exchanged them for Last Day
and rest in peace.
She wouldn't disappear, like this.
Kevin…
What is it?
This box rings a bell for me.
This is the song See-Nam wrote.
There's something written here.
See-Foon…
I'm being serious.
There's no way we can find out her last desire.
But if you want to do something for her,
both of us will help you with it.
Are you ready?
Oh, the users are flooding in.
Hello, Momo.
Hi, SomPan.
[MoMolsMe Lv.1
"Oops, who is that?"]
Oh, this is my friend named Pluem.
[MoMolsMe Lv.1 "Just a friend?"]
"Just a friend?"
Well…
Well, I don't know.
"He was just your gardener last time."
[KhimZa Lv.14
"Yeah, he's your boyfriend now? Hehe."]
Everyone, stop teasing.
[YimZa Lv.34 "I'm blushing?"]
Alright, I asked Pluem to join me today
because I want to show you all something.
[Chorcher Lv.16 "What is that?"]
[Por.Lor.Yo Lv.44 "You're odd today."]
[Por.Lor.Yo Lv.44 "Oops, guitar."]
Well, I want you to listen to a song.
It's very meaningful to me.
Because…
My younger sister wrote this.
[Por.Lor.Yo Lv.44
"Why don't you let her sing?"]
But the song owner can't come here
and sing it for you.
I'll let Pluem sing it instead.
[SomPan "It must be good," Momo "She wrote it?"]
[Por. Lor. Yor. "So excited to hear it."]
Right, Pluem?
Umm, yes.
You alright?
Stage fright. I'm about to piss my pants now.
Let's sing this song now, alright?
Come on.
♪ In the night with a gloomy sky ♪
♪ I can see the grey horizon from afar ♪
♪ my heart is trembling and lonely ♪
♪ This starless night is so dark ♪
♪ I want someone, just someone ♪
♪ Someone that saves me from loneliness ♪
♪ Looking into your eyes our hearts are close to one another ♪
♪ The empty world is no longer empty with you hidden in there ♪
♪ Your smile is so beautiful ♪
♪ The grey sky has disappeared ♪
♪ But I'm still too scared to say that word ♪
You're so awesome, Nam.
2... 3.
1… 2… 3…4
5… 6…7…8
♫ I want to say I love you ♫
♫ I love you with all my heart ♫
♫ Every time we talk more or get closer, ♫
♫ My love for you is doubled ♫
♫ I'm telling you, I have feelings for you ♫
♫ since the first time we met ♫
♫ I keep you in my heart and dream ♫
♫ I want to be right next to you ♫
♫ I will say, "love you" ♫
We should split here.
- I'm joining you later.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
- See you.
♫ Tonight the sky is full of stars ♫
♫ I look at the moon and think of you ♫
Umm, I'm See-Nam.
You're Prim, right?
Oh, yes.
Can I have your phone number?
♫ The empty world is no longer empty with you hidden in there ♫
What for?
I want to know you better.
♫ That even the blue of the sky fades ♫
Here you go.
Thanks.
Can I call you sometimes?
Sure.
♫ I love with all my heart ♫
♫ Every time we talk more or get closer ♫
♫ My love for you is doubled ♫
♫ I'm telling you, I have feelings for you ♫
♫ since the first time we met ♫
♫ I keep you in my heart and dream ♫
♫ I want to be right next to you ♫
♫ I will say, "love you" ♫
Hey, these are kittens, aren't they?
Where did you them?
I just picked them up.
Some chased me and I ran away.
Don't you know it's sinful to
split the mother from the children.
Come on. Return them to their mommy.
I didn't intend to sin.
After I know which one is See-Nam,
I will return the rest to their mother.
Which one?
Which one is her?
What are you doing?
You told me that, didn't you?
You said after the points run out,
we will be reborn as cats or dogs.
I'm just here to ask which one is See-Nam.
So I can ask Pluem and Kevin
to take care of her.
Are you insane? That was just a joke.
Just a joke?
Is it funny to you?
An old man bullying kids?
You're so mean.
Learn to restrain your feelings.
Your family passed away already.
Don't forget that.
Your remaining existence in this world
isn't permanent.
Instead of being sad like this,
you should make your remaining time count.
Your time isn't much now.
Come on, find your last mission.
Complete it before your time is running out.
Let's play the roller coaster.
Have you been ordained?
Ordained?
Yes, I have.
Do you have a crush?
What are you asking, Pluem?
I'm still young.
But I had a crush on an intern teacher.
You're blushing.
You had a crush on a teacher?
But she's married now.
Or… you wanted some adult experience.
Pitipong.
(dialogue)
Talking about teachers,
is your last desire related to school?
Do you have a friend
you still want to say goodbye to?
Of course, I do.
Kevin, do you remember
what I talked to you in your dream?
I was stressed out. My friends didn't
help me with a project.
Ah.
And I deleted their names
from the report.
After that, I was boycotted by the group.
They threatened my classmates
not to talk to me, be close to me, or hang out with me.
I had to have lunch all by myself for months.
In the end, I had to be their servant.
I had to buy food & drinks for them
and did their homework.
If I didn't obey them,
I wouldn't have any friends at all.
Why didn't you tell me that?
What would you do? Punch them at the school?
No.
At least, I could report them to the teachers.
I already did…
I told the teacher, dad, and mom about it.
But no one really helped me with that.
That means your last mission
is vengeance?
I think so.
They hurt me.
They have to pay.
Are you sure you have nothing else
you want to do?
That's the only unfinished business in my life.
Alright,
what do you want? Let us know, boss.
[GHOST ID: GH202215347 LAST DAY]
Can you see me now?
Thank you for your help.
And I'm sorry for bothering you.
Are you sure of that?
Actually, you can live for a while
with the remaining points.
You really want to exchange it
for the Last Day?
You can still change your mind.
I've thought it through.
There is a place I want to take
Pluem and Kevin to.
Good luck.
Hey, be careful, kid.
Hey, do you want to die?
Are you okay, See-Foon?
I used to think that
being dead is better than living.
I don't feel the punch anymore.
But now, It's a shame.
I don't have a chance to live
in this world anymore.
What are you going to do, See-Foon?
Everyone…
We have to submit this next class.
Please help me with this.
Let me see.
It's almost done, isn't it?
Just finish it and we're all done.
Yea, right. You almost finished it.
We can watch a movie together right after.
Don't you want to watch a movie with us?
Or, You don't want to come with us, Donut?
You like being alone, having lunch,
or going places by yourself?
We can give that privilege to you.
What's wrong? Are you mad at us?
No, I just misspelled something.
Can you hand me a correction pen?
Why don't you come and pick it yourself?
Just quickly hand her that so it can be done.
Holy shit.
Teacher… Help us, please. The ghost scared us..
What ghost, Natchaya?
This is just planning. You seem so satisfied.
Your plan is so outdated.
Are you sure you want to do that?
Hey.
You'll be mocked up by other ghosts
with that plan.
Pluem…
- Don't tease him.
- What?
You smiled. I saw that.
Finish what you want to do.
I'm feeling hungry, standing here.
"Instead of being sad like this,"
"you should make your remaining time count."
Actually, I think we still have time.
Do you want the same topping?
Yes, miss.
What topping?
Chili paste, pork floss,
and strawberry jam on top.
Huh?
It's good.
This kid ordered that every day.
But he's been gone for a while.
It's really good, Pluem.
- Here you go, the first one.
- Thank you.
Here it is, See-Foon.
Where is he?
He must be somewhere around here.
How can he be gone?
His merit points aren't running
to zero like See-Nam, right?
He exchanged them with the Last Day, didn't he?
Or his time limit is over?
No, it's not. I remember he has
more than an hour left.
Where is he then?
Oh, the crepe is ready?
Oh… See-Foon…
It's good, isn't it?
Very tasty.
This combo is weird but good.
I ate it every day before going home.
I wanted to take a friend of mine there.
But I didn't have any friends.
We're eating it with you now.
Or you want me to say I'm here
with you as your older brother?
Pluem, you know what…
I want to be like you.
You're so cool.
You can do so many things.
You can take care of your family.
I wanted to grow up as great as you.
For Kevin,
you're so kind to me.
Poor me…
I rarely met you.
Otherwise, we could be closer siblings.
But both of you don't need to be sad, OK?
I've learned that
we shouldn't feel bad about the past.
Just make the most of this moment. That's all.
Like, me sitting here and
having a crepe with you.
This is the best moment ever.
I wouldn't trade it for anything.
Are you leaving now?
What about the revenge?
Actually, I didn't come here for the revenge.
It's kind of odd…
I've never known that…
having a crepe with you
can make me this happy.
Share your stories with me.
I want to know you better.
Umm.
I'm an only child.
I also want to have a little brother.
I should have visited Thailand more often
so I could help you practice ballroom dance.
You could teach me how to play football.
And we both could go ghost hunting together.
Auntie Jeab must have been
so mad at us, you know.
But that's fine…
When we spend time together,
no matter if it's short or long,
I'm so happy about it.
And I…
Prim.
I want to talk to you about something.
At the hospital,
you waited for someone
to come visit you, right?
That person is…
See-Nam?
Well…
See-Nam isn't with us now.
[Dead?]
But…
She left this song for you.
♫ The picture of you will
always be in my memories ♫
♫ You're still there and
I want to say I love you ♫
♫ I want to be around
you, that's all I want to do ♫
Dad believed that I could take care of you.
I also believe you will be able
to get through this.
Pluem…
I'm sorry…
Why?
Why did everyone I love pass away?
It's because of me, right?
I'm bad luck.
I'm your burden.
Dad died because of me.
If I didn't say that that day…
If I didn't ask him to take me
somewhere for a birthday party…
he wouldn't be on the road, right?
[Director: Kwankaow]
I was selected to do the TVC casting.
[Next Episode]
And it's not even an extra role.
Can I invite others there with me?
Both of us will exchange the points
for the Last Day and be there.
How many hours do you have left?
It's enough to watch the sunset with you.
I've never thanked you.
Since I came here,
you've always helped me out.
I just want to be a person you can
always see when you turn around.
Mom, Pluem's eyes hurt.
That is not it.
Oh…
♫ Still searching for you ♫
Could've just told me.
♫ Hoping to meet you ♫
You're going to town on the food.
No, this is just practice.
How is it, Nutty?
Cabbage is delicious.
(dialogue)
I really want to eat BBQ.
Oh, let's turn the camera to Nutty.
Let's see.
[Ghost Host Ghost House]
He's bullying me.