[Characters, actions, places,
agencies, occupations, ]
[and events in the series are fictional
and for entertainment only.]
[They are not intended to
encourage any actions shown therein.]
[Viewer discretion is advised.]
[Ghost Host Ghost House]
[Toth, Techit Panyanaraporn]
[Boy, Nattapon Wongwanit]
[Gon, Kasidech dechwongya]
[Lina, Watcharin Anantapong]
[Guide, Chawanwit Wongpong]
[Nutty, Natamon Chantarawipard]
[Ins, Lonlada Nananukul]
[Screenplay by
Osan, Pluem and Vibie Gen Team]
[Executive Producer: Jebsit Dechboon]
[Assistant Executive Producer: Pawinee Pinnares]
[Producer: VIBIE LIVE Application]
[Ghost Host Ghost House]
[Director: Kwankaow]
[Previously]
I was reached out to for a commercial.
And it's not even an extra role.
Can I take someone with me, too?
Both of us will exchange our points
for the last day,
How many hours do you have left?
They're enough for us to
see the sunset with you.
I still haven't thanked you.
Since I've been here,
you've always helped me out.
I want to be the person
you'll see when you turn around.
[Will you be my boyfriend?]
Will you?
Can you give me some time?
What time do you need?
Time to forget him?
Or time to love me?
[BOARDING PASS BKK TO SEA]
You're not going back soon, right?
I must have left one at the beach.
[7 days later]
[Gucchi - modeling agent]
Hello, Chi.
How are you, boy? Have you
made a self-introduction video?
I was about to.
Please send it to me before 1 P.M.
Alright, I won't forget about it.
I'll confirm the series audition
with you again later.
Come next Wednesday, 1 P.M. Sharp.
It's the location I sent you.
Alright, I'll do my best.
Sorry, you cannot reach this phone number…
Sorry…
I'm so sorry, Auntie Jeab. Excuse me.
[Kevin is live: I'm back]
Hello, everyone.
It's not my usual streaming time, is it?
It's around midnight here.
[MoMolsMe Lv.1 "Where are you, Kevin?"]
"Where are you, Kevin?"
I'm at my house in the States.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you all about it.
It was a bit urgent.
As you've asked about it,
let me talk about my life in Thailand.
So many things happened.
But I can't tell you everything.
I just want to let you know that
during that time…
though it's been just a few month,
I've learned so many things.
I've learned to be vulnerable,
hurt, lost, happy,
and loved.
I knew a person who
was there for me for my entire life.
He taught me so many things
which made me who I am today.
Jake was a person I wanted to see once again.
I wanted to thank him for
everything he did for me.
But recently,
I met a person…
He isn't like anyone I've ever met.
He's strong
but gentle.
He's serious but also has a sense of humor.
When I was him,
I couldn't go a day without laughing.
He took care of me so well.
Without him,
I wouldn't have gotten through
many things that happened.
He told me that
he wanted to be a person I could always
see when I turned around.
And he succeeded in doing that.
He taught me about happiness and sorrow.
He made me feel love
and fear.
For all that time, I was so happy.
But it was so overwhelming.
It was so much that I feared to lose it.
Everyone must be thinking that
I've been through loss and untold goodbyes,
those must have made me stronger.
But in reality, it's not that easy.
I don't know
if that person is watching this live.
I don't know if he's mad at me
or hates me now…
But I want to tell him that…
Good luck.
Pursue your dreams.
I'll live my life with more wisdom
and joy here,
and succeed in whatever I aim to do.
I will be a grown-up Kevin.
In case, one day… If we have a
chance to see each other again,
I hope you will see a better version of me.
[Pluem…]
[Bye-bye…]
If we have a chance to see each other again,
I hope you will see a better version of me.
[3 years later]
The babies like you, Kevin.
Dare not to like me. I'll pick on you.
Don't even think about it.
Help me raise your siblings.
You're a big brother now.
They're coming as twins,
I must get a headache when they grow up.
God must know I'm old now.
So He gave me two at once.
He really made it count.
Don't your dad complain
you visiting me this often?
Dad told me to come.
He said he was going on a trip for a few weeks.
He told me to stay with you when I was lonely.
Your dad was going on a trip?
Yes, I told him to.
Have you two reconciled?
I didn't think of doing that.
But as we opened up to each other,
turned out he wasn't that set on his ways.
Mom, don't worry about me.
Dad and I can talk about almost anything.
Stay for dinner, okay?
I miss Thai food so much.
Are you sure it's "just the food"?
Mom, stop teasing me.
It's been a while now.
How can I stop?
That person still joins
all of your lives, doesn't he?
Which one?
Ms.P.
He's just a regular.
But I know he's Pluem.
Your issue with dad is over.
Why don't you clear this up, too?
Why do I have to?
It's nothing, mom.
He's a star, isn't he?
I saw him in the series
Auntie Meow likes to watch.
What about waiting
for him in front of the building.
Maybe, he can still remember you.
He definitely can't.
Well, your dad isn't at home.
What about you going on a trip?
Traveling to Thailand isn't a bad idea.
The beach looks amazing
in this season.
I heard you liked it a lot last time, right?
You're teasing me again.
Big brother.
Well, if you think the
script is okay, I'll go for it.
Well.
You're a superstar now,
don't you want be a bit picky?
I do, actually.
But I'm afraid all clients
will be in trouble nationwide.
Oh, tone down the confidence.
If people heard it,
they'd say I didn't train you well.
Just kidding.
Alright.
Well, tomorrow, I'm not free
from morning to early evening.
Where are you going?
I'll send my friend off at the
airport. My friend is going abroad.
A friend?
Yes, really, just a friend.
Alright then. Up to you.
Take care of yourself, alright?
I'll go taking care of a new star now.
I'm so sick of your face.
- You sure?
- Umm.
- You're going to do that?
- Yes.
You're leaving me?
Do that to the number 1 of this agency?
I'm waiting for you outside.
Get dressed.
The shooting is starting soon, top star.
[Enjoy with this trip.]
[Hope I'll get to see that person
as a souvenir.]
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
See you around.
- I'll take care of it.
- Thank you.
Are you Thai?
Yes, I am.
Sorry, I wasn't sure about that.
Where are you heading to?
Well… intersection 5, Smithjan street.
Alright, sir.
Are you back from a trip?
No, I live overseas.
I just come to Thailand on a trip.
Oh, I see. Are you staying with your relatives?
Just come by to visit them.
Alright.
- Here we are.
- Thank you.
[AIEMPHON STUDIO]
♫ The picture of you is still in my memories ♫
♫ It is still vivid in my mind.
I want to tell you I love you ♫
♫ I want to be close to you
That's all my heart wants ♫
Are you going to another destination?
No, thanks.
Sorry. Please help him carry the luggage.
Sure, sir.
Here are the suitcases.
Excuse me, are you Pluem Pitipong?
Yes, it's me.
Oh, I didn't expect to see you.
My wife is a fan of you.
She's liked you since your
first commercial. The prawn cracker.
Oh, you're such a big fan of me.
As you're here, may I have a picture with you?
Sure.
Selfie, alright?
1… 2… 3.
- Okay, thank you.
- You're welcome.
- This is the fare.
- Thank you, sir.
Are you on a trip?
Do you want to come in?
Come on in, I'll explain.
Have a seat first.
You still remember the way, right?
It's your own house.
Come this way.
Well…
You bought this house?
Why did you buy it?
Well, why are you curious about that?
There's no reason you have to.
Of course, there is. So many of them, in fact.
It's beautiful and a nice locale.
And…
It's the place filled with good memories.
When you walked in,
you started to miss this place, didn't you?
What's wrong? Why are you so tense?
Move a bit.
Why? It's my house.
Alright, I'm leaving.
Hey… No need to go
I just wanted to tease you, sorry.
Well…
I'll buy you Thailand's famous dish
to make it up to you.
What are you doing? Why did you say that?
I'm not joking around, I'm for real.
You can go out and have a meal with me?
You're a superstar now, aren't you?
Are you my fan?
I'm handsome, right?
You're a narcissist.
If I wasn't handsome, I couldn't be a star.
You could if you had talents.
So you're saying I'm talented.
Do you want an autograph?
Let's trade autographs.
I also want an autograph of
a famous ghost-story streamer.
You're as adorable as I saw on the streams.
Why did you join my streams?
Aren't you scared of ghosts?
I wanted to see your face.
I forgot all my fear.
You didn't redesign the place at all?
Well… I already told you…
This place is full of memories.
I don't want to change a single thing here.
This is the film I left at the beach.
That's right.
You forgot it last time
we went to the beach together.
I got that film developed for you.
Thanks for keeping it for me.
It's like…
It's like… finding a precious thing I've lost.
Likewise.
Kevin…
I miss you.
You're still as adorable as before.
Your eyes are still pretty
so is your nose…
Stop teasing me like this.
I never teased you about this.
This time…
Is it still too soon?
I don't want to wait any longer.
I don't want you to wait either.
Where are you going?
I'm going to take a bath.
I've not checked in at the hotel.
No need to go anywhere.
Sleep with me here.
I booked a hotel room. It's a waste of money.
I'll pay it for you. Tell me how much it is.
Don't do this.
If you will stay a night at the hotel,
I'll be there with you.
I'll get my clothes ready in a minute.
Why are you such a crying baby?
I still miss you so much.
I want to be with you, don't want you to leave.
I'll be here for many weeks.
I'm not in a rush to go back.
Oh…
Just thinking of you going back,
my heart is torn to pieces.
- Acting.
- Ouch.
It hurts.
Stop overreacting.
You have no idea that,
for 3 years,
I've been wanting to see you so badly.
And I never expected this day would come.
I still can't figure it out
why I was so stupid
to let you go that day.
Why didn't I…
at least do something?
It's not entirely your fault.
It's my fault, too.
If you weren't brave enough to ask,
so wouldn't I be.
If you think you were stupid,
I was stupid, too.
We just didn't handle it well that day.
It's fine.
But today, we're back to see each other,
you…
You're new Pluem, a better one.
And for me,
I'm also a better Kevin.
If there are difficult things awaiting for us,
I know we can get through them.
Well…
Together…
Right?
You…
What?
I'm hungry.
What do you want to eat?
Thai BBQ.
Okay. I want to eat that, too.
I'll make it for you, okay?
Yay!
- Well…
- Huh?
Where is my wage?
That's it?
This?
Here you go.
Eat up so you can quickly grow up.
This is Auntie Jeab's BBQ recipe.
It's called… BBQ with…
Egg yolk.
I just copied her recipe.
It's so yummy.
How were you there?
It was good.
I went back to study
and made some content there.
Well, your online content.
Where did you get those methods from?
Some are… too horrifying,
don't you think?
It's been quite some time,
are you still freaking out over ghosts?
I'm still the same as before.
You're not.
Now, you're Pluem Pitipong.
You're no longer a "Handsome Gardener,
Please Share to the World."
I'm still the same.
Do you see the trees over there?
I planted all those trees myself.
Also, I watered and trimmed them.
I did everything myself.
How is your sister Prim?
She's going to college now.
She's on a Work and Travel program now.
This house is messy because she's not around.
Well, how did you become an actor?
Since I did the prawn cracker commercial…
- You still remember that, right?
- Umm.
I didn't act well on the set that day.
You must have seen it.
But the director felt sorry for me, I guess.
She introduced me to a modeling agency.
Gucchi, the manager who takes
care of me now, kept finding me work.
Until one day, I got a series project,
I was the friend of the lead.
That was so fun and difficult.
I got a role as a swimmer and I had
to be shirtless for almost every scene.
There was a diving workshop, too.
I did as best as I could.
After the series ended,
I got some fans like others…
- Not just "some," I think.
- Huh?
My mom and aunties in the U.S
watched every episode of your series.
Really? Did your mom say I looked good?
Of course, my mom also said that…
Said what?
I'm not telling you that.
You've obviously grown up a lot.
You told me that
it wasn't easy to be an actor.
But look at you now. You're an actor.
And you're also a swimmer.
I once tricked you into taking off your shirt…
You were so shy about it, weren't you?
But I'm not shy to do that, anymore.
I just showed you every part of me, right?
Stop teasing me.
You're taking revenge for what I did, huh?
I didn't think like that.
You look so cute when you're awkward.
I wanted to tease you just a bit.
What happened?
Kevin.
For all that time,
did you miss me the way I missed you?
This time…
You're ready to be serious
with our relationship?
I'm sorry
to make you wait this long.
You're not going to change your mind, right?
I'm not letting you go anywhere now.
I will no longer sit there
and be afraid of losing you one day.
I learned that…
the scariest and most regretful thing
is not spending the time with the one I love
when I'm still alive.
I'll be with you.
Let's eat.
Do you want me to feed you pork.
Auntie Jeab, Uncle Art,
See-Nam, See-Foon,
Pluem has already bought this house.
He keeps many of your stuff in their places.
Your music box is still there, See-Nam.
Some of See-Foon's clothes,
those you told me they were your to-go shirts,
are still under Pluem's care.
Jake.
You can rest easy now.
I've found the one…
The one you said you wanted to see.
He doesn't love me better than you did.
Because your love for me
was the best, the best in your way.
What are you doing?
Igniting the incense to talk to your ex?
An old friend.
I just want them reassure them
that I'm so happy right now.
It doesn't matter if they hear it.
I want to tell them this anyway.
What about you?
You don't have any words for your dad?
Dad.
This is my boyfriend.
He's cute, isn't he?
Why are you being so loud?
The neighbors will wake up.
Well, you're cute, aren't you?
Stop. Come on.
[Director: Kwankaow]
Wait and action, walk away.
What? What?
- This scene…
- What's with it?
- I was about to say that this scene…
It's the last scene of our series.
- The end.