[The Inextricable Destiny]
[Episode 19]
Jiuling!
Miss!
- Miss!
- Jiuling!
Where might she go?
You go over there. I'll search this way.
Alright.
Jiuling!
Miss!
Father,
I failed you.
I actually mistook an enemy for my family.
I won't do it again.
Wait for me a little longer.
When Jialin becomes
peaceful and stable again,
I will come and join you.
You're back.
Why are you alone?
What?
D-Don't mention this to my young master yet.
I'll search with you again.
Father, you braved the heavy rain this morning
to get a safety charm for me.
Things will definitely go well.
Father, don't worry.
Don't forget
that never act like a spoiled kid.
And
Consider the Emperor first
in everything in the future.
I know that, of course.
I have confidence in
winning the Emperor's favor.
Father, Sister.
We have said enough goodbyes.
It's almost noon.
Should we hurry on?
Are you in such a hurry
to send your sister away?
Isn't this because you are in a hurry
to become the queen?
I...
The grace of a princess!
My lord, the young madam is back!
[Rong's Mansion]
You!
My lord.
He Jiuling,
you've really gone too far.
Not only that you didn't come back
for the whole night,
but also Yu is missing because of you.
You are the calamity of the Rong's family,
the calamity of Rong Yu.
Calamity?
What are you all standing around for?
Everyone get out and search.
Don't return if you can't find him.
E-Everyone out and search.
Miss, shall I get you something to eat?
I'm tired. Just leave me alone.
What about the young master?
How does he have anything to do with me?
Boss, we don't need other things.
We just want to use the stove and the table.
Okay.
Princess.
Take a rest first.
We've been on the road all day.
The dishes will be served soon.
The taste is not bad here.
Princess, try this.
Boss,
have you seen a lady?
She's about this tall
and walked this way.
No.
Thank you.
[Princess of Chu County of Jialin]
Sir, have some tea.
Do you have anything to eat?
Yes.
Master, see if you like this.
Feel free to choose.
Master,
do you think it's too troublesome
to drink tea like this?
Why not take off the hat?
Master.
- Why don't you help me up?
- Princess.
- Why didn't you hurry to help me
when you saw me fall?
Are you okay?
Boss, a bun, please.
Okay.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Thank you, master.
Master,
I am not angry
about what you did just now.
I won't punish you or kill you.
Don't be afraid.
Where are you going?
Are you going to walk there? Isn't it tiring?
Why not let me give you a ride?
Or let me see what you look like?
Don't follow me.
Who wants to follow you?
There are so many men who want to follow me.
Don't push your luck.
You're really leaving?
Stop! Come back!
Why did you get into my carriage?
What are you doing here?
Miss,
have you seen a very good-looking young man
when you were on the road?
Very good-looking?
How handsome is he?
If you don't say how handsome he is,
how do I know
if I have seen him?
You can rarely see a man
as handsome as he is in the world.
Do you think your young master is a peacock?
I can barely see a man
as handsome as him in the world?
I've never seen him.
You should look for it on your own.
Prince. Uh.
Look, how insincere he is.
He said he doesn't want me to follow him,
yet he got into the carriage himself.
Are all men in the capital so domineering?
I don't need to choose any more.
A domineering and indifferent handsome man
like him
is all I want.
Master.
Why are you playacting?
Do you like withdrawing
when you are chased after
but chasing after her when a lady withdrew?
Sorry. Sorry.
Now that we are on the carriage,
just stay here.
It's rather inconvenient to get anywhere
in this desolate place, isn't it?
Those people just now came asking for you.
I kept my mouth shut tight.
I didn't tell them at all.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Then you may just follow me.
Take me out of this forest.
This is for you.
Actually,
there would come a day
when a man apart from Father gives me money.
And
it's such a cute bunny!
Is it not enough?
Enough. Enough.
Why did they want to find you?
Did you run away from home?
I'm out seeking my wife.
I'd rather not have anyone following me.
You're seeking your wife?
I didn't see
you're pretty good at flirting.
You're such a sweet talker.
What a coincidence.
I also left home
to look for someone in the capital.
I am looking for a husband
I'm in love with.
Is this the so-called love at first sight
that Father told me about?
Nice voice.
A nice figure too.
And he even gives me money.
Other than not knowing
if he's really good-looking,
he doesn't seem to have any defects.
He's really good looking.
Master.
Look at me.
Do I resemble your wife?
Do I?
Miss, respect yourself.
Playact again.
I am quite self-dignified.
That's exactly
why I asked if I resemble your wife.
I'm just joking with you.
Why are you mad though?
Why are you not leaving yet?
Waiting for it to get dark?
A bunch of lazy ones.
Master, where are you going?
Leaving the city.
L-Leaving the city?
Turn the cart around.
Why didn't you ask?
A bunch of fools.
Master,
this is the first time we met.
Since we are on the same carriage,
how about we get to know each other first?
No need.
In that case.
Let me introduce myself first.
Not necessary.
Man, you've successfully caught my attention.
Miss, eat something.
Miss.
You don't need to worry about me.
I'm not hungry.
Has Zhanping returned?
No, he has not.
Get the horse ready.
Slow down. Slow down. Slow down.
Come over here.
Move this away.
Yes.
Put it here.
Sir.
Boss,
is there a young lady checking in your inn?
A young lady? No.
Thank you.
This way, please.
Please.
Boss, bring me something expensive to eat.
This is for you.
Okay.
Put the snacks there. Hurry.
These are homemade.
They are as good as those in the capital.
And they taste differently good.
I don't like sweets.
Take them away.
Prepare some salty dishes for me tonight
to take on the road.
How can someone look so good eating a bun?
Master.
Look at me.
Aren't I pretty?
Master.
How could I fall into the same trap twice?
You!
His nature is so good.
How could there be such a kind and gentle man
in the world?
Where is he?
♫ Drinking a cup of melancholy ♫
♫ In which love is brewed into pain ♫
♫ Unable to wait for the dark night ♫
♫ With a flickering candlelight ♫
♫ Drinking a cup of vicissitude ♫
♫ I'm no longer impetuous in my youth ♫
♫ Hearing you are somewhere across the water ♫
♫ I'll swim against the current ♫
♫ Drink the ups and downs on the journey ♫
♫ Sigh at the wastefulness of life ♫
♫ Drink the entangled thoughts ♫
♫ Let's get drunk,
for meeting you is difficult ♫
♫ Let's drink to our sorrow ♫
♫ With grey hair, I laugh
at my distressing dreams ♫
♫ I can't get over you
after all the days we spent together ♫
Now, you are neither
the Best Young Master in Jialin,
nor the young master of Astrology Pavilion.
You are just Rong Yu.
I just want you to be happy.
♫ With a flickering candlelight ♫
I just wanted to make you happier.
Then every year on your birthday,
I will accompany my little rabbit lady.
♫ Hearing you are somewhere across the water ♫
♫ I'll swim against the current ♫
♫ Let's drink to our sorrow ♫
♫ With grey hair, I laugh
at my distressing dreams ♫
♫ I can't get over you
after all the days we spent together ♫
It's time to rest.
Tomorrow
I will take you back
to Rong's mansion.
Why didn't you go back before?
Wasn't it agreed to come back earlier
and move to the courtyard?
No need for that.
Are you crying?
No.
But you are about to cry.
I really don't want to cry.
Don't cry anymore.
What exactly happened?
Tell me.
Nothing happened.
I just got lost.
Lost?
For a moment
I found that I did not recognize
the people around me.
I don't know
the roads around me either.
I don't know where to go.
I don't know what to do.
I only know I can't go back anymore.
I've lost myself.
Don't worry.
As long as I'm alive,
I won't let you get lost.
Whatever happens to you,
no matter where you are,
I will find you
and then take you back home.
Home?
Yes, home.
Do I have a home?
Everyone is guilty.
Only you are innocent.
But I can't be your family anymore.
There will be no home for me anymore.
It's all my fault.
I didn't protect you.
I didn't protect the He family.
From now on,
I won't let others hurt you.
It's okay whoever hurts me,
but why does it have to be the Rong family?
I've tasted the pain of being alone
with all those who loved me
leaving me.
But still, in the future,
I have to make you by my own hands
a person like me.
Rong Yu,
what should I do?
How could I not cry?
Don't cry.
Rong Yu,
the person I least want to hurt is you.
However...
The young master and young madam are back.
Go to notify the lord quickly.
The young master is back.
Young master.
He's fine,
It's good that he's fine. It's good.
Besides,
he can play the zither now.
Actually,
he can actually play the zither.
That's great.
Young master will definitely recover soon.
Zhanping, go prepare some food,
No need.
I want to go to the pharmacy.
How could there be such a perfect man?
Princess.
Hurry. What did you find?
It's been found out
the young man you encountered that day
is the young master of the Astrology Pavilion.
No wonder.
I told you
a man so perfect like him
could not be an ordinary person.
He was looking up at the stars that day.
Yes, but...
the young master of the Astrology Pavilion...
Young master?
So it means
I might become the madam.
Princess, but he's...
My future child
can not only inherit my territory
and my property,
but also inherit the Astrology Pavilion.
Princess, but he's...
Prepare gifts for the Astrology Pavilion.
No.
Send gifts to every lord in the capital.
I want them to know
I has come to the capital to choose a husband,
not just for fun.
The future wife of the young master
is rich
and noble.
Whoever wants to compete with me for him
should give up early.
Yes, princess. But he is...
Why are you still standing there talking?
Hurry up.
Go now.
Yes.
Princess. Princess.
She comes from the south of the Yangtze River.
Her territory is the richest
in the whole Jialin.
She's the only daughter of Prince Run.
All of the property
will all belong to her.
Anyone who marries her
will attain the highest level in one step.
Right. Right. Right.
Have you received the gifts she sent yesterday?
- Yes.
- Of course.
My annual official salary as a sesame official
is no more than a small gift from her.
That's true.
It's true.
I know the Empress Dowager and the princess
have been worshipping Buddha in these years.
Before I came to the capital,
I specifically sent people
to get this from the temple.
This one was blessed by Master Yuanhui.
So was this one.
Thank you, sister.
Chuchu,
you're thoughtful.
You should just come.
Why did you bring so many things?
I, as an elder,
should be the one preparing gifts for you.
Now,
it's the other way around.
Don't say that. I have everything I need.
If you really want to
give me something,
please find a good husband for me.
I have received the letter.
I understand your father's intentions.
I will have to choose carefully for you.
No need.
I have someone in mind already.
Didn't you just arrive in the capital?
Have you already set eyes on someone?
It can be said that it is a heaven-sent match.
It seems you have already met him.
Which man are you referring to?
I-It's...
Rong Yu from the Astrology Pavilion.
Rong Yu?
After all the trials and tribulations,
it turns out to be Rong Jiang.
I thought Father was foolish
for favoring the Astrology Pavilion.
I never
expected this.
If Rong jiang really can foresee,
it will be very tricky.
No wonder it was impossible
to take him down before.
I thought I was too weak.
Even fortune
is not on my side now?
No need to think like this.
I have a plan.
Destroy the star chart.
Star chart?
Rong Jiang once said,
one can seize the initiative
by using the star chart for prediction.
You should know
doing so will hurt Rong Yu.
I know.
But it is necessary.
No matter it's for the blood feud
or the fate of the country,
Rong Jiang and the Astrology Pavilion
must be removed.
I thought of thousands of ways.
But no matter which one I take,
I will definitely hurt him.
I have no other choice.
He Jiuling, you...
Before taking action,
give me some time, please.
Let me do something for him.
Even if my debts to him
are never paid off,
I only want to atone for my sins
to the best of my ability.
He said he went to find his wife.
It turns out he did have a wife.
In fact, the young master...
In fact, it is not normal
if he doesn't have a wife, is it?
It's my fault.
If I could come to the capital earlier,
would any other woman marry him?
It's Father who won't let me go.
Princess.
Princess what? Why are you talking so much?
Be careful of your tongue being cut.
Yes.
I am a princess.
I am a dignified princess of Jialin.
He has a wife, so what?
Who can compete with me?
Yu.
Uncle.
I heard that you can play the zither now.
If you can remember how to observe the stars,
that would be even better.
It will help
if you visit the star chart frequently.
I will ask the Imperial Physician to come
in a few days.
Yu,
you have lost weight.
How did you lose so much weight
after hunting?
How did He Jiuling take care of you?
She can't even handle such a small thing.
She takes care of me very well.
Why are you looking at me like this?
You should take good care of yourself, uncle.
Don't always worry about me
and the Astrology Pavilion.
Both He Jiuling and you
are very important to me.
♫ Under the setting sun in dusk ♫
♫ I travel far for thousands of miles ♫
♫ Playing the zither under the moonlight ♫
♫ The drinks won't let me forget ♫
♫ The longing I write down for you ♫
♫ Our fate is written on paper ♫
♫ Just like the strongest wine ♫
♫ There's no escape for destiny ♫
♫ Looking back, I see you waiting ♫
♫ Our lives are filled with joy and sorrow ♫
♫ The longings crystalize
into a bright galaxy ♫
♫ You turned around quietly
and closed the marriage book ♫
♫ Asking how many stars there are in the sky ♫
♫ The longing I write down for you ♫
♫ Our fate is written on paper ♫
♫ Just like the strongest wine ♫
♫ There's no escape for destiny ♫
♫ Looking back, I see you waiting ♫
♫ Our lives are filled with joy and sorrow ♫
♫ The longings crystalize
into a bright galaxy ♫
♫ Gently I stroke the zither,
waiting for a passerby like you ♫
♫ Turns out you are my inextricable destiny ♫