😚Timing and subtitles brought to you by Seductive Mischievus Team @ Viki.com😉
[The Inextricable Destiny]
[Episode 8]
You understood what I said?
Get the teapot. I want to drink water.
I am He Jiuling.
At least you could understand my actions today.
It's worth celebrating.
Put on your shoes. The ground is cold.
Shoes.
Madam, I've brought the things you wanted.
Here are the sweet potatoes you wanted.
You're almost running out of food, and you're still giving the best things to strangers.
Everyone who comes is a guest.
Moreover, those two are pitiable.
We should treat them nicely.
You're so kind. I'll be leaving now.
Take care.
Here. Have a sweet potato.
Thank you, madam. This is my husband.
- Thank you, madam.
- This is my husband.
He's just like your boyfriend. He doesn't speak either.
Your husband looks quite strong and capable of work.
He's unlike my boyfriend,
who can't speak and is physically weak.
But he is nice to you.
Eat it yourself.
I know how to use a spoon.
I've never seen a couple as devoted as you two.
Maybe your father is not insightful enough about men.
It doesn't matter if a man is strong or not.
What's important is that he is nice to the one he loves.
With such a young master lowering his dignity to take care of you, you are very blessed.
If this isn't enough for your father to let you marry him, he must be very blind.
I'll give you a piece of advice.
Stay at my place for a few more days, and don't go back until you two have a baby.
No need.
We will set off tomorrow.
We are going to visit a relative.
Is that relative reliable?
Don't worry.
That relative will definitely take us in.
Could you not feed me continuously?
Let me take a break, will you?
Eat it yourself.
I can eat myself. Look.
You are quite normal when you feed yourself.
Yet you fed me like a pig.
Madam, this is our thank-you gift for letting us stay.
No, I can't take it.
I just let you stay for one night.
I didn't do anything else.
I can't accept so much money.
Just take it.
And please buy me some plain clothes.
I will get it done after the meal.
Take care of each other on the road and live a good life.
Thank you, madam.
- Then we're leaving.
- Take care.
Be good. Don't run around.
Master Rong?
Master Rong!
Young Master!
Miss He?
Why are you dressed like this?
You…
You must have mistaken me for someone else.
Please do not follow us. I am scared.
You are scared?
You kicked me so hard just now, and you said you were scared?
You've already given yourself away. All right?
Miss He, so the person next to you must be Master Rong.
There's no doubt about it.
I've been drawing his picture for so many years. I won't be wrong.
Oh, Heaven.
Master Rong has finally woken up!
Master Rong. Master Rong.
He's really a fool now?
My livelihood!
I won't sell any books.
My heart aches.
He will always be the Star-picking Master.
Once I take him to Mount Wuhua, everything will be fine.
Then go.
Why are you creeping around here?
Haven't you noticed that they are searching everywhere?
Searching for you?
He's the young master of the Astrology Pavilion and His Majesty's favorite minister.
I guess the capital is probably in chaos now.
Even this small city has checkpoints.
B-But aren't you guys already married?
Nobody believes you can save him.
Me and him…
Forget it.
Keep an eye on him for now.
I'm going to the post station to see if there's a hitchride.
Your hand is injured. I will go ask.
That will do.
Then ask them if there's a carriage that goes to Shidu.
If not, ask them if there's a carriage going to Mengze in Jiangling or Xinze Lake in Guizhao.
The carriage to Mengze in Jiangling must be big.
Master Rong's in bad condition.
But if it's a carriage to Xinze Lake in Guizhao, it must be small.
There are too many officers and soldiers along the way.
If we get recognized on the way, we're done.
If there's nothing available, ask them if there's any—
Stop. You go and ask yourself.
I'll stay and take care of him.
All right.
Young Master.
I'm going to find some water.
We're out of water.
I need to get some.
T-To find water?
Wait here for me. All right?
I'll get you a bun to eat.
Bun?
Once you finish eating it, I'll be back.
Thanks.
I'm adding some seasoning powder for you.
Here, take the bun.
Take good care of him.
We have the same buns. Why does yours smell so good?
Why does yours smell so good?
Star-picking Master, it's an honor to spend time with you at such close range.
Though the timing isn't right, I want to introduce myself. I am—
You are a pig.
[Feiyun Inn]
- See you. Take care.
- Bye.
[Feiyun Inn]
Be careful. Don't slip.
Sir, do you have a carriage that goes to Mengze in Jiangling?
If not, I could rent one.
I'm not too sure myself.
Why don't you go in and ask our boss?
Thank you.
Please come in.
Do you have a carriage going to Mengze in Jiangling or Guizhao?
If you do, I will rent it. I don't mind the cost.
L-Lord Rong—
Where's Yu'er? Where did you take Yu'er?
♫ Drinking a cup of melancholy ♫
♫ Lovesickness turns into pain ♫
♫ Unable to wait for the dark night ♫
♫ A little candlelight flickers ♫
I'll never let you harm him again, and I definitely won't let you go.
♫ I'm young but no longer impetuous ♫
♫ Hearing you are somewhere across the water ♫
♫ I'll swim against the current ♫
♫ Let's drink all the way up to the high mountains
and long rivers ♫
♫ Sighing at the world of mortals and the absurdity of the years ♫
♫ Having a drink, considering thoughts ♫
♫ How difficult it is to meet each other, let's get drunk ♫
♫ Let's drink to our sorrow ♫
♫ The hair on the temples is all frost,
laughing at the distressing dreams ♫
♫ Floating clouds and changing seas, we will never forget each other ♫
Rong Yu!
♫ Sighing at the world of mortals and the absurdity of the years ♫
♫ Having a drink, considering thoughts ♫
♫ How difficult it is to meet each other ♫
Let go of me!
Let me go!
♫ How difficult it is to meet each other, let's get drunk ♫
♫ Floating clouds and changing seas, we will never forget each other ♫
♫ Let's drink all the way up to the high mountains
and long rivers ♫
Rong Yu!
♫ Having a drink, considering thoughts ♫
♫ How difficult it is to meet each other, let's get drunk ♫
♫ Let's drink to our sorrow ♫
♫ The hair on the temples is all frost,
laughing at the distressing dreams ♫
♫ Floating clouds and changing seas, we will never forget each other ♫
Ling'er!
Thank you for sending my daughter home.
- Tell Lord Rong that I can't see him today.
- Are you hurt? Are you okay?
Tomorrow, I will personally apologize to him.
General He, my master said there's no need for that.
He also stated that people from the He family should no longer visit Rong Mansion.
What?
You are not hurt, are you? Your hand…
How did your hand get all tied up?
Zong Ming, call the doctor.
The Rongs don't want Rong Yu to go to Mount Wuhua.
You insisted on taking him anyway.
I don't care about Rong Yu.
But if something happens to you, how will Father and I survive that?
Enough. It's good that she came back.
I must say.
Didn't you hear what that person just said?
He said, "People from the He family should no longer visit Rong Mansion."
And look at what Rong Jiang did.
Rong Yu is still unconscious, and he sent us engagement gifts.
Is he even human?
Are the Rong family worthy of you risking yourself like this?
Qiuting.
Father.
Actually, Rong Yu woke up.
Really?
That's good news.
Jiuling, even though you were a bit reckless, you got a good result in the end.
You should be happy for that.
I want to be happy.
But I can't be happy at all.
- Ling'er.
- Jiuling!
Ling'er!
Young Master! Young Master, you can't go out.
Young Master, you can't go out.
Young Master.
You can't go out.
Lord Rong, I am ashamed.
The current situation of the young master is something I've rarely seen in my life.
So I can only try to write a few prescriptions, hoping they can make him better.
So he's just like that?
Foolish?
He can't remember anything.
But why does he only remember her?
Why does he want her?
Why does it have to be her?
Lord Rong, this is not hard to understand.
Newborn ducks and goslings will stick with the first person they see.
The young master is now mentally like a newborn baby.
When he was conscious, only Miss He was by his side.
He naturally considers her the closest person and feels uneasy if she is not present.
The closest person…
This is going to turn the Rong family upside down.
Young Master! Young Master, you can't go out.
Yes.
Young Master, you cannot go out.
I will go back to the Imperial Medical Bureau and discuss it with everyone.
I will take my leave first.
Young Master, you cannot go out.
Young Master, please stop.
Young Master…
Young Master is awake.
Heshan, did you hear that?
In the future, you will still be his personal guards.
Thank you for your kindness.
But I can't forgive your betrayal of the Rong family.
The sin...
shall be borne by me alone.
Leave a decent person by Young Master's side.
Master, I have a thing to ask.
Yu'er, here.
Let's eat. Take these.
Let's eat.
Good. Grab them.
Yu'er, this soup is your favorite.
Here.
Come. Drink some soup.
Do you want to eat the bun?
Here.
Come one.
Eat it.
Does it not taste good?
Someone!
- Sir.
- Tell the kitchen to make whatever buns they can.
Also, go outside and buy one of every type of bun in the city.
Go.
Mister, bakeries only do early morning business.
Then bring those bakers back to make buns here.
Double-pay them.
Do I need to teach you that?
I'm on my way now.
Yu'er.
Young Master!
I am sorry.
You're awake. That's great.
Rong Yu!
Jiuling! Your hand!
Your left hand is just an auxiliary one.
Don't rush to exercise it.
Martial arts practitioners should not rush for success.
I don't.
Aren't you eager to become stronger?
But now you are too eager.
Even if you can use a sword now, I can beat you with my bare feet.
What's wrong with wanting to become strong?
In the future, no one can hurt anyone in front of me.
No one can take anyone away from me.
I know.
You don't.
In those ten years at Mount Wuhua, my master and senior brother protected me.
When I got back, you guys protected me.
But I can't protect anyone.
Didn't you say before that you were the best in the world?
That's just nonsense.
Don't use it against me.
Meet me at the training ground tomorrow morning, and let's exercise.
Can you get up on time?
I can.
If you really want to learn martial arts, we won't indulge you like at home.
I don't need indulgence.
[To my disciple, Jiuling]
I have a deep hatred for the Astrology Pavilion.
Hence, the life or death of people from that place is irrelevant to me.
I will leave the mountain and travel soon.
Don't come looking for me.
What kind of old history...
can make my master harbor such hatred?
It must be painful.
Do I have to make my master give up her hatred for the mistake I made?
Senior Brother, something is wrong with Amnesia.
After taking it, Rong Yu not only didn't sever emotional ties but was also mentally damaged.
I need a prescription to make an antidote.
I'm hoping to get a reply soon.
Send the Blood Vine Grass and Dragon Head Ginseng that I've found to Jialin quickly.
Your Highness, these are the treasures of healing you've found for our king.
It took you two years to finally get your footing right.
Now, we are at the moment where the king is re-choosing the heir.
So please don't do that.
Hurry to Jialin. This matter needs not to be discussed again.
Okay.
- How is it going?
- It’s hard to describe in one word.
Take care.
Watch out.
Faster!
Hold steady. And thrust!
Miss, are you here to see Young Master, too?
I'm afraid you might have come in vain.
Something happened to Young Master recently.
He hasn't been out in a while.
In the past, many people waited here just to catch a glimpse of him.
But things have changed.
Even my tea stand business is down.
Could you get me a pot of tea?
Okay.
I also heard that he seems to have become a fool.
He can't eat or speak.
And yet, you still like him.
You are the only one I've seen like this during this time.
He is not a fool.
All right, he's not.
Idiot.
Truly an idiot.
When I was here with my father last time, he was just staring at a bun.
This time we came, and he was still staring at a pancake.
Don't you think he looks like someone?
He looks like the dog you fed the bun to last time.
Exactly.
You also noticed his gaze. Right?
Yes, the gaze is exactly the same.
I initially planned to throw a stone at him when the two guards were not looking.
I wanted to see if he truly couldn't speak or dodge.
Who hit me?
Your nose is bleeding. Are you okay?
- Sir, do you need me to wipe the blood?
- Who hit me?
Who wants your damn rag?
- Are you okay?
- Who is it?
It's her.
Go.
You…
H-He Jiuling.
Did you throw the stone?
Tell me! Did you throw the stone?
No, I didn't. The guards in the mansion were watching closely. It was just my thought.
I really didn't throw it.
Ouch, it hurts. Miss He! Miss He!
Get me a bun.
Okay.
Miss He, what are you trying to do?
Here, miss.
This is the bun awarded to you by me. Eat it.
Eat it with gratitude.
Eat it.
Eat it now.
Eat.
He Jiuling, we were trying to stand up for you.
His Majesty granted your marriage to him.
But now he has turned into a fool.
How is he worthy of you?
What does it have to do with you?
If you keep spouting nonsense, next time what I feed you won't be just a bun.
Y-Y-You… you are lawless.
Have you forgotten the fate of the young lord?
- Sir, should we stop this?
- Everyone, get out!
They came here to see the spectacle with the excuse of visiting the sick.
I can't teach them a lesson.
Let her hit them.
- Sir.
- Is there something wrong with Young Master?
The buns are spoiled.
Buy more.
Yes.
Miss He.
Did Rong Yu…
Your face…
It's nothing.
How could it be nothing? It's all because of me…
I need to go back.
Young Master isn't feeling well.
He hardly sleeps or eats.
All he does is stare at a bun all day.
I'm adding some seasoning powder for you.
Once you finish eating it, I'll be back.
I think I know why he doesn't eat.
I will go buy it.
Miss He.
Can you visit Young Master?
No, I won't go.
I can't implicate anyone else.
Don't worry.
Nobody will be punished again.
Young Master.
Young Master, this way.
Young Master, slow down.
Slowly.
Come.
Slowly, Young Master.
Young Master, look!
♫ Sunset, dusk, and the setting sun ♫
♫ Traveling thousands of miles away ♫
♫ Appreciating the music of the zither and and the moon in the middle of the night ♫
♫ How many times will the drinks not let me forget? ♫
♫ Picking up the pen and feeling lovesickness come true ♫
♫ Fate is noisy on paper ♫
♫ The strongest wine is the most unforgettable ♫
♫ Love is so deep that there is no escape ♫
♫ Looking back, you are, waiting for me ♫
♫ Have you ever looked back on the joys
and sorrows of the years? ♫
♫ The longing crystalizes into frost and brilliant stars ♫
♫ You quietly turned around and closed
the marriage book with your own hands ♫
♫ Smiling and asking how many stars there are
in the world tonight ♫
😚Timing and subtitles brought to you by Seductive Mischievus Team @ Viki.com😉
♫ Picking up the pen and feeling lovesickness come true ♫
♫ Fate is noisy on paper ♫
♫ The strongest wine is the most unforgettable ♫
♫ Love is so deep that there is no escape ♫
♫ Looking back, you are, waiting for me ♫
♫ Have you ever looked back on the joys
and sorrows of the years? ♫
♫ The longing crystalizes into frost and brilliant stars ♫
♫ Gently I stroke the zither, waiting for a passerby like you ♫
♫ Turns out you are my inextricable destiny ♫
"Inextricable Destiny" - Song Yiren, Wang Youshuo
♫ Sunset, dusk, and the setting sun ♫
♫ Traveling thousands of miles away ♫
♫ Appreciating the music of the zither and and the moon in the middle of the night ♫
♫ How many times will the drinks not let me forget? ♫
♫ Picking up the pen and feeling lovesickness come true ♫
♫ Fate is noisy on paper ♫
♫ The strongest wine is the most unforgettable ♫
♫ Love is so deep that there is no escape ♫
♫ Looking back, you are, waiting for me ♫
♫ Have you ever looked back on the joys
and sorrows of the years? ♫
♫ The longing crystalizes into frost and brilliant stars ♫
♫ You quietly turned around and closed
the marriage book with your own hands ♫
♫ Smiling and asking how many stars there are
in the world tonight ♫
♫ Picking up the pen and feeling lovesickness come true ♫
♫ Fate is noisy on paper ♫
♫ The strongest wine is the most unforgettable ♫
♫ Love is so deep that there is no escape ♫
♫ Looking back, you are, waiting for me ♫
♫ Have you ever looked back on the joys
and sorrows of the years? ♫
♫ The longing crystalizes into frost and brilliant stars ♫
♫ Gently I stroke the zither, waiting for a passerby like you ♫
♫ Turns out you are my inextricable destiny ♫