[English subtitles are available]
[Poisoned Love]
[Episode 13]
Shi Yi's manager said it was
just a promotional material.
They are merely Yin Jiang's partner.
She is all over Weibo.
It shouldn't cause us any trouble,
our company isn't affected.
I've been talking all night,
but you keep drinking.
I am not keeping your company for that.
You have other work to do?
Of course.
I am going home to my wife and son.
You've been wooing
Zuo Yao for two months.
There seems to be no progress.
Patience is a virtue.
I am slowly collecting
an amount of impressions.
Once I've gathered enough of them,
I will impress her
enough to win her heart.
That won't work.
Why won't it work?
Mr Shi.
Well,
in terms of relationships,
I am the expert.
Okay.
So you are the expert.
I have a question for you.
I watched a drama lately.
The female protagonist...
has a sudden and special
feeling towards the guy.
But then she left without a word.
What could be the reason?
We'll dive into the nuances.
Did the guy...
somehow do something...
that let her down in a way?
Not at all.
Did the guy care about the girl?
Not very well.
What did she say before she left?
She...
packed all her belongings.
Then she told me...
"Thank you for taking care of me."
So before she left,
did she do something for you?
Before she left,
she showed me her side of the world.
She even celebrated my birthday for me.
Then...
I saw right through you.
Just tell me the answer.
With my professional analysis,
perhaps you took too long to
say the magic words,
she gave up on you,
so she dumped you.
But she is in love with Shi Yi.
Mr Shi.
Come on.
Is the relationship
between idol and fan...
the same as the love...
between a couple?
Cheers, I am here for my buddy.
I will help you with your goal.
Come.
Drink slowly, slowly
Fang Yan.
You made a wave this time, look at this.
The fan count is rising.
I didn't know...
this is the spark he talked about.
You got upset,
and Shi Yi showed up
to cheer you up right away.
He is the embodiment of perfection,
I doubt...
you will find another just like him.
Shi Yi is repaying his fans.
I should thank him for this.
Here.
I wish to take a look at your brain,
is there nothing useful in there?
I am getting famous.
But why am I still upset?
Why must you fall in love...
with that cursed demon Shi Meng?
You are drunk, let's go.
Sit down.
We aren't done...
with your trouble just yet.
There is nothing to talk about.
I am still getting used
to the life without her.
-After all my life...
-Your life is full of movies.
Shi Meng.
If you like her so much,
you should have told her.
You can't just wait for her
to take the initiative.
Shi Meng, ask yourself.
Do you even feel sad after Fang Yan left?
If you don't like her at all,
why are you...
trying to intoxicate yourself?
You are just too afraid to tell her
how you feel.
You are afraid if you confess...
and if she's in love
with Shi Yi instead,
you would lose face in front of her.
[LUMOS]
It's not like your pride
is worth her love!
Go home.
Don't touch me.
If you're in my shoes,
if you don't even know why
you can't win her love,
that will truly be hopeless.
All right.
But I've never thought about giving up.
I was here all night with you.
Do me a favour.
-What is it?
-This should be a lesson for you.
I want you to know...
what real man looks when he
doesn't falter from love.
Shi Meng?
[Hello? Zuo Yao?]
[Hao Ying Jun is drunk.]
[Hao needs you to pick him up.]
-What is wrong with him?
-[Blueberry Bar!]
I am at the Blueberry Bar!
Not tomato, but the blueberry!
Yes, Blueberry Bar.
Come here.
Tell him,
I don't care if he dies from
drinking too much.
Hello?
He hung up.
Nicely done!
Don't give her a chance to turn you down.
Well played!
Who was that?
None of your concern.
Mother.
Aren't you going to pick him up?
No way.
I am not going to help him.
I don't care.
After spending the whole day
having fun,
I still can't forget him.
It's so hard to breathe.
Yao Yao, I can't breathe.
Shi Meng, why didn't you stop him?
I tried.
I’ll leave him to you. I have to go now.
Yao Yao.
I miss you, Yao Yao.
Hao Ying Jun, are you trying
to kill yourself with drinking?
Zuo Yao, you are finally here.
I have something to tell you.
I am not a coward.
Forget it.
Can you still walk?
I think I have a heart infarction.
You shouldn't drink so much.
It's not like you were
being forced to drink.
[The first snow carries...]
[a special meaning for me.]
[My father confessed his love
to my mother...]
[during the first snow.]
[Then they fell in love with each other.]
[We can still be here...]
[for the next first snow.]
[Really?]
[It's snowing.]
[I know you would go out
to see the snow.]
[Keep yourself warm, don't catch a cold.]
[We can still be here...]
[for the next first snow.]
Really?
[It's snowing.]
[Want to watch the first snow with me?]
No.
[Fang Yan.]
[I like you.]
[Will you be my girlfriend?]
No,
that is too direct.
[Thank you, Fang Yang.]
[You taught me...]
[what destiny is.]
No.
That is too vague.
[Fang Yan, I want you to know...]
[I want to enjoy your cooking
all the time.]
No!
That would make her my babysitter.
[I had never known love.]
[But then, I met you.]
[Your smiles make
the spring breeze shy away.]
[Only those who's seen it would know.]
[I wasn't there for you in the past,]
[but I want you for the rest of my life.]
[The moon shimmers,]
[I wish I could see it
through your glimmer.]
[The rain comes to every city,]
[just like I would be there
for you anywhere.]
[I will use this song...]
[as a present to you, to reveal my feelings.]
[It needs to be perfect.
-Hello? K?
-Mr Shi Yi.
[Don't forget the filming
ceremony tomorrow.]
I get it.
The ceremony is tomorrow.
[Rest well tonight.]
[I will pick you up early tomorrow.]
Right.
For tomorrow,
I am bringing Fang Yan along.
[Fang Yan?]
[The Tale of Water Utopia,
Filming Ceremony]
[Starring Shi Yi, Lin Ling,
A Product of Concept Pictures]
Don't worry, everything is set.
Are all the actors here?
Is anyone absent?
[Our men are keeping a close eye on them.]
[Nothing will go wrong.]
My goodness.
Shi Yi actually came here with Fang Yan.
[Didn't I tell you to
get it done last night?]
[Shi Yi even has his own camera crew.]
So their interaction ended yesterday,
so he is planning to
make it official today?
Hao Ying Jun.
Keep an eye on them.
Thank you.
How is Fang Yan reacting to all this?
They seem to be having
a good time together.
Boss, where are you now?
I've never been to
a filming ceremony before.
So?
Did the viral news from Weibo
manage to ignite your passion?
Not just igniting,
I am now at the core of it.
Which is why I decided...
to continue being...
the tiny insignificant.
Tiny and insignificant?
Yin Jiang is shining bright.
My Weibo fan count...
would have stayed the same
till the end of time...
had you not boosted it with a click.
Soulmates are hard to come by.
I need but one.
You have the voice and the soulmate.
Be content.
Let's have a look over there.
Okay.
They are having fun!
They are flirting!
-I can handle it.
-They have physical contact!
Mr Shi!
Your love is betrayed!
What do we do now?
Go, confess your love!
Seize your one true love!
Go!
Why did you bring her here?
For the filming ceremony.
Hold on.
Where are you taking her?
For makeup and hairdo.
But she is a voice actor.
And she still needs makeup and hairdo.
Come with me.
Sit down.
Unless there is an emergency,
stay right here...
no matter what happens.
I’ll explain later.
Carry on with your work.
Okay.
What is wrong now?
Everyone is on edge.
So, what is the meaning of this?
I should be asking you the same thing.
You dragged her away without any reason.
And now you demand an explanation?
Shi Yi,
don't bother pretending.
You added Yin Jiang on Weibo,
it's making a huge wave.
And now you brought her here
to a public event.
If the reporters have a sniff of this,
her life will be affected.
Don't you see that?
See for yourself.
It's just like the ceremony
you put so much effort in,
what if on the day of the ceremony,
the couple from the movie...
were actually...
lovers in real life,
wouldn't you save a ton of money on promotion?
I will never use her as a tool.
What about before this?
Who used her to fool me into
signing the contract?
You should stop being so controlling.
Fang Yan is not your personal accessory.
I bet you think I want to make
our relationship official.
I am not a businessman.
I will never do that.
I won't use this method to
generate fame for myself.
I can't be perfect for Fang Yan,
but at least I am better than you.
I am there for her.
I will never use her.
[Waiting.]
[The endless waiting.]
[We either wait while alive,]
[or pass away during the wait.]
Why did Shi Meng drag me out here?
He looked mad.
Did he start a fight with Shi Yi?
Was it because of me?
"Why did you bring her here?"
"None of your concern."
"She is my roommate,
of course it is my concern."
Fang Yan, what's got into you?
Wake up!
You decided to stay away from his life!
Remember.
Forget about him.
Shi Yi, what brings you here?
Did Shi Meng bully you?
No. He asked me to stay here.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Ignore him.
Go wherever you want.
I have to take a few more photos.
Have fun on your own, okay?
It's okay. Carry on with your work.
Wei Lin will be here soon.
Once he is here,
we'll have a look around.
Okay. I will go to you
after my work is done.
We'll take some photos together,
as a souvenir for the Lake God.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
I don't like being an outsider.
Sure.
Soulmate.
Go on.
Mr Hao, this is the confirmed list,
have a look.
I'll make the adjustment
if there is any issue.
-Mr Shi.
-Go on.
Why are you here all by yourself?
Where is Fang Yan?
You failed again?
No wonder,
your rival is Shi Yi after all.
I don't care who it is,
I know how I feel about her.
Did I get that right?
You finally get it.
Seriously?
Enough nonsense.
Don't keep that to yourself.
-You have to...
-Wei Lin, where are you now?
You have to let her know too.
Where are you going?
Where is the resolve and courage
you just showed me?
Put on a smile and muster your courage.
You need to...
You need to go for it!
I am...
Go.
Go!
I am currently...
I don't know how to describe this place.
I'll talk to you later.
Why are you here?
I wasn't wandering around.
It's fine.
You have something to tell me?
I...
Nothing.
I am passing by.
Hold on.
I ran out of pickled cabbage.
The recipe is easy, I can send it to you.
It's not convenient to live with Zuo Yao.
After all,
Zuo You is growing fast
to become a man.
But aren't you a man?
Well...
The cushion for Goo Sen is
still at the balcony.
Bring it to me.
It's too dirty, I am not touching it.
Just wash it.
I don't know how.
What are you trying to say?
I need a babysitter.
Baby...
Babysitter?
It's a marvel.
It was marvellous.
Come on.
You live up to your name,
What you pulled off just now,
that was the best confession...
I've seen in my entire life.
-What else do you want me to say?
-What else?
You might as well tell her
I am in love with Wei Lin,
at least that was better than
your lame excuse.
A babysitter.
He wants me as his babysitter!
What was wrong with you?
Mr Shi?
I just want her to move back in.
Move back there?
Why should I?
To babysit that dude?
Nicely done!
How are you going to clean up this mess?
No matter how I see it,
it wasn't a good way to get her back.
Is he the kind of person...
who has high IQ and almost negative EQ?
Maybe he was in love with you
but he couldn't tell you.
I need a babysitter, come back!
Does that make sense to you?
No.
Figure out something for me.
What would I know?
This mess cannot be fixed.
I am going to confess.
Confession?
Yes.
That is not possible.
-Why not?
-Impossible.
You had been living with each other
for so long.
It may not be love at first sight,
but it could be love over time.
Shi Meng never had any other woman
in his life...
so closely for so long.
[All staff be ready.]
[The ceremony is starting soon.]
We should go over there.
Just take it easy, come on.
All right, let's go.
Let's welcome our main production crew.
The director and Shi Yi...
please unveil the camera.
The ceremony commence!
-Great!
-One, two, three!
We appreciate all the reporters...
for attending the filming ceremony
of The Tale of Water Utopia.
Up next, we will have the photo sessions.
Come.
Fang Yan, why are
you standing back there?
Come forward.
All for The Tale of Water Utopia!
This is my first time doing this.
I have no experience.
Think of something for me.
But you can't just ask someone else
to do it for you.
Is it really okay for us...
to be doing this here?
So,
why must we turn off the lights?
It's exhilarating!
Turn the lights on.
"Secret To Winning Hearts".
My grandfather left it for me.
It's from the year 1919.
Good stuff.
Wei Lin.
You can't rob the grave of your family...
to cope with your existential crisis.
I bet that book is used to kill zombies.
Even if the tricks do work,
it's way too creepy.
"There was..."
Stop reading it.
It's a little out of date.
Dear Shi Meng.
We must not let some random simpleton...
lower our class to theirs.
You have me with you.
Based on my experience,
a successful confession...
will only take place
when you show her...
the best and most unique side of you.
What is most unique about me?
You are cold.
Cold?
Cold.
Put your coldness...
on display.
How about this? Starting today,
block her.
Ghost her.
Stop contacting her.
Keep it going.
This is the fun part.
Ghost her for a few months.
Then...
show her the worst cold shoulder.
Make her take the initiative.
Hold on.
That takes too long.
With Fang Yan's brain,
she will have forgotten about Mr Shi.
-But I think...
-He has a point.
Then stop giving me lousy advice.
Mr Shi, leave it to me.
I know Fang Yan the best.
Her biggest flaw is being soft-hearted.
You can't go headstrong with her.
You need to...
get her sympathy.
How do I do that?
Tell her...
you filed for bankruptcy and
debt collectors are after you.
Then you are on the run.
You keep running.
And running all the way.
Then...
ghost her for a week or so.
Go to her in your dirty
and ragged clothes.
Just like I am now.
Wei Lin.
I think...
sympathy is all she has for him.
If I were Fang Yan,
sparing Mr Shi some coins...
would be the greatest sympathy from me.
And I noticed...
your IQ...
deserves some sympathy as well.
Mr Shi, ignore him.
We'll figure something out.
Yes.
If none of these work on her,
we have a more direct approach.
Make her comply.
What is it?
First of all,
use your charismatic voice...
to charm her.
"Hi, baby."
Then,
use your strong body figure...
to attract her attention.
Finally,
use your wealth...
to conquer her.
-Tell me you love me.
-I love you!
If this doesn't work,
it doesn't matter.
"Yan Yan!"
"Mr Shi, you must answer for this!"
-"You must answer for this!"
-Forget it, I'll do it myself.
Was that too far-fetched?
Babysitter?
He thinks I am the babysitter!
This is outrageous!
Babysitter.
Outrageous.
Fang Yan!
I lost Goo Se.
How did you lose it?
I wanted to take it out
for a walk after dinner.
It ran off for a pretty bird!
It ran off for a pretty bird?
I bet you saw a pretty girl
and forgot it!
Search over there, I'll search this side.
Let's split up.
Fine, but I warn you.
You either find it,
-or get lost!
-Fine.
Search over there.
Why are you here?
Wei Lin called me to help him
search for the bird.
Let's team up.
Hello?
Fine.
I am heading back now.
Wei Lin found Goo Se.
I am glad to hear that.
I am going home.
-I can send you home.
-Never mind.
It's not safe for you to go home alone.
Come on.
Fang Yan.
Look.