[English subtitles are available]
[Poisoned Love]
[Episode 14]
Fang Yan.
Look.
What is it?
Look closer.
It's a star.
Right.
The light from the city...
have made the star light dull.
It's because the light from city
is too bright.
It's hard to notice there is a star.
Maybe it's because you made a wish
to the Lake God.
So, we finally got to
see the stars tonight.
Lake God!
Thank you for showing the star light!
If there was any snow...
You are right.
There is no snow in a clear sky.
How childish of me.
Lake God.
Thank you for showing us the stars.
Will you please give us some snow as well?
On the left.
Fang Yan.
I am not sure if you know,
but before I knew you,
my life was all about working.
But then you came into my life.
You made a mess out of my life.
I had but one thought in my mind.
I wanted to get rid of you.
But when you moved out,
I realized...
the time I spent with you...
was full of joy.
I felt warmth.
I am sorry.
I'm sorry for not realizing it sooner.
Will you give me another chance?
Let me be there for you
for every starry night sky...
and every snow.
Fang Yan.
I like you.
That settles it.
[Concept Pictures]
Look at your proposal!
This is nothing but trash!
Do you even know how to do your job?
Stop standing there!
Get out of my sight!
Yes, my apologies, Mr Shi.
He is coming out.
What was that about?
Old Wang.
What has got into Mr Shi today?
That was intense!
As if I would know.
He has never been so angry before.
He is mad at me over punctuation error!
Just be sure to watch your backs.
-We need to be careful.
-I know.
Did he get ditched?
He never lectured me so hard before.
What is going on here?
Who is it?
-Mr Hao, stop scaring us.
-What is the fuss about?
You didn't notice I was here.
Mr Shi is very angry this morning.
Angry?
Are you sure he wasn't smiling at you?
Then you don't get it.
Dismiss, get back to your work.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
The plan worked and he became shy.
♫ The snow is deep ♫
♫ The snow seem so harsh and cold ♫
♫ It's just as cold as the wound
between the two lovers ♫
How was the snow last night?
Baby?
It didn't work out?
It seriously didn't work out?
Where were you when I confessed to her?
I thought everything was going well
between you two.
I didn't want to be your third wheel
so I left early.
[Fang Yan.]
[I like you.]
[I am sorry.]
[I can't be in love with you.]
She can't be in love with you.
That means...
loving you is troubling to her
in some way.
But come on.
You may have a bad temper,
you barely have experience in love,
your job is no normal job,
but those shouldn't get in the way.
You can at least be friends.
Where are you going?
The planning of new project.
Where is the new project?
You are holding it.
[Wandering Love]
Oh no.
This is not going...
to end well for us.
-Don't fill the cup. It's too hot.
-I am fine.
-Let me hold it for you.
-Never mind.
-You are so awesome.
-That is only necessary.
-Flirting during working hour?
-Mr Shi!
Be careful.
Mr Shi.
I am sorry.
Does it hurt?
I am asking you, does it hurt?
A little.
Remember,
that is how love feels.
-Are you okay? Let me cool it for you.
-I am fine.
That is enough.
Blow it at your home if you must.
Get ready for the meeting.
And remember to get Mr Shi some tea.
Something to chill him down.
-Get the tea ready.
-Yes, tea.
[I am sorry for not realizing it sooner.]
[Will you give me another chance?]
[Let me be there for you
for every starry night sky...]
[and every snow.]
[Fang Yan.]
[I like you.]
[Are you going to start a relationship?]
[Do you think any man would accept
your way to treat this sickness?]
[You are getting so intimate
with another man.]
[I am sorry.]
[I can't be in love with you.]
Director? What do you need?
[Fang Yan, your voice is...]
It's all right, I am having a cold.
[There is a short promotional clip,]
[they want the voice actor of Lake God
to dub it.]
[Can you help me out?]
[Come to the office at once.]
-Right now?
-[Yes.]
Sure.
Mother.
Is Miss Fang Yan on diet or something?
Why is she skipping meals?
It's best not to bother her
for time being.
You're awake.
Are you hungry? How about some breakfast?
I'll pass.
The director needs me at the office.
Do you have to go now?
See you later.
Mother.
Her eyes are all red.
Yes.
I bet she cried the whole night.
But why?
You are too young to understand that.
Have a bun.
Mother.
If that Hao Ying Jun ever makes you cry,
I will make him pay.
Don't be ridiculous. Eat now.
[Wandering Love Project Planning]
According to market survey,
the main target consumers
for Qixi Festival are still...
the female customers.
So, the target group...
[Wandering Love]
should prioritize the women.
As for the proposal,
we take into consideration...
the watching habits of the women.
So,
I...
[Wandering Love Project Planning ]
I am...
Well...
So, this is the planning department's...
recommendation for...
the premiere of Qixi Festival
for next year.
Any order from Mr Shi?
Mr Shi?
Leave.
Well...
We get the main idea of the project.
That settles it, dismiss.
Mr Shi and I will discuss it.
Okay?
-Okay.
-Go now.
Hold on.
Sit down.
I have a question about the content.
A question about the lady's motive.
As you said earlier,
the guy gives up his old lifestyle
for the girl,
which goes against his code.
He even did things he had
never done before.
So, why wasn't the girl
touched by his devotion?
Didn't you say...
the girl has special feeling
towards the guy?
Since they reconciled,
why aren't they in love?
Not bad.
You, answer me.
From the standpoint of the girl,
a guy is willing to go
against his principle...
to try something new,
a guy who is rich and loves you...
confesses to you, why wouldn't
you accept his love?
Why?
Mr Shi, I am sorry.
I will never flirt during work again.
I am sorry, I won't do it again.
Sit down.
What do we emphasize for a film?
The content and its logic.
Is their relationship logical at all?
Tell me.
All of you,
I want it in three days...
an adjusted version on my desk.
I want a detailed analysis.
I want both the original version
and the newer one.
I want no disappointment.
Wait,
what is wrong with him?
Love is trouble.
Good morning.
Mr Shi, you scared the little girl.
I didn't ask you to come out here.
Did I dismiss you yet?
I...
What is wrong with him?
Such a bad temper.
Did I tell you to come out here?
Did I tell you to dismiss?
[Psychological Diagnosis, Fang Yan]
Shi Yi.
I am sorry to ask another favor from you.
I am here for Dr. Cui...
to inquire about my condition.
I want to know
if there is a quick way to recover.
I can't always trouble you
for my personal life.
I am no stranger to you.
I am your cure.
It's perfectly normal...
for you to carry me around.
This is for Fang Yan's hypnosis.
Under such condition,
it will help you follow the command.
This is our way...
to help Fang Yan trust you more.
Let's begin.
-Good luck.
-Okay.
Good luck to me.
You are right where you always
appear in the dream.
The person who makes you feel secure...
is right in front of you.
Follow him.
Only he can lead you out of there.
Believe in yourself, you can find him.
Look into Shi Yi's eyes.
Is the hypnosis...
not working on me?
It seems like...
I am not trustworthy enough for you.
Not at all!
-I do trust you.
-I am not blaming you.
I am just upset...
I couldn't cure you immediately.
Excuse me.
When it comes to psychological issues,
the healing process will be much longer.
And your condition as of now...
has been under control.
Next, keep in contact with Shi Yi.
Build the trust from a psychological aspect.
What should we do then?
Between humans,
there are many ways to build trust.
The easiest way...
could be something like...
better understanding of each other...
and sharing secrets.
If you want to earn someone's trust,
you need to see if you have any secrets...
to share with the other person.
Why did you bring me here?
Why did you bring gifts?
Is it heavy?
Not at all.
See?
Birthday Party of Sunflower Nursery?
Dr. Cui wants us to share secrets.
You will find out soon enough. Come on.
[Birthday Party of Sunflower Nursery]
Brother Shi Yi is here.
Everyone, Brother Shi Yi is here.
Watch out.
Move forward.
Hello, Brother Shi Yi!
Let me introduce a new friend to you.
Sure!
Hello, I am Fang Yan.
Just call me Miss Fang Yan.
Hello, Miss Fang Yan.
-Hello to you as well!
-Let's check the presents, okay?
Great!
This way.
Watch your steps.
Be careful, everyone.
Let me hold this for you.
[Birthday Party of Sunflower Nursery]
Everyone, go and play with Brother Shi Yi.
Sure.
-Here.
-Hello, Madam.
Have a seat.
Hello, I am the principal here.
You must be Shi Yi's friend.
You are the first friend he has brought here.
Really?
Whose birthday is it today?
It's a birthday celebration
All of them?
-Yes.
-On the same day?
Yes.
They are all orphans.
They don't know their birthday.
Orphans?
But why make it today?
According to Shi Yi,
no one knows their birthdays.
So, he fixed it on a date.
He made it today.
No matter how busy he is,
on this day every year,
Shi Yi will be here to
celebrate their birthday.
I am grateful for him.
Madam Principal.
You did well.
The kids are having a great time.
I can tell they like you a lot.
I like them as well.
I heard everything from the principal.
On this day every year,
you would be here to
celebrate their birthday.
Shi Yi, you are so kind.
It's not kindness.
It's empathy.
I never knew...
when my real birthday is.
How is it possible?
I was adopted.
When I was very young,
my parents adopted me.
Then soon after that,
my mother got pregnant with Shi Meng.
Then...
Shi Meng and I grew up together.
Our parents were nice to both of us.
They treated us as their own children,
they were never favouring anyone.
Which is why I had never
known my own origin.
Until I was ten,
I found out...
by coincidence...
that I was adopted.
What's the matter?
Judging by your look,
you don't seem surprised by my story,
but more like...
I were some sort of monster.
Not at all.
I am glad you were adopted.
I didn't mean that.
I mean foster parents
are parents, nonetheless.
I didn't mean it.
All right, I know what you mean.
Besides,
I don't want my story...
to affect your thoughts on me
No way, that won't happen.
But Shi Meng...
I have never brought this up
with anyone.
That includes Shi Meng.
Shi Yi.
Thank you for trusting me.
Thank you...
for sharing your secret...
just to cure my illness
It feels good to let it out.
I feel better too.
After all, some secrets...
can't be kept to one's self.
That should be enough, I'll send you home.
Leave me be.
What's wrong?
Are you still bothered by my secret?
No, it's just a lot to take in.
Fang Yan.
At this rate,
I would regret ever telling you.
Sharing secrets...
shouldn't be a burden for you.
I don't feel any burden.
I feel like...
I just know a whole new
aspect of you.
I am glad you feel that way.
Today is for some quiet time
and sharing stories.
Enjoy the view.
The scenery here is pretty.
Fang Yan.
Listen to this.
[Fang Yan.]
[I...]
[Hao Ying Jun]
[Actually...]
[I have another secret.]
I need to answer this call.
It's okay, go ahead.
Hao Ying Jun, what is it this time?
[Shi Meng got into an accident,
come here at once!]
What?
What happened to Shi Meng?
Is he in trouble?
Where are you now?
Tell me your location!
[ICU]
Be careful.
[Clinical Laboratory]
[Shi Meng, pick up the call!]
There!
Hao Ying Jun.
Where is Shi Meng?
He...
[Operating Theater]
Is the patient's family here yet?
Why is this happening?
You can't go in there,
surgery is ongoing.
[Operating Room]
Fang Yan.
Leave it to the doctors.
Shi Meng will be fine.
How did he get into the accident?
He...
Answer me!
He wanted to go to the gym.
But he went too far.
He was on the treadmill the whole day.
Then he wanted to run home.
This is my fault.
I should have followed him.
I should have kept an eye on him.
[Operating Room]
Take a break.
However...
you should calm down.
I believe he will be fine.
[Operating Room]
[Fang Yan.]
[I like you.]
[I am sorry.]
[I can't be in love with you.]
Doctor.
How is he?
We did all we could.