Thanks for the food!
I told you we could
eat something else.
- You barely ate.
- They say this shop is the best.
You didn't like the food?
I did. It was good.
I'm happy as long as you liked it.
Let's go to a café.
There's a famous one nearby.
Don't get coffee.
Let's go for something else.
We're going to Yongma Land.
Let's get our drinks there.
We can get them first and go.
They serve other things too,
not just coffee.
This café's signature
dishes are famous.
Okay.
Let's go.
What to get? Ashotshu?
That sounds good.
Wow, pretty.
Senior, it's right there.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Come on!
- Welcome.
- Hello.
Senior, what would you like?
Huh?
- Americano.
- America...?
Don't you want clam cookies
or mugwort latte?
They're their signature menus.
Just get me something.
I'm gonna go outside.
- Are you ready to order?
- Excuse me.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Um.
I'm okay.
But you don't look okay.
I feel dizzy.
We didn't travel by car or boat.
What made you dizzy?
Can you give me a minute?
Can you leave me alone
for a minute?
Senior?
Shall we get ice cream?
(Love for Love's Sake)
(Lee Tae-vin)
(Cha Joo-wan)
(Oh Min-su)
(Cha Woong-ki)
(Episode 5: Relationship)
That was my mother.
Sorry.
I should have told you.
I thought we'd pop in and out,
that I'd be all right.
Did you ever look for her?
What's the point?
I would just bother her.
It was all my fault.
I'm sorry for not knowing.
Who could have known
this would happen?
No need to apologize.
No.
I'm sorry for not noticing.
Would you tell me?
If you tell me about yourself,
I'd never hurt your feelings again.
You're a good kid, Cha Yeo-woon.
I'm not a good kid.
All good kids say that.
That's because you don't
know what I'm thinking.
That's why you said that.
Got it.
Let's go to Yongma Land.
Let's make the most of the tickets
you jumped through hoops to get.
We don't have to if you don't want to.
We'll enjoy the view here.
I want to go.
I'm serious.
I want to have fun with you.
(Calculating Cha Yeo-woon's
Fondness toward you)
(Fondness 23)
Let's go.
(Temporarily Closed)
I can't go on rides anyway
since I'm dizzy.
See? I'm gonna barf.
Hey, I'm really gonna barf.
I'm gonna barf.
Cute.
I'm cute?
How cute am I?
Let's go.
Cheon Sang-won
hasen't contacted you?
Not yet.
Do I have to go look for him?
Brother, I'm gonna go find
Cheon Sang-won.
I don't know if he ran off again.
Understood.
Call me if there's a problem.
- O-bye!
- Huh?
Short for "Okay, bye."
I'm gonna go.
You startled me.
Hey, why didn't you say where
you were? You ignored my calls.
You made me cancel the shoot...
What happened to your face?
You expected me to show up
for a shoot like this?
Was it your dad?
My dad stopped a long time ago.
- I got into a fight.
- Why did you?
- You find out and then what?
- I just want to know why.
I just said some stuff.
Got in a few punches.
This was the result.
Do you know how worried we were
when we couldn't reach you?
Didn't Myung-ha ask for me?
Myung-ha?
Then again,
I never saw him
look for me first anyway.
You really fancy him?
Do I...
look like I really fancy him?
Only you know the answer.
I had a great time today.
I did too.
Thanks.
Get inside and go to bed.
Thank you for coming with me today.
If I win prizes again,
let's take another trip.
Why are you thanking me?
Friends take trips together.
Are we friends?
Aren't we?
I don't know.
Take me under your wing,
Cha Yeo-woon.
Let's be friends.
You're home.
- You're still up?
- The noise you made woke me up.
The door is old.
- It makes noise no matter what.
- Ow.
Then we must demolish
this house and rebuild it.
Grandma, I saw my mom today.
Really?
What did she say?
I didn't greet her.
She opened a café
I just popped in and out.
Has she...
ever asked for me?
Myung-ha,
People...
After we went through hard times,
there are things we want to
put away and don't look back.
She was just trying to avoid that.
Grandma,
please live a long life.
(Mission: Make Cha Yeo-woon happy)
(Penalty: death)
(282 days remaining)
(I broke the vase you gave me.
Can it be repaired?)
(A system error has been detected.)
Was it sent by mistake?
So, how do people
confess their love?
Why do you assume
I'm good at love confessing?
Don't I look more like someone
who only gets confessed to?
I wouldn't know.
But you're the only one I can ask.
Myung-ha has no desire
for a relationship at the moment.
- Not at all?
- Um.
Not at all. Never. No way.
- But he's nice to me.
- That's the problem.
From what I've seen,
he looks after you like you're a kid.
Not like a younger schoolmate.
More like his little brother.
- Or a nephew.
- He's only one year older than me.
I know that,
but you two don't look that way.
Anyway, Cha Yeo-woon,
there's no hope for you.
It's okay if he doesn't fancy me.
You must fancy Myung-ha a lot.
It's understandable.
- If I were you, I'd fancy him too.
- You can't.
I just said, "If I were you."
- But Myung-ha...
- Help me.
Say "Please help me." Come on.
"Si-a, please help me." Come on.
- Please help me.
- Louder.
Louder.
Please help me.
Why did it appear suddenly?
(Secondary Mission:
Befriend Cha Yeo-woon)
(Mission accomplished)
(You can view what Cha Yeo-woon
wanted most in the past.)
(Check it out now?)
Sang-won.
What are you doing?
You've mistaken me
for someone else.
Are you crying?
It's so embarrassing.
Couldn't you just walk past me?
I would have if you weren't
smoking in a playground.
Understood.
You're not of age.
Don't smoke yet, even if just a little.
It's not good for you.
You're so frustrating,
you know that?
Why were you crying?
Seulgi is sick.
What?
What's wrong with him?
Cancer.
You must be very sad.
Is Seulgi your brother?
Is he very young?
My grandpa.
My Seulgi is my grandpa.
Your grandpa.
Sang-won, I'm sorry
if I get this wrong, but...
Seulgi's not a person, is he?
He's a white poodle.
Twelve years old.
You must be worried sick
since he's been
with you for so long.
It must have shocked you.
Bro,
I think I'm in love.
What?
For real this time.
It's never been real in the past?
If I'm being honest,
will you accept it?
Stop being weird and go home.
I said I was being honest.
I joined the track and field club.
You have that much free time?
You think I did it
because I had free time?
Come see after school
if you don't believe me.
I'm not going.
You don't have
morning practice today?
I'm on my way to school.
What do you sound like that?
Are you sick?
No, I just slept in.
Where are you? Home?
Riding a bus.
You're really not sick?
Tell me if you are. I'll go to you.
I'm fine. I'm on my way to school.
I have to get there
for us to see each other.
You mean it?
I miss you, Senior.
I have to go to class now.
Let me know when you get here.
Watch out for cars.
I will.
Don't leave
the bottles around, please.
Do you still run in those races?
Haven't they given you prize money?
I don't have money.
When Grandma got sick,
you didn't visit her once.
You didn't show up
even after she died.
But you've come now?
Don't come for money
when you're broke...
You little piece of shit.
I told you not to slap my face.
- Are you insane?
- That's enough. That's enough!
Why isn't he picking up?
Did he get to school or not?
(You have a secondary mission.)
(Q: What's crucial to a happy life?)
(A: Every worry-free day.)
(Secondary Mission:
Saving up 3,000,000 won)
One, ten, hundred, thousand,
ten thousand, hundred thousand, million?
Are you crazy? I'm in high school.
Senior!
I'm not of age yet!
Orientation?
I have a provincial competition next month,
so I've gone to an orientation with my coach.
See you tomorrow.
(Really? Okay.
Take care. See you tomorrow.)
He said they'd gone
to an orientation.
Bro,
you finished your classes?
You did too. Weird question.
Uh, it's Seulgi.
He has to go to a hospital, but a guardian
must come too. Come with me, please.
- You're not a guardian?
- Huh?
Oh, I meant my guardian.
What's with you again?
You've been acting strange lately.
How am I strange?
My grandpa is very sick right now.
You brat, what's with you today?
Didn't you have to go to the orientation
with Yeo-woon and the coach today?
- Isn't that the coach?
- What?
The coach? Where?
I haven't seen him.
We must go now.
The hospital will close soon.
Really?
Fine. Lead the way.
(You have entered the Dating Zone.)
Hey.
Where's Cha Yeo-woon?
- Maybe he went home.
- He said he went to an orientation.
He must have gone home after that.
What are you guys up to?
Cheon Sang-won.
Do me a favor.
What?
I didn't hear...
What happened to your face?
Keep Senior Myung-ha away from me.
Why?
Just do me a favor.
Even though I don't know why,
I'll do it. It'll benefit me.
Something happened
to him, didn't it?
Never mind.
Where are you going?
He's not picking up, right?
That's fine with me.
I'll find him
since he's Cha Yeo-woon.
Look at me for once.
You're not Cha Yeo-woon.
If I were pitiful like him,
would you accept my feelings?
Can you think before you speak?
And I'm not doing this
because I pity him.
Why then?
Or because it's me?
You really can't accept me?
No, I can't.
What if I wait
until you change your mind?
There's no way. Please stop.
Go date a good man.
You're so frustrating!
Until now I only ever liked girls!
(You have entered the Dating Zone.)
Cha Yeo-woon!
What's wrong? You said you went
to an orientation. Cheon Sang...
Hey, what happened?
It's not a big deal. You can go.
Just tell me what happened.
I'll take care of it.
Take care of what and how?
Stop treating me like a kid.
It's my business. I can handle it myself.
Yeo-woon,
don't be stubborn. Tell me.
- Tell me so I can understand.
- I fancy...
I like you.
You don't like me, right?
But that's okay.
I like you anyway.
Yeo-woon.
Please like anyone but me.
I'll do what you say
and try to be your friend.
So,
please don't ignore me.
Please don't avoid me.
And please don't stay away.
(Calculating Cha Yeo-woon's Fondness toward you)
(Fondness 38)
I like you.
You don't like me, right?
But that's okay.
I like you anyway.
This is crazy, Tae Myung-ha.
(There's a reward
you haven't claimed.)
(You can view what Cha Yeo-woon
wanted most in the past.)
(Check it out now?)
I want to be happier.
(My wish)
(Mission: Make Cha Yeo-woon happy)
(Penalty: death)
(278 days remaining)
But that's okay.
I like you anyway.
I gave you my love
and got your heart in return.
Why am I not someone
from Cha Yeo-woon's world?
Jeez, Tae Myung-ha.
You're sitting alone again.
(Secondary Mission: 3,000,000 won
(2,603,120 won))
You are so mean.
How could you ask the guy you rejected
to keep an eye on another guy for you?
I'm a bad man like that.
Hey,
was Cha Yeo-woon
doing okay in class today?
He paid attention in class.
And at the club?
He ran very hard.
How was his mood?
You're asking the wrong person.
He's in a bad mood
whenever he's around me.
Hey,
did the coach
or one of you guys slap him?
I don't know who slapped him
but it wasn't anyone in the club.
You don't suspect anyone at all?
The guys who always bully him?
Ask him yourself
if you want to know.
Never mind.
- Tell me if you get bullied, okay?
- Huh?
I'll tell them off for you.
Why does he keep working
and not eating?
Does he have a big debt?
I asked. He wouldn't answer.
He's working
three part-time jobs now.
Something wrong?
Oh, you want your laptop back?
No. We were just wondering
what you were up to.
Oh, writing a paper.
How could you write that?
I just did.
Done.
Si-a, I just opened
a new IG account. Follow me.
Why? Don't tell me...
I'll collect followers
and sell the account.
Bro, you're really
pressed for money?
I can lend you some.
- It's fine. That won't work.
- Why not?
Because I tried that.
Grandma,
lend me 10,000 won?
(Secondary Mission: 3,000,000 won
(500,000 won))
Here.
Doesn't work.
(Secondary Mission: 3,000,000 won
(500,000 won))
Kyung-hun, why are you so happy?
That friend abroad said
they'd visit this summer.
Friend my ass. It's his boyfriend.
I see. The friend who studies abroad
you told me about is your boyfriend.
Um.
But you're far apart.
Can you still date each other?
Well, I like him.
You've been together long?
I've liked him
since I was little.
Even when you knew he'd go abroad,
you still liked him?
You weren't thinking,
"I have to like him
because we'll break up soon"?
That's why I thought I had to
like him as much as I could
because we might not
see each other again.
Damn it. There's not
one won in this place.
What are you doing?
You can't take that.
Give it back.
- It's Grandma's, please!
- You're not letting go?
You're not letting go?!
Cha Yeo-woon.
You'll cut your hand.
What are you doing here?
Yeo-woon.
Cha Yeo-woon.
Buy this for 500 won.
Buy it.
(Secondary Mission: 3,000,000 won
(2,999,500 won))
(3,000,000 won))
(Secondary Mission Accomplished)
(You'll learn what currently
makes Cha Yeo-woon the saddest.)
(Check it out now?)
What's wrong with you?!
I told you not to slap my face.
I wish I could run away.
What would you do, Senior?
Cha Yeo-woon,
- if you're pressed for money...
- Senior.
I asked because
I thought you were struggling,
not because I pitied you.
I know that
you're nice to everyone.
But I don't wanna be
nice to anyone.
I'm going in.