Wait,
let me add one more line.
Qin Che flips over and pins down the princess,
looking incredibly dominant.
Princess,
why are these scenes so aesthetically romantic?
True,
today's audience definitely won't accept
so many elevated shots.
No,
let's do it again.
Qin Che,
did you miss me at all?
I missed you.
I think of you
every moment of every day.
Qianqiu,
I won't let you go to that political marriage.
Really?
Really.
To the ends of the earth,
together in life and death.
This story is so interesting.
By the way, Princess,
is it really right for us
to use General Qin like this?
And what about your reputation?
Stop.
Compared to one's life,
reputation is the cheapest thing.
Since we're using Qin Che to avoid the arranged marriage,
we need to make this as big as possible,
preferably reaching the ears of the North Isle City Lord.
Worst case, we'll go all in.
By the way,
is that trending news board you mentioned really effective?
Of course,
the citizens of our Huiyin City
check the trending news board daily
to learn about stories happening in the city.
Welcome!
Tickets, please.
Please enter.
Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to our establishment.
Today's Hot News has been revamped,
and from now on,
I will bring you more,
more authentic,
and up-to-date information.
Great.
Everyone, please look,
the top story on our Hot News chart is...
Princess Qianqiu's secret bathroom rendezvous with General Qin.
I've secured good seats for us.
These stories are already spreading throughout the city.
Excellent.
Although I've escaped certain death,
Qin Che is still relentlessly pursuing me,
determined to destroy me.
Now I'm being forced to marry a 60-year-old man.
Rather than waiting for my doom,
I'll take the initiative.
Once I've tied myself closely to you,
let's see how you can kill me then.
Next,
invite Qin Che here for me.
I want to invite him for tea.
General Qin has helped me numerous times,
so I've specially invited you for tea
to catch up.
I still have official duties,
I'm afraid I don't have time to join you for tea, Princess.
General Qin, that jade pendant of yours is quite unique.
I noticed it the other day.
It's just an ordinary item,
Princess, if you have something to say, please speak.
Aren't you afraid I'll reveal your secrets?
Princess, you seem to have forgotten the pain once the wound has healed.
Princess, that hairpin of yours is quite unique as well.
What's wrong?
Nothing,
I just thought
what General Qin was planning to do.
The gossip column was right after all.
What are you looking at?
About today's private meeting between the Princess and General Qin,
if anyone dares to spread this news,
I'll rip out their tongue.
Move along!
What are you doing?
This jade pendant is mine now.
This Ma Qianqiu has changed drastically.
Could she really have lost her memory?
Isn't that General Qin?
Yes, it is.
Do you think he and the princess
are really having an affair?
Perhaps.
Fangjue,
go find out what's happening.
Yes, sir.
Princess Ruofei,
your schedule includes
half an hour of garden tour,
half an hour of dinner,
and one hour of rose beauty treatment.
So many things to do.
Isn't this my sister Qianqiu?
Congratulations!
I heard older men are more caring,
you're so lucky, sister.
Ruofei,
you're not a little girl anymore,
why are you still acting
so childish?
What do you mean?
What does she mean?
Exactly what I said.
You...
I won't stoop to your level.
Father has given his orders.
The marriage contract will be sent to Beiyu by noon tomorrow.
Sister,
you'd better enjoy
your last moments of freedom.
So soon?
Looks like I need to make my move tonight.
Ma Ruofei, I'll kill you!
Master Liu Yue
has traveled a long way from North Isle
and must taste our Huiyin's delicacies.
You're too kind, Lord of Huiyin.
We'll be family from now on,
so we should visit each other often.
Congratulations, sister.
On such an important day,
how can we just drink?
Does Ruofei have any good suggestions?
Sister just told me
that she prepared a performance
to entertain us.
After all, when she marries into North Isle,
she can't let Huiyin lose face.
Ruofei speaks wisely.
Qianqiu.
If that's the case,
Qianqiu, come up here.
Father,
I didn't prepare anything.
Come on.
Sister, don't be modest,
just present what you've
prepared earlier.
You can do it!
Your acting skills are impressive,
but I haven't prepared a damn thing.
Though I could take this chance
to interact more with Qin Che.
Alright.
To welcome Master Liu Yue,
I'll humbly offer a poem.
I hear the birds have awakened,
Love entwines two hearts as before.
In Qin's time, distant past finally meets,
Che's clear light reveals my heart.
General,
I love Qin Che.
I hope our two cities, Huiyin and North Isle,
will maintain lasting friendship.
Wonderful!
She actually managed to dodge it.
Little sister,
reading more books is indeed useful.
If there are any characters you don't understand in the future,
I'll teach you.
The princess said she loves General Qin,
really.
The princess said she only loves General Qin,
and wants to elope with him.
Princess Qianqiu and General Qin have secretly pledged to marry.
Princess,
by now,
the whole city probably knows about your confession to General Qin.
Perfect.
Lord of Huiyin City,
I'll go change my clothes first.
1,000 taels.
Be careful. Greed will leave you with nothing.
I know the princess has special feelings for you.
Do you want her to marry for political alliance,
or not?
1,000 gold taels,
bring it to me tomorrow,
or the day after tomorrow,
my price will change.
General,
our princess requests your company.
Tell the princess
I'll see her later.
Princess.
The general is here.
Xinjiang Dican.
Xinjiang Di.
Lei Cai Long Yan Peng Song Hui
Bojun.
Bojun
Zhuangcheng.
Jinsheng.
Jinsheng
Danwei Pingling.
Miao An Hao Wang Tao Rui Kai Qing Yu.
Yue.
Nan Zi Lei Ze Zhen Yao Zai Zhen Kai Jing Lu.
Ting.
Lu Ling.