General.
It's me.
What exactly happened that day?
How did you get so badly injured?
You followed the leads to capture the rebels from North Isle,
but found nothing, right?
Someone clearly spotted them outside the city.
But when I arrived,
there was no one there.
When I returned to the city,
I found out you were wanted.
I followed the markers you left
to find this place.
We fell into a trap.
It's the Governor.
No wonder he didn't pursue the matter of the bell chimes.
Not just the Governor.
Kang Hena too.
General.
Before I came,
I heard the Princess and Kang Hena have set their wedding date
for the fourth day of next month.
Kang Hena appears harmless on the surface.
But he's actually calculating and cunning.
If Ma Yangfei is willing to help him like this,
they must have formed some kind of alliance.
For our plan to succeed,
we must eliminate him first.
Focus your investigation on
his personal guards.
You might find something interesting.
Everyone outside is looking for you now.
General, you should stay here for a few days
and recover from your injuries.
One last time
let me have a crazy dream.
For me?
Do you like it?
Then put it on for me.
Okay.
Does it look good?
It's not fixed yet.
Almost done.
I think it's connected now,
let me try.
Hello? Hello?
Qianqiu.
What's wrong?
Nothing,
just a bit groggy after waking up.
That's good,
come on, I'll make you breakfast.
Qin Che,
you love me, don't you?
I love you.
You're hurt.
Let me see.
It's nothing.
Who did this?
Let me take a look.
Probably Kang Hena.
He sent someone disguised as you.
I was careless.
Come on,
I'll treat your wound.
With your high martial arts skills,
couldn't you dodge that?
I did dodge,
otherwise you'd be looking at my corpse right now.
Since we're talking about Kang Hena,
I need to ask you about Liu Yue.
Kang Hena suddenly
produced all sorts of evidence,
claiming you killed Liu Yue.
What's infuriating is that Ma Yangfei is in cahoots with him.
I need to find more compelling evidence now
to shut them up.
Do you really believe I didn't kill her?
Of course I do.
I've already sent Fang Jue to look for evidence.
Qianqiu,
for these few days,
let's set aside our identities as princess and general
and just be ordinary people.
But...
Fang Jue came by.
So you already know.
I only agreed to marry him as a temporary measure,
because we need to clear your name first
before we can negotiate with Ma Yangfei.
I...
I know,
but there's no rush.
I won't let you marry him anyway.
General.
You startled me.
Recently,
you've really changed a lot.
What are you trying to say now?
General, do you remember
how I came to be by your side?
That year during the famine,
I lost both my parents.
In Huiyin City,
I couldn't even compete with other beggar children for a single bun.
It was you,
you who gave me half a bun.
You told me
that I needed to become stronger
so others wouldn't bully me.
We secretly learned martial arts together,
went through countless battles together.
Now you're about to achieve great success
and fulfill your long-held wish.
I really don't want
you to throw away all these years of effort
because of someone like Ma Qianqiu.
Fangjue.
General, listen to me.
But I
would rather
see you live freely without constraints.
I've been watching your interactions with the Princess,
all of it.
You truly care for her.
I just want to use her.
General,
I hope you won't avoid this,
think it through carefully,
before making a decision.
After hearing the news I've told you,
what will you do?
What happened?
Ma Yangfei has fallen ill.
Looks like we need to return to the royal city quickly.
Xinjiang.
Lei, Cai, Long, Yan, Peng, Song, Hui.
Bo Jun.
Zhuang Cheng.
Jin Sheng.
Dan Wei, Ping Ling.
Miao, An, Hao, Wang, Tao, Rui, Kai, Qing, Yu.
Nan, Zi, Lei, Ze, Zhen, Yao, Zai, Zhen, Kai, Jing, Lu.
Lu Ling.