After two months of renovation
our Hot News House
is finally reopening.
That's great!
Wonderful!
Nowadays,
the romantic situation of Princess Qianqiu from Huiyin
has become quite mysterious.
We'll be using the latest live tracking technology
to bring you real-time updates.
Speaking of Princess Qianqiu and General Qin,
for the past two months,
there was
absolutely no news about them.
Everyone thought they were having a relationship crisis.
Yesterday at the ceremony,
they rang the bell together to dispel the rumors.
But who would have thought that now
the Second Prince Kanghe from Beiyu has arrived.
And apparently,
he and Princess Qianqiu have a history together.
Princess,
good afternoon.
Hello.
Your Highness, Second Prince of Beiyu,
what brings you here?
Of course I'm here to keep you company.
The Lord of Huiyin said yesterday
that you should show me around for a day.
I heard today is your Lantern Festival in Huiyin,
let's go to the city together.
What's so special about the Lantern Festival?
Come on.
Let's go.
I didn't expect the Second Prince to have this side to him.
Sister,
my feelings for you are genuine.
If you don't want to go with me,
then I'll stay here with you.
I already have plans.
Second Prince, please leave.
Brother Che,
happy fake third anniversary to us.
Look.
He was here.
Sister.
Where are you going? Second Prince, please stay.
The Princess needs to change her clothes.
A storm is coming.
Qin Che.
Take care, sir.
Come.
Let me tell you.
Just do it like this.
Understand?
Go now.
I heard the birds have taken flight,
Yet love remains between the two,
From Qin times, old bonds will reunite.
Kid.
Who told you to recite it like that?
Are you Qin Che?
Yes, I am.
A beautiful lady
said she's waiting for you at the usual place.
Alright.
From Qin times, old bonds will reunite,
Che Guang.
What are you doing here?
General,
I've finally found you.
We've spotted those Northern Isle rebels outside the city.
Let's hurry over there.
You go ahead,
I have some matters to attend to. I'll catch up soon.
All right.
Princess.
You're saying Qin Che fled after committing a crime?
Yes, sister.
I sent people to wait at his residence all night,
but he never showed up.
He can't be found anywhere in the city.
He must have known
that I found evidence of him murdering Liu Yue
and that's why he ran away.
Qin Che killed Liu Yue?
Second Prince,
don't speak such nonsense here.
I was the one
who provided Qin Che with an alibi back then.
Now he's about to become
Princess Huiyin's consort.
Rumors can be devastating.
Sister, you've been deceived by him.
I carefully searched
Lord Liuyue's study on the night of his murder
and found under the desk chair
a very thin strand of golden thread.
The same thread was found on Qin Che's clothes from that night.
You want to convict
the Second Prince based on this thread alone?
Aren't you being too frivolous?
Of course not.
I reviewed your case files from that day
and found that both of you were drunk that night.
Sister, are you certain
that you stayed by Qin Che's side the entire evening
and were completely sober?
I...
This is what I scraped from
underneath the incense burner in my sister's room.
There are still some remnants of the sleeping incense.
How dare you, Qin Che!
You dared to use Qianqiu to harm the Northern Yu envoy
and you're still on the run.
From now on,
his engagement to Qianqiu is canceled,
and he must be captured immediately.
Father!
So this is the fine husband you've chosen!
The matter is already clear.
Don't make things worse.
Father!
Sister.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you about this earlier,
but you need to understand
I'm only doing what's best for you.
This Qin Che is not a good person.
He has ulterior motives
and is only getting close to you to use you.
Stop talking.
Father.
Please give me three more days.
Right now, all we have is inconclusive evidence
that doesn't amount to much.
Father.
Lord Ma.
Besides the case of Lord Liuyue's murder,
I have another matter to discuss with you.
Second Prince, please speak.
I've fallen in love with Princess Qianqiu at first sight,
and I would like to ask you, Lord Ma,
to give Princess Qianqiu's hand in marriage to me.
Our two cities
shouldn't become enemies over someone as insignificant as Qin Che.
No!
Regarding the marriage
we must consider Qianqiu's wishes.
If it can foster goodwill between our two nations,
I would hope that the Second Prince
completes his investigation of this case
before I pass judgment on Qin Che.
I can agree to this marriage,
but regarding Qin Che's matter,
you
must keep your word.
Your daughter takes her leave.
If you ask me,
Princess Qianqiu
has spent so much time with General Qin,
she must choose General Qin,
don't you think?
Breaking news!
General Qin is wanted for murder,
and Princess Qianqiu is about to marry the Second Prince of Beiyu.
What?
Is that true?
How come I didn't know about this?
Mother.
So early in the morning,
what brings you here?
I want to use that favor.
Can you help me find Qin Che?
If the city lord can't find him,
how could I possibly find him?
Please send more people to look for him.
If you find him,
please tell him
to run far away.
I heard you're going to marry Kang Hena.
You went through so much trouble to avoid the arranged marriage before,
why are you agreeing to it now because of Qin Che?
Because I want to.
Good morning, sister.
Sister,
we're getting married in a few days,
how can you be so cold to me?
What marriage in a few days?
Don't you know, sister?
This morning, Lord Ma arranged our marriage,
set for the fourth of July, an auspicious day for weddings.
But today is already the 28th.
It is a bit rushed.
But when we return to North Isle,
I will certainly give you
a much grander wedding ceremony.
Sister, please don't overexert yourself these days.
I'll go ahead and make preparations.
Princess,
why don't we escape?
Fangjue is gone too.
Xiaoliu,
tell me,
where could he possibly run to?
General Qin has no one to rely on in Huiyin.
If we're talking about who's closest to him,
it would only be you, Princess.
Could he have left Huiyin altogether?
The closest person to him is me.
Home.
I know where he's gone.
Xinjiang, Di, Can.
Xinjiang, Di.
Lei, Cai, Long, Yan, Peng, Song, Hui.
Bo, Jun.
Zhuang, Cheng.
Jin, Sheng.
Dan, Wei, Ping, Ling.
Miao, An, Hao, Wang, Tao, Rui, Kai, Qing, Yu.
Ni.
Yue.
Nan, Zi, Lei, Ze, Zhen, Yao, Zai, Zhen, Kai, Jing, Lu.
Ting.
Lu Ling.