=Accidental Firing=
=Episode 21=
You really don't learn your lesson.
Fell into my hands again.
Want to die together?
Don't drag me down with you.
Wait. You can't die yet.
You're more useful alive.
But I'm a little reluctant.
Just now,
that smile of yours
was just like me.
Behave yourself.
Guess what I'm going to do with it?
(If I act rashly,)
(it will mess up Lu Yan's plan.)
(But...)
(What if...)
(Lu Yan, I'm sorry.)
(I can't leave Xiao alone.)
(I must find him.)
Miss Mu.
Tomorrow is our wedding day.
Come back with me.
Dong Lin.
You're still dreaming even now?
Xiao.
Can you come back with me now?
You unfilial son.
Why are you here?
Mr. Ling.
Tell your people to stay put.
Otherwise,
you will die together with Dong Lin.
Dong Lin? What are you talking about?
I have no patience.
If you dare to harm us...
Yao.
Let me make a phone call.
Where is Xiao?
He is still alive.
But you won't see him
until the wedding ends.
Even now,
you still want me to marry you?
Why not?
Miss Mu.
Life is but a fleeting mist.
Nothing can be retained.
Why make life so hard for yourself?
Marry me
and we'll enjoy wealth together.
Even if life is fleeting,
it's different for being remembered
with honor or shame.
Dong Lin.
You won't end well.
Okay.
If you don't agree,
you'll cause Liang Xiao's death.
You...
It's Lu Yan.
Young Master.
The villa's been taken.
The evidence is in hand.
But...
What?
Don't be rash.
Governor,
Miss Mu's taken away by Dong Lin.
Miss Mu.
Try on the wedding dress.
What are you scheming now?
Nothing.
You want me to exchange
Liang Xiao's life for it?
What are you doing?
How dare you be so rude?
Get out.
Yes.
Lu Yan.
Go with me.
You should be the one leaving.
Mu Lan.
Wedding dress try-on time.
Try touching her again!
Lu Yan.
Trust me.
I will protect myself well.
Lu Yan.
You can only save me if you leave.
Trust me.
You should go.
You satisfied now?
Let go of me.
During these ten years,
I have lived in fear every day.
Never dared to spend a night
with a woman.
Because I fear one slip in my sleep
will cost me everything.
You know what?
I can only live on fantasies.
I get satisfaction from fantasies.
Mu Lan.
Be obedient.
That way,
Liang Xiao will suffer less.
Look.
Aren't they beautiful?
I think we are really a great match.
But I still feel a little regret.
That is,
if you want revenge,
you should do it earlier.
Why do you work with Lu Yan?
If it weren't for him,
just you and me,
would we have been together?
Shut up.
Remember to attend my wedding tomorrow.
Be on time.
♪The night in my glass is falling low♪
♪Who shattered the silence♪
♪It was me♪
♪Fired the shot for love recklessly♪
♪I won't be a bird in the storm♪
♪Nor sleep forever where shadows lie♪
♪I only pray, in the decade to come♪
♪I'll break from the dark♪
♪Must learn the art of a silver tongue♪
♪Must have a heart like a desert♪
♪Only this stubborn flame inside stays♪
♪Let the board be flipped♪
♪The fate reversed♪
♪Though happy endings won't come♪
♪I'll stand with you♪
♪Pierce through the flame of the night♪
♪Even if the road is long and far♪
♪Have no fear for the risk and danger♪
♪When all the joys and sorrows♪
♪When the dust settles, the music ends♪
♪This romance of bravery♪
♪This story isn't over♪