=Accidental Firing=
=Episode 3=
But you still haven't told me
how this letter
got into your hands.
When I was on the train,
I saw someone else.
Young Master Lu.
Yan,
what happened?
This woman is very dangerous.
Is there some misunderstanding?
She even dares to sow discord
between my son and me.
This woman is really interesting.
I gave the evidence to Mr. Lu.
Being after me won't help.
(This afternoon,
Lu Yan will be in the western suburbs.)
You wrote this, right?
Words alone are no proof.
Governor,
you can't wrong me.
We fought on the train.
The scent on you that day
and the current one
are exactly the same as on this note.
Your evidence
is really ingenious.
(Xiao?)
Whether to repay my rescue
or for my injury today because of you,
you should take responsibility.
Let go.
Treat my wound.
(I must quickly find Xiao.)
How did you know
I'd be in the western suburbs?
Governor, you are really persistent.
Do you know Zhu?
Or
are you Zhu?
You're not dead?
I am Mu Lan. Who is Zhu?
I've been looking for her.
When I was young,
my parents were busy.
It was Ms. Wang,
Zhu's mother, who raised me.
Only Zhu was always with me.
I liked her very much.
We went to the western suburbs
to take a photo and bury it
under a tree.
We promised to dig it out together
today, ten years later.
In these ten years,
I have been thinking about this day
and Zhu all the time.
It's really touching.
Are you Zhu or not?
Only Zhu and I know
about the western suburbs.
Enough.
I can't cure your lovesickness.
You should leave.
I will repay this favor.
Let's bury the photo
and dig it up again ten years from now.
Ten years?
Will the photo still be there
in ten years?
Definitely
If it's here after ten years,
I will marry you.
Then I better dig it deeper.
Mr. Lu, Zhao Debiao ambushed Lu Yan
in the western suburbs.
He acted so quickly.
This woman is very dangerous.
So it was Mu Lan's doing.
(Using Anhe Industry as bait,)
(not only did I lure Lu Yan
from his station to Haicheng,)
(but I also provoked Zhao Debiao)
(and acquired Mu Lan,
a charming yet dangerous blade.)
(It's three kills with one stone.)
Find out more about Mu Lan.
Okay.
You're still up this late.
Are you waiting to report to me?
Tell me.
What did you say to Miss Mu?
I'm a bit tired.
You want a massage?
You're smuggling arms.
How dare you engage
in such a dangerous business?
That's because
I have you, a good son and a governor.
If you dare
damage my father's reputation,
I will make you disappear
without hesitation.
As long as you are filial to me,
that kind of thing will never happen.
Our family
will only prosper for a long time.
You don't really think
I came back for Anhe Industry, do you?
Sister.
I've been wearing it.
There's no anesthesia. Hold on.
Sister,
how did you know I was here?
You know why.
Press it.
This was the place where we first met
when we were kids.
Later,
we often looked at the stars here
and listened
to the wind.
I promised you I would wear it,
and you promised me
you would disappear from my life.
I did it, but you broke your promise.
Why won't you let me stay?
That dart will expose you.
Leave Haicheng immediately.
Or I will throw the necklace away.
You know what that means.
Let go.
Coming.
Mr. Lu.
Miss Mu.
Mr. Lu,
are you here to accept my proposal?
Of course, I can agree to your request.
But I'm still a little worried
about you.
Mr. Lu,
what should I do to ease your worries?
If it weren't for that accident,
that letter
would have been delivered to me.
But there was an accident.
Miss Mu,
if you hope
our future cooperation goes smoothly,
you need
to make that accident disappear.
Accident?
That accident
said you're very dangerous.
This woman
is very dangerous.
(He wants me to kill Lu Yan.)
♪The night in my glass is falling low♪
♪Who shattered the silence♪
♪It was me♪
♪Fired the shot for love recklessly♪
♪I won't be a bird in the storm♪
♪Nor sleep forever where shadows lie♪
♪I only pray, in the decade to come♪
♪I'll break from the dark♪
♪Must learn the art of a silver tongue♪
♪Must have a heart like a desert♪
♪Only this stubborn flame inside stays♪
♪Let the board be flipped♪
♪The fate reversed♪
♪Though happy endings won't come♪
♪I'll stand with you♪
♪Pierce through the flame of the night♪
♪Even if the road is long and far♪
♪Have no fear for the risk and danger♪
♪When all the joys and sorrows♪
♪When the dust settles, the music ends♪
♪This romance of bravery♪
♪This story isn't over♪