Come on.
Hurry in.
Put them here.
Put those over there.
This is...
The Women's clinic
has been gaining popularity in Chang'an.
I'm the boss after all.
Mr. Xiao
is afraid that the clinic can't meet the demand
the medicine supply can't keep up,
which will affect the reputation.
I've brought medicine from the south overnight,
and even calculated the wages.
Mr. Xiao,
you're very considerate.
Xinyue is fortunate
to have someone so thoughtful looking out for her.
A'Nong is right.
The medicine issue
can't be taken lightly.
I'll go to the backyard.
The backyard is over there.
Well...
I...
I'm sorry.
Five pence a jar.
Well...
It's hard to do business.
In the past few months,
we have sold less than 20 boxes
of ointment.
Our regular customers
are all flocking to that Women's clinic
to buy some Warm Palace Ointment.
At five pence a jar,
it's half the price
of ours.
If this continues,
we'll be out of business!
Exactly!
I heard
the owner of Ren'an Hall mentioned
the Xiao family's master
sent three carts of medicine from the south overnight.
Even our monopoly on Minshan angelica
has been taken by them.
If this continues,
we won't even be able to do the medicine business.
I've said it before,
that Women's Clinic hasn't been verified by the guild.
Who knows what's in
their Warm Palace Ointment?
I and you...
Shut up!
What's the point of arguing?
We need a solution.
How about hiring some thugs
to hang around the clinic every day,
saying that
women shouldn't be practicing medicine,
it's improper.
That way, those noble ladies
will be too embarrassed to go there.
Good.
Not good.
The Women's clinic
is backed by the Xiao Family.
It's not wise to confront them openly.
No matter how powerful the Xiao Family is,
they can't defy the law.
The Warm Palace Ointment is unapproved,
and sold illegally.
That's already against the law.
Tomorrow,
I'll file a complaint at the court.
I'll claim she's selling fake medicine,
causing harm.
One death
is enough to warrant her execution.
Master,
but her medicine
is effective.
Effective?
The people are easily misled,
and the truth is hard to reveal.
As long as we muddy the waters,
she won't be able to stand.
Let's do it this way.
I'll go find a few trustworthy people.
I'll make sure that the Women's Clinic
is closed.
Slow down.
Yan Ge.
There are many people today.
come down and help Xinyue with triage.
Take this number
and go queue over there.
Next one.
One for the female surgery.
Quack doctor!
Women practicing medicine
violates the natural order.
Now they're getting their just desserts!
How long has this been going on?
Quack doctor!
Quack doctor, come out!
You killed her!
The Women's clinic killed her!
She's a fraud!
My daughter
took the medicine she prescribed,
and suffered from unbearable pain
for days!
Today,
today,
she just passed away like this.
The so-called female medicine master
actually killed someone.
Are you still going to let her
continue treating patients?
She has tarnished the reputation of physicians,
a disgrace to the medical community.
Today,
if you don't give us an explanation,
I'll cover the front with paper money.
Let's see how long
this clinic can stay open!
It's you!
You killed my sister!
Pay back with your life!
Stop!
If the clinic harms people,
the law will deal with it.
You can't take the law into your own hands!
You...
What do you have to say?
Carrying corpses to protest,
and scattering paper money on the road,
do you dare let me examine them publicly?
Sir,
arrest her!
She must not harm anyone else!
Mr. Xiao,
are you going to protect
this murderer?
Sir, may I take a closer look?
She's probably trying to tamper
with the body,
cover up the evidence!
Without examining the body,
how can you blame the Women's Clinic?
What if it was a chronic illness
or there's another hidden truth?
You can't just convict us like this!
The corpse is rising!
She made the corpse rise!
How is this possible?
How could this fake death technique
be exposed?
It's broad daylight.
What are you afraid of?
You...
How dare you be so malicious
and show disrespect to the deceased?
I...
Are you so sure your sister is dead?
How about
I bring her back to life?
You...
What did you say?
Look!
What are you doing?
I don't know.
It's fire therapy.
Here we go.
You can't even tell the difference between wine and water.
Good.
So, you two are the liars.
No, no, no.
No.
No, no.
It's not my fault.
I'm just the head of the Medical Guild.
I'm just upholding justice.
Take them away.
Let me go.
What are you doing?
Please wait, Guild Master.
What?
Are you trying to implicate me in this?
Do you have any evidence?
Master,
my Women's Clinic
has been open for many months,
but we have never visited the guild.
We apologize for the lack of manners.
We will visit another day.
We would appreciate
your guidance.
Xuezhi.
Come.
I've heard that a new
Women's clinic has opened in Chang'an,
and it's very popular with the ladies.
This is Madam Yin,
and this is Madam Su.
Xuezhi
is my best friend from the Bright Moon Pavilion.
We grew up together since childhood.
You're pregnant?
Yes.
Yan Ge,
I came to tell you
that I'm pregnant
and about to leave Chang'an.
What?
What did you say?
It's been two months.
It's from a patron at the Moonlight Pavilion.
Are you crazy?
Don't get me wrong.
He's different from the other men here.
He likes to talk to me
about poetry,
the world,
and never treats me with disrespect.
Do you know who you are?
Do you know what would happen
if Mom finds out?
You must get rid of this child.
How can you say that?
Do you also think
I'm not worthy of a good man?
I'm just worried about your safety.
How much do you know about this man?
His surname is Cui.
He's a scholar.
His family owns land.
He's not a playboy.
And he promised me
to marry me
as his wife.
If he truly wishes to marry you,
why hasn't he acted sooner?
The Bright Moon Pavilion is not easily dealt with.
How would your mother allow you to leave with a child?
No,
this child
must be aborted today.
Yan Ge's concerns are valid.
The child you carry is indeed precious,
but
the road ahead is perilous and uncertain.
If things go wrong,
your life will be at risk.
I know the road ahead is perilous,
but he has promised me a legitimate place.
How can I be trapped in this
infernal pit for a lifetime?
I had hoped to share this good news with you,
and that you would offer me your blessings.
I apologize for disturbing you.
Today,
just pretend I was never here.
Xuezhi!
Yan Ge,
I understand
your relationship.
You want to warn her,
but whether she believes
his promise or not,
whether she
keeps or discards the child,
these are her choices.
No one can make the decision for her.
As her friend,
all you can do
is to stand behind her
and help her
when she is hurt.
I've been waiting for six hours.
He probably never intended to see me.
I can't just keep waiting like this.
Still waiting?
The guild's been tied up with trivial matters.
Sorry for the delay.
Forgive me for the disturbance.
I came today
only to submit the list of female doctors.
I hope it can be included.
To visit the guild,
this is all you bring?
You should be surprised.
How could a young lady
understand these?
Register?
This is a century-old rule of our guild.
How can it be easily broken?
Women practicing medicine
is against the norms.
If you want us to make an exception,
it's not impossible.
As long as your Women's Clinic
agrees to donate 60% of its profits each month
to our guild for distribution.
Other clinics only contribute 20%.
I'm here today
not just for the Women's clinic,
but also to fight for the future female doctors
to have a fair chance.
What we want
is not an exception,
but fairness.
You've got the noble ladies
all flocking to you.
60% of the profit
is not too much.
We're not here
to beg for membership,
just to file a record.
Even without the guild,
the Women's Clinic
will still stand in the market.
If you deliberately
block us,
we
won't back down.
Let's go.
You...
President.
What...
What's going on?
I don't know.
You little bitch.
How dare you have a bastard behind my back.
How could you do this?
You all watch carefully.
This is the end of being unruly.
I just want a sincere relationship.
Why won't you let me go?
Sincere?
Open your eyes.
The rouge in this building,
which one isn't made with lives?
You, a slut who's been slept with by many,
how dare you dream of flying out of this golden cage?
Hit her!
Hit her until she aborts the bastard!
Cui!