I thought
you'd abandoned me.
[After arriving in Panyu,]
[we'll switch to land route in Shangzhou.]
[At that time, we can]
[ambush and kill the Xiao family's caravan.]
No.
It's not like this.
My father wouldn't do this.
You still refuse to admit it?
Yin Xinyue,
I've given you a chance.
Do you dare to say the handwriting and seal on it
are not from him?
Yes.
But my father
doesn't know any bandit at all.
This...
This must be forged.
You have to believe me.
Do you believe
I can kill you right now?
I'm not lying to you.
For the past six months,
you have repeatedly defended him,
and I have repeatedly softened.
I'm not lying to you.
Now,
and in the past.
I won't believe a single word
you say now.
There's one thing
you all got wrong.
It wasn't my father who sought out Lord Xiao,
but Lord Xiao who approached my father.
Since my mother's passing,
my father
hasn't dared to take any risks.
He's terrified
of leaving me alone in this world.
He's so afraid of death.
If it weren't for Lord Xiao
hadn't persuaded him with the greater good,
he wouldn't have taken such risks.
Now he's
missing,
his reputation ruined.
All the deeds
of Yin Family
are here.
They're all here.
Yin,
are you sure about this?
If it weren't for your persuasion,
a mere merchant like me
shouldn't meddle in such court affairs.
But since I've promised you,
I won't back down.
Su Erman
knows me inside out.
If my mission is exposed,
he will come after me first.
At that time,
I hope your son
will take care of my daughter.
I thought catching Su Erman
would be the end of it.
But it turns out
to be linked to so many
inside dealings of the market.
The forces behind this corruption case
are deeply rooted.
If not cleaned up,
this market
will become a place for the rich to exploit the poor.
So,
I have to bother you to go with me.
You're welcome.
Although I'm a businessman,
I know the national righteousness.
Don't worry.
I have reported to the Minister.
At that time,
the Capital Prefecture will send someone
to the Xiao Family's caravan
to ensure our safety.
Perhaps,
the concerns you have today
will never come to pass.
At that time,
these documents
will be returned to their rightful owner.
But Lord Xiao said that day
he had never received any letters.
Then why didn't you say so sooner?
I didn't say anything because
I didn't want to
add more suspicion
to our newly improved relationship.
Besides,
seven years ago,
after I broke my promise,
I went to see you,
but you refused to meet me.
Now you only believe
what you think is the truth.
Have you ever really trusted me?
If someone tells you
your father killed someone
and faked his death,
would you believe it?
All the evidence now
points to my father.
What can I do
to prove myself?
By my loneliness?
Or
our friendship seven years ago?
Thank you, my lord,
for hearing me out.
Seven years ago,
we each held onto our own truths.
And now,
we've hurt each other deeply
over these matters.
Today,
I only wish to clear my name,
to honor my father's memory,
and live up to your father's words
of family and country.
From now on,
you and I
go our separate ways,
each finding our own joy.
Very well,
as you wish.
Xinyue was framed.
The arsenic incident
is entirely fabricated.
The Capital Prefecture convicted her
and used torture
before the truth was uncovered.
If bias clouds justice,
under torture,
anyone can be forced to confess.
If the law loses its fairness,
and power trumps conscience,
today it's Madam Yin,
tomorrow it could be any of us.
Ms. Lin's words,
under torture,
anyone would confess.
It truly shocks me.
You helped me.
How can I turn a blind eye?
I'm willing to sign the petition
to request a retrial.
Even if it can't ensure her safety,
it will let the world know.
May the heavens not forsake us.
and justice is done.
May the good-hearted be rewarded.
You'll need to bribe the guards.
This jade bracelet...
This...
How can this be?
Without her,
I wouldn't have the courage to face the world.
Take it.
Protect her well.
We are all women,
born into noble families,
and still have a voice.
If we remain silent,
where will the women of the world seek justice?
Rest assured,
my son works at the Ministry of Justice.
If there is indeed a grievance,
he will handle it with fairness.
With us here,
don't worry.
Open the door!
Yes, my lord.
Minister.
Don't move.
You're injured.
I didn't know you were coming.
What brings you here?
This is medicine for your wound.
Take it.
Take care of yourself.
If you need anything else,
just let me know.
I'll have my servants prepare it.
Thank you, Lord Xiao.
I am unworthy of such
consideration from you.
Your father and the Xiao Family
have ventured into perilous situations
while assisting me in investigations.
I truly owe you so much.
Madam Yin,
don't worry,
everything is for the best.
From now on,
no one in this prison will trouble you.
You must take good care of yourself
and wait patiently here.
I'll be on my way now.
Will Yunzhou blame me?
What do you mean by that?
Your husband's mourning period is almost over.
Regarding the Women's Clinic,
I intended to
ask Madam Yin to put her career aside
and get married with you.
As a woman,
she should take care of her husband
and children.
It's not a good idea
to show up in public.
But I didn't expect
her to hide arsenic in the clinic.
You must be overthinking things.
You were just looking out for me.
How could I ever blame you?
It's just that Madam Yin
was being careless.
Did this cause a fight
between you and Madam Yin?
Then I would truly be the guilty one.
You're being overly concerned.
There's nothing
to discuss between us.
By the way,
the Mid-Autumn Festival is coming up.
My niece
used to come here
around this time every year,
claiming to visit me,
but really,
it was all for you.
Your father
was quite fond of her
and considered marrying her to you.
I'll take care of it.
Yunzhou,
although you and Lady Yin
are about to get married,
but
my niece likes you so much.
I think she would be willing
to be your concubine.
How about
you take her as your concubine
after the festival?
It would be
a good deed.
My fiancée is still in prison.
Even if she's released,
she's unworthy of the Xiao Family.
However,
engagement and annulment
must follow proper etiquette.
We can't rush it.
We must consult the Patriarch
and consult with the elders.
It must also be recorded in the ancestral hall,
only then can it be considered done.
You,
you're always tough on the outside, soft on the inside.
You're deeply in love with her.
How could you just decide to break off the engagement like this?
But the Yin family
is now disgraced.
It's indeed not suitable for a high-born family like us.
The Xiao Family's reputation,
and the clan's prestige,
I must consider them.
Though the Xiao Family isn't noble,
we're a respected family in this city.
How can we allow a tainted person
to stain our name?
The Yin Family is already implicated.
The engagement must be annulled.
Liu,
you're always gentle and virtuous.
If she could marry you,
it would be a blessing for our family.
Yunzhou,
are you really so resolute?
Since the tea has gone cold,
there's no need to add more.
Hurry up!
Madam Yin,
are you satisfied?
Yes.
I...
I'm not someone
who would compromise
my professional integrity for a few coins.
This...
This is really too much.
Please,
enjoy your meal
and your drink.
The military officer in charge of the prison
has been arrested.
Your case
will be reopened for investigation.
No one will lay a hand on you anymore.
I believe,
once the storm blows over,
you'll
be out of here.
Take your time to eat,
and drink.
When you're done,
just let us know,
and we'll clean up for you.
Please,
take your time.
Enjoy your chat.
We have already
gathered the noblewomen of the city
to petition on your behalf.
Your innocence will be cleared,
so stay here and don't worry
Don't worry about the rumors.
Everything in the prison
has been taken care of.
Just stay here.
Mr. Xiao,
are you ready to discuss marriage?
Discuss marriage?
With whom?