♪Will you be my love?♪
♪Will you be my baby?♪
♪Let me watch over you♪
♪Let me take care of you♪
♪Will you be my love?♪
♪Will you be my baby?♪
♪Let me watch over you♪
♪Let me take care of you♪
♪You ask me questions♪
♪I want more than
the answers to these questions♪
♪Your questions♪
=No. 1 For You Special Edition=
Do you want to die?
You have gastropathy.
Why did you have spicy hotpot?
What's wrong with you?
College kids today are hard to understand.
You, too.
Make that for him every day
if you want him dead.
Won't do that again.
I had it.
Why are you yelling at him?
It's none of his business.
In the US, the owner of a bar
can be fined for not stopping a customer
from drunk driving.
He cooked it for you.
I can absolutely yell at him.
Zhou Shu Yi.
This stomach medicine
can ease your pain for a while.
But you still need to go to the doctor.
You can eat light and oil-free food only.
But if you want to die,
have more spicy hotpots.
How can a school doctor
threat his patient?
(School doctor)
(Pei Shou Yi)
Are you sure this dummy is the one?
You...
Have some rest.
Alright.
I'll go and get a pack of cigarettes.
You get some rest, kid.
What's wrong with them?
They look close.
Are they...
Ouch!
Why did you say that in front of him?
Just for fun.
Someone with affective disorder
can have fun too?
Yeah, fun to watch.
So that's my future cousin-in-law?
Good-looking.
Isn't it good?
Nothing else but the look.
But you don't know him well.
I really can't tell.
Maybe...
I need to know more about him.
Don't bother.
There's no way that he likes me.
And you still like him?
He makes me
who I am today.
I met him at Grade 5.
My parents got divorced
that time.
I was really sad.
How could a little kid
possibly accept the fact that his father
abandoned the family?
But I knew that
my mom felt worse than me.
So I pretended to be strong.
But sometimes, I just couldn't help it.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
Are you hurt?
Are you all right?
Hey.
Look at your snot and tears.
So ugly.
None of your business.
My dad...
abandoned me and my mom.
You've still got a mom.
My mom has gone to heaven.
Or...
I'll give you my dad.
He always causes trouble.
Nobody gives their dad away like that.
How about this?
I'll give myself to you.
Let me know if you need anything.
Think of me as your father.
Good boy. That's a good smile.
Don't waste your time crying.
Work hard and be strong!
Shu Yi.
Where are you?
Come to me if you want to cry.
I'll be there for you.
My name is Zhou Shu Yi.
I'm in Class 1 Grade 5 of
San Qiao Elementary School.
Bye.
Although it turned out
that he was probably just passing by and
came to me out of curiosity.
After I transferred to his school,
he couldn't even recognize me.
But he saved me that afternoon.
You don't understand
what his hug and shoulders
meant to me
back then.
I'm going to the class.
I thought you'd skip class
and let him know what you've done for him
so that you can...
make him fall for you.
I just want to be his friend before graduation.
Keep on with the unrequited love.
Good, bro. You're a masochist.
Fine.
Anyway, you're going to America
with your mom after graduation.
It's better this way.
He wasn't lovelorn,
I wouldn't have a chance to be his friend.
So you want to help him go through it
to return the favor?
Are you a white crane?
If you're so full of love,
spread it.
Don't you talk about me.
This cup is broken and you...
Careful with your mouth.
I'll leave him to you.
All right, that's all for today.
Let's go.
I'm busy.
Shu Yi.
Are you free?
Why?
We haven't had dinner together for a long time.
I'm kind of busy.
I was going to ask you...
You...
Do you also like Yu Xin?
Don't you say you'd give up because of me.
If you like her and she likes you,
then it's good enough.
But...
last time you saw us...
Are you OK with it?
If I'm not OK with it,
will you give Yu Xin to me?
I don't want to lose a friend.
But I like Yu Xin a lot.
I can't do this.
That's it.
Protect your girlfriend and be tough.
Never give her to anyone else.
So...
you don't like Yu Xin?
I like...
both of you!
Come on. I was so worried.
Take good care of her,
or I'll beat you up.
All right, all right!
Fang Zheng Wen.
You like her
but she expressed her feelings first.
Is that what a man should do?
Because I was worried about you.
It's good that the one you love happens to
love you back.
I'm so jealous!
All right.
You need to treat me to dinner.
Piece of cake.
-Let's go.
-Go.
What would you like to eat?
Gao Shi De.
How's your stomach?
Zheng Wen talked to me.
About what?
He asked me if I liked Yu Xin.
I said ,"If I did,
would you give her to me?"
Seriously?
He didn't even hesitate
before refusing me.
He's always been gentle.
I didn't expect him to be so tough.
I feel so happy.
I hope he treats Yu Xin well,
or I'll hit him hard.
You're right.
Time can heal everything.
Great!
Congratulations.
All right.
That's it, got it?
Hey, here are the top two swimmers
of the swimming club.
Do you want to come to
the ghost night held by the juniors.
It's like a farewell party.
In a dark and scary night,
the campus horror is waiting for you!
And
if you come,
I'm sure the juniors
will be super happy, right?
Yes!
I'm not going.
Come on, man.
You've been hanging out with him
and ignored us.
Tell you what.
We've arranged some stage games.
You'll get a nice present if you win.
And
it'll be much harder this time.
No phones allowed!
Show us how smart
and brave you are!
Come on!
Let's create some good memories
before graduation!
Alright, everyone?
Yeah!
-Competition?
-Memories before graduation.
One more would be nice.
I'll be free if I win.
Did you hear that?
Did you hear the footsteps?
Huh?
Footsteps?
There it is.
So terrible!
I told you guys.
I didn't lie to you.
This is the third one who came out crying.
I assume all of you a talisman, right?
I'm not kidding.
This school used to be a mass grave.
You should take it seriously.
Let's welcome our next challenger,
Zheng Wen.
Come on.
Please.
Please leave your phone here? Thank you.
Don't be afraid, senior.
I trust you.
Let me go first.
I'm in a hurry.
And it's not scary at all.
Alright, we've got
a tough challenger.
I hope he won't come out crying.
Sorry, senior.
Please wait for another 15 minutes.
Let's stop here.
So horrible.
It's scary.
Don't worry.
I'll protect you.
I won't leave you alone.
Don't worry.
Sorry.
They've made it too scary.
Liu Bing Wei, you can do this!
Zhou Shu Yi.
I'm coming to your rescue!
What are you doing here?
Did I scare you?
So cute.
The juniors asked me to join them.
I wanted to give you
more nice memories about the university.
Look. I even dressed like a ghost.
You're here on your own?
Well...
I'll stay with you.
You scared me!
What are you doing back there?
You got in the way.
Oh.
Go and win the games.
I thought you had already let go of it.
I'm just glad that they're happy together.
You'd better concentrate.
I'm gonna beat you this time.
(Oh, my!)
(When does the school get so scary?)
(The flashlight is out of battery.)
(Is Gao Shi De still here?)
Why are you still here?
Go ahead!
I...
I'm afraid of ghosts.
Seriously?
You're afraid of ghosts?
Well then,
let's stop competing with each other.
I won't feel the sense of achievement even if I win.
Let's just go together.
Why are you standing still?
Will I slow you down?
Don't worry.
I got your back.
Come on.
Don't be mincing.
Just follow me.
You go first.
It's more scary in the back.
Ready.
Where is Shi De?
Did you hear what I just said?
Come on, come on!
I'm begging you, come on.
Sorry.
I hit you too hard.
What?
Did you see Shi De?
Did you see Zhou Shu Yi?
What are you doing?
Let's go together.
Hands off.
Don't follow me!
Stop pulling.
Let me go.
You're insane!
Too dramatic.
Why did they hide the clue in the health center?
Yeah.
So dramatic.
What's that noise?
It's the wind.
You better start looking for clues.
Let's get out of here
after we get the stamp.
All right.
You scared me.
What's the matter?
I'm afraid you're scared.
I'm just telling you that I'm here.
Idiot.
Let's just leave it
and go to the next one.
No.
If we don't get the stamp here,
we won't get those for later stages.
Oh.
Don't be afraid.
Don't be scared.
Gao Shi De, let's get out of here!
You need to calm down.
Well done.
Zhou Shu Yi.
Hello!
Anybody?
Anyone out there?
Hello!
We're locked in here!
Is there anyone out there?
Hello!
Anybody?
You've yelled for ten minutes.
Have some water.
It's better than doing nothing.
Why does a health center
need iron-grating windows?
I thought you know this place well.
Do something!
What can I do?
I don't have my phone with me.
Perhaps...
the school police will patrol around here.
Or Shou Yi will come and open
the door tomorrow morning.
You're not helping.
The phone isn't working.
There's a laptop here.
It should have been connected to Wi-Fi.
We can ask Zheng Wen to come and help us.
Password sucks.
Hungry?
There's got to be some food here.
Here we go.
Do you have a secret crush on Pei Shou Yi?
That's why you two are so close.
You even know where he puts the instant noodles.
How long has it been?
Are you...
You know my affairs.
We're on the same boat.
Relax.
I won't laugh at you.
How long has it been?
It's been long.
It's just...
I like you, not him.
Then, I'm relieved.
You...
You like me?
No way!
Yeah.
No way.
You've got to be kidding me.
Of course I am.
You paired me up with Shou Yi.
Miser.
You like to talk back a lot.
Just another minute.
Here.
Eat up.
What about you?
I'm not hungry. Just eat.
Is this the only one left?
You talk too much. Just eat it.
Let's share it.
We don't have to starve together.
At least one of us won't be starved to death.
You don't have to do this.
That's what friends do.
What did you say?
Eat it or leave it.
Alright.
Though we are friends,
we still get to compete.
I won't lose to you forever.
And I'm not gonna let you win.
There is no winning or losing between us.
That's what friends do.
Maybe...
it's better this way.
=Lesson 3=
(It's been long)
(Next Episode)
You want a girlfriend?
Yeah.
Introduce one to me.
Aren't you going to tell him your feelings?
You're not as good as me.
Kiddo.
You like Gao Shi De...
He'll be mine.
I like you.
♪Only half of it will do♪
♪I don't understand why love♪
♪is always replaced by reality♪
♪I'm waiting at the place
where you left, like a fool♪
♪I never expect♪
♪that letting go is more painful than a breakup♪
♪You're getting further away from me♪
♪Yet I still treasure you in my heart♪
♪I've said goodbye to you♪
♪But I never want you to leave♪
♪Forgive me for never knowing♪
♪that letting go is more painful than a breakup♪
♪I will no longer be the reason♪
♪for you to be happy or sad♪
♪I've said goodbye to you♪
♪But I'm desperate to make you stay♪