♫ I won’t wish to catch those distant stars ♫
♫ I don’t want to make them mine ♫
♫ I won’t wish for the world to keep spinning♫
♫ I won’t turn back time ♫
♫ In this universe, there is nothing more meaningful ♫
♫ Than you whom I am longing for ♫
♫ I only beg for you to be with me forever ♫
♫ You're the only one I'm asking for ♫
♫ I want you to be my sky when I fly ♫
♫ Be my guiding star when I'm lost ♫
♫ I only beg for you to embrace me in the deep cold night ♫
♫ Hug me a little longer, hold me more tightly than yesterday ♫
♫ I won’t ask for anyone to understand it ♫
♫ I won’t ask for other precious things ♫
♫ I won’t ask for things that others are craving
and always trying to get ♫
♫ In this universe, there is nothing more meaningful ♫
♫ Than you whom I am longing for ♫
♫ I only beg for you to be with me forever ♫
♫ You're the only one I'm asking for ♫
♫ I want you to be my sky when I fly ♫
♫ Be my guiding star when I'm lost ♫
[Love by Chance: Episode 10]
♫ I only beg for you to embrace me in the deep cold night ♫
♫ Hug me a little longer
♫ Hold me more tightly than yesterday ♫
Hello, Pond.
My class just finished.
Can you please reserve a seat for me?
Then, can you please tell Can to reserve a seat for me?
Okay.
Where are you off to in a hurry?
I'm rushing off to the football stadium.
There is a match between our school and the Engineering Department.
I'll head off first.
Let me go with you.
Yes?
Let's go. Aren't you in a hurry?
Yes.
Ai'Pond, hurry up.
You're so slow, dude.
Yeah... Yeah... Yeah...
Woohoo!!!
Hey, save a seat for Ai'Pete, too.
Ai'Pete is coming, too?
Of course, he's coming.
Why would he come?
This is the engineering stand. Why doesn't he sit at the IC stand?
That's why I said you are so out of the loop.
Ai'Pete is coming to cheer for someone.
Not to cheer for his school. Geez.
Right, baby?
It's Ai'Ae, right?
I knew it.
Lately, they've been so damn inseparable.
Hello?
Yeah. I'm standing and waving my hand right here.
Can you see me?
What?
Your friend came, too?
Yeah... Sure... Sure... Come on over. There's space available.
'k, 'k, 'k.
Ai'Pete's friend is coming!?
Yeah.
Shit, Ai'Pond! Damn you.
- What?
- Block me.
Sit... Sit... Sit...
What is it?
Ai'Pete's friend?
Why? You haven't stopped hating his guts?
I don't really think he's as shitty as you said he was.
I've met him so many times already.
I haven't seen him do anything to me.
Except that... that he acted like I was invisible.
That's all. Other than that, he's never insulted me.
That guy is way shittier than you think.
Really? Tell me about it.
I'm leaving. I need to poop.
What!?!
If you need to poop then just go poop. Why are you telling me that??
Yeah. I'm going for sure. You should move out of the way.
I'm sorry.
Clumsy.
You, come have a talk with me.
Hey! Ae has the ball now.
Right there! There... There...
Go!!!
Yeah!!!
Just now, you did that on purpose. Right?
So, now you know that it's annoying?
What?
Do you know now?
That the way you're always looking to start a fight with me every time,
just how annoying it can be?
When did I look to start a fight with you?
Did you already forget that you punched me?
You even stuck your nose in my business.
That's because you have a dogmouth!
The first time we met, you said that we were dirty.
Another time we met you, you called us disgusting.
So, what do want me to do?
Bow down to the floor and thank you?
Just punching you only one time was generous enough.
Well, I just said the truth.
You're the one who's disgusting.
You're gay, right?
How very disgusting.
Is being gay that disgusting?
Yeah.
Then what I said was right then.
To say that your friend is very disgusting.
My friend?
Don't tell me that... that you're talking about Ai'Ae and Pete.
And if you were to tell me
the fact that I touched my lips on your lips seemed so disgusting,
then your friend might be even more disgusting than you know.
Because he uses...
to touch all over Pete.
Tin, you piece of shit.
My friend is not like you.
And when I said that being gay is disgusting,
I was insulting YOU.
I'm not insulting all gays around the world.
Ai'Ae and Ai'Pete... they're dating.
You have no right to criticize their love, damn it.
At the very least, they've never insulted others or looked down on others.
Ai'Ae is a nice guy.
Ai'Pete is also a nice guy.
Those guys are my friends.
So, whoever insults my friends,
is the same thing as being my enemy.
Are you done talking?
And you better remember this in that skull of yours...
That whether they're gay,
whether they're in a relationship,
those guys are still my friends either way.
And I'm not going to let anyone insult my friends, ever!
Do you understand?
I might be a lot more disgusting than you think.
P'Tul, nobody loves me.
Mom and dad don't even love me.
They love you, you know.
Even if no one loves you, I love you the most. All right?
Really? You really love me?
Of course, it's true.
If there's someone in this world who loves you the most,
remember that it's this big brother of yours, right here.
I hate him so much, Mom.
I don't see him as my younger brother.
Why didn't he just die when he was in your stomach?
Just wait and see.
I will take everything from that little bastard.
He has to also face what I faced.
He has to suffer even more than I suffered.
There isn't any...
There isn't anyone you can trust.
There isn't any, Tin.
Don't be stupid that foolish kid again.
Don't trust anyone.
If you don't trust anyone,
then you won't get hurt.
Engineering! Engineering! Engineering!
That's my friend. My friend. The one who scored two goals is my friend!
I'm not his girlfriend, okay?
I'm going to go insane... Acting like he got it himself.
What about your school? ChaAim.
We lost the round a while back already.
That's how it is for a school that's full of girls.
There weren't enough people that signed up, so the seniors had to play and help us.
But I think that... you look pretty happy that your own school is losing.
I'm not brave enough to shout,
but I'm still pretty happy.
So you must really like Ae, right?
Oh... I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to pry.
Let's just say we didn't say anything about it.
Am I being that obvious?
If you're asking like this, then that means I can answer. Right?
Well... Not really. You don't seem that obvious. If it was an outsider looking in, they probably wouldn't even know.
They would think that you're a guy who's handsome and polite.
But my school doesn't really have many straight guys.
So, I'm kind of more familiar with it.
You don't have to worry. I won't tell anyone.
Okay.
See? And smiling like that?
The girls wouldn't be able to think anything in time. They'd just melt first.
This is my girlfriend.
Don't sprinkle your charm on her, damn it.
Let go. You have so much sweat.
What's going on, Aim?
When it comes to Pete, you smile so sweetly. But when it's me, you brush my hand away.
That's not fair at all.
It doesn't look proper.
Okay... Okay...
If it's like this, I like it.
My girlfriend has to treasure herself.
Save it for me so in the future.
Letting me be the only one to touch you is enough, right?
Geez... Pervert.
Can't I just imagine it?
Just wait until your next life then.
We finally won!
How embarrassing...
Don't touch me... Don't touch me...
Can't stop smiling, can you?
Ae is really good.
You should've seen him when he scored the first goal, too.
Just amazing.
I'm sorry that I made your school lose.
But... I'm glad... that you won.
Thank you.
Then I'm going to go change my clothes first.
Then let's go find something to eat together.
Are you guys going to find something to eat or are you going to eat each other?
You can tell me, friend. That way I don't have to wait up tonight.
Too nosy, Pond.
Who said I wasn't nosy?
Geez... How annoying.
Geez, baby. Don't be annoyed with me.
Now you're more annoying than usual.
Come on.
Then, tonight, can I stay over at your dorm?
I'm going to change clothes now.
What were you guys talking about?
It's nothing, Pond.
You won't stop bothering them...
Come here. Come here.
He's all shy.
Get back safely, Beautiful.
When you get home, tell me through LINE too. Okay?
I have something I want to ask you.
Yes, Sir?
Pond, will you get sick of me for being too reserved?
I'm serious here.
Well, you are asking me something silly.
My friends said I'm too reserved.
And how is that a bad thing, Aim?
Aim, listen to me, all right?
If some guy tells you he's sick of you just because you won't let him touch you,
then that guy is someone who is complete trash. You can just stop being involved with him.
Which I'm not like that.
I like you because of who you are.
Even though I might be... somewhat of a pervert...
Not somewhat, but a whole lot.
Okay... Even though I might be a big pervert,
but it's not like that's the only thing I think about when it comes to my girlfriend.
If my girlfriend is not ready, I can wait.
Isn't that even better?
That means that I was able to get a wonderful woman to become my girlfriend. Isn't that right?
Do you understand?
Fine, I understand.
See? You know how to be such a good guy, too.
Why don't you act like this for others to see, huh?
Well... There are some things that I'd like to keep only for my important person to see after all...
Let's go.
Right... Aim, what do you think?
Have Ae and Pete done it yet?
You were good for three seconds and you're already back to being trash again?
But I also know... that you like that I'm like this.
I won't argue that.
There... There... not arguing it.
Ae, what would you like to drink?
I have Orange soda, Green soda, Red soda...
Red, Green, Orange...
Green, Red, and Orange...
Which one?
Geez, any drink is fine.
Okay...
Ouch!
Are you all right, Pete?
What's with you?
Are you hurt?
Come on. I'll pour it myself.
But I want to do it for you.
You should stop being shy first.
You're going to make me shy, too.
Since that day, the two of us...
haven't really had time just the two of us...
Plus... you were really cool playing football, too...
Don't say something to make me blush, all right?
I'm going to take a shower first.
My body feels damn sticky right now.
Then... I'll make some food for you to eat then.
Pa'Jiew taught me a bunch of things.
(T/N: Pa=Auntie)
Are you sure that you won't burn down the apartment?
Oh... I won't burn down the apartment, Ae.
Ai'Pete.
Did you want something?
Take a bath with me.
I think I should get out, Ae.
Hey. Then I'll get out with you.
Ae, didn't you want to soak in the water?
The reason why I wanted to soak in it, was to soak in it with you.
What are you so shy about?
I said to stop being shy already.
I've seen everything already.
- Ai'Pete, do you want me to wash your hair? I'll wash it for you.
That's okay. I just washed it this morning.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
Ae, don't touch it.
Ae!
I want to touch it a bit, come on.
Please don't touch it, Ae.
Oh, Ae. I have a question for you.
The thing is... are you available next weekend?
Why?
It just happens to be my mom's birthday next week.
I wanted to invite you to come, too.
My mom is also inviting you, too, Ae.
Will you go? Please? Please? Please?
Why are you trying to be so cute?
Just a bit... So will you come?
Of course, I'll go. An elder invited me after all.
But for now...
Can I just do this with you?
Ae! Don't...
You shouldn't ask me.
Ae, you know that I'm shy.
- You're always shy.
- Ae, you know that I never say no to you.
Why are you so cute like this?
I'm not going.
Do you not understand the human language or something?
How can we talk if I don't understand?
I don't know. Either way, I have to see P'Ae today.
Ley, you have to come with me, too.
I'm not going. It's a waste of study time.
Come on... I'm tired already. Let's go.
Let go.
Let go...
Oh no!
Why did you let go?
Sorry. But, Ley, I just wanted you to accompany me. That's all, but you won't go.
Besides, it's your brother's match today, too, right?
So what? Whether they compete and win or lose, it won't help improve our grades. Right?
Geez. So, are you really not going to go?
I'm mad at you now.
Fine... I'll go with you.
Yay! Let's go!
Either way, I still want to be in a relationship with you.
But I can still assure you that no matter what, I can't be with you, Tin.
It's not going to happen!?
Even if I steal you away?
It's hot, so hot. And there are too many people. Let's go back.
Oh... Come on...
Hey. Isn't that P'Pete?
That's such great stuff!
P'Pete is a close friend of P'Ae.
Let's ask him if he knows where P'Ae is.
Coming here to see such good stuff like this. It makes it kind of worth wasting some studying time.
P'Pete!
Hold on...
What is it? Why are we hiding?
Who are those two older guys?
Oh... That's P'Pete. A close friend of P'Ae.
As for the other one... He must be a close friend of P'Pete, I guess?
So, what are they to each other?
What are they to each other?
I-I don't know.
I thought I was coming here for nothing.
But to come here and find such a fine couple as this,
it's totally satisfying!
What are you talking about?
Shhh... Don't interrupt.
Ai'Ley, my lovely little sis!!!
Are you here to cheer on your beloved big brother?
No, I'm not... Be quiet...
Ai'Tin! What are you doing to Ai'Pete this time?
Ai'Tin, what are you trying to start with Ai'Pete this time?
Get the fuck far away.
If I want it, then I'll just steal it.
I'm talking to you right now, damn it.
P'Can, what is with you?
As soon as you get here, you just tried picking a fight with him.
Ai'Ley, don't let this handsome face fool you.
This one is the shittiest one that I've ever met.
Tin, hasn't done anything to me, Can.
I don't believe it.
Tell me what he did to you.
He really didn't do anything. I can be a witness.
This older guy was asking P'Pete to be in a relationship.
What was that?
Yeah. I heard it with both my ears.
Can someone help explain this to me? So, is P'Pete gay or is this older guy gay?
And is P'Pete straight?
Or what is it exactly?
You said you are looking for P'Ae, right? Let's just go.
That's okay. That can wait. I want to know.
Yeah, all right. I'll tell you later.
This kind of stuff... I'm an expert.
Good luck to you.
I'll be leaving now.
Can...
I think this is all just a misunderstanding, Can.
Right! Can, don't you have a soccer match coming up?
I think you should go get ready.
Ai'Pete, I saw that Ai'Ae was looking for you.
You should go see him.
I have something to talk to your friend about.
I also have something to say to "little eyes," too.
Who are you calling "little eyes"?
Your eyes are not that big either.
Uh.. then... I'll just excuse myself for now, all right?
Whatever issue you have, say it.
What's YOUR issue?
Last week, you were just insulting my friends. Calling them disgusting.
And now, you're asking Ai'Pete to be in a relationship?
Are you eating your own words or something?
Before you talk crap,
did you forget something?
This is my business with Pete. It has nothing to do with outsiders.
Yeah, I'm an outsider.
I was being nosy.
But those guys are my friends!
And you called my friends dirty.
You called them very disgusting.
And now you're trying to interfere with my friends?
You're thinking of causing conflict between them, aren't you?
You're the fucking worst piece of shit.
There are so many guys out there. Why don't you just pick one?
Don't mess with Ai'Pete.
No one is like Pete.
But Pete has a boyfriend already.
And his boyfriend is my friend.
You, do you really want to protect your friend that badly?
Yeah.
Then why don't you...
spread your legs for me instead?
Just go die, you bastard!
No one has ever punched me twice.
This time... I won't let you go.
Did we... really lose?
Yeah, we lost.
Our team lost?
Who the fuck else do you think it was?
But our team has the best athletes, dude!
Yeaaah...
We are sport science students.
And more than half our roster is from the college football team.
But we lost to the Engineering Department, 3:1.
The scores aren't even close to each other either.
And do you know who the one was that made us lose?
It's the one who kept messing up passing the ball over and over again.
Every time I sent it to you...
you kept passing it to Engineering each time, Can...
I'm sorry.
Forget it.
Winning or losing, it's a normal thing.
But... what's up with you, dude?
I'm not mad because we lost.
But I'm mad with the person who is driving me nuts.
What does that even mean?
You better remember this,
Ai'Tin.
You'll pay for this.
Wait for me, Can.
Congratulations, Ae.
Why don't you look very happy?
Well, I wanted you to win.
But I also didn't want Can to be upset.
I don't know where he is right now.
Ai'Can? You don't have to mind him.
Someone like him, he'll get over being sad in a second.
Geez, for you... You totally pummeled my team, Ai'Ae.
But I'll forgive you if you play this well in the university league next semester.
Right, Ai'Ae. Do you know what's wrong with the Albino Monkey?
Despite being kind of a nutjob, he's never been this bad before.
I don't know either. I'm worried about him, too.
If you don't know, then forget it.
Once he gets really stressed out, he'll eventually tell us himself.
Oh yeah! Where is the Engineering team going to celebrate?
I don't know. I'm not going.
What? Why aren't you going?
The reason Engineering won was because of you, you know. You scored two balls.
I can't. I have to get ready to meet my *boyfriend's family tomorrow.
(T/N: 'Faen' is gender neutral and means both boy/girlfriend)
Huh?
You didn't hear it wrong.
I have to get ready to go to my boyfriend's house.
I'm going to go pack my bag first.
Okay.
Who's his girlfriend, Ai'Pete?
Yes?
And hey... what's wrong with your face? It's pretty red. Are you sunburned or something?
So damn stupid...
Why are you insulting me?
Then... I'm going to go head out with Ae.
- Goodbye. Goodbye.
- Bye.
What the heck is with him?
Dude, you don't need to be confused.
Let's go. Let's go treat the first years to some alcohol instead.
I don't have money to treat them to alcohol...
But you are the captain.
It's always me...
- Let's go.
- Yeah... Let's go, let's go.
Come on, Ai Can.
Calm down. Winning or losing is normal.
I know it's normal. I just don't want to lose to that guy.
You mean Ai'Ae?
Not Ai'Ae! Shit, P'No. You don't fucking know anything.
Geez. I'll kick you, you Albino Monkey. I was asking you nicely.
Kick me then. Get up and just kick me. I'm not scared of you.
P'No... Please, don't hold it against him. Ai'Can is... drunk.
Good, could I sleep at your house?
I don't want to go home.
If I go back, my little sister is definitely going to laugh at me.
I even lost at football.
No...
My mom... is... going to... yell at me...
Please...
Ai'Good, I'll leave Ai'Can to you. All right? I have a call, I have to answer it.
Where are you going?
I'll be right back.
Hold on, Ai'Nic. It's too loud here.
Can I sleep over, please?
Please.
Why don't you ask the others?
Is your house available?
Let's just toast.
Hello, Ai'Nic. What's up?
Where are you right now?
I'm at a bar. I'm taking care of a drunk freshman.
P'No, what time are you coming back?
It'll be whatever time it is.
Can you give me a specific time?
Hey, you are my little brother. Not my mom.
Oh, come on, P'No. Just tell me, please.
Then I probably won't be back. I have to take care of the drunk freshman.
Tell Mom for me, okay? Later.
What's with him lately?
He's been on me even more than Mom.
Whatever.
So, my big brother isn't coming home.
Yeah, I heard that.
Then you should go home, Ai'Kla.
Who's the underclassman that P'No has to drop off?
Who the hell is he? I'm starting to hate him now.
I see you just hating anyone who gets close to my older brother.
Or should I put him in bed and finish him already?
Are you serious?
What?
It's gotten this far, and I'm not going to take it seriously?
And you have to help me, too.
Stop right there. I'd like not to get involved with this.
I have a business proposal for you on this.
Is it going to be a deal or not?
Of course, it's a deal.
You're pretty easy, dude.
Of course, I'm easy.
It's settled.
Come on, let's go inside the house, Ae.
Look at your house! You are so out of my reach.
Are you sure that I'm allowed to come?
Of course, you're allowed to come.
Well, my mom is the one who wanted you to come.
But I came here empty-handed. I don't have a single gift at all.
It's all right. Just you coming here is already the best gift.
Hold on.
Is that a gift for you or for your mom?
For Mom, of course.
Well, Mom wanted you to come. If you came, it's only normal for her to be happy.
Actually, I'm the one that wanted you to come.
You're always making yourself to be so cute, Ai'Koon Chai.
Yes... But we can't use a word like "cute" for a tall guy like me.
Then you can use it for me then.
It's not like I'm calling you "cute" or anything.
I'd say you're "Tay" (Cool/Handsome) instead.
What did you say?
I'd say you're "Tay" instead.
If a shortie like me is "Tay,"
then someone tall like you can be "cute" for me, too.
If I'm willing to be cute in your eyes.
You'll be "Tay" only for my eyes, right?
Let's go inside the house, Ai Koon Chai.
Okay.
Before I can't stop myself and kiss you, right here.
Ae, which flower do you think is pretty?
It already looks nice on the plant.
Why would you cut them?
I... put roses in a vase for my mom's birthday every year.
So, why does it have to be roses?
When I was very young,
a big bouquet of roses was always delivered on her birthday every year.
So I asked her who sent them to her.
Mom said that dad sent them.
At that time, I thought that my dad loved my mom very much.
But I also wondered why didn't dad just deliver them himself.
Until I realized that... the one who sent them was my dad's secretary.
What flowers are these? They're so beautiful.
They are roses.
Your dad sent them to mom.
Do you like them?
It's something strange.
Because presently, that secretary is my father's new wife.
He never remembered our faces, Ae.
He never remembered my mother's birthday at all.
Once dad and mom got divorced, there were no roses sent over ever again.
So I decided to pick roses for my mom.
At that time, my hands were covered in wounds.
Some roses looked nice, others were not so much.
And I also told my mom that...
From now on, I'll be the one who gives you roses every year.
Thank you, dear.
Oh, my!!! Does it hurt, son?
Thank you so much.
If you can make your mother happy,
then I will be the one to make you happy.
So, which flower do you want?
I'll cut them for you.
This one.
♫ I won’t wish to catch those distant stars ♫
♫ I don’t want to make them mine ♫
♫ I won’t wish for the world to keep spinning ♫
♫ I won’t turn back time ♫
♫ In this universe, there is nothing more meaningful ♫
♫ Than you whom I am longing for ♫
♫ I only beg for you to be with me forever ♫
♫ You're the only one I'm asking for ♫
♫ I want you to be my sky when I fly ♫
♫ Be my guiding star when I'm lost ♫
- Hello.
- Hello, Ae
I'm so sorry. I just had some important work come up.
So I wasn't able to stay and welcome you. Even though I'm the one who invited you.
So where is Pete, dear?
The roses, huh?
Ai'Pete does this every year?
Yes.
The first year I saw it,
my heart was going to stop.
His hands were covered with blood and wounds all over.
I should've hit him until it left marks on his butt.
Ai'Pete is really happy to be able to do it for you, Auntie, really.
Yes.
I know that... Pete wants to make me happy.
So it's also not wrong if I want to do everything I can for Pete's happiness, right?
Auntie, you knew...
Who came?
Khun Putch. Khun DeLi's here.
Happy birthday, Auntie.
How many times have I told you that you don't need to bring a gift, dear?
Just your feelings is enough.
I can't do that. Last year, I wasn't able to come. So this year, I have to be able to give it to you myself.
Oh! My mother also wanted me to give you her regards too, Auntie.
She happened to be stuck with some business today, so she wasn't able to come herself.
Then... please relay my thanks to your mother, all right?
Yes.
So, have you met each other before?
This is Ae, dear. He's Pete's friend from university.
Hello.
Ae, DeLi has been my friend since we were little kids.
Then I'll leave you kids to chat for first. I'll excuse myself for now, all right?
- Sure.
- Okay, Mother.
That's very nice to be able to be at the same university as Pete, too.
Actually, I wanted to study there, too.
But my dad wouldn't let me.
He said that I had to study at the same place he did no matter what.
Such a shame. Right, Pete?
Pete?
Yeah, it's such a shame that we don't see each other very much.
True.
Then... should we meet more often then?
[Preview]
Pete, you know how to peel shrimp now?
And still remember that I don't know how to do it.
You know something, right? Tell me right now.
Ai'Tum! I really don't know anything.
You came home, but you're not even thinking of greeting your older brother at all?
Gucci!
Thank you very much for...
Help...
Ai...
♫ to give to you until you take it ♫
♫ to tell you I love you until you accept ♫
♫ You are my happiness ♫
♫ If you don't take my love, I'm ready to start again ♫
♫ If in the end, you don't change your mind ♫
♫ It's okay because my heart won't change ♫
♫ You would have to wait for the world to stop spinning
before my heart would stop beating for you ♫
♫ On the day that you have no one ♫
♫ On the day this world abandons you ♫
♫ On that day turn and look, I’ll be standing right here ♫
♫ to give to you until you take it ♫
♫ to tell you I love you until you accept ♫
♫ Can you hear me?♫
♫ You would have to wait for the world to stop spinning ♫