Buried Hearts
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN SAFE ENVIRONMENT
EPISODE 7
LET ETERNAL LIGHT SHINE UPON HER
SEO YEONJU AGNES
Thank you.
How...
How could this happen?
Thank you for coming.
I won't let the bastard
who did this to your sister walk free.
That truck driver.
Once he's out of the hospital,
he must be arrested
and locked up immediately.
It's the least we can do
to let Sister Agnes rest in peace.
Stay back, step away!
Move back, it's dangerous!
Go with her.
Hold on.
Ouch.
Dongju!
You...
You really don't recognize me.
I refused to believe you had amnesia
when Sister Agnes told me.
I can't believe this happened.
I'm so sorry.
She's Madame Pi, the guardian
of Director Seo and his sister
when they were young.
Come on now,
how could he just stand by as a senior
while his juniors were getting beaten up?
Is that what they teach
in Gangshin's rugby team?
Gangshin High School's
rugby team
had never had incidents like this
before Seo Dongju joined.
I'm sorry, Principal.
I came to Gangshin to play rugby.
Please, let me keep playing.
Expulsion is unfair.
Yeom Huicheol ruthlessly beat up
the younger students first,
and when Dongju tried to stop him,
he hurt his head.
That's what the witnesses said, Principal.
Oh. It's you.
You said Dongju got dragged into this
while trying to protect you guys.
Now, tell the principal that again.
- Okay?
- Well...
At the principal's request,
we conducted a thorough investigation.
We spoke to all of them
and got their statements.
Yes, hand it to me.
STATEMENT
What in the world are you doing?
Hey, Yeom Huicheol.
Tell the truth.
You started that fight
just to screw me over.
What the heck? Hey.
Hey, you thug.
Why would I do that?
Because I'm better than you at rugby.
You're never better than me.
What did you say?
Open your eyes, you coward.
Pathetic.
Madame Pi.
- Yes, Dongju.
- Let's go.
Dongju!
You can't leave like this.
You need to beg them
to revoke your expulsion.
They stabbed me
in the back. How can I play with them?
Dad.
- Hello.
- Yes.
You were abroad for a conference.
Yes, I canceled the rest of my schedule.
I'm sorry I'm late when it's about my son.
- It's fine.
- Sir.
You paid off the rugby parents,
didn't you?
To frame me.
Seo Dongju! Shut your mouth!
Who taught you to speak like that?
Show some respect!
So it's true.
I was just throwing it out there.
- Madame Pi.
- Yes.
Dongju, since Huicheol's father is here...
You said it yourself
that guilty ones get mad first.
Look carefully.
Who's the one getting mad?
That little...
Dongju!
- Brother!
- Professor Yeom.
Why did you cancel
your conference for this?
As his uncle,
I can protect Huicheol myself.
Jeez.
8 YEARS AGO
Is this the guy who messed with
Daesan Energy's accounting records?
Yes.
He's got a face
that rubs me the wrong way.
- Was this from high school?
- Yes.
To Seo Dongju's left
is his sister, Seo Yeonju,
and to his right is his guardian,
Madame Pi.
Guho, where did you find this photo?
Seo Dongju posted this photo
the day he got into Daesan Group.
"A bold first step, like a charging boar."
That was his caption.
How did a nobody
and the great Yeom Jangseon
get tangled up like this?
Damn it.
Goodness. Life's a real piece of work.
I've got more pictures of him.
Forget it. Dig deeper into this guy.
I once stripped this guy
of his rugby uniform.
Now he's coming at me,
asking to be stripped of his suit.
Like a wild boar.
Yeonju!
Before Yeonju became a nun,
she looked after you like a mother.
Your mother entrusted you both to me
before she passed.
We've spent all these years together.
Do you really...
not remember anything about me?
When you were little,
you'd call me, "Madame Pi."
"Madame Pi."
You followed me around calling me that.
I'm sorry.
Well...
When you were at school,
you used to beat up
a punching bag every day.
You don't remember that either?
That punching bag...
I hung that up for you.
Pounding that every day
gave you strong fists.
What am I going to do with you?
What am I going to do?
What do I do?
Sir,
I have a favor to ask you.
I think I should take her
somewhere she can calm down.
Of course, Director Seo.
While I'm gone,
could you receive the guests in my place?
What?
You're the only one
I can ask for this favor.
I'd appreciate it.
Wait...
Director Seo.
Well...
How could Yeonju pass away,
leaving you all alone,
when you lost your memory...
How could she pass away like that?
Gosh...
Seo Dongju.
Your sister died because of you.
You'd better be worth it.
After all this mess,
how is it that the two trillion won
stuck in your thick skull
still hasn't come back to you?
Does that make any sense?
Dongju,
don't worry about the guests,
and get some sleep.
I'll wake you up for the funeral mass.
KYUNGUI UNIVERSITY
KEUNSOL CENTRAL HOSPITAL
Is it night training today?
- Yes.
- Hang in there.
- See you.
- Thank you.
- Who is that?
- Do you know him?
Patient Cho Yangchun
needs to receive treatment.
Okay.
Thank you.
Take care.
You have a message from Mr. Yeom.
Eyes forward.
The plan has changed.
My phone.
I'll grab it and follow you.
Did Mr. Yeom say
I don't have to go to prison?
Let's go. Where am I supposed to go?
Shoot!
Darn it!
You bastard!
Hey.
Cho Yangchun will be discharged
and arrested. You can go.
Actually, he just left for treatment.
- He's being discharged. What treatment?
- What?
Damn it!
Someone I knew was in an accident.
Yes, that's right.
- Dad!
- Yes.
What? Hey.
Ihyeon.
What brings you here?
I came for Mass.
A nun I knew has passed away.
For this church and its kindergarten,
I planted all the trees
in the playground with her.
What about you?
The nun's younger brother...
is the one you met last time.
The guy who came to our place?
- Really?
- Yes.
Hey.
Hey, Dr. Kang.
Hi.
- Let's go.
- Sure.
Sir.
You tied him up nice and tight.
Wow, he's completely wrecked.
Shall we get going now?
Guho,
Madame Pi is going that way.
Manager Cho
escaped from the hospital.
Sir, please watch your words.
Yangchun would never do that.
I didn't raise him that way.
He slipped out of the cuffs and ran.
Did you help him escape?
Sir.
If he was running away,
would he have left his phone behind?
I called because
I was worried about his injuries,
but the police picked up instead.
Hold on.
The nurse pushed him out.
It looks like Jang Ilnam,
who vanished with Dongju in Namhae.
Then that guy in the helmet...
is Seo Dongju?
It can't be him.
I saw that he went into the room...
We will now begin
Sister Agnes' funeral mass.
Please rise from your seats.
Please turn toward the church entrance.
We will now sing hymn 227.
♪ I am the life ♪
♪ All who thirst ♪
♪ Come to me ♪
Guho.
That bastard got his memory back
and is putting on a show, right?
Forget the two trillion won.
If I don't take down Seo Dongju now,
I won't be able to breathe.
♪ Take this soul ♪
♪ Into your hands ♪
♪ Angels ♪
Over there...
Is the woman next to Director Seo
his sister?
His sister...
is at the front.
Then...
it must be his mother.
Dongju grew up without a mother.
Lord, grant Agnes eternal rest.
May Agnes
and all who have departed this world
find peace in God's mercy.
Amen.
Please be seated.
To conclude,
we will now sing the hymn
"Grant Them Eternal Rest."
Could it be that
Director Seo's memory returned
from the shock of his sister's death?
Then you have...
failed.
Failed in what?
Depending on how I take it,
that could be very offensive.
If Seo Dongju got his memory back,
he would've gone straight
to the one who shot him first.
I already explained everything
over the phone.
Why did you suddenly ask for a meeting?
I told you, I'll take care of
the candidates the other party is after.
I'll shut them up completely.
Why did you insist on seeing me in person?
Surprise!
Brother.
Did you get scared?
This is hilarious.
The Elder said...
"Senior Assemblyman
Nam Sangcheol of the ruling party,
you go and settle things
with Yeom Jangseon on my behalf."
That's why I'm here.
Oh, yes!
I was told to get
a clear answer on one thing.
Why isn't the money
gushing out like it should?
Instead, it's trickling out
like a bad bladder infection.
Considering your age...
Scared?
Tell the Elder
that I've got everything under control.
He wants control of the funds.
Not me! The Elder!
The Elder is asking for it.
The Elder!
The Elder...
Jeez.
Darn it, did I mess around too much?
You're asking what the big deal is?
All hell broke loose.
Anyway, we need to meet now.
How about Seo Dongju?
Aside from visiting Madame Pi
to ask about the past, it's the same.
Sir, it seems Director Seo is trying hard
to recover his memories.
How pointless. Does he think that'll work?
I'll wring his neck
and toss him back into the sea.
A two-trillion-won feast for the fishes.
Yes, sir.
I looked
Yeom Jangseon straight in the eye
and told him.
I said, "Hand over
the funds management immediately."
SAFETY FIRST
The person Yeom Jangseon met...
It wasn't the Elder.
What?
What do you mean?
Sell off Daesan Energy?
I told you,
on the condition that Director Seo
never regains his memory, remember?
Not even the death of his sister
could bring back his memory!
That's...
not for sure.
The truck driver who caused the accident
vanished without a trace.
It's Seo Dongju's doing.
Anyway, at Sister Agnes' funeral,
Chairman Cha didn't seem mentally sound.
Why didn't you report
such an important matter to me?
I only found out...
that day.
You must stay sharp.
If Chairman Cha has dementia, that means
our opportunity is coming even sooner.
You and I have spent years
building Daesan as our golden ticket.
But one wrong move
and it's going straight to the dogs.
ADMINISTRATOR
Yes.
Mr. Yeom isn't answering my calls.
He's with his guest.
Ask him for me.
Has he forgotten about Cho Yangchun?
If he has,
I'll go find him myself.
YEO EUNNAM
The number you dialed
cannot be reached...
You won't
answer my calls or see me.
I'm really worried, Dongju.
Secretary Gong,
I'm unable to take long baths anymore.
You took a short bath today.
I'm feeling off.
Even taking baths takes stamina.
The eggs will make you
feel better, Chairman.
About the kid named Seong Hyeon...
Didn't you hear me?
The kid named Seong Hyeon,
don't you remember?
Are you talking about Director Seo?
Gosh, no.
You know, the little boy this tall
who was pretty like a girl...
A long time ago, Eunnam's father,
Yeo Sunho, brought him here.
I'm not sure who you mean.
Do you have dementia?
Hmm.
Director Seo...
You...
Has your memory come back?
Thanks.
No problem.
- I'll get going.
- Take care.
Wow.
Who is that?
Why is he...
Is he someone you know?
No, not at all.
Hello.
Seo Dongju lives here, right?
I'm Ji Seonu.
Could I see Dongju?
Ji Seonu?
- Mom, give me a second.
- Taeyun.
Let me handle this.
You should've let him meet Dongju, Mom.
If someone with amnesia
sees an old friend,
it could help.
How shocked would he be
to learn Dongju has amnesia?
Come on, Director Seo is in urgent need...
Okay, I'll stop.
I'll shut my mouth.
More trivet for the ramyeon pots.
Remember Sugyeong?
The one I studied abroad with.
Assemblywoman Seok Sugyeong?
Yes.
He's being like that because it's a book
from her publication event.
A politician's book...
You don't look well.
Ji Yeongsu's son was here.
Secretary Gong,
what's for dinner?
It's been a while since I came home.
I should indulge a little.
I prepared Korean beef rib stew.
Nice!
Father.
Where's Father?
As you regain your memories
one by one like this,
sooner or later, everything will
come flooding back at once.
Remembering the liquor safe's code
is impressive enough.
Don't you think?
Yes.
So it's...
starting to come back bit by bit.
Yes.
Fortunately,
bit by bit...
Father, I might lose Yuseong Chemical!
The Yuseong Chemical bond manager
is on my side.
But the bank president just ordered them
to halt the merger and acquisition review.
There's a slight issue
with Mr. Yeom's funds, Father.
Step outside.
This is about Daesan Chemical
acquiring Yuseong Chemical, Father.
It is my business.
If you don't leave, we will.
Fine.
Father.
If I lose Yuseong Chemical...
you must compensate me for it.
What's Yeom so upset about?
Why is he suddenly overturning
the Yuseong Chemical deal?
It's not just a tantrum, Father.
He's pressuring us to sell Daesan Energy.
Again?
No one in their right mind
would sell a profitable company.
Mr. Yeom specializes in driving
thriving businesses into bankruptcy,
forcing them to sell.
I just met with Mr. Yeom,
but I didn't expect him to act this fast.
We need to open the safe
if we want to shut Yeom's mouth.
But we don't know the code.
Well...
The place where
you keep the paper with the code...
I already checked. Right?
Are you talking about
the reading card in the books?
That's the old code.
I lost the note with the new code.
I have to hide it
in plain sight to keep it safe.
That's right.
We hid it here together.
LIQUOR SAFE
INNER SAFE
Director Seo,
you just saved Daesan Energy.
My false memories of you, President Huh,
will be cleared up soon too,
one by one.
False memories?
The memory of me...
shooting Director Seo.
Fake memories got mixed in
and messed you up, huh?
Go ahead and open it.
Take the cash and gold
and shove them down Yeom's throat.
I memorized it when you showed me.
Director Seo memorized
this 16-digit code...
That's right.
He lost his memory,
not his ability to memorize.
Right?
I knew it!
I heard from President Huh
that your memories
are starting to come back.
Yes.
The shock of watching my sister die
keeps pounding in my head.
Mmm.
Telling me to remember.
To bring it all back.
I hope you remember your sibling bond
and truly grieve for your sister.
Without the memories,
you can't even cry for her.
Your sister, who's now buried,
would be disappointed.
Thirty boxes of dress shirts
confirmed, sir.
Chairman Cha sincerely requests you
to let the Yuseong Chemical review resume.
Tell him
we'll take our time sorting things out.
More than any of that, I'm waiting
for you to get your memory back.
You have no idea
how desperately I want that.
Since you don't remember it.
You should get going, Director Seo.
Sir.
It's Manager Cho's ring.
Whose ring?
Bring the gun.
Dongju!
Get over here.
I said, get over here!
Yes, sir.
You thief.
My two trillion won
is in that head of yours!
What do you mean?
You stole my money and ran away!
Chief Cheon.
Director Seo.
You left this behind.
You killed Cho Yangchun
and faked your amnesia!
What are you rambling about,
crazy old geezer?
What money?
You...
You took the money I was going to use
for my love of this country...
Why are you so shocked?
Didn't you bring this to kill me?
Honestly, I'm tired
of chasing my memories.
And I'm left alone in this world.
I'm done.
It's all so exhausting.
So...
I'll disappear with the two trillion
stuck in my head.
I was wrong!
You didn't steal my money.
It's a misunderstanding...
Are you sure?
Why would I lie with a gun in front of me?
Do you want me to kneel and beg?
Do you?
BEE POLLEN
1 TEASPOON A DAY
Put it in tea and drink it warm.
It's the good stuff.
If it's the good stuff,
you should have it.
Come on.
Half of your body belongs to whom?
To you.
All right.
Tell them it's a gift
in return for the food they sent us
from Huicheol's birthday feast.
Okay, I will.
It's done.
I made plenty of the honey cookies
that you like.
Eat as much as you want.
Yes.
Goodness, I did my best,
but compared to the birthday feast,
this feels lacking, you know?
My birthday spread got ruined,
so I didn't really like the food, Aunt.
Your first birthday spread
as a married man got ruined?
By whom?
Someone called Secretary Gong.
The one who seems even more powerful
than my grandfather-in-law at times.
Hello.
Welcome.
Dongju.
What are you doing?
Dongju,
are you okay?
Do you see this scar?
It's from a gunshot.
The day you didn't show up for our trip,
I got shot on the yacht
and lost my memory.
And the day you said
we should go see my sister,
she died.
Sister Agnes...
I know.
You're sorry.
It wasn't your fault,
but you still feel responsible.
You're here to tell me that, right?
I'm sorry...
but I don't want to hear it.
Because I can't say it's okay.
I'm not okay at all.
This pain is unbearable,
I feel like dying.
Nothing good ever happened
when we were together.
Including how you married Yeom Huicheol.
So from now on,
don't look at me.
Turn away and live your life.
Dongju.
That's impossible.
What did Director Seo say?
He's coming down soon.
Did you tell him
it was a thoughtful gift from our in-laws?
Yes, Chairman.
Since the funeral,
he's barely come down for a meal...
I'm glad you brought good food.
Well done.
Yes, Grandfather.
- Where's Eunnam?
- She will be here soon.
She says she'll skip the meal
and come later...
for dessert.
Hey.
I'm glad you came.
Thank you.
Sit.
Let's eat.
I'll take the dessert out.
Chef Do.
Why did you put fruit here?
This batch of honey cookies
tastes completely off.
I tasted it.
She used Ceylon cinnamon
instead of traditional cassia powder
in the syrup.
You know what they say.
When the lady of the house strays,
even the food starts tasting off.
Maybe she's having an affair?
Jeez, that big mouth. My goodness.
I'm sure they're having some drama.
What?
Why is mine different?
There's cinnamon in the cookies.
I know you don't like it.
I see.
Hmm.
If Seo Dongju doesn't eat
the honey cookies with cinnamon in them,
it means
his memory loss has been all an act.
Director Seo.
Good thing you came down to eat, right?
Yes, Chairman.
Why didn't you have dinner?
Try it. It's good.
Director Seo.
Would you like some more cookies?
I've had enough.
Chairman.
- I'll go back to my room.
- Okay.
From now on,
make sure to come down for meals.
I will.
Dongju!
Call an ambulance.
Yes, Father.
What's wrong, Dongju?
Dongju!
We have a medical emergency
at 19-1 Hannam-dong. Please come quickly.
- Dongju, stay with me!
- Dongju!
What's going on?
- Open your eyes, Dongju!
- Dongju!
- Stay with me!
Stay with me.
Dongju, stay with me!
Dongju!
Director Seo!
What's going on?
Dongju, stay with me...
Dongju!
Dongju, stay with me!
Stay with me!
Dongju!
- Director Seo!
- Dongju!
Buried Hearts
Director Seo
won't make it through the night.
We don't need
Cha Gukhui's testimony.
It's crucial that Cha Gangcheon feels
the threat of his daughter being taken.
You being Yeom's favored junior
doesn't hold much value for me now.
Go confront
Yeom Jangseon head-on.
Why are you
trying to kill Dongju?
You should get rid of him straightaway.
I'll make sure
everything is...
wrapped up the right way.
Translated by Hye Min Eom