I've just a stand where I stand
Never a step that I took was to walk to you
Sister Xu, why are you back?
If I'm not back, I don't know if you're going through the storm
Don't tease me
I know you're a good guy, but you have to be careful
The body of the athlete is the most precious
This is for you
You see LA sent it
It's been more than a year
This is your last chance
You're my mom, right?
Who sent me here?
Isn't this your dream?
Don't give up your future because of anyone
I'll think about it
Tell me
How's your marriage life?
I'm not sure
How can I? Of course it's good
But I heard you have a new situation recently
When did you let me meet that girl?
I really want to know who can take our Young Master Jiang down
Don't talk about me
You talk about yourself
You didn't do it for love
You're still going abroad to get married
I'm not back now?
Yes
Did you give up your position and regret it?
I regret it
I didn't finish my studies without regret
I can't go back now
You said that because you wanted to persuade me
I think your friend circle is very smooth
Your friend circle is smooth
What about your sister?
She didn't come back with you this time
She has other things
When you are waiting for you
You will be looking forward to the end of your dream
You can walk
You can enter the idol drama
You are the one who has me
You are the apple that falls off
There is a hook
Like a fish living in the water
You are summer, I am the one
The wind that blows in the sea
Why is love so hot?
How to walk?
The 2020 Le Ang Bay autumn half-time marathon
will be held in Wuhan on October 27
The winner of this competition is announced
The result will be announced at the end of the month
Xiao Xi
What are you looking at?
Just running
You've seen this pair many times
How about I help you choose?
Actually I have chosen it
Then buy it
It's not the end yet
Wait for the result to come out
What are you talking about?
Look, this looks delicious
They make the cake with the money
It's more than 20 times
Let's eat it too
But it doesn't look very cheap
I'm asking you
No, it's simple
If you really want to eat it, I'll go with you
Really?
Hello
Xiao Xi, you finally come back
I heard your tone
Why are you here to tell me?
Tell me
What's wrong with Uncle Jiang?
Uncle Jiang has been lost by the school
The school's students
Because he doesn't talk to us
Is it that serious?
Then Uncle Jiang doesn't want to go abroad
Is it for him?
Actually I don't quite understand
Why does Uncle Jiang suddenly want to go abroad?
After Boyang left
He is like a enemy to me
No matter what
The team has given him the last pass
This is his last chance
Xiao Xi, you must persuade him
Can't let him give up his future for others
I will talk to him
But he is an adult
We have to respect his own will
Let him arrange his own life
He is in a head-on
If he missed this opportunity
He will regret it forever
I prepared a surprise for you
I will bring it to you later
What's wrong?
Brother Jie, are you confessing?
No
Are you serious?
You are a liar
I didn't see it before
You are a forbidden play
You can't give up your money
Shut up
I don't know
I will arrange it for you
Tell me the truth
You are a liar
You don't understand
You are a soldier
No
I know
Hello, good afternoon, students
Welcome to my sharing meeting
Some of you may not know me
You can call me Zi Hui
Today I want to share some of my study experience
I hope I can provide some help to you in the future
Let's watch a video first
I have some requirements such as academic performance
Language proficiency
Standardized exams
Congratulations on the achievement made
Next time if you have any questions
You can ask me
What is it?
Miss, can I ask you any questions?
Of course
But I will answer any questions
Okay, then
How do you confess to your favorite girl?
It depends on what kind of girl she is
But I think no matter what she is
The most important thing is the truth
Okay, who are you going to confess to?
No, no
I am asking you a friend's question
Any questions?
It's your birthday today
I ordered a dinner for you
You can come over here
Thank you
No need
But you haven't had a baby for two years
You are finally back
You have to refuse
I said no need
If you want to
You can ask me
No need to say
Anyone else?
How long will you stay?
About a month
Okay, that's all for today
Thank you
Long time no see
How are you?
Isn't the life abroad like that?
Qianxiang, why do you want my cake?
Cake?
Sorry, I thought it was some rubbish
You did it on purpose
Don't waste your time
Jiangbo doesn't like this kind of little tricks
What are you talking about?
I am just a cake
How much? I will pay you when I get there
Don't leave, I want to be clear
I have nothing to say to you
You are a wild man
Qianxiang, you are bothering me
Lin Yunxi
Let go
You go first
Jiangbo, you are a wild man
You are just a wild man
What are you talking about? You said I am a cake
You even pushed me
You are not even my girlfriend
Okay, I will pay you
You pay me first
Here you are
You can wear it
You pay me first
Okay, how much?
How much?
I will pay you
I did it myself
You pay me the same as Yimou
You did it, it is more unworthy
Don't pull me
Here you are
Don't be too much
I will pay you the same as Yimou
None of your business
This cake was made by Xiaoxi
Not for Jiang Mohan
He is smart
He is more smart
What about you?
You have been in the basketball team
You think you are not annoying
You are also a Jiang Mohan
What right do you have to say that?
I am more qualified than you
You don't have to be so angry
I am not
Your temper is so bad
You are more annoying
I feel better
Your dance is so bad
You are not good at managing your body
Are you ashamed to eat cake?
I have never seen a girl like you
Every day except pretending to be cute
What else do you do?
No one will like you
Chen Siyou, don't be too much
Are you okay?
I am fine
Where are you going?
Let go
It's my fault
Why did you pull me out?
I didn't pull you
I pulled Qin Siyou
Fine, I will pull you out
I haven't told you
What is your temper with me?
What is your relationship with Youjin?
Why does he live in your house every day?
Didn't I say that before?
You can beat up your brother
and fight with him every day
We don't fight with him
You are the one who fights with him
Fine, I will tell you the truth
I see you are happy
when you are together
I am not saying that you are worried about your heart
I don't care about you
You are not...
You are not happy
Tell me clearly
What is our relationship?
We are not
You don't want to say it?
Forget it, I am tired
Xiao Mohan
I like you
I will think about it
Are you jealous?
I don't need to change my shoes
Youjin
I think
she was too nervous when she left
and she was so cold
It's okay
She is quite stubborn
Where did she go?
She went to the outside to play
She might come back in a few days
Why did you stop?
I am old and I will be fine
Wait for me
You sent the cake to Wang Shunian
You made it yourself?
Yes, I made it
But I can't think of it
Don't mind it
How can I mind it?
It's delicious
Come here
I want to eat
I am hungry
I will eat