The Pleling Man
Nice.
Come on!
Next.
Nice.
Hurry up.
Hold your hands.
Keep your hands steady.
Jump higher.
Chen Siqi.
What's wrong with your leg?
It's nothing.
It's just a bruise.
I'm leaving.
Go back and rest.
Boss.
I've made an appointment to have dinner with you.
I'm leaving.
What's the matter?
Boss.
Didn't you have a date with Yu Mingxi?
Don't hang out with my dad.
I'm not hanging out with him.
I'm just caring about my teammates.
Do you know how Jie is
with Wang Chu Nian?
Last time, Jie trained him
and hit Wang Chu Nian's leg.
I said Jie has to be responsible for this.
Then Jie goes to the hospital every day.
He's been training for a long time.
He's been doing it for a long time.
I didn't see Wang Chu Nian's leg getting hurt.
What do you mean?
You just say that this is fate.
I miss you.
I'll be looking forward to the moment of my surrender.
I can't walk.
I'm lost in the life in the idol drama.
I'm the one you left.
I'm like a piece of paper.
I'm the apple you left.
I'm like a fish that lives in the water.
You are the one who made me fall in love with you.
Why is love so unknowingly?
How can I get through it?
The End
Why didn't you come to the training camp this afternoon?
Today is basketball training.
Basketball training?
You're always training basketball.
You didn't even see what you guys were doing.
Didn't you say that I won the championship?
You didn't object to me playing basketball?
What's the point of basketball?
Can you go to the meal?
Did something happen to you?
I can hide something from you.
What happened to your head?
Didn't I tell you?
I've found it.
It's good to rest.
It won't affect the game.
Chen Su Jie.
Don't let me down.
I'll tell you if anything happens.
I'll ask you one last time.
What's wrong with your leg?
The
White Moon White Moon is in Sili.
How long has it been?
I don't know.
Are you crazy?
You've been hiding it from me for so long.
You said I was fine.
You're still looking at yourself.
I can play basketball.
You're just a kid.
You can beat me.
You can scold me.
But I have to win the game.
You're not qualified to compete with me.
You're the only one who knows the treatment.
You only have surgery.
And you're getting better.
As for playing basketball,
it's impossible.
I'll hold on for a bit longer.
Doctor Zhang,
can you play a game of the wind?
Although it can be a short time,
it's painful to bite.
But it can't be predicted
by the serious level of injury.
You're a player.
Don't ruin your future
for a game.
Can you play the game?
You have to think about it.
If you decide,
come to me before the game.
Thank you, doctor.
Chief,
the wind is too dangerous.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
The team needs training.
I'll go first.
You don't need training.
Open it.
Come on.
What's wrong?
You're not coming.
Come on.
What's wrong?
You're fat.
This girl is called...
Mishi.
Right.
She's not bad.
If you sell this video,
you should earn two dollars.
I have a big brother.
I'll take it for you.
How much is it?
Brother,
this is fire.
You didn't bring it.
What do you mean?
I heard that
there's a good thing about
a small video.
Can you show it to me?
No.
You're wrong.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Sell it to me.
How much do you want to eat?
Open your eyes.
Come on.
It's over.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
Just keep it.
Nothing to do with it.
Don't worry, brother.
You'll know the rules.
Brother.
I'm the most capable man.
Why do you have two phones?
This is Yun Mingxi?
Where did he come from?
Yun Mingxi is a man
who doesn't know
what he's done.
These two
took his video
and went to his place.
The result was that
he was hit by me.
Who made him so scared?
Are you sure
he didn't do anything else?
I'm sure.
No.
I'll go back.
Wait.
What?
Why are you hurt again?
They're more miserable than me.
What are you doing?
Do you want to get seen?
What are you talking about?
What's this?
You took the video?
When did I use
this kind of handphone?
I don't know.
I just want to know
how long it's been used.
I'll go back and look for it.
Do you want to know
if you can find it?
I'm not sure.
I'll go back to the room
and take a look.
I'll go back to the room.
I don't know who you've found.
These videos
were bought by those people.
Are you here to help me
or to threaten me?
Don't worry.
My phone is safe here.
But I have a condition.
What condition?
You promised
that you wouldn't
bother about the Bohan.
I'll delete these videos.
Don't threaten me.
Don't worry.
We won't be together.
She has a foreign country.
I'll stay here.
Why are you so sure
that she'll leave?
Because
she promised to be with me.
I hope you can
keep this secret for me.
You're going to lie to her.
She won't forgive you for the rest of her life.
It's not that important.
I'm sorry.
I'm back.
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
I'm just
a shoe that I lost a few days ago.
You lost it?
It's okay.
I can keep it for 30 days.
I'll go back and send it to my brother-in-law.
How do you know
that the repair period is 30 days?
Such a expensive shoe
is usually 30 days.
Did you buy it?
Why are you laughing?
It's so expensive.
How can I afford it?
You're lying to me again.
I didn't mean to lie to you.
I just want you to
be happy
in the dance club.
How can you afford it?
And
what happened
to your fight with Jiang Man last time?
Why did you hide it from me?
I...
I'm still a little bit timid.
Stop it!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Are you okay?
No.
It's not your fault.
It's just that I was too busy
with my training a few days ago.
I accidentally broke my arm.
I'll be fine in a few days.
You went to train for others?
I...
Listen to me.