=The Rise of Zhao Jiadi=
(Adapted from "Out of His League"
by Fenghuo Xizhuhou)
=Episode 16=
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
Finish your noodles,
then go do what you want.
Got it.
Owner.
A bowl of vegetable noodles, please.
Coming right up.
I lost my job.
How are we going to pay
your tuition next semester?
Mom,
I'm not going back to university.
I'll work and support you.
If we can't change our fate,
maybe we should just accept it.
Maybe this is what we should do.
Go back to the village
and marry someone simple.
There's no place for us
in Haicheng anymore.
I have talent,
but nowhere to use it.
Why is there no place
in this vast world for people like us?
Tangchen Yipin. Take this.
With this house,
you'll have a place to stay.
No, it's too much.
It's just a place to live.
Besides, I need help
keeping it clean.
Consider it a job offer.
I can't accept this.
Shu, we can't accept this.
I just want you to know
that you don't have to beg to survive.
You can stand up
and earn the life you want
through your own effort.
You're right.
I've studied hard for years,
waiting for my chance.
All I've ever needed
is a shot at success.
Then I'll give you that chance.
Ma'am.
As long as I'm here,
Yuan Shu will be fine.
The Chancellor is expecting me.
I need to go.
Shu.
Let's go.
Who's he?
Zhao Jiadi.
No chess today.
I'll show you my real chessboard.
This is where
Haicheng University began.
Let me tell you
its story.
Decades ago,
Haicheng University was just
a vocational school
attached to a machine factory.
I graduated from here.
The Chancellor told me,
Haicheng, and my life,
(Utility Model Patent Certificate)
were meant for more.
Director.
(From vocational college to university.)
Our program was finally upgraded!
It was the hope of a whole generation.
I once promised
I'd make this institution
famous in Haicheng,
but I didn't succeed.
Years have passed,
and Haicheng University
is still the same.
My students still have talent
but nowhere to use it.
They're getting old,
just like me.
Let me give it a try.
Zhao Jiadi, it's a long road ahead.
I need you.
I'll do everything I can
to fulfill your dream, Chancellor.
I promise
this will be my starting point.
Then I hand this chessboard over to you.
No idea who took down the billboard
and got us chewed out.
Who else?
Green Leaf Tech employees, obviously.
They're advertising everywhere.
(Green Leaf Tech)
Heard Green Leaf Tech's stock
is about to skyrocket.
Really? Never heard that.
How does it feel to have
your life affected by others?
So that's how it is.
Zhao Jiadi really is something.
Good morning, Mr. Chen.
Come on.
Pop a bottle of good wine.
Starting today,
I'm going to have some fun with him.