=The Rise of Zhao Jiadi=
(Adapted from "Out of His League"
by Fenghuo Xizhuhou)
=Episode 21=
Can you tell me
if you have found
the meaning of your life?
I used to think
that my life had no meaning.
But after going through everything,
I realized
that meaning is created by us.
With great power
comes great responsibility.
Have you figured out
what you want to do next?
I can't do anything
all by myself.
I've learned that it takes teamwork.
Previously, I was arrogant,
so people around me
left me.
Do you regret it?
No.
I got expelled, got into fights,
fell out with my dad,
and let down someone I love.
I was too young and reckless
to make so many mistakes,
and I also affected others.
But only now
do I realize
that the one thing I did right.
I will never
regret it.
That's to be myself.
Time is like a sieve.
It filters out the people around you,
and in the end, it leaves
the most precious ones.
(Baliang,)
(Mu Hongli has flown back
from Paris to Haicheng.)
Dear, your mom says they've arrived.
We'll meet them
after collecting our luggage.
I want to get some fresh air outside.
Okay. I'll head over first.
Sure.
Meet me at the exit later.
See you later.
(Haicheng,)
(I'm finally back.)
Hongli.
(Zhao Jiadi?)
Welcome back.
(How did he know I was back?)
(It's time to face reality.)
(Mu Hongli,)
(you should tell Zhao Jiadi everything.)
Dear,
you're here.
Why is your phone off?
I was looking for you.
Who are you?
Hello, Mom.
Hongli and I are waiting at Exit 3.
You once said
that I didn't give you flowers.
Looks like this will be the last time
I give you flowers.
Their marriage has been settled then.
Good.
Who is he?
Zhao Jiadi,
if you had any sense,
you wouldn't be here.
So when you said you were leaving,
it was a final goodbye.
I got the wrong idea.
Jiadi...
Hongli and Yu are engaged.
Stop pestering her.
You're like a toad,
you know?
Who are you calling a toad?
Who are these people?
Baliang.
Grandma.
My dear grandson,
I'm sorry you had to go through this.
Mrs. Mu, who is this old woman?
I'm fine, Grandma.
Who's in charge of the Mu family?
(He looks familiar.)
Come out. Let me see who you are.
Some people have their eyes
on their forehead.
(Isn't she Hongli's friend?)
- I won't say anything to this girl.
- (What is she doing here?)
After all, it's a young people's matter.
However,
whose eyes are blind?
Or who's right or wrong?
As parents,
no matter how it hurts,
we have to keep it to ourselves.
Grandma.
You all crossed the line.
So many of you
ganging up on one young man.
What a bully.
Mrs. Mu,
what's going on here?
This brat
has been pestering
my daughter-in-law, Hongli.
Now, he brought his whole family
to lecture us.
We're not scared of him.
Zhao Sanjin!
(Zhao Xin? The CEO of Jinhai Group.)
(This can't be.)
(Zhao Sanjin?)
(Zhao Xin?)
(Is he that famous Zhao Xin?)
How dare you bully my grandson?
Do you have no respect
for the Zhao family?
You're the boss of Jinhai Group,
but you're not helping.
Mom, calm down.
It's trivial.
Watch your blood pressure.
(Oh no, it's really that Zhao Xin.)
Oh, it's Mr. Zhao.
Mr. Zhao from Jinhai Group, right?
We're business partners.
My husband
is a contractor for your company.
Li Qin,
I've looked into
your corner-cutting issues
in the construction of our building.
Ms. Qin, I've also investigated you.
You avoided taxes
on financial projects in Haicheng.
If you hope
to work with me on Rongman Real Estate,
that's no deal.
To be honest,
I hate dishonest people.
Dongcao,
follow up on this.
If the Li family and Ms. Qin
don't pay their fines,
hand over all the evidence.
Zhao Sanjin,
stay out of my business.
Why are you acting tough on me?
Fight back if you can.
You're all tough when confronting me,
but now what?
I don't really care
about them.
Hongli,
we won't meet again.
Grandma, let's leave.
Zhao Jiadi.
Jiadi,
I'll apologize to you.
Can you do me a favor
and not make things difficult for them?
Don't worry,
I don't take advantage of others.
It's not about me winning
and you losing.
This is all
your choice.
Ms. Qin.
Yes, Mrs. Li.
Didn't you say
Hongli was being harassed
by a social climber?
How could you lie to us?
Uh...
He's the son of Jinhai Group's CEO.
We can't afford to rub him
the wrong way.
Maybe we should cancel
the marriage.
Uh...
Dear, Li Yu,
let's go.
We have to find someone
to put in a good word for us.
Let's go.
If we really offend Zhao Xin,
we're done for.
Hongli,
it's my fault.
I apologize.