♪So this is what love is♪
♪I want to transform into a butterfly
and pretend to meet you by accident♪
♪Gentle yet playful♪
♪You are as sweet as honey
and as beautiful as springtime blooms♪
♪Yes♪
♪I have secretly fallen in love♪
♪My eyes are filled with longing.
I can't help but care deeply about you♪
♪In this lifetime, I'll practice hard♪
♪To master
your enchanting worldly charm♪
♪You are like a love story, a poem,
a dream, and a stunning view♪
♪The unparalleled and everlasting love
in this world, all that touches my heart♪
♪Your dress
brushes past the copper bell♪
♪Laughing foolishly,
feeling fortunate to have met you♪
♪Cherry blossoms fall into my heart♪
♪You are like a mood, sometimes happy,
sometimes mad, and sometimes sunny♪
♪I'm the happiest when I think of you
and I want to pick the stars for you♪
♪I'll be gentle with you
for the rest of my life♪
♪You make me want to be close to you♪
♪Let's travel together
to the ends of the earth♪
♪There's a girl, playful and unique♪
♪A smile of hers
can make the whole street bloom♪
♪How could the world ever let down
a pair like us, unmatched in the world?♪
♪The world is no longer fun.
I don't want to explore it without you♪
♪There's a girl,
mesmerized by the spring breeze♪
♪Like falling petals meeting
flowing water, hoping for eternity♪
♪I shall confess my love for you♪
♪There is someone♪
♪I really like♪
♪You are like a love story, a poem,
a dream, and a stunning view♪
♪The unparalleled and everlasting love
in this world, all that touches my heart♪
♪Your dress
brushes past the copper bell♪
♪Laughing foolishly,
feeling fortunate to have met you♪
♪Cherry blossoms fall into my heart♪
♪You are like a mood, sometimes happy,
sometimes mad, and sometimes sunny♪
♪I'm the happiest when I think of you
and I want to pick the stars for you♪
♪I'll be gentle with you
for the rest of my life♪
♪You make me want to be close to you♪
♪Let's travel together
to the ends of the earth♪
[Practice Daughter]
[Adapted from An Yimo's original novel,
The Charming Thief Princess]
[Episode 10]
Little Master, help me.
That's her.
Little Master.
Miss Mei.
Zuo, You.
Little Master, help me.
I'm here. Don't be afraid.
Your Highness.
Go get the Grand Tutor.
The Grand Tutor?
- Maybe we can find someone else.
- Quickly!
I want the best physician.
Yes.
Your Highness, Miss Mei is...
No one can know about today.
If someone gets punished for this,
I will not forgive you.
But Miss Mei broke into
the Eastern Palace...
What do you mean by breaking into?
By my order,
from today on,
Miss Mei has free access
to the Eastern Palace.
No one shall stop her.
Yes.
Leave us.
It's late. Douzi is still not back yet.
I wish nothing bad happened.
What is going on in there?
Nanbei and Zuo left in such a hurry.
Something must have happened.
Stop it.
Mind your own business.
Stop.
Where are you from?
What are you doing
away from your lady so late?
Where are you going?
I...
Take her.
Grand Tutor.
Hurry up.
- Who would do this to an old man?
- Hurry!
Getting me out of the warm bed
- in the middle of the night.
- It's a life-or-death situation.
The Crown Prince
asked for you specifically.
Exactly.
So I have to come because he asked?
- I'm going back to bed.
- Grand Tutor!
Aren't you the servant girl
from the Family Mei?
What are you doing here?
I'm here waiting for you.
Please help save lives.
Scholars of the past told us
a man's life is worth more than gold.
One who saves lives is worth even more.
Grand Tutor, you are kind and skillful.
That's why HisHighness
insists on inviting you
to the Eastern Palace.
You...
You're very good with your words.
You're trying to talk me into this.
But I quite like it.
I am pleased.
You're so much better
than those at Chongwen Academy.
Thank you.
What are we waiting for?
Let's go save lives.
Grand Tutor, this way.
The Grand Tutor has arrived.
The medical kit.
Come here.
This way.
Please wait here, Miss.
The Crown Prince won't let anyone in.
Also, thank you for earlier.
Princess Yueying.
Mei?
Xing Shi.
Do you maybe need something?
I...
Miss Mei,
I wonder if we can talk in private?
There's no one else here.
We can talk here.
I'd like to ask...
How have you been all this time?
All this time?
Thank you, Miss.
Don't worry.
I'll come back for them later.
I think
you look like
an old acquaintance of mine.
Sorry if I startled you.
My bad.
Can you tell me
who is the servant girl
that His Highness just carried
into the room?
She's not a servant girl.
She's the Grand Chancellor's daughter.
Why did you carry these here?
That old man is so annoying.
He insists
on lighting a fire in the room.
Go on then.
Are you looking for the Crown Prince?
I...
How about
I ask for
the Crown Prince's permission first
and you wait in the side hall?
Take a right
and then a left along this road.
It's right at the end.
Give me these.
Thank you, Miss.
Where's my lady?
How is she?
She needs to recover
in the Eastern Palace.
Thank you, Your Highness.
But I'm afraid it's improper.
If my lady stays in the Eastern Palace,
people will start talking.
But she's still in a coma.
How does she leave?
Your Highness's reputation
is also at stake.
Please allow me to bring my lady back.
What are you eating?
You scared me, young lady.
What a waste of such a good thing!
You're still laughing.
Stupid girl.
You don't understand. With some spices
and pepper,
it would be so good.
Who says I don't understand?
No, no.
Save me some. Come on.
You...
You have potential.
You're so much better
than those servant girls.
The last time I ate this,
they were scared,
asking me if it was poisonous.
Not as knowledgeable as you.
Of course. I've eaten so many things.
What have you eaten?
Cicadas.
Pupa cicadas.
And even grasshoppers.
These are what poor citizens eat.
Do you also eat those wild things
at the Grand Chancellor's Residence?
I've also eaten snakes and toads.
And unborn chickens.
You also eat unborn chickens?
Dead in the egg?
Wide open eyes?
They also have wings and legs.
Roast them first.
The taste is so much better than eggs.
You make it sound really tasty.
I'll have to try it sometime.
You drink this medicine first.
You only need one bowl of my medicine.
I promise, within two days,
you'll be alive and kicking.
Really?
I don't believe it.
Why don't you?
If it's not real,
can I still be an Imperial Physician?
I don't think teaching and medicine are
the same thing.
It's the same.
Scholars in the past
have already told us
that you can find beauty in the books
as well as all the wealth you need.
Different herbs together
will produce a certain drug.
The ancestors
have already put these things
- in the books then.
- Grand Tutor.
Listen to them.
- It can't go wrong.
- Look at my situation.
You still want to give me lessons.
Take your medicine then.
So bitter.
It's killing me in my belly.
Bitter medicine is good medicine.
To be honest with you,
I never gave this to anyone.
This is my deepest secret.
I didn't even give it to the Empress.
Fine, fine. I'll drink it all.
Not a drop left.
Good.
I need to tell you.
The Crown Prince forced me to come
in the middle of the night.
Baking a midnight snack by his bed,
I must be the first
and only one in the palace.
From today on,
Miss Mei has free access
to the Eastern Palace.
No one shall stop her.
Look at you.
What a waste this is!
What a waste!
You have no idea.
With all due respect,
she must stay here today.
If anyone finds out
that she was wounded here,
they will need an explanation.
I guess I didn't think this through.
I'd like to stay and take care of her
in the Eastern Palace.
May as well.
You know her needs better.
I've been wondering
why your lady changed so much
after that night at the Museum.
Did something happen
and I don't know yet?
What Your Highness said
makes no sense to me.
Mei?
Mei.
You woke up already.
Looks like it was right
to get the Grand Tutor.
I will take full responsibility.
Did he give you a hard time?
What?
I mean, you're so busy.
Why are you talking to my servant girl?
My lady, Her Highness was...
We were talking about secrets,
of course.
For example,
someone just had to hold...
Stop.
Hold what?
A... A rabbit.
There was a rabbit in his room.
So many hidden weapons here.
His name shouldn't be Nangong Yao.
It should be Nangong Kill.
Looks like Miss Mei
really likes rabbits.
What about
you hold it again?
Come. Help me back to the bed.
I have a headache.
Does it hurt badly?
Very badly.
It's getting late.
Just stay here and rest.
The pain is too bad.
I'm afraid
I won't be able to leave tonight.
The princess is still alive.
God bless Shengdong.
Leave.
Take the little princess with you.
Go.
Xing Shi.
Get the princess out of here.
Make sure you protect the princess.
Hurry.
Leave.
Father.
Father!
Father, wake up.
Father.
Make sure
you protect the princess.
I will.
Father.
Father!
It's your dying wish.
I swear I'll do my best.
Nangong Yao's name
should be Nangong Kill.
He plays dirty.
So many hidden weapons to hurt people.
About the Museum,
the Crown Prince found out about it,
but he let it go.
You broke into the Eastern Palace
and triggered the weapons.
He still chose to let it go.
Why did he do that?
He has a guilty conscience.
He's got my Moon Spirit Pearl.
Where do you think
he hid the Moon Spirit Pearl?
Is it still on him?
That was a great chance.
I can't believe I missed it.
I'll get your medicine.
I just got scared today.
They believed me.
Do you also believe me?
Look.
Then why do you
keep complaining about the pain
and stay in the Eastern Palace?
I stay here
to get close to the Moon Spirit Pearl.
Don't act rashly.
Don't worry. I know what I'm doing.
You're worried about me.
Came looking for me this late.
You're a good friend.
I promise I'll keep this in mind.
Sit up.
Don't rub around.
Sleep well and heal well.
We'll find the Moon Spirit Pearl later.
Let's sleep. Come on.
Promise me.
My dear friend, I promise you.
Stop lecturing me and go to bed.
When did you get here?
One moment ago.
I saw you reading the book and laughing.
I didn't disturb you.
What is this?
Water with sugar.
Leave me.
Hold on.
Did you
also send such water to others?
Others?
You mean Miss Mei?
Is she asleep now?
Did she take the medicine
the Grand Tutor left?
The medicine has been taken.
The lights are also out
in Miss Mei's room.
Okay.
Leave me now.
[Xingqing Hall
Douzi.
Douzi?
Maybe it's hidden in his clothes.
I'm just looking for the pearl.
Not touching him on purpose.
You... You weren't asleep?
Even your wound couldn't stop you.
Sneaking into my room
in the middle of the night.
I... I came to find the pearl.
You said you'd give me the pearl.
But I still don't have it.
When will you give it to me?
You broke into the Eastern Palace
repeatedly for that pearl.
You almost lost your life today.
Tell me.
Why do you have to get this pearl back?
I told you my friend had hysteria.
So much time has passed.
Haven't you come up with something new?
Why do you keep refusing
to give it back to me?
It's just an ordinary pearl to you.
But for me, it can really save lives.
Even if it doesn't save lives,
it belongs to the Family Mei.
Why can't I get it back?
Why?
Why can't I?
If this pearl
really belongs to the Mei Family,
you people
have committed a serious crime.
What crime?
It belonged to Shengdong.
What?
Miss,
am I hurting you?
Then I'll let go.
You promise not to scream.
I'm sorry
I offended you.
I have something to tell you.
Close the door first.
Douzi's got pretty strong hands.
So strong.
I really didn't know
it belonged to Shengdong.
I need that pearl to...
You want something
from Shengdong so badly.
How do you think I feel about that?
I swear,
I only need this pearl for...
Little Master, are you thirsty?
I'll get you some water.
We gave the Family Mei a lot of power.
Yet you betrayed your country
and conspired with the enemies.
- Tomorrow I will order...
- No, you can't.
The Moon Spirit Pearl
doesn't belong to the Family Mei.
It has nothing
to do with the Family Mei.
I'll tell you the truth.
You have to believe me.
About the Moon Spirit Pearl...
Well...
I was going to leave
after I got the pearl.
But then you asked me to pour you wine.
You know what happened afterward.
Mei Yushan and I
switched bodies
on the day of the lunar eclipse.
The pearl somehow went to the sky
and then it started to shine.
I thought you were someone
who has dignity and manners.
I didn't know that you would drag people
into your room when drunk.
Please forgive me.
I swear I'm not a frivolous person.
I really had no choice.
Otherwise, I'd never offend you.
Go on.
On what did you have no choice?
Is there any other reason
for you to come into the palace?
What do you mean?
So I am right.
Then I'm relieved.
What are you trying to say?
I already guessed
that all this time surviving alone,
you must've experienced
some of the worst things in the world
and mastered the way to survive.
All these years,
you must have suffered a lot.
Well, it's been rough.
But I brought it on myself.
Rest assured.
I'll take care of you from now on.
Nothing bad
will ever happen to you again.
You sound so weird.
Who are you really?
When I woke up again,
I became like this.
Mei Yushan and I
switched bodies for some reason.
Little Master,
don't you find this thing strange
and hard to believe?
It is strange.
I'm sure it took you a lot of effort
to come up with this story.
I knew you wouldn't believe me.
You think I'm a traitor
when I don't tell the truth.
And when I do, you don't believe me.
What should I do to get my pearl back?
In my twenty years of life,
I've never heard anything so ridiculous.
Fine.
You say you're a thief.
What proof do you have?
Come here.
It's...
Don't get so close to me.
Now you believe me?
Ridiculous.
I can't believe
you really know how to steal.
I only steal.
I don't do any other bad things.
Tell me if you believe me now.
You're indeed different
before and after you came to the palace.
In that case,
your real name is Douzi?
You finally believe me.
I got so anxious.
I thought
as the Grand Chancellor's daughter,
I would have good food,
good drink and a good life.
I didn't know there were so many rules.
Take small bites. Take small steps.
I even have to
go to the stupid school to study.
Do you know
that I never had to study before?
During those lectures,
people laugh at me.
Your Highness?
Your Highness.
Who's out there?
I heard something in your room.
It's all right. Leave me.
Yes.
What are you still doing here?
You wish to sleep with me?
I should have recognised you
the first time we met.
You have your mother, Empress Li's eyes.
They look exactly the same.
Empress Li?
What are you talking about?
Well, forget it.
You don't trust me right now.
Let's just say I'm drunk and rambling.
But one day
you'll trust me.
Since you're just rambling, then stop.
If you try it again,
I'll report this
to His Highness immediately.
Take your time.
Untie yourself somehow.
[Eastern Palace]
You have your mother, Empress Li's eyes.
They look exactly the same.
Are you feeling better?
You know what?
The Grand Tutor's medicine works.
It's almost healed.
Don't go to school today.
In case they notice your injuries
and we have to explain.
Let them ask.
I haven't done anything wrong.
By the way,
where did you go last night?
I didn't see you in the room.
Where did you go?
I...
I told the Crown Prince the truth.
The Moon Spirit Pearl
belonged to Shengdong.
I begged for it several times.
He suspects your family is
conspiring with the enemy.
I had no choice.
I could only tell him the truth.
Did he believe you?
I don't know.
I came back yesterday in a blur.
I don't know what he really thinks.
The Crown Prince is very cautious.
I'm sure he'll ask you about it again.
Don't worry. It won't hurt your family.
Douzi.
How come
I've never heard you
talk about your mother?
My mother?
Which one do you mean?
You have several mothers?
So many.
I had a Milk Nurse when I was little.
She always spanked me.
I called her Mother Zhu.
Then she'd stop hitting me.
My First Father
had a lover.
She always did my laundry.
I'd call her Mother Chen.
And then there was this Mrs. Zhang
who loved swearing.
She always gave me roast chicken feet.
I called her Mother Zhang.
When she got happy,
I'd have chicken feet to eat.
I meant
your real mother.
Real mother.
I don't have a real mother.
My fathers told me
when I was little,
I was left by someone
in a wooden box in
the middle of nowhere.
I don't know who my parents are.
Do your three fathers
treat you well?
Not too bad.
You know,
sometimes we don't have any food.
They'd take me to steal some.
I'll be there for you.
You won't have to steal anymore.
Even after we switch back our bodies,
you can stay with me.
I would treat you like my sister.
If you don't like it here in the palace,
I'll send you out.
If you want,
you can stay in my residence forever.
I'll tell my father and mother
to treat you well.
Your residence?
I haven't traveled the world yet.
And I wonder
how my fathers are doing now.
This way.
Okay.
Two guys over here.
Coming.
Catch.
Slow down.
Help me.
Be careful.
Okay.
Carry this over there with me.
All right.
In one, two.
Give me a hand.
Slowly.
Hurry up.
Don't waste time. Carefully.
Sir.
- Peace brings money.
- Hurry up.
Peace brings money.
Hurry up.
Slow down.
Hand me that.
Right.
Let's get this up.
Help me.
Stop pretending.
It's so annoying.
You said...
We'd see Douzi here.
It turned out
we didn't even get into the palace.
Well...
Stop arguing. Don't worry.
I saw some officers
went over there
with two jars of alcohol.
They're going to get drunk tonight.
Let's take the opportunity to...
Yu, do you mean
we escape?
Exactly.
Hold on.
We all sleep in a large bunk.
If we get up at midnight,
someone will find out.
I really wonder what you have
in your brain.
If anyone asks,
just say you need to pee.
No one cares about your pee.
We split up.
Wait for my signal.
Someone, come here.
Yu, you're right.
And over here.
Listen to me.
Tonight,
we do like this...
Come here!
Come on. Try harder.
Move it up.
These guys are really suspicious.
- All right.
- Higher here.
We stick to the plan.
We set a trap tonight.
And then you let everyone
in the Imperial Court know
that they hired some fake refugees.
The Crown Prince is in charge of hiring.
When the news gets out,
he will be humiliated.
In the Relief Organization situation,
the Crown Prince ordered
to raid two officers' houses.
These two officers
worked for Lord Liu Qinyuan.
This time, Lord Liu
has decided to mess
with the Crown Prince.
Come on. Over here.
I got the material.
Let's go.
[Xingqing Hall]
Mei Yushan and I
switched bodies
on the day of the lunar eclipse.
The pearl somehow went to the sky
and then it started to shine.
♪It's your mesmerizing glance♪
♪Freezing the gentle breeze
of the mundane world♪
♪Your gentle call awakens me
from my unfinished dreams♪
♪It's hard to convey my love for you
when fighting for the homeland♪
♪Our destined encounter♪
♪I am meant to accompany you
on this journey♪
♪Wishing for a bit more♪
♪So love feels even more real♪
♪You and I, each completing the other,
year after year♪
♪Accompany me to explore the world♪
♪We walk together on bustling streets♪
♪My heart leans
towards your warm embrace♪
♪We're both kites reclaimed
from the edge of the sky♪
♪If it's an unfathomable fate,
let me do it again♪
♪We're both misunderstood,
yet we accept it willingly♪
♪Step forth boldly and join me
without asking where we're heading♪