Until last week,
we greeted you in Pani Bottle's house...
without him here.
Finally, the owner of the house is back.
- Pani Bottle!
- Hello.
(The owner of the house,
Pani Bottle, is finally back.)
(In Pani Bottle's house
without Pani Bottle)
(They basically filmed "Parasite"
for the past 2 weeks.)
(The owner of the house was locked up.)
You guys did well without me.
- Pani Bottle has gotten more handsome...
- Yes?
since Season One.
- He has gotten more handsome.
- He's becoming a celebrity.
He did become a celebrity.
He was even in a commercial.
The commercial and everything
were all thanks to Adventure by Accident.
When I go to the airport,
they don't know my name,
but they say, "That is Kian84's friend."
- Really?
- Oh, my.
- "Kian84's friend."
- Gosh.
(Pani Bottle, the popular new celebrity,
in the airport)
We should get a picture.
- Kian84! I really enjoyed that.
- This is crazy.
- Oh, yes.
- I don't know his name. Kian84's friend.
(I don't know his name. Kian84's friend)
- Oh, my.
- Yes. They really all recognize me.
You even talk like a celebrity now.
- He's famous now.
- He's a total entertainer now.
(Kian84's friend, 37 years old,
professional entertainer)
Your YouTube channel became famous...
- with your India trip, right?
- Right.
- Yes.
How did you feel when you heard
about the India trip for Season Two?
This is my third time going there now.
I thought I'd have to lead...
- because I was a bit more familiar.
- You are a bit more familiar.
I don't know whether I did well.
- I don't know much.
- Gosh. What are you talking about?
- You also said so last time.
- But I really don't know much.
- That's not true.
- He didn't know India very well.
But people told me...
that travel YouTubers should be nervous.
You need to do as much as Kian84
to say you went to India.
- A lot of people said that.
- Really?
Kian84 is really a gem
in the broadcasting industry.
(Feeling shy)
Mother Ganga is waiting for us.
Yes.
Can you see it?
(Mother, I brought Dex.)
(Welcome!)
Let's go. Why don't we take a swim?
Let's go.
So naturally like that.
- I wanted to go in at least once.
- Right.
Gosh!
(The first son takes tiny steps
to go meet Mother Ganga.)
(Stepping)
A frilled-neck lizard!
(Frilled-neck lizard)
(Diving into Mother Ganga)
He seems more Indian
than the actual Indians.
(This is Dex's first time
diving into the Ganges.)
(Stepping forward carefully)
(The start and end of India...)
(lies with the majestic Mother Ganga.)
(Mother.)
- Why do you look so cool walking in?
- Hey!
(What is this?)
- You're acting too cool.
- Yes.
- What were you doing just there?
- Hey.
- A ritual.
- What ritual?
- What is that?
- Are you religious?
Hey. You don't have a religion.
(Exploding with jealousy)
Someone went in
looking like a frilled-neck lizard.
- Hey.
- Hey. What are you doing?
He did this.
- I did that to show a lot of respect.
- I see.
You look like a statue.
Seriously.
(Walking into Mother Ganges' arms
with respect)
(Going all the way in the water)
- You're going in like that?
- Oh, my.
(Shaking his hair)
(Diving fully in one more time)
You basically shot a commercial there.
How was the water?
The temperature was just right.
The temperature was perfect.
I feel...
Does it feel
like your sins are being washed away?
My mind is relaxed.
I felt a bit weird while walking in.
As I was walking in,
I thought about a lot of things.
I thought of the people
I loved and valued.
I thought of the sins
they may have committed.
I also thought about my own sins.
I thought
about washing all of that away here.
That's why I wanted
to dive all the way in.
(He naturally dove all the way in
to wash everything away.)
(While Dex takes time for repentance...)
(An extraordinary sight)
Gosh. Stop it.
(They're both enjoying the Ganges
in their own way.)
Can you swim at all, Kian84?
I can swim a little.
(Splashing)
(What?)
(Indian boys are splashing the water
to get their attention.)
Swimming together?
- Sure.
- Swimming.
- It's a battle.
- A race.
- What's best?
- No.
- He's the best.
- Who? He's the best?
- The best.
He's good.
Give it a go.
- If you lose again this time.
- Hello.
- Dex was in UDT.
- Gosh.
- His swimming must be...
- He must be an expert at swimming.
He's the best.
- Look at him.
- He has such intense eyes.
He looks
like he lived his whole life in a pool.
- I'll be the finishing line.
- Okay.
(Whoever gets to Kian84 first wins.)
Start. Finish.
(Starting line, finishing line)
- Are you the best swimmer?
- Yes.
(That's correct.)
(This won't be easy.)
Hey. Please do well this time.
(You know what I'm saying, right?)
(Representing the Republic of Korea
Navy Special Warfare Flotilla)
- Okay.
- He's not just a kid. He's very...
(Korea and India's honor
rests in our hands!)
Okay!
(The race begins.)
(Dex)
- Dex was faster.
- Oh, look. He's fast.
(Dex takes the lead
as soon as they start.)
His eyes are open. What is that?
(Oh, my goodness)
- I'm scared!
- I'm so scared.
- That's scary.
- You look like you'll kill Kian84.
I get so serious whenever I start to race.
(The distance between them grows quickly.)
Oh, my.
- Oh, my. You're so good.
- He could swim so quickly.
Gosh.
(The Indian boy doesn't give up
until the end.)
We won.
- Good.
(A nice and respectful race)
(The atmosphere was nice.)
Let's race until that point.
They're going to race.
Are you going to race each other?
I didn't want to lose.
I also didn't plan on losing at all.
(An unyielding race)
Ready. Go!
(Start)
(Dex, Kian84)
- Oh, my.
- He's good. He's fast. Neck and neck.
(They didn't expect such a close race.)
(Who will be the winner?)
(Racing as if they're
in the Olympic finals)
(Neck and neck)
(Dex shoots forward.)
Dex got past Kian84.
(Dex gets ahead of Kian84 and wins.)
You're good.
I was thinking of taking it easy at first.
I was surprised
and started going full-speed.
- He was so good.
- Kian84 had a faster start.
I was trying to recover
from my pride getting hurt earlier.
Why are you recovering by beating me?
I need a place to take out my anger.
(He didn't even get to take out his anger,
and he's exhausted.)
- I prayed a bit.
- You prayed?
Yes.
- I feel so much better.
- Look at their eyes.
Hello.
(He looks cool even when he's standing.)
- Hello.
- Oh, my.
(Following Dex
and putting his hand on his waist)
Cute!
- He's copying you.
- Are you showing off your charms?
Cute!
A picture? Okay.
(A picture?)
(Once Dex goes with them
to take a picture...)
(Left alone)
Why aren't they asking me for a picture?
He's sad again.
Dex really is popular.
(Running out in the middle of a swim)
(Everyone crowding around him)
We swam together,
but they're not asking me for a picture.
Punks.
(I want a picture too.)
(Oh, my. It's Dex.)
- "Oh, my. It's Dex." What is that?
- He went right past you.
They must've been fans
of "Single's Inferno."
(Heartbreaking loneliness)
- He's so popular.
- He has a lot of fans.
(Wherever he goes,
it turns into a fan-meet.)
You took so many pictures.
(The son of MBC is being threatened...)
(by the youngest son of MBC.)
- Kian84's looking so small.
- His facial expression.
(Lonely)
Yes.
Now that Dex is here,
I'm not lonely anymore. It's fun.
Traveling in a group is more fun...
than traveling alone.
- You don't look like it.
- You don't look like you mean it.
- Did you actually mean it?
- By your facial expression, you look sad.
(Where is your sincerity?)
(Taking care of his fans)
Look at that.
You're kind.
Okay. Bless you.
- Thank you.
(The fan-meet ends successfully.)
Gosh. Look at his body.
(Gosh. Look at his body.)
How sexy.
- Sexy.
- Seriously.
I feel so much better
after getting in the water.
- Are you happy?
- I felt so down over there.
Oh, he's good.
I don't know which body is which.
- Seriously.
- You're like this, right?
Which shorts are yours, Dex?
A ghost.
It's like a ghost picture.
- He's the one on the bottom.
- Right. There he is.
- His face is there.
- Oh, there he is.
(Dex is the one in the black shorts.)
Why are you so sexy?
I'm naturally kind of sexy.
(I'm naturally kind of sexy.)
When he was walking toward me
after swimming,
he was sexy.
He has a lot of hair.
His muscles are big.
His face too.
He has a nice jawline,
and his nose sticks out like that.
He looked cool.
I was jealous of those things.
- You're cute.
- You have different charms.
- Yes. Exactly.
I was pretty good-looking
when I was in my 20s.
- You're still good-looking.
- You're handsome.
- Don't be like that.
- Okay. Thanks.
(Thanks.)
- Shall we go?
- Shall we?
- Should we go?
- Okay.
How about we walk back like this?
- Sure. Let's walk like this.
- Let's tan on the way.
Okay.
The weather is nice.
(The weather is nice!)
It felt nice walking after swimming.
- That must feel nice.
- Yes.
(These two men,
overflowing with wild beauty,)
(happily walk along the river.)
That looks like a pictorial.
- Yes.
- How cool.
(Looking like models
in a magazine pictorial)
(When they walk by)
Look at the dogs lying there.
- Hi.
- Hey!
- You guys are so popular.
That was very nice.
- Everyone says hi so naturally.
- Hello.
People are so cheerful
and aren't afraid to start a conversation.
They like foreigners.
- Right.
- Are you normally a friendly person?
I feel like coming here made me generous.
- Right.
- It just does that.
The Ganges is the river of Mother Ganga.
Right.
(Dex and India are growing closer,
thanks to the river of Mother Ganga.)
If we have to buy new ones...
Oh, here?
We wash our clothes here?
(Laundry placed by the river)
- These are our blankets.
- What?
They came out nice and clean
from the river of Mother Ganga.
(These white cloths look very familiar.)
Are these hotel sheets?
They're hotel sheets.
- Hotel sheets are just on the street.
- I see.
- You're right.
- Towels too.
The pillowcases are here too.
- Drying in the sun.
- Oh, my. There are so many.
We were always in Mother Ganga's arms.
(Mother Ganga's arms)
It's getting crowded.
(The streets are slowly getting crowded.)
- Hello!
- Oh, my.
- Massage?
Oh, they do...
massages on the street.
There are many people
who give massages like that.
- On the street like that?
- Yes.
- Massage.
- Massage?
Massage. Body massage.
How much?
How much is the massage?
(Suddenly shaking his hand)
Okay. I understand.
- Massage?
- How much?
(While Kian84 is being held,
they surround Dex.)
- They suddenly crowded around me.
- Oh, no.
(Confused)
- How much?
- Oh, okay.
Money. How much is it?
(Continuing to massage his hand
without answering)
(Starting to massage Dex's hand too)
Okay. I understand.
Okay. Let's try.
- Sitting. Come.
- Hey.
How much?
He won't tell me how much it is.
(He is only quietly holding his hand...)
I hope they haggle well first.
- I know.
- Really?
You're quite good at haggling, aren't you?
- It wasn't easy in India, even for me.
- I see.
How are you supposed to haggle?
Are you supposed to go really low,
- and then...
- You have to be bold.
The most important thing...
is to look uninterested.
- Like you don't care if you don't get it?
- Yes.
"I don't need this. I'm going."
You need to look like that.
Even if that's not the truth.
- But it's not easy to act.
- No.
I'm worried. How did they do?
(They move with no time to haggle.)
(What is that sack?)
The one with the hole for the face.
(Don't you have a massage bed
with the hole for the face?)
No seat?
(No seat? Go over there.)
- There must be another place.
- Another...
They are moving.
- They are moving the whole store.
- Yes.
Anywhere he wants.
That's great.
(VIP seat with a great view)
(Dex follows Kian84...)
(and gets a seat upgrade.)
(He is bewildered,
with his shoulders seized.)
(It's okay. We just have to trust them.)
(He is twice as cautious.)
(Comfortable)
(But...)
What are they doing?
(Suddenly)
How many people are working on us?
It's okay.
(Many...)
Look at him.
- Are they all a team?
- I have no idea.
- Are they all masseurs?
- What is that?
Gosh, how many are working on him?
What's going on?
How many people are there?
- There are five.
- What is that?
That's so funny.
I thought I was being kidnapped.
Before I realized it,
there were so many hands.
It felt like I was being dragged
by a monster with many hands.
Just one person.
I want one person.
(No way.)
How many people are working on us?
(Dex is also getting a good treatment.)
(Others have 2 at the most...)
(Dex: 4 people)
(Kian84: 5 people)
(They have a luxurious total of 9 people.)
"Luxurious?"
There were nine people,
before they knew it.
"Luxurious?"
- It is luxurious.
- We can't see them.
- Look at them.
- That's so funny.
When we go to a massage shop in Korea,
- we can ask for four hands...
- Yes.
- and pay a higher price.
- This is 10 hands.
- It's 10 hands.
- It's a royal version.
(They are getting 10 hands,
without knowing the price.)
What if they ask for 100 dollars?
This massage is too much.
(And the gaze from this person
is too much.)
(Interesting)
- That's so funny.
- I haven't seen anything like this.
How did this happen?
Are you a professional?
Yes.
- Are you a professional?
- I am.
For how long?
- For 10 years.
- For 10 years?
- Yes, everyone here.
- No way.
- Everyone here?
- Yes.
- Hey, Dex.
- Yes?
Does it feel good?
Well, they said they are professionals.
They're not professionals.
A few of them are just touching me.
(Pinching)
- What is that?
- Look at that.
- Are they making dumplings?
- What is that?
(Pinching them like dumplings)
- They got busted.
- Look at them.
One person is just touching me.
- I know.
- He's just touching me.
One person keeps touching the same spot.
- He is.
- They're just bored.
I think that...
The two on my legs are just freeloading.
It's like they are lipsyncing
in a group song.
Some are just touching him.
- One hour?
- His phone keeps ringing.
(He got a call mid-massage.)
He must be getting a reservation.
He must have two jobs.
The floor is so hard.
Yes.
(He is really a pro.)
(This masseur has nice hair.)
(He only focuses...)
(on scratching his head.)
Isn't he just scratching your head?
(Pulling)
There are six people,
but it doesn't feel good at all.
I heard that...
when you watch ants at work...
only 40 percent of the ants...
are actually at work,
- That's right.
- and 30 percent does nothing.
(Freeloading ants)
It was like that.
(The two can not get out of it.)
Gosh, okay.
I love India.
(He wants them to go easy.)
- Relax.
- What?
(Calm down and relax.)
(Getting him a pillow)
- That's his shoe.
- Look at that.
That's yours.
- Yes, it's mine.
- That's your shoe.
Who's shoe is that?
Why are they using that as a pillow?
Strong.
(Pressing)
(That shoe...)
He stepped on poo with that.
Really?
Shoot.
It's holy.
Why is your shoe here?
(Holy)
They're burying my face in your shoe.
(His face is full of holiness.)
(He fights for an alternative.)
(Yes, my shoe!)
(Jammed)
(He barely gets it and smells it.)
(I can't use this either.)
This is an Indian local massage shop.
They say they have
ten years of experience,
but I think they're only touching
the same place.
(Hush)
How are you feeling?
Two people are freeloading.
(He tells on them.)
I can tell exactly.
Two of them.
The one working on my leg...
- is also...
- Right?
- This isn't a massage.
- They're freeloading.
Say something. Powerful.
- Ouch.
- Hey.
- What?
- Did you see that?
- I saw that.
- What?
- Wait a minute.
- Seriously?
He was seriously just a passerby.
(Embarrassed,
he was seriously just a passerby!)
- They don't usually do that at massages.
- What is happening?
Why is he doing that?
(Just then...)
(Warning)
Tell them to do better.
We will be paying them.
I don't even know how much they will ask.
We're going to be ripped off.
Gosh, but I don't think he...
washed his hands...
His hands are a bit...
They're damp.
My face...
Sir, no.
Face, okay.
Okay.
(He protects with his body
since he cannot communicate.)
I want my scalp.
(He gets up to get a scalp massage.)
Yes, okay.
(What?)
- What? Are you getting praised?
- I don't know.
- They're all different.
- You're getting praised.
Is he brushing off my dandruff?
Why is he doing that?
It doesn't feel good at all.
Why is he doing that to my head?
- Do you want a therapy massage?
- A therapy massage?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- There is something.
- Okay.
There is a method.
They have a technique.
- Wait a minute.
- Why did he put that in my hair?
- What is that?
- Is he styling it?
I still question it.
Why did they dust my hair like that?
It didn't even feel good.
What is this?
(Somewhere between a hair shop
and a massage shop)
I respect it since it is the culture here.
Their hands were weak,
but they did massage me.
It was a new experience.
- Nice?
- Nice.
He accepts it since he respects them.
(The pure traveler accepts
the cultural difference.)
Goodness.
This sure is a massage.
We're in front of the holy Ganges River,
and I almost called out
the Buddhist scripture.
What is going on with him?
They were doing wrestling moves on him.
- From behind.
- Why are you doing another match?
- They were choking me.
- It's another match.
- They were choking me like this.
- Like this?
Why are you doing
another wrestling match over there?
- What is that?
- It wasn't a massage.
Your face seems to be enjoying it.
(Soaring adrenalin)
(Groaning)
(Screaming)
I'm dizzy.
(Ear massage next)
(Hey friend...)
(You have two ears.)
What's wrong?
(Laughing)
I like it.
- Have you had a spiritual awakening?
- It's not refreshing at all.
You look like a really loved newborn.
(Looking like a really loved newborn)
(He became younger
thanks to the Indian massage.)
(He is falling into it, just like Kian84.)
Good.
- Feeling good.
- "Feeling good?"
(Whispering)
- What?
- What time is it?
- It's 5,000.
- What?
- It's 5,000?
- Yes.
- Ten minutes?
- What?
- It's 5,000?
- Finished?
- Ten more.
- Quiet.
Are you kidding me?
(Yesterday, when he was blessed,)
(it was 5,000 rupees.)
The prayer was also 5,000.
- I guess they start with 5,000.
- Yes.
They just give a high price first.
- They're not really asking for it.
- They do?
They just say it first,
and then work down.
He said everyone will be happy
if we pay 5,000.
But 5,000 rupees...
- How much is that?
- How much?
It's 80 dollars.
It's similar to the price in Korea.
(Super positive)
But in Korea, one masseur...
- costs 80 or 90 dollars.
- Yes.
- There were five people.
- I could accept the price.
- Since there were five people?
- Yes.
So was that about an hour?
- How long was it?
- It seemed shorter.
- It was about 15 minutes.
- Yes.
- No way.
- That was too short.
You shouldn't fall for it.
It's an absurd price.
That's too much.
You have to haggle.
Thank you.
Yes.
Okay.
When did you...
(He gives them 500 rupees each.)
- One more.
- Okay.
- No.
- One more.
Enough.
- His eyes are firm.
- That's it.
(Hesitating)
(Anxious)
- No.
- Okay.
(Firm)
- Oh, good.
- That's it.
- It's about the tension.
- Yes.
- Dex was firm about this.
- That was 42 dollars.
- Give them 500 each.
- Okay.
Don't give them more.
They will ask for more.
(He makes sure,
after succeeding in haggling.)
(Kian84 got a massage from 5 people.)
It's 500 each.
Here.
(He gives 500 to 2 people...)
(To 3 people, 4 people...)
(To 5 people...)
(To 6 people?)
Six people?
Six? What?
- Who is that guy?
- There's another one.
Who is that?
Why did he get the money?
(He was about to leave...)
They're saying something.
(It suddenly turns serious.)
Why are you fighting?
Don't fight.
I'll give you more. Don't fight.
(I'll give you more. Don't fight.)
(Goodness!)
What are you doing?
- My goodness.
- Peace.
Don't fight.
Thank you.
Okay. Don't fight.
What are you doing?
(Massage fee, a total of 3,500 rupees,
which is about 56 dollars)
I think there were about
seven people at the most.
But there was no space, so some left.
I'm not sure.
But I just go with the flow,
now that I'm getting older.
"Just take it."
It's not a big deal anyway.
- He didn't want them to fight.
- Yes.
You need to act like Dex, as a traveler.
- You have to be firm.
- You need to be firm about your limits.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- But looking at this,
- Yes.
- I'm sort of a pacifist, like Kian84.
- I don't want people to fight.
- Yes.
I think I would have
given it to them as well.
- Just like Kian84.
- Me too.
I'm like that as well.
- Right.
- I would say something...
- if I spoke the language,
- Yes.
but since that's not the case...
- And they're older, so...
- Yes.
And it was hectic.
- It got confusing.
It could happen
since he was not used to it.
This can happen to anyone...
- while traveling.
- Sure.
There is no right way.
- You're right.
- It's because there is no answer.
- Yes.
- There's no right answer.
I remembered something we must do.
We need to change more money.
- Money?
- Yes.
We only have 500 rupee bills.
- We need 100 rupee bills.
By 100?
We only had 500 rupee bills.
- Yes.
- You need smaller notes.
We burned as many calories
as we did while working out.
- Right?
- Getting a massage is hard.
- I'm hungry. Let's go.
- Yes.
Let's go and eat.
You got hungry after getting a massage.
(Laughing)
(It all turns into memories.)
It wasn't a massage,
but it was some technique.
I lost all my energy.
It's here.
- This one.
- Here.
- The hotel.
- Our guesthouse.
This is the restaurant. I found it.
Gosh, it's hot.
- Hello?
- Hello.
(Hello)
- Hello?
- Hello.
(They enter politely.)
Gosh, the view is...
(Amazed)
- It's amazing.
- The river view.
Gosh, it's good.
Menu, please.
- Thank you.
I don't like strong smells.
No vegetables.
We only have vegetables.
All vegetables?
- Only vegetables.
- Only vegetables?
Really?
(They can only order vegetarian meals.)
Chicken?
No chicken.
- No chicken? Okay.
- Okay.
They have eggs.
- Boiled egg?
- Boiled egg? One.
One boiled egg.
And where is the rice?
The rice.
I will have the egg biryani. One.
Okay.
I want one cheese omelet...
and one tomato sauce spaghetti.
You can't go wrong with that.
Sure.
It's hot.
(It is 10 a.m.,
and the temperature is 32°C.)
- We could burn to death.
- Right?
It's here.
(The food is finally here.)
- Thank you.
- Okay, thank you.
- Here.
- All right.
Thank you.
Let's have a drink.
- It was so hot.
- Here.
(Gulping)
- That looks so refreshing.
- Gosh.
That must be so good.
What's wrong? Was it too cold?
- Was it because it was so good?
- It was so good.
This is what I ordered.
- It's...
- This is my egg.
Biryani is Indian fried rice.
- Biryani?
- Spaghetti?
- It's hard to go wrong with that.
- That's good.
- What is that?
- This is just...
It's fried egg.
- It's fried?
- Yes.
- Have some rice.
- Okay.
(He takes a big bite of the local food.)
(Enjoying)
- How is it?
- It's so hot.
Here.
(He takes a careful bite.)
How is it?
(Enjoying)
- Is it good?
- It's okay.
Yes, it's good.
Okay. Pass.
How is it? Is there any cilantro?
Cilantro?
- I can't...
- Why do you hate cilantro?
- Is cilantro your enemy?
I don't eat cucumbers either.
I heard you say...
you hate those about ten times here.
I kept reminding him.
(Do you eat cilantro?)
(I can't eat that.)
(I can't eat cilantro.)
That darned cilantro.
(The baby hates strong smells.)
He is a hippie in terms of his physique,
but he has a weak stomach.
I will eat all your cucumbers
and cilantro for you.
- Do you eat those?
- I do.
You can eat it.
There are no cucumbers
or cilantro in this.
- Really? Let me try.
- Yes.
Try it.
(Baby Dex tries the local food.)
(Eating)
(Will it suit the baby's tastes?)
How is it?
It's okay, isn't it?
(Let me see...)
- It's okay, isn't it?
- What is that?
It's okay,
but it tastes too much of vegetables.
- Oh.
- Bell peppers,
onions, peppers...
What?
You just don't like vegetables, do you?
He has a baby's taste buds.
It's true.
(However, the older brother...)
(Eating)
- It's good.
- What is this?
(He is enjoying the local food.)
Kian84 can eat anything.
Kian84 has a good stomach.
(Amazed)
I think my stomach...
Do you know the Komodo Dragon?
Its gastric juice is so strong...
that it even melts bacteria.
I think my gastric juice is strong...
like the Komodo Dragon.
I was worried about food,
but I think I'm okay.
I don't get sick often.
Kian84's stomach...
already went through so much.
I think it surpassed humankind.
It already went through an evolution.
That's what I think.
(He is a Neoanthropinae
that already went through an evolution.)
It's not just strong,
he won't even get sick,
no matter what he eats.
Good.
He can eat anything.
Even things that were on the floor.
(He is the Human Komodo.)
(The Human Komodo hunts the local food.)
(Looking)
- There are camels here.
- Where?
Across the river over there. Camels.
I'm very curious about that place.
(There is a vast land of sand.)
Watching the sunset there...
is a very wonderful experience.
A lot of people go there at sundown.
- Goodness.
- It's a camel.
There are lots of hotels
and restaurants now.
It's a vacation spot?
(Across the river...)
(is a place of life and death.)
It's so...
That's odd. It's peculiar.
It's a different place,
divided by the river.
Two types of cities.
(The two different tastes
came together to eat.)
(Enjoying)
That's it.
- This is a nice eating show.
- I liked it.
(Their palates might be different.)
(But the meal satisfied...)
(both the picky eater
and the human Komodo dragon.)
Our room... It's lunchtime.
So we have to check out soon.
- Really?
- Yes.
But we need to take a shower.
We also have to do laundry.
I think we should go and extend
our stay for one more day.
We made a spontaneous decision...
to prolong our stay for one more day.
It was too hot for us
to go somewhere else.
- It wasn't bad.
- Right.
- You're okay with that, right?
- How much is this?
I'll pay for this.
- Gosh, Kian84.
- It's my treat. It's not a lot.
- Thank you.
Thank you for the meal.
- Let's go
- Yes.
I want to take a shower.
(He buys a meal for Dex
as if it's nothing.)
Around this time of the day, in India...
- The receptionist.
Right. One day.
(Namaste)
Master.
We will stay here for one more day.
- Yes.
- One more day. An extension.
How much?
- It's about 4,000.
- It's 4,000, sir.
- And...
- Okay.
- And our beds...
- Yes.
- Clean?
- Sure.
- Reform?
- "Reform?"
- If you give me the key,
- Okay.
the maid will go and clean everything.
Okay. But sir, can we...
(Flapping)
- Wash the clothes? Yes.
- Yes. Wash the clothes.
- Of course.
- Really? How much?
Gosh. He understood you perfectly.
Five pieces.
- That's our list. Okay?
- I see. This is the price list.
- Right. We should get them cleaned.
- Here.
Socks. I see.
- It's nice that there's a price table.
- Pants.
- I see.
- Do you wash them...
- We wash them.
in the river?
- No.
- You saw how people washed laundry.
We have a separate place.
- Clean water?
- Okay.
- Really?
- Thank you.
- If you give me your clothes now,
- Now.
I'll give them back this evening.
- This evening?
- Yes. Today.
- I see.
- Hey, tomorrow afternoon is too late.
No. He said we'd have them by tonight.
(Realizing his mistake)
- Maybe, around 7 p.m. or 8 p.m.
- His English is good.
- Okay. No problem.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Thank you.
- He's cool about it.
(He quickly leaves as he's embarrassed.)
- Oh, no!
- What is it?
Gosh, it's humid.
Gosh, it's so humid.
What do we do?
This just doesn't make sense.
- This...
- I want to take a nap in a dry place.
What's wrong with this air conditioner?
(I have to take action.)
(While Kian84 takes a shower...)
The hotel we stayed in
didn't have the best conditions.
Everything was humid
like the blankets, pillows, and towels.
So I talked to the owner
and asked him to change everything.
We needed the room to be dry
for us to rest.
- Nice.
- And the air conditioner...
was like a fan.
I asked him to change the mode,
so we got cool air.
We got cool air from the air conditioner.
Very cool.
Very cold. Thank you so much.
Okay. Thank you. I'll tip you.
- Two hundred each. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Thank you. Namaste.
Okay. Thank you.
- Gosh. This is nice.
- Is it nice?
Goodness.
- How is it? Do you feel fresh now?
- This is nice.
This is great.
(He took a shower and is lying down
in a clean bed, so he's in paradise.)
(Chuckling proudly)
Actually,
I briefly talked to the owner downstairs.
I asked him...
how much tip I should give in India.
I asked him for an average amount.
According to him,
200 rupees was the minimum.
But we could tip people as much as
we wanted if we had the money.
- Is that so?
- But here's what I know for sure.
I won't give tips to everyone.
If I do that, people will swarm around me.
- So it has to go over the line for you.
- Yes.
It's not that, per se.
I just have a starting point.
(He has a clear starting point.)
- I got it.
- Okay.
- I'll take a nap.
- He'll take a nap.
- A naptime.
Goodnight.
- Lights out for the nap.
- Time for a nap.
It's too hot in the afternoon.
We have to take a nap.
It's like having a siesta.
I bet he slept deep.
(Sleeping soundly)
(Dex takes a shower
while Kian84 is taking a nap.)
(Changing into new clothes)
(He gets the bag of laundry
and heads out.)
He's diligent.
Let's see.
Master. Check, please.
Our clothes.
- Okay.
Okay. Our underwear and T-shirts.
(Fancy clothes)
You got my fancy clothes washed too.
(He took out the flower shirt
for an occasion to dress up.)
(Sniffing)
(He brought this dirty laundry
all the way from Seoul.)
At what time
should I come and pick them up?
From 8 to 9 o'clock.
- From 8 to 9 o'clock.
- Yes.
- Okay. Thank you.
- He's a reliable partner.
Gosh, it's 38°C.
(In the meantime, monkeys
are playing in front of the lodging.)
Right. There are a lot of monkeys.
(In the meantime, monkeys
are playing in front of the lodging.)
- They look cute in videos.
- How cute.
(Creaking)
(Startled)
Come here.
(Come here!)
Why are you picking a fight with them?
Do you want food?
Do we have any food?
- Are you hungry?
- Do we have food?
There's a monkey outside.
(He takes some snacks for the monkeys
and goes out.)
Monkey.
Hello.
Come here.
(Luring the monkey with the snack)
(Grabbing)
- Oh, no.
- Just take one.
(Approaching another monkey)
Come here. You have one too.
Here.
I guess this one has the highest rank.
(Give us some too.)
No.
(The monkey tries to snatch it.)
Gosh. Just have one.
I need to give it to other monkeys.
- Hey.
- So many of them swarmed around him.
Look at that.
It looks just like getting a massage.
(This irresistible man...)
This one looks strong.
(draws people and animals too.)
Gosh, there's a baby monkey.
It's a baby monkey.
- Gosh.
- Gosh. So cute.
Gosh. You must've been baptized too.
Hey. Darn it.
The monkey took it.
(Ripping)
(Laughing)
Look at this punk.
(Munching)
(Creaking)
- Hey. Not there.
- No. Oh, no.
- Dex. Oh, no. What about Dex?
- Why did they go in there?
No!
(Dashing away)
(He was about to go out.)
(Stopping)
- There were so many of them?
- There were more than I expected.
- Come here.
- It was a zoo.
(He stays close to the wall
as he walks out.)
(On alert)
Let's go.
- I found out later.
- They are so cute.
- I fed them because they were cute.
- Yes.
But don't do that. It's dangerous.
- A lot of people get bitten.
- The monkeys...
- In India?
- Yes.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
- Where are they going next?
- Let's go
We have to book train tickets.
As a matter of fact, I did look into that.
Where we could reserve train tickets.
We had to buy train tickets
from Varanasi to Delhi.
- To meet up with Pani Bottle.
- Yes, that's right.
(Last night,
they video called Pani Bottle.)
You must meet me there.
I'll be arriving in Delhi.
- Okay.
- Yes.
There will be a lot of travel agencies
around your lodging...
- in Varanasi.
- Okay.
Go and ask if there are any tickets left.
Just get on the train you want.
The train departing to Delhi.
- Okay. In two days.
- See you then.
(They will meet up
with Pani Bottle in Delhi.)
You can buy the train tickets online too.
But it's complicated for foreigners
to buy them online.
- The travel agencies help you.
- It's better that way.
You just have to tell them
which class you want.
- In person.
- They do everything for you. It's easier.
Just follow me.
- Do you know what's crazy?
- Be careful.
Watch out for the mines.
We're taking the path
that doesn't exist on Google.
- Really?
- Yes.
The path to the restaurant
didn't show up either.
- Gosh.
- Be careful. What is it?
- Something fell on me.
- What is it?
- Hey, the monkey pooped!
- Come on!
- The monkey pooped.
- Gosh.
(Screaming)
- Hey, the monkey pooped!
- Come on!
(The scream of a former soldier in UDT...)
(disrupts Varanasi.)
Come on.
(Embarrassed)
What happened to the manly guy, Dex?
Come on. I had just taken a shower then.
- I'm not sure if they filmed the monkey.
- Gosh.
I'm serious. It was so precise.
- The monkey's anus was...
- It... Okay.
aiming at people
while watching them like this.
- Did the monkey do that on purpose?
- I was so shocked.
- I'm sure the monkey aimed at Dex.
- Gosh. That's crazy.
- Gosh. But...
- That pose helps your bowel movements.
- What is this?
- Gosh. Look.
The monkey is pooping up there.
- This one.
- Look over there.
Look. It's over there. Didn't I tell you?
(Everyone, look at the monkey.)
Over there. The monkey
was sitting on that metal thing.
Gosh.
How could he poop right at that moment?
- I want to go home.
- Let me see.
- Oh, no.
- Where...
- This is so annoying.
- I had a mental breakdown.
- You must've gotten a reality check.
- Gosh.
(Dex, the former solider in UDT)
- This is it.
- He's getting the flag again.
- Stop using this clip.
- This is the famous clip.
- Stop with the flag! Gosh.
- Stop that.
(A beast-like guy, full of masculinity)
That's useless.
(He showcased the beast-like class.)
Dex is so manly.
- I want to go home.
- Let me see.
Where...
- This is so annoying.
- Let me see.
- No.
- I just took a shower.
Wait.
- Where did it splatter?
- It just came down like this.
- It came down in one go.
- It fell on you?
(Contrary to the fuss he made,
only a drop hit his cap.)
Right. It was only a drop.
Come on.
Luckily, it must have been dry poop.
- Is that supposed to make me feel better?
- So...
Kian84 kept making it worse
when he talked to me.
- You're bad at comforting people.
- He's not good at that.
If it was soft, it would have smeared.
- The powder?
- Yes, the powder.
- I see.
- What is this?
Right. It's okay since it wasn't liquid.
I don't think it was poop.
- I think it was the dirt on the bottom.
- Is that so?
The monkey was rubbing the bottom
on the rebar like this.
- The poop powder fell on you.
- The poop powder.
- What's on it?
- It's starting to attract flies.
- There are flies?
- Flies are sitting on it.
- Right. There were flies.
- I guess it was poop.
Gosh. I went to the Ganges today.
What's going on with me?
- It could've been worse.
- Right.
- Okay.
- Gosh, the alley.
- We're almost there.
- It brings back such fond memories.
- Right.
Hey, my friend.
- You didn't rip me off.
- Thank you.
The bag is very useful.
He's like a local.
- You bought it from him?
- Yes.
He didn't rip me off.
Where is it? Is it here?
After this, we can make a left turn.
I think this is the place.
It was one of the activities
on my bucket list.
I want to stand on the moving train.
I want to experience that.
But I'm not sure if I can do it...
because I don't know how the train looks.
I had this fantasy of taking the train...
- with the locals in India.
- Okay.
- I was looking at the map. Hello.
- Namaste.
(They enter the travel agency
to reserve the train tickets.)
We're going to Delhi tomorrow.
So we want tickets.
How long does it take to arrive in Delhi?
- Twelve hours.
- Twelve?
- It was that far?
- Twelve hours?
- Yes.
- Okay.
I will check which train is available.
- Eleven.
Only one train.
The name is Shramjeevi Express.
Ramjeevi Express.
- Shramjeevi.
- Ramjeevi.
And the departure time...
- They need to know the name.
- is three...
twelve.
Departing from Varanasi.
He wrote everything down,
so it was easier for us to understand him.
Even if we didn't speak English,
he still helped us like this.
He's kind.
- I see. We arrive at 4:40 a.m.
- In Delhi.
- Finished in Delhi.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Delhi is the last stop.
We want to change...
(Stuttering)
- Change the class.
- The class.
Which class?
Okay. Can I use the pen?
We want...
the rooftop,
economy,
and...
- first class.
- I understand.
- But this is important.
- First class.
A very short time for the rooftop.
A very short time
for the rooftop and economy.
- Long time for first class.
- Gosh, seriously.
- You were accommodating to me.
- I understand.
This train...
- You're at least trying.
- For this train,
only silver and SL classes are available.
The rest of the classes are not available.
- Back then, we had to buy tickets...
- Is SL class lower?
- for the train that left the next day.
- Right.
All the good seats were sold out.
Personally,
when I first got on the train in India,
it felt like taking the CSAT.
- Why?
- Here's why.
A lot of people made reservations.
- So I wasn't sure if I could get a seat.
- Right.
- It's tough.
- Later,
they give out numbers for the waitlist.
You have to go and check your number
at the station.
Back then, they put up papers.
- So...
- Getting on the train was no joke.
it was like taking the CSAT
back in the days.
I had to check if I could get on the train
or not at the station.
I couldn't get on the train
if my reservation number wasn't on it.
Can we stay in the SL class...
- and then change to the rooftop?
- SL class.
So it's an upper bed.
- Okay.
- An upper bed.
No rooftop. An upper bed.
- An upper bed? What's that?
- Yes.
No chairs?
No chairs.
- I see.
- Beds.
- One bed, two beds,
- Okay.
- and 3 beds. And 1 and 2.
- That's why there are no chairs.
- I understand.
- Eight beds.
I thought we were going to sleep
on a red carpet like ferries in Korea.
I thought so too.
- It's like taking vessels.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- The compartments must be divided.
We can get some fresh air on the rooftop.
And we can come down and sleep
when we're done.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Okay. That's the best.
We buy tickets.
(If we buy tickets...)
Our area is...
clear?
Your bed...
- Other people can't use it.
- How did he understand Dex?
- They can't use it?
- No.
- Really?
- He's amazing.
- Only you can sit and sleep.
- Okay.
Your bed only.
I'll give you the ticket.
- So it has your bed number.
- The bed number?
- I see. The number.
- Yes.
- There's a number?
- Then it's good.
- We were relieved after hearing that.
"Only you can sit and sleep on your bed."
I thought the 12-hour train ride
wouldn't be that bad.
Kim Jin Young.
- Your name is Jin Young?
- Yes.
- You were a Kim?
- I was a Kim.
I'm a Kim too.
Then you're Kim Kian?
No. That's my nickname.
Then are you Kim Dex?
(Kim Dex and Kim Kian)
- Kian suits you really well.
- Which Kim clan are you?
- The Gimhae Kim.
- The Gimhae Kim?
- What about you?
- The Gyeongju Kim.
(Dex's intellectual level is dropping.)
All right.
It's 440 rupees
and 70 rupees on top of that.
- It's not that expensive.
- Okay.
Here.
It's going better than I thought.
- This is your ticket.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Namaste.
Thank you.
Hey. By the way,
- This isn't easy.
- given the price of the train ticket,
we should be frugal.
- Why?
- We've been too generous.
- Right? You felt that now. Right?
- I mean...
- The ten-something-hour train ride...
- That was a pricey lesson.
- costs about 500 rupees.
- Seriously.
We gave 500 rupees per person
for a mediocre massage.
It's okay as long as you realized that.
- The massage taught him a lot.
- That's good then.
I was really grateful that
he told me that himself.
As I was younger,
I couldn't tell him how to spend money.
- No. But you know,
- He told me that himself.
I was angry at that moment.
- Because you spent money recklessly?
- Yes.
(A belated realization)
- Then...
- We have some time before the wedding.
We're going to a wedding.
- Let's buy some clothes.
- I see.
- Clothes?
- To be polite.
Right.
(He met a couple yesterday on a boat.)
(And Kian84 got
a wedding invitation from them.)
- That's an interesting way to meet.
- Gosh, that's so fascinating.
(We'll be happy if you come.)
(He somehow ended up
accepting the invitation.)
Hey, they invited me to a wedding.
(He told Dex that
they had to go to the wedding.)
(That was random.)
(Dex wants to be respectful
at the wedding.)
- Clothes?
- Yes.
To be polite.
You may think I don't care about fashion,
but I care a lot about it.
- You must be lying.
- I'm serious.
Should we just look around?
- Look.
- We have time anyway. Let's browse.
- Fine. Go.
- Okay. Let's go.
(Let's see.)
You know what you like.
I'm the Fashion King.
You have a strong sense
of your own fashion.
Of course. I do.
I see. You'll buy clothes
to be a proper wedding guest?
Yes.
This is the main stage of Varanasi.
Right. I took that path.
- You know, right?
- Yes.
When you go there, you can experience
how it feels to be a celebrity.
- They all want to take a photo with you.
- It's...
- Really?
- Yes.
- They didn't ask me for photos.
- Is that so?
- No.
- But you know,
it might have been just yesterday.
(Scanning)
- Over there.
- There it is.
- Right?
- It's over there.
Should we go and check out men's clothes?
When you attend weddings
as guests in India,
you can't wear short-sleeved shirts.
- Long pants and long-sleeved shirts...
- Right.
are the basic outfit for guests.
- They look expensive, right?
- They do. Let's ask.
- Namaste.
- Hello.
This?
- This one is neat.
- I think this one looks the best.
- This. Five.
- This?
(The outfits for the Indian wedding)
- You guys look nice.
- We spent a lot of money again.
This one.
- Thank you.
(Bye.)
It's night already.
It said the wedding started at 8 p.m.
That was around 6 p.m.
- You had two hours left.
- What's he doing?
It was really hot.
I wanted to eat ice cream.
- Kian84, what are you doing?
- Hey, eat this.
- Have ice cream. I bought it.
- Ice cream?
(It cools down the heat of the night.)
The ice cream was really good.
How did it taste?
It tasted like yogurt with a sour note.
It washes away the heat.
Do you think 30 dollars would be enough?
(He's wondering how much
he should give the couple.)
- Wouldn't that be more than enough?
- Right?
Coming up with an amount
for the cash gift is hard.
I don't think they will come...
- to our weddings and give us cash gifts.
- Right.
- We're givers here.
Let's think of it
as paying for our meals there.
Wait.
So 500 rupees is 8 dollars.
Eight times four...
(How much congratulatory money
is reasonable?)
- So...
- About...
- how about 2,000 rupees each?
- We can pay 2,000 rupees each.
Two thousand rupees
is less than 30 dollars.
Eight...
Eight times 1 is 8, 8 times 2 is 16
Eight times 3 is 24, 8 times 4 is 32
Eight times 4 is 32? No.
- Eight times 3 is...
- Eight times 4 is 32.
No, it's not. 8 times 3 is...
But 8 times 4 is 32. 8 times 3 is 24.
Eight times 2 is 16.
Eight times 2 is 16, 8 times...
Eight times 3 is 24.
(I said so.)
What's wrong with you, Kian84?
- Eight times 4 is...
- I thought it was wrong for a minute.
I hate this kind of me.
- Eight times 3 is 24, right?
- I'm slowly becoming dumb.
(Then how much should we pay?)
- Eight...
- Let's each pay 2,000 rupees.
- Two thousand rupees?
- Yes. 2,000 rupees.
- Let's go.
(Heading to the wedding)
Should we take a rickshaw?
The rickshaw sounds nice.
- Okay, driver.
- Hey.
We...
are here, and we will stay here.
- Can you go there?
- Yes.
- Do you have GPS?
- The drivers have gathered.
- Right.
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven drivers.
- They come within seconds.
- Area name.
- Area name? This.
Ambika Patika.
Rather than using GPS,
they use the area name to find the place.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- How much?
- Five hundred.
- "Five hundred?"
From here to there,
- it's 500?
- Yes, 500.
- Okay.
- Finish?
Finish.
- Two people, 500?
- Okay.
- Dex is good at bargaining.
After learning a lesson from the massage,
it was best to make the price clear
at first.
- Yes.
- Totally.
Dex uses two words to bargain.
- What is it?
- Finish and enough.
(Just 2 words are enough.)
- He bargains with those two words.
- Yes.
- I like "finish."
- Finish. Enough.
Remember those two words when bargaining.
- Finish.
(Please repeat after them.)
- Finish. Enough.
Why are we repeating him?
- To memorize it.
- It's just natural.
- We could go to India one day.
- Of course.
Let's move.
(Going to the wedding)
Oh, yes.
What kind of songs do you like?
Me? NewJeans.
NewJeans.
(NewJeans?)
- "How do I get to Hongdae?"
- Attention
You know it, right?
- "How do I get to Hongdae?"
- I can get there in seconds.
"Hype Boy by NewJeans," is the answer.
I like "Attention."
"Hype Boy by NewJeans" comes after...
"How do I get to Hongdae?"
Don't you know it?
There's something like that?
(Screaming)
What? Something like that exists?
- Do you know what it is?
- Yes. It was trending for a while.
If you ask someone passing by,
"How do I get to Hongdae?"
They leave after saying,
"Hype Boy by NewJeans."
- How do you know that?
- And I
You're 40 years old.
I'm Generation MZ.
- I'm AOMZ.
- He's a social butterfly.
You should age well.
That doesn't suit you.
It was all over social media.
- Is that so?
- What about you, Do Yeon?
I found out a few days ago.
When I was asked the question,
I said to take line two.
"Line two takes you to Hongdae."
"Hype Boy by NewJeans."
"Hi for You?" How come?
You say, "Hype Boy by NewJeans."
- Why?
- It's just a meme. Memorize it.
Only then am I... Is that so?
- That's the meme.
- Gosh.
- Let's practice.
- Okay.
(Checking if he got it)
Let's do it.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
"How do I get to Hongdae?"
"Hi for You by NewJeans."
"Hi for You."
(Laughing)
Is that how it goes?
(The dance is necessary.)
This is it, Kian84.
Gosh, I...
(Learning the latest fad from Dex95)
(Singing)
(Twirling)
Going to the wedding
has made you two excited.
Let's go!
(After boosting up their energy,)
Gosh, this feels nice.
(they're off with high spirits.)
- Ever since we got on this rickshaw,
- Yes?
- we moved about 20m.
- Yes, 20m.
Gosh, look at the road.
None of the cars can move right now.
I can even touch the car.
- Please wipe the headlight.
- Should I wipe it?
Like this? The headlight.
- Gosh.
Just look at the road.
(People pass through the gaps.)
Bolivia was nothing
compared to this place.
How come?
Cars passed each other with a slight gap
in between.
But here, cars pass each other
with barely any gap.
(He has already experienced
Bolivia's traffic congestion.)
(Enraged)
(Cutting in)
(All 3 cars are enraged.)
The drivers in South America were furious.
But in India,
the drivers didn't get angry.
They were very chill
about minor collisions.
- It's their everyday life.
- Yes.
- That, and the cars bump into each other.
(Honking)
Calm down.
(He finds a gap.)
(We're passing through.)
(An order in disorder)
The school bus on the other side...
is trying to crush us to death.
No, don't.
- On the other side, this car is also...
- What?
- trying to crush us...
- They just squeeze in.
- to death.
- That's risky.
- Us... Hurry up!
- Save us!
They almost sandwiched us.
We almost died.
Even if a car hits me,
I think I'll be cool about it now.
(Honking)
(Honking everywhere)
That was tough.
It's surely wearing us out.
Yes. Gosh.
(Exhausted within minutes)
Invited yesterday,
- we're heading...
- Yes.
to the wedding with excitement.
I wonder
what India's wedding culture is like.
I heard weddings were held for three days.
- The wedding?
- Yes.
They party day and night for three days.
(On the day he arrived in Varanasi,
he witnessed a wedding party.)
(The groom is in the wedding carriage.)
(Amazed)
- I can't wait.
- Me, too.
It really looks fun.
- Isn't it literally Bollywood?
- Totally, like a movie.
- Like they dance in groups.
- A group dance.
Is this the place?
- Gosh.
- We're finally here.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Okay.
This is the place.
- Gosh.
- It's about to start.
- It's good that you went.
- I wonder...
what India's wedding is like.
- It's more like a club.
- I've been...
to many weddings here and there in Korea.
- But an Indian wedding is...
- It must feel special.
Thank you.
The extravagance really surprised me.
We finally arrived at the wedding.
"The small fruits became one,"
"and we have become a couple."
There are soldiers here
with spears, Kian84.
(The soldiers with spears
guard the entrance.)
In Korea, the groom and his parents...
greet the guests at the entrance.
- Yes.
- That's right.
But there are soldiers here.
So it started at 8 p.m. sharp.
Gosh.
- Ki! How are you?
- How are you?
- Namaste. Congratulations.
- Congratulations.
- My friend.
- My gosh.
- They invited you two.
- Yes.
This is my brother.
- This is my brother.
What's your name?
My name is Kim.
- "Kim."
- Kim.
- Okay.
- "Kim."
- Have a seat.
- "Have a seat."
- Hello.
Can the guest bring someone...
without a heads-up, like Dex,
to a wedding in India?
A wedding in India lasts long
for 3 to 5 days.
It's better for many guests to come
and congratulate the couple.
That must be why they invited him.
Having many guests must be better,
like in Korea.
- It's a happy day.
- The more, the better.
(They entered an Indian wedding
by accident.)
We should prepare
the congratulatory money.
Where do we put it?
Where is...
- the congratulations money?
- "Congratulations money."
Outside of the party.
- "Outside?"
- Outside.
- Okay, sorry.
- Please take your seat.
Okay, I will go.
- No.
- No, we have money.
We have money.
- Congratulations money.
- Outside.
(They gave congratulatory money.)
Okay. Sorry.
It's different from Korea.
Everything is so interesting.
- It's like I'm watching a movie.
- They have a DJ with a dance party.
- That amazed me.
- They're full of excitement.
- It looks fun.
- That was interesting.
(The Indian wedding
is full of excitement.)
- Lohit!
- Yes?
Where is your sister?
She's finishing her wedding dress.
After the show,
I will take you to meet her.
- Okay.
- You will meet my sister.
- Not yet?
- Not yet.
- Right. Let's greet her later.
- Let's take pictures.
In Korea, if the wedding is at 1 p.m.,
the ceremony starts
at 1:30 p.m. at the latest.
We saw the bride taking photos,
putting on makeup,
and walking around upstairs.
But the groom was nowhere to be seen.
(As the bride starts getting ready)
Gosh, how colorful.
Where's the groom?
(The groom gets to the wedding
by elephant or horse.)
(Slow)
Remember the wedding gift culture
from the groom to the bride in Korea?
It's like doing that on his way
to the wedding venue.
(The wedding venue is missing the groom.)
When we came to the wedding venue...
(Bap, bameudora!)
(What was that?)
- What?
- My gosh.
- It was a remix.
- It's a nice beat, right?
They're greeting you to have food.
- Food, have food!
- Have food!
(Food, have food!)
It would've been awkward
if you hadn't come with me.
- My cheeks hurt.
- That was nice.
- It was hilarious.
- Nice.
- It gets me excited.
- Gosh, you...
- They're playing club songs at a wedding.
- Yes.
Are you enjoying the party?
I'm enjoying it.
- Yes, I'm enjoying it.
- It's so good.
How long does this party last?
What time does it close?
- At 6 a.m.
- At 6 a.m. In the morning.
At 6 a.m?
- In the morning?
- Yes.
(All night until the sun rises?)
- Until 6 a.m.
- All night.
Until the morning, what...
Do you dance all the time?
Yes.
Dance and food?
- Yes.
- Good.
Singing.
- Yes.
- You sing.
(They eat and dance for 10 hours
even though it's the 3rd day.)
I came to the wedding
of someone I've never met in my life.
We met twice.
It's really awkward
as I've never met them.
Yes, it's a little awkward.
It's a little awkward.
(And they maintained silence.)
Gosh.
It's awkward.
Gosh, this is...
- What is everyone doing?
- Hey.
- Yes?
- She's my sister.
- Your sister?
- Sister?
It's similar to what we do.
- Playing a video like this.
- They play a video like this.
The wedding video is like a music video.
It's like a Bollywood movie.
- Right.
- You're right.
Yes.
It looks cool.
Eat.
Yes. Thank you.
- Thank you.
(Savoring)
Is it nice?
- Very delicious.
- Delicious.
A vegetable bowl?
Yes.
- It's a buffet.
- That's nice.
- It's like a standing party.
- It looks delicious.
It's a curry buffet.
It's amazing.
(Even the picky eater
who has a taste palate of a child...)
(is satisfied.)
(As they eat...)
They do this until the morning?
(About 40 minutes have passed
and it's currently 8:40 p.m.)
They've been there for 40 minutes.
The groom isn't coming.
The groom was really late.
I was like, "Is it okay?"
I'll go and look around. You stay here.
- Let's go together.
- What?
- Let's go.
- Take a rest.
(They decided to look around the venue.)
- Okay.
- Hello.
(Saying "hello" with confidence)
Hello.
(Two brothers are looking around
as if they're their relatives.)
I guess this family believes
in the elephant deity.
Do they?
Maybe that's why they have
this statue here.
- It's Ganesha.
- Ganesha.
- He's a famous deity.
The bride and the groom
will probably enter here...
and go up like this.
- I guess so.
- They would sit there.
I guess so.
I guess it's like a bridal suite...
where people bless
the bride and the groom...
and take pictures.
There's no seat for the officiant.
I know.
And a friend who sings for them.
(There is always someone who sings
at a wedding in Korea.)
- That was eight years ago.
- Oh, my.
It's been such a long time
since I watched this.
(To meet you)
(I'll stop here!)
- Were you at a karaoke? What was it?
- It was a rehearsal.
- Was it a rehearsal?
Someone must sing.
- They have a proper stage here.
- Yes.
Did you see the stage prepared?
- The white one.
- Yes.
No one went there yet as they were shy.
The one who starts dancing over there...
will set the mood
for the wedding that day.
- They will lead others.
- Yes.
I guess some people might want...
- to draw attention.
- Yes.
I think he was itching to do it.
(Who is he?)
- What?
- What is it?
(Kian84 is gone.)
Where did he go?
Did he go to start dancing?
(Laughing)
Thank you.
(Where did Kian84 go?)
(Kian84 is wandering around.)
Hello.
Are you getting married here?
No.
- What is it?
- What's going on?
Is your sister getting married?
- Yes.
- Your sister is getting married.
Congratulations.
- That was nice, Hee Min.
- Yes.
- She's her sister.
- Do you like it here?
- Sorry?
- Do you like everything?
- The building?
- Everything.
- "The building."
- Everything?
- Yes.
- I like it.
- Okay.
Is this a tattoo?
- What?
- Tattoo?
No, this is called mehndi.
- "Mehndi?"
- It's henna.
- Henna.
- I know it.
- Yes.
I got one at Gyeongpo Pavillion in Korea.
- It's called henna.
Henna. I know it.
In India, we call it mehndi.
"Mehndi?"
(They draw mehndi on their hands and feet
to bless the wedding.)
- That's mehndi.
- It's beautiful.
Yes. Like this.
- Beautiful. Yes.
- Yes.
(Beautiful)
- She's beautiful.
Thank you.
(Smiling)
Come. Let's go.
- Over there?
- Come.
- Now, dance?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- They're going together.
All right. Let's dance.
- Oh, my.
- Gosh.
(Just a moment.)
She's leading him.
They're going to dance.
(Modest)
(She picked a song.)
Dance.
Yes. Just do it.
Wait.
(Saxophone sound)
You dance?
(What's with the song choice?)
- What?
- Blues?
Is it blues time?
You dance?
(Laughing)
Gosh.
Oh, my.
- Okay.
- It's an upbeat song.
(Grooving)
He's starting the engine.
- Swag.
- "Swag."
Okay.
He yelled out, "Swag."
(All eyes are on him as they heard him.)
- Show them.
- Swag.
(Who is dancing?)
- They're coming.
- They're gathering.
(Excited)
He's really excited.
This is driving me crazy.
(At that moment,
his friend was waiting for him.)
He told me.
"Your friend is over there."
What are they doing?
You were wondering what was happening.
(What?)
(He saw his friend moving his hips.)
(Immersed)
I was shocked. It was shocking.
This is driving me crazy.
It's hilarious.
Dance time.
(This is what dance is!)
(The one who starts and sets the mood?)
(I set the mood.)
- I didn't know he would be the one.
- I know. Kian84 did it.
(He took over the stage with fancy steps.)
Look at his steps. They're intricate.
(I should record this.)
(Shocked)
- Swag.
- Once you start dancing,
you get excited.
What's wrong with him?
Why did he get excited out of nowhere?
(I don't know.)
- "I don't know."
(Swinging)
(Tossing)
(She dances with him.)
(Flailing)
- He's going to make it.
- My gosh.
Oh, my goodness.
(Before Kian84 danced)
(After Kian84 danced)
- Seriously, so many people gathered.
- Swag.
He was shaking up India.
(Yes!)
She must've been so surprised.
(Sorry)
(He wraps it up in a hurry.)
This is embarrassing.
(He pretends not to know.)
(The hiding skill
of a former special forces agent)
Why were you doing that?
This is embarrassing.
(He tries to hide belatedly.)
I'm embarrassed.
- I'm embarrassed.
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- What is it?
I'm fine. I'm very shy.
- Are you okay?
- After he danced like that?
- I'm very shy.
- He did everything.
- The reality hit him.
- He regrets it.
Are you shy? You were very good.
- Thank you.
- You're a beautiful dancer.
(They're coming.)
Why was he doing that?
What was that?
- He doesn't know him.
- I thought he might drag me.
- What was wrong with you?
- He was embarrassed.
This is my table.
- Okay.
Do you want to go to my table?
- Let's go.
- Yes.
(Laughing)
Come here.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
It was Dex's seat.
(While he was hiding,
someone took his seat.)
Dex wasn't important at that moment.
(He forgot about his friend for a moment.)
I look terrible.
(He's fixing his hair.)
I should have at least got my hair done.
What's your name?
- Naina.
- Naina?
- Yes.
Your name? Naina.
- Naina.
- Yes.
(Gosh, Kian84)
You know the meaning of "Naina?"
- I know.
- What?
Your name.
In India, when we tell someone our names,
we tell them the meanings.
It means "eye."
- Eye?
- Yes. It means "eye."
- Eye.
- Your name means "eye."
- Yes. Eye.
- Gosh.
- Yes.
- Your eyes are good.
- Beautiful.
- Yes.
He was talking to her
very enthusiastically.
I'm very happy to dance with you.
This is the most fluent
I've seen you speak English...
Yes, I keep getting better.
All my life... I won't be able to forget.
"I won't be able to forget."
Remember... Remember India...
Remember dancing with you.
- He told her how he truly feels.
- Yes. Thank you.
- Very beautiful.
- I also liked dancing with you.
- Yes. I loved it.
- I loved it.
Next time, dance. Next time.
(Gloomy)
Are you married?
Yes, I'm married.
You're married?
- What?
- Gosh.
- Wait.
- What?
It's not that she was interested in him.
- Right, she was just dancing.
- She just likes to have fun.
What if I get a scolding?
Won't your husband be angry at me?
No.
You're a very kind person.
- Is he a very cool guy?
- Yes.
I see. Thank you.
I'm...
- single.
- Single.
- I see.
My brother is...
- in the fire pit of singlehood.
- "The fire pit of singlehood."
I'm single.
(The younger friend,
who is in the fire pit of singlehood,)
(and the older friend, who is just single)
(Is this sweat flowing from my eyes?)
Her husband came to say hi later on.
He told me to take it easy and have fun,
so I felt at ease.
- Since it's a party, anyway.
- Right.
(Naina leaves after having fun.)
(He turns around.)
- Dex. Come over here.
- Yes?
- Now, he's looking for him.
- Right.
- Is your blind date over?
- What?
No, she's married.
Why did you start dancing all of a sudden?
She asked me to dance with her.
- "Shall we dance?"
- Yes.
It felt like "Scent of a Woman."
("Scent of a Woman" is a movie
that came out 30 years ago.)
- You had a good time.
- Yes.
(I was happy.)
It's past 10:00 p.m. now.
(Current time: 10:05 p.m.)
It feels as if
we're waiting for a celebrity.
We really couldn't tell
when he would get there.
The ceremony itself...
- continues until 6:00 a.m.
- That's right.
There's not much of a difference whether
he arrives at 10:00 p.m. or 11:00 p.m.
So the bride will keep dancing
until 3:00 a.m.
As long as he gets here.
They're all moving around
as if this is the torch relay.
- As long as he's there before morning.
- Yes.
Even the elders are dancing.
(Ever since Kian84's opening performance,
the dance floor was opened.)
- Gosh.
- You started it off well.
The stage was opened thanks to Kian84.
(They're each enjoying the ceremony.)
The groom isn't here,
but the people are excited.
(The groom still isn't here.)
Hello.
(Approaching)
(The Dancing Man came looking for Kian84.)
You're the best dancer.
You dance the best. Yes.
- Do you want to dance together?
- Dancing?
They heard about him.
They heard that there's
a Korean dancing machine here.
Dance? Dance now?
Go? All right, I'm going to go dance.
- He's going. He's going again.
- He's going.
- He won't back down now.
- He's going to show them.
Let's dance.
("Let's dance.")
Kian84 had dreamed about this
before he went there.
(Dancing with Indians)
- It's like Bollywood for him right now.
- That's right.
(He's warming up to fulfill his dream.)
(Revving)
He's dancing like
he's starting the engine.
(Now, it's time for him
to fulfill his dream.)
Nice.
(He's just amazed at Kian84.)
(He's flapping around diligently when...)
("I want to join.")
- Isn't that Lohit?
- Yes.
Lohit's amazing.
Gosh. They're so enthusiastic.
Lohit.
I'm the bomb.
(The loneliness he felt
at Mother Ganga's river...)
(has been healed.)
He's shy during the day
and active during the night.
- You're insane. What are you...
- He's stronger at night.
- You're insane.
- What?
He's healing. This is where he heals.
(The air is hot.)
(That foreigner knows how to party.)
- Go.
Go. Move.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
Move.
Yes.
Turn.
(He's dancing like
he'll be entering Bollywood.)
(They've taken over the stage.)
I'm glad you went to India.
Where's Dex?
Lohit, come.
- Hayarubbam.
He's taking the lead. Goodness.
(When Kian84 gets on his knees,)
(they get on their knees with him.)
This is Bollywood.
(He has even learned the footstep dance.)
How many is he dancing with, by himself?
It looks fun.
Dancing together like that is elating.
(Shaking around diligently...)
There were more and more people.
(is getting him exhausted.)
(He spotted an exit.)
(Well then, goodbye.)
He's getting out of there.
It looks natural.
I'm exhausted.
He caught him.
"Where are you going?"
"Where do you think you're going?"
I'm exhausted. I'm tired.
- Here.
- No.
(They won't let him talk.)
- Here.
- No.
(Welcome to the fire pit of dancing.)
- Goodness.
- They didn't let me go.
How long have you been dancing?
He's been dancing for about 30 minutes.
Gosh. I'm tired!
Stop!
You must have no regrets.
(Bollywood84 fulfilled
his dancing dreams to the fullest.)
So did the groom show up or not?
I don't think he's here right now.
That day...
(The groom...)
He's coming.
- Gosh.
- Finally.
(Do we finally get to see the groom?)
(The unending wedding party
is coming soon.)
(The day after Kian84's wild night
of dancing at the party)
(Dex)
(I feel like my body's broken.)
(With the wedding that Kian84 enjoyed
more than the groom behind them,)
(the two begin...)
(their India trip full of energy.)
(Namaste)
(They get a sacred start to their day
by being blessed in the morning.)
(A blessing touch)
(Give me 1,000 rupees.)
(To the sadhus who are after
enthusiastic consumers...)
(No! Enough!)
(Dex is standing firm.)
(Kian84 is scared.)
(With the protection
of his reliable friend,)
(he goes to take the train,
which is on his bucket list.)
(It's over there.)
(It's here.)
(Dex, who is in shrewd traveler mode,)
(I'm going to sleep.)
(and India84,
who is in local mode without fail.)
(Same space, different temperature)
(They enter the long-awaited train,
which was on Kian84's bucket list.)
(Why is our seat...)
(Kian84's seat)
(It's disconcerting from the start.)
(Their dynamic train journey
is coming soon.)