Timing and Subtitles brought to you by My Girl Team @ Viki.com
[Song: What's wrong with being imperfect? by Huang Yali]
♫  In the crescent moon lives a daydreaming girl  ♫
♫  In dreams smiling sweetly like cotton candy  ♫
♫  Ignite the fairy stick and close your eyes, wait for him to appear  ♫
♫  A boy shared his thoughts to the tree hole  ♫
♫  Fall down and get back up, look up to the blue sky  ♫
♫  Put on a suit and become the knight she wants  ♫
♫  Who hasn't been hurt before?   ♫
♫  Wounds can turn into strength  ♫
♫  What's wrong with being imperfect?  ♫
♫  After rain it becomes sunny, meeting the light  ♫
♫  Being imperfect is also beautiful  ♫
♫  With half a pair of wings can also soar high  ♫
♫  What's wrong with being imperfect?  ♫
♫  As long as there is a future with full of expectations  ♫
♫  There is always a place for love  ♫
♫  We're not perfect, but we are meant for each other  ♫
💄  [My Girl] 💄
[Episode 8: Hand cream, remain in obscurity.]
Miss Meng, CEO Shen asked me to notify you to attend tomorrow's party drink.
It's to make up for the last incomplete cocktail party.
Why did you come?
This is Meng Hui, Miss Meng, our Director Shen's girlfriend.
Could you  be able to not without my knowing
attend my work's function.
I want to sort out my thoughts
and our relationship.
Do you think he  feels I give him a lot of trouble?
But he initially brought me to the company. I believe he wouldn't mind.
Hence, I helped the program team to deliver the proposal.
Plus, it is his staff asking me to attend the work evening party.
Who knows it's not a standard cocktail party but a 'Golf' gathering party.
Who would know they arranged a gathering party at the golf course?
How could I know that?
First, both of you have different work nature.
Also, the income gap is very obvious.
After the honeymoon phase, he'll want to take a break.
So he wants to keep the distance from you.
And he has been busy recently.
That meant he regretted it, right?
You didn't catch the main point.
The main point is Shen Yi has been busy, right?
The main point is Xu Xing Yao schemed against you.
Because of her,  you two had had an argument.
I just said you are naive, being tricked by someone.
What you said, I got it now.
I think I need to have a friend like you.
What could I do now?
This is not my area.
How about, you ask her.
We might as well keep it simple and directly find Xu Xing Yao to tell her
who's Shen Yi's official girlfriend.
Stop taking small actions. With that small idea of hers,
she merely thinks after working hard with Shen Yi for many years and working by his side too,
can she still expect a water-front pavillion to get the moonlight first?
(T/N: advantage of being in a favored position)
Just tell her that when a man and a woman who have been working together for many years,
didn't develop any sparks in love,
can she still expect to be Shen Yi's wife in a few years?
- You want me to say this?
- Just say this.
You... put on your makeup and go.
First, we must now show our weaknesses.
You can lose people but you can't lose. Understand?
[Tick Take]
Why did you call me here? Let's make it clear.
- Do you like Shen Yi and that's why you deliberately go against me?
- Yes.
Are you trying to tell me that after knowing Shen Yi
for many years and there's nothing between us, it will never happen in this lifetime?
Even if this is the case, Shen Yi and I are together.
If you like him, you can publicly announce this.
You can't do something like what has happened at the cocktail party.
What did I do?
I merely let you put on the wrong dress. It was just a minor mistake.
Is this a serious matter?
Do you know what kind of work Shen Yi and I are busy with?
As for you, you are quibbling just over a dress?
Do you know ever since he met you,
Shen Yi made a lot of mistakes?
Because of you,
he even gave up his many years of research for the liquid foundation's formula.
Didn't he tell you that LS Company is now facing financial crisis?
It's that serious?
- I'm not aware. He didn't tell me.
- Why do you want him to tell you?
Would you understand?
When you gave up the surgery, in order to accompany you,
he gave up the opportunity to negotiate with the England Laboratory. He paid them ¥5 million deposit.
In order to accommodate you, he even messed up the cocktail party for the bidders yesterday.
I went to England to clean up the mess for him.
What were you doing then?
You were at a team building.
You offended the colleagues till there's nothing left, Miss Meng.
Shen Yi and I pioneered this. We advanced and retreated together.
Without a career, he's not a match for you.
You think love can guarantee your love.
How long can it last?
Shen Yi is a workaholic.
His goal in life is to research and launch that liquid foundation.
He will never allow anyone to hinder his career.
I'm the only one who can help him in this undertaking.
As for you,
you can only make him cough up compensations.
I won't be drinking the coffee. I have matters to attend to.
You have more time. Take your time to drink it.
You think Meng Hui is not suitable but Shen Yi thinks she's suitable.
He's deeply in love and can't extricate himself from her.
I'm an official ex-girlfriend and I'm not even jealous.
What stance do you have to make decisions for Shen Yi?
You also know that you are his ex-girlfriend?
You sound so dignified but insincere in substance. You said you are Shen Yi's business partner and soulmate.
Frankly, you are only borrowing Shen Yi's status
to serve as a foil for your independence, capability, and ambition.
You think you are strong, capable in your work and are always intoxicated by this, "Look at how outstanding I am."
With your career, why don't you compare yourself with Wu Zetian?
(T/N: only female Emperor in Chinese history)
You keep thinking that LS company can't do without your capability.
But why is the company always in deficit?
Am I more beautiful than you? Do I discriminate you?
Do I make more money than you? Do I flaunt off in front of you?
Many men like me more than you. What should I say?
Move aside.
Miss, are you okay?
What are you doing?
She pushed me.
What's going on? Are you okay, Miss?
We have a monitor here. We can replay it for you.
Forget it. She's such a scoundrel too.
Thank you.
Shen Yi, sorry.
I wanted to help you and go with Miss Meng to the cocktail party. It was for your sake.
I didn't expect her to misunderstand my intention.
She threw her temper at me just now.
She even misinterpreted our relationship.
I explained to her. She refused to listen.
This has nothing to do with you. It has been hard for you.
Have a good rest this weekend.
Don't worry. I won't let this minor matter affect my work.
It's my fault. I will clarify this with Meng Hui.
Shen Yi and I pioneered this. We advanced and retreated together.
Without a career, he's not a match for you.
You think love can guarantee your love. How long will it last?
I have thought it through. I think we are still not compatible.
Let's break up. Sorry.
In order to accompany you, he gave up the opportunity to negotiate with the England Laboratory.
He paid them ¥$5 mililion deposit.
Can you, without my knowledge,
enter my work area?
I want to sort out my thoughts. Also,
our relationship.
Shen Yi
will never allow anyone to hinder his career.
I'm the only one who can help him in this undertaking.
As for you, you can only make him cough up compensations.
Let's break up.
Isn't it just a career? I can make money for LS too.
Xiao Mei, hurry up. We're running out of time, help me out.
The stencil, give me the eyebrow stencil.
Stop for a moment.
What are you guys doing during work?
- You scared me.
- You scared us to death.
It's Assistant Meng.
Good morning.
Assistant Meng. Who told you I am an assistant?
Did Shen Yi say that?
Why are you here so early? Director Shen is not here yet.
Take a seat here first and have a cup of coffee.
Have a seat.
What are you guys doing?
We—
We're preparing to develop a new eyebrow pencil.
We're investigating the current trends for eyebrow shapes.
- What's wrong with your eyebrows?
- The company has rules—
Yesterday everyone worked overtime till very late.
We're not really in a rush today. So we didn't really handle it very well.
Sit.
Cotton pad.
Eyebrow razor.
Your eyebrows are too thick. They just need to be trimmed a bit.
Filling in your eyebrows will only overdo it. Using eyebrow stencils will cause even more of a disaster.
Right?
You say I'm a fifty year old man who has to wear makeup at work.
I'm already a disaster.
You know that we're quite busy with work.
We had no choice but to use these stencils to fill in the brows.
After a while, we end up losing one of the pairs.
Sometimes we use it backward and it ends up even more awkward.
This really is too tragic to look at.
Next time don't put on makeup when you come to work.
- Really?
- Can this work?
Of course it'll work.
It's working hours. What are you guys doing?
- Director Shen.
- Good morning, Director Shen.
- Meng Hui.
- What are you doing during working hours?
What's wrong with you? You're the last person to arrive to work.
Are you throwing away your work attendance?
Is your workaholic self only for me to see?
She's changed into another person again.
Well... let's go into my office first.
It's my first time seeing an assistant giving the boss a lecture.
It was even a harsh lecture.
I feel like they have something on.
It's been cleared up, but who would believe that?
- I don't believe it.
- I don't believe it either.
- Me neither.
I'm begging you guys please stop talking.
Sit down and talk.
Do you feel uncomfortable now?
- Do you remember who you are?
- I came to the office at 9 am. And you?
Don't you know the company's rules and regulations? You're only arriving at this time.
I—
You mean that you're now an employee of my company, right?
We're all part of the company. We're all employees.
What I mean is... right now, are you... my assistant?
- You said the opposite?
- Said the opposite?
I am the assistant?
- Meng Hui, please try to recall your memories.
- I told you to call me Director Meng at the office!
Director Meng... this company... can not only have you as the boss, we can have two. You see?
What nonsense are you saying? Our company is a listed company.
So naturally, we have shareholders and a director.
You are not even clear about the regulations.
So that's to say, you're the only boss of the company.
Then... the company has got nothing to do with me at all?
I just said that you're my assistant.
But I'm also the CEO.
Fine. You're the CEO's Special Assistant. I'm the CEO and you're the assistant.
I—
- Enter.
Miss Meng is here too.
She's Director Meng.
Director... Meng.
- Then... if I'm the special assistant, he is?
- The special assistant's special assistant.
Director Shen, Miss Meng is...
so I got demoted just like that.
I've been demoted too.
Has my salary been cut as well?
If you can't find a perfect explanation to hide this situation, then your salary gets cut as well.
What are you guys whispering about?
Tell me what you guys were saying.
- Uh...
- Well...
Let's have a meeting.
At the last team-building exercise,
I said that Meng Hui is my assistant.
That's actually not the case.
Boss! So I can tell the truth, right?
She's the other boss that I looked for.
After the team-building exercise last time, I did some reflection.
I think I really am not suited to be the boss of a cosmetics company.
So I found Meng Hui who is more professional to be the boss.
I got it so I need to ...
- So she's not Assistant Meng.
- Yes.
From now on you will have to call her... Director Meng.
- Director Meng.
Today's earth-shattering gossip!
Director Shen finally admits that he is not specialized in the field of cosmetics.
Do you not understand the current situation?
Since Director Meng's arrival, aren't we working for two bosses now?
Shouldn't we get double the salary?
How is that possible? But
just close your eyes and buy the stocks of the companies Director Shen invests in.
Guaranteed profits. No losses.
Just take that as your double salary.
Don't you think the it's weird between the female boss and our boss?
I don't know anything.
Stop the car.
- Don't stop.
- This—
Are you the boss or am I the boss? Also, you clearly have a driver so why did you ask Jiang Jiang to drive the car?
Exactly. How did I become a driver?
Aren't I the special assistant's special assistant?
You are the boss. But right now we have a very important collaboration to discuss.
We can discuss the collaboration at the company. We still have a meeting in the afternoon.
- Turn around and go back to the company.
- We're going to go discuss the collaboration.
Are we going back to the office or discuss the collaboration?
You are the driver, so you listen to me.
You are the assistant, so you listen to me.
I am your assistant so I will arrange your work.
We're discussing the collaboration. Listen to me.
Go to Ah Tao's to discuss the collaboration.
Okay, okay.
Why are you looking at me? Look at him! There's definitely something wrong with him.
Not only are you stingy but stubborn as well.
You are self-centered and never care about other people's feelings.
You have an emotional disorder and don't understand human language.
You ridiculously went back on your words.
The entire company can't stand him. If you don't believe me, ask Jiang Jiang.
I can understand the big stress because of work.
But you cannot bring this negative mood to the company.
Him being this way has severely impacted his other colleagues.
As the boss, I can't just not interfere in this.
That's why I brought him here.
Well, Director Meng, the company has some matters for you to attend to.
Why don't we go out first
and let Dr. Ah Tou and Director Shen...
Assistant Shen have a talk.
Fine. Then have a good talk.
I'll reimburse him the money.
What on earth happened?
At the cocktail party the other day, Meng Hui was still fine. What triggered her PTSD so suddenly?
That girl was the pupil at No.3 Primary school.
But Meng Hui first started studying at No.5 Elementary School and went to Chong Hai later.
And it's impossible she studied at No.3 Primary school.
I think we're moving forward too quickly.
She suddenly charged into my world and I didn't prepare myself enough for it.
So... I broke up with her.
From my observations, Meng Hui thinks her career is not on par with yours, causing you to break up with her.
So she is imagining herself as a highly successful
career woman that is good enough to be with you.
What should I do?
All you can do now is to cooperate with her.
Let her firmly believe that she is the CEO of LS.
Once her innermost wishes are fulfilled,
you can smoothly get through this episode of PTSD.
I understand. This happened because of me.
I'll take responsibility.
As for your relationship,
if you really feel that you're not suitable,
then you can wait till she's stable, and then have a talk with her.
As a friend, I hope that you're more genuine.
Tell her why it doesn't work
instead of breaking up with her through a simple Wechat message.
It was my problem. I worried too much.
The priority now is to stabilize her mood. Don't let her suffer any trauma again.
I will have to trouble you for this period of time.
It's a given.
You both decided to break up and you are still taking care of her.
You are already doing well. I should thank you instead.
I have wronged her.
Director Meng.
This isn't right.
What?
Why did you bring me here?
Back to home.
Who's house?
Your house.
Why would I live in such a small place?
Director Meng,  you have to know that
some directors don't even live as well as you.
I don't understand this.
The profit from my investment for the past years was a total of ¥60 million
including the bonuses from the shares.
Even if we deduct LS Company's operating costs and the expenses for research,
no matter how, there's still a balance of  ¥10 million.
How do you know my salary?
Why can't I live in a better and more comfortable place?
I understand.
What do you understand?
I will eventually return what I owe you.
I will pay you back. Let's go.
Wait a moment.
So who's house is this?
Mine.
Then you're pretty hard working.
Where's Meng Hui?
She conned me into doing spa.
It's almost time now.
Why don't I forget about this?
It's too inconvenient to stay in your house.
I will look for a better hotel apartment for her.
You are living next door.
You have two houses in your small suburb?
When I bought them, I had a feeling you may need them.
I'm going now.
This is more like it.
Director Meng, is this place acceptable?
I already said,
when we are alone, just call me Xiao Hui.
Okay, fine. Xiao Hui.
Although the quality is slightly lacking
but it's still okay. I will put up with it and live here.
Then... I caused you inconvenience.
Your ability to execute tasks
is rather fast.
Then... have a good rest and relax.
Don't think about the company matters. Just leave them to me.
Actually, I'm rather tired.
Okay, put down my stuff
and prepare the bath water for me.
Bath water? What's that for?
I want to take a bath.
T-T-Take a bath.
Okay.
You can relax then.
No one has lived here for a long time, right?
There are some scented candles in my suitcase. Light them for me.
Okay.
Hang my clothes in the cloakroom and place my coat on the rack.
Just place my undergarments in the drawer.
Why are you still here?
I- I was thinking to leave after you fell asleep.
So, we are having a 24-hour service relationship?
You can't call it a service.
What about... collaboration?
We have a lovers relationship.
I remember now.
What did you remember?
I started LS Company from scratch
and had feelings for my male assistant after knowing each other for a long time.
They were originally in perfect harmony.
A pity that later, the woman became stronger than the man.
As long as you are happy, you can think whatever you like.
Are we considered to have reconciled now?
I know I'm a very strong person.
It has been tough for you but it's too cold sleeping on the  sofa.
Why don't you go back to sleeping on the bed?
You... you are mistaken.
No. We didn't reconcile.
Are we still having a fight?
There's definitely a problem in our relationship.
This requires time to resolve.
I think we should now
maintain our distance. It's more appropriate.
Don't tell me I have been using my authority to pressurize you?
You weren't willing?
By the way,
the latest eyeshadow color you were talking about today,
I didn't really understand. Could you explain it to me again?
I...
We are already home.
Don't talk about work here.
Then... what should we do?
Assistant Shen.
I want to do something which only two people can do.
Please arrange it.
T- Two people.
Sure.
Why did you bring me here?
[Buy One Get Second Half Off]
The second is half off.
I think it's not worth it for me to buy it alone.
Choose one.
I want fried rice cake with cheese
and spaghetti too.
These two are not...
discounted.
You can choose first and take it.
Hello. Did something happen at the company?
Everything is going well at the company but I'm not.
My small suburb is repairing the electrical circuit. They stopped the electricity and water supplies.
I went downstairs to find a power bank to charge my cellphone,
but I left my keys at home.
When I was downstairs, I then realized that
all the power banks have been borrowed.
My phone only has
twenty percent of battery left.
It's Friday today and all hotels in the city are full.
Aren't you and Miss Meng staying at Doctor Sui's condominium for a few days?
Then... can I go to your house for a night?
Okay. Come and get the keys from me.
My phone only has eight percent left, can you pick me up?
I have to look after Meng Hui, I can't leave.
There's only seven percent left.
I can't do anything then. Think of another solution.
Director Shen, Shen—
Ah Tao, help me. My house's water and electricity supplies have been cut off.
I don't have any cash with me and my cellphone has only
three percent of battery left. I left my keys at home too.
I don't want to sleep in the street for the night and walk to work again tomorrow morning.
Wait there, I'll pick you up.
Really? Okay.
Then I'll... wait for you.
What's with "A friend in need is a friend indeed"?
Shen Yi, you loser.
Why do you have two sets of this?
Even the bathrobes too?
How is it the same? Mine is grey, yours is navy blue.
What do you think about Meng Hui?
Will it affect work?
Of course.
Do you think it's very annoying?
This affair is because of me.
I'll take responsibility.
Thanks to you. If not, I would have slept on the street tonight.
It's okay. Just make yourself at home.
I will get a pajama for you.
Thanks.
It's almost your size.
- Go and change.
- Okay.
J- Jiang Jiang!
The bathroom's over there.
This—
I'll do it myself.
Sure, I'll get the plates then.
Sorry, I usually live by myself, so it's pretty messy.
I... I imposed on you. I didn't think too much about this.
It's okay. Have some supper.
Come and sit here.
A can each. Just nice for two people.
I better not drink.
Didn't you say to drink together and watch the movie?
It's not good for a girl to drink too much.
Girl?
Net assets per share,
bid per share.
Come in.
Love Psychology
Establishing Gender Awareness.
It's okay. Just make yourself at home.
Girl?
Because men and women process problems differently in their brains.
When a man handles a problem, it's done from a perspective of the core
but a woman handles it from a perspective of feelings
to look at the problem.
Working overtime will affect the rest. This problem is very simple.
As long as the staff's overtime exceeds 10 pm the day before,
they will be exempted from wearing makeup for the second day. Perfectly solved.
Furthermore, I don't understand why every staff must be issued a makeup kit.
It takes up a lot of budget. Is there a need for this?
You can't just simply solve the staff's problem this way. You should consider their feelings too.
Why don't we cancel the system for staff to wear makeup at work? It will be more convenient for everyone.
Because we are a cosmetics company.
Give everyone a set of makeup kit then.
I—
Cancel the system of wearing makeup at work.
Okay.
The system of wearing makeup at work is canceled]
[Shen Yi]
What's up?
- Where are the documents that Director Zhou send to us?
- It's in the red file.
Red? There's no red file. Found it.
Also, where's that financial report?
It's in the blue file.
Found it.
There's only ten percent of battery left on my cellphone. I'm hanging up.
By the way, if there's anything in the future, use the internal line. Don't call my personal cellphone. Thank you.
- Where's that proposal?
- There's still eight percent left.
- I need this for the afternoon meeting.
- Six percent.
Hello?
Isn't there still 98 percent battery left?
The 98 percent battery is to maintain my private life unless
I roam in the street.
Sorry about what happened yesterday.
I really couldn't leave and take care of you.
But I really have lots of matters to seek guidance from you.
This is my first time as an assistant. I don't know what to do.
Here's your bank card and password.
This is your work schedule.
This is your private schedule too.
All these belong to Director Meng now.
I need to remember all this?
Anyway, you wanted to accommodate Miss Meng, right? You should do it till the end then.
In any case, what's important is that you should do a self-check.
Those documents which you handed to her were not that urgent.
Those in red files are important documents you should handle.
Those in blue files are for Miss Meng to handle. They are not urgent.
The kind that won't even matter if you threw it into the paper shredder.
Don't ever mix up these two files.
What's this?
Miss Meng personally stuck those on.
Boss. Boss?
Don't use those evil eyes to look at the files, okay?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by My Girl Team @ Viki.com
The shape of the eyebrows is the soul of a makeup look.
If  your eyebrows look good, your makeup will look more three dimensional.
If your eyebrows stand out too much, your makeup will look unnatural.
I'm that eyebrow.
♫  Unable to escape; unable to retreat  ♫
♫  I have long been used to this chaotic world  ♫
♫  But I can feel you here in this world  ♫
♫  Before approaching you, I secretly counted down the time  ♫
♫  I want to find you; I want to hold you tight  ♫
♫  For this, I would wait another thousand years until I meet you  ♫
♫  Unbelievably beautiful and incomparable  ♫
♫  Your eyes shines like diamonds captivating me  ♫
♫  You're the most dazzling spark in this darkness  ♫
♫  Don't let me wander in the world ♫
♫ Leading me ♫
♫  Like the North Star protecting all the corners  ♫
♫  Please let me be loved, too  ♫
[Song: My Polar Star by Chen Xueran]