So well-behaved! Name?
Staying still.
Its name is "Budong".
"Budong"?
Nah, its name is Happy.
That's a nice name. Happy.
Hey, Happy!
Did you get in touch with your dad?
Yes, I did.
I totally forgot
about the time difference.
Thanks for letting me stay here,
or I'd be sleeping rough tonight.
I don't believe that.
Really!
I actually like it here.
It feels safe.
Can I ask you something?
My dad won't be back home for a while,
so during this time,
could I stay here?
Because my stepmother
and her son are at home...
I understand.
Thanks.
I remember you told me
you were raised by your grandmother.
Quite a lot has happened recently.
Yu posted the clip
of you as a designated driver
in the overseas students' group.
Only then did I know you were back.
Stop messing with the sofa.
If you don't mind,
I've cleaned up that room.
You can stay there.
I'm fine with it
as long as you don't mind.
Thanks, that's really kind of you.
Hey... why'd you
end up working at the zoo?
I never knew
you liked animals.
My grandmother loves animals.
She says they're easier than people.
There are lots of pigeons upstairs.
Can I use them as models?
I want to draw them.
You flew all this way
just to draw pigeons?
Of course not!
Pigeons are everywhere.
I draw what I see.
I signed a contract with a gallery.
I came back to sign the contract
and get some inspiration.
You want to draw pigeons?
Go ahead.
This place works.
The view is nice.
I can set up my canvas
right here
and paint.
Sure, sure.
The environment is pretty basic.
If you're serious about art,
clean up this mess first.
How amateur.
Art can happen anywhere.
Remember when we used to
be at the activity center
or community center,
rehearsing?
How's the drama club doing now?
The drama club?
Well,
it disbanded right after you left.
Without you there,
what's the point of getting together?
Let me ask you,
why did you never
keep in touch with everyone?
Did you really not
miss any of us?
Looking back now,
in Canada,
I was quite naive.
Back then with the drama club,
I wasn't even sure
if I was really interested.
For me,
it was just killing time.
Am I hearing right,
Ge Kaiyang?
This doesn't sound like you.
Didn't you always say
to just do things
without overthinking the meaning?
If it's fun,
isn't that enough?
Experience changes people.
After losing everything,
I see how privileged that sounded.
When I was in Canada,
I sometimes had this
internal dialogue
about the
meaning of life.
Back then,
I thought living happily
was enough to make life worthwhile.
It wasn't until I came back
that I realized how much I'd missed.
I failed my grandmother
and I failed
to handle things at home.
I just hope
that from now on,
I don't fail anyone else.
There's also someone else
I owe a lot to.
That's my emotional knot.
Can you tell me now
why you came back too?
Kuang Dazhi's personal guarantee
fell through.
My work visa was cancelled.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's all in the past.
Why don't you go home?
I... I came back
in a panic.
Which home should I go to?
What are your plans now?
I just hope my parents' issues
get resolved soon.
Live well
and take care of my grandmother.
I wonder when I die,
what will be written on this form,
and who will
fill it out for me.
So much happened after I got back.
Luckily, Lu Xinying was there.
Otherwise I don't know
how I'd have made it.
How did you two end up
like this now?
I don't want to get into details.
But I definitely owe her a lot.
Life is but a stage.
[Recently, the National Space]
[Weather Monitoring Center]
[has issued consecutive solar activity warnings.]
[Due to active regions,]
[large-scale]
[coronal mass ejections,]
[Earth is experiencing]
[sustained strong solar winds]
[and geomagnetic storms.]
[While the spectacular aurora phenomena]
[have caught public attention,]
[but solar winds]
[and geomagnetic storms]
[have caused navigation and positioning errors]
[and other issues.]
[Official reports indicate]
[that over the past two weeks,]
[traffic accidents nationwide]
[have increased around 18%]
[from the previous month.]
[However, experts assure]
[these solar winds and geomagnetic storms]
[pose no health]
[risks,]
[so we should remain calm]
[but stay vigilant about travel safety.]
Hello,
Mr. Li!
Um, about this...
I received the pilot program proposal,
but why is it only
Mr. Fu?
I understand,
I understand.
Yes, but Mr. Fu...
I know, I know.
You see, because Mr. Fu
is actually
very shy.
Yes, and
when he sees cameras,
he'll definitely be nervous.
I was thinking maybe I could
participate too,
help create a better atmosphere,
and then also
introduce the products.
What do you think?
I understand.
Alright,
I get it.
Of course, I get it.
Okay then.
Alright, that's it.
Good!
Thank you!
Well,
you go alone.
It's impossible, absolutely impossible.
Go alone
and face the cameras?
Wasn't it agreed before?
I'm just supposed to be a mascot
while you do the talking!
Well, they don't want me,
so you'll have to go solo now.
Don't mess up!
Let's do this,
forget about the brand story first,
memorize the product introduction.
Hurry up!
You go!
Quick!
These clinical trials,
I'll just
display them
for you to read.
You do it.
Get moving!
Quick!
How can I remember all this?
You're a PhD,
what can't you memorize?
Let me see,
these Asian skin characteristics...
How about I
write them on your hand?
I think
tonight's going to be tough
if you need to memorize.
In a foreign land,
we faced
many challenges together.
I saw my wife's
struggle with skin issues
caused by the new
climate and environment.
Watching her
in discomfort
broke my heart.
Please stop! I'm begging you!
Does this sound natural?
The way you're speaking, really,
is even worse than
AI reading!
You have such good resources,
but here you are,
memorizing this,
while I have to watch.
What resources?
Zhang Ran,
the host, broadcaster, and influencer,
could easily coach you!
Are you two still on bad terms?
Look at what you're doing,
making me feel so guilty!
My bad.
Really!
Really, from now on,
I won't say anything, really.
But you can't entirely blame me.
Yudong, let me tell you,
such a big thing with your father,
you didn't tell Ran about it!
Are you still letting me memorize?
Are you still letting me
participate in this pilot?
Fine, you're a rare specimen now,
just keep memorizing.
About my situation with her,
it's complicated to explain.
What do you mean?
That day,
I meant to explain
but got interrupted
and missed the chance.
But she should understand.
No, what do you mean by 'should'?
You can't just guess in relationships!
Ran even came to me
specifically about this matter!
About Cheng Man's merits and interests...
There are so many merits.
Basically,
all of humanity's virtues.
She has a bit of each one.
Does she have
anything she particularly likes.
She loves lots of things.
Fresh air, healthy food.
Flowers and plants, jewelry.
She loves them all.
My son.
And me too.
She's quite fond of both.
Drink like that, you'll get thrown out.
Is that so?
Yes.
I'll kick you out.
She asked you about Cheng Man.
She wants to learn from a good example.
She just wanted to learn
how to be a good wife?
Look at her.
So proactive at solving problems.
Now look at yourself.
You should
step up your game.
Nian.
Why are you
playing with puzzles here?
Where's Mom?
His mom's not here. But I'm here.
Why are you here?
Don't let him drink that.
His mom doesn't allow it!
His mom's not home right now!
Come on, quick! Nian...
Where did his mom go?
She went out for dinner.
With whom?
How should I know?
Slow down.
Come here.
Who is it?
Yudong, what's up?
Who's Zhang Ran
having dinner with?
I might be wrong.
Probably with Cheng Man.
She wants to learn from her.
Don't slack off.
It's a good chance
to practice those eight dishes.
Get out.
Mom, can you do something about him?
Yudong's getting so disrespectful.
Nian, go to your room
and play for a while, okay?
Come on, Nian, be good.
Dad will play with you.
Let him play alone.
No, I'll go with him.
No, he should play alone.
I want to play.
He plays alone! Sit down.
Take this, quick.
Nian, go play
in the tent.
Wait for me in the tent.
We'll play
Crazy Caveman later.
Don't spill it.
The cavemen are invading.
Stop howling - sit down.
My ears are bad.
I don't want to hear anything.
Don't talk.
Bad ears or not, you have to listen.
I've gone deaf.
Can't hear anything.
This is serious.
Look at this child.
At this age,
still staying at home.
No, about this,
Cheng Man has her own plans.
She'll plan and arrange things herself.
Just leave it be, okay?
I'm his grandmother.
How can I not worry?
What about Cheng Man's
arrangements?
What plan does she have?
Her arrangement is just
to keep the child at home.
Kids need to play with other kids.
They need to be outside often,
running around, back and forth.
That's how their personality develops,
right?
That's how they'll
integrate into society faster.
Staying home all day,
what kind of life is that?
Are you sleeping?
No need to integrate into the society.
How old is he anyway?
What do you want from him?
You tell me.
You're being ridiculous,
making alarmist statements.
How am I being alarmist?
I'm stating facts.
Fine, I see
how it is.
No matter what I say,
it's wrong.
While your wife Cheng Man,
everything she says is right.
You always just say yes
to everything.
Everything she says is right.
I just don't understand you.
A dignified grown man like you,
six feet
tall.
Your family has just three people,
including that hamster.
Son, you rank fourth.
I'm telling you.
Your family status is really concerning.
Mrs. Wang, you're now attempting
to stir up trouble
in my family.
You...
Besides, at our home,
how do I not have status?
Look, the living room now
is all my space.
This is all mine too, see.
Come on, is this really yours?
This is her greenhouse.
Knew it was a greenhouse. Sharp.
At least I have
one small area.
Stop joking around, I'm being serious.
Stop laughing.
Okay.
So full of ideas?
Tell Cheng Man yourself.
I'm afraid when relaying your message,
I might miss something.
No.
You know I don't dare talk to her.
That's why I'm telling you.
I've found the root.
I got it from you.
Get out.
Yudong got it from you too.
Look at this.
How did you pass these traits
even to Yudong?
Stop talking nonsense.
I'm trying to discuss something serious.
I'm trying to discuss
something serious.
I know, I know. You don't worry.
Stop playing, Nian.
Dad will take you to university.
Damn you.
You're killing me.
Come here, caveman.
Don't listen to your dad.
He's talking nonsense.
Weren't we playing cavemen?
Why are you playing video games now?
Just let him play games.
Sit down.
Your mom's not home.
You're really letting loose.
This will do for now.
Okay, please wait.
Let me pour it.
Thank you.
I've been wanting to find a chance
to thank Li Daoqi and you
for helping us so much.
This is something I bought for you.
I picked it.
I don't know if you'll like it.
If you don't like it,
I can exchange it.
Don't look at me like that.
I don't have other intentions.
Li Daoqi and Fu Yudong
are like brothers anyway.
If we look at it that way,
we're sisters-in-law.
It's not strange for me to treat
a sister-in-law to dinner.
Tell me what's on your mind.
Just a small matter.
I want to invite you to be my friend
and record a talk video.
I've never recorded videos before.
I'm new
to your industry.
Besides,
we're not really close friends.
Right?
I'm sorry.
Actually,
there's a script.
If during the recording,
anything goes wrong.
I'll definitely take responsibility.
Isn't that deceptive?
Zhang Ran.
Maybe you're used to deceiving yourself.
But I'm not.
I'm not questioning you.
It's just... we work in different fields.
We're different people.
Don't rush to decide.
Let me honestly
talk to you about myself.
Mom!
It's so late.
Why are you still here?
Let me call you a car.
I'm really sorry.
It's fine.
I can spend
more time with my grandson.
I made some white fungus soup for you,
wait, let me get you some.
Thanks, Mom.
Don't mention it.
The temperature's just right.
Mom, did you give Nian candy again?
Well...
He was crying so hard,
I couldn't calm him down.
All that crying is no reason for candy.
If you satisfy him once,
what about next time?
This added sugar
is not only bad for his teeth,
but also affects his intelligence.
Is it that serious?
I actually ate most of it.
That medical journal
I showed you before...
Especially with
Nian's condition now,
it's particularly bad.
That... that journal,
I didn't really understand it.
I'll remember this time.
If you want
me to watch Nian next time,
whatever requirements you have,
just tell me in advance.
If anything's unclear.
Are you fighting?
What are you talking about?
I called you a car.
It's here, let's go.
The car is here?
Go, go, hurry!
I'll go then.
Remember to drink the soup!
Thanks, Mom.
You're welcome.
Oh!
I almost forgot.
Since Li Daoqi
sold the wedding house for his startup,
so after thinking it over,
I had to set some aside for you.
Take it.
No, no, no!
This money was given to you.
This house is yours now.
Take it.
You've supported him enough.
And now you
don't have much income.
Consider it our filial duty.
Take it.
Don't look at me.
It's not from me.
I tried to persuade her last night.
She insisted on giving it to you.
This is her filial duty to you alone.
Well, well...
If that's the case,
then let's consider
this money as being kept with me.
When you need money,
just ask me.
I'll give it back to you.
Alright, alright, that's settled then.
Okay, time to go.
The car's here, the car's here!
Hurry, it's late!
Okay, get some rest.
Okay.
We're going.
Thanks, Mom.
It's no trouble.
Don't forget to drink the soup!
Take care, take care!
Text me when you get home.
I will, I will.
Take out all the money
and bury it in the hole.
I'll bury you instead.
Goodbye.
Take care.
I know.
Time for bed, time for bed.
Someone doesn't want to sleep.
Are you not tired?
Stop spoiling your mother.
We have to be firm about Nian.
Right. She won't come next time.
She only causes problems.
I'll tell the security
whenever they see her,
to escort her out.
I'm being serious.
I know, I know.
But sometimes,
with Nian, you're really
a bit too worried.
It's unnecessary.
What do you mean "too worried"?
He's my child!
Who else should I worry about if not him?
Yes, I'm talking about my mom.
My mom came today
to cover for you, right?
And taking care of Nian is not easy.
She even made you white fungus soup
and everything,
worried you'd be hungry coming home late.
It's just a piece of candy.
You come in and say all that.
Eating candies is no big deal.
I've been eating candies since little,
right?
She's elderly.
Couldn't you be more understanding?
I know your mom worked hard,
but about the candy issue,
I've already
told her many times.
And, look,
Nian must have
played games all night.
Look at this!
When did he turn on the game console?
I don't even know.
Was it my mom who played?
She loves playing games these days.
Let me tell you,
we should just hire a nanny.
Then your mom won't
work so hard.
One isn't enough. Let's hire four!
Put up a protective circle
with Nian in the center,
so nothing and no one
can get near him!
Fine, I understand.
I'll seriously tell my mom.
I've realized that
this matter is very serious.
I'll let her know, don't worry.
I'll tell her
to listen to you, absolutely.
Listen,
everything I do now
is for Nian and you.
Why did I
come home so late tonight?
I had dinner with Ran
for your sake, you know?
Yes, yes.
And you're still criticizing me!
Really, Zhang Ran must
learn from you, truly.
Compared to you, Zhang Ran
is nothing.
Wanna take a shower?
No.
I can scrub your back.
No need.
Then you scrub mine?
No.
Just a little scrub...
These influencers nowadays
are really interesting.
It's getting a bit oily.
Perfect!
Please put on your earpieces.
Can we wear them on either side?
Yes.
When the director speaks,
we'll all be able to hear.
If later
things get too intense,
do you have any concerns?
I'm fine with anything.
You're the main character, up to you.
Do you have any?
Even if I do, it's okay.
I can overcome it.
Let's just
be honest with each other.
Lying would be too troublesome.
Okay.
Alright, crew members,
please clear out!
I know you don't like me.
Actually, I don't like you much either.
The reason I came to meet you today
is because
I have no one else to turn to.
I don't have any close friends.
As a person,
I have some personality issues.
So whether in China or abroad,
I don't have many friends.
Despite how I've appeared
successful these years,
it doesn't really matter.
When times are good,
you feel like you're surrounded
by friends.
But once good times have passed,
you're left with no one.
It's quite sad.
I thought
about finding an extra to help out.
But after thinking it through,
at least I know Li Daoqi
inside out.
You wouldn't try to cheat me.
So I thought today,
we could give it a try.
It's okay. I can understand
if you don't want to.
And you indeed have every right to be.
That's fine.
Do you think we
look like close friends?
Whether believe it or not is their business.
If you're willing to help me,
I'll accept whatever they think.
Okay, let's look at the next question.
Have you ever
talked behind your best friend's back?
Please answer.
Three, two, one. Show your answers.
Great, Team Anran
gets another point.
For this round of
the "Meeting of Minds" segment...
Isn't it about being honest?
I'm just trying
to make myself look good.
I'll be honest on the next question.
I've checked out
the other nine brands' products.
Let me tell you, tonight,
they're just to make up the numbers.
I have a feeling
that Dr. Fu
might become famous overnight.
Just watch.
Dr. Fu, Mr. Li.
Hello, Ms. Wang!
Well.
I think you're clear
about the livestream process.
Yes.
But I still need to emphasize.
In tonight's stream,
including yours,
there will be ten brands.
Understood.
Each brand has five minutes
to showcase products.
Five minutes?
Yes, during these five minutes,
please make sure to follow
the outline we sent you earlier
and introduce the products one by one.
Lady Wan will lead you.
Understood.
Follow her lead
and introduce accordingly.
Understood. Don't worry.
Hold on, let me greet Lady Wan.
I'll be right back.
Dr. Fu, did you understand
what I just said?
Do I need to repeat?
No need.
Then please prepare yourself.
Lady Wan, this is Dr. Fu.
He might be very nervous,
so please try your best
to support us.
If anything goes wrong,
try to bring him back on track.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Relax.
Lady Wan has everything under control.
Just stay calm.
Be as natural
and relaxed as possible.
No problem.
It's over...
What's wrong?
No, no, don't say that.
I can't remember
a single word.
That's good!
It means you and Dr. Fu.
have become one.
This is what we call
the greatest form has no shape.
And the greatest memory is like forgetting.
Is that even a saying?
Relax, it's fine.
It's fine.
Relax.
You're doing great.
Hello, Dr. Fu!
I want to ask on behalf of all girls.
How can we girls
maintain our best skin condition?
Sunscreen.
That is, try to avoid
direct sun exposure.
For example,
for who live in coastal areas
and highland regions,
and who
often engage in outdoor activities
and work,
their skin
gets damaged more severely.
Instead, those who
live in places with year-round rain
where they don't get
much sun exposure,
their skin is much better.
What if we get
sunburnt?
The best way
is to apply some aloe vera gel.
What should we use
to repair our skin?
Repair...
How to repair it?
For...
For repair...
There's something called
ceramides.
It exists in our
skin's stratum corneum as
a phospholipid.
It can function as
repairing our damaged skin
and moisturizing.
Yeah.
How about your wife?
My wife is doing well.
As far as I know,
when you were studying
in Toronto,
you lived with your wife.
The climate there,
along with skincare products
for your wife's
sensitive skin type, was very unfriendly.
You tried many methods,
but nothing helped.
So you decided
to develop your own product,
is that right?
Yes, my wife's
skin is actually...
Her metabolism speed
is relatively slow,
so the conventional
moisturizing and hydrating products,
including those
for skin repair,
didn't really
help much.
So there's something called
bifida ferment.
What it mainly does is
to increase our skin's
metabolism,
while at the same time
it helps delay aging.
It's impossible
that using any single product
can fix
all of
the skin problems.
If any brands
claim that
after using their products,
you can go back to
how you looked
years ago,
it's either a scam
or the products contain hormones.
Right, I remember things
about bifida ferment
and anti-aging.
Yeah.
From chemistry
background,
there are many things
I can explain to you.
It's quite easy to understand.
I think if I explain it,
it might be
somewhat helpful to you
about skincare.
I just thought of something.
Would you like to hear it?
Yes.
Okay.
Of course!
Hold on.
Do you have a pen?
Thanks.
This...
Bifida...
What's he going to talk about?
He's probably going to say
some chemistry equations
related to his major
and such.
How long is he going to talk?
I should tell you all,
you only have one minute left.
I know.
Everyone knows
ceramide's
molecular formula
is quite complex
for ordinary people.
I won't get into that.
I'll just explain
what you can understand.
Through synthesis,
it reduces to
what's actually called
sphinganine.
Finally...
Lady Wan
seems to be losing interest.
It's over.
Fu Yudong...
Isn't this failing at the last hurdle?
Well, that's
basically it.
If you have
any questions,
ask me anytime.
I will
answer them online.
Thank you. Thank you, Lady Wan.
Well then...
Wait, Dr. Fu,
we haven't sold anything yet!
Come, sit down.
Let's talk.
Yes, we haven't sold anything yet.
Did you use molecular formulas
to pursue your wife back then?
Don't be shy!
Who pursued whom first?
How did you meet?
We...
Weren't we supposed to be selling products?
Alright, let's sell first.
Everyone, if you're
interested in Dr. Fu's story,
then please
show your support!
Three, two, one,
link is up!
Sold out instantly!
Sold out!
Dr. Fu, we've hit one thousand orders.
Since our consumers are so supportive,
shouldn't you
answer the question from earlier?
Actually, there wasn't really
any pursuing between us.
It just happened naturally.
I don't believe that!
Look,
everyone wants you to tell the full story!
No, no, let's not...
Actually, I...
Weren't we here to sell products?
We've sold out.
Let's leave that time for
other brands.
Don't waste their time.
Wait!
Mr. Li,
can we add another thousand orders?
No problem at all!
Alright, three, two, one,
link is up!
Looks like we can
chat a bit longer.
Actually, when my wife and I
first met,
it was overseas.
I came home
- from work that day. Then...
- The viewer count is rising.
Right, right.
I was about to have dinner
when I heard outside my window
very loud noise.
I wondered what was going on.
So I stuck my head out
and looked.
Then I saw a girl
who was
arguing with a group of people.
Those people were always
there.
They had parties
until early hours
and didn't sleep,
making noise there every day.
I wanted to complain about them,
but never dared to.
Then at that moment,
[I suddenly saw this girl]
[rushing forward,]
[arguing with these people]
[for her rights.]
[I thought she was really brave]
[and impressive.]
Finally, I watched this girl
eloquently argued with the group
and drove them all away.
Then I heard her voice,
and I thought...
Looking closer,
I somehow felt that
she isn't a foreigner.
After their argument ended,
I went to talk to her and saw...
She is indeed Chinese,
a Chinese girl.
I wanted to chat with her then.
I really
admired her courage.
Just as I was about to speak, she was bent over.
When she looked up at me,
she was crying heavily.
She kept crying.
At first,
I asked what was wrong,
but she didn't speak.
Then suddenly I understood.
I could relate to her.
I'll help you.
I don't have money.
It's so hard.
You know, for people like us
who often live abroad.
To be honest,
we often feel very lonely.
Even though we
have work
and friends there,
but no matter what,
in that kind of
environment,
you never quite feel like you belong,
and never feel like it's your home.
Only when you return to China
you do realize,
"I'm home".
This is the first time our livestream
has sold so well without even
talking about the products.
This is quite innovative.
Then later,
I tried to comfort her.
She didn't pay much attention.
Before I left, she suddenly said
that it was her birthday.
So I wondered what should I do.
I said,
"I should get you
a cake
to celebrate."
Then I said,
"I might as well take you out
to buy a cake."
But those foreign stores,
well, you know,
they close very early every day.
So that day,
we looked for a long time,
but couldn't find a single cake shop.
Finally found one,
but they were just closing.
What could we do?
We had to go back.
After returning,
the more I thought about it,
the worse I felt.
I felt I still needed to
do something for this girl.
So then,
I took out a large rice cooker
and I cooked
a big pot of rice.
I took that rice and
shaped it into
something like a cake.
I thought we need a candle.
Looked around the house and well,
no candles either.
What to do?
So I took
some paper
and drew a candle.
Then I took that candle
and stuck it in the rice.
Then I held it with the candle
and sang "Happy Birthday to You".
That's how we met.
Happy Birth...
What's your name?
Zhang Ran.
Happy Birthday, Zhang Ran!
Blow out the candle!
Did you make a wish?
No.
Make a wish!
Ready, go!
Happy Birthday to you!
She was very touched at that moment.
Then...
You live alone?
Let's try being together.
Just like that.
So she was the one who pursued you!
To tell you the truth,
when we were
driving on Toronto's streets late at night,
looking for a cake shop,
I think I had already fallen in love with her.
And after all these years,
I actually
never told her this.
You
won't broadcast this, right?
I used to think romantic dramas
were all fake.
Never thought in real life
these things actually happen.
Dr. Fu, you've really given us
a dose of romance!
Come on, everyone,
if you're
interested in Dr. Fu's story
too...
Lady Wan,
hit another thousand orders!
Dr. Fu, it seems everyone
wants to chat more with you.
Mr. Li,
how much inventory do we have left?
Three thousand units.
Let's add three thousand more!
Link is up!
[Hearing Dr. Fu]
[share his story with his wife,]
[I was really moved.]
[It shows how much energy and love]
[Dr. Fu invested]
[in developing products.]
[I believe this sincerity...]
Alright!
This worked out unexpectedly well.
The second half!
Let's go!
This time,
in Lady Wan's livestream,
we specially prepared
a carefully crafted limited edition.
This is a newly updated design,
very exquisite.
What we're bringing you
is a complete set from skincare to makeup,
everything included.
Look what Xing Kai said!
I knew this would work out!
You did great, Yudong!
You know?
Sorry to interrupt,
do you both have time later?
Yes.
After the livestream,
Lady Wan wants to talk with you.
- No problem.
- About what?
Why do you have so many questions?
We'll talk after.
She probably
wants to continue to work with us.
Why are you being so nosy?
You're happy, but I'm in trouble.
What trouble?
Remember the cake thing?
Remember how badly I was criticized?
This time I'll probably be
criticized even worse.
Impossible. Let me tell you,
times have changed!
Ms. Wang just told me
the livestream viewers
all really like you.
I'm telling you,
Xing Kai is completely convinced now.
[To tell you the truth,]
[when we were]
[driving on Toronto's streets late at night,]
[looking for a cake shop,]
[I think I had already fallen in love with her.]
[And after all these years,]
[I actually]
[never told her this.]
[You won't]
[broadcast this, right?]
What a coincidence
to meet you here!
Long time no see!
Didn't you say you don't want
me to talk about us in public?
But you told our story with passion,
even getting emotional.
The National Husband.
Then you must be
the National Wife.
Oh, stop it.
Alright!