[This time is]
[different from before.]
[You must unleash]
[your potential.]
[My lady.]
[Act natural.]
[Lady Tiger.]
Here you are, honey!
My dear!
I've missed you so much!
Look at you.
How skinny you are!
Don't tease me!
I love you too much
to ever tease you!
I tell you...
She looks a bit fatter on camera.
I don't think so.
She's not that fat.
That's not a lunch box.
That's a rice barrel!
You're so clumsy with words!
I'll send my assistant
over to you tomorrow.
It's a deal.
Deal.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Alright?
Do you remember Miss Lan
who just won Best Actress?
Days ago,
I met her on an event.
Her figure
is the result of relentless dieting.
I saw her savoring
every single leaf of lettuce.
My gosh!
Don't follow her example!
That's not your style
and bad for your health.
Alright. Let me introduce.
Come here.
I'm Zhang Ran. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
My entire family are your fans.
My parents watch
your videos every day.
They follow your daily meal plan.
You're always making them laugh.
Thank you! Your
entire family
are my bread and butter.
You're making me blush.
Just let yourself go
during acting.
Don't be nervous.
Okay.
We'll go get ready.
Wait. I'll introduce
you to the director.
His videos have all gone viral.
Director.
Nice to meet you.
We've met before.
Ten years ago.
I remember you.
Ran, it's the director.
Handshake!
Okay.
You're Mr. Yu, right?
Yes.
Director.
Nice to meet you.
We'll go get ready.
Go get changed.
See you in a bit.
Okay, see you.
See what she got?
That's way too much!
I believe you can do it.
I can't!
You can. I believe you.
I'm going to persuade her.
Then you'll have to do that too.
Director!
Wipe on my sleeve, Ran.
Come on.
Is this rainproof fabric?
Then wipe on here.
Bo.
Is anyone outside?
Yes.
Me.
What?
Is this going to work?
I can't believe it.
Well...
What?
Ran.
What do you think?
To be honest, Ran.
I don't know whether it's going to work,
but I can tell
that you're working hard.
Really.
Shut up.
I'd ruin my reputation.
Ran, hurry.
Come over here!
Have you memorized
all the dance moves?
Yes.
Okay.
The four of us
have identical figures.
As long as we move in unison,
they'll think we're the same.
Come a little closer.
No one will notice the difference.
Let's practice it again.
Come and sit.
You can do it. Ready.
Girls, stick your heads out!
Royal Laundry!
Follow the beat!
Wash it!
Harder!
Faster!
Come on!
[Hello, hello.]
[Test. One, two.]
[Hello, everybody.]
[Welcome to]
[Today's Financial Interview.]
[I'm the host, Zhang Ran.]
[Life seems to happen unexpectedly.]
[I thought I would be an interpreter.]
[But now,]
[I am a host instead.]
Over there!
Why does Ran's dancing
look so pitiful?
No.
You don't know her.
Really?
[Come on!]
[Follow me! Royal Laundry!]
[Go!]
I knew you have talent.
Lady Tiger's team
spoke highly of Zhang Ran.
They want to work with her again.
I went out on a limb to sign you.
I knew you
wouldn't let me down.
Look at
this rising data.
Faster than anyone else in the company.
All thanks to both of you.
I never imagined it
would come to this.
It's a lucky accident.
I will keep working hard.
Anran.
Guys.
Have a seat.
Anran. Please have a seat.
I'm fine.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
You've become an overnight sensation!
Everyone is talking about you.
Congratulations!
Thank you for your encouragement.
This one is for
Mr. Lin.
I've had it.
Here.
Ladies first.
Great!
Anran.
Lady Tiger intends to continue
collaborating with Zhang Ran.
You've got to work harder.
That's silly.
That's cute.
Since everyone's here,
I'll say a few words.
Okay.
Zhang Ran's success also
represents an exploration
in collaboration for our company.
This exploration
proved to be quite effective.
We will press ahead.
This isn't my first
venture into entrepreneurship,
but it's the one
where I've given it my absolute all.
Why?
Because this endeavor
is so meaningful.
It brings joy to the people.
It's very important.
With more effort from you,
the world will have more joy
and less sorrow
for the families.
We are not
merely fulfilling
company KPIs.
We are cultivating ourselves.
[Only after this job did I realize]
[how much work there is]
[at an overseas education agency.]
[Though it's tough at first,]
[it's also]
[fulfilling.]
[All I want now is to]
[have my own...]
[...have my own client.]
[Then I'd get a commission.]
[I'll]
[treat you to malatang then.]
Hello?
[Hello, Kaiyang.]
[I'm Yu.]
[I apologize for my]
[attitude last time.]
[We've heard]
[about your family.]
[Please take care.]
[Look,]
[I just met a guy who could]
[be a big help to your family.]
[You must come meet him.]
[I'll send the address.]
[See you.]
Hello, sir.
Hello.
Who are you looking for?
Have you clocked out for the day?
No.
I'm still on duty.
I'm here to consult about
my child's study abroad options.
People say you're
the best agency
in Lucheng City.
I'm here to ask for advice.
I see.
I'm the consultant.
You can come to me
if you need anything.
I'm Lu.
That's great!
Thank you.
I'm Gu.
[I've read the contract.]
[I'm okay with it.]
[I'll go with the most expensive]
[all-inclusive package.]
[Just take care]
[of everything for my child.]
[And,]
[the application deadline is approaching.]
[Please hurry up.]
Okay, no problem.
Mr. Gu.
I'll find you the best
consultant tomorrow.
[No need.]
[You can work on it.]
[You must be responsible]
[to work this late.]
[I choose you.]
Okay.
I can do it, Mr. Gu.
[Alright then.]
Tomorrow, I...
I've brought you drinks.
Thank you so much.
You're all sweaty from the rush.
How's the setup here?
Pretty good?
Yeah?
It's going to rain.
Let's get
down to business.
Don't be in such a hurry.
Let me make the introductions.
Bro.
Kaiyang.
And this is Sis.
Tonight, your problem
will be taken care of.
If there's nothing else, I'll leave then.
Kaiyang, I need to talk to you.
I fished
here all day and didn't
catch a single fish.
The boss said I'm not skilled enough.
I wasn't happy about it.
Kaiyang.
If the fish didn't behave,
we must discipline it.
The same goes for a person.
Yeah?
I've got things to do.
Kaiyang.
If you're still my friend,
you've got to help me out.
You won't have come in vain.
You will be rewarded.
I've got this fish up here.
Boom!
How about it?
I've already resolved most of it.
But the more I think, the angrier I get.
This place
must be burned down today.
Give us a hand.
Yu.
What are you doing?
Don't be a coward.
I won't shortchange you on money.
80,000 yuan.
Or I'll make it 88,000?
What are you doing?
Just take it!
Take it!
Do nothing but take it!
It's worth 88,000 yuan!
Leave the rest of the work to me!
Kaiyang!
Call the police!
Run! This way!
Stop there!
What did you do?
Get them!
Get them! Call the police!
It's not me!
We saw you!
Liar!
Hold him down! Call the police!
Stop!
Don't let them get away!
Have you caught the rest of them?
Yes.
Pal.
What have you done?
Go ahead and tell me about it.
Ge Kaiyang.
How about now?
If you remember,
tell me about your family
and your address.
I checked it.
His parents are imprisoned
for illegal fundraising.
Do you have any other
relatives to help you?
Only a dog remains.
If I were to stay here,
I'm afraid it would
starve to death.
You won't be able
to go out anytime soon.
It'll take at least 15 days.
Is your dog at your
registered address?
Alright.
We'll ask the neighborhood
committee for help.
Go back to your seat.
This big client of yours is really great.
I hear this rich man
doesn't have any
complicated demands.
Whatever you say goes.
Great.
He's just in a hurry.
The application
deadline is approaching.
He just wants to spend money
to get his daughter
a degree abroad.
He doesn't care about school rankings.
How enviable!
He doesn't care about rankings
and doesn't skimp on tuition.
You are free to choose
any school and apply it.
When will I ever get
such easy work?
I didn't treat it easily.
I've applied to
over twenty schools and
prepared materials every night.
I'm exhausted.
Over twenty?
Are you done yet?
Yes.
They've been submitted.
You're good!
You're sure to
get this month's bonus.
Treat me to a meal?
Okay.
How about malatang?
Malatang doesn't
match your bonus.
Something fancier.
Don't look down on malatang!
I want something fancy!
Don't push your luck!
Lu Xinying!
Yes?
The boss is looking for you.
Why is she looking for me?
Is she giving you a bonus?
I'll go take a look.
See you.
Good luck.
Okay.
Mr. Gu.
Finally.
See for yourself.
And these.
These are
the materials I prepared for Beibei.
Is there a problem?
So you know
they're application materials.
What's wrong?
I'll tell you what's wrong.
Check this.
And this.
Are they the same?
This is the template
I sent her.
I told her she needed
to change
the school's name to
the one she was
applying to before submitting.
You told her?
Yes, I told her.
Look, I've told her
both in the group chat
and via email.
I don't care.
Look,
I made it
perfectly clear
from day one that I needed
someone to handle
everything
from start to finish.
All-Inclusive package,
you know?
Don't you know what it is?
I know.
I had intended to help her
modify the template
and had asked her for
her email password.
But she refused,
saying it was
her personal privacy.
So I couldn't.
Was she wrong?
It is her personal privacy!
This showed
she's cautious!
Listen.
This concerns
my daughter's future.
If I don't get
an explanation, your agency
won't be able to operate.
Mr. Gu.
We'll give you a
satisfactory response today.
[Xinying, stop making excuses.]
[In any case,]
[you have already had]
[an impact on our company.]
[If it weren't for the fact]
[that you're broke]
[but diligent at work,]
[I'd make you pay for all]
[the damages and fire you.]
[I've decided with HR]
[to withhold your salary]
[and bonus for this month.]
[You really need to work twice as hard]
[to repay me]
[and the company.]
Yes?
Aiying.
I just dreamed
about you last night.
Really?
Yeah.
That's sister connection.
What would you like for dinner?
I'll cook it for you.
You know nothing about cooking.
Let me cook for you.
Is there something you want from me?
I'm ok.
Your face says it all.
I'm fine.
I just miss you.
Did Lu Ming upset you?
Then it must be Lu Xinying.
Don't mention those two to me.
None of them are any good.
If you have something to say, spit it out.
Don't keep me waiting.
Lu Xinying
is back.
I thought it was something big.
She misses you.
That's not true.
She had a perfectly good
bank job in Canada
and she just dropped it and came back.
And she didn't just return today.
She's been back for a while now.
Lu Ming even knows about it.
The two of them are in cahoots,
keeping it from me all along.
What kind of father is this?
He has no sense of right or wrong.
He told me it was fine
that she could
find a decent job.
I'm open
to hearing their thoughts.
They stood before me,
painting a grand picture of the future,
and I actually bought into it.
It almost felt like
having them around was nice
and the job seemed respectable enough.
Then at least put in some effort.
She just started and she's already taking leave.
I said, Ying
how could you do this?
You just started this job.
You should at least try to make a good impression.
How can you just take leave like that?
You're sick or not feeling well?
She tells me a friend has something going on.
I ask, what friend?
A friend
who's not even close.
Same.
Zhang Ran is no different.
Getting married on a whim
then poof, she's gone.
And then she just got divorced out of nowhere.
I haven't even processed it yet,
and she remarried.
And I'm always the last one
to be informed.
The two daughters we have...
But,
I think Zhang Ran
is better
than Lu Xinying.
She's more mature.
Aiying,
you have to do me a favor.
Please talk to Zhang Ran for me.
Get her
to sort things out
with Lu Xinying.
They are easier to communicate with.
I just can't figure out
what Lu Xinying
is thinking right now.
Fine.
I'm feeling really anxious.
Let me tell you.
Look at this.
See?
Look at all this hair falling out.
Fine.
Just stop worrying about it.
I haven't been sleeping at all.
But you not sleeping won't help.
Alright,
I'll have Zhang Ran talk to her.
Let's see what she's really thinking.
You know you mom sent me here.
I figured.
Have some coffee.
I don't usually drink coffee.
I can't sleep if I drink it.
Oh, you don't drink coffee.
I... I don't know.
It's fine.
Wrong place.
Our relationship
isn't very close.
It's really beautiful here.
Sitting for a while is quite nice.
Xinying...
I...
I actually feel quite guilty towards you.
After being in Canada for so long,
I haven't really looked after you much.
And I'm not trying to make excuses
for myself.
I actually
couldn't really help much at the time.
You're overthinking it, Ran.
I have
no idea why,
but I just woke up
in Canada.
I don't like it there either.
My mom just thinks
staying in Canada
is a success in itself.
That way, she herself would be successful.
I just wanted to make her happy,
so I did many things
that I never liked doing,
that I never wanted to do.
Then I thought
I should live for myself this life.
Ran, are you doing okay over there?
Back then,
why did you want to go to Canada?
I...
I guess because of my dream.
I majored in English, right?
Back then,
I was doing pretty well.
I became a host.
I felt like
all the doors
were open to me.
I just thought
what if I could go abroad?
I just gave it a try.
You know sometimes
the choices people make...
When you have to choose a path,
you get this feeling.
You feel like
this path was laid just for you.
And you just went for it
without a second thought.
But, after all the twists
and turns,
you realize
that sometimes what you lose
might be far more
than what you gain.
Right.
Well,
I wound up
back here anyway.
Actually, when I was little,
my mother had high hopes for me.
Making me learn this and that.
But after I grew up,
I didn't meet their expectations.
I failed.
I embarrassed her.
This is my mother's value system.
This is just how my mother is.
She thinks that's the only version of me
that qualifies as success.
It's been like this since I was a child.
We are completely at odds with each other.
Are you low-key talking about me?
Is there a possibility that
her original intention
was actually for your own good?
Of course, there's a generation gap.
People from their era
do believe it's for your benefit.
But from my own reflection,
I think in this life
you should do the things you want to do
with all your might.
Give it one last push.
If it doesn't work out, forget it.
Ran, how's your push going?
I'm being a clown right now.
Didn't you watch my livestream?
I did.
I don't think you're a clown.
I believe
hard work pays off.
And you?
What exactly are you doing now?
I'm at a study abroad agency.
Sales?
That's right.
Sales is pretty tough.
But I chose it myself.
[It's been years]
[since we had]
[a meal together.]
Welcome home, Xinying.
Come on.
Let's eat.
Here.
Thanks, Dad.
Let me say a few words.
Ying, you're grown up now.
Actually, Mom has been thinking
about these words for many days.
I want to say...
I need to adjust myself as well.
I might have given you
too little encouragement before.
But everything I do
is definitely for your own good.
Mom loves you most.
You know that, right, baby?
Dad knows me well.
My bark is worse than my bite.
Mom can make mistakes too.
Sometimes I might
hurt your feelings.
I've thought it over carefully.
If I do something wrong in the future,
you need
to tell me,
okay?
And then,
I want to say I'm sorry.
I'll change from now on.
Mom.
Mom,
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have been so willful
and argued with you.
Then I shouldn't always make you angry.
I'll change in the future.
Come on, eat.
Mom, hurry up.
Eat this fish tofu.
Mom, you eat some too.
Xinying, you love eating this,
but you still need to
cut back on spicy food.
Alright.
Eat less spicy food.
Cool down your temper.
No, I'm not angry at all.
I'm actually quite happy now.
Is this not cooked properly?
Then put it back in.
Raw food cools me down.
Here's a cooked one for you.
Okay, okay.
Dad got a little emotional today,
so he can handle spicy food.
I'm just overjoyed.
Watching you two being so sentimental,
I don't even know what to say.
You're just here enjoying the show.
Hurry up and eat.
Shut your mouth.
Alright.
Here's what I'm thinking.
Now that our daughter's back...
More words?
It's good to be back.
Now you can stay home every day,
eat well and sleep well,
then call up your friends
and head out,
hit some restaurants,
watch a movie
and just relax.
Then if you have anything to say,
you can talk to me anytime.
We'll sort things out together
after you return to Canada
about how to move forward in the future.
For example,
if you tell me
you don't want to work at the bank,
I think that's fine too.
We don't necessarily have to
work at a bank.
just because we studied finance.
Let's say, if you want to continue your studies
and take the postgraduate exam,
we will support you.
Yes.
You won't feel any pressure.
Why don't you eat something first?
All you think about is eating.
Can you stop interrupting me?
And you've grown up now.
If you told me,
"Mom, I want to get married.
I want to be in a relationship."
What's going on here?
I'm an open-minded mom.
What are you up to today?
I'm a woman too.
I've been your age before.
I can share the lessons
I learned
with you.
Wait, what lessons?
The lessons I learned from you.
You have no self-awareness.
Listen, Xinying.
Listen to me.
No matter what,
you need to find someone locally
who's respectable
with status and position
and at least has a stable income.
Where are you even going with this?
You own a place over there.
So if you marry into that family,
you can stand tall.
Of course,
you can have your own thoughts too.
Just tell me.
I'll try to see things from your perspective,
okay?
What do you think?
My work visa
has run into some issues.
The visa issue is nothing.
Just a
man-made problem.
I'll handle it for you.
I'll smoothly
send you back.
Mom,
this isn't that simple.
When my work visa was about to expire,
my job was gone.
So, to transfer my immigration status,
I hired a lawyer,
and I got a personal guarantee,
which was somewhat illegal to begin with.
Then the guarantor ran into trouble
and I got put on
the list of untrustworthy individuals.
So,
I'm being deported immediately
and can never go back to Canada again.
So I can only stay
in the country.
But look,
I haven't been slacking off here.
I found a job
and I support myself.
It's been quite fulfilling.
We can still get together often,
right?
Did you know about this?
No.
Why didn't
you tell me before?
Something this big,
why didn't you let me know?
Dad, listen.
It's pointless.
It's already happened.
It's already the result now.
Acting, huh?
You old liar.
You little liar.
You two teamed up to deceive me,
Right?
What did I lie to you about?
Haven't you lied to me enough?
About her coming back,
I did keep it from you.
But the fact that she can't go back,
I just found out about it myself.
Let me tell you something.
You, in my eyes
have absolutely no credibility.
As for your job,
have you ever told me the truth?
Oh no.
So this isn't over?
Didn't I already
explain this to you before?
I told you
that's because I was afraid you'd worry.
That's why I didn't tell you.
Do you think I'm not upset
about losing my job?
I wanted to talk to someone about it too.
Who could I even talk to?
You go find someone to talk to.
I didn't.
I'm just...
I can only talk to my car.
I make money
to fill that hole.
But the wound inside me
remains unhealed.
You know who can fix it.
Is this ever going to end?
Are you going to bring this up forever?
Dad.
Why do you always mention this?
So angry now?
Can you two stop fighting?
Dad, Mom.
I never would have thought,
after all these years away,
our family would end up like this.
How could you two
end up fighting like this?
Just think about
what's most important
in our family?
I'll take responsibility
for myself.
[Back when I was in Canada,]
[I waited day and night]
longing to return home
to have a meal with my family.
I never imagined
the meal I dreamed of
would end
with my family falling apart.
Don't be too sad about it.
To be honest,
just leave it
for them to solve.
There's no use worrying about it.
When I was little,
no matter how strict my mom was,
making me practice the piano
day and night,
even making me do homework,
I always knew
she did it for my own good.
I never doubted that.
How could
our life
become so unhappy?
I suddenly felt
that even family,
the closest of bonds,
can change.
I used to look forward to growing up.
Thinking back, it was so foolish.
[Now that I've grown up, I have to rely on myself.]
[But,]
[when I can only rely on myself,]
[it really hurts.]
Have you lost weight?
Yang, I'm right here.
Yang, looks like you're starving.
You haven't been in much
so you're not used to it.
Enough talk.
Where's the food I told you to prepare?
Serve it up for Yang.
See?
We haven't forgotten you.
Eat this piece of tofu.
From now on, we'll all
live with a clear conscience.
Eat it.
We stick together.
I'm giving you a way out.
You should
stop doing designated driver.
From now on, work for me.
Be my personal driver.
You won't lose out.
I keep my word.
Seeing how pitiful you are,
we are giving you some money.
Spend it for now.
We'll leave it all here.
Just a token of our goodwill.
How can you just get up and leave?
Are you still working as my driver or not?
Pay the bill.
[So now,]
[your biggest life goal]
[is to throw a stone]
and make it skip seven times?
Don't you think that phrase
sounds philosophical
coming from you?
Let me ask you a question.
When your play is over,
what are you planning to do?
Truth or Dare.
Whoever wins gets to ask.
Come on.
Rock, paper, scissors.
I'm planning to buy a small asteroid.
Why don't you buy the moon?
I actually bought an asteroid,
named after me.
I thought you were dead.
I almost died.
[Kuang Dazhi's personal guarantee]
[has a problem.]
My work visa is invalid.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's all in the past.
It was just my bad luck.
It wasn't your bad luck.
Maybe my misfortune
was passed on to you.
I was just thinking I'd die.
What can be filled on that form
And who would be
the one to help me fill it out?
I'll help you collect your debt.
You still dare to help me?
Of course.