Pang Jingfu.
Doctor.
Fu.
How is he, doctor?
He's out of danger.
Fu.
I knew it.
You're lucky and powerful.
The King of Hell can't beat you.
Fu.
Do you know?
Sister Yan has been waiting for you.
Wake up.
Otherwise, she can't fall asleep.
Well.
Can you bear it?
Brother Fu.
Hey.
Be quiet.
Let Brother Fu have a good rest, okay?
Do you really think
he likes me?
Oh,
of course!
You don't know Brother Fu well.
He's got a tough exterior,
but his heart is soft as tofu.
He may seem all cold and distant,
but deep down,
he's clueless about relationships.
Sister Yan, trust me on this.
I can assure you,
he's never been like this before.
Sister Yan, I mean it.
I mean it.
Alright, alright.
Go eat your fish skin peanuts.
We're short one player for the game.
You scared me to death.
I couldn't get in touch with you.
Isn't Pang Jingfu
in a coma?
His men have been around me.
I had no chance.
As long as you're safe.
Hey.
Our men found Zhu Ruoyun
at the scene.
Did you rescue her?
No.
She ran away
with Fan Siqing.
Does Fan Siqing
have something on her?
You don't need to worry about that.
We'll find a way to rescue her.
By the way,
how's the investigation
at the jade factory going?
Excuse me,
would you like to choose a song?
Let me check this watch.
Where were we?
Oh, the workers.
The workers.
Nothing abnormal was found in the workers.
There are no signs of
violence, control, and torture.
And the families were not threatened.
But
the workers in the jade factory
were all provided by
provided by the Fengyue Villa.
The Fengyue Villa owned by Ouyang Qing?
That's right.
The Ouyang family
and
Pang Zhengsong, Pang Jingfu's father, are old friends.
Since Pang Jingfu
became the chief,
Ouyang Qing and him
have been working together closely.
Let me put it this way.
Fengyue Villa
provides workers for the factory.
And the workers will
go back regularly
to receive training.
Fengyue Villa.
It seems that Pang Jingfu
colluded with the Ouyang Family.
There should be more detailed documents
in the darkroom.
I have to go back.
Tian Yan,
I'm worried about you.
Why would Pang Jingfu
risk everything to save you?
Did he discover something?
Is he trying to
test you
and control you?
I think you're in more danger
than Zhu Ruoyun.
This time,
I'll take your place.
I think
he might
be interested in me.
Really?
Yes.
Well,
that's good.
It's going better than we expected.
But why do you look
not very happy?
You're overthinking.
I'm very happy.
While Pang Jingfu is not awake,
I should check the secret files of the Fengyue Villa.
What's going on?
Is the automatic security system activated?
At 9 o'clock in the morning,
there is a game.
Pang Jingfu.
Great.
You finally...
You finally woke up.
I found you love going to the study.
I wanted to
put the cookies in there
after baking them.
I saw you love eating them.
I failed last time.
I thought this time,
when you came back,
when you came back.
But
the door was locked.
I couldn't open it.
What game?
Mahjong club's VIPs.
They wanted to play,
but one was missing,
so they called me
to help them
form a game.
But it's only 9 o'clock in the morning.
When I went there before,
wasn't it still closed?
They are VIPs with membership cards.
Don't mention 9 o'clock in the morning,
even if they want to play at 4 o'clock in the morning,
we would still be open.
Speak up.
Hello, bro.
The number that just paged Sister Yan was a mobile phone number.
When checked, it was already deactivated.
Why don't you just ask Sister Yan for the person's name?
It's actually easy to find.
Brother Fu, are you listening?
I always feel there's something wrong with this matter.
Are we still investigating or not?
No.
Ah.
Fingerprint registered successfully.
Why?
You are at your own home.
You can sleep anywhere you want.
What do you think
of me?
You seem
to be decisive,
but you're
a pathetic and paranoid madman.
You're not pretending anymore.
Because Mr. Fu
doesn't like pretentious people.
Does it matter to you
what I like or not?
Why?
Why do you believe me?
Because you are born to be my soulmate.