=The Glamorous Night=
(A few days ago, FamilyMart)
I've done the math.
This round of layoffs,
someone in our core teams
will have to go.
At least one person per group.
I plan to cut the least attractive ones.
That doesn't seem to be fair.
They do the same work.
If you're ugly and incompetent,
you have to go.
So we can hire someone prettier.
You could do the same.
My group only has a few underperformers.
There are no unattractive ones.
Your group?
You're planning to fire Tao?
Out with it. Who is Tao to you?
You kept this well hidden.
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
She's my mentor's child.
I had no choice.
Do you know
her performance is dead last
in the group?
I know, I know.
Well, I just found out.
I had to ask her myself.
She's usually quite sensible.
Never asked me for anything.
Now that she knows
she's getting laid off,
she's been losing sleep
night after night.
Alright, I got it.
Thanks.
(Compassion)
(Shanshui Hall)
(Blessing in disguise)
(Rebound)
=Episode 6=
(Opportunity)
I know this wasn't right of me.
But we had no choice.
Say whatever you want.
I know you won't listen.
I had to go to Fan.
This is a multi-million project.
You... you...
You know...
I'm free tomorrow.
Tomorrow it is then?
Hello, Fengyun Express.
You're Qiaoqiao, right?
You have a COD package.
When will you be home today?
I'll deliver it.
Perhaps around
11 PM or so.
Eleven? That's too late.
What time do you leave tomorrow morning?
I leave around 7 AM.
You work such long hours.
How about this?
When you're almost home these days,
give me a call.
If I'm nearby, I'll drop it off. Okay?
You have my number?
Write it down.
Okay.
Alright, thanks.
(Fan)
Ms. Tan, anything else to add?
This is fine for now.
I bet right now you're scheming
how to convince me to hire you
while cursing me nonstop.
You're half right.
The first half.
Did your boss give you trouble?
That day,
I shouldn't have lost my temper.
You're my client, after all.
I shouldn't have spoken like that.
I'm sorry.
So he really gave you trouble.
My boss called me in
because I caused him trouble.
Okay, truthfully,
I've been a bit on edge lately,
because of other projects.
Sorry.
Okay.
Apology accepted.
Thank you.
I know
you lost the GST project
because of your wife's speech.
Did Xiao Yang tell you?
He also has a duty
to brief me about you.
Besides, I'm a major client of GST.
Seems I have no secrets left with you.
I watched your wife's speech.
I quite like her.
Actually, not just sales ladies
face these issues.
Take me,
even as a boss,
I'm often looked down on,
slandered and harassed.
But I don't dare to speak out
like your wife does.
I can only keep it bottled up.
These were all pre-arranged.
Pre-arranged?
That's right.
GST holds a sales promoter conference
every quarter.
Had you heard about it before?
So it was intentional?
My wife is in a difficult position
at the company now.
The one who got into trouble
was her direct superior.
The one being harassed
was her female subordinate.
For her, offense is the best defense.
Besides, GST urgently needs
crisis PR right now.
What better way to win
public sympathy
than showing vulnerability?
You taught her that?
I said negotiate through pressure,
not to attack wildly like this!
You felt cornered at the company,
so you decided to burn everything down.
That's not it.
Execution matters more.
But she succeeded,
and you lost the project.
This sounds unprofessional,
but in my heart,
she matters more than any project.
Didn't I tell you I was pitching
to your company?
We were about to close the deal,
but now, how do I face them?
Actually, even if she loses her job,
we can still live very well.
I can support her.
But I know
she loves her job,
just like I love mine,
and you love yours.
Ms. Tan.
No need to call me that.
Call me Stella from now on.
Stella.
Didn't Xiao Yang tell you?
I've already gotten
the GST project back.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Dad, everything's fine.
Don't worry.
Busy? Of course.
But being busy is good.
The real worry
is having nothing to do, right?
The leaders treat me well.
They've included me in several projects.
Gennadiy.
You even tried that wine.
You said it was tasty, remember?
Yeah.
That brand is our client.
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of myself.
The cost of living is high,
but your daughter earns enough.
Right?
Got it.
Don't worry.
Alright.
Take care of yourself too.
Gotta go now.
I have a meeting soon.
Hanging up now, bye.
Why are you back so soon?
About my...
It's set.
Meeting at their HQ tomorrow morning.
Thank you so much.
I knew you are the best
smooth talker with women.
If I had half your skills,
I'd be flying high by now!
Why are you drinking alone here?
Let's go out, my treat.
I found a great spot recently.
No, I'm tired.
Li Dongming, this isn't like you.
How can you say you're tired?
I mean it.
Another day.
Alright then, my treat another day.
The employee evaluation scores are out.
I saw you raised Tao's score.
Thank you.
(27 Tao Ling, Li Dongming Team
28 Qiao Hailun, Li Dongming Team)
I heard the comprehensive
evaluation scores are out.
But they say it's confidential.
Confidential for subordinates,
but not for superiors.
I heard the evaluation scores
will be the main basis for layoffs.
You believe that?
Why wouldn't I?
Since ancient times,
the sole criterion for layoffs
has been one and only one.
The boss's preferences.
So the question is,
what are the boss's preferences?
Who knows?
If I knew, I wouldn't be working here.
Qiao Hailun,
you've got the least to worry about.
Mr. Li likes you so much.
That's not true. Don't talk nonsense.
Is there a possibility
that the boss doesn't know
what to do either?
Think about it.
We all graduated
from a top-tier university.
We're working overtime
until 2 or 3 AM every day.
Every one of us
has both the qualifications
and the work ethic.
If they really have to lay off someone,
the boss can only
rely on personal preferences.
You're quite understanding.
Empathizing with the boss
is my greatest joy in life.
Tell me,
among the bosses in our company,
who's the lecher?
You prudes.
(Mr. Li)
(Come to my office.)
Mr. Li, evening.
Come in.
Get the door.
Take a seat.
Mr. Li,
is the company letting me go?
I knew it.
Don't worry.
The evaluation results
are confidential.
Scores won't be leaked.
Externally, we'll say
you resigned.
It won't affect your future job.
I'm afraid I'll never find another job.
Here. I'll write you
a recommendation letter.
That might help with your job hunt.
If any new company
wants a background check,
just give them my number.
I'll vouch for you.
Thank you, Mr. Li.
All the best.
Oh, right.
(Kangya Group Project Research)
What's this?
The preliminary research
on Kangya Group?
Did I ask for it?
I prepared it in advance.
I was afraid that when you ask,
I won't have enough time.
Why do you think
I can land this project?
You were there when negotiations
with Tan Min broke down.
I believe
as long as you want it,
you can definitely win this project.
And as long as Ms. Tan isn't blind,
she can see that you're the best.
We've secured the Kangya project.
Really?
We'll discuss the details next week.
That's fantastic!
It's just a shame
I won't be part of it
or work with you anymore.
Perhaps you can still
stay on the project.
Deciding
an employee's fate
based solely on one evaluation score
is too arbitrary and unscientific.
Especially for a consulting firm
that prides itself on talent strategy.
We shouldn't do it that way.
Are you saying
you won't lay me off?
Work hard from now on.
Thank you, Mr. Li!
(She hugged me so tightly.)
(I knew her gratitude was genuine.)
Thank you, Mr. Li.
(But she didn't know)
(that I was grateful to her too.)
(Everyone around me,
including Zhao Mei,)
(has so many ulterior motives.)
(But she's different.)
(She showed me how real she was.)
Liang.
- Congratulations.
- Mr. Ke.
- Your business keeps growing.
Thank you.
And you're looking more elegant.
For today's crab feast, I've specially
prepared three wines for everyone.
What our sommelier is pouring now
is Moonlight City Vintage Champagne.
This champagne
has been properly chilled
in an ice bucket.
The second wine
is Gennadiy 25-Year-Old.
I brought a limited edition today.
Finally, our Gold Label Gustav.
How does that saying go?
Cognac endures forever,
classics live on forever, right?
Live on.
The legend does live on.
Ms. Liang,
eating crab calls for yellow wine.
So, do you have yellow wine?
Yes! What don't I have?
I specifically brought two jars
of fifty-year-old Shaoxing yellow wine.
Ask me if you need some.
Fifty years.
Especially for you.
I need some.
Your requests can't stump Liang.
Ms. Liang.
Is it not quite appropriate
to drink yellow wine at your banquet?
Mr. Zhang, just hearing that tells me
you're not familiar with me.
All my friends know
I have only one principle for drinking,
to drink happily.
As for what wine we drink,
as long as it makes us happy,
it doesn't matter, right?
Right.
Yes! As long as today,
we don't drink Wilson's wine.
Any wine is fine, Ms. Liang.
Ke, you're teasing me again, aren't you?
Let me tell you,
I'll have several more drinks with you.
Drink until we're drunk!
Let's see who outdrinks whom.
Today, the chef has prepared for you
hairy crabs brought over
from Yangcheng Lake.
Alright! Then let's begin.
Let's raise our
Moonlight City Vintage Champagne.
Cheers!
Thank you, Mr. Li.
Mr. Zhang, leaving so early today?
I'm quite unhappy about that.
I really have something to do today.
Next time, if you invite me,
I promise to stay with you
till the very end.
Alright?
To the very end.
Okay.
Come on, pinky swear!
Don't lie to me!
Okay!
That limited edition wine you mentioned?
I need it for my girl.
You got it, huh?
Liang.
Of course, how could I not?
You can't do this.
Then I'm off.
Okay.
Alright, Mr. Zhang, take care.
Bye-bye.
Had some drinks?
Why are you lying face down?
My back hurts.
I can only type this way.
I'll probably have to sleep
on the couch.
What about you?
What do you mean?
Didn't Li Dongming
call you into his office
and then you both left together?
What did you do?
Nothing.
Are you serious?
Of course.
Then what's that hickey on your neck?
What hickey?
Where?
Just kidding.
Are you crazy?
Li Dongming called me to his office
to talk about the GST project.
Then he asked me to accompany him
to entertain clients. That's all.
If that's all, that's all.
Look how worked up you got.
There's really nothing
between me and him.
Don't make jokes like that anymore.
But among us,
he really does prefer taking you out.
Maybe I'm more obedient.
What?
Obedient?
That's quite far-fetched.
Do you know what others say about you?
They say the reason Li Dongming
likes taking you out so much
is because you have big boobs.
What?
That's utter nonsense!
So I'm just giving you a heads-up, okay?
I don't need that kind of heads-up.
Anyway, believe it or not,
there's really nothing going on
between us. He's my boss.
I can't decide who he takes
to business dinners.
Besides,
what people say about me
isn't something I can control.
So tell me the truth,
do you actually like him?
What do you mean, like him?
He's my boss, and I work for him.
He and I...
We have a professional relationship.
Wait,
why do you keep asking
such strange questions?
You.
Didn't I say it already?
I'm just warning you to be careful.
These kinds of situations
can be messy to handle.
I know that.
I'm not stupid.
Some people!
I really meant well
when I told you all that earlier.
If you don't like how I put it,
just ignore it.
Your birthday's coming up.
Happy birthday.
This is for you.
Thank you, Tao.
(LAN Communications)
I was just about to ask
when you're coming over.
I'm almost there.
Uh,
I saw...
Honey,
take a look at the third-round draft.
Okay.
We'll wait for you.
Alright, let's talk when I see you.
(Does Li Dongming)
provide enough physical value for you?
He... Well,
he usually enjoys working out.
And people from consulting firms
tend to have a lot of energy.
Plus, we've only been married
for two years,
so we're still newlyweds.
(Thinking about how happy she looked,)
(I feel conflicted.)
(What kind of best friend
truly counts as a good one?)
(Do I share)
(LAN Communications)
(everything I see,)
(or do I selectively hide things)
(to ensure she can stay happy longer?)
The comments need to keep going.
If the buzz drops suddenly again,
it'll seem fake.
Your turn in one minute.
Okay. Wait.
We have to keep it steady here
and don't let it drop.
Alright, thanks.
Over here.
By the way, what were you
going to tell me earlier?
Nothing.
I wanted a supplier's contact info.
But then I found it.
Okay.
Here's to everyone.
Congrats.
Cheers!
(Ms. Lan, Founder of LAN Communications)
Let me summarize first.
As of 9 AM today,
we've secured four trending topics.
The buzz score hit ten thousand.
That means nearly ten million people
have noticed our heroine, Zhao Mei.
(Watching Zhao Mei
clear another hurdle,)
(I was genuinely happy for her.)
(But this was expected.)
(She's always so capable.)
(Being best friends for ten years,)
(sometimes when I look at her)
(I feel like
she's another version of me,)
(the ideal me,)
(capable, decisive, and lucky.)
(I'm Liang Danning.)
(From an ordinary sales lady
to a top VIP salesperson,)
(for ten years, day by day,)
(I've been drinking and selling liquor,
drinking and selling liquor.)
(In middle age, with kids below,
an elderly mom above,)
(and a useless husband in between,)
(sometimes I think
life is just pointless.)
(How could someone as smart, kind,
and hardworking as me)
(have it so hard?)
(But still, I have to thank heaven)
(for getting me
into imported liquor sales.)
(At least, I can get drunk for free.)
Yes, I was just about to bring it over.
Someone's home, right?
Okay.
What? You want two more bottles?
That might not be possible.
This is Gennadiy Fifty-Year.
There are only six bottles domestically
and fifty bottles worldwide.
Okay.
Alright. See you soon.
You scared me to death!
These are the last two bottles
of 50-year Gennadiy in the country.
Alright, I'll get back to work.
Okay.
Drive carefully.
Will do.
Bye.
(Shanshui Hall)
Mr. Jin, I'm at your doorstep now.
But there's no one here.
Should I just leave the wine
on the ground for you?
What are you doing?
You must be Mrs. Jin?
Hello, I'm Liang from GST.
I'm here to deliver
some wine to Mr. Jin.
Should I give this wine directly to you?
Okay.
Be careful when you pick it up later.
Here's my business card.
If you have any questions,
you can call me.
On behalf of the company,
we thank Mr. Jin for his patronage.
I think you're using the company's name
to represent yourself, aren't you?
I've seen enough vixens like you.
I'm hanging a peach wood sword here
to ward off hussies like you.
Mrs. Jin, you've misunderstood.
I'm not a vixen
or a hussy.
I'm here to deliver wine.
If there's nothing else,
I'll be leaving.
Mr. Jin, the wine is delivered.
Your wife received it.
Talk about rotten luck!
Misfortune really came knocking.
Sirius! No biting!
Sirius!
Come here, Sirius!
Get back!
Sirius!
Don't let your dog just bite people!
He's protecting his owner.
I can't hold him back.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
Thank you, Mr. Shen.
Do you know me?
I'm Liang Danning,
a salesperson from GST.
This is my card.
Here you go.
You're bleeding.
Yeah.
Who you calling?
911.
I'll just leave my car here.
If the security asks,
could you please explain for me?
You're quite tough.
No need for 911.
I was just about to head out.
I'll give you a ride.
Alright then. Thank you.
Is it still bleeding?
No.
I feel like I've seen you before.
Really?
Last year's Distributor Conference?
No.
Then maybe the night Cocoon opened?
I was there that night.
Sorry, handsome. My apologies.
That's right! That was the night.
Right outside Cocoon.
You even called me "Handsome".
Well, I wasn't wrong, was I?
You are handsome, after all.
I'm flattered.
Excuse me, I need to take this call.
(Dong Yue)
Yes.
Okay, okay. No problem.
I'll be your guarantor for this.
By the way,
come by the house on Saturday.
(The boss actually gets
to go to Mr. Shen's house?)
Okay.
Bye.
Danning.
What are you doing here?
What happened?
Got bitten by a dog out of nowhere?
Don't ask. A run of bad luck.
Let me see the wound.
Don't look.
Does it hurt?
No.
Just got a few stitches.
It's disgusting. I hate it myself.
But I had a great encounter.
You know who gave me a ride?
Who was it?
Shen Mo.
Liang Danning.
Sir.
Are you okay?
Nothing serious. Just a few stitches.
I just need seven days of rabies shots.
You can't drink alcohol
during the rabies shots.
Oh, no!
But it's okay. I can still sell liquor
without drinking.
Don't worry, boss.
That's not what I meant.
Just rest well for now.
We'll take you home.
No need.
I appreciate the gesture, both of you.
But,
for now, I don't want
my mom or my daughter to know
about the dog bite.
Another time.
I'll treat you both to barbecue
at my place another day.
Alright. Head home early then.
Okay.
Danning, this is for you.
Thanks, boss.
Got it?
Yes.
I'm off.
Look at that.
Honestly.
Avoid spicy and irritating foods.
Got it.
Good night.
Leaving now, boss. Bye.
Bye.
Danning has it tough.
Yeah.
But Liang Danning won't cause trouble
with the company over this.
Don't worry.
Even if she complains, I'd understand.
But honestly,
Danning may
seem careless,
but she's actually very rational.
Rational?
She's just got no other choice.
Her burdens are heavy.
I heard she is
separated from her husband.
He gambles and owes a lot of money.
Anyway,
even if she doesn't complain,
what happened today was so unfair.
Who cares if they're clients?
They can't bully people like that!
Too bad Liang Danning
isn't in the Promotions Department.
Otherwise, I'd demand justice for her.
I hear you.
Do you?
Here,
how about I introduce Danning
to two new clients?
Deal.
I'll thank you for Danning.
No problem.
Let's go.
Mom.
Takeout today?
Where's Grandma?
She went to the shop.
So you're home alone?
Weiwei, dinner's ready.
You're back so early.
What are you doing here?
Came to see Weiwei.
Haven't seen you in days.
Let's eat.
Keep your head back.
Weiwei, come here.
Let's stop watching for now.
Dinner time soon.
Come on, wash your hands.
Okay.
Here you go.
What's wrong?
Mom.
How could you
leave Weiwei to Yao Xiaohui?
Good thing I came back.
He didn't do anything to her.
Besides, the shop was busy.
I know that, but...
Fine. Never mind.
If you're busy,
don't bother coming back.
I'm staying tonight.
Okay, okay. I'll go now.
Go ahead. Bye.
Weiwei.
You've lost weight again.
Here.
Eat more meat.
Nourish yourself.
Stay healthy to get good grades.
Eat more vegetables too.
Honey.
I'll do it myself.
Mom, what happened to your arm?
It's nothing.
Mom's fine.
Let me see.
Just a scratch, it's fine.
Does it hurt?
It doesn't hurt. Eat well, sweetie.
Mom's not in pain.
I told you this job isn't suitable.
It's dangerous for a woman
to drink so much every day.
What does danger
have to do with drinking?
Some are dangerous without drinking.
They go bankrupt.
Weiwei.
Have you had any exams lately?
Just took one, all A's.
Really?
Awesome!
See that?
My daughter. That's my girl!
Weiwei, actually,
sometimes you shouldn't
always get perfect scores.
It makes others dislike you.
Getting a lower score
helps make friends, okay?
Got it.
How can you say that to our child?
Mr. Danan, hello.
I'm at home right now.
Hold on a second.
Um, I...
Just a moment.
Don't worry, Mr. Danan.
No problem.
I heard your teacher
mentioned in the group chat
about an English speech performance.
Did you participate?
Oh, I know.
I did.
It's about how to make zongzi.
It was really fun!
Explain how to make zongzi in English?
Yeah.
Your school sure is interesting.
Of course!
Study hard. Mom suffered
because of poor language skills.
I would've been promoted.
Mom, eat more.
Okay, you too.
Going to play cards again?
No, Mr. Danan needs to ask me something.
Honey, since you're back,
I'll head out now.
Okay, I'll take out the trash.
Weiwei, Mom will be back soon.
Weiwei, Dad's leaving now.
Study hard at school.
I'll come see you again later.
Okay, bye.
See you.
Bye, Dad.
Bye.
Goodbye.
See how nice it is
having dinner together?
Let's give our child a complete family.
Honey, let's not get divorced.
Honey.
You...
Just let me explain.
What's there to explain?
Yao Xiaohui.
I've tried saving your face
in front of our child.
And you?
You graduated from a nice university.
But look at you now,
lying and gambling.
Now you're stealing too.
And you ask why I want a divorce?
Have you no shame?
Honey, trust me one more time.
Stop talking.
Leave.
Take this out.
Mom's back!
♪All the stars are out tonight♪
♪Too much of shame♪
♪To waste it crying♪
♪Leave all behind you♪
♪Gotta go on to better things♪
♪You know how far you've gone♪
♪In the fire you rise again♪
♪You made it through the worst♪
♪The best is yet to come♪
♪Isn't it magical♪
♪Listen, look,
how beautiful the night is♪
♪With countless lights on,
is someone heartbroken again♪
♪The sound of a heart
shattering on the ground is so crisp♪
♪Turn on a light.
A lonely heart needs comfort♪
♪Sweat, toil, dawn, dusk♪
♪Devaluing self-respect
just for some hot food♪
♪But I don't want to♪
♪Sell dignity at a price,
trampling on past vows♪
♪Until 3 AM♪
♪Locking dreams away in a drawer♪
♪Just to earn some meager profit♪
♪No matter how hard I try,
it only brings sobs♪
♪Renewing yearly, gone with no return,
teetering, utterly bland♪
♪Leave all behind you♪
♪Gotta go on to better things♪
♪You know how far you've gone♪
♪In the fire you rise again♪
♪You made it through the worst♪
♪The best is yet to come♪
♪Isn't it magical♪
♪All the stars are out tonight♪
♪And I see them sparkling♪
♪Nobody knows♪
♪What tomorrow brings♪
♪You made it through the worst♪
♪The best is yet to come♪
♪Isn't it magical♪
♪Feeling uneasy,
yet no one's chasing me♪
♪Retreating step by step,
everything turning to ash♪
♪I'm silent, I'm roaring♪
♪This helplessness
keeps pushing me towards the cliff♪
♪Trembling legs
carry away a shattered soul♪
♪Who wants to be just a passerby♪
♪Isn't it magical♪