[Sunshine of My Life]
[Episode 22]
People can leave,
but I always have a backup.
In the same way, you're also a company leader. What did you do?
Not only did you violate the company's rules,
your subordinates to leave their posts.
I am so disappointed in you.
Mingxuan, it's not like that.
All these years, I have been by your side.
Yet you keep ignoring my hard work and sacrifice.
Since Mo Fei appeared,
in your eyes and heart, there is only her.
No matter what I do, I am not as good as her.
What do I need to do for you to see me?
Like the first time we came here,
when you cared about me.
I never ignored you.
You should be very aware of how much I trust and rely on you.
But my trust is not a weapon for you to do what you want with at the company.
Don't you think what you did has ruined our friendship?
I know what I did was wrong.
But I don't want to leave the company.
I don't want to leave you.
I never thought of firing you.
You were the one who wanted to leave.
Think carefully
about whether you'll stay or leave.
You make the choice.
Oh, right.
Didn't you approve of Liu Pei's leave?
I recommend that you also rest during this time.
Calm down and think it through.
This... is all I'm going to say.
Xueling.
Where did you go? I was so worried.
Mom, I didn't go anywhere. I just went out to relax.
When you went out to relax, Tang Mingxuan came to the house looking for you.
He came here?
Yes. I wanted to scold him, but your father stopped me.
You two stop chirping out there.
Xueling, come here.
Let me ask you something.
Dad, what is it?
Sit.
Xueling,
I hope you'll...
be honest with me.
You and that...
that Tang Mingxuan,
what exactly...
what exactly is going on?
Dad, don't ask.
I want to solve my own problems.
If you can solve them yourself—
If she doesn't let you ask, then don't ask.
Fine, fine. I won't ask this. I'll change the topic, is that all right?
In the past you were doing well, studying oil painting,
but for Mingxuan you insisted on switching to fashion design.
After you graduated, you cried, saying you wanted to work at Mingyuan.
I didn't agree at that time but what did you say?
"I am willing to work at Mingyuan, no matter what difficulties I encounter in the future,
I definitely won't retreat."
Xia Xueling, is that what you said?
That is the promise you gave me then, right?
Yes. That is what I said.
Then, how are you going to explain now?
You encountered a little difficulty, and you took your suitcase with you as you left.
Are you trying to be a deserter?
Is that it? Tell me.
Our child has just come back, can't you say less?
Is she still a child now? She is an adult.
Right now, she is Mingyuan's Design Director.
It is not important as to whether or not she is my daughter.
She encountered a little difficulty and just ran.
Xia Xueling, do you think what you are doing is proper?
Xueling must have suffered injustice at Mingyuan,
so she did that.
She must have encountered a problem she could not solve, so she left.
It is all that Tang Mingxuan's fault. Our Xueling worked by his side for so many years—
Stop, stop!
Right now I am talking about work with Xueling.
If you want to listen, that's fine. If you want to say those things, then go upstairs.
- It is all one matter!
- How is it one matter?!
- It is one matter!
- How is it one matter?
If it weren't for Tang Mingxuan, would our Xueling go work at Mingyuan?!
Right now, I am asking her what her relationship with Tang Mingxuan is, yet she's not willing to answer.
You keep saying, "Don't ask! Don't ask," yet now
- you are mentioning Tang Mingxuan—
- Enough! Stop arguing!
It is all my fault, okay?!
I caused you two to worry!
Back then it was my decision to go work at Mingyuan.
Now also, I won't give up easily.
Xueling, if you are not happy working at Mingyuan,
then let's not go. I'll make the decision for you.
What decision are you making? You. Go upstairs right now.
- Why should I go upstairs?
-This—
- Enough, Mom.
Dad is not wrong. I am wrong in this matter.
As an adult, I should not have left without a word.
I will go to work tomorrow.
Look at you!
Look to what extent you have forced her!
What did I force her to do?!
All day it is "Mingyuan, Mingyuan, work, work!"
You also saw what attitude Tang Mingxuan had when he came!
Tang Mingxuan can not care about my daughter.
But Xueling is your daughter!
You also don't care about her?!
In this family, do you want to be in charge?!
- Do you want to be in charge?
- So unreasonable.
Then be in charge. Be in charge.
Solve everything!
It'll be great if only you can solve everything.
Hello, Director Xia.
Director Xia!
Director Xia, where have you been? Everyone's been asking.
That's right.
I was at the hospital for acute appendicitis and had a small surgery.
Then, why didn't you tell us? We should've visited.
It was very sudden. Besides, I don't like people seeing me weak at the hospital.
By the way, Liu Pei is still on leave.
You all split her work.
Okay.
Brother Xuan, do you know...
Do you know that Director Xia got acute appendicitis?
She didn't come a few days ago because she had surgery.
She is now at the design office. That's what all the colleagues said.
I know.
You know?
Director Xia must have told you beforehand.
I was thinking no wonder you're—
Why do you have so much to say?
I just wanted to tell you.
I'll leave now.
Appendicitis surgery.
Can't believe she would come up with that.
Are you Miss Mo?
You are?
People call me Uncle Zhong. You can call me that as well.
- How can I help you?
- I'm here to see Xiaoyu.
I've been looking for him the whole day and haven't seen him. Do you know where he is?
I don't know. But you can ask Li Qi. They're often together.
I've asked everyone I can think of.
I've also looked everywhere.
However, I haven't found him.
But I really have no idea where he is. I'm really sorry.
I'll be leaving now.
Just one minute, Miss Mo. It's like this.
It's Fang Xiaoyu's birthday today.
His relationship with his dad hasn't been very good.
Today his dad would like to celebrate his birthday with him,
so they can be together and repair their relationship.
Well, if I run into him,
I'll let him know. However, I have to go to school now.
All right. Thank you.
Bye-bye, Uncle Zhong.
[INSTITUT FRANCAIS DE LA MODE]
This is none of my business.
I shouldn't say anything.
Hello.
For today's class,
I've invited a special guest,
Fang Xiaoyu.
Everyone knows about the company he works at, Cayman.
You all probably
also know of Mr. Fang.
Among the outstanding designers
at Cayman Group,
he's the youngest.
He excels in Chinoiserie designs and produced a series of research work in that aspect.
It's a series of remarkable works.
All right then, I won't keep talking.
At this time, I present Mr. Fang Xiaoyu.
Mo Fei, you're not a true friend. How can you not tell me Fang Xiaoyu is the lecturer?
I didn't know either.
André mentioned Chinoiserie just now.
Therefore, today I will explain what Chinoiserie is.
What are the elements in the true Chinoiserie?
In recent years, Chinoiserie has become popular on the world stage.
[WIN AN IPAD PRO]
Are you waiting for me?
That was a very good lecture.
Then please give me good reviews. Thanks.
- There is actually something I want to tell you.
- Go ahead.
I met an Uncle Zhong on my way to school.
Is that what you want to tell me?
Let's change the topic.
Fang.
Your speech was very enlightening.
I would like to treat you and the students to dinner tonight.
Dinner tonight...
I will get going first.
Mo Fei, please wait a little.
There wasn't enough time. The students want to discuss with you more.
They asked me to let them have more time with you.
Please, don't disappoint them.
Mo Fei, join us.
- I go as well?
- Yes, we'll all go together.
Wow.
- Please sit.
- All right, I'll sit here then.
So, my dear Fang,
please choose what you want to eat.
Since you are the one treating us, you should choose.
Listen, I want to thank you for the lecture today.
So, it is my pleasure to treat you. You choose whatever you want to eat.
Why are you so generous today?
Guess.
My dear Fang, today is your birthday.
To you, a great designer,
I wish you unlimited creativity.
Even though you are not in China, but as your friend, I don't want you to feel lonely here.
All of us are here to celebrate your birthday.
Mr. Fang, you can make a wish and then blow out the candles.
- ♪ Happy Birthday to You! Happy Birthday to You! ♪
- Thank you, thank you.
♪ Happy Birthday to You... ♪
What's happened? Was I mistaken?
Isn't today his birthday?
You don't even know how awkward it was for André when you left.
I don't really appreciate what André did in there.
I don't want to celebrate my birthday at all.
So... is that why you don't answer Uncle Zhong's calls?
Yes.
When my mom was still here, she, me and my sister,
the three of us always celebrated our birthdays together. After my mom passed,
it has just been me and my sister.
For the past three years, even my younger sister has not been with me.
So I don't like to celebrate my birthday now.
I'm sorry. I had no idea.
Today, I was indeed in the wrong.
Tomorrow, I will apologize to André.
I heard that restaurant makes delicious fish.
Yes. You should've eaten it before leaving.
How about... I gift you a fish?
You know how to cook?
[Uncle Zhong]
Your craftsmanship is not bad.
Compared to your drawings, I'm a bit lacking.
I wish you a long, healthy life
as well as an abundance of "fish" (wealth).
Thank you. I will definitely keep it safe.
Well... I'll head inside first. Happy birthday.
Mo Fei.
I know you are with Tang Mingxuan now.
I just hope you won't be a stranger to me from now on,
avoiding me.
Since you brought it up, I want to have a good chat with you.
Yes, I'm with Mingxuan.
There are things you don't care about,
but he does.
And I care about him.
Because I care about him,
I have been avoiding you.
I just don't want to cause any unnecessary trouble
that'll upset him.
Am I... that bad compared to him?
You are an outstanding designer
as well as a good friend.
You are just as good as him in every way.
However, the feelings cannot be compared to each other.
I admit that I admire your talent very much.
But that's all.
To me, you are just a great friend.
That's all.
It's late now. Rest early.
Happy birthday.
- Goodnight.
Uncle Zhong.
Xiaoyu, didn't I call you a few days ago to tell you to come home for dinner?
The chairman is still waiting for you at home.
When did I agree to do that? Why don't I remember agreeing to it?
This child. How many times have I come up these stairs today?
I came to pick you up early this morning
but you were nowhere to be found.
You also didn't answer my calls.
My old bones...
have suffered because of you.
Uncle Zhong, how are you old?
You are still strong.
When will you grow up?
Hurry and come home with me!
I haven't eaten all day. I also said I won't go back.
Xiaoyu, listen to me.
The chairman went home very early today just to have dinner with you.
If you don't go,
he'll be very upset.
Uncle Zhong, I respect you as an elder.
Can you not ask me to do things I can't accept, every time you see me?
Xiaoyu, don't be like this.
Your father has been hurting
all these years, too.
Hurting?
Why can't I see that?
He seems to be living quite happily with his wife.
Quite carefree.
Xiaoyu, when are you
ever going to let it go?
How many times have I already told you?
Your mother's death had nothing to do with the chairman.
Otherwise, your uncles
would never have let him off so easy. Isn't that right?
No one was more devastated than the chairman
when it happened.
You didn't see how heartbroken he was, holding your mom in his arms.
Is there any meaning to say all that now?
Mom is gone and he has someone new.
Tell him to live his life well. Why come and see me?
Go back and tell him
I won't go back to have dinner with him.
Tell him to take care.
After my mom passed, I haven't liked celebrating my birthday.
- But I've told you all...
- Uncle Zhong, I've told you, please return.
I've said all that I should.
- You are back.
- Yes. You're still up?
You still couldn't persuade him to come back?
He still isn't willing to come back.
I tried to persuade him tonight.
He still cannot unravel the knot in his heart.
I'm thinking... Should you find time,
sit down, and have a good chat with him?
Chat about what?
What is there to chat about?
He still thinks that I have wronged his mother.
I've been with you for so many years.
I completely understand how you are feeling.
But as they say,
"The one who tied the bell is the only one to untangle it."
The knot in his heart
needs you to unravel it.
What do you say?
We'll see.
Knowing he's fine puts me at ease.
I'll worry about the rest in the future.
- I'm going to bed.
- All right. Goodnight, Chairman.
Cousin, something happened!
- Look.
- In such a panic, what is it?
[Fang Xiaoyu: Finally, on my birthday, I can forget all the unhappiness and receive a handwoven gift from the person I like.]
Isn't a birthday gift very normal?
It's Fang Xiaoyu. Aren't you angry?
Your girlfriend is about to be stolen.
If you love someone, you must trust them.
Such a child!
Yang Guang.
Didn't I tell you to come pick me up at 7:00 a.m.? Where are you?
I'm sorry, Brother Xuan. I... came late.
It's just that before I left, I had diarrhea.
So...
Brother Xuan, how about y-you scold me?
You can also hit me. You being like this...
makes me uncomfortable.
You were 17 minutes late and have spouted nonsense for 3 minutes.
Yang Guang,
what do you think about us taking your salary and using it to pay
for a company retreat?
I was wrong.
[Mo Fei: Are you busy today? I miss you.]
♫ I want to write the sweetest song for you ♫
♫ Dissipate your fatigue ♫
♫ and quietly listen to you now ♫
♫ I want to give you the world's gentlest understanding ♫
♫ When you feel tired ♫
♫ I'll be your softest pillow ♫
♫ I want… ♫
♫ You to personally tell me you love me too ♫
♫ That I'm the inexhaustible candlelight ♫
♫ to your endless night ♫
The night lights of Paris today are very beautiful.
If you were with me, that would be great.
Originally, I wanted to send a message to you.
But I was afraid you'd be busy. It's fine though!
I can say it to you here.
Today...
Mo Fei.
- I want to talk to you about what happened tonight.
- What happened?
Don't play dumb. About Fang Xiaoyu, of course.
Do you know why he left?
- How would I know?
- Don't give me that.
Tell me. I'm dying of curiosity.
André was being nice, trying to celebrate his birthday
so why did he leave?
I-It's like this.
Fang Xiaoyu came to our school to give a lecture today.
It happened to be his birthday.
Then André invited the students
to dinner to celebrate his birthday together.
Guess what happened in the end.
When he found out, he left.
Then it was especially awkward.
After dinner, on my way home, I ran into him on the stairs.
Thinking of how he saved us that day
and I didn't do much to repay him,
I just casually used Chinese knots to braid a fish
for him as a birthday gift.
I don't know if you would mind
that I gave Fang Xiaoyu a birthday gift.
If you mind, I won't do it again.
[Good girl.]
What is this?
You're so busy yet you still have time to be jealous.
So petty!
Petty, petty!
Lu Zhu! Slow down.
Who told you to follow me?
At least tell me why you are mad.
Could it be that you've gained weight?
Are you looking for death?
You're cursing me.
- Did I?
- You're cursing me to gain weight.
T-That was because I didn't know and took a wild guess.
Why don't you just tell me?
Did you have drinks with Kitty? And even sang with her.
Yes. Didn't I invite you, but you didn't want to go?
You... Are you dumb?
What exactly is wrong?
I don't like her. Stop playing with her from now on.
- That's it?
- Yes.
Of course, I can do that. No problem. I'll promise you that.
Your silent treatment these days has been killing me.
- Really?
- Yes.
All right, I promise you. So don't be angry, okay?
I guess you're sensible.
You are not mad anymore, are you? What do you want to eat later? I'll take you.
You! What now?
You are famous!
Look! You're famous!
Lower your voice. It's just a magazine.
"A prodigy of homegrown male models."
Wow, such high praise.
T-This reporter is exaggerating. So embarrassing.
You really participated in the right event.
Girls nowadays all like contrast cuteness.
(T/N: contradictory characteristics)
What cuteness?
Just like you.
On the runway, you're an ascetic male god.
Off the runway, you're a naturally cute puppy.
What is that? I have no idea what you are saying.
Such a straight male.
I'll just look at the magazine. I find the boy on the cover more appealing.
Really? Other people say he is cuter in person though.
Oh, right! Didn't someone recommend you to be an actor?
With this popularity, you definitely can.
A-An actor?
I don't really want to be that.
Why not?
I don't want to act in kissing scenes.
What?
My first kiss is still out there.
Student Mo Fan, are you that much a young girl?
Seriously though, an actor
has to pretend to be different people
and say all kinds of things. As for me...
I just want to be me.
So I'll stick to modeling.
Then... have you decided on the contract with Cayman?
I haven't decided.
But... I may need to talk to my sister when she's free.
Do you want the magazine or not, Miss? You've been looking at it for half a day now.
Yes, yes, yes! These and these. I want all of them. Do you have more in there?
- I'll buy however many you have.
- Seriously?
- Seriously, I want them all.
- Okay, okay.
Why are you buying so many?
For a keepsake, and to gift to everyone.
You made your family proud.
Made my family proud?
Yes.
Mingxuan, you said Miya
agreed to talk to the board about a collaboration.
The way I hear it,
there are issues.
It's like this. Miya indeed cannot make the decision herself.
They also need time to discuss it.
But SLC is interested indeed.
However, with my years of experience,
my gut tells me it's a trap.
They lead you on at first,
right? As well as let some news out.
They keep us hooked and just drag it on like this.
Why are they dragging this out when they want to collaborate?
I think there can only be one reason.
They want to raise the price.
At this moment,
there are better offers than ours.
We have to give them time to make a decision.
They are indeed doing just that.
This is considered... raising the price maliciously.
Mingxuan, it's not that SLC isn't good.
It's just a bit chaotic. How about we switch to another company?
Uncle Xia,
a project that was passed by the board of directors
is not a game of house. We can't just call it off.
As for SLC,
I won't take no for an answer.
Mingxuan, you are young but you didn't go into business just yesterday.
With regards to these things, you cannot act based on emotions.
What do you mean you won't take no for an answer?
If you continue like this, I think you won't be left with anything but failure.
Don't be so impatient, Old Xia.
Mingxuan is not someone
who acts irrationally.
SLC is an old French brand.
The word is out, so why wouldn't there be competition?
It means that our judgment is right.
We are on the right track.
I didn't say it's a bad idea
to acquire SLC.
Before the budget was approved, right?
But in this situation,
what will we do if they raise the price? If they do, I have no extra money to give.
That's right.
Uncle Xia, don't get worked up.
Let me think of a way.
I'll figure it out. All right?
All right. I'm sorry I was a bit worked up.
All right. Let's end the meeting, then.
- Hello, Director Xia.
- Hello.
Dad, what are you doing here?
I just got out of a meeting, so I came to see you while I was here.
- You designed this?
- Yes.
You designed all of these?
Of course.
Not bad.
- You guys were confirming the SLC acquisition, right?
- Yes.
How was it?
You designed this as well?
I asked you a question.
What do you think is going to come of this kind of meeting?
It's all a joke.
So you don't plan on increasing the budget?
Well, I think...
you just do your job.
Don't worry about the rest. Your dad is here.
I just want to know about the company's situation.
If you really want to know,
then you need to keep your composure right now.
Don't let your heart melt
just because someone said something. Right?
Listen to you. I didn't do anything.
I'm just afraid you're in a difficult position.
You're just afraid Tang Mingxuan is in a difficult position, right?
You scared me to death!
You and your little thoughts.
- Don't touch it.
- I know how to do it.
You are messing it up.
I'm actually not making things difficult for that brat on purpose.
The company is everyone's, not just the Tang family's.
Our Xia family has a part in it, too.
When I see problems, I must mention them.
I must make a stand
and stand by my principles. Right?
You're not listening.
Fine, I won't say anymore. By the way,
when you get off work, don't go home. Your Uncle Tang invited us to dinner.
Uncle Tang?
It wasn't Auntie Lu who wants to see me?
All right. Whatever. I'll see you tonight.
I'll walk you out.
What is it, Old Tang? Are you not feeling well again?
Just some small ailments one is bound to have.
But if you think I can't beat you while I'm on medication, you are wrong.
Feel free to concede any time.
What are you talking about? Let me take another look.
You're not in good condition today.
I can still beat you.
There.
Are you sure?
No regrets.
You are as competitive as you were when you were young.
I have a young attitude.
Because of that,
my body is better than yours.
I'm not the one who's on medication every day.
It's okay to be on medication. We are at that age.
It's better than being muddle-headed. Being muddle-headed is not good.
That's not fair, Old Tang.
Why chitchat when we're playing chess?
This doesn't count.
You just said "no regrets."
Let's stop playing. It uses a lot of brain energy.
One more round.
We've played our whole lives.
It's beautiful out there. Let's go for a walk.
Let me take another look.
Forget it. Come this way.
♫ I say you're an April day ♫
♫ The sound of your laughter lights everything up ♫
♫ Even the spirit of a light breeze ♫
♫ In the midst of the brightness and beauty of spring,
shift as one would in a dance ♫
♫ You're the mist on a dry April day ♫
♫ The gentle breeze blown during dusk ♫
♫ The unintentional sparkle of the planetesimal ♫
♫ The fine rain that's sprinkled in front of the flower ♫
♫ The gentlest moment is when you lower your head ♫
♫ Like a shy water lotus that bows to a cool breeze ♫
♫ Time is like water, wordless ♫
♫ If you're well, it's a lovely day ♫
♫ The gentlest moment is when you lower your head ♫
♫ You're like the ivory field after snowflakes ♫
♫ You're the round moon every night ♫
♫ You're the naïve ♫
♫ white lotus that floats on the water ripples of your dream ♫
♫ You're the flower blossoms of tree after tree ♫
♫ The swallow twittering within the beams ♫
♫ You are love, hope, and warmth ♫
♫ You're an April day ♫
♫ The gentlest moment is when you lower your head ♫
♫ The bittersweet parting words of "take care" ♫
♫ Time is like water, wordless ♫
♫ If you're well, it's a lovely day ♫