[A Love Story: Sunshine of My Live]
[Episode 1]
The prince met a fox.
The fox said to the prince,
"Good morning!"
But when the prince looked back, he didn't see anything.
The fox said "I am here!"
"I am under the apple tree!"
How do you feel?
Did you see anything?
I dreamed of a girl just now.
She was telling me a story.
Do you know her?
I don't.
I want to know what the dream I just had
represents.
It can only represent a situation that can bring you
the most ease so far.
Are you still having fitful sleep and insomnia lately?
It's still the same.
You still have to keep taking Lexapro. I'll prescribe more to you. (Lexapro a selective serotonin reuptake inhibitor (SSRI) used to treat anxiety in adults and major depressive disorder)
Thank you.
[Service Center & Gift Packing Area]
[The Little Prince]
Boss, where are we going now?
Boss, your ass.
Yang Guang, how many times have I already told you?
Call me Brother Xuan.
B-B-Brother Xuan.
Head to the company.
It's so late yet you're still going to go to the company?
Yang Guang, I noticed you've been full of nonsense lately.
Hello, President Tang.
In such a big, bustling city, is there a place that truly belongs to you?
In the era of meeting and parting hastily,
is there someone you want to work hard for?
If there is, that's your fortune.
If there isn't...
Then there isn't.
Let me tell you guys.
Even if your father is extremely wealthy,
it's impossible for your life to be perfect.
Only through your own unyielding hard work
can you live the life you want
and live a life that is colorful.
Look at me. Recently, besides studying Su Embroidery intensively. (T/N: Suzhou Silk Hand Embroidery Art)
I am also preparing my works for the French Trade School of Couture.
Once I get through this difficult phase,
I'll go found out what swimming in the Seine-et-Marne River is like.
Then I will make a bonfire by the river
and make some barbecue or something similar.
Speaking of it, I'm a bit hungry. All right, that's it for today.
Next, I shall play some music for you.
[1 New notification]
[Shen Jiaxi - Are you free for a call?]
[Voice Call]
[Shen Jiaxi]
Hello, Mo Fei?
I was able to get two tickets to Mingyuan's press conference for their new product launch.
Go with me tomorrow.
- At what time?
- Two in the afternoon.
But I have an appointment with a client tomorrow afternoon.
Ah, Mo Fei, just go with me.
It just so happens that my cousin's wedding dress hasn't been chosen yet.
Go with me, all right?
I say that you don't treat me as your best friend at all.
You treat me as a boyfriend.
All right, boyfriend, go with me. Okay?
Fine! Bye-bye!
[Mingyuan Group's Product Launch Press conference]
[Tomorrow]
[Mingyuan Fashion's Prroduc Launch Press Conference]
[Mingyuan Fashion's Product Launch Press Conference]
So handsome.
Today, I'm very grateful to all the peers of this industry,
guests, as well as our media friends who have come here.
Thank you all for coming here to watch our product launch press conference.
Let me give a simple introduction.
Mingyuan Group was founded by my father, Mr. Tang Qiren.
I remember that when I was young,
my family manufactured the simplest clothing.
In the blink of an eye, thirty years have passed.
Mingyuan Group's structure
has gone through a huge change now.
Within these past thirty years,
through the hard work of generations of people at Mingyuan,
our designs, development,
production, and sales
have already reached our domestic industry's
highest standards.
Of course, great numbers are important.
But what our Mingyuan wants to do
is Chinoiserie with true ethnic origin,
so we can truly service our consumers. To have our designs
become a cultural phenomenon. To have our designs
carry Chinese culture forward.
So that in the end, it will be on a world stage!
Thank you, guys. Thank you.
Hello, President Tang!
President Wu.
Today's press conference was very successful. Watching it made me very excited.
I believe our collaboration will be a success, too.
Thank you. Please take good care of me.
It's a must. Collaboration is about a double win.
Xueling, come.
- Hello.
- Miss Xia.
Wow, your designs are very beautiful.
Thank you.
The main theme of our design this time is the red-crowned crane.
It represents an unswerving and loyal love.
Many people aspire to have that, right?
Oh... that's a great creative idea.
I believe that a lot of girls will like it.
This new product will definitely sell.
Let's meet and discuss things at my office next week.
Okay, no problem.
Their designs are really nice.
But I feel like there isn't anything special.
But the red-crowned cane on this embroidery
uses two different techniques: Su embroidery and drawnwork.
I indeed never thought of that.
Everywhere you go, you're learning. My gosh.
But I don't really like Xia Xueling's designs.
I think her designs are all too superficial.
Besides, she used a topic related to love just for publicity gimmicks.
Think about it. If a bird can represent some kind of everlasting love,
then didn't Liang Shanbo and Zhu Zhu Yingtai die in vain? Am I right? (T/N:Chinese legend called the Butterfly Lovers in which a tragic love story happens)
Miss,
may I ask if there are any problems with our clothes?
My God, what do I do?
- Come, let's sit and talk.
- Sure, let's sit.
Teacher Xia, I apologize, I was just expressing some of my opinions. (T/N: Teacher, used as an address to someone senior to her in the industry)
I wasn't targeting you.
For example? Go ahead and tell me.
I'll say it then?
I think that if organza is used,
(T/N: Organza is a sheer fabric traditionally made from silk)
the whole attire would look even more magical.
So you are a designer?
No, I major in fashion design.
So, I'm technically not a designer yet.
I'm truly sorry for my offense just now.
Hello, Teacher Xia. Please come this way for an interview.
- Sure.
- This is my notebook.
Your notes are quite detailed.
Don't tell me you want to plagiarize, right?
You've misunderstood. I just major in fashion design.
I want to record some stuff only. That's all. I don't intend to plagiarize.
We've already registered a trademark for this red-crowned crane. It has a patent on it.
Did you know that plagiarism is the greatest insult to the original creator?
You have a trademark for this red-crowned crane logo, but have you trademarked the red-crowned crane itself?
Besides, I've already told you. I'm not plagiarizing. I'm just recording it.
Okay, I'll return it to you.
What's the use of giving it to me? You've already remembered it in your heart.
- Then, what do you want?
- Give it back to you.
Say, didn't you have a press conference to let others see your work?
Let's go. Let's go. Sorry, President Tang.
- Why apologize?
- Let's go. Let's go.
Why? I didn't do anything wrong!
Wait, Jiaxi! What are you doing?
- Hey, I dropped my notebook!
- Let's go.
What are you doing?
I'm exhausted. Slow down! Slow down! I can't run anymore.
I was almost scared to death just now.
We didn't even do anything wrong. Why were you so scared?
- You even made me drop my sketchbook!
- Sketchbook?
Yeah! I think that Tang guy picked it up.
Sorry, sorry! I really didn't notice.
This won't do. I have to go find that cold-faced guy and get my book back.
Do you really have to go now?
How about later? After his interview is over, I'll go with you.
But that book is really important.
It's fine. I'll buy you tea and then go with you later.
- No—
- Let's go. Let's go.
Isn't Mingxuan going to come down to eat?
The press conference just finished. He still has some documents to organize.
I'm guessing he'll be busy for some time.
Later, I'll have Nanny Wu reheat the food and bring it to him upstairs.
Let's not wait for him. We'll eat first.
- Xueling, help yourself.
- All right.
Hasn't the press conference ended already?
Besides, Xueling came today.
I was even happily looking forward to
our entire family finally having dinner together.
He's the president, after all.
He is busier than us and has a lot to take care of.
It's okay. We can eat together next time.
But I don't really like Xia Xueling's designs.
I think her designs are all too superficial.
I think that if organza is used
the whole attire would look even more magical.
[Design is missing something.]
[The design is very unique.]
Picture. Take a picture. (in French)
Picture.
Is there a charge for the entry? (in French)
[Fly to this Little Corner]
[I want to start a live stream]
(T/N: her name Fei sounds the same as the word for "fly")
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Hello, everyone! Welcome to
"Fly to this Little Corner."
I am your beloved Little Fei Fei.
Even though it's already very late today,
I can't help myself but vent a little.
Say, can all the accounts on the various websites be unified?
The username for each website is different.
Also, the password requirements are entirely different.
Besides, it is already very hard to remember one, to begin with.
To every website's boss,
can we consider some kind of collaboration?
This way, we can use one account for everything.
So even if you forget your password, it's fine.
Then you don't have to be like me, so pitiful.
I wrote down everything in that sketchbook.
But my book was taken away by someone else.
I can't even get it back.
I've decided.
Tomorrow, I'm going to Mingyuan
to get my book back.
Sorry, you don't have an appointment with President Tang so you can't go in.
B-But he knows me.
I asked President Tang's secretary and he said that he doesn't know you.
How is that possible? He took something very important to me.
Hello? Hello, this is the front desk.
Let me look for it.
Miss, you can't go in!
Security!
We remember your face so don't cause trouble, okay?
Leave.
Fine.
- Come in.
- Brother Xuan.
This is done. Where should I put it?
Put it there.
Oh, right.
[It's because you've wasted time on your rose so it seems that your rose has become so important.]
Is that little girl... still downstairs?
She is. She still won't leave even when the security asked her to.
I've never seen someone so relentless.
No... stubborn and unyielding miss.
Do I let her in?
Let me ask you something.
What is this Ximalaya?
[Ximalaya Account Number for "Fly (Fei) to this Little Corner]
(T/N: Podcast Platform in China)
It's an app.
What does it do?
Let me show you.
It's an internet radio station. What are you looking for?
[Fly (Fei) to this Little Corner]
This?
"Fly (Fei) to this Little Corner"?
[Fly to this Little Corner]
That's why I say I like smart people like Tim Berners-Lee.
(T/N: Known as inventor of the World Wide Web)
Who?
Lee who?
If you have nothing else to do, you can leave.
Brother Xuan, phone.
I'll leave now.
Ximalaya. Ximalaya. Ximalaya.
What a lousy company. Since you like books so much, why don't you just go buy yourself one?
I went to get my own stuff back yet they chased me out!
They even say that they're an enterprise that understands the spirit of traditions the most.
Do you really understand the spirit of traditions?
Do you understand the benevolence, justice, etiquette, wisdom, and trust that our ancestors spoke about?!
Do you understand our ancestors' saying of "not pocketing money that you picked up"?!
You don't understand anything! You're just a trash enterprise!
Oh my! I-I got new fans.
Hello to new fans, I'm Little Fei Fei.
There's...
[Be careful or you might receive a letter from a lawyer.]
A-A lawyer's letter?
Sis, what's wrong?
I just got another fan.
There are people who listen to your rants from that ancient platform?
What do you even know? This is called "a faithful friend is hard to come by."
Being your fan,
listening to you complain all day must be boring.
Don't talk about my fans! I now have the means to spoil my fans.
As for you, stop training!
If you continue to train, you can become a fitness trainer. Look at your small arms.
- I want to be a model.
- What?
Sis.
Cayman Agent Company is recruiting model trainees.
Mom definitely won't agree.
Everyone's way of living is not the same.
In any case, once I've passed auditions and become famous, she will have no choice but to agree to it.
Think about it. If I become a world-famous model,
I will pay your tuition for when you go study abroad in France.
Really?
No, these are two different things.
We can't do that.
Sis, can you not tell Mom for now?
Just let me try once. All right?
Didn't you say I was blessed by the heavens to fit in any clothes I wear?
I did say that, but I can't let you do that!
I'm begging you, Sis.
Think about it! I will become a world-famous model
and you will become a master fashion designer.
I will wear the clothes you design for a runway show.
Won't our mom be overwhelmed with beauty as she watches from below the stage?
No, our mom will beat you
to death backstage.
I don't care! I have already registered for it anyway.
Being a model?
That's pretty good.
♫ At five past ten, you suddenly appear ♫
♫ The sunlight instantly becomes hot ♫
[08:04 AM]
♫ Like a little deer, a bump my head and blush for days ♫
♫ At five past ten, you suddenly appear ♫
♫ The stars instantly open their eyes ♫
♫ The leaves and cicada start to secretly fall in love ♫
♫ But suddenly you've gone far away ♫
♫ You turned around without a "goodbye" ♫
♫ My world changed since that moment ♫
♫ Tell me how to miss you less ♫
♫ Oh, yearning, oh, yearning, it surrounds me ♫
Good morning, Brother Xuan.
♫ Oh, every day, oh, every day, I miss you a bit more ♫
♫ I want you to suddenly appear again ♫
Brother Xuan, you seem to be in a good mood today.
You must have slept well.
That "Fly to this Little Corner" is not bad.
Brother Xuan, then how about giving me a raise?
♫  Let's do it again ♫
- President Tang! President Tang! President Tang!
- You can't go there.
President Tang! My notebook! My notebook!
Notebook! Notebook! President Tang! President Tang! My notebook!
President Tang! President Tang!
Book!
What does it have to do with you?
I am not even inside the building!
[Cayman (Shanghai) Group]
Hey, Li Qi? Help me buy a cup of coffee.
What?
I am not at the company.
Director Fang, do you still remember me?
- Bai...
- Bai Xiaoman!
Yes. I'm the one who hired you. I remember.
I heard you're back here at Cayman. I'm super happy!
Really? How have you been doing lately?
I've been pretty well.
I've been in quite a few business shows these past two years.
That's pretty good.
- Director Fang—
- Director Fang! Xiaoyu, you're really back?
- Sister Linda said you would be back today and I didn't believe it.
- Really?
- Are you going upstairs? Let's go upstairs together.
- Let's go. Let's go.
I will go upstairs first.
I still think that that space is too empty.
[Cayman (Shanghai) Group]
- So, when there's no one there for referral, take the shots closer. All right?
- All right. No problem.
Also, there's this problem.
- Director Fang, this way, please.
- For here, don't line them up so close together.
Sister Linda, Director Fang is here.
- You may go.
- All right.
Long time no see! All of you can go back to work.
You, oh, you. Your demeanor is just as great as before.
Sister Linda, I'm supposed to be in my prime.
Tell me. Inviting me, a great designer in his prime
to such a trivial competition, are you purposely messing with me?
Here we go again. How am I messing with you?
Don't you know that these people could be wearing your clothes in a runway show in the future?
How could you not come?
My clothes?
Are any of my clothes out there lately?
You're talking about that?
Look. You went to travel the world for three years.
I heard that the headquarters in France
will expand in China this year.
If you still don't come back, I'm afraid there's no place for you anymore.
I knew you were still concerned about me.
Therefore, don't leave after the competition is over.
You are giving me an ideological lecture again?
- Director Fang! Sister Linda! Have some water.
- Good that you know.
Director Fang.
I will have coffee.
Thank you.
Let's sit then.
First of all, congratulations to everyone who has passed Cayman's
preliminary round for the model training.
Next, we will have a re-examination round.
First, we will showcase men's casual wear.
Please.
Quick. Hurry. We only have two minutes to change.
- Who are you? Why are you here?
This is the men's changing room!
I'm in the wrong place.
You have a good figure.
What a pervert!
President Tang!
President Tang! President Tang! President Tang!
President Tang! Notebook! Notebook!
- President Tang! President Tang! President Tang!
- Sorry, Miss. You can't enter.
President Tang! President Tang! Over here! Over here!
I'm sorry. You really can't come in.
- Here. Let's pretend this is wine.
- Director Fang.
Here. Here. Here.
You don't even know. When you were not here,
- we really missed you. Right?
- Really?
Brother Xiaoyu!
- Lu Zhu?
- Are you surprised? Did you expect me? Did you miss me?
Brother Xiaoyu, thank you for the necklace.
I wear it every day.
Don't do this. These are my bros.
- What are you doing here?
- Let's go.
You're quite good at acting, right?
What? I was helping you get rid of those superficial flowers.
Aren't you going to thank me?
When you were young and fought with your older brother,
I would cover for you. All right?
Why didn't you thank me then?
- You and my cousin...
- Stop!
I don't want to talk about him.
Brother Xiaoyu, say,
can we really not go back to how we were in the past?
Not in this lifetime.
However, I'm a sensible person.
You will always be my good younger sister.
Then I will seek shelter with you.
- Seek shelter?
- That's right.
Brother Xuan, Director Xia will be here soon.
Did she have an umbrella?
Director Xia is in the car. She probably doesn't need an umbrella.
Are you referring to the person downstair?
How many days has she been waiting downstairs?
Probably a few days now. It's already been raining for a week.
Have her come to my office.
Have a cup of coffee first. Wait here for a moment.
Thank You.
He's even put a rose here.
[It's because you've wasted time on your rose so it seems that your rose has become so important.]
Oh, you even read "The Little Prince," but did you understand it?
I've confirmed with President Wu just now. He's already confirmed all the new clothes we're providing to Fashion Daily.
He said that it will be posted online as soon as possible.
Well done!
Who are you?
- Yang Guang!
- Hey!
I invited her here.
Give my sketchbook back to me!
Hey, I'm speaking to you.
You've come here to get someone to do something for you yet you don't even greet them.
Isn't that very impolite?
President Tang, can you give me back my sketchbook?
I can but your sketchbook isn't here.
Then where is it? I can go get it myself!
My home.
Y-Your home?
T-Then, what should I do?
Let's do this. Leave me your address and I'll send it to you.
Here.
Y-You have to remember to send it to me soon. This sketchbook is really important to me.
Depends on my schedule.
And...?
Thank you.
Wait.
Mingxuan, do you want to see if your office is missing anything or not?
Say, the people at your company are really quite strange.
This office does have a lot of things missing,
such as... humaneness.
- What did you say?
- Humaneness.
Xueling, she's a little girl. She doesn't know any better.
Don't bother with her.
Move aside.
[Mo Fei's Address and Phone Number]
Director Fang.
- Are you waiting for me?
- Yes.
I... I have something I want to ask you for help with.
Go on.
Isn't Cayman's charity banquet happening in two days?
My qualifications are relatively low so I wasn't invited.
You can go talk to Linda about this matter. She can take a lot of people in.
But Sister Linda isn't taking anyone so she certainly won't take me.
Then, what are you trying to say? Have me take you in?
Is that okay?
You should ask others. I'm not sure if I'm going or not.
You're so important at Cayman. How could you possibly not go?
All right. Okay. No problem.
Okay. Thank you, Director Fang. Thank you!
Thank you! I'll take it that you agree to it!
Thank you, Director Fang! Thank you! Bye-bye!
[Xiongying Design Studio]
Look. The whole neckline needs to be tightened. That will look more fashionable.
The rest is fine.
Mo Fei, you're here?
Why did you borrow so many embroidery books?
I accepted a tea ceremony attire job.
I want to embroider some auspicious cloud patterns
to go with its primary lotus design.
[Beijing Embroidery]
Like Chinoiserie?
I don't want to casually print the pattern from the books on there.
Then work here.
You can use all the equipment here.
Thank you, Teacher Pan Su.
However, it's been a bit busy here so I need you to help me do some alterations.
Okay. There's no rush for this tea ceremony attire anyway.
An evening gown.
No problem, right?
I'm thinking... if...
Teacher, take a look. Is this alteration okay?
The client commissioned this to use for a charity banquet.
If we do this.... would it be too conservative?
I don't think so because of the fabric chosen. If indistinctive yarn is chosen,
it will look better.
All right. I believe in your judgment.
Mo Fei! I guessed that you would be here at Teacher Pan's.
Shen Jiaxi? Aren't you supposed to be at school preparing your graduation piece?
Didn't I... come here now... to work on my graduation piece?
I say you two treat this place as your own work studio now.
Teacher Pan, you're the kindest. How about this?
Once Mo Fei and I graduate, we'll come here to help you.
You better be able to graduate this time.
[Painting Frame and Mount]
♫  The sun points to the direction  ♫
♫  Where you're at ♫
♫ Will instantly become sunny ♫
♫  That day, you said some words ♫
♫ Her smile ♫
♫ Is like the glow in the sky during sunset ♫
♫ Heavens, the person you spoke about is me ♫
♫ Light a starlight so you'd stay ♫
♫ I say you're an April day ♫
♫ The sound of your laughter lights everything up ♫
♫ Even the spirit of a light breeze ♫
♫ In the midst of the brightness and beauty of spring,
shift as one would in a dance ♫
♫ You're the mist on a dry April day ♫
♫ The gentle breeze blown during dusk ♫
♫ The unintentional sparkle of the planetesimal ♫
♫ The fine rain that's sprinkled in front of the flower ♫
♫ The gentlest moment is when you lower your head ♫
♫ Like a shy water lotus that bows to a cool breeze ♫
♫ Time is like water, wordless ♫
♫ If you're well, it's a lovely day ♫
♫ The gentlest moment is when you lower your head ♫
♫ You're like the ivory field after snowflakes ♫
♫ You're the round moon every night ♫
♫ You're the naïve ♫
♫ white lotus that floats on the water ripples of your dream ♫
♫ You're the flower blossoms of tree after tree ♫
♫ The swallow twittering within the beams ♫
♫ You are love, hope, and warmth ♫
♫ You're an April day ♫
♫ The gentlest moment is when you lower your head ♫
♫ The bittersweet parting words of "take care" ♫
♫ Time is like water, wordless ♫
♫ If you're well, it's a lovely day ♫