[Sunshine of My Life]
[Episode 04]
♫  I want to write the sweetest song for you  ♫
♫ Dissipate your fatigue and quietly listen to you now ♫
♫ I want to give you the world's gentlest understanding ♫
♫ When you feel tired, I'll be your softest pillow ♫
♫  I want...  ♫
♫ You to personally tell me you love me, too ♫
♫ That I'm the inexhaustible candlelight to your endless night ♫
♫ You're the one I love extremely ♫
♫  You're a sweet-and-sour piece of candy  ♫
♫  Please put away your worrisome face  ♫
♫ I really want to see your smile ♫
♫  Many people come and go  ♫
♫ I want to be your last visitor ♫
♫  So please don't be afraid anymore  ♫
♫ Follow me in taking a huge step forward ♫
Thank you for driving me home.
I'll have the legal department prepare the contract immediately.
- After that, take it to your master for changes.
- Okay.
Mo Fei.
Thank you for doing so much for me.
Actually, it's not all for you.
I just hope that the embroiderers' children can have an extra chicken leg at dinner.
I now understand what you meant about sincerity...
a bit more.
That's good then.
All right. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
What are you doing?
You aren't thinking that I want to take advantage of you, are you?
Then, why did you suddenly come over to hug me?
This... What are you doing?
No, that person just now almost crashed into you.
Say, do you have a persecutory delusional disorder?
Bye-bye.
Don't you think that the delivery man just now
had the intention to crash into you?
I don't think so.
Your little home looks quite cozy.
I-I'll get you some water.
This looks quite like you.
[Bachelor en Modélisme]
(Bachelor in Modeling)
When I was little, I used to come to this area often.
Is there a Jing'an Temple nearby?
Yes.
Although the building is a bit old, it's warm during the winter and cool in the summer. It's very comfortable.
Here. Have some water.
Thank you.
I see that you are preparing to apply to
the School of Union Chamber of Parisian Couture.
But you like the Chinese style so much
and the domestic market now is so good,
why do you want to go abroad?
Didn't you also come back from abroad?
Don't have such a limited scope for your question, all right?
I'm going there to study.
Studying does not distinguish between domestic and foreign countries. It is borderless.
That's right. Studying is always a good thing.
Say, we finally have a little consensus.
We've already reached a consensus on something
long ago.
Then, do you know why I wanted to help you acquire the embroidery workshop?
Because of your master.
That's just one of many reasons.
When I was in school,
I wrote an essay on Songtang's brand culture.
Back then, I did a lot of research.
Initially, Songtang's designs
were actually very forward-thinking. I really liked them.
However, in the last few years, the designs have been barely satisfactory.
I think that you must know where the problem lies,
so that's why you want to acquire the embroidery workshop to change the situation. Am I right?
I also think that creators in every field
are essentially the same.
Their original creations are based on their own national culture.
Just like when it comes to suits, we can never surpass Westerners.
However, when it comes to the cheongsam,
(T/N: Chinese style dress)
they are unable to create the same oriental charm as us.
So if Chinese clothing wants to establish itself in the world,
it must have its own Chinese culture.
That's how it will go far.
I think that Songtang can do that.
- I forgot what I was going to say.
- What?
By the way,
will you be going to Suzhou again anytime soon?
I don't think so. I'll be in Shanghai.
Have you completed your design to submit to the institution yet?
I still have a little bit of work to do, mainly because I have work to do at the studio.
You even have a studio?
I'm just a newbie designer.
How would I have a studio?
I just work part-time at Teacher Xiongying's studio.
Are you busy with Xiongying's solo showcase?
How did you know?
I'm in the industry after all.
Although I may not have the time to attend,
Xiongying will definitely send me an invite.
What?
Aren't you going to ask me what "newbie" mean?
I do have life experience after all.
Hello, Brother Xuan.
Yang Guang, let me ask you something.
What is this thing called "newbie"?
What? "Newbie"?
"Newbie."
I'll look it up and then let you know.
Okay.
All right.
Come in.
Brother Xuan.
Hey, Yang Guang.
When is Xiongying's solo showcase?
I think it's tomorrow.
All right, clear my schedule for it.
Didn't you say you wouldn't be going?
They already sent the invitation, if we don't go...
that'll be rude.
No, didn't you schedule a meeting for tomorrow?
Are you in charge
- or am I in charge?
- I...
Oh, right!
This is... newbie. I've looked it up for you.
I'm heading out now.
Go ahead.
Newbie...
- Hey. Long time no see.
- Long time no see.
Waiter, tequila. Thank you.
What are you busy with lately?
- I've been busy with fashion week.
- Fashion week, really?
Director Fang.
Do I really look like a waiter?
Long time no see. Even the way you greet people has become so unique now.
It's because I haven't seen you in so long, I almost couldn't recognize you!
This... does make you seem quite like a waiter.
- A headwaiter.
- What did you just say?
Director Fang, you haven't changed at all. You still have that sense of humor.
Tequila. Thanks.
Teacher Xiongying, everything looks great today.
How did you find this place?
All thanks to Xiaoyu.
The credit belongs to Xiaoyu.
Come. I'll take you to see Xiaoyu.
- Not bad, right?
- Yes.
- Xiaoyu.
- Yes!
Teacher Xiongying.
Let me introduce you to Keke.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Is she a designer, too?
- My... best friend.
All your best friends are so beautiful.
Thanks for the compliment.
[Baopu Art Museum]
Didn't you say you weren't planning on coming?
I happen to be free so I came to take a look.
If that's the case, go on inside. It's about to start.
I don't like crowded places.
Say, you're quite strange. Don't you go to a showcase to see the people?
It's work.
It seems you don't like your job that much.
It's just work, right?
There's nothing to like or dislike.
I'm different from you.
I am very passionate about my own job.
That's why you are awesome.
How have you been?
I-I've been just busy over nothing lately.
Give me a tour.
I want to ask you, how many people can this venue accommodate?
Don't you know?
Mo Fei! Mo Fei, hurry and come help. It's about to start.
Go ahead. I'll walk around myself.
- There are 15 minutes left. Hurry up, everyone.
- Okay.
Final check.
I already told you to be more careful!
Why did you ruin the outfit?
What's going on? What's the problem?
Sister Mo Fei, my scissors didn't touch her.
I didn't do it. I don't know how it ripped.
How did this happen?
Xiao Yang, help me bring the toolbox here.
- Okay.
- Get what toolbox?
From what I see, it's too late.
If I say we can fix it on time, then I will.
Put it here. Thank you.
Let's see how you'll fix this.
I saw everything that day.
You did it on purpose, right?
Do you feel really proud of yourself right now?
- What are you talking about?
- What do you think?
Charity banquet.
It's definitely you who coaxed Fang Xiaoyu to take you inside.
Oh my. Because of me, you've really put in a lot of effort.
- I'm not even going to bother with you.
- You started it.
Forget the other things,
I'm still not over you framing me to get me expelled from school.
Say, Mo Fei,
do you think I'm easy to bully just because my family isn't powerful or wealthy?
Bai Xiaoman, if you continue, I'll sew you and this outer layer together.
What happened?
I don't know how her clothes were ripped, but Sister Mo Fei is mending it for her.
There are five minutes left. Hurry up.
- All done.
- Not bad at all.
Thank you, Director Fang.
Bai Xiaoman, if you trip on stage,
then you're ruining your own career.
Since you're so smart, you should know what I'm talking about.
Come. Let me take a look.
- Such great handiwork.
- What's so great?
Director Fang, just now...
The embroidery is done quite well.
What's good about it?
Did you just arrive?
- I heard that this showcase of Teacher Xiongying's is done quite well.
- Yes.
Go take a look over there. It's about to start.
Okay.
Yang Guang.
My boss is asking you to go over there.
- Then, I'll head over there.
- Go ahead. I'll be here.
What a coincidence.
Didn't you tell me to come over here?
I didn't.
Then, just now, Yang Guang, he...
I asked you to come over here to explain things to me.
But I still have work in the back.
Bro, can we switch seats? I'm over there.
Thanks.
[Xiu'r - Xiongying]
What is it?
[Orange Car Service]
You can't park here. Hurry and leave.
There are so many cars parked here. Why don't you care about them?
I don't care about them. But your car can't park here.
Is it because their cars are more expensive, so you don't dare talk to them?
Do you think you can bully me seeing that I drive this?
Stop your nonsense, leave now.
All right.
You're just a dog looking down on people.
What did you say?
Who are you swearing at? Say it again.
Teacher Pan!
Xiaoyu?
- You can go ahead.
- Okay.
The crowd control today is not bad.
It's all thanks to you coming to stand in the crowd.
Aren't we friends? We should help each other.
I heard that you even helped us resolve some problems backstage.
I didn't do anything.
It was your good student, Mo Fei.
In a very short time,
she used Su embroidery to mend a ripped outfit backstage.
She's smart and has great skills.
She is Master Li's student,
so her Su embroidery is naturally good.
Master Li?
The one in Suzhou?
Yes.
That old grandma treats Mo Fei as her own granddaughter.
I heard that she even let Mo Fei handle the acquisition discussions
with Mingyuan's Tang Mingxuan.
Then she has a great bright future.
That girl, Mo Fei, is indeed motivated.
Among my students, she's considered the best.
In order to improve herself, she has also applied to the School of Union Chamber of Parisian Couture.
The school I attended before?
Teacher Pan, would you like to take inventory of the clothes? The models have already taken them off.
All right.
- Then I'll get back to work first.
- All right.
Xiaoman, are you going back by yourself? Is no one going to pick you up?
I... I'm waiting for a driver.
Xiaoman, that's awesome!
You haven't been a model for that long, yet you already have a driver?
Man Man, I'm here to pick you up.
Man Man?
Is this the driver you were talking about? You seem to have quite a good relationship with your driver.
He says your name so intimately.
There is probably a difference between the city and rural areas, right?
The "driver" that Xiaoman said is different from what we understand a driver to be.
All right, you hurry on back then.
Let's go, let's go! We still have a cocktail party to attend.
Let's go, let's go!
Who asked you to come?
I especially borrowed this car from a friend from our hometown to come and pick you up.
How many times have I told you?
Stop embarrassing me!
So fucking annoying!
Man Man!
[Baopu Art Museum]
We can eat soon. Just wait a moment, okay?
Are you done or not? I can't get rid of you, can I now?
I told you to scram, did you not understand that?
Listen to me. Your grandpa called you but you didn't pick up.
He asked me to come and see you.
What is it? Did I do something wrong again?
Tell me! I will change.
Change what? It's all because of you!
You've caused me to be ridiculed, bullied,
and laughed at by them!
Then tell me, what can I do for you?
The only thing you can do for me now
is leave! As far as possible! I don't want to see you!
Okay.
Then don't be angry anymore, all right? Calm down.
I find that you have no capabilites at all.
You only know how to tell me to calm down.
If you're capable, then go deal with Mo Fei,
or go deal with those evil girls.
Move!
Man Man, then call me if anything happens.
Remember to call me!
So delicious.
I love eating this.
Oh, my!
D-Didn't you say that you registered for that TV show...
what is it... "Chinese Style," the competition show for designers?
Not me.
It's the both of us.
I-I'm not participating!
Aren't you going to France? The reward for that is very generous.
But I don't have time.
When it comes to time... you can always squeeze some time out.
Think about it. I am busy with the design for the school in France,
and am also helping my master keep an eye on Mingyuan! Oh right! I need to call my master.
Why don't you take off your gloves?
I need them to eat.
By the way, how are things going with France?
Did you get a letter? How many designs have you sent?
I sent a lot.
Why do you seem dejected?
Are you worried about the designs you sent to Paris
so you are really nervous?
I think it is fine if you just create the designs as you usually do.
You will definitely get in.
Actually,
you don't have to work so hard.
You can change your way of thinking and take advantage of the current opportunity.
You have such a treacherous smile. There's more to it than meets the eye. Say it!
How am I treacherous? I'm just giving you a reminder.
President Tang... Mingyuan...
Aren't they opportunities you should grasp onto now?
Speak a human language.
I'm analyzing it for you!
- Look, your master wants you to handle matters with Mingyuan right now.
- Yeah.
- Then you spend a lot of time with President Tang.
Isn't that now the opportunity you have? You have to grasp onto it well.
Your master has already helped you to this point, yet why can't you understand? You silly girl.
Work hard to hold onto President Tang and become the wife of Mingyuan's boss!
Then, will I also—
What are you thinking about?!
What are you hitting me for?
I'm waking you up, that's what.
Why are you thinking of nonsense all the time?
[Master Li]
Hello, Mo Fei?
I have sent you the details of the contract I went over with President Tang to your WeChat,
did you get it?
I've looked at it.
Then, what do you think about it?
I think it's not bad.
Then, next, we will...
Next, we'll proceed with the contract.
Okay, okay! Then I'm hanging up now, Master!
Bye-bye!
[Master Li - End]
So great!
- Xueling.
- Mingxuan?
It's so late, are you still working overtime?
I was looking at the contract.
By the way, how is our "Chinese Style Fashion" going?
Right now, we have sponsorships and intermissions lined up.
They will send some A-listed celebrities to come and shoot advertisements for us.
The price is also much better than ordinary companies.
Then, how many of our company's contracted designers
are in the open auditions?
I've discussed it with the TV stations. Our designers will be exempt from the open auditions.
That will be beneficial for our brand promotion.
Why do I think it'll be a bit unfair to do that?
Do you not trust the people I hire or my judgment?
You take care of what you are in charge of.
- I'm leaving now.
- Oh, right!
- What is it?
How has Auntie been lately? I want to go see her.
My mother has been feeling very well lately.
Let's make arrangements another day, all right?
Go home soon.
♫  The sun points to the direction  ♫
♫  Where you're at ♫
♫ will instantly become sunny ♫
♫  That day, you said some words ♫
♫ Her smile ♫
♫ is like the glow in the sky during sunset ♫
♫ Heavens, the person you spoke about is me ♫
♫ Light a starlight so you'd stay ♫
[The Little Prince]
♫  My heart, just this one is for you  ♫
♫ Protect me, hold me in the palm of your hand ♫
The prince met a fox. The fox said to the prince,
"Good morning!"
The prince also very politely said to the fox,
♫ I'll treasure all the light in your eyes ♫
- Welcome back to the country.
Let's hang out together when we have time.
Hey.
♫ The sun rises ♫
Mo Fan!
♫ And the sun rises over the horizon ♫
[Livehouse - Shanghai]
♫ The sun rises ♫
Come on! Let's go!
♫ The sunshine on my skin ♫
Lu Zhu, long time no see.
Come, let's drink together.
I can't drink that much.
I'll go first, all right?
♫ And the sun rises over the horizon ♫
- Drink up.
- ♫ the sunshine on my skin ♫
I really can't drink that much.
- Drink up!
- Drink it!
Just drink the whole bottle.
- Wait.
-Just drink it and considered it as giving me face.
- Why did the music stop?
- All right? Drink it.
Drink, just drink.
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
- What's doing on?
First of all, thank you all for coming.
Also, my good friend Lu Zhu is here today.
Those who are around her must be her friends, right?
Then here's a toast to you all for coming to support the show.
Next, I want to sing a song for Lu Zhu.
[Livehouse - Shanghai]
♫ The sun rises over the horizon ♫
♫ the sunshine on my skin ♫
♫  And I feel enlightened  ♫
♫ Yeah, I got all the answers; I want to feel it on ♫
♫ I wanna do better. The sun rise over the horizon ♫
♫ No matter whatever happens ♫
♫ The next day will be a new day,
and I'm not afraid to find a new way ♫
♫ The sun rises as always ♫
♫ Get yourself together once again ♫
♫ Forget the pain of last night;
I know victory is waiting up ahead for me ♫
♫ The sun rises as always ♫
- Mo Fan!
- Yes?
- Where are you going?
I'm going home.
I'll take you.
You take me home? Isn't that strange?
I've always been a strange person.
Thank you for earlier.
Thank me for what?
You drank for me and even sang such a great song for me.
That's nothing.
Since you sing so well, why don't you find a chance to debut
and be a singer?
How is it that easy?
Right now, if I can sing at a bar
to make some money, I'm already really happy.
Are you in need of money?
I have a gold credit card with no limit.
Take it!
I indeed want to make money,
but I must do it with my own hard work.
One day I want to be just like you and depend on myself to live.
Show my cousin, aunt, and others that I can.
Is that why you want to get into Cayman?
Keep up with the hard work! I think you can do it.
Okay, but do you like singing more,
or do you like being a model more?
I actually like both...
but I don't think that money is most important.
Right now, I can do what I like
and support myself through that, so I'm happy when I work.
Are you drunk?
No.
Listening to your words just now,
I think I kind of... like... you...
All right! Hurry back home. It's so late.
Let's go together. Mo Fan, I'll take you home.
What do you mean by "together"? Go!
I'll take you home!
No need, I can go by myself.
- Bye-bye.
- Mo Fan, let me take you home.
Bye-bye!
She gave me a card?
Director Fang, what is this?
These are the scissors that Alexander used.
This is worth a lot more than that autograph you got.
You can have it.
No, no! I did nothing to deserve this.
I can't just accept it like this.
Just treat it as a first meeting gift to my junior sister.
Take it.
A few days ago, at the showcase, I heard Teacher Pan say that you are applying to the School of Union Chamber of Parisian Couture.
I graduated from there.
Really?
As the design director of Cayman,
I plan to write a recommendation letter for you.
That way you will be accepted without a problem.
Even though I really want to get into that school, I still want to do it through my own hard work.
Please don't misunderstand.
I'm willing to write you a recommendation letter because I recognize your talent.
The admission committee lacks my kind of insight.
The possibility of not being admitted is still there.
But if the committee does not approve of my designs,
it's probably because my design is not compatible with the school.
So, I also won't go to a school that is not compatible with me.
But the School of Union Chamber of Parisian Couture is a really good school.
If you can study there, it will help you a lot.
Then I'll accept this gift. As for the recommendation letter...
I still hope I can be accepted with my own hard work.
- Then I'll get going now, Director Fang.
- Okay.
Why don't you go in?
Are you that afraid of our company's security guards?
Who's afraid? I'm just afraid of going inside and disturbing their work.
Then, do you think that asking the boss to come down to see you during work hours
doesn't affect the workflow?
Aren't you just forcing me to admit it right now? Fine, I'll admit it!
I feel bad for the employees here after I made such a ruckus last time.
But when I called you, I couldn't get through. Then what do I do? I can only wait here for you.
I'll reluctantly accept that excuse.
Tell me. What do you need?
My master agrees! We can proceed with the contract.
Really?
All thanks to you.
It's nothing. Then just draft the contract first. After that, I'll go over the details with my master.
I'll draft the contract as soon as possible.
- Well, I've relayed the message. Bye-bye!
- Wait a second!
Do you think leaving like this...
is appropriate?
What's not appropriate about it?
First of all, this was accomplished through our joint efforts.
So, should we...
celebrate a little?
Celebrate?
♫ I say you're an April day ♫
♫ The sound of your laughter lights everything up ♫
♫ Even the spirit of a light breeze ♫
♫ In the midst of the brightness and beauty of spring,
shift as one would in a dance ♫
♫ You're the mist on a dry April day ♫
♫ The gentle breeze blown during dusk ♫
♫ The unintentional sparkle of the planetesimal ♫
♫ The fine rain that's sprinkled in front of the flower ♫
♫ The gentlest moment is when you lower your head ♫
♫ Like a shy water lotus that bows to a cool breeze ♫
♫ Time is like water, wordless ♫
♫ If you're well, it's a lovely day ♫
♫ The gentlest moment is when you lower your head ♫
♫ You're like the ivory field after snowflakes ♫
♫ You're the round moon every night ♫
♫ You're the naïve ♫
♫ white lotus that floats on the water ripples of your dream ♫
♫ You're the flower blossoms of tree after tree ♫
♫ The swallow twittering within the beams ♫
♫ You are love, hope, and warmth ♫
♫ You're an April day ♫
♫ The gentlest moment is when you lower your head ♫
♫ The bittersweet parting words of "take care" ♫
♫ Time is like water, wordless ♫
♫ If you're well, it's a lovely day ♫