[English subtitles are available]
Hello, old times
Hello, old times is a 30 episodes series, adapted from August Changan's novel of the same name.
Xinrui is damn annoying. How can he be seated in the middle?
Indeed. Why not take a look at herself?
How dare a minor role can like me?
Enough.
I am not a minor role. Not.
You are an audiance all your life. We are the lead.
Episode 18 The Farthest Distance
bright and early...blab, blab, blab...
Can we just take a good sleep?
You bastard. Get up right now.
Our daughter has been helping look after the shop for a long time.
Hurry up and done your meal soon. Then go to school.
Mom
What's wrong?
Want money?
I want a mobile phone.
I know it. No way.
Mom
Could I buy a repeater?
What is that for?
It's necessary for recording when reading the textbook.
Buy what the fuck repeater?
That's a waste of money.
You don't think I know nothing about the dumb English,
which doesn't need to speak,
but just read and write.
But
But what
You use the pen or your mouth to take the exam
Pen.
That's right
You bastard,
I will let you die there if you don't get up now.
Okay. Okay.
Hey, Yu.
Why are you so upset?
You don't like that movie?
Yes, I like it.
Then that must be Lin Yang.
He is still worrying about that thing happened during New Year.
I don't know when he will let it go.
In my opinion, you can't fully blame it on him.
He is just too care about you, which lead to the mess.
He is worrying about you.
But that's too much.
Ah. Let's leave him alone.
Again. You come so early to take the seat.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just thought you wouldn't come today.
I don't want to come either.
That's all because of this physics competition.
I must well prepared in the last minute rush.
Ahh...
My apologies the other day.
If I knew that was a movie,
we could date together.
Is this your book for the physics competition?
Can I have a look?
Yes.
Bravo.
All these are beyond our reach.
Nope.
You have done your routines.
And then you could still spare some time to do this.
Ahh
Here is an extraction.
I always found my pronunciation not very accurate.
It's a bit weird.
Is this one?
Your pronunciation is much more accurate than mine.
No. Mine sucks.
If you want to read this well,
you must listen to the tape as much as you can and then practice it accordingly.
I have lost my tape long long ago.
How I wished I worked hard at the early stage.
Actually, I haven't utilized the tape for a long time.
You could also listen to MP3.
Yes. But its storage capacity is too limited.
Actually, I always burn CDs.
Listen to CD directly.
Burn CD?
That's burn MP3 into CD.
it's convenient. And the storage capacity is okay.
It includes main content of high school, senior and junior.
It is a piece of cake.
How about this? I will give a CD to you.
to me?
Thanks for
saving seat for me all the time.
Thanks.
No problem.
Anything good happened?
Nothing.
Good shot.
What are you watching?
You know her?
We are in the same after-school class.
Really?
Why is Xin Rui running everyday?
That proves you watch her everyday.
She is gorgerous these days.
Nothing changed compared with what I saw last time.
You are wavering.
What are you talking about?
Anyway, not smarter than our Qianqian.
But I think
better than Zhouzhou
There is an elective course called aesthetics in college.
I suggest you could major it.
Lin Yang
Do you need me to save a seat for you tomorrow?
Appreciate it.
It's really hard to get up so early for me.
No worries. I go to bed very early.
Ah, that CD.
I will keep that in mind.
See you.
Bye-bye.
What happened?
Don't you see it. She was borrowing English CD from me.
Do you have some difficulties with Yu Zhouzhou?
Alter your target?
What is wrong?
Actually, I really want to
have a talk with Zhouzhou.
But each time it becomes super embarrassing.
I don't know why.
If you'd like to take my advice,
I think you just care about Yu Zhouhou too much.
The correct attitude is
take it easy.
Morning.
Ah
I brought the CD you mentioned last time.
CD
English CD?
Yes.
Thank you.
That's all right.
Here you are.
made by L.Y
L.Y Lin Yang
I carved it onto every CD.
All rights reserved.
Then this smile is must also belonged to you.
[English for High School MP3 MADE BY LY]
I just draw it casually.
Unfortunately, I don't have a CD player.
Oh. I bring one with me.
Here it is.
Thanks.
I could hear it. I could hear it.
How are you I'm fine
Thank you
This is junior high school, right?
Correct.
This is next one.
All senior high school English texts begin with G.
The following digits show the volume and lesson.
Let me help you.
This one.
Okay. Let's take it.
Indeed. It is this one.
Thanks, Lin Yang.
You can't be serious.
I've know no one like English more than you.
Lin Yang
Can I take a look on this?
You have so many CDs.
These are my recent selections.
Which one sounds good?
Let me have a look.
I think you've heard Jay Zhou's and Stefanie Sun's
Ah, have you ever heard the band of The Flowers?
A very fabulous band.
The vocal is just a few years older than us.
I will listen to their songs while I am doing my homework.
Which one is your favorite?
The last one,
called Foam.
Previously
I always think they are not decent and act inappropriately.
Later on, a friend recommends it to me.
Once I heard it, single cycle for a month.
This is the homework for today.
Please help to give out your homework.
Zhouzhou
Can I borrow that?
Yes.
Just in time. My ears hurt.
Ah, what songs are you listening to now?
No, I am listening to English textbook.
CD.
A friend gives it to me.
You've made such big progress recently.
I am supposing you will surpass me soon.
Impossible.
I will bring you the charging line.
You don't need it?
No, I don't.
The huge progress you have made
give me very big pressure.
Don't be ridiculous.
Fighting.
Thanks.
You are welcome.
Lin Yang, you haven't got a seat?
Come here to dinner with us.
I am afraid I am not so welcome by someone.
Who will be not glad?
Lin Yang,
what lessons do you want to teach us?
We will try to reflect ourselves soon.
I had better sit over there.
What is wrong with you?
Can we just turn to another page?
You've heard his deliberately surly talking.
Too hard to deal with. Hopeless.
Just eat.
Stop.
Xin Meixiang
This one works, right?
What are you doing?
Nothing. We need to talk.
What happened to you these days?
What are you talking about?
I think you've changed.
Do not read too much Stands Literature.
What have I changed?
Look at your hair.
How can it be this?
You skin is whiter.
Your temperament has changed, too.
Your marks has increased.
And you are running every day.
So
can I take it as a compliment?
Take it as a compliment.
Let me tell you.
No matter what you've done,
You are still that tasteless Xin Meixiang.
You don't think you change your name to Xinrui,
you could become fancy.
That's useless.
Boring.
You know yourself
you won't be Ling Xiangqian
or Yu Zhouzhou.
Then what you expect me to be?
The same as you.
Playing games when having classes?
Smoking at the corner all day long.
Robbing money from pupils?
Bullying girls?
If you don't like that, I can change.
Just do what you like.
That's nothing to do with me.
I see that recently you become close to Lin Yang.
But you know that yourself
You are not the same people.
We
We and they have nothing in common.
Is there any meaning that you force yourself?
None of your business.
Are you happy?
Yes.
You surely are.
You can study hard.
You can get higher marks and become smarter.
All that.
But is there anything wrong with previous Xinrui.
Do you know me?
Be anyone else,
except myself.
So you want to be You Zhouzhou.
You want to do what exactly what she does,
even grow fond of Lin Yang, right?
Shut up.
Okay. Please pay attention here, everyone.
You may encounter various issues here.
Then, I will explain to you.
Paraphrasing.
Sometimes, though there is some new words in the article,
I am late.
the author may
-explain the new words somehow -Just started.
That's all because of Jiang Chuan.
Requested me to play CS.
I've got very bad luck today.
I lost several sets.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's a little difficult today.
What's wrong?
You don't talk much today and look preoccupied.
Nothing.
Maybe because I didn't sleep well last night.
Well, just go back and have a good rest.
Ok, see you tomorrow.
Bye.
What happened?
Come here.
Never mind.
Can you still walk?
Yeah, I'm fine. You go back first.
The bus stop isn't far anyway.
I‘ve got to go.
Ah, let me hail a taxi to see you home.
My house is up ahead.
[Mei Xiang Grocery Store]
You live here.
Yeah, it's shabby.
It has long been said that the house will be demolished,
so we didn't decorate it much.
You know,
when I was a child,
what I envied most was the children whose families run snack bars.
I always think they can have endless snacks,
endless notebooks and pens.
It's too good to be true.
If my mom knew I was taking something,
she would slap me in the face.
You are so serious even when you‘re joking.
Thank you for taking me home.
Then, I have to go now.
Ok,
oh,
remember to apply cold water to your feet,
when you get home.
Otherwise it will be difficult to reduce the swelling.
I used to sprain my ankle like this when I was playing basketball.
Thanks.
Bye.
You bad girl!
Mom!
Why you come back so early?
Have you skipped the class？
Mom!
How dare you?
Mom, I'm not.
I came back by taxi, so...
You took a taxi back?
You know how to enjoy life now.
Mrs, Mrs!
The thing is that,
Xin Rui sprained her ankle,
and I called a taxi to take her back.
Who are you?
I'm her classmate, in the same cram school.
What's your name?
Lin Yang.
Which school are you in?
Also in Zhen Hua.
Zhen Hua... Lin Yang...
Oh! It was you who were praised by the teacher
at the last parent-teacher meeting.
Thanks for taking Xin Rui back.
Come on in and take a seat.
Mrs.
Mom, our home...
Lin Yang took a taxi to bring you back.
Let him in for a glass of water.
Come on, Lin Yang, come in.
Ok, ok.
Lin Yang, have some candies.
Thank you.
They're almost overdue.
Eat it. She's talking nonsense.
Ok.
Lin Yang.
If I recall correctly,
your parents are both government cadres, right?
They are just responsible for trivial matters at work.
That's pretty good.
Don't like me.
I just run this small store,
working my ass off every day.
This daughter, ah, is also not good enough.
Mrs, Xin Rui is good.
Good? She has brought so many troubles since she was  child.
There is nothing she can do for the home.
And now, she becomes more weird.
She goes to bed when coming back.
And always getting up in the middle of the night,
which makes it difficult for her father and me
to have a good rest.
Do you really go to bed at eight?
They always quarrel. So I can't study.
We quarrel?
So it's our fault?
Your cram school
cost me a lot of money.
How long do I have to work to earn these money.
Mrs, I think,
the most important thing for students is study.
When Xin Rui first came to Zhen Hua,
her study was not good in fact.
After only half a semester,
she has made great progress.
She must have made great efforts.
As parents, you should give her more understanding.
Really?
You didn't show your mother your report card?
I did,
but she just made a perfunctory reply,
and didn't take it seriously.
There are so many students in the school,
and it is normal for
the ranking to change from time to time.
Zhen Hua is the best high school in our province,
and it has the best students as well.
It's very difficult to
make a little progress.
Not to mention that Xin Rui is a transfer student.
In such a short period of time,
it is not easy to
make such a great leap.
And I think she still has room for improvement.
She?
Come on.
Ah, can't you keep your voice down?
This soup is so delicious.
You are so gluttonous and lazy.
Did you play cards with Mr. Wang again today?
I was going to come back early,
Mr. Wang insisted on taking me there.
I'm full.
I'm going to bed.
It's only seven thirty now.
Don't you wash the dishes?
I have to go to bed early,
and get up to read.
By the way,
If you want to quarrel,
keep your voice down.
I'm afraid I can't sleep well.
Eh, when does she dare to talk to you like that?
Leave her alone.
Zhouzhou, let's go.
Xin Rui.
You must have done well in the English exam this time.
I'm sure I can't compare with you.
I got to go now.
Eh,
we finally finished the exam,
don't you take a break?
You haven't come to the comics and animation club for a long time.
I am weak in basic knowledge,
so I have to read more books when you spend your club time.
I‘m leaving now.
So horrible.
You know that I've always been afraid of two kinds of people.
One is those who can lose weight after the New Year,
and the other is those who can still study after the exam.
Is there anything else that these two kinds of people can't do?
Affectation.
Who knows whether she goes back to study?
She has done well in the exam once, and she becomes complacent.
It seems like she has put a lot of pressure on you.
Don't you worry?
Zhouzhou,
I think you should be careful about Xin Rui.
Why?
Are you afraid she'll overtake me?
I don't care about it.
I can't tell you why,
but I think that,
you are too good to her,
and she is ambitious.
I vaguely feel a little dangerous.
Vaguely?
Did you feel it by sight, taste or touch?
It's my seventh sense.
[Lin Yang: Zhouzhou, how long are you going to have the cold war with me?]
[New Message To: Lin Yang It's you that always say something obscure.]
[Lin Yang: If there's anything I've done to upset you, I apologize.]
[Can we have a talk tomorrow?]
[New Message To: Lin Yang Ok. ]
Hey, let me tell you something.
The score gap between Zhouzhou and Ling Xiangqian is very small this time.
The math score of Ling Xiangqian is 145, which is five points higher than that of Yu Zhouzhou.
But Yu Zhouzhou's Chinese and English combined scores
are 12 points higher than Ling Xiangqian.
But their scores of history and geography are about the same.
Well, you are really worried about others.
You screwed up the exam yourself,
and you still have time to care about the other two.
You're wrong.
I can't take part in the Olympic Games.
Can't I, can't I watch the Olympic Games?
Besides, they compete so fiercely in every exam.
I get nervous every time, you know?
You really have the spirit of entertainment.
But Zhouzhou screwed up politics this time.
Ling Xiangqian's score is 93.
Yu Zhouzhou's score is 77.
Oh my God, Yu Zhouzhou is out of the game directly.
You have overlooked a contestant.
She has done very well in the exam this time.
Come on.
She is the unseeded player.
Hey, Xin Rui, have you calculated your score this time?
No, I haven't.
[Xin Rui No.1 Ling Xiangqian No.2 Yu Zhouzhou No.3]
The ranking of the mid-term exam.
I just printed it out.
Take a look at it.
Is there anything you want to say?
Xin Rui has been working very hard recently,
but I don't expect her to make so much progress.
I didn't do well in this exam. I have nothing to say.
I'm not the kind of teacher who only looks at rankings, right?
Xin Rui has made great progress this time.
All teachers are very happy.
But the reason why she got the first place in the exam,
mainly thanks to you two who are going backwards at the same time.
Did you two discuss to retrogress together in advance?
Ling Xiangqian, English is your strong point.
But it's 20 points less than the last time.
Yu Zhouzhou,
Your politics just get a score of 77.
I thought I had typed it wrong at first.
The teachers also came to ask me
whether you've had some psychological pressure.
I say, what kind of psychological pressure do you have?
Mr, I was just lazy and didn't review politics well.
I was probably too nervous.
I want to tell you
and remind you that,
now is the critical period in high school,
and never relax yourself.
Ok, you guys go back.
Come back.
Send these out.
Come on.
I don't believe that you don't care about the scores.
You've made so much progress this time.
Maybe you can get into the top ten in the class.
If that's the case,
I'd be grateful.
The exam results of this time have come out.
The No.1 is...
Xin Rui is the No.1.
Many students have got the wrong answer to this sentence pattern.
Next, I'm going to ask a student to talk about it.
Xin Rui.
Mrs.
Although you have won the first place in the exam, you should listen carefully.
I know, Mrs.
The treatment of the first place is different.
Even the teacher's attitude towards her has changed.
You've made a lot of progress this time,
especially in the English composition.
There are three full-mark compositions this time.
But I like your composition best.
Can you read it out?
Ok.
Very good, excellent.
Xin Rui's progress
confirms what I said before.
English is a subject that can be improved
as long as you are willing to work hard.
During this period of time, I think that every student here
has seen Xin Rui's efforts.
But I'm still very surprised.
Xin Rui's spoken language has also improved so much.
It can be seen that she has made
a lot of efforts behind her that we have not seen.
Okay, let's move on to sentence patterns.
What's the matter, Miss Ling?
Why are you lose your temper?
I'm not lose my temper.
I'm just in a bad mood.
You got second in the exam.
How do you know?
The school just finished the exam,
it must be because of the grade.
Bad mood must not be the first,
but you are not crying.
Who is crying?
That means no.
It's not so bad without crying.
Either second or third.
You know me pretty well.
Of course.
I also heard from the student union of your class
that Xin Rui is the first one this time.
Well, you know that,
and you pretend to analyze it.
But what I said makes sense.
But I don't like Xin Rui,
and I don't know what I think.
I think even if Yu Zhouzhou takes the first place,
I won't be so uncomfortable.
To Xin Rui, I can't say how it feels.
But I heard that she has improved a lot,
especially in English.
The English corner of the school radio station
also wants her to be a role model for progress.
Chu Tiankuo. Are you disgusting me on purpose?
I didn't arrange it.
The teacher in charge at the school said that
she could be a role model for other students.
But I think our Ling Xiangqian
will definitely not be afraid of her.
Where are you going?
Study.
Otherwise, I'm afraid I will lost to Xin Rui next time.
Yan Yi, if there is something you don't understand,
let me help you.
That's ok, Zhouzhou.
I 'll look for Xin Rui.
Is there a feeling that you are over party?
What over party?
The first one in the liberal arts class of Zhenhua Middle School.
My ancestor, when will you get it back?
I am in a hurry.
Piece of cake.
Zhouzhou.
Do you have your CD player?
What's the matter?
Jay-Chou!
How about it? Is it awesome? Is it awesome?
Hey! Show me!
Isn't it posted in a few days?
I bought the pre-sale in the first batch.
I just pretended to be sick
and took it back from the store.
Hey, stop and get the CD player quickly.
It is with Xin Rui.
Then you go and ask, how can I go?
Xin Rui, did you bring my CD player?
Give it to me.
Thank you.
Never mind.
No, isn't it a mouth?
I didn't see.
Zhouzhou, give you a headset.
Chen Yao, you will listen later.
-Why?
-Xin Rui.
-The disc is mine and the CD player is Zhouzhou's.
-I still don't know this question.
-You will listen later.
-Can you tell me more about it?
It's okay, you listen first,
I'll listen later.
Thanks!
Yu Zhouzhou.
You solve it according to my answer first,
and then I'll get some water.
Ok, fine.
So you know that day I looked for you all day
and made all the calls I could make.
I know,
and I thank you very much.
I'm not asking you to thank me.
I'm worried about you.
I almost went to the police station to report the crime.
Are you so worried?
Are you worried about my safety,
or are you worried about my being with Chen An?
You know it.
I don't know it.
The former.
Can you be frank?
All right, I worried all about it.
Lin Yang. I have my own friends
and my own circle.
Chen An and Ben ben are both kind people.
You can't blaspheme their kindness,
just I don't let them
blaspheme your kindness.
How can you always take it for granted?
And speak so arrogantly.
I'm worried about you. Am I wrong?
How do yo turn it into
blasphemy against the kindness of others?
Yes, you Yu Zhouzhou has been popular since you were a child.
Everyone is around you.
You don't need my worry at all.
How can you still be as unreasonable as when you were a child?
Yes, no matter how popular I am,
I can't match you, Mr Lin.
The girls who chasing you all ran to the cinema.
How can you say that?
That was all a misunderstanding.
Sweet misunderstanding.
Zhouzhou, can we two
talk peacefully?
Less force and...
And what?
And insincerity.
I'm not insincere?
Yes.
You haven't told the truth
since we first met.
So are you going to start from an early age?
Yes.
You lied to me the first time we met.
From child to adult.
Do you remember when we graduated from primary school?
How hard did I want to make you to
write a classmate record for me?
But you sent me away with four words.
You also told me that we could go to the same junior high school.
Do you know the day when school starts,
I searched for your name all day,
do you know?
It turns out that you are so dissatisfied with me.
I...I'm not.
Those four words at that time
were the best blessing my grandmother told me.
I haven't written to anyone.
And what happened when we were in junior high school,
I also explained it,
I didn't mean to.
I didn't mean that.
Let's go to class.
Hey, Xin Rui, I've been looking for you.
-Hey, Chu Tiankuo.
-You are looking for me?
The class is begin.
Mr Wu. I'll have a quick chat with Xin Rui
about the student union.
Oh, please hurry.
Ok.
I'd like to invite you to be the anchor of the voice of the English program
in the school radio station tomorrow, is that okay?
Can I?
No problem.
Several classmates have recommended you.
Find yourself an article about reading
and just read it aloud.
All right.
Ah, yes.
Can I choose this background music by myself?
Yes, you can.
Thank you.
It should be me. Thank you.
Then I'll go in first.
Ok.
Xin Rui, your disc.
Oh.
I can't do everything as I wish,
how can I do everything I want comes true.
Please play the last song for me later, thank you.
Ok.
Are you ready for the English article to be read in a while?
Yu, let me listen to the CD.
Welcome to today's English broadcasting room.
-Thanks.
-It's okay.
Today we invite Xin Rui,
a student from Class 3, Grade 2.
Xin Rui's English score have improved tremendously
in just six months.
Today she prepared an English poem,
The furthest distance in the world.
Hey, Jiang Chuan.
You go first. I'll come later.
Hurry up.