[English subtitles are available]
[My Huckleberry Friends]
[Based on a novel of the same name written by BA YUE CHANG AN]
[TV series with 30 episodes]
[Episode 6 Wanna go back in time and try to keep the stroy going]
Don't chase me anymore.
I won't give you the Martial Arts Cheats.
Me, heroine Yu, have never thought of today.
Who are you?
Yu Zhouzhou.
That's not what I am asking.
Then what's your question?
Where are you from?
Home.
Lin Yang.
I asked Miss Yu
for the spare balloons.
We went for it together.
Shut up.
Lin Yang, we are waiting for you. Come on.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Now you are my forth imperial concubine.
That's for the queen.
I don't agree.
How could you have a forth imperial concubine?
I am the king.
Guards. Banish her to the Cold Palace.
Catch her.
Are you revolting me?
Run.
You two go chase them.
Which one is for the king?
The yellow one.
You have been stuck.
What a useless king you are!
Zhouzhou.
Mama.
Yu Zhouzhou.
Will you come here tomorrow?
Okay, I will come.
Then I will wait for you right here.
It's a deal. You can't break your words.
Come on. Get on the bike.
Yes.
OK
Where have you been?
You got so sweating.
Zhouzhou.
Go get your grandma a glass of water, okay?
Grandma.
Here you are.
Grandma, don't switch channel.
I am watching.
Grandma, what happened just now?
Xiao Qing
was sleepy, so she fell asleep.
Zhouzhou.
It's almost dinner.
Don't eat too much snacks.
I am not.
Leave her alone.
She must be playing by herself in the room.
How could you again come in by crossing over the balcony?
Benben.
My father beat me again.
You father is so cruel.
But I am no match for him in fighting.
I will definitely beat him well when I grow up.
Benben.
Zhouzhou.
Yes.
Have you seen Benben?
No.
What a brat! I will give him a good beating when I find him.
Zhouzhou.
Yes.
Tell Benben to come home early if you see him.
Okay.
It's pork joint.
Do you wanna eat?
Yes.
Follow me.
Wow, the hill looks really steep.
There must be many treasures on it.
If we clime up the hill, we can have them all.
Help! The mountain collapsed.
Zhouzhou, stop it.
I am kind of feeling like throwing up.
The matter we talked about last time is done.
If you are available, you may come outside.
I have something to discuss with you.
It's for Zhouzhou.
It's him again.
Mr. Outsider.
Come on. Let's take a look.
Wow, it's the new arrival of game console.
What is the Mr. Outsider?
Mr. Outsider comes a lot.
He just stood outside the door every time he came.
And auntie didn't tell us his name.
So we call him Mr. Outsider.
Zhouzhou told me that.
Yes.
Zhouzhou.
Go play with Benben in the room.
All right.
Come on.
Why did he come again?
Didn't I tell you to stay away from him?
How could we explain if people around sees him?
I know.
This time.
He came for Zhouzhou's school matter.
You said that
you would be responsible for the decision you made.
He has nothing to do with Zhouzhou.
I do want to get him out of our lives.
But,
I don't want to encumber Zhouzhou.
If Zhouzhou is not able to go to school,
I will teach her.
I want to go to school.
I want to go to school, too.
I am coming.
Waiting for someone?
No.
Are you still thinking of your forth imperial concubine?
She's definitely not coming.
You know nothing.
Come on. Don't be mad.
Come to my house to play games.
No.
Class, in our last lesson...
Come in.
Come.
Class, let me make an introduction of
our new fellow.
Lin Yang.
-She's a bit late for registration.
-See, your forth imperial concubine. She's here.
That's why she just arrived.
Now we will have her to make a self introduction.
Introduction?
What's your name?
I am Yu Zhouzhou.
That's all?
Okay. Let's give a warm welcome to Yu Zhouzhou.
Zhouzhou, we have just finished the seat arrangement.
You could just sit there for the moment.
Okay, let's start lesson.
Stand up.
Salute.
Good day, teacher.
Good day, class. Sit down, please.
Here is a good news.
All of our class have passed
investigation for joining the Young Pioneers.
Hand this out.
Tomorrow we will have the otah-taking ceremony.
From tomorrow, all of us will be
the honourable young pioneers.
The red scarf represents a corner of the national flag.
It was dyed with our martyr's blood.
Therefore we must show our respect to the red scarf.
After we officially join the Young Pioneers tomorrow,
we shall wear the red scarf
everyday in the school.
Remember?
Yes.
Right. Zhouzhou.
Because you have just arrived,
you missed the application in this semester.
We will apply for it in the next semester, okay?
Yes.
All right. Ask Little Swallow
if any of you don't know how to tie the red scarf.
[Name]
Qianqian.
Could you help me tie the red scarf?
Yu Zhouzhou.
Yes.
Do you still remember me?
Why didn't you come that day?
I forgot.
You.
I am sorry.
Mum, is there anything different between me and other kids?
What's wrong?
Why do you suddenly ask me like that?
Why did I go to school later than other kids?
It's my fault.
Mummy forgot the registration time.
I am sorry.
Well then, it should not blame you.
Is anyone in the school
bullying you?
No.
Nobody dares to bully me.
[Chinese]
[Yu Zhouzhou Class 3 Grade 1]
Why did you pull my braid again?
I would get stupid if you keep pulling my braid.
Why did you keep playing one game?
I have only one cassette.
Hey. You should tell me earlier.
How could you have so many cassettes?
I have more at home. The whole drawer is full.
You may come to my home to play next time.
Great.
Yangyang, come on.
Mama.
Is this your classmate?
Right.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Come to my home for playing next time.
Okay.
It's settled.
Dad.
May I help you?
I am good at it.
Well then.
Let's start.
Don't run away.
You are good at it.
Okay. We won.
What's your name?
You should have known me.
Didn't your mother tell you?
We call you Mr. Outsider.
Because you were always standing outside the door.
You are smart.
Just like your mother.
Come on.
Mama.
A chicken draws bamboo leaves.
A dog draws wintersweets.
A duck draws maple...
Stand up.
From now on, whenever I discover anyone using anything that
has nothing to do with the class,
I will confiscate it with no exception.
No matter how expensive the item is.
If you want it back,
get your parents to come to see me.
Yu Zhouzhou, now.
Pick off one of your little red flowers.
[Yu Zhouzhou]
Well, we shall go on taking the course.
[Count Report Measure]
Let's have a look at this few words.
So be it. Yu Zhouzhou.
I give you a chance.
You may read these words on the blackboard.
[Count Report Measure]
If you are correct, you may sit.
Yes.
C O U N T. Count
R E P O R T. Report.
M A S H E R. Masher.
Yu Zhouzhou. What are you saying?
You are such a yound kid. How could you learn something bad?
Keep standing up.
And.
Pick off your last little red flower.
Yes.
We are going to mark the initial consonant
of these words.
Do you want your game console back?
But the performance of Class 3 is not so good.
The mathematics of Class 3 keeps in low score.
I will go in and draw Miss Yu away later.
Then you are going to get it, okay?
Miss Yu.
What's the matter?
Jiang Chuan is again
badgering with Ling Xiangqian in the classroom.
He doesn't let her go and tries to kiss her.
What?
You should go see it.
Oh, you kids.
Have you got it?
Not yet.
Miss Yu is almost back.
I dare not to try.
You have got it back.
Why are you still being so unhapppy?
I have never been happy in the school.
Is it because of the phoneticizing?
I can teach you if you don't understand it.
It's actually not so difficult.
It's not difficult.
It's me being too stupid.
No, no.
Do you know this characters?
[Wang's Physical Therapy Shop]
Wang's Physical Therapy Shop.
See. But I don't know.
It is because you are also stupid.
Yes, we both are stupid.
Well then, you teach me for characters.
And I teach you for phoneticizing.
Okay.
Well. I show you something funny.
What's this?
Science teacher gave me this.
You may see rainbow with it looking at the sun.
Where is the rainbow?
What are you doing?
Jiang Chuan.
I gotta go.
Jiang Chuan, you are done.
Benben, what's going on?
See.
I am here for cupping therapy.
It's really just a therapy shop.
Stop wrangling, please.
You shut up.
Nobody believes in you.
You come here almost everyday.
What kind of therapy you are receiving?
You guys see this small room.
A male and a female claim they were doing cupping.
Who would believe that?
Believe me. This is a formal physiotherapy center.
I've received professional training.
If you don't believe. Come in and see by yourself.
You look so coquettish.
Young as you are, you have many other career choices. Why did you choose this?
If you still feel angry, I can apologize.
I can make a formal apology to you.
But you can't beat people,
nor can you insult us.
It's you whom I want to insult.
No more words, please.
Shut up!
What are you doing?
You live here with your kids. How unbelievable!
Come here, Benben.
What a coquettish woman!
Don't get out until I told you to do so.
Why are you so disappointing?
As you guys can see,
there are two children.
Leave here. Stop being onlookers.
I'm sorry. I really don't know this before.
Here you are. I didn't lick this part.
I don't mind if you did.
Don't stay here.
There are kids inside.
You say. How to deal with this?
-Benben
-You seduce my husband into going here every day.
What does coquettish mean?
I think it means beautiful.
Then I'm coquettish.
I'm more coquettish.
Why didn't they like my mom?
She is so beautiful.
Is it because you don't have a dad?
Everyone has his dad and mom.
You aren't alone. I don't have a mom, either.
But someday I will find her.
Yep.
She would come here, wouldn't she?
Lay off!
Look over there!
Why are you so late?
The map you drew is too difficult to understand.
I'm happy you could come.
Your turn. Go!
Stay here.
How many numbers should I count?
From one to one hundred.
One, two, three, four, five, six...
Ninety-three, ninety-four, ninety-five, ninety-six...
Ninety-seven, ninety-eight, ninety-nine, one hundred.
Uncle
Today we invite many old comrades. Be more careful.
Yes, I will. Director Zhou, don't worry.
What's the matter with you?
That uncle is my friend.
But it seems he doesn't know me.
Uncle Zhou?
Do you know him?
I'm thinking about whether he is...
What?
Nothing.
He, he is my friend.
Then I can take you to see him.
Okay.
Lin Yang
Zhouzhou
The game is still under way.
Do you continue?
Lin Yang. Zhouzhou.
He is over there.
Uncle
Comrades, dear colleagues.
Today Director Zhou has come to
the dancing party for retired staff.
Let's welcome him to deliver a speech.
Please welcome with applause.
Give the game machine back to me.
Who are you?
My dad bought it. You aren't entitled to play.
Give it to me.
It's mine.
Give it to her.
Why?
My dad bought this.
You shouldn't play.
My mom said you are the daughter of a bad woman.
Never dream of taking my dad away.
It can't be powered up.
You can play mine.
I will give it back to you after having it repaired.
Thank you.
Adults are troublesome.
I won't let anyone insult you anymore
Yangyang, did you really beat your schoolmate?
Speak!
Don't blame him.
He is a good boy, which I know.
This time.
He must have been abetted by other kids.
What do you mean?
It's OK that you hold against me.
But don't get kinds involved.
When the above behave wrongly, the below will do the same
This little girl is good at play her hands.
Several days ago she even burst into my husband's institution.
Not inferior to you at all.
In those years, all I wished was to stay away from you.
It was you who kept an eye on us.
Her being able to study at this school
must have been arranged by my husband uopn your request.
Miss, this girl doesn't have registered residence.
According to the rules, she couldn't study here.
Enough! Can't you just be quiet?
Children's conflicts are easy to deal with.
But the conflicts among adults
are beyond our capacity.
Zhouzhou, Yangyang.
Apologize to Zhou Shenran, quickly.
Then we will end this conflict.
Yes, yes, yes. Make an apology. Hurry up!
I'm sorry.
Speak!
Excuse me.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Can you see what she said?
She didn't admit her mistake at all, did she?
I'm sorry.
Fine. Now that they have apologized,
you don't need to blame.
They're all kids and this isn't a big deal.
I'll go back to work.
What's the point of apologizing?
What if your daughter still
insult my son later?
What do you want?
Send her to another school.
Originally she shouldn't show up here.
I've told you many times.
Why can't you remember?
Look at my eyes and repeat
"I won't play with Yu Zhouzhou anymore". Now!
I won't play with Yu Zhouzhou anymore.
Louder.
Time for dinner. Zhouzhou.
I have no appetite.
Mom, why was I wrong?
You didn't do anything wrong.
It was those adults' faults.
I want to transfer to another school.
If you do,
how about your friends here?
I don't need any friend.
It's adequate for me to have you and grandma.
[Ferris wheel]
Let's go to...
Do you want to try this?
Yes.
OK. Let's go.
Yeah!
Mom, can you accompany me?
Mom
There will be a day
when you grow up and could understand that
grandma and I
would leave you one day.
Then I wish I would never grow up.
[In 2003]
See you.
Zhouzhou
It's really you!
Who are you?
I'm Lin Yang. Can't you remember?
We haven't seen each other after graduating from primary school.
You become so tall!
Well, I knew that you were admitted to Zhenhua High School,
and so was I.
We can be schoolmates again.
Do you have mobile phone?
Can you give me your phone number?
In this summer vacation during free time
we can hang out together.
No, I didn't.
Zhouzhou
Is this your classmate?
Aunt, I'm Lin Yang. Do you remember me?
Yes, I do. You are so tall.
By the way.
This is Uncle Qi
Nice to meet you.
Me, too. Have some beverage?
Thank you.
Zhouzhou, it's yours.
Well,
Will you spend more time with Lin Yang,
or will we...
I'll go home with you.
See you, Lin Yang.
Oh, see you.
See you.
Goodbye.
Lin Yang looks more high-spirited and vigorous now.
Yes.
What's the matter with Lin Yang that day?
What?
I care for Zhouzhou, as you can see.
I think Lin Yang
cares about Zhouzhou.
How can you find this?
Young boy like him
is easy to be understood.
He was Zhouzhou's schoolmate at primary school.
They were huckleberry friends.
And he was willing to stay with Zhouzhou.
However, due to some reasons,
they didn't play with each other as they used to.
Here comes a question.
Think about it. Zhouzhou has changed greatly in those years,
and he could recognize her at first sight.
You really have obeserved a lot
and analyzed reasonably.
When you were young,
you must have cared about other girls.
Everyone has a memorable youthhood.
Be careful!
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
You're back.
Your mother pricked her finger.
Do you have any bandage at home?
Yes. It's over there.
I'll find it for you.
I'll bandage her wound.
Eat more eggs.
OK
Hey, there.
Hello, aunt.
I'm Lin Yang. Is Zhouzhou there please?
OK. Hold on please.
Zhouzhou
Uh huh
A call looking for you.
Who?
Lin Yang
Hello
Zhouzhou
Yes
Can you come out this afternoon? I have something important to do.
How can you find this phone number?
Is there anything I can't do?
Ignore this.
Let's meet at our primary school two o'clock this afternoon, ok?
I won't go.
Or I can go to your home.
Do you still live in the same place as before?
Why do you come here?
I have a game machine which I gave to you, right?
Do you still keep it?
I'll fetch it this afternoon.
What game machine?
It's decided then.
Don't you eat?
After a while.
So many years have passed.
Why did you still want it?
I've tried. It can still be played.
I had promised to give yours back after repairing it.
Have a try.
Thank you.
Wow!
I haven't played Pokémon for a long time.
Zhouzhou.
Uh-hum
Let's try once together.
Okay.
Why  are you still so bad at playing this?
I'm giving way to you
After all these years
these games are still the most interesting
Zhouzhou
Yes
I'm so sorry
For what?
You changed school because of me
when we were kids
I also promised my mom to never see you again
They are long time ago
I've forgotten them. How do you remember them?
Have you forgiven me?
I've grown up now
and I can make some decisions by myself
without my parents' permission
Zhouzhou, take out the trash
Well, okay!
Of course I forgave you
But I can't make decision without
my mom's permission
Zhouzhou
Yes
Can I ask you to play with me again?
What are you doing? Zhouzhou
Uncle Qi
Where are you going?
Lin Yang asked me to go swimming with him
Get in, get in
I can drive you there
No, thanks. I can wait for a bus
It is coming soon
I have something to say
Get in. I'll drive you there
Where do you go swimming?
At the seaside
What do you want to tsay?
I want to propose to your mother in few days
I know it's not a good time to tell you today
You might feel sudden
It's okay. If my mom says yes and so will I
I couldn't be happier!
But
But?
Don't make me  call you dad suddenly
I can't do it  for now
Well, that is okay
You can call me whatever you like
Oh, by the way
My mom is usually easy-going
but you have to make efforts on the proposal
Otherwise she won't say yes
Well, it makes sense, Zhouzhuo
Let's go to the seaside
Okay
Can you swim? Zhouzhou
No, I can't
Why not?
Nobody taught me when I was a kid
Let me introduce her to you
You've met before
My fourth concubine, Yu Zhouzhou
Now I remember
Qianqian
you banished her to the cold palace.
Do you remember?
Jiangchuan, you!
Look! I drew it for you
You are so childish
Here, you can draw it
Well, fine
Lin Yang, you...
I really don't want to finish our holiday
I wish that summer vacation will last forever
Zhouzhou
Have you seen the student list?
Yes, I have
We are not in the same class
What does that matter?
Well, let's go out again in several days
Didn't you just go out few days ago?
But this time
Just you and me
Aquarium?
The tickets for the first week were sold out,
were they?
I have some soicial connections
I'm not quite used to wear this dress
Can I change it?
No, it's beautiful
Zhouzhou, what do you think?
It's beautiful!
It looks like it was made for you
You have good taste, young man
Let's go!
Okay, try to smile naturally
Smile more naturally
Good!
Bridegroom, please
I wonder that if I will be as handsome as him
when I get married
Don't think too much!
Excuse me
can you take a picture
for all of my family?
Okay, thank you
Well, Zhouzhou, come here, come
Let's take a family photo!
Come, stand behind me
Alright, look at the camera
Okay, smile
Ready? Three, two, one!
Zhouzhou
Dinner will be ready soon.
Come out and have dinner!
I'm coming!
Right. Zhouzhou
I've taken care of everything
We'll set off on Saturday
Where are we going?
Didn't we say we were going to Thailand?
This is gonna be our honeymoon
Should I go with you?
Of course
You have to carry our bags
and take pictures for us
Oh
What's the date on Saturday?
I think it's 17th
Yes, it's 17th
17th
I'd rather not go then
I was kidding
We won't let you carry the bags
No, I mean
Lin Yang asked me to
go to the aquarium with him on Saturday
It's an eternal problem
If Lin Yang and your mom fall into the sea
who will you save first?
That's enough
I'll absolutely save your mom
Stop it
Zhouzhou, call Lin Yang right now
and tell him you can't go to the aquarium
with him
He still has time
to go with someone else
But It's not easy for us to travel abroad
How can we go there without you?
Well, alright
Go ahead
Those tickets
cost all of my gift money
I got them through my father's
social connections
I'm sorry. I didn't mena it
You can ask Jiang Chuan to go there
It's not appropriate for two men to
go to aquarium
I just want to go with you
Lin Yang
This is Uncle Qi
You can go to the aquarium on 17th
I'll go to the travel agency and
put off our travel
It's okay
Thank you so much
Well, this is it
You're young. I can understand
Right?
I was young, too
That is how you spoil her
Thank you so much
You helped me
I will help you, too
Help each other. That is great
Anyway, I'm losing my place
in this family
You are still the one who have the final say
in our family
Have dinner
Come, Uncle Qi
Try some vegetable
Thank you
Hello?
Is that Zhouzhou?
Come to the hospital
Your mom and Mr. QI
had an accident
Zhouzhou, Zhouzhou, listen to me!
Your mom had a car accident
in front of the travel agency
Zhouzhou, Zhouzhou
Zhouzhou
Clam down
Get up, get up
Let's go
Go, go
Go, let's leave here
Listen to me, let's go! Leave here
Zhouzhou, listen to me, Zhouzhou
Zhouzhou, there, there
Go, go, go!
Zhouzhou
How is the situation?
Hurry up, hurry up!
Come on
Zhouzhou
Finally, it's all over
Okay, thank you
Zhouzhou
Let's go
It's all right