[English subtitles are available]
[My Huckleberry Friends]
[Based on the BA YUE CHANG AN's novel of the same name, 30-episode series]
I'm so angry.
What's going on? Is your paper rejected again?
Pan Yuanshen. He has become my deadly enemy.
I wrote so many words,
but he completely returned the paper to me without taking a further look.
To play up to him,
I even tore off the poster.
What if he doesn't think you play up to him?
Then what else does he want?
Should I stick his photo on the desk and pray to him?
No way.
All right. You guys stop laughing.
I'm not in the mood for joking now.
How about
this?
I see other clubs also have dancing programs.
How about we also make such a program?
In this way, we also have a program.
If so, should we still call the animation club?
No. No.
I have an idea.
Go ahead.
I studied the cello before.
If we enroll in the program in the name of music,
we can play for the stage with the mixture of the musical.
Would it be OK?
Do one thing under the cover of another thing.
Zhouzhou, you are awful.
My pleasure.
All right. I feel relieved that
the animation club has you who is so devious.
These are all Lin Yang's ideas.
He even wrote a stack of modification advice to me.
He is so devoted to your things.
Come on. I think I finally figure it out.
He is the sun.
You are the sunflower.
It's so warm to be irradiated by someone.
Hi. Director Pan.
Lin Yang.
Yes. Director Pan.
Come here.
I have read the program.
Ah. Excellent. It's worthy of praise.
However,
I feel that the program still has a little shortcoming.
It might be short of a singing program,
especially the vocal solo.
You see
we are on the same page.
Ah, do we?
Look.
So I add a new program. Have a look.
You are going to play fun with the people.
I just want to liven up the atmosphere at the scene.
Director Pan.
As usual, you are a serious person who has an aura of dignity.
If you integrate yourself with everyone,
no one will be afraid of you.
At that time, you will not have the aura of dignity.
Care about your own business.
You only see my hard look,
but you don't know my gentleness.
This program's purpose is to let the students
see a real Director Pan instead of singing.
The meaning of this program is so great.
I will try my best to arrange it for you.
Do a good job.
Yes. OK. OK.
[Episode Nine The script doesn't have this scene.]
Zhouzhou, are you going to play a song?
I haven't heard Zhouzhou playing yet.
Let me enjoy it now.
I haven't played the cello for a long time so that my skill might be rusty.
No worries.
Yes. Feel free to play.
She is not modest, right?
Mi Qiao.
Can I borrow this book?
You just say if you will join the animation club or not.
As long as you join the animation club, you can read all these books.
Can I do that?
What procedure do I need to go through?
It's not so difficult.
You can just buy me a popsicle.
OK, I will join the club.
Oh, as you are so crisp,
you don't need to buy the popsicle.
Congratulations. You open the new world's door.
We are ready now.
OK. Let me hear it.
OK. OK. Yu, it's OK.
I played two wrong notes.
I didn't recognize how many wrong notes you played.
But it might be rhythmless.
I haven't played the cello for a long time.
You need to let me have some time for practice.
I have played the cello much better than yesterday.
If we wait for your skill to be mature,
how will this song sound like?
Oh, it will be this level.
Wow. Fabulous. It's so picturesque.
You are too overreacted.
Yu.
We will temporarily trust that your skill will be recovered
in such a short time.
But the song that you just played was
the instrumental ensemble between the piano and the cello.
Of course, it's a cover for you to play the cello.
But I think one cello's performance
might not be good enough.
Right?
You are coming so early today.
The teacher rarely didn't delay the class.
You are so hardworking and still doing the review.
No. I'm afraid that the dialogue will be lost
so that I put it in the book.
Where is Zhan Yanfei?
Oh, she told me that
she wanted to practice by herself.
Thus, she will not practice with us.
Qianqian. In my opinion, you should not always play a joke to her.
I'm not playing a joke to her.
OK. Today there are just three of us.
Let's do it as quickly as possible. Practice the lines.
Come on.
Zhouzhou.
Oh, I will not laugh at you.
What's wrong with you?
The ancient people make a few regulations that everyone should comply with.
Yu Zhouzhou has made more and more regulations with me.
Forget it. I'm looking for Ling Xiangqian today.
Ah? Looking for me?
Our animation club wants to perform a program at the arts festival.
What we told Director Pan was the instrumental ensemble between the piano and the cello.
But what we are actually doing is our animation drama.
We want to invite you to play the piano with us.
Would it be OK?
It might not be a good idea.
You are standing up to Director Pan.
This can not be said as "against".
We just seek loopholes.
Zhouzhou, you'd better think twice.
It will be serious if Director Pan blames this thing.
Ah, you think too much.
The arts festival is held for the students
instead of Director Pan.
Oh. What's more,
Ling Xiangqian, you really liked to play the piano when you were young.
Just in time.
Let me think about it.
Oh, why are you playing the piano again
instead of reading books in the room?
The school has the activity and requires me to perform.
Why do you take part in those useless activities?
Go to read books as soon as possible.
I have already done my homework.
Can I just play the piano in half an hour?
No. Your Teacher Wu has said that
your recent score has a step back.
In this case, why do you want to play the piano?
In other words, playing the piano can't get the extra point for the college entrance examination.
You go to read the books as soon as possible.
I should have sold this piano long ago.
You just play the piano if you want.
Qianqian, what are you doing here?
I just passed by.
Ah, you have just passed by for a while.
You have been spying on me.
How do I dare to spy on you?
I'm just too outstanding.
Are you bullying Jiang Chuan again?
No. I just passed by.
I have something to discuss with you.
Are you talking about presiding over the program?
Yes.
Just in time. Let's chat while walking.
OK.
What a doomed couple they are!
Don't talk nonsense.
Just by yourself? Do you still want to contend with Chu Tiankuo?
Are you still hesitating if you should accept
Yu Zhouzhou's invitation or not?
If they would do it in such a way,
Director Pan would blame.
Actually, I think what Lin Yang said yesterday did make sense.
The arts festival is an activity that
should collect all the people's ideas for fun.
But I haven't been playing the piano for a long time.
My mom also doesn't support me.
Do you like playing the piano?
I quite liked it when I was young.
But I don't like to do it for getting the extra point
and the piano grading test.
And then it was not necessary anymore.
My family also didn't let me play the piano.
Actually, I think life should not be too utilitarian.
It's not necessary to care about exterior details.
And Director Pan is also not a monster.
So you suggest accepting the invitation.
This decision still needs to be made by yourself.
But whatever choice you will make,
I will always support you.
Oh. One more thing,
recently little swallow is not in a good mood.
She still has some habits as a host.
You would not be that hard on her.
OK.
Come on.
Did you bring the stuff?
I'm begging you. Can you give me a break?
My mom almost finds it out.
OK. OK.
Just such a damn thing.
What happened if it would be found out?
Ah. Give me back. This is not mine.
Your life is good now.
Don't break it.
I'm leaving now. I borrow this book for several days.
It depends on your ongoing performance.
Xu Zhiqiang.
Li Bai is Sailor Moon.
Li Bai is not Sailor Moon.
Li Bai replaces the original character in Sailor Moon.
And Du Fu replaces Seiya.
And then they fall in love with each other.
Uh, they are not falling in love.
This is a feeling between men.
They are like friends or brothers.
Soulmate.
Yes, soulmate.
Alright, any situation is ok.
As we want to play, we should play well.
So you accept it.
Let's have a try.
The passion of youth is fire.
The passion of youth is.
I left my stuff here.
Are you looking for this?
Oh, yes. Thank you.
Lin Yang.
Do you have a crush on Yu Zhouzhou?
I just took a glance over it.
I was not intentional.
Are you talking about this?
How should I say this?
But Yu Zhouzhou
has a crush on someone now.
This is what we borrowed from the music classroom.
It's convenient for us to rehearse.
Ah. Right. Ling Xiangqian.
Can you sort of bear with Zhouzhou?
Her level.
I did practice a lot these days.
OK. Let's have a try first.
Good job.
I accidentally played several wrong notes.
I didn't recognize any wrong note this time.
Oops, you are so excellent. Ling Xiangqian.
Let me say something that is against my will.
You are a beautiful lady when you are playing the cello.
Then you don't tell the truth.
This is also my first time cooperating with other people.
I don't realize that it went smoothly.
Mi Qiao, I'm kind of looking forward to our show now.
Were you reluctant before?
Before.
OK. Then we take a look at the script and allocate the roles.
Ah. OK.
Xin Rui, which role do you play?
I I can't do it.
Ah, no way.
If you don't play, people are not enough.
I haven't played before.
I'm afraid I will be nervous.
If so, can you play as the horse? It has no lines.
How do you know this?
She told me personally.
But the person is not you.
No need to be nervous.
She told me this when I was in primary school.
Oh, the primary school.
At that time, it was popular to say who likes whom
and who likes whom.
Benben. I'm Benben.
But I really envy Yu Zhouzhou.
She is smart, beautiful, and doing well in her studies.
And she is not that remote like Ling Xiangqian.
What Ling Xiangqian talked about you was not spiteful.
She is just not good at expressing herself.
I know. Everyone has no malice.
As a child,
the teacher of the Children's Palace was not spiteful
to say that I was suitable for learning to be a host.
Everyone is not spiteful to praise me that I'm smart and beautiful.
When I grow up, study suddenly becomes the top priority.
My teachers and parents are not spiteful to say that I'm doing no decent work all day.
After that, I'm getting fat.
My best friend was not spiteful
to snigger behind my back.
Do you know
I actively apply for this time's host to Director Pan?
I'm not reconciled to it.
Little swallow, actually everyone has recognized your improvement.
I'm sorry to suddenly say so many words.
You can leave first. I want to practice for a while.
OK.
Will you come to rehearse tomorrow?
Yes.
Holy shit.
I'm so mad.
The accounts are still incorrect this week.
Did this store encounter any thieves?
Xin Rui.
Did you secretly steal the store's stuff?
It's not me. How do I dare to do this?
I bet you would not do it.
If I catch the thief,
I will let him die.
OK. Today's lesson is over. Class dismissed.
Stand up.
Goodbye, teacher.
What's going on?
Have you already learned off the dialogue?
Have you learned off the dialogue?
Mi Qiao, I still think that
the dialogue is too much.
You are just not serious.
How can you learn off the text?
Who said that? I also didn't learn off the text.
You.
Ah. I think our dialogue is a bit too much.
We should refine it.
Yu Zhouzhou and I have discussed some songs
to cooperate with the progress of the stage performance.
I think we should always keep in mind
that the music perfectly matches the specific stage performance
and specific note.
This sounds good,
but it might be a little complex.
My thoughts are that
we can add some asides
which are controllable
and the result is also good.
You are meaning that
we find someone individually say the dialogue.
Yes.
This might be good.
I have an idea.
As our show is related to Li Bai and Du Fu,
can we use ancient poetry as a replacement for asides?
This sounds a little interesting.
I think this is good.
Yes. We have an action scene at the beginning of our show.
I think we can use Du Fu's poetry
for the scenes that Li Bai moves ten steps to kill one person
and the scene before the struggle.
The Pressgang at Stone Moat Village
I seek shelter at nightfall. What is the pressgang coming for?
This also explains the background.
This is good.
But who can say the asides?
Both of you have to play and I'm unable to it.
I recommend a person.
We can ask her to have a try.
Come in.
Teacher Zhan is coming.
We just finished the modification.
If you do that,
I'm leaving now.
No. No. We really can't do this.
This is our script. You can have a look first.
We are lacking of a monologue now.
Our story is mainly related to classical culture,
but we really can't find a person who can read this like a well-educated person.
a literate person to read the article.
It seems interesting.
Would you join us?
My task is to read these characters, right?
Yes.
Read the red characters.
They are mainly ancient poems.
Let me have a try.
Okay.
I seek for shelter at nightfall. What is the pressgang coming for?
My old host climbs over the wall. My old hostess answers the door.
It sounds great.
Let's try to add music on it.
You're right.
Ride off without stopping for a thousand miles.
I have asked you to have dinner, but you didn't hear it.
Why are you acting so crazily?
Mom, I will have a performance at the school's festival.
Performance?
What can you play?
Okay. Today's class is over.
Students who have questions can come to ask me.
Can you give my comic book back?
I haven't finished reading it.
Are you insane?
I can't steal things from my home anymore.
This is the last time.
My mom is more fierce than you when beating someone.
It's so boring.
Let's play it again.
What's wrong with you, my dear horse?
I...I'm nervous.
There's nothing to be nervous about.
It's just a rehearsal today. And you have no line.
It's my first time to play on such a huge stage.
Mi Qiao, aren't you afraid of playing badly or being embarrassed in public?
Life is short. I have no time to think about these.
Mi Qiao is heartless.
The word "nervous" can't be seen in her dictionary.
You're right.
I tell you,
if you are nervous,
you just think that
the audience are pigs.
Then you won't be nervous when thinking of it.
Zhouzhou, you're greater. I admire you.
This is what Littile Swallow taught me.
Zhouzhou.
Have you finished the table tennis game?
They're showering. I come to see you.
For you.
Thanks.
Oh, you are really like a little old man after sticking the beard.
Get away.
I'm the Immotral Poet, Li Bai.
When does the formal performance begin?
On half past four tomorrow afternoon.
Our exercise will be finished just at that time.
We will come to support you.
Okay.
No, no, no.
Don't come to make trouble, please.
Yu Zhouzhou, I'm standing still.
You're coming towards me.
Ah, you can keep standing still.
You have someone you like, don't you?
What do you mean?
Just the literal meaning.
You have someone you like, don't you?
I know you have.
Is the boy called Benben?
You're talking nonsense.
Tell me whether you have.
I have promised all what you have forbidden me to do.
But when will the condition change?
I'll be late for school.
I'm sorry. I'm not intentional.
Lin Yang, I'm warning you again.
I don't allow you to
come to me in any way, like walking, running, and jumping.
I don't allow you to talk and smile to me.
Don't touch anything of me.
It means that I can come to see you merely by rolling, right?
You can do it.
Don't be late for school.
Xin Yue, I have signed my name on your papers.
I'm putting them in your bag.
Okay.
You are rehearsing with Qianqian and that boy everyday.
Do you think that they have fallen in love like others say?
I don't see it.
What are you thinking about?
Are you thinking about how to roll to her?
Get away.
Will you roll?
Xin Yue has been absent all morning. What's wrong with her?
Zhouzhou?
What are you thinking about?
You have talked about Xin Yue.
Let me give her a call.
Mom.
Mom, I beg you to let me out.
Mom, please.
Nobody answers.
She always tells us she is nervous.
Is she going to sneak away before the performance starts?
She can't let Li Bai that I act walk to anywhere.
Leaders have attached great importance to this rehearsal.
The principle have mentioned it to me for several times.
You must take it seriously. Do you understand?
It's Mr. Pan. I forgot to think about him.
We have planned to feign our actoins and secretly reach the real purpose.
But the truth can only be revealed when we stand on the stage.
If we are stopped by him, our efforts will be in vain.
What can we do?
Please tell us. We really don't know it.
I ask you and you answer it.
Ah, I only know Pavarotti.
So, you, you, you.
Your functions are like the walkways'.
Swagger into that place.
Others come with me.
I know a secret path.
Be in a good state.
Be more positive.
What about my state today?
Hello, Director Pan.
Director Pan.
You're here. Where is Mi Qiao?
Mi Qiao?
She hasn't come.
I hear that you have prepared a musical
about Li Bai and Du Fu, right?
Yes. We have combined the musical with historical themes.
It can show great historical contents.
That's the right behavior.
Themes like anime are not decent.
Programs like yours are quite excellent.
Rehearse it seriously.
I'm confused. Why Director Pan suddenly approved our program?
Oh, I see.
Don't talk nonsense. It's not true.
Chu Tiankuo.
For our program, thanks a lot.
Why do you thank me?
Come in, come in.
Close the door.
Let me tell you.
I have investigated this place.
It's near our backstage.
To be on the safe side,
let's change our clothes here,
and go to the backstage before our performance starts.
You're very thoughtful.
Of course.
Will anyone use it?
You can prepare for the show now.
Wait for me for a moment.
Change your clothes first.
[Male Bathroom]
Hey, was my forehand shots just now
unbeatable?
-Amazing!
-Are you convinced?
I tell you,
I didn't exert my strength just now.
If I exerted it, you must lose.
Xiao Yu.
You're admiring yourself again.
Why can't I admire myself?
Beat him.
Who's there?
Don't move.
Chase her!
Lend me the place.
I'll let you out for a while.
Who? Open the door.
Who? Open the door please.
Don't leave. Open the door.
It seems that Director Pan has no problem.
Let's prepare for it.
I refuse. What if he want to create a diversion
and draw the snake out of its hole?
I think the safest plan is to step on the stage before our performance starts.
What's wrong?
Mi Qiao, why is your face so red?
You just go out for a moment.
And you come back in this state. What happened?
It's none of your business. I'm hot.
Anyway, I won't go.
I will go. I will help you to have a look.
You prepare for the performance.
Hey, Xin Yue hasn't come.
What are you laughing about?
It begins. It begins.
The passion of youth is like fire.
The passion of youth is like wave.
Let's sing in the embrace of youth.
Let's fly freely in the songs.
The Club Festival of Zhenhua High School this year
now begins!
The Foolish Old Man sweared to move the Wangwu Mountain away.
That would make his life better.
Can you tell me the reason?
Because it wouldn't block the signal.
We must hurry up.
It will be our turn after only one program.
Hasn't Xin Yue come?
What can we do?
You can give up riding the horse.
How can I?
Zhouzhou.
You see, can we ask your friend for help?
Are you insane?
You peered us and locked us in the bathroom.
Don't get angry with me. My beard is going to drop.
I can let you have no beard forever.
Benben.
It's Mi Qiao's fault indeed.
If you want to teach her a lesson, please wait for a while.
We really need your help now.
For what?
An actor of our performance doesn't come.
I won't help you.
I haven't finished.
Don't expect me to help you.
It's very easy.
It's just like the role-play
we have did in our childhood in the yards.
You can regard it as a game.
Will you join us?
Which role?
What have you done?
You have promised the festival would last for three hours.
It has performed for a longer time.
Brother, I'm sorry.
Please make an exception.
We have only two programs
and a curtain call left.
There's another performance after yours.
I'll give you the last ten more minutes.
Hasten to adjust the programs.
If the program can't be finished playing, just stop performing it.
Brother.
How's it going?
Director Pan,
he said he would only give us ten more minutes.
Only one program can be performed from the solo and the musical.
What's your opinion?
Do you need to ask?
You can't do this.
Who is the director, you or me?
I can't obey it.
Listen to me. You must obey.
I...
This festival is for students.
And Class Three has prepared for this program for a long time.
They must perform it.
Director Pan,
what about your solo?
I can't sing well.
Let them perform.
I see, Director Pan.
Thanks for the great performance from the members of Computer Club.
What's the next program, Lin Yang?
Next program is wonderful.
It's the ensemble of the piano and the violin.
One of our hosts is a player.
Really?
Let's expect the next program together.
"A Fairy Tale of Moon and Stars"
Who are you?
Come
Ma
What?
- Kneel down. /N -Release my mom.
Release me. What are you doing!
Jerk
You release her. You don't move.
Burry them for me.
OK
Release them!
During Anshi Period, Du Fu traveled through mountains and rivers.
He came to a village.
You shameless people.
Tie this crap up for me as well.
Got it.
Ah
Minister
I was seeking shelter at County Shihao at nightfall, and found some sergeants catch people at such night
An old man climbed up the wall, and an old lady watched outside the door.
How angry was the sergeant’s shout! How bitter was the woman’s cry!
Are you alright, minister?
[Zhenhua Middle School Clubs' Show]
Mi Qiao, you are done.
Shut up and go.
Fight!
You are great, Mi Qiao!
Director Pan
This show is good.
Your students are really devoting to the performance.
What do  you want?
I'm so tired. I will quit acting. Bye
Do we continue acting? Where are you going?
Li Bai's horse died of arrow shot,
so Li Bai left with tears.
There is no such scene in the script.
Are you OK?
I'm fine, fine.
Thanks a lot. Thanks a lot.
You deserve it.
Slow down, hero.
Is there anything I can help you?
I'm Du Fu.
Thank you for the help.
Please.
Du Fu and Li Bai traveled through mountains and rivers together,
and visited all the friends.
Thinking that we still have an appointment to find Mr. Beiguo.
Please, bro Zimei.
Thanks, bro Taibai.
Please.
With the scenery here, would you like to compose a poem, bro Zimei?
Well,
Facing the scenery here, I would read aloud bro Taibai's
Leaving the White King's Town at Dawn.
Well?
Leaving at dawn the White King crowned with rainbow cloud, I have sailed a thousand miles through Three Georges in a day.
With monkeys' sad adieus the riverbanks are loud. My boat has left ten thousand mountains far away.
Ah
Great poem. Great poem.
Flattered. Flattered.
Thanks. Thanks.
Hahaha
Bro Taibai, look.
What great mountains and rivers!
Beautiful!
Great!
I didn't break the rule.
I rolled over here.
Li Bai was set up and left the officialdom.
One day, to scoop the moon from the water after drinking,
Li Bai fell into the water.
While Du Fu……
With monkeys' sad adieus the riverbanks are loud. My boat has left ten thousand mountains far away.
Great poem. Great poem.
Zhenhua is so good.
Talents really come from your school.
What?
In last one minute,
our art festival will be over.
Let's save the last minute
for a special person.
He has made careful preparation for the song You Are My Eyes,
but hasn't got the chance to sing it for everyone.
Next, let's welcome Director Pan.
With only one minute left,
I would like to say something.
Why do I choose to sing this song?
I have been a director of teaching for over twenty years,
sending tens of thousands of graduates away.
Although I haven't been anywhere else but Zhenhua
my students are all over China.
I am so proud,
because you are my eyes.
[Zhenhua Middle School Clubs' Show]
Director Pan, Director Pan, Director Pan.
You are good, Lin Yang.
After the disciplinary action of being kept in school but placed under surveillance is cancelded,
your condition is truly different.
You look like the cat that ate the canary.
Cocky.
You are running.
I wanna, wanna lose some weight.
Was the one yesterday you?
Yesterday?
When Zhouzhou's instrument was broken , the one helped her raise it.
I was just for the performance.
Do you remember I told you before
that Yu Zhouzhou had someone in her mind before?
Are you telling me who it is now?
But I can tell you that
who she talked about was a cartoon figure.
That is very Yu Zhouzhou.
So, you still have a chance.
Zhouzhou,
do you have anyone in mind?
Why are you asking this suddenly?
Many people in the class are talking about topics like who likes who recently.
I'm just asking.
Then you cannot tell anyone else.
I won't tell anyone.
Uesugi Kazuya.