Wu, something's wrong.
Wait.
It's a trap. Let's go.
Mowen.
You don't deserve to learn how to set up a trap.
Come out!
Young Master and the others are ambushing snipers.
Let's go.
Young Master.
Wu.
Get up.
Go!
Let's go.
Manman.
Don't do anything you'll regret.
Young Lady, bad news!
Something happened to Young Master.
Chu.
Look.
Manman went home.
How did he get hurt so badly? Where's Wu?
We were ambushed by Mowen.
In order to protect Young Master,
Let's go.
Wu.
I was too reckless
to find out the truth of my father's death.
I knew there was a mole in the Qin family.
Mowen is the mastermind.
I thought...
I thought I could lure him to the station.
Things have come to this. It can't be changed.
Don't blame yourself too much.
You were in a coma for three days.
but you escaped Mowen's hunt.
Why did you save me?
Because
our childhood friendship.
Am I right?
Gu Chi.
Even if you hide your identity,
but how can you hide
How can you hide it?
The Qin family sent an allergy medicine.
Guess
how I got it.
You mean
she gave it to you?
Mr. Gu is as smart as always.
You worry too much.
I won't be angry
But Young Master Shen
I wonder when
so nostalgic?
Or
you have another purpose?
I'll be frank with you.
I don't care what happened between you and her.
Manzhi.
is now my fiancee.
I won't allow anyone
to get any closer to her.
Fiancée.
If she's willing to marry you,
why would she care about a traitor like me?
Gu Chi.
If you're sensible,
take these
and leave Yan City forever.
What if I say
I won't leave?
In a few days,
Manzhi will know.
Mr. Gu of the Gu family
has been working for the Qin family for seven years.
You're already a traitor in her heart.
Now,
if I know
your grudge with the Qin family,
Guess.
Will she choose her brother
or you?
Now!
It's not too late.
Get lost
Young Master Shen
I appreciate your kindness
I can walk by myself.
Do you know why...
Do you know why?
There are many rumors.
But how do I know
how can I be as clear as you?
You
and the whole Shen family
have nothing to do with this?
The Shen family is honest.
But what can I hide
from the world?
Gu Chi.
The back door.
Count the time.
Qin Chu Shi should wake up.
Good.
give the Qin family a target.
You're brilliant, Young Master.
Lu Huai was killed by Young Master Qin.
he has completely severed Miss Qin's mind.
A bunch of losers.
You can't even catch a traitor.
I want to see
whether they can
whether they can avoid it or not.
Everything is fine, Su.
Please send her to the lake in three days.
Xiaowu's blood can't be wasted.
Mowen must die.
Brother.
What we want is Mok Moon's life.
not to die together.
Move.
Did Xiao Wu hesitate when he took the bullet for me?
If you die,
what's the point of Xiao Wu's sacrifice?
Okay.
I'll remember Mowen's life for now.
But the traitor
must die.
Go follow the newspaper boy
and see what Madam has told him.
Yes.
Why did you come out?
What should I do if I catch a cold?
I won't see you when I wake up.
I'm flustered.
Let's go.
Madam.
Young Master went out.
He brought a lot of people.
Go to the lake
and ask her to come home quickly.
Tell her the situation has changed.
Go. Yes.
Miss.
The Qin and Mo families are looking for you in Yan City.
How dare you come to see me?
Lu Huai is afraid of death.
But some things
are more important than life.
I said I'll kill you if I see you again.
Do you think I wouldn't dare?
I do have a grudge against the Qin family.
but I'm not doing this for Mo Wen.
Miss.
You don't deserve to call me that.
This shot
for saving me in the big world.
teach me how to use a gun.
From now on,
you are no longer a member of the Qin family.
Since my brother suspected you,
I tried my best to protect you.
I even thought
if you could catch the shadow at the station,
and make up for your crime,
I'll take you back to the Qin family to accept your punishment.
The Qin family treats you well.
But what about you?
How can I tell you
I'm Gu Chi.
Our blood feud
can never be forgiven.
Miss.
What you said
is true.
Lu Huai.
I can't explain.
My life
on your account.
When Lu Huai fulfils his wish,
you can do whatever you want.
What a wish.
Is your wish
related to the Qin family?
At this point,
I have only one question for you.
When you saw my rouge and old stuff that day,
when you saw my rouge?
Miss.
Madam asked me to tell you
something is wrong.
Leave at once.
Two hours later,
if you haven't left Yan City,
I will kill you with my brother.
Let's go.
Those who betrayed the Qin family
never had a happy ending.
The moon shines on the moon