Miss.
Do you remember?
The dress I had custom-made for you back then.
I promised
I would make you the most beautiful bride in Yan City.
Now the dress has arrived.
Try it on.
Hurry and help Miss Qin get dressed.
I'm sorry, Miss.
I can't do it.
I've never blamed you.
Miss,
hold on.
Madam will surely come to save you.
Abo!
Don't try to resist.
The more you resist, the more you'll lose.
Drive faster!
It's Madam.
I hope we're not too late.
Mo Wen.
Where is Qin Manzhi?
That's none of your business.
Now
let's play a game.
This gun
has three bullets.
Each time you pull the trigger,
the cylinder rotates two chambers automatically.
You'll use this gun.
Each person gets one chance to shoot at the other.
Whoever survives
will be allowed to attend Miss Manzhi and Young Master Shen's wedding.
How dare you treat Manman like this!
Mowen,
people like you belong in hell.
Qin Chushi.
The angrier you get, the happier I feel.
Mowen, you play the part of a petty man
who's drunk with success perfectly.
My nephew is angry with me.
I won't hold it against you.
This time, the first move
is yours.
You must make good use of this opportunity.
Make this traitor
die as he deserves.
Aren't you afraid I'll shoot you dead?
Unless
you want Qin Manzhi to die before me.
Begin.
I've been waiting for this moment for a long time.
But I never thought it would be in a place like this.
Manzhi.
You look even more beautiful
in that dress than I imagined.
I've done as you asked.
Where are my brother and Lu Huai?
When the time comes,
you'll find out.
You usually have quite a temper.
I didn't expect
you'd be so nice to your sister.
Cut the crap and shoot!
The third bullet is jammed in the fourth chamber.
Statistically speaking, there's still...
It's the Qin family's people.
Madam, the young master instructed us
to follow you.
Given the current situation,
would you like to...?
Surround this house and search!
Find them alive if possible,
or dead if necessary.
Qin Chushi,
I've always wanted to ask you something.
If you were given another chance,
on the day my family was massacred,
would you stop your father?
No.
The Qin family needed to rise to power.
There was no other choice.
How brave of you.
Lu Huai.
Oh no,
Gu Chi,
what are you waiting for?
You think I'll let you manipulate me?
Kill me,
and you'll all die with me.
I've already made up my mind.
Whether you shoot or not,
the Qin family,
Qin Chushi,
what the Qin family owes you,
I'll pay it back.
Brother.
Manman.
Don't cry.
Someone from our Qin family has to die.
Save her.
Qin Chushi.
Brother,
no!
Don't leave Manman behind.
Let her go.
I know exactly what gun
you're holding.
You only have one bullet left.
Even if you shoot,
it might be empty.
But my gun
never misses.
Come back or I'll shoot.
Miss.
Brother.
Qin Chushi.
Lu Huai.
Manman.
Where are you?
The nearby warehouse exploded.
This house won't hold.
Forgive me, madam.
We promised the young master
to keep you safe.
Lu Huai.
Miss.
Thank you
for saving me again.
It's bad!
Mo Wen chose this place deliberately.
The cellar is about to collapse.
Let's go quickly.
Brother.
Manzhi.
The young master is already dead.
He wants you to live on.
He wants you to survive.
Let's go.
Manzhi,
stay here.
We couldn't share a life together,
but we'll share the same grave in death.
You go first.
Miss, hurry and go.
Hurry!
Quick!
Go!
Now!
Gu Chi.
Gu Chi,
give me your hand.
Give me your hand!
Miss.
This is the first time
I've heard you call me by my name, Gu Chi.
It sounds nice.
I'll call you that many more times in the future.
Hurry up and give me your hand.
I've already decided.
Either I take you out of here,
or you take my body out.
But either way,
you will survive.
From now on,
you are part of the Qin family.
When I first entered the Qin household,
I hated myself.
Just a guard.
But...
But I've never regretted
becoming Qin Manzhi's guard.
I know.
I know everything.
While there's still a chance, Lu Huai,
I forbid you to give up.
Qin Manzhi, you must get out of here.
Forget Gu Chi.
Forget Lu Huai.
Live well.
Start anew.
Gu Chi!
Don't touch me.
It's alright, sister-in-law.
If you're tired,
you should rest.
I...
I can find my brother and Gu Chi.
They're gone.
That's impossible.
Gu Chi and my brother are waiting for me.
I'm not tired.
I hate my own helplessness.
I couldn't save my brother,
nor could I save you.
You said you never regretted becoming my guardian.
But from this moment,
I suddenly regret meeting you.
I've lost you.
If it weren't for me,
at this very moment,
what would your life be like?
I imagined many endings, but never thought
I would never have my brother again.
And Gu Chi,
since I woke up,
has disappeared without a trace.
Sister-in-law refuses to speak about what happened that day.
I arranged to meet the lady here at seven o'clock.
The time now
is just right.
I think
I'll never see him again.
Miss,
I've finally waited for you.
You are...
A client paid me a large sum earlier
to take you to the train.
And instructed me to give this to you.
I originally planned to take the money and run.
But my wife said,
with such a large sum,
I should at least fulfill my obligation.
Rouge as new,
start over again.
So you
had already made new rouge for me.
You never
intended to take me away.
This isn't what you think.
Shut up.
I once hated you for using my trust,
until today I finally understand
that you were the one who always believed in me.
You never wavered,
never gave up protecting me.
Gu Chi.
You always told me to start over.
But from now on,
through the long years ahead,
the one I'll think of is you,
but the one I meet won't be you.
My remaining life will be restless.
Rouge as new.
Start over again.
I knew you were still alive.
The doctors wanted to give up on me many times.
But I thought of you waiting for me.
I didn't dare to die.
Yue Zijiao, Yue Zhenbai's love.