Why are you so careless?
Chu.
You're not drunk.
Are your legs
Are you surprised?
Drunk is the same as my wound.
I pretended.
For...
to trap you.
Who do you want
to?
I did it for myself.
When you abandoned me in the opera circle,
I almost became someone else’s toy.
I hate you so much.
I hate the Qin family.
As long as this contract is announced to the public,
the truth behind Gu's fire.
At this time,
you still have to
to yourself.
The person behind you is Gu Chi.
So what?
Joo-Ryu.
Let me ask you one thing.
When you married into the Qin family,
when you married into the Qin family?
My sincerity
in the opera circle.
I chose gifts for you with joy.
And you?
My pillow.
Don't waste your time on me.
I won't tell you where Lu Huai is.
Qin Chu Shi.
Kill me.
I never take back
will never be taken back.
As long as you are in the Qin family,
you will be Mrs. Qin.
As for Lu Huai,
watch carefully
and see how I killed him.
I let him go on purpose.
He was just a move I made.
Lu Huai.
will die for sure.
Guards.
Keep an eye on Mrs. Qin.
If she leaves the room,
you will be punished.
Yes.
Manman.
You're good at shooting now.
This person
is the spy Mak Moon arranged at home.
Did Lu Huai tell you that?
Brother.
I made a deal with Lu Huai.
Miss saved me again.
And I owe you last time.
you owe me last time.
Do you know where Mowen is?
The suburb warehouse.
You're smart.
She never makes a loss.
But do you know
you could enter the dungeon so easily,
it means Qin Chu did it on purpose.
Because he knew
once I escape,
I'll look for Mak Moon.
He's using me
to lure the snake out of its hole.
You know everything.
why did you tell me everything?
Since the day of the accident at the station,
I swore in my heart
I won't
from you.
But Miss,
will you believe me?
Mowen was the last spy in the Qin family.
There's a scar on his chin.
Lu Huai.
After you leave this time,
can you stop being enemies with the Qin family?
Miss.
Lu Huai
Lu Huai has no choice.
Miss,
You have no choice.
I know it's impossible
I still hope
After Mowen died,
you and the Qin family are no longer enemies.
That would be great.
Manman.
There's a gap
between you and Lu Huai.
I know even if you don't tell me.
Brother.
Let Lu Huai go.
He shouldn't
on Zhou Liu.
Did he tell you
he and Zhou Liu
with Zhou Liu.
in the Qin family.
Sister-in-law, don't make it hard for yourself.
You should know
who I am.
You still call me sister-in-law.
I don't believe you don't love me and my brother.
If that's the case,
you could have killed me
you could have killed me.
Manman.
I can't go back.
Sister-in-law.
You're still in the Qin family.
Lu Huai is still alive.
It's not too late.
We get along well.
We once treated each other sincerely.
I'm afraid
to be your sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law.
are willing to leave me and the Qin family.
What about my brother?
The people from Qin Mansion didn't tell me.
The line seems to be broken.
I'm afraid
in the Qin family.
This is our last spy.
If he dies,
we can no longer know Qin family's whereabouts.
Lu Huai is the only one
is Lu Huai.
You mean
Lu Huai escaped?
It's a trap.
has been prepared for the Qin family and Lu Huai.
Qin Chu's leg was broken.
As long as he crashes into my net,
he'll die.
They would never expect
I have a perfect partner.
Now I know where Mak Moon is hiding.
Prepare the weapons and follow him.
Cover the servants' mouth.
Don't let her know.
Father.
I can finally
is finally over.
Why aren't you telling me?
Don't forget that you're mine now.
Did he go to see Mak Moon?
Young man,
someone booked a boat ticket for you.
Boss has seen through your cooperation with the Qin family.
Run!
The boss knows you're suspicious.
You'll die if you go back.
I can't watch you die.
Move.
Shadow, I'll go.
I have my own reason.
Don't stop me.
The reason
for Qin Manzhi?
When you and I worked for Mo Wen,
we walked all the way here
All I think about is how to survive.
It's dangerous,
but I'm alive.
And now...
Look at you.
You're crazy.
You're right.
I'm crazy.
I don't know when
I fell in love with her.
Although the Qin family and I
with the Qin family,
But I can't.
I can't be her enemy.
Please let me go.
I'm sorry.
Lu Huai.
We promised to live and die together.
If you insist on going this way,
don't blame me for betraying you.
If it weren't for you,
I would have been cold.
Cheers.
You're injured.
Don't drink too much.
Fine.
Consider it as we've had the Netherworld Wine together.
From now on,
If you die,
I won't live in secret.
It's just a drunk talk.
Don't take it seriously.
You can use
for yourself.
A drunken joke.
But I'm serious.
Lu Huai.
Let's go.
Young Master, we're late.
This is a diversion.
Go back to Qin Mansion now.
Yes.
Let's go.
Miss, run! I'll stop them!
Go after them!
Come with me.
Why did you come back?
Why did you hurt your hand?
It's just an old injury. I can handle it.
Let's go.
Where do you think
you can go?
Miss.
You're still here to save people with your injuries.
That's my fastest gun.
What a pity.
Let's go. Let's go.