Keep an eye on your wife and Lu Huai.
Remember to send a message.
Yes.
You've been here quite often lately.
You didn't even say goodbye to me.
without even saying goodbye.
As long as you don't have a clear heart,
I won't be able to live in peace.
Manman has grown up.
He has his own ideas.
Don't push Manman too hard
because we're close.
I'll be angry with you too.
Don't worry.
But
I have to remind you again.
someone
is suspicious.
You mean...
You're always smarter than me.
You should know who I'm talking about.
Father saved this for you.
According to his order,
to save money regularly every year.
to be used by you in the future.
Shen Panshu is not you
I'm glad and disappointed
Young Master.
The fire at Gu House that day...
I'm glad you're not a member of the Gu family.
That's why we met again.
But why am I getting more and more afraid
to find you?
Father.
Since Manzhi returned to the Qin family,
my brother has been taking care of me.
Now,
I have to leave and do something for the Qin family.
Miss.
Why are you here?
It's so cold.
in such a cold day.
But Young Master told me
I knew you wouldn't leave me alone.
You must be kidding.
Lu Huai.
Of course I won't leave you alone.
Are you sure?
Lu Huai.
I never break my promise.
I told you before that I wanted to escape.
I wanted to leave Qin Mansion.
It's true.
No matter where you go,
Lu Huai is like a shadow.
Why don't you ask me where I'm going?
When?
If you don't tell me,
I won't ask.
But Lu Huai
to protect you.
I'm going abroad.
The sooner, the better.
But Young Master told me
the Shen family is your best choice.
Are you sure
leave Young Master Shen?
How can a person with an unfaithful heart
is not the best choice.
Yes.
Lu Huai will buy you a ticket
when buying butterfly pastry tomorrow.
Bao.
Who sent you here?
Miss.
Young Master asked me to keep an eye on you and Lu Huai.
If my brother sent you here,
you wouldn't have praised me.
I'm a perfect match for the page book.
I don't like people talking about me.
How could he let you mention the page in front of me?
At this point, Bao has nothing to say.
I didn't do my job well with money.
Just accept your fate.
How much will the page book give you?
I'll pay you double.
Miss.
You're not going to kill me.
You heard it.
I plan to leave the Qin family.
Go to my room and get the reward.
then leave Yan City.
I'm not leaving.
No.
If you don't leave,
my brother will punish you
he will punish you.
You can't explain to the Shen Family either
Siu-shun thought I was clever
So he bought me from the trafficker
But Young Master Shen and he never treated me like a human
Although I'm illiterate,
but I know the word "righteousness".
You treat me sincerely.
Bao is willing to help you.
You know too much.
I can't keep you.
My Lady, my identity has been exposed.
If you don't accept me
Siu-shun will kill me for sure
If you go out from the Qin Mansion, you'll be in trouble
you need someone to inform you.
I will do my job.
I won't trouble you.
If you insist on staying,
if you insist on staying.
Thank you, Miss.
In order to hide your identity,
you should keep in touch with the Shen family.
But what should I say
what should not be said,
what I shouldn't say.
Get out.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I just realized
what you mean
What does that mean?
I just feel...
Miss.
You're different
from before.
I'm from the Qin family.
I've been drawing with you all these years.
Can't you learn that?
Yes.
Miss is from the Qin family.
Manman.
Bao told me you wanted to see me.
Sister-in-law.
I've made up my mind.
I won't marry Shen Panshu.
Okay.
I'll tell your brother for you.
I asked my sister-in-law
not for this.
There's another thing I need your help.
I'm rich.
Really.
Two train tickets can be sold at this price.
Say it.
That person was in your hand.
when did you buy the ticket?
Lu Huai.
Stop.
Let's go.
I've saved these years.
It should be enough for you and her.
You know everything?
Young Master Shen is very strange.
I hid the truth about Ding Xiang for you.
But Chu is suspicious. She will find you soon.
Luckily,
you and her are leaving soon.
No matter how Manman feels about you,
she's willing to take you with her.
at least it means she's serious about you.
Manman doesn't know.
But I should ask her.
the girl you met when you were young.
Have you really forgotten her?
Su.
She couldn't escape.
She died in that fire.
Shouldn't you be sleeping at this hour?
Why are you so kind?
You even come to see me.
Don't say that.
You've been drunk these days.
Stop talking about me.
I barely see you.
Don't think I don't know what you're thinking.
Your birthday is coming.
I remember.
That's why we're all here to finish our work.
Did you prepare a birthday gift?
I'm sure you'll like it.
Well said.
The gold jewelry you made last year was crooked.
What are you talking about?
It's gold even if it's crooked.
It will be fine this time.
Didn't you say it's too boring to hold it in Qin Mansion?
This time, I've booked the whole world.
Then I'll wait for you.
waiting for you to slap my face.
Miss, we can go now.
Sister-in-law said
I'll take her and Xiaowu to the Great World tonight.
Sister-in-law will help us get him drunk.
Bao will help us stall the remaining guards.
Let's go straight out.
Just tell him we're going to the Great World to pick him up.
Miss.
If you regret it now,
you still have a chance.
I, Qin Manzhi,
never go back.
You were drunk yesterday.
and finally finished your work.
Why don't you sleep more?
Tomorrow is Manman's birthday.
I have to make sure everything is perfect.
You don't have to worry about my birthday.
I haven't celebrated it with you.
Oh.
As you know,
I promise you I'll be with you
every year.
Miss is missing.
Young Master.
The dress you brought Ms Qin here is here.
What are we waiting for?
Follow me to Qin Mansion.
Call Chu Shi before you leave.
and talk about the delivery time of this batch of fragrance powder.
Yes.
You mean
Miss and Lu Huai are missing.
They only left a letter.
Yes.
Yesterday, she said she would bring Lu Huai to the Great World to pick you up.
Then she didn't return overnight.
Did he stay out all night
or eloped with Lu Huai?
Shen Panshu, what do you mean?
Chu.
Calm down.
Because of our years of relationship,
I didn't fight you.
Watch your mouth.
I'm sincere to Manzhi.
The Shen family is the same to the Qin family.
Your father refused to sell the secret recipe to the foreigners.
The Shen family took over this hot potato.
It's between our parents
between us?
This punch
for Manman.
If you didn't push him too hard,
why would Manman run away from home?
Young Master Shen.
Is this the attitude of your family?
When Qin Chu was young,
you trusted the wrong person.
Wu, what are you doing?
Manzhi refused to marry me in the way of running away
is a disgrace to the Shen family.
My father won't give up easily.
The Qin family
We must give the Shen family an explanation.
The moon shines on the moon