Andy Arellano kidnapped you?
Is this Juan's statement?
"I believe that Leon Almazan
got me kidnapped."
What did Sandro's son say?
He said there's a treasure
in Hotel 88.
That might be the reason
why Andy wants to take over.
What if there's gold
in the hotel?
We need to know what it is.
If it's even true or not.
This could be one way
of protecting our families
against Andy.
Mister Andy?
Is this a surprise visit?
Luna...
I'd like to personally talk
to you about the partnership.
About Hotel 88.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you believe Justin?
[GIO] He's full of nonsense.
It's not unusual that he
came up with this treasure hunt.
I couldn't believe it
at first, either.
But if you think about it,
it might be true.
Okay, sure.
If there was a treasure,
Papa would've told us.
What if it's what he was
gonna say on the video
if he didn't get cut off?
Gio is right.
Why does only Justin know
about the treasure?
Why didn't we know about it?
Aren't we the sons
of the real owner?
Fine.
Leon said
he was investigating someone.
Sandro Soliman.
He used to be Papa's contractor
for the hotel.
And?
[SIGHS]
A few months ago,
he saw Sandro about
to kill Papa and Uncle Fred.
I don't think we're
supposed to talk about that.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYS]
Leon accidentally killed Sandro.
[KIKO] What?!
Leon killed a guy?
Did he tell you all that?
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
He saw him
about to kill our fathers.
[INHALES]
So, he ran over him.
Leon has been suspecting
that our fathers
didn't kill each other
because he knew
something had happened
that could've been
the reason for everything.
That Sandro guy?
But...
What does he have to do
with the treasure?
[EXHALES] Justin.
He said he's spoken
to Sandro's son.
That son told him
about the treasure
and his father's involvement
in all this.
And he believed
that murderer's son?
Gio, please.
I know it's hard to believe,
but that's not the worst part.
Sandro is not alone
in his search for the treasure.
Do we know his accomplice?
Accomplice, ally,
whatever you wanna call it.
Who is it?
Andy.
[DRAMATIC ZING]
Andy Arellano,
the Almazans' friend.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
[MARINA] Juan is in the station.
Um...
Edward told me
that Leon doesn't want
to partner with me.
Now, I don't know
where he's coming from,
if he heard something bad
about me,
but let's be honest here.
You guys know me.
Your Dad and I have been friends
since you were kids.
But, Mister Andy...
I'm sure Leon has his reasons.
And those reasons are?
We haven't talked to him
about it.
Uh...
Can I ask you a question?
[JADE]
Why do you want to help us?
I mean, there are a lot
of businesses out there.
Why Hotel 88?
Because it has something I want.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYS]
You know, uh...
Hotel 88 is the only prime hotel
on this island
that I still don't own.
When Michael was in charge,
there was absolutely no way
I could get in.
But now that
there's an opportunity,
is it bad to try and fulfill
my business goals?
Look.
You know, Edward and I
were very happy with Hotel 88.
We're very invested.
Because this isn't just
a business between partners.
You know, we're choosing
to do this with people
that we consider our family.
[CHUCKLES]
Don't worry, Mister Andy.
I'll talk to our lawyers.
We'll go on
with this partnership.
Good.
I know Cheska talked about this
on her podcast.
About hidden treasures
guarded by spirits.
But those are just stories.
This one...
What?
Isn't true?
Just keep searching.
It can be anything.
Diamonds, gold, or something
with a high monetary value.
We've searched
this place before.
Raphie almost shook it out.
You're just looking
for documents last time.
But we didn't find
anything expensive.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
It's not here.
You really don't believe it?
If it was a treasure
that Papa knew about,
he wouldn't have kept it
in the library.
You said it yourself.
In Papa's video, right?
"Don't sell the hotel off,
there's something important."
So, you believe it, too?
I'll believe it
if I see it with my own eyes.
[EXHALES]
[GIO] How about you, Kiko?
Well...
I believe that Papa
wanted to tell us something.
If it's a treasure...
then, yes.
I believe it.
Then, there should be clues.
Clues as to where to find it.
That's what
we should be looking for.
Ma'am, thank you so much
for your help.
It's my job to accompany you
even in medical services.
Are you going home?
I can't go back to Papa's house.
That's where Andy's men
attacked me.
I was about to leave for Manila.
Are you leaving today?
I can take you to the pier.
You don't have to, ma'am.
I'm fine.
No, it's okay.
It's not too far off.
- Shall we?
- Okay, ma'am. Thank you.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
Ma'am, are we going
somewhere first?
Don't worry, Juan.
This won't take long.
Okay, Luna. So...
I'll see you tomorrow
for the final signing, okay?
Yes, Mister Andy. Thank you.
- Leon--
- What are you doing here?
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
You couldn't buy me off,
so you beat me up?
Leon! What's going on with you?
And now, you're trying
to buy my sisters off?
Leon, what are you saying?
Let's about this in private.
I know what you're trying to do.
You're an evil man!
Leon, what's going on?!
Why are you so mad at him?
[ANDY] You know what?
Go on, tell them.
Actually, tell us.
What's going on?
I'm confused, too.
Have I done something wrong?
- Leon, Leon!
- Leave us alone.
Leave my family alone!
Get out of my house
and never come back!
[JADE] Leon, please.
Luna, go inside!
Just go inside!
Leon, Justin,
this is so embarrassing!
Either you go inside,
or I'll kick you out.
[JUSTIN]
He's serious, Luna.
[JADE] Please, Luna.
[LEON BREATHING HEAVILY]
[JUSTIN GRUNTS]
Uncle Andy, I'm so sorry.
[JUSTIN] Calm down, Leon.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LEON GRUNTS ANGRILY]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LEON SIGHS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Ma'am, this isn't
the transport terminal.
[DOOR OPENS]
Whoa! Hey!
Let me go! Let me go!
[THUDS]
- [GUN COCKS]
- [JUAN SHOUTING, PANTING]
They've been looking for you.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
How dare you, Leon!
Justin, how could you let him
insult Uncle Andy?
He only wants
what's best for us!
You're smart, Luna.
But you're not using
your brain!
Even if I were the
smartest person in the world,
I wouldn't understand
what's going on in your head
because you're not
telling me anything!
You're hiding something too,
Justin!
There are things
you're not telling us.
Leon, please.
Tell us the truth!
What are you hiding, huh?
What do you know?!
Do you really want
to know the truth?!
- Fine!
- [SLAMS TABLE]
Uncle Andy was the one
who had me beat up!
[LUNA SCOFFS]
You already heard that earlier,
but what?
- You had no reaction!
- Because it doesn't make sense!
Why would he do that?
Because I'm investigating
Dad and Uncle Michael's deaths.
But the case is already closed!
It was Roi!
Roi was the one
who killed them!
That's not true.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you saying?
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
Because I killed someone.
Leon...
You killed someone?
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
Before Dad and
Uncle Michael died...
I saw them.
Someone wanted them dead.
[MUSIC TURNS UNSETTLING]
So I ran over him.
I killed him.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I didn't mean to kill him.
But that guy is a monster.
If I hadn't killed him...
If I hadn't done that...
Dad and Uncle Michael
would've died.
What?!
Who was it?!
It was Sandro Soliman.
Juan's father?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Is that why Juan
has been following you?
Maybe!
But Dad said
he and Uncle Michael
handled everything.
That I shouldn't tell
anyone what happened.
To forget all about it.
And you hid that from us,
Leon?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
But what does that
have to do with Uncle Andy?
Because Uncle Andy and
Sandro, who wanted Dad dead...
...were working together.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
But how?
Why would they do that,
Leon?
Believe it or not...
there's a treasure
hidden in Hotel 88.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Damn you, Leon!
You ruined all my plans.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
[RINGING CONTINUES]
What? I'm not in the mood.
[MARINA] I can fix that.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
We have Juan.
[SCOFFS]
[SIGHS] Okay.
Okay, that's good.
What are we going
to do with him?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARINA] Copy, boss.
[CELLPHONE BEEPS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
I find this so-called
treasure hard to believe.
Even what you've discovered,
Justin.
I know.
Even Leon and I
don't believe it.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I found a burner phone
near where I killed Sandro.
I didn't know who owned it
or what I was going
to do with it but,
one day,
we were at the hotel
with Uncle Andy...
the phone rang.
It was Uncle Andy.
He thought I was Sandro.
That's how I found out
they were working together.
Are you saying that...
Uncle Andy had something
to do with Dad's death?
I'm not sure, Jade.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm sorry.
I tried to protect
all of you.
So I kept all of this
to myself.
I'm sorry.
You need to believe us,
Luna.
Whether Uncle Andy
was involved
or not...
it's clear he's only using us
to get what he wants
from Hotel 88.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Uncle Andy is dangerous.
That's the truth.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JADE] I'm sorry, Leon.
I'm sorry you had to
go through this alone.
Leon, I'm really sorry.
[JADE SNIFFLES, EXHALES]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Leon.
Justin.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PAGES FLIPPING]
[PAPERS RUSTLING]
Can we just give up?
We're not leaving empty-handed.
We've turned the place
upside down already.
Monette and Raphie
have checked everything too.
Even Papa's library.
There are no clues here.
I'm out of here.
Wait a minute!
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
Is this also a cabinet?
[INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PANEL CLANKS]
[SLIDES OPEN]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Check it out.
Give it to me.
[MARTIN] It's empty.
[GIO] What? Another book?
[INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's not just a book.
[CLINKS]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Almazan.
Sir Henri.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You seem to be in a hurry.
What do you want?
And yes,
I am in a hurry.
[MARINA]
We received a report that
Juan Soliman was kidnapped.
According to their statement,
you kidnapped him.
[HUFFS] Wait a minute.
That's not true!
I don't even know him.
[MARINA] Syvera.
Check the back!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Alright, open it up.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[COVER FLAPS]
- [GUN COCKS]
- Don't move!
Put your hands up!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[HENRI] Put your hands up!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Put 'em up!
[HENRI] You're under arrest
for the kidnapping
and murder of Juan Soliman!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
How many times
do I have to tell you?
I don't even know him!
[HENRI] But he knew you.
He mentioned you
in his sworn statement.
Okay, I may sound arrogant,
but I'm an Almazan!
A lot of people
on this island know me!
Sure. You're right.
But explain this.
How did Juan Soliman's body
end up in your car?
- I don't know.
- [MARINA SCOFFS]
That's the truth!
Only you and your family
have access to your car keys.
How come you don't know?
How did a body-- a dead body,
end up inside your car?!
I don't know!
I didn't put the body in my car!
You didn't, so someone else did?
So, you had an accomplice?
What?
Did you have an accomplice?
I didn't have an accomplice,
because I had nothing to do
with the dead body!
It's impossible for a dead body
to just end up inside your car!
I need my lawyer.
[MARINA] Of course, you do.
I won't say anything else
without my lawyer here.
- Then, you should've--
- De La Paz!
Let's just wait for his lawyer.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
My brother has no enemies,
so whoever it is...
It's Soliman.
Juan Soliman's dead body
was found in your brother's car.
I need to come clean.
Unless you have evidence,
Leon won't be set free.
Don't drag yourself into this.
Don't drag Luna and Jade
into this.
They say, fish is easily caught
by their mouth.
You have to be careful
with what you say.
For me, it's easier if they
didn't know that you're fishing.
What are you doing here?!
I don't understand.
- Don't touch me!
- Hey!
What do you want?