♫  I opened my eyes and saw a smile  ♫
♫  I'll hold out my hands and be embraced by you  ♫
♫  The world is noisy, but definitely won't disturb  ♫
♫  Bitter, spicy, sour, and sweet are all important  ♫
♫  I know everyone will grow old  ♫
♫  But remaining the same is not necessarily a good thing  ♫
♫ How to meet optimism when we hesitate in our youth? ♫
♫  Even if you fall, keep running  ♫
♫  We are young, following the music and dancing  ♫
♫  Throwing ourselves into our passion is what makes our youth beautiful  ♫
♫  As much as we like something, we embrace it,  holding tight our dreams of going toward the sunlight  ♫
♫  We're not afraid of thunderstorms  ♫
♫  We are young and shining as we go on our first journey  ♫
♫  Let's all charge together to that far away place we want to reach  ♫
♫  We're not afraid of thunderstorms  ♫
♫  We are young and shining as we go on our first journey  ♫
♫  Let's all charge together to that far away place we want to reach  ♫
(Almost Famous)
Why didn't I find out earlier that you are this messy. Everything has been heaped up on Brother You's bed.
When Brother You comes back, you'll have to tidy up everything!
His company makes sure that he gets to live a good life. Why will he come back?
Brother You! You are back!
Quickly come in! I'll help you carry your bag.
Oh my God!
Why does this dormitory looks like in such a condition?
Who did all of this?
-He did it.-He did it.
Doesn't matter who did it. Quickly make it the way it was before.
-I have come back to stay.-You have moved back here?
Why? Am I not welcome here?
Of course you are welcomed!
We welcome you with firecrackers and drumrolls!
But this bed...
I guarantee that by tonight this bed will be cleaned even more tidier than Ding Dongong's
bag.
Alright!
-Hello?-Cheng Ming, where are you?
I have come back to our dormitory. Let's go and eat together.
But right now I am not in the campus.
I am going to meet an agent for an interview.
Agent? Who?
He isn't an imposter, right?
Isn't it the last year of college? All our classmates have been to interviews whereas I haven't.
Now, with so difficulty one agent contacted me. So, I will certainly got to meet him.
Don't worry! I can sense if there is any wrongdoing.
How about I accompany you?
You don't need to. I am not a fool.
You quickly set up your dorm room. Everything must certainly be messed up.
I'll call you after my interview is done.
-You...How can you—-Bye!
(Episode 17)
(Teaching Block)
Dong Nan, what have you thought about Amy?
I think Ai Li has raised her very well for these many years.
Didn't you also say that she is very talented and sincere?
I am afraid that my current social status
will on the contrary only cause trouble for her.
Just mentioning again but you also know Ai Li's temperament.
That year, she just said and left.
For all these years, even she didn't tell Amy anything.
Actually, she doesn't want me and Amy to know each other.
You believe that is alright to not admit and break up familial flesh-and-blood ties.
But sooner or later you will have to confront it. Think properly about it.
Amy also really wants to meet you.
-Hello Cheng Ming!-I am Si Tuying.
Everyone calls me Sister Ying. You can also call me that.
We have done your overall assessment. Even though the image isn't excellent but the foundation is good.
Our company is looking for recent outstanding graduates to go to USA.
And participate for around six months in a training session for Broadway performers.
A training session for Broadway performers?
Yes, a training session for Broadway performers
Our classes are all in English and we have closed master classes.
Outstanding graduates will also become Broadway signed actors.
However, we do collect a tuition for training costs.
We will also purchase the roundtrip plane tickets together,
buy you guys need to pay for it yourself.
Let me think about it.
I'll give you a reply by tomorrow. Is it alright?
Sister Ying, I'll leave now.
Alright.
This Cheng Ming is a bit troublesome.
Looks like she didn't believe it all.
However, have faith in me. I will certainly fix up this girl.
Where is it?
(Life &amp; Design)  (Transfers happiness)
Qu Shiyun!
Cheng Ming! What are you doing here?
Someone just now took my interview here.
Did it go well?
I am uncertain.
-What are you doing here?-I am also here for an interview.
But I am a little bit afraid.
Cheng Ming, how about you accompany me.
Let's go! Let's go!
-Is there anyone else?-Me!
I am here!
-What is your name?-Qu Shiyun.
-Come in.-You wait here for me. I'll be back soon.
-Alright. Do well!-Yes!
Hello! I am Qu Shiyun. I am final year student of Starry Art Academy.
I already sent you my profile and information earlier. Please take a look.
Director, here it is.
Yes.
Alright.
The director might be a little busy. Why don't you film an audition excerpt first?
Uh, alright.
This scene? Alright.  ♫  grow  ♫
It can't be replaced.  ♫  I know this ♫
♫  endless solitude is all for tomorrow  ♫
♫  I have no fear of the future or the present  ♫
♫  Whether it’s for a passing moment or my everlasting future  ♫
♫  I’ll build a lighthouse with my dre— ♫
Are you here for the screen test?
Oh, go ahead.
Cheng Ming.
You're done. How was the interview?
I didn't even get to finish introducing myself when the director left to make a phone call.
They want me to record a demo video. I don't even know if the director will watch it.
They'll surely look at it. Let's go back and wait there, okay?
Let's go.
- You Zhiqi!  - Cheng Ming!
You're ears are showing.
- Then, help me fix it.  - Let's go.
How was your meeting with the agent today?
After the interview, she arranged for us to meet again tomorrow.
So, I think the interview was pretty successful.
That good?
After I finished the interview, I bumped into Qu Shiyun. She was there to interview too.
She wanted me to go with her.
It was called...something like... Director Lin. Sounded like it was a big project.
Director Lin's work?
- Then, she won't get it.  - Why?
Because Director Lin does intense work, taking over 6 months to make his choices.
Every selection he makes is based his own impressions.
All the roles he chooses fits the person themselves.
He's that amazing?
When I was waiting for her today, someone came out to ask me whether I was there to interview.
At that moment, I was rehearsing a song and he spooked me.
You rehearse wherever you are.
Why didn't you go for that interview?
If you had, who knows, maybe the role would be yours.
- So you have to go see that agent again tomorrow?  - Yes.
But I don't think she's that reliable.
She said she'd take me to America to attend some...
Broadway theatrical performance training.
Broadway training course?
I don't know. She's called Situ Ying. Have you ever heard of her?
I think she seems like a liar.
But I still want to go; what if it's true?
That's no good.
I'll go with you tomorrow.
But, tomorrow, I've got a meeting to do some work with a producer. Never mind.
Let's do this. I'll put off that meeting and go with you.
Aiyo, You Zhiqi. You need to trust me.
I'm just afraid you'll be cheated and get scammed for some money.
I won't. Just relax and go have your discussions with the producer.
I just hope that the two of us can both become better and better.
So, you can't put off your own work because of me.
I am looking forward to seeing the gloriously radiant You Zhiqi.
Let's go.
Have you thought about this, Cheng Ming?
You need to know that this a rare opportunity.
I admire you very much; so I've kept this opportunity especially for you.
Sister Ying, I think that this matter
- must be...  - You're a student right now.
Opportunities for you right now are extremely important.
In order to express my good faith, I've brought the contract.
(Peach Entertainment Film and Television Production Company)  (Artist Contract)
So you're Sister Ying, right?
You You.
What are you doing here?
Isn't your greatest expertise in deceiving these kinds of inexperienced young girls
into signing a contract? Then, you take all of them and turn one of them into a star.
And you don't care about their special talents; just give them all makeovers so they're changed beyond recognition.
What?
Now you've become to lie to them about taking them to study abroad on Broadway?
I'm talking to an artist? What business is that of yours?
What I utterly detest is this kind of liar who messes around and pollutes our profession.
Fortunately, this one is a friend of mine.
You're looking for trouble.
I have no idea what you're saying. Cheng Ming,
I'm very sincere about this. I hope you will consider it carefully.
When you've decided, give me a call, okay?
You were almost cheated. She's a famous liar.
Sister You You, what are you doing here?
Didn't you tell You Zhiqi about this matter?
Today, there is a small budget moving looking for a music composer. He went to discuss that matter.
But he was worried about you. So, he asked me to come take a look.
Actually, I understood what was going on.
But being on Broadway is a dream of mine, so I still wanted to come and check it out.
You're not foolish. Fortunately, you didn't sign with her.
Otherwise, You Zhiqi would have gone crazy.
I'll answer this call.
Hello.
What? Director Lin chose me!?
- Director Lin.  - You You.
What are you doing here?
Haven't I brought this actress you've been looking for?
She's one of yours, You You?
We've been looking at masses of people from all over the country; we haven't been able to nail down the 2nd lead.
Why have you been hiding her?
I I hadn't bumped into her that day, I'd be dying of worry.
Director Lin, she's not my artist. She's my friend.
No need to quibble about whether she's your client. You've brought her today, so she's yours.
Young lady, what have you acted in?
I haven't acted in anything.
Nothing? Don't be nervous.
What I'm looking for is a blank piece of paper. We're looking for a 2nd female lead.
She's a music lover; someone who's obsessed with it.
Fortunately, that day I heard you singing. You gave me exactly that feeling.
Exactly what I've been looking for.
You aren't thanking Director Lin for giving you this opportunity.
Thank you, Director Lin.
That's settled then.
If there's nothing hindering this, Cheng Ming, you can immediately become one of our team.
Next week, we'll begin closed-door rehearsals.
Because in this piece, there are a lot of singing and dancing scenes.
Before that, you can become familiar with the role and prepare for it.
Director, what is the time period closed door rehearsals?
Right away.
- Approximately...for 6 months.  - Half a year?
- Half a year...is a little...  - Cheng Ming.
What are you talking about?
- Director Lin, can I thing about this?  - Okay.
You can think about it.
Cheng Ming, what are you thinking?
You need to take more time to consider this? This is a chance so many people can only dream of.
For a new person to be able to work on Director Lin's production is a huge leap upwards.
I know. But...I'm going to be in the graduate production very soon.
Wait Graduate Beijing opera?
I want to be in the graduate Beijing Opera. We're about to start rehearsing.
Cheng Ming, do you know how brutal this profession is?
So many people dream of getting a role as 3rd or 4th lead, much less this special, rare opportunity.
Even less so being the 2nd lead for Director Lin.
- I know, but I...  - Do you really?
Every year there are countless arts school students graduating. They'll remain unknown their whole lives because they don't get this kind of opportunity.
You must be every more aware of this than me, right?
Now, you've encountered such good fortune.
In our industry, how many would do anything to have this kind of opportunity? Do you understand that?
I do.
Sister You You, just let me think about it.
I can only give you 2 days. You must give Director Lin your answer day after tomorrow.
Once you've made a decision, there won't be any way to back out.
- Okay.  - Let's go.
You and You Zhiqi really were born with this same type of thinking.
(Student Apartment)
- Mom.  - Lili, what's so important?
Sit.
Li Li, your dad's already met with the leader of Haima troupe for you.
The leader already agreed
and said for you to join right after you graduate.
- You can be a leading lady. - Mom.
Why did you decide for me and not ask for my opinion first?
What I do is for your sake.
You never ask me what I think. I'm clearly starting at the same point as all of my classmates.
I'm not worse than anyone.
But you always make me stand out using these methods. Have you every considered what I think?
Can you use feelings to make a living?
Li Li, in the future, you're going to be the female protagonist of a large production.
This is the most realistic.
I don't want to join Haima.
I also don't want to be a female lead like this.
We're about to put on the graduation play.
I want to use my own efforts
to earn a good role.
Have your studies made you stupid, Fang Yali?
Do you know how much effort your dad put into this?
You can get into Haima and be the female lead. Why think about a graduation play?
Besides, if you want to act,
just have your dad recruit some friends and put on a show.
You'll still be the female lead, right?
Mom, do you know what I want?
You can stop making decisions for me.
I've had arrangements to have dinner with my friends. You can leave.
Fang Yali! Why don't you know what's good for you?
You're making me angry!
Why are you here?
Why do you look upset, Little White Rabbit?
You You already told me.
I'm stunned.
How did this opportunity fall onto my head?
Qu Shiyun called me just now and got so angry she cried.
I don't know how to face her.
Plus, do you know they're about to start half a year of private training?
It'll start immediately.
Rehearsals for our big show are about to start.
But I want to go.
I've completely given up the graduation show.
I know what you're struggling with.
Then what do you think I should choose?
Cheng Ming, what is your dream?
Where your heart is, that's where your dream is!
What are you doing? You look like an advertiser.
By the way, did today go smoothly for you?
At the start, it wasn't going smoothly.
Because of my different past identifies and reasons,
they don't really believe me. But!
I played them one of my songs and everything worked out.
Plus, a production team like them doesn't have much funding.
They can only use people like me.
What type of people are like you?
Our You Zhiqi is the best! Am I right?
Let me take this call.
Hello, Amy.
I...
All right, okay. I'll be right there.
Oh no, Amy told me to go to the diner. They prepared a celebration feast for me.
But Qu Shiyun will be there too.
What do I do?
We're gathering tonight for something special.
Cheng Ming got selected for a great role.
That's right, Cheng Ming. Congratulations!
You can surprise our top idol, You Zhiqi.
Congratulations, Cheng Ming.
Thank you.
Cheng Ming, you're so lucky.
I actually get to witness this movie-like plot.
Actually...
Before, when we did underground dance battles,
there would often be those dance god show off there skills at critical times.
It's normal. Today you win, tomorrow I win.
I think having a good attitude on this career path
is also an important lesson for you to learn.
Eat. Take care of your health.
As an actress, you need to maintain a confident mindset.
Cheng Ming,
now that you've gotten this great opportunity,
why does it feel like you're not happy about ti?
It's like this. First,
regarding this matter to Qu Shiyun,
I'm really sorry.
Second, I really
don't want to give up the graduation show.
What? What do you mean?
According to my knowledge, Director Lin's shows require half a year of private training.
If you join, then you won't be able to participate in the graduation show.
What's there to struggle about?
Of course, you need to film Director Lin's drama.
What are you thinking?
I also think Director Lin's show is more important. The opportunity is hard to come by.
Who knows? Maybe you'll make your debut.
I've thought it through, Cheng Ming.
Since you got the opportunity,
then you should make the best of it.
Think of me and give it your best.
If you don't do well, then you'll do me wrong.
Come on, come on, what's with the sad atmosphere?
No matter what, what happened today is a good thing.
We should wish our superstar Cheng Ming
a successful debut in advance. Here, cheers!
- Cheers! - Here, here. - Cheers.
- You can do it!- Best of luck!
Since everyone's here today, I'm happy.
So I'll share a rap I haven't sung in a while.
I'm going to start. Don't laugh at me.
Hey! Yo! Everyone is here and happy, Wei Feng isn't here.
Cheng Ming lives in melancholy, looking out the window.
You Zhiqi looks at Cheng Ming with excitement.
Qu Shiyun's not in the mood to eat.
Zhang Yiyong is currently serving food to Fang Yali.
It's a good script.
Professor, I love it.
I hope you hurry and refer me to meet them. I want to invest in them.
Plus, I want to see their graduation show.
It's all about youngsters chasing their dreams.
This script
makes me think of when I was young.
I want to have this film.
You're so impatient.
I'll arrange it for you. The child is good.
His name is Ding Dongdong. You must guide him well.
Rest assured, professor. You just worry about setting things up.
When I see potential, I get impatient.
Dongnan,
about Amy,
what are your thoughts?
After all, she's worked so hard looking for you all these years.
She's about to graduate,
you don't intent to come and watch?
- Professor Li.  - Wei Feng?
What's the matter? Come in.
There are still come questions about the admission information that I wanted to check with you.
Professor, since you have some work to do, I'll take my leave.
Don't be in a rush to leave. Let me introduce you.
This is Wei Feng, Amy's friend.
Hello.
Wei Feng, this is Mi Dongnan.
He's my student and Amy's father.
I know you've been helping Amy look for him.
Since you met, you should have a good chat.
Go ahead and ask what you want to ask.
Amy has been looking for you for four years.
Why don't you want to meet her?
Because of Amy's mom.
When she decided to go abroad that year,
I was a poor rascal at that time.
I didn't have the capability to give her the life she deserves.
Do you think now is a good time to disturb their lives?
But Amy has always wanted to see you.
As her father, shouldn't you give her an explanation?
All these years, I've actually been monitoring them.
It just...
without Amy's mother's agreement,
I can't just insert myself into her life.
All right, all done.
Daughter,
I made all these dishes,
are all your favorites.
Dad, your cooking skills is awesome.
Have some soup.
- You've worked hard. - It's nothing.
Take a look,
doesn't our daughter look skinner now?
You're being silly, she's gain some weight.
- Did she? - Tell us.
Why did you suddenly come back home?
What else? She's just coming to visit her home.
I gave birth to her, I can tell.
Since she's entered the house she has been very anxious.
Ming Ming, did You Zhiqi do something...
He dares?
If he dares to bully our Ming Ming, I'll go to the school right now and give him a good beating!
And then afterwards you won't have to be with him.
Dad, Mom, I came back to discuss something with you.
What? Tell me.
It is that Director Lin is casting for 'A Moment of time'. Did you knew about this?
It is all over the internet!
This Director Lin is someone who I admire a lot.
I have seen all his films. My girl, what is it?
This is very comical. The casting
must already be done.
I went for an interview.
Did you get turned down?
I passed.
You passed?
She passed it.
- What? - I got the second female lead.
Did you hear? Did you hear her?
Our daughter is amazing!
My girl, when later on you will join the group,
I'll come to meet the actors and also click a photo with Director Lin.
Isn't it great? I'll finally get to meet my idol.
What are you saying? Didn't you think properly?
She is studying musical theater. How can she act?
Director Lin is amazing! I have seen all his works.
-But right now she is just a student.-Child actors also work and grow up this way.
Mom! Dad!
Please don't quarrel! Mom!
Don't quarrel!
I haven't yet decided if I should or shouldn't do it.
If I go then I'll have to give up on performing in the Chinese Opera prepared for our graduation.
So right now even I am very confused.
I don't know what to choose.
From the bottom of my heart I hope that you can go.
Now, you have grown up.
You can make your own decisions.
There is a saying,
Live life like a chess piece and go down without any regrets.
No matter what you choose,
we both will always support you.
Finally, you gave a good reply.
I agree with your father.
Before, I didn't let you take the art entrance exams.
It was just because I was afraid that it would interfere with your good future prospects.
But as these years passed by
I saw that you are pursuing this with determination.
So I have decided
that in the future I won't meddle in your life.
About what was being said just now, don't take it to your heart since
I believe in you.
Dad! Mom!
Thank you!
Why are you being so polite to us?!
So very polite!
-Here, eat this.-Here, eat more!
-Alright!-I'll give you.
Now that you are back home, you must eat a lot! I'll be very happy to see you become healthy.
Here.
Professor Li, what are you doing here?
I saw that the lights were on so came in to check.
Why are you here all alone?
I think that it very quiet when all alone.
Are you bothered by anything?
I got a role as the second female lead in one of Director Lin's films.
But on the other side is the Chinese Opera which all of my classmates have sincerely prepared for our graduation.
They all will feel that I cherish more this opportunity of acting in the film.
But I think that the Chinese Opera which we are performing for graduation is also very important.
Right now, I don't know what to do.
Cheng Ming,
There will be many times
when you will find yourself at a crucial point in your life.
Right now your are faced a decision to
find a path that is suitable for you.
From the students who I have taught in these years,
there were some
similar to you who got an opportunity in the industry.
Some became very famous,
some
struggled at the bottom.
Because they didn't have time to practice their skills,
they had to leave musical stage
and couldn't find an opportunity to perform on stage.
But if you choose this opera,
you will become an opera performer
and will also complete your studies.
You should think about this carefully.
Which it is that you want to do the most.
Thank you Professor Li! I know what I should choose.
Cheng Ming!
-Professor Li, you are also here.-Yes,
I was just on my way back when I saw Cheng Ming sitting here. So I just came here to talk to her.
I was just thinking about how to comfort you.
But looks like you have already found your answer.
Now I already know what I have to do.
♫  When I let down my guard, I'm fascinated by dreams because of you  ♫
♫  Your appeal is making me forget to breathe  ♫
♫  I love you, so love you, I need you  ♫
♫  For you, I'll be persistent with stepping forward and not looking back  ♫
♫  I'm going to leave all my defenses behind me
♫  My obsession, thoughts of you can be perceived through my eyes  ♫
♫  In the end, you're the reason I'm relentless, it's okay  ♫
♫  I once secretly caressed your sleeves as I let my mind wander  ♫
♫  My love for you can no longer be concealed, our love will be our safeguard  ♫
♫  My heart  ♫
♫  When I let down my guard, I'm fascinated by dreams because of you  ♫
♫  Your appeal is making me forget to breathe  ♫
♫  I love you, so love you, I need you  ♫
♫  For you, I'll be persistent with stepping forward and not looking back  ♫
♫  I'm going to leave all my defenses behind me  ♫
♫  My obsession, thoughts of you can be perceived through my eyes  ♫
♫  In the end, you're the reason I'm relentless, it's okay  ♫
♫  I once secretly caressed your sleeves as I let my mind wander  ♫
♫  My love for you can no longer be concealed, our love will be our safeguard  ♫
♫  My heart  ♫
♫  I once secretly caressed your sleeves as I let my mind wander  ♫
♫  My love for you can no longer be concealed, our love will be our safeguard  ♫
♫  My heart  ♫