I'm afraid I'll be lost in the dark.
I'm going to forget the past.
I'm sure I won't be able to meet you.
I'll have the future.
I'm afraid I'll be lost in the dark.
I'm going to forget the past.
I won't give up.
I'll be lost in the dark.
I'm afraid I'll be lost in the dark.
The Star of the Moon
Episode 1
Are you going out?
You're going out to run around the sea in the New Year.
Do you think Grandpa can agree?
You should leave first.
I'll go up and talk to Grandpa.
I can still help you to make him happy.
Thank you.
Han Ting.
Happy New Year.
You're almost there.
You're sitting in the dining table.
Why are you still playing with your phone?
You're not working all day.
Why are you still looking at girls?
Don't worry.
If there's no girl, I'll be with you.
I'm happy to have a family with a smile.
Brother, don't say that.
I'm really in trouble.
Let's go.
I'm going to go to the kitchen.
Hello.
It's so late.
Okay.
Where's Xiaoting?
Didn't you go to ask her to eat?
She has something urgent to do.
What's wrong with this kid?
It's New Year.
She's not leaving after eating.
It seems to be about Xing Chen.
Xing Chen?
I've invested 20 million in a company.
It's okay if the money is transferred.
Now even people are transferred.
Xiao Yan.
You should help Xiaoting more in the future.
She just returned.
Don't let her lie to you.
I know.
Mom.
Take care of yourself.
Xiaoting.
She has her own business.
She has a share.
Okay.
Let's eat.
Eat.
Ji Song.
I've packed the food you want.
Take it.
Thank you.
Have a seat.
Why didn't you answer the phone?
The phone is out of battery.
You're looking for me?
I'm going back now.
Don't worry about it.
You're a big-time fan.
Why are you so scared?
If it weren't for Xiaohan,
we wouldn't have been able to find you.
Okay.
I know.
I'll go back and talk to you.
I don't know why my dad came here.
Sorry for bothering you.
It's okay.
You can just leave me alone.
Dad.
Mom.
Wake up.
Why didn't you tell me beforehand?
It's not your mom.
She didn't want to surprise you.
Wake up.
Xiaohan.
Uncle and aunt.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Mr. Han, give it to me.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
Go home.
Xinxing.
Xiaohan has been looking for you for a long time.
It's too late.
We can't go home hungry.
Exactly.
You know it's a long time.
Mr. Han is going home to eat your dinner.
Xinxing.
Xiaohan, didn't you arrange dinner?
I didn't arrange anything.
That's great.
We can eat together.
It's so hot.
Exactly.
Just so happen that you can drink with me.
Thank you.
Go to the door.
Let's go.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'll do it.
Don't move.
Come.
Come on.
I'll do it.
I'm too young to have a job.
Just treat yourself.
Xinxing.
Take care of Xiaohan.
You guys can sit here.
Okay.
I'll have a meal with him.
Okay, I'll call you.
So pitiful.
What's the name of the song?
It's called The Yellow.
It's a good name for raising.
This is the Yellow.
He's so fat, you can recognize him.
I'm so fat, you can recognize him.
Zhizhou, the show is about to start.
What are you doing in the house?
Mom, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
What's my job?
Sister Li,
Happy New Year.
I celebrate him a hundred years.
Something is strange.
What I said
has something impossible,
even from scratch.
Guan Huai constantly talentless self-insiruption
Too dumb
Sister Li
Which one of you
Here
Your takeaway.
Thank you.
Hello.
Hello, Sister Li.
Happy New Year.
Are you hurt by the taste of the egg?
I got it.
Why are you brainwashed on me?
I saw some pictures of you
at your girlfriend's store
and the logo on a cup cup.
I checked it.
When are you going to eat salmon rice ?
We must eat dumplings
during the New Year.
Meaning our two of us
agreed it won't help even a matter of years.
Take two.
Thanks.
I mean,
I'll pay you back.
Yes.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Sister Li,
why didn't you go home
for dinner last year?
You're the one who's got the dinner here.
I'll leave it to you.
Happy New Year, Zuzhizhao.
Happy New Year, Sister Li.
Bye.
Happy New Year, Zuzhizhao.
Are you awake?
Yes.
How do you think of Han?
He's a good guy.
Yes, he's a good guy.
I like Han more.
I think he's more happy
with us.
Welcome.
You're really a good guy.
Although Han looks like
no boss,
he's also a big boss.
Is it appropriate to be with him?
Our Xinxin is not bad either.
At least he's a female boss now.
Being alone in the new room,
being able to be with Han
is because of someone.
I don't know.
You're really
thinking about it.
It's true.
We really have to see the fate.
Besides,
we don't care about it.
What matters
is how the kids think.
He's the same.
You've never met him
for so many years.
You're so obedient.
That's because of my personality.
That's a good thing to remember.
Why didn't you see him last time?
Last time?
Come on.
Let's keep drinking.
Let's sing a song for everyone.
Come on.
Grandma, let me help you.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Let's play.
I don't know.
Maybe he doesn't want to see you.
I'm here to see you.
Didn't you say you'd been home for a year?
Now that the ability of the householder
is getting higher and higher.
If it weren't for Uncle and Auntie,
what are you going to do today?
I'm working overtime
and eating New Year's Eve dinner.
How do you know I'm waiting for breakfast on the New Year's Day?
Thank you for today.
Da Huang is getting fatter now.
He's so heavy.
You left when you said you'd leave.
If it weren't for me,
he would have gone to the New Year's Eve now.
Ten years.
I didn't expect to see you again.
Everything is fine.
It is.
Look at him.
He's so fat.
He knows how to eat every day.
He's so lucky.
Xin Xin, it's time to eat.
Coming.
Have a seat.
It's the 12 dishes.
They're both so good.
I didn't order so much.
Most of them were sent by President Xiao.
It looks like Mr. Han's face.
Come on, don't be so cold.
Let's eat.
Han, don't be shy.
Just eat at home.
Thank you.
That's right.
There are no rules in our family.
Be more casual.
Try this.
It's the best beef bowl in the world.
My dad made it.
You're a little boy.
Come on, Xiao An.
Come on.
Have a drink.
Uncle, I'm sorry.
I'm allergic to alcohol.
You don't drink alcohol?
If you don't drink alcohol, that's great.
Then drink it yourself.
Yes, I'll drink it myself.
I'll drink it for you.
Okay, drink it.
Come on.
This dish is delicious.
It tastes good.
But I don't think it's good last time.
Maybe it's the holiday.
They'll have a rest in turn.
If you want to eat,
tell me.
I'll contact the chef and make it myself.
Okay, okay.
Thank you, Mr. Han.
The family's holiday is so good.
Last year, we were with that...
So many dishes.
Eat it.
Here.
Let's start a new year.
Let's drink it together.
Yes, yes, yes.
Here.
Happy New Year.
Thank you for your work.
You made me look for it every morning and evening.
It's been a long time.
I'm so worried.
I'm doing well now.
Very good.
That's right.
I believe my daughter
will meet the right person.
That's right.
The right person is still behind.
Let's have another one.
Here.
Welcome Mr. Han to our house.
Thank you.
Try this.
My dad made it himself.
And this.
The old Chen Ji's vegetables over there are so delicious.
My dad brings them to me every time.
Try it.
It's delicious.
Here.
Xin Xin.
I heard that our new job
has a firework show on the weekend night.
After eating, you take Xiao Han to see it.
Don't stay at home.
I'll clean up your dad and watch TV.
We'll watch the show at home.
Yes.
I'll have a second-person meeting with your mom.
You go play.
Mr. Han, don't you go home to celebrate?
I celebrate with you.
Same.
Okay.
Come on.
This is Xin Xin's favorite,
the best.
Try it.
Thank you.
You have one too.
Let's have another one.
Welcome Mr. Han to celebrate with us.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Come on.
Hello, the mother-in-law of the live broadcast room.
Hello.
Welcome to my live broadcast room.
I'm your smart girl.
I'm your host, Zhu Dajia.
Congratulations on your big success.
Today, we're singing a special show.
We're going to introduce
the new year's dinner.
Dumplings.
These are all from Guo Guo.
This is carrot skin.
This is spinach skin.
This is the original flavor.
Guo Guo's buns are so great.
Yes, the buns are so beautiful.
Thank you for your praise.
If you're interested,
go to Guo Guo's special channel
to watch some videos to teach you how to make dumplings.
Ms. Han, why are you so scared?
Everyone is in the restaurant.
You're hiding here and playing with your phone.
Do you think it's appropriate?
It's so beautiful.
And...
Mr. Xiaomeng.
So you're watching Mr. Xiaomeng's live broadcast.
I'm not going to watch it myself.
It's from Ruan Jin.
Okay, I know.
I don't know Mr. Xiaomeng.
Do you think he's still in the live broadcast room?
Zhezhe Yan.
Listen to me.
I've never seen him live broadcast.
You go get me some hot water.
Go.
You're still going to watch it?
Just watch it for a while.
Go.
I haven't had a good son for a long time.
Don't take me.
Don't move.
I know.
So cute.
You can't see me.
If you're in love,
you must have this sugar.
Love is sweet and beautiful.
If you want to do business,
you must have this rice cake.
Do you know what it means?
It's a great opportunity.
There's also a cleaning bag.
It's detailed.
It's very professional.
This is the bag.
You must use the hard-to-use water
to disinfect the medicine.
Then you can put it in.
Can I get a paper?
Paper is not enough.
Baby, it's hard-to-use water.
Here,
you can have a good photo.
You can have a good photo.
I wish you all the best.
In a new year,
you can earn more money
by managing the garden and the garden.
It's like my secret.
Are you all busy?
It's late.
I'm not free to visit聰明.
There are few people in the live broadcast room.
It's not a bad thing.
It's a big New Year.
I'll give you a gift.
I'll give you a good rainbow.
Tell me about the gift.
It's okay.
I'm here.
Go ahead.
Wow!
It's so fair.
Thank you.
Thank you for the gift
Mr. Lu gave me.
I wish you all the best in a new year.
It's so nice.
So cute.
Thank you.
Thank you for
thanking Mr. Lu again.
Thank you for the gift.
Thank you.
In a new year,
you can earn more money
by managing the garden and the garden.
I'm so happy.
Okay.
It's late now.
We have to go to the drama with the family.
I'm going to play the game.
Bye.
See you.
Okay.
Thank you.
Happy new year.
Happy new year, boss.
Thank you.
I remember when I was in college,
I liked to buy the red-tripped food
at the entrance of the school.
Have you thought about where to move the new city?
Not yet.
I've found some places
that are full of rent.
Come again.
Dongyang?
You're kidding me.
The village is full of money.
I can't afford it.
There's a company
that invests in Dongyang
to invest in the city.
They're going to expand the economy.
You can use their previous office
to pay for rent.
You can take the loan.
Really?
Thank you, boss.
The work attitude of you
is good recently.
The original one is 8 million yuan.
You can pay me
the new one first.
I'll give you 4 million yuan.
Shen Deyin will pay you
to pay me
to pay you to pay me.
You're my angel investment.
I have a request.
Don't worry.
I'll make the product experiment
in a certain time.
I believe you.
I won't let you down.
I'm not afraid.
I hope you can
be more and more successful.
It's more important to be a fire-cracker.
Firecrackers are the most like
the firecrackers.
You can do everything
you want
Ji Qing.
I wish you a happy life.
Thank you, Mr. Han.
Don't call me Han Tian in the future.
Call me Han Ting.
Happy New Year, Han Ting.
So nice.
I just gave Mr. Xiaomeng
some gifts.
What's your expression?
Son,
look at Xiaomeng
receiving so many gifts.
How happy he is!
Ms. Han.
Who?
Who called me?
Why didn't you call me?
Who?
This house.
I can't do it.
I'm coming.
Who is it?
What's going on?
Don't you think
I'm interesting to him?
Don't misunderstand.
Will it get darker and darker?
It's a long story.
What do you want?
What's wrong with the car?
No.
I have to put my hand down first.
Don't be anxious.
I understand.
I know you're upset.
You'll regret it.
I'll give you the gift.
You're just
looking down on me.
You're so funny.
You don't have to return.
I'm happy.
Mr. Xing Xing,
the King is back.
Yes.
The King is still young.
He can't be sure.
Mr. Han.
Why don't you go upstairs?
I'm waiting for my colleague.
You go upstairs first.
You have to open the door.
I'll wait for them here.
It's okay.
I'll go.
Okay.
You're in a good mood.
After all,
I came back
after all.
It's different from the previous months.
You're out of breath.
A little.
Since I moved to Dongyang,
I've gained a lot of experience.
It should be
the newbie or the newbie.
But there's also a newbie.
It's full of dreams and energy.
And there's no bad news.
So the newbie
is the newbie.
He's a trainee.
What's this?
That's...
Fu Yangfei from 10 years ago.
After her life,
we'll have the half-gone course.
No, no.
I can raise a person like you.
You can raise a person like me.
I'll send him a life照.
I'll know his life condition.
Okay.
Wait a minute!
Wan'er.
This way.
That way.
이죠.
This way.
A little more.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Everyone admires you.
The legend is too exaggerated.
It's just your luck.
We're so close now.
We'll have a month-long break.
Okay.
I'm here.
Bye.
See you, Han Song.
Okay.
Han Song, bye.
Have a good day.
Sister,
why are you calling so early?
We're moving to a new house today.
Let me show you.
Is it big?
Right?
That's my office.
You have a great office.
It's so great.
Sister, come here.
It's your breakfast.
Come here.
What?
Your daughter's office.
It's so small.
Let's go there later.
Okay.
But Xinxin,
remember,
you must be careful.
Don't put the little thread on the ceiling.
We can't afford to pay Han Song.
Right?
Okay, I got it.
Who are you looking at?
Hello, aunt.
Hello, Lili.
You look good, too.
Thank you, aunt.
You two need to take care of each other.
We're at ease
if you can help Xinxin.
Xinxin is the CEO now.
She's the one who helps me.
We're helping each other.
Okay, I'll get back to work.
Bye, uncle.
Okay.
Bye.
Here's a new office for you.
Blue Wind Spirit, Xinxin.
Lili,
how do you know what I want?
Don't be so excited.
I bought a ticket for Su Zhizhou.
He's the one who sent it.
Why did you buy a ticket for him?
He didn't give you a gift
when he was in the New Year.
He gave you a bag
and gave me such a expensive bottle.
I don't want to owe him any money.
I'll give him a memory card
and a suggestion card.
It's useless to use it.
He should understand what I mean.
He won't waste time on me.
It's just pity on us.
Why don't you pity me?
Do you need pity?
I do.
You're so much more pitiful
than others.
That's right.
Get out of the street.
I'll go back to my new office.
Okay.
I feel like I'm dreaming.
I have my own office.
It's so big.
This is the dream.
Sister Li.
Mr. Li.
You guys talk.
I'll go back to work.
Give it to you.
My skincare products were too expensive.
Don't give me such expensive stuff.
This is your gift.
Thank you, Sister Li.
You're so thoughtful.
It's a suggestion card.
You...
Why did you tell me?
I should have guessed.
The most important thing in the gift is Li Shang.
It's not a surprise.
I'll go back to work.
Okay.
Thank you, Sister Li.
I'll go back to work.
Okay.
Thank you, Sister Li.
I'll go back to work.
The first gift card.
Sister Li, this is for my health.
Look who's here.
Xia.
Hello, everyone.
I'm back.
Sorry.
I was in trouble
when I left the most difficult time in Xing Chen.
Xing Chen is in a bad mood now.
Xing Jie is willing to take me back.
I invited Xia to come back.
She's in a good position in the big city.
But she's still willing to go back to Xing Chen
and start a new business with us.
Okay.
Welcome Xia to come back.
You're our technical consultant.
You'll be the top again.
Xia, hello.
I'm Li Li.
Welcome back.
Hello, Sister Li.
Xia.
You're still by my side.
We'll fight together.
Here, let me help you.
Thank you.
Here.
Okay.
We're in a good working environment now.
What else do we need?
To buy the soldiers.
Right.
Those who rejected our candidates
if they knew we changed
such a high-ranking shop,
they would have regretted it.
Actually, some candidates were pretty good back then.
They were professional.
How about we contact them?
What do you want to contact?
The job is to adapt to the environment.
Not to adapt to the environment.
They used to be a big fan of Xing Chen.
Now Xing Chen is a big fan of them.
That makes sense.
But I still have to ask you.
Don't use the talent of others
because of this little thing.
Use what you have.
Okay.
Remember.
Now you're getting more and more like a boss.
Let's look at the functions of each of us.
I'm mainly in charge of
the overall operation management of our company.
We're in charge of the technology.
We're small in size.
We're in charge of the technical support
to the intelligence report.
We're in charge of the acquisition of the power.
When we get the product,
we'll transfer it to the sales department.
Xing,
I'll take the company to the laboratory first.
Okay.
I'll go to the company first.
Let's split up.
Okay.
Let's go.
Did you hear that?
The company is in the field of technology.
They've helped Dongyang to get a big job.
They're on our floor.
Ji Xin is now a big boss.
I'm still giving people a big job.
Xing Chen got the investment of Mr. Han.
Ji Xin is Li Yu.
He's been born.
He's been doing business with our Mr. Zeng.
This is called the 30-year contract.
The 30-year contract.
The contract is also changing at any time.
Who can be sure?
It may not be the same as the first time.
Who?
Mr. Zeng.
Ji Xin.
I should call you Mr. Ji now.
Congratulations, Xiaoxian.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Xing Cui Pingye.
The original material.
Do you know who he is?
I don't know.
The new boss.
The famous Zeng Di.
He's the boss of the company.
Come to see us now.
Okay.
Take a seat, Zeng.
Kowtow to you.
No, I'm here to add oil to you.
Do it well.
It's from our Guang Hua department.
Don't touch our Guang Hua company's face these days.
I'll work my heart out
and never let you down.
I'm sincere.
Then I'll pretend to stand by.
Sure.
I'll send you.
Zhou Zhou.
Go and check this painting.
Xing Xing.
Is this painting real?
It should be real by Han Ting, right?
This painting's author is very rare.
This is his golden dance.
This is the painting he bought for me as a father in the past five years.
Xing Cui Ping.
The price of the purchase of this painting is
70,000.
I knew this painting would be so expensive.
We need money to sell it.
We can sell it right away.
Why are you writing it?
Well,
I'm just saying why I'm doing this.
don't touch it.
What if it's dirty?
Han is the one who sent it.
It's a flower.
It's love.
It's so nice.
Don't talk nonsense.
Well,
I don't have anything with Han Ting.
I don't think so.
Han.
Han, you want to see me?
Sit down.
How long have you been in the company?
It's been 13 years, Han.
I've been a assistant to Zhang Xing Hua for seven or eight years.
Ten years.
You have a good salary and a good career.
If you were the sales director,
what would you suggest to the management of the sales department?
Han,
I'm not a good person.
I'm quite jealous of my current state.
As long as I can contribute for the company,
I don't care about the quality of the goods.
The water is not a good thing.
I think you really have the ability to be a father for a lifetime.
Han,
thank you for your recognition of me.
But Zhang Xing Hua has a sense of honor for me.
Even if I resign,
I don't want to stand in his way.
I hope you can understand.
Han,
how are you going to deal with this?
Since he has a good person like you,
I think you should know
what to do to get the best result for him.
I see.
Thank you for your recognition, Han.
I'm sorry.
You have to understand.
My suggestion is not to harm him.
On the contrary,
I'm giving him a way out.
I believe that after you sit in his seat,
you can continue to act like a car.
You won't make the same mistake.
I...
If I agree to you,
Zhang Ke is in the east.
He forced me to leave.
He's been working in the east for 15 years.
As long as it doesn't affect the company,
I'll give him a comprehensive solution.
Lin, come here.
Come and take a look.
Look at this bag. It's so pretty.
What bag?
Look.
This one.
I bought it before.
It's a good one.
It's so good.
Yes.
This bag is so pretty.
It's so expensive.
I used it to make money.
It's not expensive.
It's all good for you.
Brother Su,
I can only help you here.
Hello.
How much is this bag?
It's a little bit more expensive.
I'll send you a gift.
What does a high-tech goods mean?
Is food and pictures the same?
Don't worry.
We're all craftsmen.
We're perfect for every detail.
Are you sure your bag
is the one I sent to the customer?
Dongqian, don't worry.
We've got the package and the certificate.
We'll be able to compare them.
How much is it?
So expensive.
It's the lowest price.
You'll know when you see our shop's sales.
The quality is guaranteed.
Okay, I'll go get the bill.
I'm afraid I'll be too scared to leave.
We'll leave half of it.
I'll give myself a full-time visit.
I won't be afraid to leave.
I'll have a hard time against the wind.
I'll break the law.
I'll be able to exchange feelings for the past.
I won't be able to leave.