I'm afraid I'll be lost in the dark.
I'll go to the end of the world.
There won't be a word of doubt.
I want to go to the end of the world.
But I won't give up.
I will have faith in time
Even if the bell rings
I do not know what have changed in the past 3 years.
Wait for now,
Water rich kids are much closer.
Suite is so small to me.
to enter the right content.
Don't go.
Is this what it looks like?
Once more.
Once again.
I have shown you a deep image of me,
again.
Please.
I wish to.
I don't want it anymore.
I don't want to be independent anymore.
I don't want to back consequence.
I don't want to see you.
Don't break up, okay?
You're going to bury me.
I'm not okay.
Why don't you leave?
I'm begging you.
Don't leave.
What do you want me to do?
I just bought a honeycomb.
Can you give me the meal?
You're not going to accept the code.
It's the same.
Is it convenient to call your friends?
What?
I'm not a bad guy.
I just sent the message back.
Hurry up.
It's too late.
Okay.
Send me the payment record of the honeycomb.
Go.
Take care of him.
Thank you.
In the meantime, let's live a happy life together.
It's म işteเสquiera awareness.
Is that right?
It's just that you don't,
anyone together...
What does it mean?
Why is it so hard to find a person like me now?
It's just...
you...
Because we are both here
Do you remember
what you did last night?
What did I do?
I can't recall
Where have I been?
I remember I was
drinking, drinking
And then
How did I come back?
An Tian sent you back
Han Ting?
You met him at the bar.
Then,
who changed clothes for me?
I did.
Okay, okay.
Then,
what's the big deal?
Don't you know how scary you were last night?
You made us three so angry.
You came yesterday.
Not us three.
It's me, Han Ting,
and an important person.
The one who met Mr. Lu
in front of Qiu Zi's house.
Oh, right.
I saw a lot of
Lu Ling's crisis
when I woke up this morning.
He said you were drunk.
He asked me for the address.
But I didn't get it
when I slept last night.
But he asked
Xiaomou's address later.
Forget it.
It doesn't matter.
Ji Xing,
do you know
you've been singing
all the time
after you drank too much?
I couldn't even pull it out.
I had to carry you back to your room.
What?
Take care of him.
Thank you.
Come on.
Let's continue drinking.
Let's sing a song for everyone.
Come on.
Okay, Ji Xing.
We've drank enough.
Okay.
Let's continue drinking.
Drink it.
What's wrong with me?
Okay, okay.
I won't sing anymore.
Okay, give me the wine.
I'll drink it.
Okay.
Don't make trouble.
I'll drink it.
Ji Xing, you're my eldest nephew.
You're my eldest nephew.
What eldest nephew?
I don't care who he is.
Thank you.
No, no, no.
Ji Xing, Ji Xing.
Come back.
I won't sing anymore.
I'll sing with you next time.
Okay?
No.
I'll accompany you
to continue drinking with you, okay?
Okay, okay.
Stop it.
Come back.
You're mad at me.
You've never told me
a word of hatred
for so many years.
You're mad at me now.
I'll sing it.
Let's sing a happy song.
Okay, okay.
Ji Xing, Ji Xing.
Come down.
Come back.
Which room?
Let's continue.
Come back.
Stop it.
Oh, no.
He must think I'm a psycho.
It's okay.
You've drunk too much.
It's normal.
But, Ji Xing,
why did you suddenly go to the bar
and drink so much?
Did you quarrel with Shao Yichen?
He came to the village in the morning.
He left in a hurry.
I didn't even have a chance to ask him
what's going on.
I didn't see you quarreling with Shao Yichen.
Why did he make you so angry?
We broke up.
What happened to
Brother Yichen?
You've been in a good relationship.
He said we're different from
the future.
But we've been in a relationship for four years.
How could we let it go?
Okay.
I'll go.
Okay, okay.
Don't ask.
Ji Xing, you're not awake yet, right?
Go to sleep.
Sleep for a while.
I think we should sleep for a while.
You broke up?
No.
I called Shao Yichen.
I...
Don't ask.
Ji Xing, he won't joke about this.
He said
Shao Yichen must have come
to a place where there's no return.
This is the past.
From now on,
you all don't mention Shao Yichen
in front of him.
Don't make him sad.
I'll go.
That's how we feel.
We'll decide together
before we start.
But one person
can decide to end it.
We've been friends for four years.
That's all.
We can't let it go
in my life.
I...
When will Xing Chen's new product
be released?
Do you have a plan?
I'll speed it up.
I hope you'll do your best.
Don't worry.
I'll see
the specific year of Xing Chen
before the New Year.
I'll do it.
Remember to have breakfast.
Otherwise, you won't get a rabbit.
I'll go.
Wait a minute.
I'll take the money.
Excuse me.
You can go.
Stand here.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Xing, don't run.
The scarf is gone.
The screen is about to start.
You forgot your phone.
You forgot your ticket.
I'll leave it to you next time.
Okay, I'll listen to you.
Let's go.
Let's go to the store.
Let's go watch a movie.
It's a weekend.
Don't stay at home.
You don't have a date today?
The one who wants to date
is not free on weekends.
Xing Xing is not at home.
He has to work overtime again.
He said that
the investor is urging him to work.
He has been working for a long time.
He can't stay here.
He's going to be a good guy.
To him,
the tiredness on work
is not as painful as the pain on feelings.
He and Shao Yicheng have been talking for so many years.
They are family.
It must be very uncomfortable to be alone.
So he is getting busier now.
He is not thinking about it.
It makes sense.
Xing Xing has been working all over the body.
He must not have the energy to look for Yichen.
He is now busy.
The company is not as good as the normal one.
So,
Mr. Han is Xing Xing's girlfriend.
Mr. Han,
I've done some research these past few weeks.
I found that
there are still many problems with the commercial planning.
I will report to you
after I finish the repair
in the annual planning.
Okay.
Boss,
Mr. Qi hasn't come to report to us recently.
Do I need to check the progress?
No need.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Are you here for the meeting?
You know everything, right?
I know
how you feel about the four years.
You must be very reluctant.
But I know Xing Xing very well.
He is a stubborn and coward.
Since he can't go back,
you must make the decision.
I understand.
He is very strong.
As long as he is determined,
he will do well.
I will break up with him.
I believe he will come out.
Brother, you...
I am fine.
I just...
I just need some more time.
But you are so excellent.
You should think about
your work.
You should work harder
when you are in a relationship.
But you should drink less coffee.
It will make you lose weight.
Okay.
Is it convenient?
I will go to your office later.
I have some questions about the materials.
Please teach me.
Okay.
Let's go.
This way.
What's wrong?
It's okay. The water pipe is broken.
I will find someone to repair it.
The new generation of Hanhai
is pursuing the fusion of the oil and gas products.
It has been released to the public.
What is the medical center?
What are you going to do
with Xing Chen?
Don't talk to me.
Xing Chen is completely
in sync with Hanhai.
The faster Hanhai is developing,
the more pressure Xing Chen has.
The fish is bigger.
Xing Chen just started.
I am worried that your sister
will make excuses for Xing Chen
and make you suffer.
Without Xing Chen,
will my sister let us go?
At least she won't be like
now.
If I knew it,
I wouldn't have asked you to vote for Xing Chen.
Don't worry.
Xing Chen has his own way to go.
That's enough.
You should comfort yourself.
I advise you.
You should invest more in love.
And invest more in investment.
Let Xing Chen be the one to do it.
I am still saying that.
I have no use for it.
You are so stubborn.
The evolution of Hanhai
is not clear.
You are not clear?
When Hanhai's products
are released,
I will not have to
talk to Dong Shihui about it.
The market will force Xing Chen to die.
I have confidence in my machine.
You are not eating?
Hanhai's products are released.
I am willing to not let
Xing Chen find a chance to do it.
You are in the office?
Meeting.
Boss,
you are so busy
for the sake of things.
Mr. Yuan is still in the high-ranking meeting.
And the high-ranking members.
It's always raining.
I can't do anything.
They only care about their own interests.
They only care about the result.
There is nothing wrong.
But Xing Chen
is really going to speed up.
He is going to get the result soon.
Otherwise,
all the pressure will be given to you.
You can't always
be so worried about them.
Have you ever lost your mind?
Of course.
How long do you want to leave?
A month or two.
But even if I lost my mind,
it won't affect my job.
A month or two?
Mr. Han,
Xing Chen's annual planning plan is done.
You can come to your meeting
when you are free.
Today,
it's 6.30 p.m.
Okay, I will come at the right time.
It seems that you don't need to be so long.
Go back and practice.
You need to see your ability.
I am going to practice.
No,
I will go to work now.
Come in.
Mr. Han.
Finally, Mr. Ji.
I thought you were not Xing Chen anymore.
I am sorry.
I drank too much that day.
I said he was drunk.
Drunk?
Obviously after the meeting.
The Treason
Come on.
It's okay.
Let's go to work.
Okay.
Come on.
This is the plan plan for next year.
I'll send you the e-mail of the e-mail.
This is the paper version.
You can print it.
The creator is not only working hard,
but also physical.
I hope you can quickly adjust your state.
Don't be 45 cm in height.
Otherwise,
I'll think about the next one.
Do you want to be printed?
Is there such a requirement?
Why do you have to be 45 cm in height?
You just want to be printed and print,
which means...
just one cloud won't consistent with the next phase.
Yown!
forcing you down!
Could wezione a little while more v lamb knee dance?
Maybe next year.
No need. I have something else to do.
Okay.
Did you come out?
You're back.
Let me see.
Really?
You girl.
If I didn't call Yichen,
I wouldn't know you broke up.
Why didn't you tell your dad about it?
I don't want you to worry about it.
We're the ones who don't say anything.
Look at you.
You've been in a lot of trouble.
You didn't tell me about it.
You quit your job.
You're in a serious business now.
You're even more serious.
We don't know
if you're doing well.
You can only worry about your family.
I'm really worried about you.
Come and see me.
Okay. I'm wrong.
Don't talk to me.
Okay.
Are you hungry?
Yes.
I brought you a lot of delicious food.
It's hot.
Wash your hands first.
I'll eat it right away.
We'll talk later.
Where's Tu Xiaomeng?
He said he had an appointment with a friend.
He's out.
He's not in the mood.
OK.
I'll call you back.
I'll be back.
I'm gonna go get some tea.
Bye.
I'm sorry.
You can go.
Let's go.
I'll go.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
No, no.
I'll make soup for you.
Why are you here?
I know you're still awake.
I brought you some salt.
Please.
How is it?
Do you like the style of Zhou Xue?
I knew you wanted to go back to China
to find a house for you.
You've been
in the sofa for several times.
You're always good.
You should take care of yourself.
The sofa is for you to sit there
and relax and rest.
It's not for you to work overtime.
Come here.
Come on, try it.
Do you like it?
The moon is bright.
Ting Zai Zhou, your favorite.
Her char siu,
char goose,
and other things.
They're all good.
Try it.
It's all your favorite.
I heard the board of directors
has been in trouble lately.
Don't be too stressed.
I talked to Dr. Jiang.
He gave me a lot of inspiration.
He also recommended some excellent talents to me.
I believe that Xiao Bai will have
a breakthrough in the second stage.
When I show you the report,
will you be stressed?
You did a good job.
But Xiao Bai doesn't need to be the director.
You can just move on.
I'll listen to you.
I...
Actually,
I have something to ask you.
Go ahead.
I want to ask Dr. Jiang Huai
to be our consultant in the department of technology.
I'll talk to Dr. Jiang.
Really?
Thank you.
Look at me.
I told you to have a good rest
and eat well.
I said I had to work again.
The fish is so pretty.
Who gave it to you?
Grandma Gu gave it to me.
It's a pity that you can't control it.
How about I choose
some beautiful fish tomorrow?
No need.
The fresh sauce is good.
It's also good.
The water is the best.
The fish is good.
It's good.
Come and have some soup.
Here, let me measure it on tank first.
You go the rest.
What you say can be easily.
It's a COMM是 for Wednesday
and there must be
a hospital for week-end聚集班.
Don't be afraid.
It will be difficult to get your heart.
but that you're from a capital house.
Move the back請.
Staying Here, I don't upright work.
Where is it?
Where is this picture?
You are...
I found it.
Okay, okay.
Come back soon.
You are Su, right?
I am Xin Xin's mother.
Xin Xin mentioned you to me.
You investors are so true.
Let's go.
You are working overtime on weekends.
If you young people
are busy,
no matter what,
I can't finish this job for you.
Give me your hand.
You are not feeling well.
So you must eat and drink more.
Come in, Su.
You ordered the delivery, right?
Young people like to eat delivery.
I tell you,
you can't do this in the future.
If you don't have any benefits for your body,
come on, thank you.
Help me wash the strawberries.
Okay.
Come on.
Hurry up.
What's wrong?
Oh my god.
The water pipe is broken.
Come on, wipe it.
Okay.
I have wet your clothes.
Change your clothes.
Don't catch a cold.
It's okay.
It will be dry soon, aunt.
You didn't get wet in the company, right?
I tell you, young people like you,
there is a change in the world.
Why do you have to get wet in the company?
Come on.
This is the new dress I brought for you.
No need, aunt.
No need.
Listen to me.
If you catch a cold,
your parents will be so sad.
Change it.
I chose the big one.
You can wear it.
Dad.
You young people.
Don't get wet in the company.
I can't tell you now.
When your wife gets sick,
you will regret it.
Mom.
You are back.
Come back for dinner.
Hurry up.
Mr. Han.
I'm back.
Fallen river is broken.
I have becauseststood.
Thanks.
Xuxi.
You called Mr. Han that,
is it Xiaosu?
What Xiaosu?
He's the head of my company,ider North and Mr. Han.
Then, I just called Xiaosu,
how come you didn't call別 home?
Then, it must be possible
for someone to give you a chance.
What did you say to me when you were in your brain?
Go wash your hands.
Han, let's go.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Come on, let's eat.
Don't be polite.
Just call me Han.
Okay.
Actually, I came here
to give Ji Xing a gift.
Thank you.
You eat.
I'll go first.
Han, don't go.
You're just a thief.
Besides,
I guess you're not in trouble
with your heart.
Hurry up.
Han, let's eat here.
Look at all the dishes.
Try my mom's cooking.
You eat so many dishes.
How can we eat them?
Okay.
Come on, sit.
Han.
Thank you, aunt.
Have some more.
You're too thin.
You have to keep it.
Okay.
Can you sell it on a Sunday?
No, I can't.
But I can pack it.
It's delicious.
Unfortunately, I didn't eat it last time.
Mom, try it.
It's not good to have your mom
cook it on a Sunday.
Han, you're eating
my cooking.
She cooks it well.
I'll eat it myself.
It's delicious.
Han,
are you a local?
You're a big boss.
You're usually busy.
You can have time
to eat with your mom.
Mom,
Han is busy.
Don't ask him.
Let him eat well.
Okay.
My parents are dead.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
It's old.
Well,
after dinner,
we can add a WeChat.
Okay.
You have time
to eat when you're here.
You can cook whatever you want.
Han is
a kind of kid who doesn't let others worry.
Unlike you,
my heart is beating fast.
He's naughty.
And he's very gentle.
I remember when I was a kid,
I saw his writing.
He said that my mom
looks like a hard-working man.
Okay.
Xin Xin,
can you tell your mom
what's better?
What's the good thing about it?
How beautiful it is!
What do you think of it?
Our teacher said
he didn't let me make a scene.
At that time,
he was changing his teeth.
He was alive.
Don't talk about it.
It's so funny.
I remember
when I was a kid,
I saw him looking for a picture.
Why didn't you know?
I didn't know.
Don't.
Look at him.
You didn't know?
He was so mad.
What did he think?
You didn't think of anything.
Who didn't think of anything?
He was so mad.
I think he's like that.
He's like that.
He's so mad.
How many things do you want?
I'll bring them to you.
No need.
We can do it ourselves.
Mom.
Kids.
Thank you.
It's okay.
I'll go open the door.
See you later.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
My mom is used to
packing all the leftovers home.
I'm in trouble.
It's okay.
Come on.
I'll bring them to you.
Let's go.
Mr. Han.
Thank you so much.
I didn't expect you
could even embroider a dragon head.
What's the big deal?
After all, I've been living
in China alone for more than ten years.
Alone?
Didn't your grandpa
accompany you?
I was with you when I first arrived in Germany.
I didn't come back
because I was busy with the country.
Did you eat a lot of food?
I didn't eat much.
You're not like this.
Here.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'll wash your clothes
as soon as possible.
It's okay.
I won't.
I'm sorry, Mr. Han.
I didn't see you
so stubbornly.
Don't blame me.
I won't.
You always wear a bright and bright color.
A bright and bright color.
You're not like a good painter.
I'll look after you
when I get back.
You should go back and rest.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
I don't want to see you again.