♪I waited through spring rain,
summer heat♪
♪Autumn leaves, and winter frost♪
♪But I never got to be with you♪
♪To plant flowers
across all four seasons♪
♪I watched sunsets blend into the night♪
♪Waited as the moon drifted,
Milky Way shifted♪
♪Still, I never stayed with you♪
♪Through the dark,
seeing a world so bright♪
=The Secret Contract of the Witch=
=Episode 8=
Do you still trust Xia Mo now?
Come on in, please.
This way.
Take a seat.
- He's quite the looker.
- So handsome.
This is the famous Astrophysics PhD,
young and talented.
Hey, are you here alone?
Come home with me.
I could take care of you.
Hey, you're really good-looking.
Wanna hit the gym with me?
You look great, honestly.
Don't be shy now.
Chat with us a bit.
- Yeah, come on.
- Seriously.
So, are you both happy with this?
- Of course.
- Yeah.
- Super happy.
When can we get our license?
- Exactly.
- Talk to us a bit.
That's enough.
I said enough!
Why did he yell at us?
Is something wrong with him?
Xia Mo, what is this for?
Weren't you the one who said,
love makes people lose their minds
and just get led around?
When you fall for someone else,
you'll do as I say
and help me with the contract.
Xia Mo.
- So many types.
- What do you mean?
None of these are your type.
Do you think the love I mean
is about all this stuff?
Alright then.
Sorry, ladies.
Seriously.
Boring. You're a real mood killer.
Bye.
Do you really think this is fun?
Yeah.
I do think it's fun.
What do you actually want?
I thought you'd get it after all this,
but actually,
we can't even see eye to eye.
I have no idea what you're saying.
On the surface,
you brought Xiaoyan hope.
But in reality,
you hurt her even more.
Is there a problem with that?
I've lived here for over a century.
I've seen it all by now.
I helped them get what they wanted,
so how is that wrong?
♪Tell me, what am I seeking?♪
But what about Tao?
Does he want to forget Xiaoyan?
Is this truly what he wants?
Tao?
Yeah.
If he ever learns the truth
that hope came
at the price of a life,
how could he repay that?
What are you talking about?
♪Falling somewhere in between♪
I thought we truly knew each other,
but now I see,
we're just from different worlds.
♪In my heart, there's a question♪
Hello?
I'm Xiaoyan's attending physician.
Xiaoyan?
♪Have my efforts been needed?♪
Xiaoyan has passed away.
Before she left, she asked me
to hand this to you
in person.
(Cornea Donation Consent Form)
This is the outcome you wanted.
Are you satisfied now?
It's him.
You gave his feelings back.
Why didn't you tell me?
(Cornea Donation;
Authorized Recipient: Xia Mo)
Xia Mo.
We'll come back.
Together.
I thought you'd get it after all I said,
but actually,
we can't even see eye to eye.
I thought we really knew each other,
but now it seems
we're from totally different worlds.
Xia Mo.
Xia Mo, are you okay?
You're awake.
Why am I here with you?
You just coughed up blood.
Don't you remember?
Really?
Yeah.
What's going on here?
(I think I got hit by backlash)
(from changing Xiaoyan's contract.)
(I ended up with temporary amnesia.)
It's fine.
I'm totally okay now.
Seriously?
Yeah.
This is for you.
I don't need it.
My phone number's inside.
You can reach me anytime.
Aren't you the one who'll need me?
Don't you need me at all?
If I want to find you, I will.
Alright then.
I usually don't take gifts.
I'll make an exception.
Do you know how to use this?
It seems pretty easy, right?
Xia Mo, are you free tonight?
No.
What is this place anyway?
My hair's getting all messed up.
Just wait a sec.
You'll love this.
So, what do you think?
Not into it?
Did you set this up?
Yeah, I did it all.
It's just okay.
But this, you'll really like.
♪On nights when I can't sleep♪
Seriously, you'll like it.
Telescope!
♪Lost in restless thoughts alone♪
I can see the Milky Way.
And even Orion.
What's it like over there?
♪But I can't catch the light♪
Just like here,
it's beautiful.
Even more beautiful than you?
♪Loving with all my heart
leads to letdown♪
I envy you.
Your lifespan is so long.
Not like us,
we're more like fireworks,
never knowing what comes next.
An accident and I could be gone.
♪Your eyes hold a steady gaze♪
As people here always say,
"No one knows what tomorrow brings."
Xia Mo,
tell me,
can contracts grant any wish?
Is that really true?
If you pay the price, yes.
So I can trade my life for my parents' life.
♪Please remember how the Milky Way burns♪
Xia Mo,
can I trust you?
Yes, you can.
♪You're the one who shines the brightest♪
Eyes,
aim,
bullseye,
all lined up together.
Picture your least favorite person,
then let it go.
Slow your breathing,
like you're stalking prey,
just relax,
and shoot.
That's good.
But it's not enough.
I need to take him down.
Who made you this mad?
Someone who should've been gone years ago.
He doesn't deserve to be here.
When I see you mad at someone else,
I can't help but get jealous.
You should be thinking about me.
Want me to take you down with a shot?
Go ahead.
Come on.
Don't chicken out.
Aim right here.
♪On nights when I can't sleep♪
♪Loneliness fills my heart♪
♪Lost in restless thoughts alone♪
♪The moonlight shines down the hall♪
♪Like a land of tender solace♪
♪But I can't catch the light♪
♪When I struggle so hard alone♪
♪Loving with all my heart
leads to letdown♪
♪The grown-up world feels so tense♪
♪Then you show up by my side♪
♪Stay with me through thick and thin♪
♪Your eyes hold a steady gaze♪
♪I keep that look close to my heart♪
♪If you happen to look at the moon too♪
♪Let the moon say what I wish to tell you♪
♪All those simple moments we share♪
♪Are honestly all I ever wish for♪
♪If you happen to look at the moon too♪
♪Please remember how the Milky Way burns♪
♪In this endless sea of people♪
♪You're the one who shines the brightest♪