♪I waited through spring rain,
summer heat♪
♪Autumn leaves, and winter frost♪
♪But I never got to be with you♪
♪To plant flowers
across all four seasons♪
♪I watched sunsets blend into the night♪
♪Waited as the moon drifted,
Milky Way shifted♪
♪Still, I never stayed with you♪
♪Through the dark,
seeing a world so bright♪
=The Secret Contract of the Witch=
=Episode 22=
I'll cut the brisket like this.
Chop the tomato into pieces first.
Wait, that's not right.
Don't cut it yet.
You need to peel it first.
♪When the day stops♪
♪We'll play our favorite songs♪
♪With heart and soul♪
♪Dancing with the moon♪
♪When my dreams get so hazy♪
♪And sky becomes gray♪
♪You'll be the one to guide♪
♪On nights when I can't sleep♪
♪Loneliness fills my heart♪
♪Lost in restless thoughts alone♪
♪The moonlight shines down the hall♪
♪Like a land of tender solace♪
♪But I can't catch the light♪
When will the shooting stars show up?
They said in about half an hour.
That's the best time to watch.
That's a long wait.
Catching shooting stars is tough.
Couples everywhere are waiting too.
Do you think they wait like this?
Or maybe they wait holding each other?
♪I keep that look close to my heart♪
♪If you happen to look at the moon too♪
♪Let the moon say what I wish to tell you♪
Now that's more like it.
A meteor shower is really romantic.
I want you to feel it too.
That kind of passionate love.
But not every love needs to be intense.
I think what we have now is perfect.
♪You're the one who shines the brightest♪
No,
I just want to give you the best things
in the world.
So you can be even happier,
and smile even more.
♪When I struggle so hard alone♪
A shooting star.
Where is it?
♪The grown-up world feels so tense♪
♪Then you show up by my side♪
♪Stay with me through thick and thin♪
♪Your eyes hold a steady gaze♪
♪I keep that look close to my heart♪
♪If you happen to look at the moon too♪
♪Let the moon say what I wish to tell you♪
♪All those simple moments we share♪
♪Are honestly all I ever wish for♪
♪If you happen to look at the moon too♪
Sorry about that.
You didn't get to see a shooting star.
It's not your fault.
The clouds are just too thick.
We can try again next time.
I just don't know when that'll be.
Maybe next year.
Or maybe even now.
♪If you happen to look at the moon too♪
Look, a shooting star. Make a wish.
Mu Hanyu.
I hope from now on,
you eat well,
sleep tight,
and take care of yourself.
♪Please remember how the Milky Way burns♪
Xia Mo,
I hope
♪In this endless sea of people♪
we can always stay together.
Mu Hanyu,
meeting you
has been the best thing for me.
I hope from now on,
you keep chasing your dreams
and leave the sadness behind.
(Lane 66)
Xinyi.
Gone again?
Xinyi!
(Lane 66)
Xinyi.
I know you're here.
Xinyi, come out now.
No matter what comes our way,
we'll face it together.
(Lane 66)
Don't be scared.
I'll shoulder this with you, okay?
Xinyi,
I'll wait for you to come home.
(Mo, I know I was wrong.)
(I need to make up for what I did.)
(Lane 66)
(Mu Hanyu should know that J is still alive.)
Xia Mo.
(I saw her come in.)
Are you here to see her?
Yeah.
Is she not here?
Don't you usually call her first?
She brings you into the bar.
I already reached out to her.
She hasn't replied to me.
I came over because I was worried.
Even though the rose petals stopped falling,
her pain just got worse.
She doesn't have much time left.
Rose petals?
Oh, right.
You were the last one to see him.
He...
Is he really gone?
Did he say anything before he died?
Did he ever mention me?
You care about him a lot.
No.
I just want to know.
Was it painful when he died?
Did you want him to suffer,
or not suffer at all?
Of course, I wanted him to suffer.
I hope he suffers when he goes.
You hate him that much.
He deserved it.
I know you're worried about Mo.
I believe in you.
You'll finish the contract and save her.
Come on, let's go.
I'll take you into the bar.
Xinyi.
Hanyu.
What brings you here?
I was a bit worried about you.
So I came to check on you.
Are you alright?
I'm fine, really.
How did you get in?
Xinyi helped me get in.
I knew she'd come back.
But she's still avoiding me.
She...
She actually cares about you.
She worries you don't have much time.
She asked me to save you by the contract.
As long as you agree,
I'm willing.
What's up with you today?
Didn't we agree to face this together?
Did you forget?
How could I, babe?
I just want you
to keep living well.
Babe?
♪On nights when I can't sleep♪
♪Loneliness fills my heart♪
♪Lost in restless thoughts alone♪
♪The moonlight shines down the hall♪
♪Like a land of tender solace♪
♪But I can't catch the light♪
♪When I struggle so hard alone♪
♪Loving with all my heart
leads to letdown♪
♪The grown-up world feels so tense♪
♪Then you show up by my side♪
♪Stay with me through thick and thin♪
♪Your eyes hold a steady gaze♪
♪I keep that look close to my heart♪
♪If you happen to look at the moon too♪
♪Let the moon say what I wish to tell you♪
♪All those simple moments we share♪
♪Are honestly all I ever wish for♪
♪If you happen to look at the moon too♪
♪Please remember how the Milky Way burns♪
♪In this endless sea of people♪
♪You're the one who shines the brightest♪