(Butterflied Lover)
(Episode 9: Family)
Father.
Why did you call me so urgently?
You unfilial son!
How dare you act clueless and ask me why I call you here!
You have been flaunting your authority at the court,
and I've turned a blind eye to it,
but you are trying to marry the princess forcefully.
What intention do you have?
I have no other intentions.
I like the princess.
Nonsense!
How many times have you seen the princess?
Father, I've made my decision.
I must marry the princess.
If you are free on the wedding day,
remember to come and have a drink at the banquet.
I'm not done yet!
Come back!
Won't you have dinner first before you leave?
(Did the black peonies soup completely fail?)
The princess is here!
Your Highness.
Qian Yue!
- Qian Yue. - Your Highness.
You better stay away from me.
Qian Yue, did you recover from your cold?
Cold?
I'm feeling much better.
- Thank you for your concern, Your Highness. - That's great.
Qian Yue.
I'm getting married.
Married?
I see. You are going to marry Marquis Wu An.
Yes.
I want to marry the one I love.
Everyone in the palace is afraid of him.
I have no one to tell my joy to.
So, I'm here to tell you.
You look so happy.
I'm sure you like him a lot.
In that case,
I will use tea instead of wine
to congratulate Your Highness.
Thank you, Qian Yue.
It's getting late.
I'm going back then.
If He Xi realizes that I've sneaked out, he will start nagging again.
I only need one more day.
No. Just a while longer.
Whether it's another day or a while longer,
you still failed.
Madam Yuan, are there any other ways?
Drink this soup.
- This is... - Just an ordinary ginger soup to get rid of your cold.
It doesn't help much.
Your Excellency.
This is not the "Book of Curses".
This should be the "Book of Million Curses".
My back hurts and I have a headache.
You don't even blink. Aren't you tired?
Search every word.
Don't talk to me before you find the word "butterfly".
Yes.
Black peonies soup.
Madam Yuan.
Can I still drink black peonies soup again?
The Butterfly Curse was a secret technique
used to save people by the witch doctors of Yilan.
I didn't expect it to be used
to harm countless people right now.
As long as there's a chance,
I will definitely help you.
Three years ago, you came to me.
I gave you black peonies soup,
and it made you suffer in pain for seven whole days.
Haven't you had enough?
If I can become normal,
even if I have to suffer the pain ten times,
I'm still willing to do it.
Madam Yuan,
is there really no other way?
When a living person is planted with the Butterfly Curse,
he will become a slave.
Butterfly Slaves are as vicious as beasts.
Butterfly Curse can be removed when the Butterfly Slaves
drink black peonies soup.
Your Excellency, there's a cure for the Butterfly Slaves.
Before the curse is removed, one must overcome
the seven days of heart-piercing pain of black peonies soup.
After experiencing death...
Where have you been the last seven days?
Your Excellency,
can I not tell you?
(Heart-piercing pain.)
(Experiencing death.)
(You have been suffering so much for the last few years.)
Qian Yue!
(You went missing for seven days)
(because of me.)
Chang Feng.
You are back.
Your Excellency!
Why did you come back so late today?
What's wrong?
(How did you overcome the suffering for seven days?)
(Your hope is crushed after three years.)
(You must have felt so much despair.)
Have you eaten?
Let me heat up...
Qian Yue.
You are my wife.
You are the most important person in my life.
No matter when, where, or in what situation,
I will never give you up.
I know.
Chang Feng, you looked troubled since last night.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
It seems like many things happened
over the last few days.
Are you worried about me?
It's fine.
I am in front of you just fine, am I not?
I've been doing well in the last few years.
I don't think anything will happen in the future.
It's fine even if I'm not a normal person.
Perhaps it's just temporary.
In the future,
it will get better.
It will get better.
Soon,
something auspicious will happen.
Something auspicious?
Princess Bao Zhu is getting married.
To whom?
Marquis Wu An.
Marquis Wu An?
My second brother?
Why would he marry Princess Bao Zhu sincerely?
You are so nice.
I'm sure your second brother is a very nice person too.
The Yilan Tribe proposed to Princess Bao Zhu back then.
The late emperor did not want Princess Bao Zhu to get married
because she was too young,
so my sister was made into a princess to replace her.
Unexpectedly,
the Yilan Tribe turned my sister into a Butterfly Slave
and sent her to the underground.
Father, I got the Kirin Blood!
Sister!
The commander shot her himself?
Yes.
Since then,
Chang Jin hated the Yilan Tribe.
So, I think he wants to marry Bao Zhu
because he has an ulterior motive.
It has been many years since that incident.
I think he has let it go.
Bao Zhu looked so happy.
I think this will be a good marriage.
I hope so.
Qian Yue.
You must not let my second brother find out about your identity.
I'm afraid he will look into your background.
I understand.
The princess also got someone
to send us the wedding invitation a few days ago.
However, I can't attend.
Chang Feng.
Help me take this gift
to the princess.
Sure.
I want to take a quick peek at the princess.
Can I?
Congratulations.
- Thank you. - Congratulations.
You are too polite.
Marquis, make a toast to everyone.
Chang Feng.
There are many people inside. It's very lively.
I think your brother is sincere towards the princess.
Don't worry.
I hope so.
Why don't I get down, so you can climb up and take a look?
No.
I don't want to.
Fine. I'll help you see.
Come. The marquis is making a toast to everyone.
(Marquis Wu An's Residence)
Commander.
- Softer. - Since we are already here,
why don't we just go inside?
We are just passing by.
I don't think it's necessary to go inside.
I think we just took a detour.
Besides, I am the commander of the empire.
If I go inside without getting an invitation from them,
isn't it too embarrassing?
There's nothing inside.
Nothing.
How boring.
- Let me hold you. - Be careful.
Come.
Be careful.
It's a pity that I didn't get to see the princess.
If you can't see her, I'll go to the roof
and take off a piece of tile.
Sure.
- Commander? - Commander.
He didn't give you two an invitation as well?
However, isn't this a little dangerous?
Sang Qi, let's go.
I'm the only one without an invitation.
I'm the only one who got hurt.
He Xi.
When will the banquet finish?
It looks lively outside.
When will the marquis return?
My precious Princess Bao Zhu.
The marquis is a cruel man.
A few days ago, he just got rid of He Ying a few days ago.
You must be careful in the future.
The marquis will also be soft-hearted.
Oh, He Xi.
Are there any steps to a wedding night?
I do know,
but I don't know much.
What do you mean?
I can't get married.
I should have asked Qian Yue.
The marquis is entering!
Thank you, Marquis.
I hope you have a child soon.
Congratulations, Marquis.
Eunuch He,
you may go out.
Thank you, Marquis.
I will be leaving.
Marquis.
The precious Princess Bao Zhu.
Eunuch He.
What are you doing?
I'm worried about the princess and the marquis
since this is their first marriage.
I'm afraid they don't know the necessary procedures.
It hurts!
It hurts? Your Highness!
It's a necessary procedure.
Marquis.
I'm bleeding.
She's bleeding?
Eunuch He, get the imperial physician!
I'm going inside.
Calm down.
A normal procedure.
Marquis.