=Forever Love=
=Episode 21=
(You Bad Man, You Kissed and Ran)
You're strange
today.
I'm not.
You won't leave me, will you?
I will do
what I promised you.
I've left.
(Resignation Letter)
Take care.
You will get used to it.
Sorry,
the number you dialed
is temporarily out of service.
Please try again later.
Sorry,
the number you dialed
is temporarily out of service.
Please try again later.
Qin Moyao,
who allowed you to resign?
You
get back to me right now!
Qin Moyao,
you are joking with me, right?
Have I treated you too well recently?
Stop joking.
Come back now.
Qin Moyao,
don't forget
you sold yourself to me.
You owe me a huge amount of penalty.
You can't just run away like this.
Do you hear me?
(Transfer Record)
Qin Moyao,
you're rich now, huh?
You think you can leave me?
If you dare, say something.
As far as I know,
no one has survived
the three attacks
of the Jixing Organization.
You are simply courting death!
Chi Shan said he would cancel
the order in three days,
but knowing him as I do,
he's very likely to go back on his word.
To eliminate the threat
to Xintong from the source,
I must withstand these three attacks.
After Jixing Organization
tears up the contract,
Chi Shan will have no way.
Qin Moyao,
can't you think more about yourself?
Look at these documents.
What are these?
All my property
and the 60 million of Xintong
that I got from Chi Shan.
If something really happens to me,
you pay her back for me.
But before that,
you'd better wish me success.
I've entrusted her safety to you.
Qin Moyao,
what are you talking about?
You sound like
you're leaving a last will!
Don't get excited.
I'm just fine.
I'm doing this just in case.
Just in case.
Just in case what?
Take these back,
and I'll pretend I didn't hear anything.
The Hongfu shares I bought in your name.
Just keep them.
After all,
I might still need you
to take care of my mom.
Qin Moyao.
By the way,
I always thought
Chi Shan only wanted money,
but what he really wants
is the Hongfu Group.
He even handed me that 60 million.
There must be a secret
between him and Lin Guofu.
Check it out for me.
If you find something,
don't tell Xintong.
Do whatever you want.
Qin Moyao,
I warn you.
You must...
Alright.
Eat.
It'll be cold.
Remember to do the dishes.
Bad man.
He really took everything with him.
Don't ever come back since you've left.
Hang in there. Hold on.
The ambulance will be here soon.
There's been a car accident.
This is Hubin Road.
Why is there also a scar
on your lower back?
I was naughty as a boy
and fell when climbing a tree.
Liar.
Zhou Mo,
with your dimwitted brain,
how did you become
friends with Qin Moyao?
Who would have thought
that a rich lady would have
such countersurveillance skills?
Fine,
you win.
I gotta go.
Wait.
You're going to see Qin Moyao, right?
We go together.
Who said it?
Isn't Qin Moyao at your house?
You need to make it more believable.
Would you have followed me
if Qin Moyao hadn't asked?
Did he ask you to protect me?
I don't know.
Even if I did, I wouldn't tell you.
Miss Lin,
I haven't signed
any servitude contract with you.
Don't order me around.
Don't you know where his house is?
Go find him yourself.
If he were willing
to open the door for me,
would I need you?
I don't care.
I'm just going to follow you.
Wherever you go, I go.
I don't believe you two won't meet.
Do it if you want.
As you wish.
(Death Contract)
(According to our principle,)
(you survived our three attacks,)
(so the contract
on your and that woman's lives)
(is invalid now.)
(Qin Moyao,)
(you're pretty good.)
(You're the only one who did it.)
Hey,
what's wrong?
Qin Moyao,
you better get back here.
If you don't, your woman will die.
Qin Moyao.
Qin Moyao,
you're back.
don't blame me.
She can really hold her liquor.
I lost.
I had no choice but to call you back.
If you don't come back, I'll die.
I'm leaving.
You two do whatever you want.
I don't care anymore.
You're drunk.
I'll take you home first.
Home?
Whose home?
Yours.
I'm not going.
You're drunk.
Be good.
Let's go home first.
We can talk about everything tomorrow.
Qin Moyao,
you're a liar.
You kissed me and ran,
and now you want to chase me away.
I didn't lie to you.
I didn't abandon you either.
I just have my own things to deal with.
Really?
Then what about this?
This?
How did you get this scar?
Here.
You know it?
Why did you lie to me?
You said before that Chi Shan
was the one who saved you.
I told myself
that if one day I grow on you,
I don't want it to be for this reason.
I hope
you like me for real.
♪The world is full of unpredictability♪
♪The light is lost in the eyes♪
♪How can we hide the panic♪
♪How can we not be on guard♪
♪Can I forgive that♪
♪The one I deeply love is lying♪
♪Who is by my side♪
♪The vision is empty♪
♪I can only measure with intuition♪
♪The direction of love♪
♪Could it be an illusion♪
♪Slowly falling into an invisible net♪
♪Exploring in the dark♪
♪Surviving the night♪
♪Lighting up all the vows♪
♪The answer is unclear♪
♪Can love take away my insecurity♪
♪Exploring in confrontation♪
♪I don't want to dodge anymore♪
♪Say all the truths♪
♪How to let go♪
♪Turning around, I hear your call♪
♪Exploring in adversity♪
♪Regaining a sense of security♪
♪Time erases regrets♪
♪Is it a habit♪
♪Your love is so passionate and warm♪
♪Slowly forget to explore♪
♪Facing the light ashore♪
♪Leaving a light for me♪
♪No longer alone♪
♪You are my answer in the dark♪