Thank you.
That's nice and warm, isn't it?
It's nice to come out
for a walk like this.
I know, right?
You must be cold.
No, I'm fine.
No, your colds always last for so long.
I'm really fine.
Are you sure you won't be cold?
-Please, it's just a--
-It's okay. I'm really not that cold.
Maybe we've been outside too long.
Let's start heading back now.
Na-eun?
Yes, let's go.
EPISODE 1
FIRST PITCH
Thanks for everything, Jun-hyeong.
I'll head in.
Hold on.
Let's finish this song
before we say goodbye.
All right.
I'll head in now.
You should get going. It's cold.
I wish I didn't have to go.
I really have to go. You should too.
Fine. I'll leave once
I see that you've made it inside.
No. You leave first.
Oh, right.
You should put this back on
before you leave.
Good night.
Bye.
Oh gosh. It's too cold out, isn't it?
Jeez, it's cold. Let's hurry up.
Gosh, it's cold.
What would it feel like
to get married?
Hey, Na-eun.
Hui-seon, what took you so long?
-Sorry. Where is Su-yeon?
-She went to the bathroom.
-Hurry up.
-Hey there!
The ceremony started already.
This couple has vowed
to love each other forever.
They will now exchange their rings,
a symbol of their love.
The groom will place his ring
on his beloved bride's finger first.
They must be really happy.
-Nervous and excited at the same time.
-I doubt it.
Then do think you'll feel
the responsibility when you get married?
As if.
-Now, the bride will present…
-Then?
As someone who's already been there
and back, this is how it feels.
"Why did I ever decide to do this?"
Gosh, please.
How could you say that to someone
who started considering marriage?
Marriage? Are you going to get married?
Congratulations!
I guess it's about that time for you.
You've been in a relationship for 2 years,
and you're 32 and Jun-hyeong is 36, right?
Gosh, why do you have to
bring age into this?
You're just like our parents,
thinking we need
to be married by a certain age.
I'm against the idea of that as well.
-Marriage…
-Just crunch the numbers.
Then go for it
once everything seems to add up.
What?
So…
Your boyfriend has it all
when it comes to looks.
As for his career, he has a dream job
working in the public sector.
Then I guess it all comes down to this.
How prepared are his mother
and father for their retirement?
Hey, how can you talk about
something so materialistic
while at a sacred place like this?
Wedding halls aren't necessarily sacred.
We pay an admission fee to get in.
What do you mean by that?
Do you mean the congratulatory money?
Jeez, you young people these days…
Su-yeon, congratulatory money
is hardly an admission fee.
You should think of it
more as a type of variable insurance.
Minus any service fees,
you can get back
about 80 percent of the initial amount.
This applies to congratulatory money too.
You guys have no respect
for the institution of marriage.
Where did you have your wedding ceremony?
I bet it was at a really expensive place.
Gosh, you must have been
absolutely gorgeous back then.
Jeez.
What are you doing?
This wedding hall is really pretty.
They have
such a nice atmosphere too, right?
Are you really thinking
of getting married?
Did Jun-hyeong ask you to marry him?
No, it's not that.
I was at the park the other day.
And I saw an old couple
taking a walk together.
They just looked so peaceful
and happy together.
I started to imagine that
if Jun-hyeong and I got married,
that's how we'd end up one day.
I started to look forward to our future.
Hui-seon, I should get married
if I'm starting to feel like this, right?
That's right. You get married
when everything feels like that.
And when you start to think
that going to jail after killing him
might be a good idea,
you should get divorced.
Gosh, do you have to be so extreme again?
So? Are you going
to be getting married soon?
-I'd have to talk with Jun-hyeong first.
-No.
Don't do it.
You should never be the first
to bring up marriage.
Why not?
It shouldn't be the woman
who brings up marriage first.
Okay, but why?
Marriages…
only happen when the man
has the will to get married.
Please, Hui-seon.
It's the 21st century, okay?
Why do you speak so old?
It's like she's trapped
in the 90s all by herself.
You're going to
see Jun-hyeong later, right?
You should buy yourself
a nice bouquet of flowers,
and tell him you caught it at the wedding.
Then you'll naturally start
talking about marriage.
All you have to do
is steer the conversation
so that he's the one
who brings up "marriage" first.
Na-eun, just get out of here. Jeez.
Wait for me.
Hey.
What is it?
Don't you like the sound quality?
No, I just started thinking
of something Hui-seon told me earlier.
What did she say?
She said marriages only happen
when the man has the will to get married.
Marriage?
Yes, isn't that just ridiculous?
She sometimes says things that make
no sense in such a sincere way.
I think today was one of those days.
I mean, why should marriage
solely depend on the man's opinion?
It should happen
when things click between both people.
What? Yes.
Do you think the marriage will be
messed up if the girl brings it up first?
No, right?
If either person in a relationship wants
to get married,
then they can talk it out
and let things go their natural course.
Let's say I were to bring up the topic
of marriage with you first,
-it's not like we wouldn't get married--
-Hey, well…
I think we better pick
which one to buy now.
-What?
-Do you…
like this one?
Or do you like this one?
I don't know.
Let's go with whichever one you like.
The one I like?
Well, what I like is you.
All right, I guess
I'll go with this one then.
Marriages…
only happen when the man
has the will to get married.
I mean, why should marriage
solely depend on the man's opinion?
It should happen
when things click between both people.
What? Yes.
Don't you like the pasta?
Should I get something else for you?
No.
I guess I haven't fully digested my lunch.
-Should I get you digestive medicine?
-It's not that serious.
I just have something
that's been bugging me, that's all.
What is it?
-Before, when I mentioned marriage--
-What?
I think they're having
some promotion here. Look.
The first prize is a free ride on a yacht.
Awesome!
Seriously?
Could he really be avoiding
talking about marriage?
Let's ask for our ticket.
That can't be it.
There's no way. Why would he?
I bet all the servers
are pretty busy though.
Maybe we should wait
instead of bothering them.
Marriage.
What?
Marriage!
What are you talking about
all of a sudden?
-What about marriage?
-I just wanted to say the word.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Na-eun…
Was he really trying
to avoid talking about marriage?
That doesn't make any sense.
Jeez.
WOULD IT BE OKAY
FOR ME TO GET MARRIED TO HIM?
I mean, whoever wrote this
must already know the answer.
It's obvious they shouldn't be getting
married to someone like this.
Jeez, get real.
"Please…
don't get married to anyone
who makes you want to reach out
to strangers on the internet."
-What do you want?
-Hui-seon, this is crazy.
What is?
Jun-hyeong keeps on avoiding
talking about marriage.
You ended up bringing it up first,
didn't you?
I mean, technically I brought it up first.
I didn't ask him
for us to get married or anything.
Since I went to a wedding earlier today,
I brought it up naturally.
He's being so rude
and just openly ignoring it.
It's just as ruder to keep talking about
marriage when he isn't even interested.
Who's side are you on right now?
Do I have to pick a team or something?
-I'll go with whoever's going to win.
-Come on!
-Is this any time to be joking?
-I wasn't joking.
Why would he start
avoiding talking about marriage?
He wasn't like this.
Do you think he's changed his mind?
But that can't be it.
Is he trying to tell me that
he won't marry me? But why?
Slow down, Na-eun.
This is exactly why I told you
not to talk about marriage first.
Girls like you
who always overthink things,
end up with crazy scenarios in their head
if the man starts acting odd.
Take a look at where you're standing.
I bet you've already dug your own grave.
-What do I do now?
-What do you mean what do you do now?
The marriage was already mentioned
and Jun-hyeong isn't
interested in it at all. That's it.
But it's not that simple.
Something feels really off.
Well, that's just how you feel.
Don't get yourself all worked up
and give yourself a hard time.
Just take it easy, Na-eun.
Anyway, hang up. I'm busy.
As soon as I saw Jun-hyeong
focused on his phone
despite my short absence,
I realized…
why I had felt so strange
when nothing had happened just now.
Excuse me, do you have any glue on you?
Glue?
I was hoping I could get you to "stick"
around so I could ask you something.
I have some tape though.
Sorry?
To tape your mouth shut
if you try to talk to me.
I brought my own glue this time
so that I can "stick" around.
I'd better go find myself some tape.
Some heavy-duty stuff.
Gosh, you're not making it easy, are you?
What?
I gathered my courage
to approach you like this.
I know how lame my jokes are.
Do you have any idea what it feels like
to keep using them just to talk to you?
So why do you keep on doing it then?
Because I'm interested in you.
This entire time…
I always thought that
I had the upper hand in this relationship,
thinking about how much he was dying
to be with me
when we first started dating.
I'll get going, then.
What is it?
Is there something you want to tell me?
Yes. Get home safely.
Is that it?
What?
Yes.
There's something we haven't covered yet.
What's that?
And that's why
whether it came to dating or marriage,
I was confident that things would
go exactly the way that I wanted.
However…
it became overwhelmingly clear today
that things have done a complete 180.
Hey, are you feeling better?
I'm sorry, but I think
we should call it a night.
-What?
-Sorry, my stomach isn't feeling good.
Well, I'm hungry because
I haven't had anything since lunch.
Could we at least finish this?
-Jun-hyeong--
-I'll be quick.
Just give me a second.
I'm sorry to bother you.
We're currently running an event
to celebrate our fifth anniversary,
handing out scratch tickets
to our guests as a part of the promotion.
You can choose one of the scratch cards.
Thank you, we'll be leaving soon.
I'll pick them.
Right now?
You know that
I have the Midas touch, right?
I always get lucky
when it comes to raffles.
Do you want to scratch it off?
No. You do it.
Okay. Then I'm going to
put all my skills to the test.
FREE MEAL AND FREE YACHT RIDE
This is wild.
I think I might actually have a gift.
-Congratulations, sir.
-Congratulations!
Careful.
Hello.
Wait.
You can't come in here.
This is off-limits.
-But you can head upstairs to the deck.
-Sorry?
The thing is,
this place is a mess right now.
Plus you're supposed to make reservations
at least a month in advance,
but you didn't. So it's too messy.
It doesn't have to be tidied up.
Can I just stay inside for a moment?
I'm so cold right now.
Come on, damn it.
Oh gosh, I'm sorry.
Either way, you can't go in.
You really can't go in.
Just go upstairs.
How many times do I have to tell you
to just go up to the deck?
Just go up, please.
Let's just go up to the deck.
It's incredible up here!
Rather than the view, it's just too cold.
The night wind is no joke.
You're right. It is pretty cold.
I wouldn't do this
even if somebody forced me to.
What?
What do you mean?
Isn't it so nice up here?
I didn't know
a nice place like this existed in Seoul.
Right. Maybe
it's because we're on a yacht.
We have always wanted to hop on a yacht.
Sitting on top of a yacht
and feeling the wind is refreshing.
Look.
What am I supposed to say
in a situation like this?
Should I ask him
why he's avoiding marriage talks?
Or…
A place like this in Seoul?
…should I ask him
if he doesn't want to marry me?
-Should I?
-Where are we, though?
-Look.
-But what if he says he doesn't?
I love it.
-What would happen then?
-It's so nice being on a yacht together.
This isn't going to work.
I'm too cold, so I'm going to ask him
for a blanket or something.
Hey! I'll go ask him.
I'll ask the captain
and bring back a blanket for you.
No, I'll just go.
But why?
Because I'm just about ready
for a fight right now.
If he doesn't give one,
I'm ready to push him overboard
and sail this yacht.
Na-eun.
The captain said
we weren't allowed to go in there.
I'm just going to see if he's there
and ask for the blanket if he's in there.
Maybe you're a bit worked up right now.
It'd be better if you calm down for--
Please…
Is this why you told us
not to come in here?
-It's not like that--
-You could have told us.
That you were getting ready
for your next guests.
I thought
you were being rude to us
because we came for free.
NA-EUN, WILL YOU MARRY ME?
You were…
trying to propose to me today?
I had no idea.
What do I do?
It's okay.
It's all right.
I'm such a dummy. Seriously.
-It's okay.
-It'll be a good memory.
Well, it's better than
everything going as planned.
You must have worked so hard
to plan all of this.
I got caught up with all these
weird thoughts and ruined everything.
I told you, it's fine.
This wasn't the kind
of surprise I was planning,
but you were surprised nonetheless.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
Take a look over there.
A really handsome guy is about to pop out.
Hey, Na-eun. You must have been startled.
I wanted to say thank you for saying yes
when I asked you out
on that bright winter day back in 2019.
Every day since then has been happier
than anything I could have wished for.
Thank you so much for everything.
Cut! Gosh, this is the worst.
Why Na-eun, though?
What do you even mean?
Am I in love with someone else
other than her?
Can't you understand at once?
That's not what I'm asking you.
-Then?
-Come on, you've dated before.
Based on their looks and other factors,
a lot of them were better than Na-eun.
Jeez, so what do you want?
I mean, whenever any of them
mentioned marriage,
you felt pressured and dodged the topic.
But now, you think it's so obvious
to marry Na-eun.
-That's why I was just curious.
-I guess that's because
I love her?
Jeez, then you didn't love
all of your ex-girlfriends?
Are you some kind of dating robot or what?
Hello, I am Giga Jun-hyeong.
Will you marry me?
Seriously, damn.
Is it because you're
now ready for marriage
and it just so happens
that you're currently with Na-eun?
Or is it because she's good enough
and isn't lacking or has too much
that you're willing
to settle down with her?
Well, that's…
Why do I want to get married to her?
Is it's because I think she's good enough?
Or…
is it's because I'm ready to settle down
and she just happens to be with me?
No.
I'm doing it because it's Kim Na-eun.
Because she is the one
I love more than anyone else.
That's why I want to marry her.
I want to love her and cherish her
more than anyone else in my life.
I love you, Na-eun.
Let's get married.
Kim Na-eun.
Will you marry me?
Thank you.
Thank you more.
Are you happy, Na-eun?
Gosh, today was not an easy day for me.
You have no idea
how much energy I wasted today, either.
Seriously.
You hardly ever bring up marriage.
"Does she not want to get married to me?
Or does she not want to get married now?"
You put all these crazy questions
in my head.
Marriage!
But once I finished
preparing for the proposal
you started to bring up marriage.
I'm sorry, but I think
we should call it a night.
Well, I'm hungry because
I haven't had anything since lunch.
Could we at least finish this?
-Jun-hyeong--
-I'll be quick.
I had everything planned out,
even the little scratch tickets.
But you wanted to go home
because your stomach was upset.
WE'LL BE HEADING OVER THERE SHORTLY
You can't come in. You really can't.
How many times do I have to tell you
to just go up to the deck?
Let's just go up to the deck.
I scheduled it so we'd be there
20 minutes after leaving the dock,
but you kept insisting you'd go in there.
Jeez, man.
Rather than the view, it's just too cold.
The night wind is no joke.
Gosh, you're right. It is pretty cold.
I had the engagement ring hidden
in my coat,
but then you kept hinting you wanted me
to give you my coat.
And at that moment
we finally made it into the cabin…
Is this why you told us
not to come in here?
I don't think I'll ever forget tonight.
I don't think I'll ever forget it either.
Thanks, Jun-hyeong.
I love you.
Oh my gosh, congratulations!
You'll be filling in that empty spot
that I vacated.
Is that similar
to the law of conservation of idiots?
Of course. Slots need to open
for the next woman to get married.
You really have a way of turning tragedies
into comedies.
I guess that comes with being Korean.
Congratulations.
Are you planning to get married this fall?
Probably?
Wait. Do you want to catch the bouquet?
She doesn't even have a boyfriend.
Why toss your bouquet to her?
She might be planning on
setting me up on a blind date.
Me?
-Okay, I'll ask Jun-hyeong about it.
-Great!
So I'll be the one
who catches your bouquet then.
If you're going on a blind date now,
to catch the bouquet--
Don't you worry a thing about any of that.
I fall in love at the blink of an eye.
Don't worry about that.
I'm worried that you might
end up embarrassing me.
I'll be expecting a lot of coaching
from you too.
What's the point of that?
You both don't listen to me at all.
How much of a happy ending
would it have been
if you didn't bring up anything
about getting married?
It's still a happy ending.
Honestly, having those twists makes it
feels more like a fairy tale.
It's been a bit rocky,
but now I'll be sailing smooth.
Like Cinderella.
Who told you that things will go smoothly?
This is as happy as it gets.
Just wait until you start
getting things ready.
Happiness ends, and the hardships begin.
Are you throwing shade at me
or trying to curse me?
-I have to know, so I can repay the favor.
-I'm only giving you the facts.
You have no idea what kind of a hard road…
No, it's a path of suffering, actually.
That's okay.
No matter what might lay ahead of me,
I'll be happy as long as
I'm with my Jun-hyeong.
Can I try it on just once?
Reveal yourself!
Who dares to touch the remote control?
The game hasn't started yet.
The game has started.
Baseball starts
the moment the first pitch is thrown.
What has gotten into you, sir?
But it's just some celebrities
throwing the ball.
No, not at all.
It's more like the eve of the festival.
And it's like the proposal
before the marriage.
It's like a marching parade before battle
and a ritual during which
we pray for victory.
So imagine how lame the game will be
if we missed out on that.
Exactly.
Okay.
Kim Hae-ri, the cheerleader,
will throw the ball to start the game.
The first pitch is over.
It's time for the main game to start.
Friend, let's keep our guard up.
The festivities are over,
and war is upon us.
-What's the first step to getting married?
-The meeting of the parents?
That's the first thing
you should do before getting married.
Just think of it as
preparing for some kind of a summit.
So please avoid talking about
any wedding gifts and smile.
What, did a stork drop you off?
Did I pick you up under a bridge?
How could you have still not
discussed these things with him?
-Time bombs?
-My mom overreacts to everything
and my dad jokes around too much.
And he sure isn't going to
make it any easier.
You're no joke either, Mother.
I was absolutely stunned
when I first met you.
If you have that much sense in you,
then you better watch it today.
It's as if I'm in a minefield right now.