I like you.
I said I like you.
I know this is sudden.
You can take your time to respond.
- I can wait—
- I like you, too.
What?
Sir, I said I like you, too.
Hyung!
Oh? Editor Na?
What are you doing here?
Oh, this.
I came here for this.
Yes.
I left this in CEO Yoo's car while covering a story.
But what brings you here?
I came because I was worried about you.
You said you'd be home resting, but I couldn't reach you.
I worried you were sick.
I'm fine.
I'm glad.
Editor Na.
Let's go have a beer at Hyung's place.
What?
Oh, no, no.
I have something else I need to do.
Well, then.
I'll get going.
Did you sleep well last night?
Yes, I'm having breakfast now.
Then are we... in a relationship starting today?
Yes.
Yes!
You seem happy.
You said you were looking to invest in Jejudo.
Did you finally land something?
No.
But I think I landed something even better.
Na Young Won's heart.
Seeing how happy you are, I guess you really hit the jackpot.
Yes, well...
I did hit it, and it's bursting.
This Yoo Ja Sung's heart.
Hi, Editor Nam.
Hello.
Take a seat.
How's your nose? Let me see.
It's all right.
- Don't say that.
- Ouch.
It must've hurt so bad.
I said I'm fine.
How can you be?
You got hit by a piece of pig's bone.
Why aren't you picking up?
I have to get ready for work.
I'll take personal calls later.
What's up with you?
Refusing to take your cutie pie's call?
- Amazing.
- Good morning!
Oh, sir!
Did something good happen?
I've never heard such a cheery morning greeting from you.
Yes, well...
- Should I make you feel even better?
- What?
The thing is, our Editor Nam
didn't take his girlfriend cutie pie's call
since work hours are about to begin.
I mean, showing off at work that you're in a relationship is so tacky.
It's ill-advised behavior that disregards
your warning to keep things professional at work.
Right?
Yes, of course.
What do you think about his excellent behavior?
Doesn't it make you feel good?
Yes, very good.
Quite excellent. I'll be off.
Yes, sir.
See you later.
Right.
I should own up to what I said.
No ill-advised behavior.
Keep things professional...
♫  You’re my love  ♫
♫  Look at me, I’ll be standing right here  ♫
♫  Like a dream, like a dream  ♫
♫  Always, there for you.  ♫
♫  Don’t worry. (Baby just hold my hand)  ♫
♫  Don’t worry. (Don’t ever let go of me)  ♫
♫  Like a dream, like a dream  ♫
♫  I’m always there for you  ♫
Hello.
Wow, amazing!
Why do you look so different today?
She changed her style.
It looks so good on you.
Thanks.
Doesn't Sunbae Ui Joo have that dress, too?
Wow, you have a sharp eye.
I lent her my dress.
Wow, I wouldn't have known.
It fits you perfectly.
Thank you.
Oh! Editor Nam!
I heard you won a subscription.
Congratulations!
Finally!
Thanks.
Okay. Let's all get to work.
The CEO is glaring at us.
MBTI is a personality test.
It analyzes people into sixteen types.
People do it a lot nowadays.
For this issue, I'd like to write an article
on interior design preference by MBTI type.
I need your test results as samples,
so please give the results to me by today.
How long will the test take?
Ten minutes.
You can see how compatible you are with others.
- Is that so?
-  You look very pretty today.
I wonder who will be compatible with me.
I think the most compatible person
is me, Choi Go.
Have lunch with me.
Stop!
- What are you doing?
- Pardon?
Why are you on your phone during a meeting?
I'm sorry. It was an important text.
Important how?
Is it work-related? Let me see.
Oh, no, no. It's personal.
I'm sorry.
I don't know who it is, but tell them to stop texting during work hours.
They know you're at work. Why do they keep texting?
Lacking such common sense!
They need to screw their heads on straight!
Don't forget
CEO Yoo's stern warning on only focusing on work during work hours!
Got it?
Yes.
I did well, right?
Yes, you did well. Very well.
So when will you send in your results?
What results?
You know, the MB whatever...
Here's the revised storyboard for the second home.
I'm sorry about earlier.
It's okay.
I know I shouldn't, but I can't control my feelings.
Should we just go public instead?
Tell them we're dating?
Pardon?
No, let's not.
You said to keep things professional.
If we date openly, I'm worried about what people might think.
And they'll also be uncomfortable around me.
Right.
You have a point.
Then I'll be more careful from now on.
I'll do my best so people won't find out.
Okay.
On that note,
let's go get lunch secretly.
That's not a good idea.
Why not?
Sir.
Let's go.
Where?
We were invited to an advertiser's franchise.
All of us have to have lunch there.
I told you that in the meeting earlier, too.
I know, I know.
All right, I'll go.
Here.
Editor Nam isn't coming?
He has an interview with an architect.
He's having lunch there.
Stop.
Editor Na Zero Won, don't sit there. Sit somewhere else.
Sir?
This is what's wrong with you. You are tactless.
What do you mean...?
You have many opportunities to talk with me while covering stories.
I want to talk to other people during informal occasions.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
Anyone who'd like to have an honest talk with me, please sit.
First come, first serve.
They're hesitating because they all want to sit.
The competition is fierce.
You must feel so great, sir.
I guess the honor is mine!
Here we go, I'll serve you first.
Give that to me, I'll serve.
- It's okay. I'll do it.
- I'll do it.
I want to serve you all today.
Okay. Here you go, Chief Editor Choi Go.
Just like your name, I know how hard you work all the time.
I always anticipate your articles, our trustworthy Editor Yeo.
Oh, thank you.
Joo Hee, Mi Ra.
It wouldn't be an exaggeration to say that our office runs well thanks to the assistants, so thank you always.
- Oh, thank you.
- Thank you.
Hold out your dish, too, Editor Na.
Everyone has some, right?
Let's enjoy and eat up and let's fight on!
Sir, you left out Young Won.
What?
Oh, dear. I forgot about Editor Na Zero Won.
Oh, well. It's okay. I'll do it...
This is your problem, Editor Na, this. Not having a presence.
- Sir?
- If you didn't get some, you should've spoken up.
Why didn't you say anything? This is what I don't like about you.
There's one left here.
Eat.
Thank you.
You were going to give it to her anyway. You could've given it to her nicely.
Well, she ended up getting the biggest one.
It's weird how the biggest abalone was left.
Eat up.
Did you have meat by yourself?
Even abalone gets stuck in my teeth!
I'm sorry about earlier. I was cold to you so they wouldn't know about us.
I hope you're not upset.
Oh, no. I'm not. You did well.
If you keep this going, no one will suspect anything.
See? I get things done when I set my mind to it.
Sir, what are you doing there with Editor Na?
What?
Editor Na! This is what's wrong with you! Stop pestering me!
It's lunchtime! Talk about work during work hours! Why would you bother me during off-hours?
This is what I don't like about you. This!
Why is he so harsh on you today?
It seems like you did something really bad.
No. I didn't do anything wrong.
Then why's he like that? He has such a temper.
And why walk like that like an old man?
Hey. How long are you going to haul that bag around?
I can't keep it in the studio. Someone might see.
Then send it to Editor Na's house. And tell her how you feel.
We're at the office. Someone might hear you!
- No one will...
- Hear what?
- Editor Na!
- Who shouldn't hear what?
Oh, nothing. By the way, you must have an important appointment.
- What?
- Yes, your look is awesome. You look like a movie star.
Oh, not at all. I was at Sunbae Ui Joo's last night and...
Never mind. I'll be going in now. Bye.
Bye.
Get a grip.
What a shame. For that look, that bag in there is perfect.
Shut up. I almost got caught because of you.
Let's just go to the shoot.
Why's it because of me?
Editor Nam.
Oh, Editor Nam. Oh, dear.
You must be exhausted from the interview.
Did you have lunch?
Yes, I did.
Just a second. I have something to give you.
What's this?
20% discount coupon for Shinna Hotel Wedding Hall.
Don't be moved just yet.
20% discount for Jung Ongdal Saem-mool bridal makeup.
Wait, there's more.
20% discount for Park Sul-nam wedding hanbok.
What are these for?
What do you mean? You got an apartment, and you proposed.
You're getting married soon, right?
So I prepared these gifts. What do you think? You're so moved, right?
Oh, right. I'm so moved.
That's incredible. They're big names in the wedding business.
I used to work at a wedding magazine.
I used all my contacts there for this. I bent over backward to get these coupons.
Why go to all that trouble?
What? How can you say that?
Why do you think? Editor Nam and I are very close. He's like a brother to me.
I prepared this as his brother.
Thank you.
- Don't thank me yet.
- What?
I'll help you get the lowest prices on everything wedding-related.
Stop that. Why give him gifts he doesn't want?
Why are you dampening the mood? Are you jealous?
But I have bad news. I can't do this for you when you get married.
Why? Because he's the only one I think of as a brother.
My brother, Editor Nam. I love you.
Your big brother loves you a lot.
Thanks.
Oh, right.
Jeez.
She seems to be happy with my acting.
Is it this easy to make a woman happy?
- Hello?
-  Hello, sir.
The water leak repair work has just finished. Your tenant can come back right away.
What? Already?
Wasn't it going to take a few more days?
Yes, it was supposed to,  but I nagged them to work faster for you.
Why? I'm not special. You didn't have to nag them.
I'll tell my tenant so don't contact her.
I just got word that the repair work on your place...
will take longer.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry. I don't want to inconvenience you more.
Don't be. I'm very happy that we can be together longer.
What? He's making me blush.
Let's have dinner, just the two of us. Alone.
Sure.
Wow, it's the long-awaited first date.
Should I let my hair down?
No. It's better up.
What the? What?
What?
Ouch, that hurts.
What's going on?
₩1.05 million? ₩1.05 million ($1,050)?
This is insane.
Even with my remaining living expenses, I only have ₩500,000 ($500).
How will I get ₩1.05 million? Darn it.
Oh? Right. My monthly rent.
Could I pay this month's rent next month?
I need the money for an emergency.
How can I ask him that?
Even if it's urgent, how can I humiliate myself like that in front of my boyfriend?
I'm sorry.
I ruined your expensive designer dress.
Yes.
I don't think I can get it fixed.
I'll pay for it,
but can I pay by installment?
I'll pay ₩100,000 every month without fail.
I'm sorry,
but that won't do.
Right.
Of course.
Of course, it won't do.
That dress doesn't even cost ₩100,000.
- What?
- That's an ST.
It's not designer. It's styled after it.
An imitation.
- You know?
- What?
I can't wear designer clothes all the time.
Wow, I had no clue.
I died and was resurrected.
Right. Since you were resurrected, live well.
Sunbae.
I love you.
Here's the revised article.
Thank you.
What shall we have for dinner?
Korean? Western?
Japanese!
Sir. I don't think I can have dinner tonight.
- What?
- I have plans with Sunbae Ui Joo.
I'm sorry.
Why all of a sudden?
She drops me and makes plans with Editor Yeo?
Why?
What do you mean, "why"?
Editor Yeo must've clung on, saying she's bored.
Darn it.
Editor Yeo, do you have time tonight?
Why do you ask?
If it's because of work, I have other plans tonight.
Really?
Then what should I do about this invitation?
Invitation?
Oh, dear.
Oh, that's Gorgeous.
The high-end fashion magazine targeting the upper class.
They're famous for being elite.
Yes, that's probably why they chose the guests extremely carefully.
But I have a previous engagement.
I was hoping you would go instead.
- Me?
- Yes.
The only one to go to this dignified event in my place is you.
Oh, well. That is true.
But I have other plans. I'm sorry.
Stop. Stop.
I heard that actor Gong Yoo would be there.
Is he that famous?
What? Gong Yoo?
Yes.
I don't know celebrities that well.
Oh, and who else...
Oh, oh. Actor Hyun Bin.
I'll go. I'm going.
I will go.
What about your plans?
Who cares about the measly plan?
It's Gong Yoo and Hyun Bin, after all.
I don't want the others to know.
They might feel hurt.
Of course.
Thank you, sir.
What shall we eat for dinner later?
Oh, I meant to tell you.
- I don't think I can do dinner tonight.
- Why not?
I forgot I have to give the CEO some material by today.
Oh, really?
- Then I'll help you.
- What?
Editor Na, Editor Na, Editor Na!
This is what's wrong with you.
- That you have so many problems.
- Sir?
Just focus on your own work!
If you nosily help others and tire yourself,
you can't write the important promo article.
For tomorrow's work, go home right now and rest.
Maintain your best condition!
Yes. Just go home.
I'm okay.
Okay.
It's not just an ordinary amount of problems either!
You're just full of problems.
I have no idea how much I have to fix you!
Editor Na, think hard.
You must've done something wrong.
Indeed. I wouldn't treat my parents' enemies like that.
- Editor Na. Go home quickly.
- Go.
Look. He's glaring at you.
Go. Quick.
Well, then. I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye.
Editor Na!
- Please, get in.
- Pardon?
Let's eat dinner!
Oh, I'm sorry, but...
I suddenly have something important to do. I'm sorry.
Editor Na!
What the?
Sunbae.
I love you.
(Me too.)
It'll be our first date, but I nearly cried a river.
Are you happy?
Have you become happy so quickly?
What?
That's ridiculous!
He's over thirty and he doesn't have ₩1 million?
What a relief I didn't send that text!
If I had, that would've been so humiliating.
What the?
Why was this sent?
I didn't press send.
Give him the moving cost and tell him to move out right away.
Pathetic.
I'm humiliated. How can I face CEO Yoo?
Oh? Editor Na!
Didn't you have other plans tonight?
You're not dressed to be at a convenience store.
I did... have plans,
but I canceled.
Why?
No reason. I felt down.
You know that kind of days.
Then to change things up, how about we go to my second home?
What?
Oh. Camping at the Han River?
When you look at the open view of the river, you'll feel much better.
Maybe I should.
As a matter of fact,
I want to go home really, really late tonight.
There's no place like my second home to kill time.
I'll throw this away.
Hello?
What? My mail?
I kept all the mail for you during repairs.
Collect them when you move back in today.
"Move back in today"?
What do you mean...
Didn't CEO Yoo tell you?
The water leak repair work is done.
He said he'd tell you himself and wouldn't even let me tell you.
He must've forgotten.
Right.
Okay.
Thank you.
I just got word that the repair work on your place will take longer.
Don't be. I'm so happy.
That we can be together longer.
Oh, then this was...
Editor Na! I'm home.
Is she not home yet?
Editor Na?
What? Where is all her stuff?
I heard the water leak repair work is done.
I'll return to my apartment.
Thank you for everything.
What?
She left, just like that?
Without even seeing me?
Does she not want to be with me?
Wait.
Did she avoid having dinner on purpose?
Stop.
This is what's wrong with you. You are tactless.
I'm sorry.
No, wait.
She definitely said she wasn't upset.
This is what's wrong with you! Stop pestering me!
Editor Na, Editor Na, Editor Na!
I have no idea how much I have to fix you!
I wouldn't want to be with me either.
I wouldn't want to...
You must be tired preparing for the wedding.
I'm buying, so eat up.
Thank you so much, Chief Editor.
We're off work. Call me Hyung.
Oh, how could I?
You're like a real younger brother to me.
Oh, dear. The expensive meat is burning.
Eat up.
Thank you. Hyung.
Good.
Since I'm your hyung,
I'd like to ask a favor for my child.
What?
The new male math teacher where your fiance works.
The one who cost more than ten billion won to recruit.
The unrivaled number one instructor in Daechi-dong.
What? I don't know him.
Didn't you hear from your cutie pie?
Take a look. It's him.
Only children who pass the level test can take his classes.
My child didn't make the cut by one point.
Ask your cutie pie to get your nephew into his class.
That won't work.
Why not?
My child said that those two are very close.
They're joined at the hip at the academy.
There's even a false rumor they're dating.
Please help me out.
I talked big, saying I could get my child in through you.
If I don't, my wife said she'd rip my head off.
You know how she is.
Dongsaeng Sang Soon.
(T/N: Dongsaeng - younger brother)
Call your cutie pie and ask...
I said no!
I'm sorry.
No.
Don't be sorry.
You won't do anything that'll make you sorry.
You'll do this favor for me, right?
My dongsaeng Sang Soon?
I'm really sorry, Hyung.
You bastard.
How dare you call me Hyung?
If you really were my dongsaeng, I'd have broken your legs right now.
I'd have knocked out all your front teeth!
Jeez!
I'm sorry, Chief Editor.
Forget it.
You pay for this expensive beef.
What?
Darn it!
Chief Editor...
This is insane.
It's me, Mi Ra.
Why don't you ask?
About why I'm secretly living at the office?
If you wanted to tell me, you would have.
That's right.
By the way, what were you watching?
Just some YouTube videos.
Oh? Chan has a channel.
What's his content theme?
There's no theme at all.
He just films us hanging out.
What?
Wait.
Was it too harsh just leaving a note?
Hi, Ui Joo.
Oh, I'm not at my friend's house. The repair is done, so I came home.
Are you nearby?
Sure. See you soon.
Bye.
What? Is she already here?
What?
Sir!
- How can your love change?
- What?
Have I been dumped after one day of dating?
Do you not like me anymore?
Sir...
Yes.
I know I deserve it.
I was cold to you on purpose.
But I overdid it. I went too far.
I understand that I hurt you.
No, that's not it...
I'm sorry. What I did was wrong.
So please give me another chance.
I can't get dumped without going on a first date.
Go on at least three dates with me. Please?
I promise I'll be good to you...
I said that's not it!
What?
It was because I was humiliated.
The text that I sent you... I was so humiliated by it.
Text?
What do you mean...?
It's humiliating.
When you saw that, I knew you'd think I was pathetic.
So I didn't have the guts to see you.
But I really wasn't going to send it.
Honest.
I don't know how it got sent, but it was an accident.
The emergency is resolved.
I don't need the money now.
I know I said it,
but it's so pathetic.
I think I lack so much to be with you.
No.
- Oh, right.
- Young Won!
Why is Editor Yeo here?
Young Won, I'm here!
I'm here. Open the door.
Young Won!
Stay here.
What took you so long?
Sunbae! Your clothes...
I'll explain later.
I'm so mad. I need a drink first.
Sunbae. Want to get drinks outside?
There's a great new cart bar.
What? A cart bar?
Do you think I'd go to a cart bar in this?
I'm just going to stay here and drink.
What the...
A VVIP secret party?
Yes.
CEO Yoo gave me an invitation and told me not to tell anyone.
That's why I lied to you.
Sorry.
I flipped out at Gong Yoo and Hyun Bin.
- So why are you here?
- What do you think?
This is all because of that bastard Yoo Ja Sung.
As it turns out, the party was yesterday.
CEO Yoo said it was today,
but it was yesterday.
He did it on purpose to screw me over.
That son of a gun!
- Sunbae.
- That son of a...?
He must've made a mistake.
Forget it!  You're not what's wrong. He is.
He's a problematic man!
- Sunbae...
- Problematic man?
"I got the date wrong."
"It was a mistake."
"I'm sorry."
Now he apologizes?
I can't stand him.
I hope he gets stuck somewhere and can't get out!
I drank on an empty stomach.
I'm feeling the booze.
Why? Do you want to go home?
I'm going, all right.
To the bathroom.
Come out.
Goodbye.
♫  You make me  ♫
♫  Much better when you’re here  ♫
♫  I’m lucky  ♫
You're the first person to
make me this happy.
You don't lack anything at all.
You're an amazing woman.
♫  From falling much deeper  ♫
♫  Just listen here we are again  ♫
♫  Through the fire, through the rain  ♫
♫  The roads we crossed they built  ♫
♫  Story of us  ♫
♫  Write the story of us  ♫
Hi.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hello.
- Give me.
- Sir?
The wedding hall discount coupon I gave you.
Calmly hand it over!
Oh, okay.
There's more. I sent you a whole lot yesterday!
Give back the makeup and hanbok coupons, too!
What are you doing? Taking back what you gave?
You said they were gifts because he's like a dongsaeng.
Dongsaeng, my foot.
I sent them because I was in need.
My wife is about to divorce me.
I'm about to be a divorcé.
What? Why?
This bastard didn't do me a small favor.
So our marriage will be destroyed.
How do you feel, Editor Nam?
Destroying a family?
I'm sorry.
What favor did you ask?
Forget it.
Who's supervising at the print shop?
Who's going to check for typos?
You and me.
Jeez. I'm not going!
My life is a typo. I'm not going.
Editor Nam, you go.
What? Me?
Why? You don't want to do this, either?
I really want to ask.
I want to ask Socrates.
♪ Oh, Socrates! ♪
♪ Why is Sang Soon like this? ♪
♪ Why is that bastard like that? ♪
♪ Oh, Socrates! ♪
Darn it!
My coffee's gone cold!
What?
Why did you ask for such an unreasonable favor?
Why is that unreasonable?
Is it that hard to put in a good word for me?
It could be.
He might have his reasons.
His reasons?
More desperate than mine?
I'm on the brink of a divorce!
Chief Editor.
Just leave Editor Nam alone.
You'll regret this later.
Why would I?
He just lost a good Hyung.
I'm going to make him regret this forever.
It's the first draft of the ocean view second home.
I'll be waiting for feedback.
Editor Na.
Yes?
Can't you stay a little longer?
What?
I guess not.
No.
Since it's work hours.
Yes.
- Editor Na.
- Sir?
Your article lacks material.
We need additional coverage.
Let's go right away.
Yes, sir.
You got reprimanded so much yesterday, yet you make a mistake again.
This is what's wrong with you, Chief Editor!
Unnecessarily butting in on other's business!
Do your own job well!
See you later.
That rude bastard.
I'm going to butt heads with him one day.
What are you staring at?
Are you done with the presentation for today's meeting?
Well...
Can you give me one more day?
I want to add a little more material.
Never mind.
What's the use in adding more now?
Add character to your personality instead!
Chief Editor!
What?
Editor Nam didn't do me a favor.
Why should I do him a favor?
I don't see any reason why.
Do the presentation today, no matter what!
Yes, sir.
Seriously.
You walk better than me, who's used to surveying.
Aren't you tired?
It's strange how I don't feel tired at all today.
We're here for work, but I'm so excited.
We really are a perfect couple.
A match made in heaven.
I was thinking that exact same thing.
Isn't it so beautiful?
Yes. Beautiful.
Very.
Seriously.
It's so surreal how beautiful it is.
Yes. It's so surreal.
Truly.
Right.
I read something about this temple.
"United minds make flowers bloom even in ruins."
This place fell into ruins because of a huge forest fire.
But seeing how it is so firmly restored,
I think that description fits perfectly.
Yes. I hope nothing like that happens again.
We are visitors who come and go,
but this place is a precious home to the monks.
Editor Na.
Your heels...
When did that happen?
It's probably because of my shoes.
I didn't know.
Stay here. I'll go get some ointment...
No, no.
I'm fine.
I didn't even know it hurt until now.
It's okay. Come on in.
♫  You’re my love  ♫
Get on.
What?
No, it's okay. I'm fine.
I'm not fine. Get on my back now.
But I'm really okay.
I'm not moving until you get on.
♫  Don’t worry. (Don’t ever let go of me)  ♫
♫  Like a dream, like a dream  ♫
♫  Always, there for you  ♫
♫  Don’t worry  ♫
♫  Baby just hold my hand  ♫
♫  Don’t ever let go of me  ♫
People are staring.
Who cares?
We can't show that we're dating at work,
so I want to show off here.
♫  You’re my love  ♫
My special article for this issue
is on the beautiful resorts near Seoraksan Mountain.
Take a look at this.
Wow, it's pretty.
It's amazing.
Can I get a discount on that place if I go through you?
Oh, don't do that.
He won't do you a favor.
Well. I'll ask.
Really?
Thank you. All right!
What's gotten into you?
Doing a favor for someone?
Stop it, please!
So it's me you won't do a favor for.
Chief Editor!
Continue, please.
When it snows, the view is a masterpiece.
It's pretty.
What do you think? Amazing, right?
As I expected, you are all shocked.
Okay.
I believe that even foreigners will respond quite enthusiastically.
That's all.
This lodging is amazing, right?
No.
Don't turn around.
What?
What's the matter?
No...
I hope you have a nice life.
I'm sorry.
Let's take a break.
Editor Nam.
Editor Nam! Sang Soon!
Oh, dear...
I'm sorry, Editor Nam.
I didn't know.
I was being petty.
It's not your fault.
It's okay.
Yes?
Thanks for saying that.
I hope you don't take this the wrong way, but don't be too distressed.
There's nothing you can do if it's not meant to be.
No.
It's just a hiccup.
We've been together for three years.
All those years, we had no problem.
We can't end just like this.
I will turn it all back.
Wait and see.
My cutie pie and I will never break up.
I can't believe this.
This is for you.
What?
Why?
It's a thank you gift for the camping gear and yesterday's beer.
It's okay. You eat it.
- Still...
- I'm really sorry.
But I actually don't like chocolate.
I'll just accept your appreciation.
Yes, Editor Yeo?
I'll be down right away.
Bye.
Going for a poop?
Oh, hello.
I was delivering the schedule sheet.
Do you want this?
What?
Why?
Enjoy it.
What the...? Making me feel burdened...
This is a restaurant a local recommended.
Please refer to it in the article.
Okay.
Why aren't you eating the shrimp?
Pardon?
Oh, because there's so much to eat.
I'm taking it slow.
Come on.
This is a shrimp restaurant. You must eat shrimp.
Here. Say ah.
No, it's okay.
I want to show off that we're dating while we're here, at least.
It's okay.
Say ah.
Ah.
Oh, I can't eat shrimp!
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Actually, I had shrimp when I was little and got really sick.
Then I would've taken you to eat something else instead of shrimp.
It's okay.
This is for the article, so we can't cater it to me.
Actually, covering the story is good and all,
but I brought you all the way here
because we didn't get to enjoy the beach last time we were here.
Pardon?
I wanted to make you happy.
But I really screwed up.
You hurt your heels, and you can't even eat properly.
It's all my fault.
Oh, no.
I had a great time.
Let's go.
Let's eat something you like.
Oh, no, it's okay.
Let's just eat here and go back to Seoul quickly.
We can't just leave like this.
Let's eat something you like and take our time heading back after enjoying the night view.
Wait, wait...
To be honest, I have to send in an advertorial by tomorrow.
I think I have to pull an all-nighter even if we get back to Seoul now.
What?
I wonder if Editor Nam is doing okay.
The more I think of it, the worse I feel.
I told you you'd regret it later.
You should've grabbed me by the collar and stopped me.
What do I do?
Whose call are you avoiding?
My boyfriend's.
Why? Are you having problems, too?
No.
He wants to get married.
Really?
- Congratulations...
- So I'm breaking up with him.
What?
You know me.
I don't want to get married.
I'm not one to string along a good man.
Why don't you want to get married?
No reason.
He told me not to worry about rent.
What's he doing that he forgot it?
I said I didn't see.
I can pretend I didn't see. Nothing's the matter.
I understand everything.
So let's put it behind us...
I'm sorry, Oppa.
I can make you happy better than anyone.
I won a subscription now, so we have an apartment we can live in.
Oppa.
Someone said
you don't know when you're living in a small place,
but once you move to a bigger place,
you see how uncomfortable the other place was.
What are you...?
That apartment... I don't want to live there.
What?
I'm really sorry.
Let me out here.
Someone might see if we're close to the office.
Oh, okay.
Thanks for the ride.
- Editor Na.
- Stop.
Stop saying you're sorry.
I'm really fine.
To be honest...
it's my first time dating, so I'm clumsy at it.
I've been focused only on making money.
I've never dated before.
I'm regretting it for the first time.
If I had dated a lot before now,
I wouldn't have shown such a clumsy side of me.
And you wouldn't have suffered because of me.
What do you mean, "suffer"?
I really had a great time.
No.
I'm the one that's actually lacking.
I'm humiliatingly inadequate for you.
Oh, no.
- That's nonsense.
- But...
I'll try very hard.
I'm Gaeryong Yoo Ja Sung.
I had nothing and came this far.
There's nothing I can't do if I put my mind to it.
I'll make you happy no matter what...
You're the first person
to make me feel happy all day.
You're the one who's truly an amazing man.
♫  Like putting one ice cube in an americano  ♫
♫  Our first encounter was lukewarm  ♫
♫  We’re so different, let me tell you, we’ll never get close  ♫
♫  That’ll never happen, I bet, you know  ♫
♫  You seem so uptight  ♫
♫  I’m not the only one who thinks this  ♫
♫  You know this too  ♫
You must be hungry.
You couldn't eat because of me.
Please wait.
I'll bring you some late-night snacks.
- No, it's okay...
- I refuse
your refusal.
He changed his profile pic.
Someone once said
that united minds make flowers bloom even in ruins.
♫  It’s especially quiet in my room today  ♫
♫  Feels like it’s embracing me  ♫
♫  Things didn’t go my way today  ♫
In the moment of ruin when everything is lost...
♫  It was a day filled with easy sighs  ♫
Even if you're precariously hanging on...
♫  Everyone goes through this kind of day  ♫
Chan and Gyeom's camping!
Come on, say hi.
The day will come when flowers bloom
and you can smile again.
♫  Thank you for getting through this lonely day  ♫
Just like this beautiful temple that stood firm
amidst all kinds of ordeals.
Of course,
it'd be better if there were no ordeals.
What?
They're already back from repairing the equipment?
Those klutzes.
♫  Like a dream, like a dream  ♫
♫  Always, there for you  ♫
♫  Don’t worry (Baby just hold my hand)  ♫
♫  Oh don’t worry (Don’t ever let go of me)  ♫
♫  Like a dream, like a dream  ♫
♫  I’m always there for you  ♫
♫  Don’t worry (Baby just hold my hand)  ♫
♫  Don’t worry  ♫
~ Preview ~
How long will you address me so professionally?
Here is the material you asked for.
Ja Sung.
Are you crazy, Editor Na?
Let's go on a date tonight.
Let's watch a movie.
Are you okay?
I won't let my personal issues affect the workplace.
Just turn a blind eye.
How can we turn a blind eye when he's so obvious?
If I see a couple today, I'm going to end them!
I don't think we should tell Sunbae Ui Joo we're dating.
Who is that?