This series is adapted from novel. All characters, stories, and scenarios are made up. Viewer discretion is required and some actions can't be followed.
Are you going home?
No.
My dad just misses me, he'll drop me at my place later.
Um.
He's here.
I've got to go.
Hello dad.
Hello dad!
Ouch!
What the hell?
Dinosaur Love.
Ka Kong Montree as Rak.
Pepper Phongpat as Dino.
Aom Thakrit as Suea / Mos Kitrawee as Chalarm
Boss Sutthiphat as Mhee.
Get Sorawut as Top.
Phet Chanapoom as Korn / Hat Sornsakol as Bank.
Peak Nutchanon as Mek / PoonPun Jittaboon as See-kram.
Sun Worrachid as Tart.
Akin Akinkorn as Temp.
Seoul Weeramethachai as Manager Gift / Sprite Samon as Sis Pat.
Michell Ravisara as Please.
Meen Chawanakorn as Ping / Phet Phacharapol as Toon / Film Patcharapol as Aun.
Jeng Thanawat as Aob Aob.
Special guest: Peak Peemapol as Sim.
Tonnam Piamchon as Bro.
Sammy Samantha as Pla-bu.
Park Panupat as Sud-yod.
Ohm Thanakrit and Tu-Safe Krittawat.
Ton Sarun.
Mean Phiravich.
Dinosaur Love
Hello, Mhee.
Rak.
How's Dino?
I heard that his phone is dead.
Are you with him?
No.
I haven't seen him.
Oh.
Did you know that Dino got hit?
Huh?
Rak.
Are you alright?
Don't tell me that he hasn't told you yet.
I know it from you just now.
Is he alright?
Yes.
He just got hit at the arm.
Do you want to visit him?
I can pick you up.
He might have a reason for not telling you.
If you want to know anything, I recommend you to ask.
Don't imagine things.
Now I'm parking my car and about to go to my bar.
Less than 10 minutes from here to college.
If you want to visit him, just wait at your place.
I'll take care of your absent.
Dino might afraid you'll worry about him so he didn't tell you.
Normally, he doesn't tell anyone when he got hurt.
What about the person who shoot him?
He was arrested already.
Do you feel better?
Trust me, Dino is thinking about how to tell you.
He doesn't like making his significant ones worry.
He doesn't even tell his mom when he got hurt.
And doesn't tell me also.
I just know when he's already recover.
I'll bring some food for him.
Ok.
I'll pick you up.
Thank you.
Rak?
How did you get here?
Mhee took me here.
Where's Mhee?
He's just left.
Actually, he wanted to visit you too.
But he has urgent call from his bar so he had to leave.
By the way, how are you?
Come in.
Have you taken medicine yet?
No, I haven't
Are you alright?
Um.
Don't cry.
Rak.
Seeing you cry makes me hurt more than getting hit.
Then why are you holding me?
Because you're crying.
Do you still hurt?
Just a little.
I'm fine.
What did you bring here?
Food and Ichitan drink.
So fresh.
What a fresh drink!
It's the best.
What are you doing?
You acted like a child.
At least it makes you smile.
I'm afraid someone might think that I'm weak.
I know.
Do you want to eat now?
You're right-handed, right?
Um.
Actually, I can eat by myself.
But if you feed me, it would be more yummy.
Dino.
Then let's eat.
So you can take you medicine right away.
Um.
But I won't let you come home tonight.
I haven't said I'll leave.
Can I stay with you tonight?
You have to sleep in the same bed with me.
Um.
You're so obedient.
I just want to make sure
that you're going to be ok.
You can be sure.
Don't rush.
Seems like you're thirsty.
You drink like a child.
Have you had dinner?
No, I haven't.
Why don't you eat?
Don't you know it's dinner time?
You can't scold me for that.
Why?
You haven't had dinner as well.
My arm hurts, I can't go out to eat.
Your arm hurts not your legs.
I have a headache too.
I might have fever.
See?
You're hot.
Do you still have a headache?
No.
This is just a prank.
But my arm actually hurts.
Where's your medicine?
I'll go grab it.
In my bedroom.
Dino.
You have such a kissable lips.
[The second I saw you]
[You stole my heart]
[The second we meet]
[is always special]
Ahem! Dino.
It hurts.
Why don't you hit another arm?
Is this yours or a bear slap?
Don't do this.
I hurt you.
It's just a prank.
I'm afraid I might hit you again.
Do you worry about me?
Um.
I'm worried about you so much.
I'll go grab your medicine.
Why are you making a stressful face?
No, I'm not.
Your face looks like this.
Is this a stressful face?
Does it inflame?
Does it still hurt?
Why are you staring at me?
It's not your business.
Rak.
Stop it.
I don't know.
I don't want to talk to you.
But I want to.
Get off of me.
What?
Ah, get off of you.
I won't.
Dino.
Yeah, that's my name.
You're so cute.
You're going to make my hair messy.
Why?
I like it like that.
What's the problem?
You said you'll go out tomorrow, right?
Um, I'll buy a new phone.
Do you want to watch a movie?
Nah.
I'll go back to do my laundry.
See?
It smells bad.
Because I haven't washed it for a couple days.
Let me try.
It smells nice.
You mean my shirt, right?
Your cheeks.
Dino.
I'll hit you.
If you hit me, I'll kiss you.
You can hit me hard,
because you're in adverse condition.
I won't hit you anymore.
You have to come with me tomorrow.
Why don't you go alone?
I said you have to come with me.
My arm still hurts.
Will you go or not?
1..
2..
Answer me.
I'll go with you.
I'll go with you, alright?
Are you happy now?
You're so obedient.
I'm happy now.
Whatever.
Why are you smiling?
I'll go with you.
I know.
You want me to go with you, don't you?
Let's continue watching movies.
Do you want anything?
Err...I've been wanting this for so long.
I don't know if it's good or not.
I'll buy it for you.
Anything else?
But it quite expensive.
Then it's for me.
What about this?
This one is also good but expensive.
I'll buy this one for you.
Are you hanging out here?
Yeah, what's the problem?
Nothing..
for now.
Maybe in the future might be.
Who's behind you? Looks so familiar.
Looks like a freshman.
Answer me.
Who?
Are you two close?
Can't answer?
Get yourself ready to be in the cheer room this evening.
I'll set a meeting for juniors
including you.
Dino, Rak, how long have you been waiting?
Hello.
Did you come with them?
Yes, I asked them to be here but we're about to leave.
What are you doing here?
Actually, it's our businesses.
But it's not a secret if you want to know.
We're discussing about the Faculty's star.
Faculty's star? This boy?
Are you kidding me?
I didn't said that.
Rak and Chalarm are friends.
We wanted Chalarm to participate but he denied.
So, I just want Rak to recommend others.
You know we have to do the Faculty's star contest after cheering end, right?
Yes, I know.
Yeah, that's it.
Don't think we don't know what you did.
I hope this boy doesn't get any privilege during cheering time.
There haven't been any problems yet.
And there won't be.
I heard that you gave our batch's gear to the one who's not participating in any activites.
She's a girl.
And also your girlfriend.
Isn't this called privilege?
Fine, see you at the college.
Let's go.
You come with me.
Dino, you go back alone
otherwise they'll catch it.
Thank you, Please.
Thank you.
We arrived.
Yes.
Coming with me makes you sign like that?
Not like that.
So,
Did you just hang out with Dino?
It's not hanging out.
He needed to buy a new phone.
Really?
His phone is dead.
I knew.
Why did you go there?
I just bought some snacks.
It has a shop there.
You seem to like it.
Yes, I like it.
Well...
How are things
between you two?
We take thing slow.
Umm.
Hey, Please.
Hmm?
Do you have a crush on Dino?
I need to go I have to attend the cheering practice.
Wait!
About...
me having a crush on Dino.
Am I that transparent?
You seem to dislike me since you saw me at Dino's room.
Dino has never brought anyone to his room.
He has never been in love.
And he has never had a crush on anyone.
I'm sorry for saying bad things to you on that night.
It's ok.
Anyway, I still want to warn you.
Because the seniors aren't happy that Dino is a SOTUS leader.
If he makes another mistake,
he might got ban from being a leader.
Did you know that he didn't want to be a leader
if it's not because of you.
Don't make his intention a waste.
Why?
You'd better ask him yourself.
Yes.
Um.
There's nothing between me and you then.
About me having a crush on him,
I don't know whether he knows it or not.
Please don't tell him.
I still want to be friend with him.
And...
please take care of Dino.
I believe that he won't hurt you.
I'll take good care of him.
Um.
I think we're cleared.
I have to go.
Bye.
Bye, Please.
Hey!
Do you remember what we talked about yesterday?
You guys don't understand, right?
She said 'Do you remember what we talked about yesterday?'
Ahhh.
Keep listening, soon you'll get used to it.
I'll be the translator in the beginning.
What?
Big surprise.
Today we have a big surprise.
We're not going to do the ragging.
Be quiet, please.
No, you have to be more aggressive.
Be quiet!
Can you make a frown face?
Guys, be quiet.
Like this?
I did a frown face already.
Argh! You!...
What happened to your face? Why is it so stiff?
I had botox injections because you said I'll look nicer!
Freshmen! Silence!
Remember what I told you?
If you interrupt
and don't stay quiet,
how could you hear what the seniors are saying?
If you have no manners like this
we won't allow you to do activities
but we'll go back to our ragging session, shall we?
Pay attention when we asked you to listen.
You may continue.
Er... as we said earlier,
today we're not gonna be ragging you or ask you to sing any songs.
Instead, we prepared a fun activity for you!
It's called Brotherhood bonding activity!
Yayyy!
You know? This Brotherhood bonding activity...
we spent 3 days trying to come up with a name.
What do you think?
The name suggests that the goal is to strengthen bonds.
However...
freshmen and sophomores are already quite close.
No worries, though.
Sophomores won't participate.
We'll give juniors a chance to get close to you.
Each SOTUS leader will team up with a freshman.
But don't get your hopes up too early
thinking you'll be paired with a charming senior
because men can only pair up with men
and women with women.
This is for safety purpose, so don't violate it, alright?
That's it, leaders can start selecting now!
Yay! // Hooray!
Ahem!
Please choose one freshman.
Who caught your interest?
I choose Rak.
Okay! Rak it is!
However, you don't have Rak in your team yet.
Because... // We have a special rule!
That is... juniors can choose the freshman that's already chosen.
They can do that? // Yes! // What a surprise!
And freshmen are free to choose who they wanna be with.
Ah, you have the right to choose.
This rule is so interesting.
Yeah!
So next is Dino's turn.
Who will you choose?
I choose Rak.
Huh?
Woah, Rak is so hot! He's number one!
Then please come out here, Rak.
Rak, choose who you want to be with.
It's all up to you.
Why did you choose me?
Because you'll choose me, am I right?
Babe?
Um.
Don't start gossiping just yet!
I know you wanna gossip about them and I do, too.
Rak.
Now you're standing between two handsome seniors.
We're giving you the chance to choose who you wanna team up with.
You'll give me the answer on the count of three.
Drum, please.
and 3!
I choose Dino.
[Thank you for coming into my life]
[and changing my world]
Don't be upset.
You're just not the right person.
Try again.
Choose whoever you want.
Alright? // Yes. // Wonderful!
Everyone, I have to take a quick trip to the restroom.
Rest up and look after yourself.
When we're back we'll continue playing the game:
Brotherhood bonding activity!
*Cheers*
Alright! I'm back!
Three pairs of freshmen and leaders are already here.
Let's give them a round of applause!
Are you ready to listen to the rules?
Yesss.
The name of this game is...
Longer, longer!
Woah. // Yeah!
You are confused why it has to be this name, aren't you?
There's a legend that I'll tell you later.
Let's listen to the rule first. // Ah.
The rule is... we'll give these 3 pairs...
clues to a certain place.
And everyone must work together to decipher the clues. // That's right.
Take last year as an example,
The clue is...
I have 4 eyes, 8 legs... // Woah.
2 tongues, 4 nostrils...
What the heck is that? // and I'm black.
That time, we were sitting like this.
Until dawn.
Yeah, we start thinking from 4 p.m. until dawn.
That's why this game is called "Longer, longer."
And guess what...
the answer is a couple of black dogs in front of the uni!
I was absolutely clueless at the time.
But don't worry, this year's riddles aren't that hard.
If you're ready, should we distribute the riddles?
Here you go. // Okay. // I'm excited to see what you get.
Hey, don't peek!
Here.
Okay, choose one each.
Okay, so all of them already got the clues.
The staff will give you a sign...
This sister will count to three
then you'll set out and find the clues as quickly as possible.
Let's start counting!
1!
Say it clearly.
1!!
2!
3!
Go go! // Yay!
That's all I've got, why don't you count it yourself?
A tree is eating me. I can be opened and closed.
How about that tree? // Let's check it out.
Here?
Are you sure?
This one?
In the sky? Is it the moon? // Huh?
Dino, it's getting dark. // Is that it?
This one?
Rak, what's the last riddle?
It says... I'm in the sky beside the moon.
In the sky and beside the moon?
Dino.
Hm?
The stars are so beautiful tonight.
Indeed.
That side is even more beautiful.
Huh?
Oh, you're right!
It might be over there! Let's go! // Hey!
Dino, where is it?
They all look the same.
Dino, I found it.
Dino.
Can you give me a piggyback ride?
Should I climb up there?
Never mind. You'll get hurt if you fall.
Come on.
Yeah! We got it!
Ouch!
Rak, are you alright?
Are you hurt anywhere?
I'm fine.
How about the star? Where is it?
You should worry about yourself first.
Nursing unit! Over here!
Dino.
I'm not injured
and not that hurt.
It's just an accident.
What I want to say is...
I don't want this to happen.
But it happened, and I'm not seriously hurt.
Dino.
Please don't blame anyone for this.
Try to imagine.
If it's not you and me...
if someone else fall, what will happen?
It's my job to take care of all the freshmen
not just you.
I get it, Dino.
But this only happened to me.
Please don't scold the staff.
I'm still the same rabbit you know.
You're as cute as always, rabbit.
Here's the star.
I'm... leaving first.
How about the paper star jar?
Er...
I'll add some more
because you made me feel really good today.
I'm waiting for it to be full.
Hmm, Dino!
Don't do this.
I'm off!
[You're talented at making a man think about you]
[and yearn for you every day]
Hey, Rak.
Let me tie a thread for you.
Don't mess with my man.
Hey!
Mind your own business.
Sorry.
Can you switch places with him?
Dino.
You didn't have to say it like that.
Can't you talk nicely?
You have no idea...
how long I've been waiting for you today.
Be a good boy
for your dad and me.
You know?
Constant dripping wears away the stone.
What if the stone... is taken?
There's zero chance for everyone else.
Should I bang you right now?
Why not?
I'll take you to Chiang Mai after this.
Your only answer is yes.
Hm.
I'm going.
[Is love at first sight real?]
[Just saw you passing by without saying a word]
Don't let anybody else tie it.
There's no one else, except you.
[Why did I fall for you?]
Chalarm.
Chalarm!
The professor is coming.
Wake up.
Huh?
The professor is coming.
Where are you going today?
What do you mean?
The orientation's already ended.
So are you going to work?
Um.
Mhee's bar is closed today.
So there's no work.
And you?
Are you going home?
Yes, I am.
Um.
When will you be back?
On Monday.
Chalarm.
When you're back,
bring some pies for me.
Mhm.
Chalarm.
I heard buddy lines are giving out snacks.
Really?
Have you heard about it?
No.
And I don't want to.
But there could be many kinds of snacks.
Both savory and sweet.
And also ice creams.
Chalarm.
Are there any things you like...
aside from Omelette?
I only like Omelette.
Just. Omelette.
Oh.
Chalarm!
Argh.
No more sleep.
Ask whatever you want.
Hello.
I had no idea you'd be my buddy.
Hm.
Me neither.
Look. Dino is giving me the side eye.
Rak~
Here's snacks for you.
Ah, thank you.
Well.
You're really adorable.
No doubt one SOTUS leader never leave your side.
Haha.
Enjoy eating.
Thank you.
Speak of the devil.
Yo. Come here.
Stay out of trouble.
I gotta go. Enjoy!
Hey.
Have you finish packing?
Yes.
Don't forget to bring a sweater.
Or should I bring it for you?
I have it ready.
How about pants, socks, and gloves?
I've already packed them all.
I'm reminding you, not letting you talk back, understand?
Dino!
Hmph, my cheeks hurt.
What? // It's swollen.
Again? // No! Enough.
Wait here.
I'll be right back.
Yes.
Eh.
Is this for real?
Are you really my buddy?
Hm.
Chalarm.
Is it real?
Not sure.
Ha?
Say it again. Are you really my buddy?
May be?
Is that so?
Argh.
You are my buddy?
My head hurts enough with Suea alone.
What the f*ck are you saying??
Hey!
If it's not because of me,
there will be no Rak.
Remember that!
Do you want a beating?
Oh, sure!
How ungrateful.
Ah, stop it, guys.
Er...
You're
Chalarm?
Yes.
I'm Mhee, a senior.
And these are Dino and Suea.
Guess you know them.
So should we have a meal together?
How about pork buffet? // Your treat.
Suea.
I invited you guys.
Of course it's on me.
Why are you this stupid?
Bro.
It's just confusion,
not stupidity.
No.
You're stupid.
Hey!
Are you asking for trouble?
Why can't you be grateful?! // You started this.
i don't eat pork buffet.
I don't like pork.
Wait, are you serious?
You don't?
I don't.
Er... so...
what do you like to eat?
Shabu?
Seafood buffet?
Omakase?
Or Fine dining?
What's your favorite?
Choose what you want. Mhee will take care of the bill.
Omelette with rice.
Huh?
I want to eat omelette.
Ah, alright.
Omelette.
That's settled?
Okay.
The end.
I got a headache.
Chalarm.
You damn bastard!
Hmph.
From...
Pork buffet, Shabu,
Seafood buffet, Omakase and Fine dining...
to just an omelette?
Objection! You're not my buddy!
Ha, I'm heartbroken.
Don't mind him. I'll buy you a drink.
Chalarm, my dear brother.
Let's eat omelette together.
Lemme give you a kiss.
Let's eat omelette.
Go!
[When will you be my lover?]
Directed by Zanook and Tonnam Piamchon.
Dinosaur Love's uncut version is only available at IQIYI and iQ.com
[I’m not imagining things]
[You're talented at making a man think about you]
[and yearn for you every day]
[When will you be my lover?]
[I'm counting the days until I can be yours]
[I smile every time we meet]
[And you feel the same way]
That's right.
I'm very possessive of the one I love.
When someone gets close to my lover,
I'll be just as you saw.
And I'm quite unlucky...
for being shot. But it's not serious.
I planned to keep it a secret from Rak.
But Mhee told him.
It let me know that Rak worried about me, though.
We got to be so close...
that I can't suppress my feelings.
Rak's cheeks really smell nice.
His neck too.
And
We've come this far,
so you might know that I wanna promote Ichitan.
Buy it. It tastes really good.
(Tha Phae Gate)
Chalarm.
Your hair color...
Dino!
Your hair color!
And you?
Are you ready to bemine?
[When will you be my lover?]
I...