♪The evening breeze grows cooler♪
♪Gently swaying the bells of time♪
♪Do you still remember
when the pear blossoms were fragrant♪
♪Can the scars carved deep be mended♪
♪Navigating layers of past illusions♪
♪Searching for light among the cracks♪
♪Even if the abyss lies ahead♪
♪It can't hide the brightness
in your eyes♪
♪Life is vast
I defy the barriers of fate♪
♪Holding tight to the promise we made♪
♪No longer wanting to dwell
on the unforeseen hardships♪
♪In this moment, by your side♪
♪Love and hate flow through
this world like tides♪
♪Destiny is hard to define♪
♪Only in a moment of trance
the memories still♪
=Scent of New Dawn=
=Episode 15=
(Wanxiang Department Store)
We're now offering a deal.
Take a look at this.
Take care.
Come back next time!
Hello, guest.
Get lost.
Get lost, now.
Get lost, hurry.
Get out!
What are you doing?
Take both of these crates.
No, you can't take them.
Why not?
We paid for them.
How can you take them?
We can't take them, huh?
Beat them.
Beat them to death.
Stop!
The Chamber of Commerce
asked us to take them back.
(Chamber of Commerce?)
Tell them to stop.
I'll personally return the goods.
I can tell them to stop,
but you must agree
to be my concubine first.
Great.
Did you see that?
In broad daylight,
the shop owner actually hit me.
You barged in
and tried to rob them first.
Now you're turning the tables?
Didn't you see them hitting me?
So what if they did?
Consider yourself lucky.
I could even shoot you.
Miss Gu.
Shoot me.
Right here, come on!
Shoot me!
Shoot me right here!
Yanran,
they're here to cause trouble.
Don't fall for their trap.
You don't dare shoot?
You should've said so earlier.
Come on, brothers,
take the goods!
Hurry!
Hurry up!
You can't take them!
You!
What are you doing?
Let him go! Stop!
Let go!
Go away!
Did you see that?
The shop owner fired a gun in public!
She's trying to harm innocent civilians!
Make way!
Firing a gun in public is illegal.
Take her.
- Yes.
Do you know who I am?
My brother is Gu Liancheng!
If you take me, he won't let you off!
Wanyue.
He's the leader.
He's the one who beat us
and smashed our shop.
Take her too.
Yes.
And
clerks from Wanxiang,
Wanyue!
take them all!
Yes.
Wanyue!
Brothers.
Yes!
Follow me!
Oh, Governor!
You dare touch my people?
Oh, Governor.
This is a misunderstanding.
I already
let them go.
Governor.
Arresting my sister
is already a capital offense.
Governor, don't shoot.
How would I dare
hurt Miss Gu,
your sister?
Ouch!
Speak!
Where is she?
She...
Well...
Liancheng.
Governor.
Look,
isn't she right here?
Your superior came to fetch her.
How could I refuse?
My superior?
Brother Gu.
What superior?
That's too formal.
Mr. Feng?
Brother Gu.
It's been so long
since we parted in Nanjing.
Brother Gu,
I've been so worried about you.
I heard
you were recently ambushed.
How's your recovery?
Are you alright now?
Thanks for your concern, Mr. Feng.
I'm fine now.
An assassination is no small matter.
By the way,
have you found out who was behind it?
Not yet.
But with time,
we'll get it out of him.
That won't do.
These matters require
swift, precise action.
Dragging it out won't help.
How about this?
I'll help interrogate.
Mr. Feng,
why is my prisoner
in your hands?
It's a minor issue.
Who holds him doesn't matter,
as long as we get the truth.
No one is perfect.
If you confess honestly
about who sent you,
I'll ask the governor
to show mercy
and let you go.
Mr. Feng,
it was...
It was my own mistake.
No one sent me.
Good.
At least you take responsibility.
Alright,
apologize to the governor,
and if he's generous,
he'll spare you.
Thank you, Governor!
Thank...
A traitor who betrays his own superior
doesn't deserve to live.
You already knew who was behind it,
but you didn't want me to keep digging.
Nice move, Mr. Feng.
Silencing the witness
and cutting off my lead.
I killed the man
you wanted dead.
I protected the person
you wanted to protect.
You owe me one,
whether you like it or not.
Oh, right.
Brother Gu,
think carefully.
Don't waste
the prime seat I've saved for you.
Please.
This gentleman
(Sato, Japanese merchant)
is a friend from Japan.
Mr. Sato
is doing business in Jiang City
and will be
stationed here long-term.
Since fate brought us together,
let's keep in touch.
We're all brothers.
Here.
It seems
the governor doesn't
want to drink with me.
It's not that.
There just isn't enough wine.
All of this would be enough.
Apologies.
I'm late.
It's my fault.
I'll take a penalty drink.
I'll drink.
It's my fault.
Drinking alone isn't enough.
Let me show some hospitality.
Here.
Mr. Zhang
is very sincere.
Master Zhang,
you really know how to do business.
Liancheng,
let's purchase this summer's
military mosquito coils
from Master Zhang.
I've approved it.
As for the payment,
you'll cover it first.
Come on, let's keep drinking.
Come.
Drink.
Master Zhang, please.
(Liancheng,)
(the wind may uproot trees,)
(but it can't bend grass.)
Sometimes, a man must bow his head.
And if I refuse?
(A snake struck at its weak spot dies.)
(A dragon touched at
its scale is wounded.)
(Brother Gu,)
(you're not alone in this world.)
(Yanran, don't blame me.)
(I can't let you take the risk.)
Starting tomorrow,
watch Miss Gu carefully.
She can't leave the manor.
Yes.
Father,
I hear the Japanese
influence is growing.
I don't think
Gu Liancheng is a threat anymore.
Gu Liancheng?
He's just this.
(Bishop)
This game isn't over yet.
Father,
what's our next move?
(Pawn)
Move it.
At a crucial moment like this,
what can a mere pawn do?
Never be careless when you're ahead.
A pawn crossing the river
is still a threat.
(Cannon)
Sir,
I'm here to collect
the sandalwood powder.
We're not selling.
Sir,
don't go back on your word.
I have the order form right here.
I pay you,
and you sell me the goods.
Xiaohu,
right now in Jiang City,
you won't find any sandalwood powder.
Go back
and tell your master
to give up.
What?
Wait.
Sir,
you can't refuse to sell.
Without sandalwood powder
as an adhesive,
we can't make incense!
Sir,
I beg you,
please sell it to me.
If you sell,
I'll do anything to thank you.
I can't sell it.
Wait, sir.
Great.
Xiaohu.
Ergou.
You'll do anything?
You said so.
Xiaohu, help me!
Xiaotao?
- Xiaohu!
- Mother?
Mother!
You...
Xiaohu, you have two choices.
Either
we kill your mother right now.
Or
you strip your woman naked
for everyone to see.
I'll kill you!
Go ahead!
Kill me!
Xiaohu!
Come on!
Kill me!
Let go of me!
Look at what you've done.
You're really ungrateful.
If it were me,
I'd just strip her right away.
So tomorrow,
I could find another woman.
Right?
That's right, brother.
Mother...
Oh?
So you don't want
to save your mother, huh?
That makes sense.
She's old and doesn't have much time left.
But this woman
can keep you company for a bit.
I didn't expect this.
Xiaohu,
turns out you're a devoted man.
Ergou,
I don't want the sandalwood powder.
I don't want it.
Hey,
how can you say that?
I already brought it to you.
Here, take it.
Here it is!
You think you can just ask for it
and then refuse it?
You think you can treat me like a dog?
Then I'll trade my life for it.
Xiaohu!
Ergou,
tell them to let me go.
I...
I'll take off my clothes.
No!
No, Xiaotao!
Ergou,
we're from the same place.
Please spare us, okay?
I beg you.
Beg me?
Begging me now?
Where were you before?
Where were you?
Now you want to beg me?
Come here.
Ergou,
we're from the same place.
I beg you.
- Alright.
- Please spare us.
Let me be honest with you.
Since I first laid eyes on Xiaotao,
well,
I've been dying to know
what she looks like
underneath her clothes.
You beast!
Ergou, you beast!
- You beast!
- People like him
are just too much.
Ergou!
You beast!
Xiaotao.
Shameless.
Come here.
Shameless!
Get closer to me.
Xiaotao.
No!
Do it.
Folks,
since you're all here,
let's all have a look at this.
You beast, Ergou!
Xiaotao!
Red.
Bright red.
My lucky color.
Seeing red excites me.
Hurry up and strip!
Come on!
Let me help you.
No!
Ergou, let Xiaotao go!
I'll do whatever you want!
Good.
Now that's a real man.
Ah, enough.
Why did you do that to them?
Xiaohu,
I respect you.
You're a man of loyalty and love.
Don't worry.
I won't kill you.
I won't touch them either.
I'll even give you
one way out.
(Pawn)
(Cannon)
(As long as you burn down
the warehouse at Wanxiang,)
(I'll let these two women go.)
Mother,
Xiaotao,
I'm sorry.
♪Moonlight climbs onto the windowsill♪
♪Carrying a faint fragrance♪
♪When you and I entered
this abyss together♪
♪The sound of silver bells entangled us♪
♪Pear blossoms fall like snow
on your brows♪
♪Memories entwine reality♪
♪The cycle of stars continues,
only you anchor me♪
♪Through joys and sorrows♪
♪So many obsessions, all in vain♪
♪So many promises,
ultimately unfulfilled♪
♪I only hope to be with you♪
♪Wind sweeps through the mottled years;
the path ahead is rough♪
♪You're the sole spark of light
in the endless darkness♪
♪Yet, if the ending separates us
by life and death♪
♪Is it still worth it?♪
♪We're trapped in this river of time,
brushing past in silence♪
♪Lifelong devotions
have scattered like dust♪
♪Love is hard to let go,
but we still remember each other♪
♪We embraced once♪
♪Pear blossoms fall like snow
on your brows♪
♪Memories entwine reality♪
♪The cycle of stars continues,
only you anchor me♪
♪Through joys and sorrows♪
♪So many obsessions, all in vain♪