♪The evening breeze grows cooler♪
♪Gently swaying the bells of time♪
♪Do you still remember
when the pear blossoms were fragrant♪
♪Can the scars carved deep be mended♪
♪Navigating layers of past illusions♪
♪Searching for light among the cracks♪
♪Even if the abyss lies ahead♪
♪It can't hide the brightness
in your eyes♪
♪Life is vast
I defy the barriers of fate♪
♪Holding tight to the promise we made♪
♪No longer wanting to dwell
on the unforeseen hardships♪
♪In this moment, by your side♪
♪Love and hate flow through
this world like tides♪
♪Destiny is hard to define♪
♪Only in a moment of trance
the memories still♪
=Scent of New Dawn=
=Episode 24=
The ancients said,
at 50, one understands destiny.
I have come this far
by following the tide.
Now,
the Empire of Japan
is thriving,
leading East Asia
in harmony and prosperity.
It's an unstoppable force.
I'm unworthy
yet honored by Mr. Sato's recognition,
serving as the chairman
of the Sino-Japanese Liaison Committee.
From now on,
I look forward to your support.
Cheers.
Thank you, Chairman Zhang.
Oh, Qiao.
You're a rare sight.
Governor Wang,
you're not from Jiang City,
so you wouldn't know Qiao's story.
Come, let me tell you.
Oh, a story?
This is the famous
Qiao of Jiang City.
Back then,
Qiao of Jiang City
was the top courtesan
of Qinhuai Pavilion.
Her first night
was sold for an exorbitant price.
Mr. Ma of Jiang City spent a fortune
to take Qiao home.
But who would've thought
he wasn't blessed to enjoy it?
The following year,
while heading south to smuggle salt,
he ran into bandits
and was killed.
From then on,
the Ma family
was held together
by Qiao alone.
Oh, quite the remarkable woman.
Ah, but you left out her true specialty.
Ah, right,
I almost forgot.
Back in Qinhuai Pavilion,
Qiao had a unique skill,
one that even money
couldn't always buy a glimpse of.
Oh my.
What kind of skill?
I was fortunate to witness it
once in Qinhuai Pavilion.
Well,
they say
this skill has a foreign name,
Dogman.
It's said to have been passed down
from the Western courts.
Dogman?
Yes.
Does it mean a dog man?
Ah, Governor Wang,
I heard you studied abroad.
You're knowledgeable.
Qiao,
grant me this favor
and show everyone
your skill for fun.
Come on.
Just for fun.
Bravo!
Bravo! Show us.
Show us.
Are you denying me this favor?
Forget it.
There will be plenty of chances.
Chairman Zhang,
let's drink.
Drink.
Go to Jiang City Private Primary School.
Bring me the child named Ma
from Class Three.
Yes.
Don't touch my son!
That depends on you.
Or do you want to perform
in front of your son?
Housekeeper.
Yes.
I'll do it.
Here's a bone for you.
Come.
Crawl.
Dogman.
Ah.
Bravo.
Applaud.
Wonderful.
Governor Wang, there's something better.
Crawl through.
Dogman.
Hey.
Applaud.
That's not ordinary.
Qiao, get up.
If you keep kneeling,
I'll kill you.
Oh, it's Wanyue.
I've been looking for you.
Didn't expect you to come uninvited.
I wasn't invited
for Master Zhang's birthday,
so I had to come myself.
I even brought you a gift.
Ah.
Ah!
This is a coffin.
This is a coffin!
Outrageous!
You...
What are you doing?
Take her down!
Quick, throw her out!
Throw her out!
Chief Li,
an attack at my doorstep.
Will you intervene?
Chief.
Chief Li.
You're the police chief.
Do you still want your job?
Arrest her!
Will you intervene, Chief Li?
Well,
I'm sorry, Master Zhang.
This matter
is beyond our jurisdiction.
What do you mean?
(Newly appointed Chairwoman
of the Sino-Japanese)
(Liaison Committee, Lin Wanyue)
Sato replaced you.
Rumors can't be trusted.
Chief Li,
tie her up!
Apologies, Master Zhang.
Urgent business at the station.
I must take my leave.
You...
Don't leave just yet.
You haven't finished the meal.
Miss Lin.
Very well.
Since you've come to your senses
and joined Mr. Sato,
then from now on,
we're friends.
This coffin is good.
It symbolizes promotion and wealth.
You're my guest.
Please come inside.
I'd also like to see
Master Zhang's special skill.
Special skill?
Not everyone
can perform such a skill.
Master Zhang is no ordinary person.
Fine.
Bark for me.
No,
that way.
Watch closely.
Don't let her kill Zhang Wencai.
(The show)
(is just beginning.)
Are you crazy?
Ouch.
Hanyi,
please.
I won't disturb you.
Young Master, do you still remember
the tune I taught you?
What if I do?
And what if
I don't?
Things have changed.
It doesn't matter anymore.
You can hate me.
I told you long ago.
The greatest goal of my life
is revenge.
This is medicine for your eyes.
I won't be by your side,
so you must control the dosage yourself.
I no longer wish to see this world.
Is that necessary?
I don't blame you.
Then let's just say
we were never meant to be.
If there is a next life...
Enough.
There won't be.
I only know that
in this life,
you loved me.
That's enough.
Take care, Young Master.
It's you.
It's this man
who personally killed your own son.
Hey!
Open the door!
Open it!
Open...
Stop it!
Open the door!
♪Moonlight climbs onto the windowsill♪
♪Carrying a faint fragrance♪
♪When you and I entered
this abyss together♪
♪The sound of silver bells entangled us♪
♪Pear blossoms fall like snow
on your brows♪
♪Memories entwine reality♪
♪The cycle of stars continues,
only you anchor me♪
♪Through joys and sorrows♪
♪So many obsessions, all in vain♪
♪So many promises,
ultimately unfulfilled♪
♪I only hope to be with you♪
♪Wind sweeps through the mottled years;
the path ahead is rough♪
♪You're the sole spark of light
in the endless darkness♪
♪Yet, if the ending separates us
by life and death♪
♪Is it still worth it?♪
♪We're trapped in this river of time,
brushing past in silence♪
♪Lifelong devotions
have scattered like dust♪
♪Love is hard to let go,
but we still remember each other♪
♪We embraced once♪
♪Pear blossoms fall like snow
on your brows♪
♪Memories entwine reality♪
♪The cycle of stars continues,
only you anchor me♪
♪Through joys and sorrows♪
♪So many obsessions, all in vain♪