♪The evening breeze grows cooler♪
♪Gently swaying the bells of time♪
♪Do you still remember
when the pear blossoms were fragrant♪
♪Can the scars carved deep be mended♪
♪Navigating layers of past illusions♪
♪Searching for light among the cracks♪
♪Even if the abyss lies ahead♪
♪It can't hide the brightness
in your eyes♪
♪Life is vast
I defy the barriers of fate♪
♪Holding tight to the promise we made♪
♪No longer wanting to dwell
on the unforeseen hardships♪
♪In this moment, by your side♪
♪Love and hate flow through
this world like tides♪
♪Destiny is hard to define♪
♪Only in a moment of trance
the memories still♪
=Scent of New Dawn=
=Episode 5=
Master.
Wencai.
Can you spare Qianli this time
for my family's sake,
huh?
Using your family to pressure me again?
I...I didn't mean that.
Twenty years ago,
I bowed to your family's influence.
But now,
my family is the most respected
in Jiang City.
Master.
Master,
he's your favorite son!
Master.
Father.
I...I know I've done wrong.
I acted foolishly.
Father,
I'm sorry.
From childhood to now,
I've spoiled you endlessly.
And yet, you committed
such shameful acts.
Drink this
and preserve our family's reputation.
Father.
We're father and son.
You've given me wealth and luxury,
and treated me with kindness.
I'm a useless son
who has broken moral taboos.
I'll repay your kindness
in another life.
This is the incense shop
managed by Madam Chunxiao.
It's yours to run now.
Thank you, father.
Don't forget to make the perfume
for the governor.
I understand.
Father.
The tea isn't poisoned.
You're my most cherished son.
How could I bear to let you die?
Father.
Father, you've forgiven me?
Remember,
you're the Zhang family's only hope.
Your brother can't compare to you.
Everything I have will one day be yours.
As long as you ask,
I'll give it to you,
even my concubines.
Father.
I...I acted foolishly.
I'll never deceive you again.
Never again.
She was just a woman.
In my eyes,
women are merely money.
But
what belongs to me,
even a needle
or a thread,
it's yours if I give it to you.
If I don't give it,
you must never steal
or snatch it.
Understood?
Yes, father.
I...
I know I've done wrong.
I...I'm sorry.
I'll never do it again.
Father.
Please believe me.
Alright.
Your mother is worried about you.
Go reassure her.
Father,
I'll go at once.
Master,
Young Master Hanyi has gone to the shop.
Keep a close eye on him.
Yes.
I'll prepare immediately.
(Zhang's Incense Shop)
Come again next time.
Hey,
blind man,
what are you doing?
Hey,
over here.
Master has already instructed.
The shop will be managed
by Young Master Hanyi.
Watch your mouth.
You...
Happy now?
Let me make it clear.
In the Zhang family,
there's only Young Master Qianli.
What Young Master Hanyi?
Never heard of him.
Hey, blind man,
get out of here!
Go away.
Who are you?
A maid.
Young Master Qianli's maid?
Young Master Hanyi's maid.
Darn it.
You're Young Master Hanyi's maid...
Hey.
Ouch.
From today on,
I'm the owner of Zhang's Incense Shop.
You may not have heard of me,
but you must respect my maid.
She represents me entirely.
Am I clear enough now?
You just...
You just wait!
Everyone, go back to work.
Yes, Young Master.
Put it there.
I'm sorry, Young Master.
I shouldn't have
strayed too far from you.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Can you check if there's
any fragrance powder on my shoes?
Fragrance powder?
None.
Young Master.
It's nothing.
You walk so quietly.
That way,
I can hear
where you are.
The environment outside Zhang Manor
is too unfamiliar to me.
I need you to stay by my side
at all times
to be my eyes.
I need to always
hear the sound of the silver bells.
Don't make me lose track of you again.
Then,
let me first show you around the shop.
First is the counter area.
All the products are displayed here
for customers to choose from.
This is our incense counter.
Incense is our shop's signature product.
Further inside is the experience room.
Be careful here.
There's a curtain.
Careful now.
There's a sofa here.
The sofas are
the latest Western designs.
Next,
can you smell the fragrance?
This is...
This is
the fragrance workshop.
Young Master.
This is your fragrance workshop.
Young Master,
call out if you need anything.
I'll step out now.
Get out.
Get out,
all of you.
Hurry.
(Zhang's Incense Shop)
Is Young Master Hanyi here?
I'm here for the perfume.
Young Master has prepared
your Ruoshui Perfume.
I'll fetch it right away.
Governor.
We received a telegram.
Miss Gu's ship returned
to Shanghai ahead of schedule.
She's in Shanghai?
Yes.
She's on her way back here.
She even asked in the telegram
about whether you're married.
I'll load the perfume.
(Oh no,)
(I forgot about this.)
Governor,
the perfume you ordered
has been handed to your guards.
(Liancheng,)
(you must find a wife)
(before I return.)
Young Master was checking the goods.
I apologize for the delay.
I'll go get him.
No need.
Bring the box inside.
This is...
I'm taking all your shop's stock.
Close up early today.
Come with me.
May I ask what you mean?
There's no need to be so tense.
I just want you to come back with me
to be my wife for one day.
Your wife?
We'll discuss it further later.
Let's go.
Governor...
Governor, you came.
An esteemed guest arrived,
but you didn't tell me?
Hurry and make tea.
Yes, Young Master.
Your presence graces my humble shop.
I should've welcomed you sooner.
No need for formalities.
I've taken a liking to your maid.
I'll borrow her for a day.
You may not know, Governor,
but Wanyue is my personal maid.
I rely on her due to my disability
and can't do without her.
Did I mishear, Zhang Hanyi?
Even your father wouldn't dare defy me.
Who do you think you are
to refuse me?
In Jiang City,
no one says no to me.
And no one can simply take her from me.
You protect this maid so fiercely.
Don't tell me you're fond of her.
Yes,
I care for her.
As long as you withdraw the request,
I'm willing to do anything.
I admire people with such loyalty.
Since you've said this much,
show me
how deep your feelings truly run.
How should I prove it?
I've heard the hearts
of devoted men weigh heavier.
Today, I'd like to see
if the rumors are true.
If you spare Wanyue,
I'll take my heart out right now.
Hmm.
I, Gu Liancheng,
will keep my word.
Do it.
♪Moonlight climbs onto the windowsill♪
♪Carrying a faint fragrance♪
♪When you and I entered
this abyss together♪
♪The sound of silver bells entangled us♪
♪Pear blossoms fall like snow
on your brows♪
♪Memories entwine reality♪
♪The cycle of stars continues,
only you anchor me♪
♪Through joys and sorrows♪
♪So many obsessions, all in vain♪
♪So many promises,
ultimately unfulfilled♪
♪I only hope to be with you♪
♪Wind sweeps through the mottled years;
the path ahead is rough♪
♪You're the sole spark of light
in the endless darkness♪
♪Yet, if the ending separates us
by life and death♪
♪Is it still worth it?♪
♪We're trapped in this river of time,
brushing past in silence♪
♪Lifelong devotions
have scattered like dust♪
♪Love is hard to let go,
but we still remember each other♪
♪We embraced once♪
♪Pear blossoms fall like snow
on your brows♪
♪Memories entwine reality♪
♪The cycle of stars continues,
only you anchor me♪
♪Through joys and sorrows♪
♪So many obsessions, all in vain♪