♪The evening breeze grows cooler♪
♪Gently swaying the bells of time♪
♪Do you still remember
when the pear blossoms were fragrant♪
♪Can the scars carved deep be mended♪
♪Navigating layers of past illusions♪
♪Searching for light among the cracks♪
♪Even if the abyss lies ahead♪
♪It can't hide the brightness
in your eyes♪
♪Life is vast
I defy the barriers of fate♪
♪Holding tight to the promise we made♪
♪No longer wanting to dwell
on the unforeseen hardships♪
♪In this moment, by your side♪
♪Love and hate flow through
this world like tides♪
♪Destiny is hard to define♪
♪Only in a moment of trance
the memories still♪
=Scent of New Dawn=
=Episode 27=
I want to see Sato.
Sato.
Young Master Zhang.
You
are my final spice.
Young Master Zhang,
I've handed the incense to Mr. Sato.
Please go back and rest.
He'll come to see you.
This is
the true maiden incense.
What are you doing?
You're not Wanyue.
Where did you
get this hairpin?
I picked it up in the hallway just now.
(Then do as you said.)
I hope you'll survive.
As for what exactly
the maiden incense is,
I'll think it over again.
Wanyue.
Sato.
I want to see Wanyue.
Wanyue.
This medicine for treating
the eyes is effective,
but the dosage must
be strictly controlled.
If overdosed,
although it can restore vision,
it'll also be lethal.
If Sato is poisoned by One Thought,
his subordinates will
immediately know it's you.
You still won't escape.
So,
I didn't choose a lethal poison,
but a hallucinogenic one.
It can make people hallucinate,
like moths drawn to a flame,
seeking their own demise.
Jerk.
Wanyue.
Shijinosuke.
I miss you so much.
Father.
I was wrong, father.
Sweetheart.
My daughter.
Don't be afraid.
It's okay.
Who are you?
I'm here to help you.
Can you take me to the riverbank?
No.
You can't die.
But living is so painful.
If I die, I won't be beaten every day.
I won't have to starve anymore.
You must live on.
One day, you'll meet
a very important person.
You must wait until that day,
understood?
Live on.
Don't die.
Understood?
Come on.
Last time wasn't enough.
Let's fight again.
Brother Gu.
Hurry up.
Stop waiting.
Hurry!
Why are you standing there?
Stop spacing out.
Hey!
Brother Gu.
What are you doing?
Two grown men
in broad daylight.
Hey!
If you don't let go,
I'll throw you over!
Brother.
Zhang Hanyi!
Why are you hugging my brother?
Only I can hug my brother.
- Come on.
- If you want to hug,
go home and hug Wanyue.
♪I have a tale to tell♪
♪For all the gentlemen to listen♪
♪Gentlemen, please♪
♪Calm your hearts and minds♪
♪Let me sing♪
Young Master.
The osmanthus powder is sold out again.
Hurry inside and restock.
Miss Wanyue is overwhelmed.
Come on, Young Master.
Xiaohu.
Wanyue.
Young Master.
Come inside.
You came.
Why are you standing there?
Come over.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying,
huh?
I'm reluctant.
I'm afraid
the next moment,
the happiness will be gone.
Don't worry.
We'll always be this happy.
You don't smell like Wanyue.
You aren't Wanyue.
I am Wanyue.
If you stay,
I'll be very happy.
No.
You aren't Wanyue.
I'm going back to save her.
Stay.
In a moment, you'll be able to see.
I should've killed you,
you wretched child.
Wanyue.
♪Moonlight climbs onto the windowsill♪
♪Carrying a faint fragrance♪
♪When you and I entered
this abyss together♪
♪The sound of silver bells entangled us♪
♪Pear blossoms fall like snow
on your brows♪
♪Memories entwine reality♪
♪The cycle of stars continues,
only you anchor me♪
♪Through joys and sorrows♪
♪So many obsessions, all in vain♪
♪So many promises,
ultimately unfulfilled♪
♪I only hope to be with you♪
♪Wind sweeps through the mottled years;
the path ahead is rough♪
♪You're the sole spark of light
in the endless darkness♪
♪Yet, if the ending separates us
by life and death♪
♪Is it still worth it?♪
♪We're trapped in this river of time,
brushing past in silence♪
♪Lifelong devotions
have scattered like dust♪
♪Love is hard to let go,
but we still remember each other♪
♪We embraced once♪
♪Pear blossoms fall like snow
on your brows♪
♪Memories entwine reality♪
♪The cycle of stars continues,
only you anchor me♪
♪Through joys and sorrows♪
♪So many obsessions, all in vain♪