♪The evening breeze grows cooler♪
♪Gently swaying the bells of time♪
♪Do you still remember
when the pear blossoms were fragrant♪
♪Can the scars carved deep be mended♪
♪Navigating layers of past illusions♪
♪Searching for light among the cracks♪
♪Even if the abyss lies ahead♪
♪It can't hide the brightness
in your eyes♪
♪Life is vast
I defy the barriers of fate♪
♪Holding tight to the promise we made♪
♪No longer wanting to dwell
on the unforeseen hardships♪
♪In this moment, by your side♪
♪Love and hate flow through
this world like tides♪
♪Destiny is hard to define♪
♪Only in a moment of trance
the memories still♪
=Scent of New Dawn=
=Episode 3=
Master,
better not force it.
I've long grown tired
of matters between men and women.
I'm not tired yet.
I still want it.
Master.
I'll strangle you, you wretched woman.
I'll strangle you!
Go back to your courtyard now.
Without my permission,
you're not allowed to leave.
Did you hear me?
Yes.
My father
can't get it up?
Yes.
That's why I can't be pregnant.
It's almost showing.
Think of something.
We can't keep the baby.
I can't leave the manor.
Buy the miscarriage medicine.
Remember, don't buy it in Jiang City.
And be quick.
So much trouble.
Fine,
leave it to me.
Stay out of it.
Let's go.
They're gone.
You've learned so many secrets
on one night.
What's your next move?
Stay still for now.
Secrets held in hand
are like a sword.
If you strike at the wrong time,
you'll only hurt yourself.
Let's go.
Madam Mu,
why don't you try this?
This will cover the scars.
When did you come in?
Two days ago, I accidentally got hurt
and have been using this balm.
See? It covers them completely.
Leave.
Madam Mu, don't fear me.
Let me help you.
Come, apply this first and see.
Look.
We can try.
Just try.
See?
It's completely covered.
It's really gone.
I just
don't want
anyone to see the scars on me.
I understand.
You have one on your neck as well.
Don't move.
Done.
This is my mother's secret formula.
Isn't it effective?
I don't think
I've ever seen you before.
Which courtyard are you from?
Madam Mu,
I'm from Young Master Hanyi's courtyard.
You can call me Wanyue.
Thank you.
Stop.
You're Wanyue?
Yes.
Madam Chunxiao.
You're the one Qianli mentioned,
the wretched woman.
Madam Chunxiao,
did I do something wrong?
You're a maid.
Do I need a reason to hit you?
How dare you hit me?
Madam Chunxiao,
I must return this slap.
My mother said I've had demonic energy
since I was little.
If someone hits me,
I must hit them back.
Otherwise, the one who hit me
will lose their blessings.
You dare mock me?
I haven't finished.
Madam Chunxiao.
What I have to say is crucial,
but
I can only tell you.
It's true.
Please believe me.
Madam Chunxiao,
I know your secret.
Don't provoke me.
Otherwise,
I'll let the entire household know.
Madam Chunxiao,
I won't do it again.
Please spare me.
Go.
Thank you.
You said you want revenge
on Zhang Wencai.
What's the plan?
Though the Zhang family is large,
it's far from indestructible.
We can break it down step by step,
from the inside out.
With just a blind man
and a maid?
I'll be your eyes,
so you won't be blind.
You'll be my backbone,
so I'll no longer be a maid.
(Even so,)
(we're just two ants
clinging to each other for warmth.)
(Without strength,)
(how can we bring down a mountain?)
(Since we don't have strength,)
(we must find a way)
(to obtain it.)
(What do you plan to do?)
Young Master,
to bring down Zhang Wencai,
what we need
is a higher patron.
And now, that patron
has already arrived at the gate.
(Gu Liancheng, Governor of Jiang City)
Ah,
you're indeed unpretentious, Governor.
Indeed a true soldier's demeanor
and a pillar of the nation.
Spare me the pleasantries.
I asked you to recreate
a perfume for me.
Today,
I've come to collect it.
Of course.
Governor, please come in.
So
you already knew
the governor would come here?
And you knew
how to use him.
There's a certain scent
the governor has sought for two years.
No one else has been
able to recreate it.
I've heard the Zhang family
are the top incense makers.
Master Zhang, don't let me down.
Governor,
rest assured.
My master
fully understands your intention.
Young Master,
this is your chance.
As long as you gain
the governor's favor,
he'll be our patron.
Do you know the saying,
"Being near the patron
is like being near a tiger"?
Indeed, he's a tiger,
but also a strong support.
With him as support,
we can act against Zhang Wencai
without fear.
Great.
You broke
one of the pair of vases
used by Emperor Chongzhen,
leaving the other
as the only one of its kind.
Well done.
Zhang Wencai,
you're trying to fool me with these?
There's something more substantial.
Carry it in.
Governor.
If I wanted money,
would I need to play games with you?
Three days.
I'll give you three more days.
If you can't create the perfume
I want in three days,
it won't just be vases that get smashed,
huh?
Take it away.
Don't waste Master Zhang's
good intentions.
I'll leave it to you, Master Zhang.
You're so sure
he'll give the task to me?
Master,
I've asked all the incense makers
in Jiang City.
They said
there's no scent
in it.
It seems the governor
is determined to have it.
But we can't recreate it.
Master Zhang,
Young Master Hanyi is quite talented.
Why not let him try?
If he succeeds,
it'll be a pleasant surprise.
He's my own flesh and blood.
What if he fails?
Let him take the blame?
Forgive me.
Some sins are best borne
by one's own
flesh and blood.
♪Moonlight climbs onto the windowsill♪
♪Carrying a faint fragrance♪
♪When you and I entered
this abyss together♪
♪The sound of silver bells entangled us♪
♪Pear blossoms fall like snow
on your brows♪
♪Memories entwine reality♪
♪The cycle of stars continues,
only you anchor me♪
♪Through joys and sorrows♪
♪So many obsessions, all in vain♪
♪So many promises,
ultimately unfulfilled♪
♪I only hope to be with you♪
♪Wind sweeps through the mottled years;
the path ahead is rough♪
♪You're the sole spark of light
in the endless darkness♪
♪Yet, if the ending separates us
by life and death♪
♪Is it still worth it?♪
♪We're trapped in this river of time,
brushing past in silence♪
♪Lifelong devotions
have scattered like dust♪
♪Love is hard to let go,
but we still remember each other♪
♪We embraced once♪
♪Pear blossoms fall like snow
on your brows♪
♪Memories entwine reality♪
♪The cycle of stars continues,
only you anchor me♪
♪Through joys and sorrows♪
♪So many obsessions, all in vain♪