♪The evening breeze grows cooler♪
♪Gently swaying the bells of time♪
♪Do you still remember
when the pear blossoms were fragrant♪
♪Can the scars carved deep be mended♪
♪Navigating layers of past illusions♪
♪Searching for light among the cracks♪
♪Even if the abyss lies ahead♪
♪It can't hide the brightness
in your eyes♪
♪Life is vast
I defy the barriers of fate♪
♪Holding tight to the promise we made♪
♪No longer wanting to dwell
on the unforeseen hardships♪
♪In this moment, by your side♪
♪Love and hate flow through
this world like tides♪
♪Destiny is hard to define♪
♪Only in a moment of trance
the memories still♪
=Scent of New Dawn=
=Episode 16=
Xiaotao.
Xiaotao, your hand.
Xiaotao, don't move.
Give it to me.
Don't save me.
Xiaotao.
Let me die.
Xiaotao, listen to me.
This is
from Xiaohu.
I beg you, open it and take a look.
Just open it first, okay?
This is what Xiaohu saved up.
(Land Title Deed)
It was Xiaohu's last wish.
He hoped you can carry his share
and live on.
Xiaohu.
We must work hard
diligently and earnestly.
(Once we save up enough money,)
(we'll buy a home of our own.)
(We'll never worry about
being homeless.)
(Xiaohu, what do you think?)
Alright.
I promise you.
In the future,
I'll make sure you live a good life.
(Land Title Deed)
Wanyue,
we're just ordinary people.
We just want to survive.
- It's alright.
- Why is it so hard?
It's okay.
Things will get better.
Let's take Xiaotao away first.
Alright.
Come on.
Get up.
Wait.
Someone's coming.
All this crying is so inauspicious.
Well,
Miss Wanyue, you're here.
Xiaotao,
in a moment,
just watch closely.
Mm.
It's time.
What...
What did you
just pour on me?
Syrup.
Sy...
Syrup?
It's so hot.
Want to taste it?
This is a misunderstanding.
Is this because of Xiaotao?
Xiaotao...
I'll marry her, isn't that enough?
Shut up!
Ah, no!
No!
Xiao...
Xiaotao!
Tell her to stop!
Xiaohu is already dead.
Besides me, who else would want you?
Miss Wanyue.
Xiaotao,
you're the best.
I'll do it myself.
Young Master Zhang,
was Xiaojiu's service
satisfactory last night?
Sure.
Then the money...
Put it on the tab for now.
It's not like I won't pay.
You haven't paid for days now.
Murder!
Ergou!
(A life for a life)
Xiaotao,
take the money for now.
Leave Jiang City for a while.
Stay out of trouble.
I can't take this, Wanyue.
I can't repay this favor.
You don't need to.
But I want you to remember
to never give up on yourself,
okay?
Alright, take care, Wanyue.
Let's go.
Wanyue,
what are you planning next?
The Governor's Manor has sent word.
The situation is unstable.
The governor is unable to help.
Now, if we want
to save Wanxiang Department Store,
We can only rely
on ourselves.
Young Master, do you remember
what the best-selling perfume
in Jiang City was 18 years ago?
Are you referring to Mosquito Repellent?
Exactly.
Because it was easy to carry,
It sold even better than mosquito coils.
If we can recreate Mosquito Repellent,
Wanxiang will come back to life.
But wasn't the formula for it
lost long ago?
What if I told you
I have the formula
for it in my hands?
Governor,
why exactly
did you summon us here?
I have a friend
who wants to meet you.
This is all I can do for you.
Thank you.
Many thanks.
Mm.
Everyone,
no need to be so on guard.
We're here
to make friends with you.
Make friends?
I'm sorry.
I'm not interested.
I'll take my leave first.
Goodbye, everyone.
Are you interested
in Mosquito Repellent,
everyone?
Mosquito Repellent?
You made it?
Don't joke around.
That formula
has been lost for 18 years.
You can check it for yourselves.
It really is the scent
of Mosquito Repellent.
So what if it is?
Business isn't just about quality.
It's also about
connections.
You don't understand.
Don't talk nonsense.
Connections
are determined by profits.
Think about it.
How much money
can Mosquito Repellent make for you?
(Back then, Zhang Wencai schemed
to seize the formula.)
(He even set fire to my home,
killing all my family.)
(But despite his efforts,)
(in the end, all he got
was merely our mosquito coil formula.)
For all these years,
Zhang Wencai has a monopoly
on mosquito coils
to control the Chamber of Commerce.
And our trump card
is Mosquito Repellent.
Only a more profitable product
can deliver a fatal blow
to Zhang Wencai.
If I sell it to you
at one silver coin per bottle,
and you sell it at double the price,
for every bottle sold,
you make one silver coin.
Sell a hundred bottles,
you earn a hundred.
Sell a thousand
you profit over a thousand.
Jiang City
has a population of over 200 thousand.
Of course,
we won't force you
to fall out with Master Zhang.
To show our sincerity,
the Mosquito Repellent we sell to you
won't have Wanxiang's label on it.
Everyone,
what do you think?
But the chairman
of the Chamber of Commerce
is Master Zhang.
What if
my last name is Lin?
Eighteen years ago,
the Lin family that made incense?
(Wanyue, maid of Zhang family)
Is there
(Lin Wanyue, of Lin family)
a second Lin family in Jiang City?
How arrogant of you?
She dares to claim
she's from the Lin family.
Oh wow.
From the Lin family?
I think
she's going to say
she's Lin Zhennan's daughter.
Back then, in that fire,
not a single member
of the Lin family survived.
I saw it with my own eyes.
I think
you're just using the Lin family
to make yourself look good.
The summer before
the Lin family's downfall,
a malaria outbreak occurred.
The market was sluggish.
Everyone here
was losing money.
The Lin family developed
the Mosquito Repellent
and gave it away for free
to help you all
through the crisis.
If I weren't from the Lin family,
how would I have the formula?
If I weren't Lin Zhennan's daughter,
how would I know
these events so clearly?
Well, there's...
there's no proof.
Even the servants
of the Lin family
would know these things, right?
Right, everyone?
Exactly.
Mr. Zheng,
I still remember back then
you lost everything.
And you lived
in our west guest room for a year.
To express your gratitude,
on my birthday,
you gifted me a longevity locket
engraved with my birth name,
Wangshu.
It's...
It's really you?
It's been 18 years.
Have you
only remembered the Zhang family
but forgotten
your benefactors?
I
am no ungrateful man.
You're Mr. Lin's daughter.
I'll support you.
Well,
everyone,
what do you think?
We all
will support you.
(Governor's Manor)
The Four Families have agreed
to purchase the Mosquito Repellent.
It'll officially go on sale tomorrow.
Wanxiang Department Store
will soon reopen.
That's great, Wanyue!
Would you be willing
to return to Wanxiang then?
Of course.
If my brother hadn't locked me up,
I'd have come looking for you already.
You didn't know,
I haven't been eating
or sleeping well these days.
It's great that you're fine.
Otherwise, I'd feel guilty for life.
What's troubling you so much,
Brother Gu?
Sorry, brother.
I haven't helped much recently.
You're joking.
You brought
the Four Families to us.
We're already very grateful.
That was nothing.
If I weren't dealing with some trouble,
I'd have taken care
of Zhang Wencai long ago.
Is the trouble you speak of
related to the Japanese?
Ugh, don't mention it.
Hanyi,
I have a favor to ask of you.
Please, go ahead.
If one day I can
no longer protect her,
can you take Yanran out of Jiang City?
I will,
but I hope that day never comes.
Hey,
I already said "if".
By the way,
don't tell Yanran
I want to send her away.
Brother Gu,
you haven't told her
about your situation yet?
Once the moment is missed,
some things
can never be said again.
Once you hesitate,
some matters
can never be undone.
This is the best choice for now.
Alright,
I promise you.
Thank you, brother.
I said I owed you my life.
Yet in the end,
I still need your help.
Bad news.
None of the four department stores
sold Mosquito Repellent.
I heard
all our stock
was sent to the Zhang Manor.
Is all the stock here?
Don't worry, Master Zhang.
Everything is here.
All four stores
didn't keep a single bottle.
I missed
this scent.
It's a shame.
This Mosquito Repellent
will never bear the Zhang name.
Well.
You traitors!
Heartless ingrates!
Do you have no conscience?
Conscience?
That I can keep
and sell for a good price, huh?
Wanyue.
Wanxiang Department Store
is finished.
♪Moonlight climbs onto the windowsill♪
♪Carrying a faint fragrance♪
♪When you and I entered
this abyss together♪
♪The sound of silver bells entangled us♪
♪Pear blossoms fall like snow
on your brows♪
♪Memories entwine reality♪
♪The cycle of stars continues,
only you anchor me♪
♪Through joys and sorrows♪
♪So many obsessions, all in vain♪
♪So many promises,
ultimately unfulfilled♪
♪I only hope to be with you♪
♪Wind sweeps through the mottled years;
the path ahead is rough♪
♪You're the sole spark of light
in the endless darkness♪
♪Yet, if the ending separates us
by life and death♪
♪Is it still worth it?♪
♪We're trapped in this river of time,
brushing past in silence♪
♪Lifelong devotions
have scattered like dust♪
♪Love is hard to let go,
but we still remember each other♪
♪We embraced once♪
♪Pear blossoms fall like snow
on your brows♪
♪Memories entwine reality♪
♪The cycle of stars continues,
only you anchor me♪
♪Through joys and sorrows♪
♪So many obsessions, all in vain♪