♫ The top of the mountains where the snow never melts ♫
♫ The plains where the wind blows ♫
♫ What finds me in my sleep are the nightmares about you ♫
♫ In the endless abyss ♫
♫ Your face gradually emerges ♫
♫ A love that budded unknowingly to us continues
to grow and blossom ♫
♫ Who risked his life for mine? ♫
♫ I had braced myself for the end, but my heart frets for you ♫
♫ It turns out there is an end to my waiting for you ♫
♫ At the hills where the grasslands end where
it will always be spring ♫
♫ I find the boundless river of stars in your eyes ♫
♫ Only with your hand in mine is this life worthwhile ♫
[Shining Just for You]
[Episode 25]
Who did it?
Any clues?
I asked a few mystics to check Fengyin's body.
They said that they'd never seen...
a body like that.
It's a secret arts skill that has never appeared before.
I suspect that someone is using your wedding to plot something evil.
[Fengyin]
Arrange a grand state funeral for Fengyin.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
I think Supervisor Yong was right.
You shouldn't open the city gate
during your wedding just in case.
We can use this chance
to lure all of them out.
Your Majesty,
you can't do that.
It's okay.
I want to see how capable...
they are.
- You are here.
- It's a happy day today.
- Duke.
Congratulations, Duke.
Chao is fortunate to have you be the Minister of Rites
of His Majesty's wedding today.
My fellow officials.
You are too kind.
I haven't done anything much.
The person who you should congratulate today is His Majesty.
You are right.
Duke.
His Majesty and Her Majesty have already done their morning routine.
According to the flow, it's time for us to go and escort His Majesty.
Okay.
There's no need to rush. We'll just wait here.
Yes, Sir.
[Treasury]
Congratulations on your wedding, Supervisor.
May your love last forever
and be with the stars in the galaxy!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Our guests are already here.
Why don't you go
and welcome them?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Get into position now.
Roger that.
Attack!
Isn't it a little bit too late now?
Report. Duke, Her Majesty will reach Qianyuan Hall soon.
Why is she coming so soon?
Where are your Winged Guards?
I can handle you all by myself.
You knew that I'd be coming.
I knew that you'd be coming.
And I know why you are here.
You annihilated my clan and took away my lover.
Of course, you know why.
Yi Wuyou, you've been refusing to see the truth
about everything and about yourself.
Today, I'll teach you how to see the truth.
Official Fan, shouldn't we depart to Qianyuan Hall now?
- Yes.
- Sir, it's late already.
Guards!
Official Fan, what are you doing?
Something major is happening today.
I don't want any of you to get hurt.
So, please stay here for a while longer.
Do it now!
Be careful with your weapons.
Fan Ruhui.
What are you trying to do?
It...
Just wait.
Just wait for great things to happen.
Put down the carriage!
Your Majesty.
What happened?
There are assassins inside.
Please wait for a moment.
Take me in.
Please obey the order.
Who are they?
They are Fan Ruhui's men. He has revolted.
Let me take you back to the Bureau of Astrology first.
We can come here again when it's safe.
I'm getting married today. I won't go back.
This is His Majesty's order.
Don't put yourself in danger.
We agreed to live and die together.
- Open the gate!
- Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Do you think I don't know what you did in Tianqi?
If it wasn't for me who allowed you to come in,
do you think you could enter Qianyuan Hall today?
For the revival of the Winged Clan,
I should've come and killed you earlier.
If it hadn't been for me,
there would've been no end to the constant wars and divergences among the Nine States.
Even without you, the Nine States would have had an emperor who deserved this position more than you.
The emperor who deserves this position more than I do is not you.
You are going to lose.
Why would I lose?
Your Divine Mirror has shattered.
Who told you that?
I don't need anyone to tell me that.
I know that you hate me for taking her away from you.
Bai Lu is mine.
I will kill you for her.
You don't understand.
Even without me,
you wouldn't get her.
It's okay.
When you are dead, she'll be mine.
I'll prove it.
As the emperor, I'll win.
And as a man, I'll definitely win.
Good.
You deserve to be my opponent.
No!
♫ If you have given up hope ♫
♫ I can't guard against the pain ♫
♫ My feelings have turned into tears ♫
♫ I'll be the wind to smooth out your frown ♫
♫ I don't expect you to understand my feelings ♫
♫ My age is distorted by the memories ♫
♫ Our fate is encumbered by our destiny ♫
♫ Morning after morning and night after night ♫
♫ I'm hurt everywhere ♫
♫ Piecing my broken dreams together with a broken heart ♫
♫ I'll be there for you, even if I have to rip off my wings ♫
♫ Facing each other from a distance ♫
♫ Pulling out, leaving it be ♫
♫ The gap between us is hard to close ♫
♫ All thoughts are blasted ♫
♫ Who wishes to return with me? ♫
♫ If we fall apart in this lifetime ♫
♫ May we find the right path in our next life ♫
♫ My age is distorted by the memories ♫
♫ Our fate is encumbered by our destiny ♫
Your Majesty, please give Yi Wuyou a proper burial.
♫ I'm hurt everywhere ♫
♫ Piecing my broken dreams together with a broken heart ♫
♫ I'll be there for you, even if I have to rip off my wings ♫
I will now confer the title of Winged Emperor to Yi Wuyou.
His body will be sent back to Ningzhou where he will be given a grand funeral.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Are you...
still willing to be my empress?
♫ Pulling out, leaving it be ♫
♫ The gap between us is hard to close ♫
We can't change the past.
Yes.
I will be by your side from now on.
I don't regret it.
I don't regret it, either.
Your Majesty.
Bai Lu, despite what happened, you are still willing to be with me
and stay by my side forever. Right?
Yes.
I'm going to be your empress.
What happened?
- Why are they here?
- What's going on?
The Fan Family has committed treason.
What's happening now?
This is not the end yet.
Yao Song.
Sir.
Arrest the traitor!
What's going on?
Official Fan, Fan Ruhui,
His Majesty already knew about your treachery.
You are doomed now.
You!
- Greetings, Your Majesty.
Be at ease.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Leave us be.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Let me take off your clothes for you.
Your wound.
I'm fine.
You already knew about Fan Ruhui's plan?
Yes.
Is that why you didn't allow me
to enter Qianyuan Hall today?
But I was the one who made the plan for today.
We promised to live together and die together.
He hated me for a long time.
And he'd do anything to kill me.
I couldn't put you in danger.
But not everything...
that happened today was as you expected. Right?
Are you talking about Yi Wuyou?
Yes.
I never thought that he'd acquired an artifact.
But so what?
I... still won.
But you are seriously injured.
I have once promised you
that I would accompany you forever
and travel across the Nine States.
But I'm afraid that this time, I'll have to break my promise.
Your Majesty, it won't happen.
No one can kill you.
I... trusted a lot of people.
And I wanted to share the world with them.
But in the end,
they either wanted to kill me,
or I had no choice but to kill them.
I'm... not afraid of death.
But I feel a smidgen of regret.
The world is so big.
But there are so few who actually understand me.
Bai Lu,
I know that you are the person
who knows me best in this world.
♫ The mountains are my heart ♫
♫ The rivers are my eyes ♫
♫ And the flora is the peace of my heart ♫
♫ Separated from one another ♫
Look. It's a happy day today.
Why are you crying?
Let me dress your wound for you.
I'm fine.
I'll recover tomorrow.
Your Majesty, even if you will recover tomorrow,
your wound will still hurt today.
Let it hurt then.
♫ We enter the battlefield for the peace of the world ♫
♫ Draw the lines of fate, carve destinies ♫
♫ And our roles in the world with me ♫
♫ All worldly desires fall from your fingertips ♫
♫ The mountains and rivers between your brows
orbit the seas like a song ♫
♫ I'll trade my youth for yours ♫
♫ I'll trade my youth for your kiss ♫
♫ We enter the battlefield for the peace of the world ♫
♫ Draw the lines of fate, carve destinies ♫
♫ And our roles in the world with me ♫
♫ All worldly desires fall from your fingertips ♫
♫ The mountains and rivers between your brows
orbit the seas like a song ♫
♫ The stars shine brightly for you and me ♫
Your Majesty, Commander Ling has been waiting outside for a long time.
Your Majesty.
What is it that is so urgent?
Fan Ruhui committed suicide in prison.
Okay, I got it.
Ling Yun. Interrogate the guilty ones of the Fan Family.
Then, give me a list of their crimes.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The assets of the Fan Family have been confiscated.
All of the names of the relatives are on this list.
We've confiscated more than 340,000 gold beads and 2,400 pieces of jewelry.
Commander Ling.
First Young Master.
May I ask about my father and brother?
Your father and brother are already dead.
I've been ordered to confiscate the Fan Family's properties.
Please forgive me.
Long live Your Majesty!
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I... have married my empress according to the will of God.
We are protected by the gods in the celestial world.
The empress's life star complements mine.
From today onward, we will build the world
and protect it together.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
The winged man, Yi Wuyou, colluded with Fan Ruhui to commit treason.
Xie Yu'an.
What's the progress of the investigation?
Your Majesty, Xue Xuanjing and Xue Lanwei have already been killed.
Fan Ruhui committed suicide in prison.
And his second son, Fan Zheng, fell off a cliff to his death during a chase.
The eldest son of the Fan Family, Fan Ping, and the eldest grandson, Fan Tianshou, are not involved in this.
They've been demoted to commoners.
Okay. I got it.
What's the progress of the construction of the canal?
Official Gu, how long and how much money
do you think it'll take to work on the canal?
Your Majesty.
We can start in three months' time.
But it'll be winter in three months.
So, the construction will cost more time.
What do you think?
I've always supported the construction of the canal.
We've asked the people of Ningzhou, Wanzhou, and Lanzhou for their labor service before.
And now, Zhongzhou needs people to strengthen the embankment due to the flood.
We don't have enough people to work on this.
Your Majesty, we haven't asked Yuezhou for their labor service this year.
We can ask them to do that now.
What do you think?
The people of Yuezhou are quite supportive of the construction of this canal.
I think they are the best choice for this job.
Your Majesty, if the people of my clan can complete this project,
I have a favor to ask.
The construction of the canal can help with the flood issue in Zhongzhou.
It'll be an act of kindness.
I hope that you can pardon the people of Yuezhou
who have once gone against you.
Give them the freedom to travel around,
and let them be good citizens of Chao.
That's a great idea.
What you are proposing is the right thing to do.
Of course, I'll pardon them.
We'll do as Her Majesty suggested.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
Please have a seat.
Were you looking at the path of the canal?
Yes.
Official Xie, I have something to ask.
Based on my design of the canal, how many people will be living near the canal?
More than 100,000 people I think.
That many?
What is it? Are you planning something?
I want to use the canal as a pathway for business.
So, I'm thinking, if it's possible, to ask the people near the canal to become merchants.
All of them?
It's really considerate of you to worry about the livelihood of the people.
But it won't be easier than building the canal itself.
I... I can't promise anything.
I understand. Please do your best then.
I will.
After the canal is built, I'll do my best to promote this idea.
You can plan for it beforehand when you get back to Zhongzhou.
I'll do as you say.
Please accept my thanks.
[One Year Later]
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Brother Gu, I heard that the construction of the canal will be completed soon.
That's right. I've completed it on schedule.
After you and His Majesty stamp on the as-built drawing of the canal and name it,
the canal can be open to traffic.
Channel Manager: tony83n_283
Chief Editor: kakashiandme
Please put your stamp on the as-built drawing and name the canal!
Chief Segmenter: bjohnsonwong
Segmenters: dorameiro774, porkypine90_261, sabrinafair, nentelder, raycarneiro, yam_88, tamboreen_266 , kitty100
Moderators: charlie40 (French), sima_330 (Hebrew),
nelliblue (Hungarian), isabellaeldanna (Italian),
luvidal & cahcodognatto (Portuguese),
tony83n_283 (Romanian), azupeque (Spanish)
Cover Designer: dimghro
May Yunwang Canal be useful to our future generations.
Long live the Emperor and Empress of Chao!
After Yunwang Canal was open to traffic,
the Emperor of Chao fell ill.
Fortunately, he managed to recover after receiving an effective prescription.
Sixteen years later, his son took over the throne.
He cut down the taxes for the people and won over his people with his virtue.
He ruled the nation with a kind hand.
Finally, the Nine States were united and in harmony.
Yuezhou that was once remote and isolated
can be reached easily through the canal now.
The once desolate and barren land is now blessed with a bountiful harvest.
Finally, the remaining people of Yebei
gain equality and liberty in Chao.
[The End]
♫ The earth as a plaque ♫
♫ The sun and the moon as a poem ♫
♫ Turn the skies into the palace under the plaque ♫
♫ Time as a scroll ♫
♫ The stars as the inkstone ♫
♫ Writing with the light of the sea ♫
♫ Through several lives and reincarnations ♫
♫ I search the world for wisdom ♫
♫ To smooth the folds of the years ♫
♫ There is a hole in my heart ♫
♫ Void of someone ♫
♫ Now I know what forever tastes like ♫
♫ I'll trade my youth for yours ♫
♫ I'll trade my youth for your kiss ♫
♫ We enter the battlefield for the peace of the world ♫
♫ Draw the lines of fate, carve destinies ♫
♫ And our roles in the world with me ♫
♫ All worldly desires fall from your fingertips ♫
♫ The mountains and rivers between your brows
orbit the seas like a song ♫
♫ I'll trade my youth for yours ♫
♫ I'll trade my youth for your kiss ♫
♫ We enter the battlefield for the peace of the world ♫
♫ Draw the lines of fate, carve destinies ♫
♫ And our roles in the world with me ♫
♫ All worldly desires fall from your fingertips ♫
♫ The mountains and rivers between your brows
orbit the seas like a song ♫
♫ The stars shine brightly for you and me ♫