♫ The top of the mountains where the snow never melts ♫
♫ The plains where the wind blows ♫
♫ What finds me in my sleep are the nightmares about you ♫
♫ In the endless abyss ♫
♫ Your face gradually emerges ♫
♫ A love that budded unknowingly to us continues
to grow and blossom ♫
♫ Who risked his life for mine? ♫
♫ I had braced myself for the end, but my heart frets for you ♫
♫ It turns out there is an end to my waiting for you ♫
♫ At the hills where the grasslands end where
it will always be spring ♫
♫ I find the boundless river of stars in your eyes ♫
♫ Only with your hand in mine is this life worthwhile ♫
[Shining Just for You]
[Episode 7]
Cursed woman, you're everywhere.
Many people of Yebei have died.
But now, you still want to kill each other?
- Ye Lingshuang.
- You're still alive?
Princess Lian. Princess Lian.
Yezi.
That's what happened.
After that, I was sent to Tianqi together with the female captives of Yebei.
What about now?
I wish to find out about the whereabouts of A'Rui in Tianqi.
That's why I joined the Bureau of Astrology.
Now, I'm the director.
Well, well.
So, you've started serving that emperor?
Your Highness, kill her.
The cursed woman has betrayed Yebei.
Chu Ye, calm down.
She's an official of Chao. She serves the emperor.
If we kill her, our location might be exposed.
We will suffer less if she stays away from us.
I was nowhere near during the Battle of Yebei.
Didn't you guys suffer, too?
You'll bring calamity to us as long as you're alive.
Chu Ye, back off.
Yezi, I don't wish to deceive you.
We came to Tianqi to end Yebei's suffering.
We plan to assassinate the Emperor of Chao.
Assassinate the emperor?
But that's too risky.
Of course, I know it's risky.
I would never have believed this if I hadn't seen it for myself.
The Emperor of Chao is inhumane.
What did you say?
That day...
To hell with you!
Dayuangu cast the Hengchen Skyfire Spell.
But even the Skyfire didn't hurt Yu Xiuming at all.
Yu Xiuming was struck by the Skyfire...
but was unharmed?
At least we couldn't tell that he was harmed.
If that's the case, normal methods won't work on him.
Maybe it's because his armor contains extraordinary power.
That's a possibility.
Consort Tian told me that his armor
was crafted by a master blacksmith from the Heluo Clan
using the Glacier Metal gifted by the Kuafu Clan.
He never lets anyone touch it.
He polishes it himself every time.
If it's due to the armor, then we'll stand a chance with this plan.
I plan to sneak into the Ceremony of Stars and assassinate him.
According to the customs, he needs to wear the imperial robe and crown during the ceremony.
He won't be able to wear the armor in that case.
Without the armor's protection, with the princess's celestial power,
I'm sure she can kill him if she uses all her powers.
Princess Lian, please think twice.
Yu Xiuming has always been arrogant.
Even so, he's undefeated.
He probably has something that other people don't.
Anyway, I'll investigate the case for you first.
I'll leave it to you, then.
Yezi,
all this while, Chu Ye and the rest have experienced many misfortunes.
That's why they were harsh with their words.
Don't take their words to heart.
It's fine. I'm already used to it.
The people of Yebei have always treated me like this.
It has never changed, from the past to the present.
It won't happen in the future. I will stop them.
Yezi, to me,
you're just as important as A'Rui.
A'Rui once said that you were her best sister.
She always wanted to be like you.
Now, A'Rui is no longer around.
Can you call me Sister on her behalf?
But Princess Lian...
Call me Sister.
Sister Lian.
Dayuangu's Hengchen Skyfire Spell didn't hurt Yu Xiuming at all?
Could it be...
that he's not a human?
Yun Wen.
Yun Wen?
Master Yun Wen!
Do not interrupt my meditation.
Master, you're wise and knowledgeable.
I have something to ask you.
Say someone was hit by Hengchen Skyfire Spell
but stayed unharmed,
what do you think would be the reason?
I won't tell you even if I knew.
I think you have no idea. You're just trying to confuse me.
Wise and knowledgeable?
You're just boasting. I'm sure you're a fraud.
It's useless.
I won't fall for your trick.
This is the largest secret of the current era.
If anyone can find out why,
it must be you, not me or other people.
I'm not that great.
Master, thank you for the high praise.
You know what?
I've spent the entire night thinking about it. But I have no idea at all.
It's useless for you to just think about it.
But you also know that Yunji Building is tightly guarded.
Even Di Lanzhang said only those with Yu Xiuming's order can go inside.
As for the Bureau of Astrology, only the officials of the Directorate of Astronomy can get inside.
I can only stay here and think.
I knew your cleverness was temporary.
You're still as dumb as a brick.
Yes, Master Yun Wen. I'm dumb.
How can I enter Yunji Building?
Your Majesty, Great Steward, Fan Ruhui, seeks an audience.
Let him in.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
My loyal subject, what do you need of me?
Your Majesty, the Ceremony of Stars is the first ceremony of the State of Chao after its establishment.
After a discussion with Wei Qi, the supervisor of the Bureau of Situ,
we think that this ceremony represents the authority of the state.
We should make it as grand as we can.
Therefore, we have tried to gather more funds from all around the state.
We might be able to get another 120,000 taels of gold and 10 million taels of silver within one month.
We'll spend them all on the Ceremony of Stars so that it can be perfect.
Do we need to spend that much money?
How should we deal with the aftermath if a calamity strikes all of a sudden?
We've kept enough for situations as such. Your Majesty, we dare not make you worry.
Great.
I don't want to make my ministers fret
because of the Ceremony of Stars.
Think about it. We've seen all kinds of matters
in the past two decades.
Money is the least of our concerns, am I right?
Your Majesty is wise!
Take a look at what's inside.
The Quell Fire Cup?
This is an item from my hometown, Weidi.
That's right.
I miss Weidi, too.
I went to your house when I was 12.
That's how I became who I am today.
You can have this.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
By the way, there's one more thing.
Regarding the construction for the Ceremony of Stars,
the Bureaus of Astrology and Public Works
actually replaced obsidian with dark jade
in order to take a cut.
Is that true? I will investigate it immediately.
No need for that. I've already done my investigation.
Guan Yi is the mastermind.
However, I need to punish him to serve as a warning to others.
If not, the entire world wouldn't take it seriously.
Your Majesty is wise.
Well, you can handle the execution.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Wait!
You forgot your box.
[Treasury]
What if... we change the number sequence?
Hurry!
What...
Official Bai, what's going on?
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
You wretch! How dare you frame me!
Guan Yi, what goes around comes around.
You!
Official Bai, this is just a misunderstanding.
Do me a favor. Plead for me in front of His Majesty, will you?
Save me!
Official Bai, save me!
Official Bai!
Regarding the bribery case related to the Ceremony of Stars,
Guan Yi embezzled the fund entrusted to him.
After His Majesty's investigation,
he has ordered to imprison Guan Yi and interrogate him.
The Bureau of Astrology is the most important department of Chao.
But the series of incidents has incurred His Majesty's wrath.
We should be deeply vigilant and feel guilty.
I hope you all can take this as a lesson.
Serve the state dutifully
and never commit such mistakes.
- Yes, Sir.
All right. Dismissed.
Sir, I have something to ask you.
It was Guan Yi who was in charge of building the altar for the Ceremony of Stars.
What should we do from now on?
His Majesty once ordered you to supervise the construction of the altar.
You shall take over his position.
Sir, thank you for that.
However, I'm too inexperienced.
Can I recommend someone else?
There's a director in the Bureau of Public Works called Gu Wangran.
He's an upright and meticulous person.
Can I leave this to him instead?
You can do as you see fit.
Thank you, Sir.
[Fan's Residence]
Old Master, we received news from the palace.
They've ordered the Bureau of Justice
to investigate the corruption case related to the Ceremony of Stars.
- What did you say?
- I heard that Guan Yi of the Bureau of Astrology has been sent to prison.
They're also arresting people from the Bureau of Public Works.
Say no more.
I understand.
His Majesty is wise.
He found out that the culprit was Guan Yi.
I've already contacted the Bureau of Justice.
This case will end. No one else will be implicated.
Father!
Scram!
Bring Fan Chang here.
Yes, Old Master.
Time to eat.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Tell him to leave.
Tell him to see me in the afternoon.
Do I need to repeat myself?
Yes, Your Majesty.
I, Jie Zhuying, the son of the traitorous subject,
greet Your Majesty.
Did you have enough of Yebei?
Your Majesty, I deserve to die for disappointing you.
However, my father and I never intended to betray you.
I watched you grow up.
I know how bold you are.
You should return to the imperial army.
Your Majesty.
Is there anything else?
Your Majesty, thank you for sparing my life.
On account of the service of you and your father,
I shall allow you to hold a mourning ceremony at home.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
[Jie Residence]
Brother Yu'an, thank you.
Zhuying, take care.
Zhuying.
I shall take my leave.
Brother Yu'an.
Take care.
Uncle Fan.
My child, you must've suffered.
Uncle Fan, thank you for visiting me.
I'm grateful that the Jie Family is still able to stand.
I just never thought...
that I couldn't see my parents for the last time before their deaths.
[The Late Father, Jie Haitian]
[The Late Mother, of Xiao Clan]
His Majesty's feud against your father wasn't formed overnight.
Both of them had their own ideas.
When they were fighting together,
it's okay to express their thoughts.
But once the ruler and the subject have been determined,
by no means should the emperor be the one to compromise with others.
As time passed, His Majesty's loath of him gradually increased.
When that happened, His Majesty no longer cared about
the validity of your father's words.
He'd only think that your father was disrespecting the emperor.
- So, His Majesty was unsatisfied with Father long ago.
- That's right.
You were monitoring the army in Yebei.
It's a tough job. You've contributed to the state.
My child, take care.
You can find me if you need anything in the future.
Thank you, Uncle.
Father, I would like to speak with Zhuying.
Here.
What is this?
I rushed here immediately after hearing about the news.
But your mother already took the poison.
She entrusted me with this letter for you.
She said your father left it to you.
Fan, thank you so much.
I wanted to meet you at the courier hostel.
However, my father said it would do you no good
if His Majesty found out.
I'm sure Uncle Fan had his reasons.
I can't thank you enough for being there
with my mother during her last breath.
Please accept my condolences.
Zhuying, my child,
if you're reading this letter,
that means I've already departed from this world.
I never regretted my decisions.
And I already expected this ending.
I only pray that you live a healthy life,
have a virtuous wife and a filial child.
You must take good care of yourself.
Father! Mother! I've let you down!
I've let you down!
Father told me not to blame His Majesty for this.
Then whom shall I direct my hate to?
If you don't know whom to hate,
you should stop hating.
Remember the warm and joyful moments.
Warm?
Joyful?
For example, the moments when your parents expressed their love for you.
Or the moments...
we spent together.
I no longer dare...
to remember those moments.
You must promise me that you'll never forget them.
You must take good care of yourself.
Princess.
Who are you?
Do not panic. I'm just like you.
I have a feud with the Emperor of Chao, too.
I don't know you.
And I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm Huo Lu.
I was Director Jie's subordinate when we fought in Zhongzhou.
You're a general of Chao?
Why would you have a feud with the emperor?
Back then, I was just a child who was captured to serve as a slave.
However, they thought I was a rebel and wanted to execute me.
I was only able to survive because of Official Jie.
Were you referring to Jie Haitian?
That's right.
What do you plan to do?
The Ceremony of Stars is nearing.
I've already bribed the officials.
I plan to uphold justice for Director Jie during the ceremony.
Your Majesty.
How was it?
Qihai Lian wasn't suspicious of me.
She agreed to cooperate with us.
Good.
I never expected Jie Zhuying to be a coward.
But now, the princess of Yebei is on our side.
The people of Yebei hate Yu Xiuming to the core.
They'll surely assassinate him somehow.
Back then, I underestimated that lowly boy, Yu Xiuming.
I let him grow in power.
I never expected myself to abandon my state...
and call myself his subject after so many years of war.
Fan Ruhui will give you an opportunity to strike during the Ceremony of Stars.
Now, my army is stationed in Liaoyang.
Once Yu Xiuming dies,
my army can arrive in Tianqi within a day.
The Cai Family shall reign supreme again!
I shall sacrifice my life to fulfill your goal.
You did great this time.
You can request anything you like.
Your Majesty, you were the one who saved me.
It's my honor to share your concern with you.
I have nothing to request for.
I will surely take good care of your family.
Mr. Duanmu, what are they doing?
The Directorate of Astronomy is checking the inventory of the ritual tools
they need for the Ceremony of Stars.
36 pieces of green jade ramparts for worshipping the sky.
36 pieces of yellow octagonal jade badges for offering sacrifices to the earth.
Cauldron...
Come.
Don't leave yet.
I wish to see what the cauldron looks like.
- Bagui.
- Bagui?
Since the Ceremony of Stars is nearing,
Tianqi will tighten its security soon.
All of you must be thorough.
Sister Lian is still waiting for my news.
I have to find a chance.
9 stands for sacrificial food, 26 sacrificial vessels.
[Yunji Building]
You scared me.
I thought you had an idea in mind.
What?
I also wanted to go in instead of sneaking.
I observed this place for two days.
This place has been forbidden since long ago.
No one comes here usually.
However, Di Lanzhang doesn't come here
because he's afraid of His Majesty.
His Majesty doesn't study. That's why he doesn't come here.
It means although the main gate is tightly guarded,
the surrounding has low security.
So, you're just a sneaky thief.
Who are you calling a thief?
You.
You're the thief here.
This is so narrow.
Secrets of Star Trail?
The Diagram of the 48 Phases of Star?
Yun Wen, the diagram does exist.
It's a pity that you can't learn them yet.
This place is huge.
A Dream of Guzhen?
Tianqi used to be Guzhen City, right?
Manual of the Emperor Star?
Yun Wen, I found the complete Manual of the Emperor Star.
This should be useful.
Who dares to come here without permission?
Who's there?
Who are you?
Yunji Building is a forbidden ground within the Bureau of Astrology.
How did you get in?
I got in by using the same method as you.
Are you here to steal the books, too?
Steal the books?
Are you here to steal the books?
I'm not here to steal the books.
I'm here to catch the book thief!
Your Majesty, what are you doing here?
Who were you talking to just now?
No one.
Who is Yun Wen?
Yun Wen?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You better tell me the truth.
Don't be scared. He can't hear me anyway.
Your Majesty,
I'll be honest with you, then.
You see, I have a weird habit.
Whenever I find a good book,
I'll talk to myself.
Sorry about that.
I'll see for myself.
Good book, huh?
You're smart, eager to learn, and knowledgeable in many fields.
Are you that interested in me?
Hurry and make up an excuse. Your life depends on it.
That's right.
If so, tell me why you're here.
Think twice before answering.
If you say something wrong, you shall be expelled from the Bureau of Astrology.
Hurry!
Your Majesty, I just wanted to know more about your noble deeds.
I admire you.
You're pretty adept at licking my boots, huh?
Tell me then. What do you admire about me?
At 17, you fought the Kuafu Clan at Jushi.
You rode into the valley alone and slew over 60 of them.
After that, you conquered Xi, Tang, Cao, and Luan.
If we include the Battle of Yebei,
Your Majesty, it took you 17 years to establish your state.
You must be more than 30 years old now.
You're good at calculating.
In the battle of Jushi that you mentioned,
our army was surrounded.
The Kuafu people were three times taller than normal men.
And more than 10 times stronger.
They also fought with no fear of death.
When they rushed toward us,
our army was massacred, except for me.
Bai Lu, what you're reading right now
is the result written down by historians.
However, no one cares about the process.
You must be out of your mind.
How dare you come here again.
How can I know his secret if I don't come here?
"Mianshi Bridge, built in Hanzhendi.
An ancient temple lies beside it.
This is an ancient ground.
Rumor has it that it's blessed by the powers of the primordial truth masters.
According to nosy people,
mysterious events happen there all the time."
Yun Wen.
Look.
Does this Mianshi Bridge have something to do with the Truth Masters?
You know about the Truth Masters?
I don't. That's why I'm asking you.
You should know something, right?
The Truth Masters are an ancient clan in myths.
They do not die or get hurt. They're everlasting.
Their appearances can remain the same even after hundreds of years.
Are they that powerful?
Of course.
Not just that,
but the Truth Masters are capable of anything and everything.
They know all the secrets in the world.
They're amazing, right?
Could it be that the Truth Masters
imparted some of their powers to Yu Xiuming
so he was able to avoid the Hengchen Skyfire Spell?
That's only your random guess.
That's not a random guess.
According to the records, Yu Xiuming only conquered the world after more than a decade of war.
But don't you think he looks a bit young for that?
Who knows?
I'm sure he won't tell anyone about a secret like that.
I don't care.
I'll find out his secret somehow.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, Bai Lu, Director of the Bureau of Astrology,
has presented you with a box.
What box?
Director Bai said she prepared it for you.
I didn't sneak a peek.
What if it's a contraption used to harm me?
And you brought it to me just like that?
I will check it immediately.
Wait.
Just a little trick.
It's not like I'm afraid of her.
♫ The earth as a plaque ♫
♫ The sun and the moon as a poem ♫
♫ Turn the skies into the palace under the plaque ♫
♫ Time as a scroll ♫
♫ The stars as the inkstone ♫
♫ Writing with the light of the sea ♫
♫ Through several lives and reincarnations ♫
♫ I search the world for wisdom ♫
♫ To smooth the folds of the years ♫
♫ There is a hole in my heart ♫
♫ Void of someone ♫
♫ Now I know what forever tastes like ♫
♫ I'll trade my youth for yours ♫
♫ I'll trade my youth for your kiss ♫
♫ We enter the battlefield for the peace of the world ♫
♫ Draw the lines of fate, carve destinies ♫
♫ And our roles in the world with me ♫
♫ All worldly desires fall from your fingertips ♫
♫ The mountains and rivers between your brows
orbit the seas like a song ♫
♫ I'll trade my youth for yours ♫
♫ I'll trade my youth for your kiss ♫
♫ We enter the battlefield for the peace of the world ♫
♫ Draw the lines of fate, carve destinies ♫
♫ And our roles in the world with me ♫
♫ All worldly desires fall from your fingertips ♫
♫ The mountains and rivers between your brows
orbit the seas like a song ♫
♫ The stars shine brightly for you and me ♫