♫ The top of the mountains where the snow never melts ♫
♫ The plains where the wind blows ♫
♫ What finds me in my sleep are the nightmares about you ♫
♫ In the endless abyss ♫
♫ Your face gradually emerges ♫
♫ A love that budded unknowingly to us continues
to grow and blossom ♫
♫ Who risked his life for mine? ♫
♫ I had braced myself for the end, but my heart frets for you ♫
♫ It turns out there is an end to my waiting for you ♫
♫ At the hills where the grasslands end where
it will always be spring ♫
♫ I find the boundless river of stars in your eyes ♫
♫ Only with your hand in mine is this life worthwhile ♫
[Shining Just for You]
[Episode 1]
From the harmony of Heaven and Earth,
the dawn of chaos unfolds.
The Truth Masters descend upon the world.
They are powerful, yet elusive
and nowhere to be found.
Since then, the lands have been ruled alternately by the Human Clan and the Winged Clan.
The flames of war raged on.
There was no end to the clash of arms.
Even the Kuafu Clan
and the Heluo Clan were caught in the crossfire.
It was not until the end of the late Xian Dynasty
that a young general emerged from nowhere
who united the five clans...
and built an unprecedented dynasty like no other,
the Great Chao.
All that the birds could reach belonged to Chao,
except for one place known as...
which had yet to be conquered.
Underneath the veil of such greatness, however,
was the never-ending war
among the seven tribes of Yebei.
I didn't know there were so many interesting places outside of Yebei!
Let's sneak out again next time.
All right!
Princess Zhuyan has returned!
Princess Zhuyan is back!
Princess Zhuyan!
Her Highness has returned!
- For you, Your Highness.
- Thank you.
[Princess Zhuyan of Yebei, Qihai Rui]
Your Highness!
- Grandma!
- You're back!
Here, have some of the milk tea I made you.
[Ye Lingshuang, Daughter of Dayuangu of Yebei]
(Dayuangu, title of a high-ranking official in Yebei)
- How is it?
- It smells wonderful!
Yezi, don't worry.
If Dayuangu is to punish you, I'll ask my father to help.
It'll be all right.
Ye Lingshuang!
Dayuangu!
[Ye Jingqing, Dayuangu of Yebei]
The audacity!
How dare you bring Princess Zhuyan out of Yebei without permission?
That is a crime punishable by death!
It wasn't her fault!
I wanted to leave Yebei for fun.
Yezi came along because she was worried about me.
Princess Zhuyan, you don't have to make excuses for her.
She was born inauspicious.
She must be admonished and kept in check
so that she does not bring calamity to our people.
When has she ever brought harm to our people?
Dayuangu, Yezi is not cursed!
She is your daughter.
It's one thing for others to say that, but you're her own father!
[Qihai Zhenyu, King of the Seven Tribes of Yebei]
How could you say that about her?
Rui.
Your Majesty.
Father, I've missed you!
Rui, you mustn't be disrespectful to Dayuangu.
Understand?
I do respect him.
But elders must be reasonable, too.
It's not as if Yezi wanted to do it.
She was only worried about me.
Princess Zhuyan, you're still young.
You do not understand what is at stake.
Enough.
You, back to your tent!
You are not to take one step outside for a month!
Father! The autumn tournament is the day after tomorrow!
We hurried back just for that.
Let Yezi attend it with me.
Right, Jingqing.
The autumn tournament is only held once a year.
Let the girls attend it.
You are to stay in your tent after the event
and not to leave it again!
Yes.
Your Majesty, we've received a message from Tianqi.
The Emperor of Chao sent an envoy
to seek an alliance of marriage with Yebei.
What do you think?
Should we accept it?
Your Majesty,
I've heard that while the Emperor of Chao came from humble beginnings,
he was able to conquer and unite the five clans.
He is a formidable man.
I'm afraid Yebei will suffer grave consequences
if we refuse.
Yebei has over a hundred thousand brave men,
all skilled in horsemanship and archery!
Why should we bow to Chao?
But… the seven tribes may obey Your Majesty on the surface,
but in reality,
they fight for their own selfish intentions.
We will be at a disadvantage
if we rush into war now, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, why not use the marriage alliance as a ploy to distract Chao
and seize the upper hand?
This marriage alliance must happen.
But they say that the Emperor of Chao is ruthless and violent.
All princesses who've been sent to marry him have met unfortunate ends.
Her Highness's life will be at risk if she is to be wedded to him.
We do not have a choice in that matter.
Dayuangu.
You're finally back.
I thought someone
would hide behind Princess Zhuyan forever.
I wasn't hiding.
Besides, there are things that you can't hide from.
At least you know that.
Enough.
Since His Majesty has spoken,
you'll attend the autumn tournament with Princess Zhuyan.
But His Majesty and Queen Lan have given orders,
forbidding you from staying by the princess's side after that.
I'll send you to the Black Water Tribe.
You should bid farewell to the princess.
That won't do!
I can't leave Rui's side!
Insolence!
Since when do you get to make the calls around here?
You should've known this would happen
when you took the princess out of Yebei!
Fine.
But you have to unseal me before I go.
What did you say?
I said unseal me.
You sealed my celestial powers when I was seven years old.
I've lived in pain ever since.
You need to unseal me.
No.
You never compromise on things related to you.
Answer me! Did you foresee another disaster?
I'm not a child anymore!
I know I'm not the one that causes these disasters.
I can just see them coming before others do.
If that makes me a harbinger of calamity,
then so are those astrologers!
Besides, the Bureau of Astrology is regarded as the most important department of Chao!
Their job is to predict auspicious and bad events. What about them?
Lower your voice!
I'm warning you.
You must never say such things to others.
If you dare to spout nonsense to mislead others,
I'll end you myself!
Begone with you!
Princess Rui!
Chu Ye and the others are back.
Princess Rui.
You guys made it back before the autumn tournament at last.
If you hadn't, the title of the bravest warrior
would go to someone else.
Let's go, Rui.
- All right.
- Stop.
You cursed woman! I've got unfinished business with you.
Chu Ye! Don't bully Ye!
Rui, she is inauspicious.
Who gave you permission to call me that?
Princess Rui, you shouldn't be around her.
Chu Ye, that's enough.
She tricked you into leaving Yebei!
She should've been sentenced to death!
What proof do you have that she tricked me?
I was the one who wanted to leave Yebei.
Yezi is my best friend.
Anyone who bullies her shouldn't follow me!
We'll never be separated.
That's right.
- I say...
- Stop!
Don't say anything.
The bravest warrior of Yebei
is afraid of little ol' me talking?
You cursed woman.
What proof do you have that I am cursed?
You bring misfortune everywhere you go!
If that doesn't make you cursed, what does?
Well, I'll show you a real cursed one.
Run! Get out of here!
Look at those cowards!
[Lan, Queen of Yebei]
Your Majesty!
The seven tribes of Yebei have gathered here for the autumn tournament.
The champion of the tournament
will be named the bravest warrior of Yebei.
Men of the seven tribes,
do not let the blood in your veins run cold.
Do not forget that cowardly sheep
will be ripped apart by vicious wolves.
There shall be only battles in the autumn tournament of the seven tribes!
I hereby declare the autumn tournament begins now!
Here comes the wolf!
The Snow Wolf King is here!
Run!
A'Rui!
Run! Hurry!
The Wolf God of Yebei!
It's our protector, the Wolf God of Yebei!
A'Rui, go!
Yezi!
Princess Rui, you must leave!
- Don't stop me.
- Go!
Yezi!
- Yezi!
- Watch out!
Miss, the wolf seems to have its eye on you.
What will you do?
Then, I'll…
I'll kill it.
All right.
It is courageous of you to do the impossible.
Miss, stare into its eyes.
If you don't fear it, it'll fear you.
You don't know martial arts.
I don't.
Why won't you run, then?
If I run, it'll come after you!
Crazy girl.
Watch this.
Our Wolf God!
They killed the Wolf God!
They did!
The Wolf God is dead!
Kneel!
Our Wolf God is dead!
Who are you?
Someone who is here to help you.
Help me?
Yezi!
Yezi! Are you all right, Yezi?
I'm fine.
You killed Yebei's Wolf God!
I did.
Stop!
Take Prince Miao Li to seek medical attention at once!
[Qihai Lian, Eldest Princess of Yebei]
[Jie Zhuying, Commander-in-Chief of Chao]
Who are you?
Why did you draw your weapon in Yebei?
I don't care who you are! How dare you hurt our prince!
General!
Envoy of Chao, Commander of the Lanyi Army,
General Who Defeats Bandits, Xie Yu'an,
greets His Majesty, King Qihai.
The envoy of Chao?
King Qihai,
I was sent to forge good relations with Yebei.
Is this any way to treat your guests?
General Xie drew blood upon your arrival.
Is this how Great Chao treats their hosts?
Prince Miao came at me with unkind intent.
If I hadn't fought back,
I would've been a dead body by now.
We came to seek an alliance, yet you sought to harm an envoy.
I'm afraid it would do you no good
if Chao learns of this, King Qihai.
General Xie is unlike what is rumored.
Very well. Please proceed to the royal tent.
Your Majesty!
He killed our Wolf God!
You cannot let this slide!
The heavens will punish us, Your Majesty!
It's the cursed one!
It was she who disturbed the Snow Wolf King!
That's slander! Yezi didn't do anything!
All these people saw it!
King Qihai, she cannot live.
We must sacrifice her
to appease the Wolf God!
Yes! She must be sacrificed!
Men!
Stop!
Father. Dayuangu. Say something!
Yezi is innocent!
Rui, don't waste your breath.
The heroes of Yebei are great indeed.
You do not distinguish between right and wrong.
Adults of decades-old bullying a little girl.
Well, you've certainly opened my eyes.
Miss, you may be a woman,
but you're far braver than most that stand here.
This is a token of Chao.
Accept this.
If anyone dares to slight you again,
they will make an enemy of Chao.
Live or die.
It's your choice.
Yezi! What's the matter, Yezi?
- You're awake!
- A'Rui.
It gave me such a scare today.
I can still feel my heart pounding.
This is something easy on your stomach. Have some.
You must've been frightened, too, Yezi.
That Snow Wolf King was terrifying.
And that Luo Wuyi.
That old man is even worse than the Snow Wolf King.
Father and the chiefs of the other tribes held a bonfire feast
to welcome General Xie.
Let's go and take a look, then.
But…
A'Rui, since when did you become such a worrywart?
Look at me! I'm perfectly fine!
Don't worry.
All right.
Princess Rui, dance with us!
Go on.
What was that for?
To rid you of all that bad luck.
Is that enough bad luck for you?
- You.
- Enough, Chu Ye!
Let it go.
Come on. Let's get a drink.
Carry on!
Come on.
Miss.
I can see that you're not welcome here.
Why don't you come back to Chao with me?
I can help you slay your enemies.
I don't need that.
I didn't do anything because none of them is worth my time and effort.
Besides, I hate people who think they can tell me what to do.
So you better not mess with me.
That's my liquor.
I drank it, so it's mine now.
Listen.
No one in Yebei dares to drink liquor that I drank.
Afraid? Now, go away.
So this is how Yebei treats their guests.
You have to snatch liquor from another's hands.
Why don't you look happy at all?
Why should I be?
Good food, good wine, music, and dance.
What's not to be happy about?
All of these are enjoyed by others.
Not me.
Besides, such joy is only temporary.
Just like those flowers behind you.
They bloom by the warmth of the bonfire.
But their fate has long been decided.
They will wilt and wither away...
in the midst of tomorrow's frost.
There.
Its fate has been changed.
That doesn't count!
Why not?
A little girl like you shouldn't harp on things like fate and destiny.
They are but excuses for the weak.
You don't believe in fate and destiny?
Why should I?
But…
But what if someone was born cursed?
No one is born cursed.
Remember this. Your fate is what you make of it.
You must grasp your destiny firmly
in your own hands.
I understand now.
Thanks!
I didn't expect to hear a "thanks" from you.
You saved my life, after all. I should thank you.
You should treat me to a few more bottles of Yebei's liquor, then!
Your Majesty.
Why are you standing there like a log?
Take a look at this.
There are rumors in the army that you have a divine mirror
that allows you to see all the beauties in the world.
I can't believe it's true!
Is that girl the one who has caught Your Majesty's eye?
Who?
The girl you gave the Seal of Loyalty and Courage to.
Oh, her.
You call her a beauty?
Well, she is dressed plainly,
but I think she has nice eyebrows and eyes…
That's enough from you.
I've always thought you had questionable taste in women.
But you gave her the Seal of Loyalty and Courage.
There are only seven of those in existence,
and you gave her one just like that.
That's why I thought you might've felt differently about her.
Shallow-minded.
Not anyone can become the Empress of Chao.
Only a noble princess of Yebei is worthy of this position.
Oh, right.
Aren't you going to meet the lady in your heart tonight?
You found out, Your Majesty?
The eldest princess of Yebeistudied for four years in Tianqi
under the alias of Qingheng.
If my covert guards weren't even able to learn that,
why should I keep them around?
Your Majesty, why didn't you say anything about it, then?
Even if I did,
would you be able to take back your heart that you'd given her?
[The Royal Tent of the Qihai Tribe of Yebei]
The imperial envoy has arrived.
Envoy of Chao, Xie Yu'an,
greets King Qihai.
We appreciate the Emperor of Chao's sincerity.
The seven tribes of Yebei accept the proposal of a marriage alliance with Chao.
Thank you, King Qihai, for your generosity.
May the Great Chao and Yebei be allied for all eternity.
I thank you on behalf of His Majesty.
Please be seated.
Please.
This is my eldest daughter, Qihai Lian.
I'm sure you've already seen her.
Chao has come a long way to Yebei in search of an empress.
It is fated by the heavens.
That is why we offer you a precious gift.
What is it?
The Great Chao would like to offer the Mirror of Youth
for the hand of Princess Qihai Rui of Yebei in marriage.
Dayuangu, please save A'Rui!
Make His Majesty change his mind!
She cannot marry the Emperor of Chao! She'll die!
Do you think
His Majesty will change his mind at this point?
He will. That's his beloved A'Rui!
But His Majesty is the king of the seven tribes of Yebei.
- But how can he…
- There is no "but"!
Why can't you understand your place?
It is a miracle that you were allowed to live as long as you have.
What right do you have to dictate the future of Yebei?
She must board the wedding carriage to Chao
and fulfill her duties.
That is not to be changed!
What duties?
It's only an excuse you guys came up with because you aren't willing to find a solution and take responsibility!
You want to use the marriage alliance to buy time.
But Chao will conquer Yebei.
It doesn't matter if we marry off a princess to Chao or not!
Why is Princess Rui the one to be wedded to Chao?
I heard it was the emperor who chose her.
But the emperor is said to be ruthless and merciless.
It's as good as a death sentence for Princess Rui!
Princess Rui.
Don't worry. I won't allow you to be sent to Chao.
Chu Ye, where are you going?
- Let go!
- Where are you going?
I'll go to Xie Yu'an and challenge him as per the customs of Yebei!
Even if Yebei were to marry a princess off in a political alliance,
it would be for the sake of peace between the two kingdoms.
Not because we fear them!
Have you gone mad? He is the imperial envoy of Chao!
- Don't try to stop me!
- No! Get back here!
Stop it!
Your Highness…
Greetings, General.
Who are you?
General, Queen Lan ordered me to prepare freshly brewed milk tea for you all.
You've had a long journey.
So we've prepared the finest and most authentic milk tea for you all.
Please drink it while it's hot.
Wait.
This pot of milk tea is for General Xie.
Leave it. I'll take it to him.
Actually, I wanted to express my gratitude to General Xie.
That's why I took this task.
Could you please tell him I'm here?
Please give me a chance?
All right. I'll inform His...
I mean him.
Thank you, General.
- General.
- General Xie wants to see you.
Yes.
General Xie.
Why are you here?
General Xie,
I wish to take A'Rui's place and become Empress of Chao.
How dare you!
Do you think anyone can become the Empress of Chao?
The Emperor of Chao has high regard for the art of astrology and divination.
And I've been studying this art with my father since I was a child. I'm well-versed in astrology.
Princess Zhuyan is beautiful,
but I would do a better job
at winning His Majesty's heart.
Besides, I'm a daughter of noble status too.
Why must you insist on taking her?
Noble…
Do you think I don't know anything?
You've spouted inauspicious omens since you were a child.
All of Yebei regard you as a harbinger of calamity.
If it weren't for Qihai Rui, you wouldn't have even been here today.
Someone like you is unfit to be the Empress of Chao.
General Xie, you are a man of knowledge.
I know you won't believe those baseless rumors.
Besides, the emperor is all the way back in Tianqi.
As long as you don't let them hear of this,
they won't know a thing.
I didn't expect to hear that from you.
It seems I've underestimated you.
Look, General Xie, I genuinely want to go to Tianqi.
There's nothing keeping me here in Yebei.
Wouldn't it be better to take me back
instead of Qihai Rui who is unwilling to go?
That's enough.
Let's get back to business.
Why don't you want Qihai Rui to marry into Chao?
I hear that the emperor is violent and ruthless,
and all of the princesses who were married to Chao have died.
I don't want Rui to go through that.
Preposterous.
The marriage alliance is to put an end to the war.
His Majesty is not a heartless emperor, as you claim.
Even if that is a false rumor,
it's a true fact that she'll have to abide by strict rules in the Chao Palace.
A'Rui is kind and innocent.
She shouldn't have to live like that, and neither should she go there.
She would go insane!
Are you saying that you want to live like that?
I only know that I can't have everything.
I just want A'Rui to live happily.
But the generals of Chao are all loyal.
What makes you think I would lie to my emperor?
So…
So you won't help me.
Enough... You may go.
I shall take my leave, then.
Oh, right.
You must drink the milk tea while it's hot.
General Xie, this is a token of Queen Lan's appreciation.
Please do not refuse.
To Queen Lan.
What…
What's in the milk tea?
Don't expect anyone to save you.
They wouldn't wake up even if I held a knife to their necks right now.
Everyone knows
that King Qihai's queen is kind and gentle.
I don't think she was the one who made the milk tea
that harms the envoy and threatens
to break the alliance between Chao and Yebei.
I don't care about Tianqi, Great Chao,
or a marriage alliance to end the war.
My A'Rui will not be married to Tianqi!
I've put deadly poison into this milk tea.
And only I have the antidote.
So think carefully.
Will you lose your life or work with me?
You're a clever man. You should know what to choose.
I, Xie Yu'an,
am not one to be coerced.
Fine.
Then…
Just wait until you lose all the senses of your body.
By then, the others will have woken up just in time to collect your corpse.
♫ The earth as a plaque ♫
♫ The sun and the moon as a poem ♫
♫ Turn the skies into the palace under the plaque ♫
♫ Time as a scroll ♫
♫ The stars as the inkstone ♫
♫ Writing with the light of the sea ♫
♫ Through several lives and reincarnations ♫
♫ I search the world for wisdom ♫
♫ To smooth the folds of the years ♫
♫ There is a hole in my heart ♫
♫ Void of someone ♫
♫ Now I know what forever tastes like ♫
♫ I'll trade my youth for yours ♫
♫ I'll trade my youth for your kiss ♫
♫ We enter the battlefield for the peace of the world ♫
♫ Draw the lines of fate, carve destinies ♫
♫ And our roles in the world with me ♫
♫ All worldly desires fall from your fingertips ♫
♫ The mountains and rivers between your brows
orbit the seas like a song ♫
♫ I'll trade my youth for yours ♫
♫ I'll trade my youth for your kiss ♫
♫ We enter the battlefield for the peace of the world ♫
♫ Draw the lines of fate, carve destinies ♫
♫ And our roles in the world with me ♫
♫ All worldly desires fall from your fingertips ♫
♫ The mountains and rivers between your brows
orbit the seas like a song ♫
♫ The stars shine brightly for you and me ♫