♪Looking up at the burning future♪
♪We are like the ever-lasting dust♪
♪Even if we drift
in the dazzling mundane world♪
♪We will not bloom♪
♪As long as my life still exists♪
♪The colors in my heart
will never fade away♪
♪The crowd drowns me♪
♪Time burns me♪
♪Amid the ashes, stars still twinkle♪
♪Even if I stand alone♪
♪I'll still remember
to clench my fists tightly♪
=Behind The Scenes=
=Episode 3=
=The Dangerous Beauty=
(Father,)
(you taught me from a young age)
(that in this era,)
(women should discern right from wrong,
(distinguish good from evil,)
(recognize what is good and bad,
and understand what is worth.)
(Now I have found the one)
(who killed you.)
(Don't worry.)
(I will definitely not disappoint you.)
Why are you so nervous?
Are you afraid that I will eat you?
I find you especially charming tonight.
If you need it,
I could give you my life.
Hide.
(Heaven has eyes.)
(Not just me who wants to kill you.)
♪Looking up at the burning future♪
♪We are like the ever-lasting dust♪
♪Even if we drift
in the dazzling mundane world♪
♪We will not bloom♪
♪As long as my life still exists♪
♪The colors in my heart
will never fade away♪
♪Let the wind blow out my light♪
♪Let the night devour me♪
♪Let me fall to pieces♪
♪Let the tears run dry♪
♪Let the truth pierce me♪
♪Let me remain silent yet move forward♪
♪The crowd drowns me♪
♪Time burns me♪
♪Amid the ashes, stars still twinkle♪
♪Even if I stand alone♪
♪I'll still remember
to clench my fists tightly♪
Help me.
Ok.
Miss Bai, please help yourself.
I don't know where the medicine box is.
In the cupboard on the right.
Thank you.
If it weren't for you,
the one who got injured would be me.
But look at how awkward I am now.
Sorry for that.
Let me help you.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
It's just a small effort.
I don't know
if what you said still counts.
As long as it doesn't go against morals,
I will absolutely not break my word.
Since that's the case...
=Behind The Scenes=
♪The world is heartless♪
♪Why should we shed tears for love?♪
♪The fading rain in the spring smoke♪
♪Where can I seek the broken soul?♪
♪Even the cold pillow is heartless♪
♪You don’t know my heart♪
♪Dreams shattered, with no one to speak♪
♪I fear the most that you leave me♪
♪With what kind of gaze♪
♪What kind of identity♪
♪Should I wait
for your glance and a kiss?♪
♪No matter how far♪
♪No matter how many lifetimes♪
♪I long to see your love, no parting♪
♪I just want to be with you♪
♪Roaming the mortal world together♪
♪Even if I have to go♪
♪Through several reincarnations♪
♪I just want to be with you♪
♪Under the falling stars♪
♪Holding an umbrella♪
♪And waiting for the rain to stop♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)