♪Looking up at the burning future♪
♪We are like the ever-lasting dust♪
♪Even if we drift
in the dazzling mundane world♪
♪We will not bloom♪
♪As long as my life still exists♪
♪The colors in my heart
will never fade away♪
♪The crowd drowns me♪
♪Time burns me♪
♪Amid the ashes, stars still twinkle♪
♪Even if I stand alone♪
♪I'll still remember
to clench my fists tightly♪
=Behind The Scenes=
=Episode 10=
=Can I still Trust You?=
Good morning, Mr. Cheng.
Mr. Cheng.
- Good morning, sir.
- Morning, Mr. Cheng.
Congratulations on achieving new merits.
In today's Morning News,
the whole layout is about you.
(The Station will conduct an operation.)
Yeah.
Mr. Cheng has made a significant breakthrough.
The concession is expected to be peaceful.
Mr. Cheng,
shouldn't we ask to drink to celebrate?
- Is that so, guys?
- Is it?
- Yes.
- That's right.
We really need to have a drink.
- Right.
- Let's celebrate it.
In a few days.
There are some matters at home.
It seems that Mrs. Cheng is quite strict.
Come on.
Yang Ming,
tell the people in the Chamber
that the President is not doing well lately.
Later, all the company's affairs
will be entrusted to me.
Is this the President's intention or...
Mrs. Yan, don't misunderstand.
I didn't mean to offend.
Did you forget
this chamber was founded by my father?
He was able to become the President
because I recommended him.
What?
Are you questioning my abilities?
No.
It's just...
If we take away Yan Liang's power,
and he finds out,
will he...
What if he finds out
we both wanted to kill him before?
You need to understand, Yang Ming,
that I chose him back then
just because of the rules my dad set
that women can't be the President.
He is just my dog.
What do you want to do?
He likes to deliver things to the Station.
Why not send himself in there as well?
(Dongping Account Books)
Sure.
Then I'll hand the books to the Station.
What is this thing?
This is my kindness for you.
If this gift is not valuable,
I will not accept it.
Mrs. Yan, rest assured.
You will definitely like this gift.
Mr. Yang,
your taste is getting worse and worse.
Ru, what brought you here?
You must be hungry, right?
Eat it while it's hot.
Do you still remember my favorite dish?
Taste it, it will be cold soon.
Report.
Sir, we found evidence.
Have you confirmed it?
I've confirmed it.
Prepare the vehicle.
Notify Team One and Two quickly.
Yes, sir.
What's the rush?
Are you going on a mission?
I won't eat today.
It's ok, I'll clean up.
Work is important.
I think I'll go home a bit late today.
After cleaning up, you go home early.
Be safe.
(Archive)
What you see may not be the truth.
(Cheng Feng,)
(what are you hiding from me?)
(Can I still trust you?)
(The operation targeting opium smuggling...)
Mr. Cheng,
what brought you here?
(Arrest Warrant)
Yan Liang,
you are suspected of drug trafficking.
We lawfully arrest you.
Your fiancé,
no,
ex-fiancé Cheng Feng,
in order to seize power and profit
and consolidate his position,
he really made such a small move
with us.
For example,
that time at the nightclub.
Speaking of Cheng Feng,
he's quite bold.
Our people said
he's just a policeman,
but he dared to trade opium with the Gang.
Ru, you have something on your mind?
No.
I'm a bit worried about you.
I happen to have something to say.
Today we arrested Yan Liang.
He is suspected of trafficking opium.
He was finally brought to justice.
So I don't think you need
to work outside anymore.
Places like the Grand World,
you know,
are full of mixed people and unsafe.
From now on,
just stay at home.
I will take care of you.
Ok.
But Xia usually treats me well.
I want to hold a ceremony
to say goodbye to them.
No problem.
I have one more thing.
Ru,
will you marry me?
A lot has happened during this time.
I have also understood a lot.
Only by keeping you by my side
can I better protect you.
- So...
- How about
giving it to me at the ceremony?
I want more people to witness this moment.
Ok.
Here.
Is it tasty?
=Behind The Scenes=
♪The world is heartless♪
♪Why should we shed tears for love?♪
♪The fading rain in the spring smoke♪
♪Where can I seek the broken soul?♪
♪Even the cold pillow is heartless♪
♪You don't know my heart♪
♪Dreams shattered, with no one to speak♪
♪I fear the most that you leave me♪
♪With what kind of gaze♪
♪What kind of identity♪
♪Should I wait
for your glance and a kiss?♪
♪No matter how far♪
♪No matter how many lifetimes♪
♪I long to see your love, no parting♪
♪I just want to be with you♪
♪Roaming the mortal world together♪
♪Even if I have to go♪
♪Through several reincarnations♪
♪I just want to be with you♪
♪Under the falling stars♪
♪Holding an umbrella♪
♪And waiting for the rain to stop♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)