Come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
The situation has changed.
You still have the time to talk nonsense here?
Liuli has a connection with the palace.
To deal with them,
we need to use Shen Jiayue to make contracts with them.
It’s good that you understand.
You're always together.
I'm afraid you'll forget that she's the daughter of the Qiu family.
I'm here to remind you
not to forget your plan.
You're awake.
Your Highness.
If something like this happens again,
Stay away if you know you're useless.
Don't cause any trouble.
I made you worry.
You think too much.
I have two concubines.
Why should I worry about you?
I'm just reminding you.
it's not your duty to protect me.
Know your place.
Don't think there's anything special
with me.
Are you worried that I'll get hurt?
I'm a prince.
You are the queen.
That's all.
I'm not the daughter of the Tai family.
I shouldn't have wished for his love.
Take care of yourself.
No.
Her Highness is awake.
Can you let me go?
It's only been a day.
How did he lose favour?
Your Highness.
His Highness is in a hurry.
Where are you going?
I wonder how Sister Shen is doing.
I'm going to have a look.
Would you like to come with me?
She's awake.
That's great. I should go check on her.
That day,
you stayed in the mansion
for taking care of Shen Jiayue.
I didn't punish you.
But I never ordered you to go back.
Your Highness.
I meant well.
How could you be so cruel?
When Sister Shen was away,
I was the one who went back to host them.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness, you've done a great job.
Besides, it's getting late.
If we go out now,
I'm afraid we won't be there until dark.
It's not safe.
That's why I'm asking you to leave as soon as possible.
What?
Is there any reason for Lord Xu to stay in the mansion?
On the first day of the lunar month, send her back.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, please.
Shen Jiayue is injured and she can pretend to be miserable.
I will be kicked out overnight.
Enough, Your Highness.
You hurt your nails.
You're lecturing me.
Come home with me.
What's the use of having you?
How dare you sit down?
Don't be arrogant and impatient.
Only when everything is done,
to avoid mistakes.
It's useless.
What excuses are you looking for?
Shen Jiayue joined the army without permission.
Why don’t you use such a big mistake?
Your Highness.
Did Shen Jiayue join the army not delay the military?
and took a sword for you.
If you find out that we entered the mansion without permission,
it will backfire.
But Shen Jiayue’s injury
gave us a chance.
For Shen Jiayue, Chu Jingyan kidnapped Song’s doctor.
He has no excuses.
Why did you drag His Highness into this?
Do you want me to talk to Her Majesty?
If the people around her
are as timid as a mouse,
what's the point of keeping it?
I have no choice
I have no choice.
But even if I tell the Empress,
I cannot tell anyone right now.
I believe the Empress will agree.
I'll say one thing.
You stand up.
It's the opposite.
Your Highness, the cloud roll has recovered.
I was ordered by my parents
to continue serving Her Highness.
How dare you!
Did I let you in?
Are you all bullying me?
You're all bullying me.
When did I let you in?
They all bully me.
Assassination and poison.
I've seen too many in the mansion.
That's why I said you can't lose favour.
We must take back his heart.
Otherwise, he will come and kill us anytime.
That's not impossible.
I can still live without him.
What? Where was I?
Kill us.
Yes, beat us to death.
It's not impossible
to kill us.
His Highness threatened me with the lives of his family.
Not only did he kidnap me to treat you,
and imprisoned me.
This is ruthless.
Crazy.
He won't let me out if I don't cure you.
Did you misunderstand him?
Absolutely not.
You have an extraordinary status in his heart.
I'm confident that I can help you win back your favor.
and you let me go.
I don't want to see him.
and I don't want any favour.
Instead of worrying about love,
it's better to cut the crap
and do what you should do.
and go far away.
Look how nice the weather is today.
It's normal to be afraid of cold.
Just take a walk.
When we go back,
I'll make you a bowl of good lotus seed soup.
Why is there no one here in broad daylight?
Do you know where he is?
Your Highness.
Say it.
How dare you not answer her question?
Tell me.
His Highness entered the palace in the morning.
and was detained.
What?
Why?
I heard that Imperial Physician Song complained.
Let's go to the palace.
Slow down.
His Highness ordered you two to stay in the hospital.
I'm afraid of you.
The news has spread to the palace.
I will go out one day.
It's Lady-in-waiting Xu.
For you,
because of you.
I was afraid they would disturb you.
Really?
Then...
His Highness told you not to be nervous.
He can handle it.
Okay.
By the way,
Forget it.
I need to check again.
No way.
Father, how's the matter with the female doctor?
What else?
King Li came back with merit.
to ask His Majesty for credit.
Besides,
Physician Song's daughter didn't get hurt.
His Majesty didn't scold him.
Lady-in-waiting Xu,
It's all your good idea.
I'll rip your mouth.
Stop!
What are you doing?
That's a court lady.
Look at you now.
Are you going to help outsiders bully your daughter?
I...
used to think I owe you so much.
I thought Jiayue took yours.
But this time,
do you think this life is too peaceful?
to provoke a court lady?
My life is so hard.
I was pushed down by a fake.
and was driven back to his maiden home by His Highness.
The fake was just sick.
A minor injury
His Highness wants to kidnap the physician.
I'm worried that the royal mansion will be in danger.
But no one worries about me.
It's all my fault.
Even the father I cherish the most
only loves her, not me.
Liuli.
How can I not love you?
Of course I love you.
Right?
By the way, I have a big coral.
You must like it.
That's right.
Let's go. I'll take you to get it.
Virtuous Virtuous Virtuous Virtuous Peak Army
The Virtuous Dragon Gate
The handsome and handsome man Bin Ying and Cheng come to Xinxin Kingdom
Lei Jian, the handsome and handsome man Bin Ying and Cheng come to Xinchun Hui, Ningzhuahua, the strongest and the strongest
Yoonan.
Nini.
A red sky.
Superfish.
The morning of the army
Superfish
Woyi Dong wins.
Xu Yi Dong Yue.
Wai Xin Bin Hui Min Hua
Hurry.
Feng Yin Liang.
Wan Juanqi.
A good deed.
Loyalty and graceful.
Yi He Min.
Qing Shabai Yi He Min
Qingsha, Bai Yi He Min.
Bin Hanyue.
Ye Yang becomes Kun Yan.
My promise is fulfilled.
The crane is shining and the snow is shining.
The crane is shining with snow and fruit.