(Touch Your Heart)
(Episode 5)
Who is it so early in the morning?
I'll be seeing a client,
so will be in an hour late.
Alright. I see.
It's going to be cold today,
so make sure to dress warm.
Was that going too far?
Make sure to dress warm too,
Ms. Oh Jin-shim.
Well, he told me to dress warm,
so I'll dress warm, then.
Pink is always right!
I look so pretty.
Doors closing.
Wait! Please wait for me!
Ah, thank you.
Oh, it's you, Kwon.
Doors closing.
As always, I bump into you
in the elevator.
Even though I came in an hour late
as I was seeing a client.
If someone else heard us,
they'll think that
I'm always waiting around the
elevator to bump into you.
I was also seeing a client too,
that's why I came in late.
By the way, I have some good news.
I don't want to know.
Your good news has
never turned out to be
quite good for me.
I mean it this time!
I have two amazingly good news,
so which would you like to
hear first?
There's the big good news,
and the small good news.
Fine.
Since us men always go for big,
I'll tell you the
big good news first.
Always may be
taking on a big, big case.
It's 99% confirmed at the moment,
but if we do take it,
we'll be able to make
a name for ourselves.
Just what is this case anyway?
Oh, that's a secret.
Now the small good news.
We're going to have
a group dinner tonight.
Kwon?
Kwon, where's your answer?
We're going to have
a group dinner tonight.
I won't be there.
You always say that.
Why can't you enjoy even the
good news that's brought to you?
He's a weird one.
Sorry I'm late today.
Ah, you're here.
What's all this?
It's so pretty, right?
Spring is coming.
So I decided to make it
all... Pink pink!
Even if spring is approaching,
"pink pink" for
a law firm, is a bit...
So...?
Are you saying it's not allowed?
You do realize that
that's violating my right to
pursue happiness,
and my freedom of
common action, right?
How did you...
You told me at the
drive-in theater.
I have a good memory,
so I remember everything.
Fine, then.
Do what you want.
What is all this?
It's not nice to just
skip your desk, so...
Still, I prefer black over
"pink pink."
Even if you do prefer black,
why don't you try pink sometimes?
You'll find that it cheers you up.
Please respect my right to
pursue happiness,
and my freedom of
common action as well.
Alright, I'll clear them.
The strawberry...
Oh, um.
Take these, too.
Just keep them.
When I'm away from my desk,
you could just leave
a note for me, can't you?
So that we don't both just
forget about it.
Then please excuse me.
Then...
What the...
Yes.
I'll send that certificate of
contents through, then.
Alright.
(Please send that certificate of
contents to Ms. Jung Da-young)
Please send that certificate of
contents to Ms. Jung Da-young.
(Yes, Mr. Kwon)
Yes?
"Yes, Mr. Kwon."
She could've just said it instead.
Could you submit an application to
change Mr. Park Jae-won's hearing
to next Tuesday?
It's been re-scheduled for
February 26th, at 3 p.m.
Please contact the Prosecution
Service in Cheongju
and ask for Mr. Baek Sun-myung's
case files.
All done.
Please check and inform
Mr. Han of the appellate deadline.
The deadline is the 27th,
and he'd like to appeal.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I've been
dumping work on you.
No, it's alright. Anytime.
Yes, hello?
Is this quick delivery?
I'm Dan Mun-hee from Always...
Yes.
I need to send something by
quick delivery.
Alright, I'll be waiting.
I wonder what he thinks of me.
He...
He likes me,
he likes me not.
he likes me,
He likes me, he likes me not.
- He...
- ...likes me!
I guess he must like you, too!
But you know, I've seen
people do it with flower petals,
but never with mandarin oranges.
It's my first time, too.
I'm just so desperate to know
what he thinks of me.
What's he like?
Is it still one-sided?
Well.
I think he's interested
in me, too, and...
Will you hear me out?
Yes, sure.
He's the quick delivery guy
who often comes to our office.
And his tone changes
when he's talking to me.
To other people, he's like,
"Did you call for
delivery service?"
But to me, he's like, "Did you
call for delivery service?"
Just shows how much
he's excited to see me.
But that's not all.
They give you a free keychain
after you use their
service for five times,
but I only called 4 times.
Just four times,
and only four times, yet...!
Yet he gave me this key chain.
Love makes you want to give
everything you have, right?
Wow, that's so pretty.
I guess he's head over
heels in love with you.
- Really?
- Yes.
Since it's coming from you,
who's dated a ton of guys,
I'll believe you.
Huh?
I've never… had a relationship.
Oh, right. I read your interview.
So you've never had a boyfriend.
But even though
I've never been in a relationship,
I'm good at giving advice on love.
Remember that
matchmaking TV show?
I even hosted that show!
So from how I see it,
it's 100%.
Oh please!
Yay!
- This is a secret, alright?
- Sure.
Wow.
She must really like him.
So with mandarins oranges...?
Should I try it too, then?
He likes me,
he likes me not.
(He likes me
He likes me not)
He likes me...)
He likes me!
Ms. Oh Jin-shim,
it's time to go to Court.
Yes, I'm coming.
Our witness' testimony just now
validates my client's alibi as true.
In other words, he was not
present at the scene.
So Your Honor,
I ask that you sentence him
not guilty.
Mr. Kwon.
It looks like we'll win, right?
Yes, well...
No need to be so humble!
You're smiling, so that means
you're confident that we will.
I guess you're a lawyer,
being happy over a win.
By the way, why did you
decide to become a lawyer?
From what I heard,
I heard all your friends from
college are now prosecutors.
Lawyers make much more money.
Oh what? He became
a lawyer for money?
So he's honest too, isn't he?
The more you get to know him,
the more charming he is.
It's lunchtime,
so should we have lunch
before going back in?
Sure.
Oh what?
Ah, that's right.
What if she asks us to
join her for coffee again?
No.
Since it's lunchtime, she might
ask us to go for lunch.
Aren't you coming?
I am. Let's go!
Come on, hurry up!
- Kwon Jung-rok!
- Huh?
UFO!
- What?
- Over there!
It went over there.
Come on, hurry up!
- Hurry up!
- Jung-rok.
Hey.
I guess you had a trial?
Yes.
I'm bumping into you
quite often, aren't I?
What, you don't like that?
Hello, so you came with him
today, Ms. Oh.
Yes, well...
If you're alright for time,
how about we go for lunch?
How does pasta sound?
Pasta?
You see, there's something
I want to talk to you about.
- Is it something important?
- Yes.
It's very important.
And quite confidential, too.
I'm very sorry, but
please go ahead first.
What?
Go ahead first?
He promised to go have
lunch with him first,
so why won't he keep his promise?
Doesn't he know
just how much I like...
...pasta?
So, what's this important and
confidential subject?
- You know the Lim Yun-hee case?
- Yes.
I've been put in charge of it.
Here we have a woman who's
a long-time DV victim,
and she stabbed her husband to
death when he beat her up.
So, is this homicide or
self-defense?
What are your thoughts?
But if her claim of
self-defense is accepted,
not only is it a burden for the
prosecutor leading the
investigation, but many more
people in a similar situation
will claim self-defense
in the future.
And all the lawyers too,
will take this as an example
and argue for
self-defense as well.
As you can see, it's
a sensitive topic for us.
But this is a grey zone.
Right?
I wasn't asking you,
hoping for an answer.
I just took the case, pretending
I'm ready to handle it,
but really, I'm quite lost.
Shall we go get coffee?
No, I have to get going.
Why? I thought
you still had some time left.
I have something to do.
I'll catch you later, then.
Why's he so busy?
Why were you in there?
To confiscate these!
You're not qualified to
have these notes.
Do I need to be? For notes?
Why? I thought you didn't
want them from the start.
Now you want them, do you?
Not quite, but why take back
something you gave to me?
Because I want to.
These were mine anyway.
If that ticks you off,
then sue me.
I don't think that's necessary.
There's still 20 minutes to go,
so why don't we go out
so you can eat lunch?
I'm not in the mood for
lunch anymore!
Why are you glaring at me?
I'm not.
People always tell me my
eyes always burn with intensity.
But to be an actress,
you need to be able to knock back
the camera with your eyes.
Alright, then. Have a nice one.
Um, excuse me.
Yes?
Did you have something to say?
This is totally out of the blue,
but let's have lunch sometime.
- Sorry?
- How about tomorrow?
Why don't we go somewhere
nice together for lunch?
Oh... I don't think I'll be
all that hungry tomorrow.
Then let's watch a movie!
Do you like melodramas?
How about "Love in Titicaca?"
- How does that sound?
- I watched it yesterday.
It comes out tomorrow.
Oh... So it comes out tomorrow.
Um, I'll just be direct.
I like you too, Chan-seong.
"I like you too?"
So I'd like to
see a movie with you
or have lunch with you,
so that I can get to
know you better.
Sorry, but I really
didn't see this coming.
Will you give me
some time to think?
Of course.
But how much time?
About...
...ten years?
Take care, then.
I'm off to see a client, and
will go straight home from there.
Alright.
Are you mad at me for something?
If this is about
how I broke our promise to
have lunch together earlier...
It's nothing like that.
Then why are you...
Do I have to tell you everything?
Don't you know we have
the right to privacy?
Did I teach you this, too?
No, I learned that on my own.
It's stated in Article 17,
of our Constitution.
But that's not
what's important here.
Alright, then.
I'll respect
your right to privacy.
Um...
Can I ask you something?
Between "Avatar"
you watched in 2009,
and "What's Wrong With
My Lawyer" you watched last week,
which did you like better?
Sorry?
I'm asking,
which you liked better,
and which was more memorable.
"Avatar" dealt with a unique theme
so it was entertaining,
but so was
"What's Wrong With My Lawyer,"
because I could relate to it.
So you like both,
and can't choose between the two?
You're really bad, you know that?
Then I'll see you on the
day of the trial.
Sure, please tell me if you need
any more documents.
- I'll see you, then.
- Goodbye.
Please re-check with
our witness that
he'll be standing in Court
next week,
and guide him through
the procedures.
(OK)
"OK?"
What's wrong with her?
Welcome.
Should I have booked
a private room?
Yun-seo,
are you fine with having dinner
in an open space?
Sure.
I'll just sit in a corner,
like this.
Mr. Kwon's not joining us
again, is he?
Have you ever seen Kwon
join us on his free will?
Hey, over there!
He's joined us on
his free will tonight.
- Alright, cheers!
- Cheers!
We've the whole team here
in a long time.
Ms. Dan, why are you
drinking like that?
She's been rejected again.
By that quick delivery guy
this time.
- Really?
- Wow.
You were quick to fall for him
and to be rejected, weren't you?
You must be quite busy, Ms. Dan.
Being rejected at least
once a week!
What did you say?
Anyway, what happened?
You said you won't be coming,
just this morning.
What changed your mind?
Well...
Why are you looking at Yun-seo?
Are you here to see Yun-seo?
Yes. I'm here to see
Ms. Oh Jin-shim.
Whoa, he straight up admitted it!
Then something's going on
between you two, is there?
What?
That's just preposterous.
- It's not like that.
- Then...
...why that shocking statement?
It's nothing shocking.
I'm really here to see
Ms. Oh Jin-shim.
I had something to ask her.
Something to ask her?
She's been working diligently,
and very enthusiastic
about her work too,
even using her own time to
study law.
But today, for some reason,
she was half-hearted in her duties
and expressed her
discontent with me.
I know she's not someone to
do that without a reason,
so I came here to
clear any misunderstanding.
Ms. Oh Jin-shim.
Just why are you mad at me?
What... You're asking,
in front of everyone?
Yes. I thought I should
so others can hear us out.
And if the majority judges
it was my fault,
I'll try and fix my faults.
So please. Go ahead and tell me.
You said it wasn't because
I couldn't keep my promise
that I'll have lunch with you.
Then is it perhaps because
I forbid you from decorating
my office in pink?
- Excuse me, Mr. Kwon.
- What...
What's this about?
Um, you see... I like pink.
I really do.
So uh...
I decorated
Mr. Kwon's office in pink,
and he said he hates it. And I...
But that's not why I'm mad.
Then are you mad because
I gave you so much work today?
Because I kept sticking notes
on your desk?
Tsk, you've no humanity, do you?
If you have work to give her,
ask her politely in person,
instead of just chucking
notes on her desk!
Even I'd be offended. Right?
No, it's not because of that.
It's uh...
Well, I don't think I had
a particular reason, really.
I think I was just...
...all sensitive, because
I was hungry.
Yes, right.
I'm sorry I made you
misunderstand, Mr. Kwon.
It's alright.
I'm glad that's been cleared up.
So it was nothing after all.
Then why don't we
drink to your making up?
No, there's no need.
I guess Mr. Kwon feels much better
now that it's been cleared.
Come on.
Cheers!
That's nice to see.
Please, go on.
Sure.
Mr. Kwon?
Can I talk to you?
Sure.
I thought we cleared
our misunderstandings.
So what's this about now?
Why did you?
Why did you do that?
- Why did I... What?
- It's...
This is about us,
so we should solve it between us.
So why did you have to go and
blab about it, in front of
everyone else? Why?
Blab about it?
As I explained before,
I wanted everyone to
hear me out, and
if the majority judged that
it was my fault...
What, is this a trial?
Picking faults in front of
everyone, that's...
How's that different to a trial?
I'm sorry if that offended you.
But now that we finally
cleared our misunderstanding...
Clear our misunderstanding?
Whatever!
Oh no, we're not done yet.
Why?
Because the reason
why I'm mad at you, is...
...entirely something else.
Just what...
Why did you go have pasta
with her?
Why not me?
I wanted pasta, too!
Then you were mad at me
for the whole day...
...over pasta?
Let's go get pasta tomorrow, then.
Why did you?
Why did you have pasta
with someone else?
I hate that.
Pasta...
Pasta!
I wanted pasta, too...
Welcome home.
Sure.
By the way, Ju-won told me.
He saw you having pasta
with Yeo-reum.
Pasta again?
What do you mean, again?
This is the first time
I'm asking you about it.
So what? What if I had pasta?
What about it, huh?
I'm saying, I'm jealous.
What?
- Jealous?
- Of course.
Though I'm like this now
after breaking up with her,
that doesn't mean
I'm completely over her.
What, you don't think
I'll be mad when I hear that
the girl I'm interested in is
having pasta with another man?
If you're mad that she had
pasta with someone else...
Does that mean...
...you're interested in her?
What?
She's interested in me?
Hyuk-jun.
Shall we go for a drive
to the sea?
What are you on about
from so early in the morning?
You need to go to work.
Right?
I need to go to work...
Did you do something
stupid again, drunk last night?
Who do you think invented alcohol?
So you did. Yep!
I want to ask myself, too.
Just who invented alcohol,
only to drive you into
a corner, each time?
So what did you do this time?
- I don't know.
- Whatever, tell me!
That way, I can cover up for you
or make excuses for you.
I said, I don't know!
I want to be alone. Get out!
What, here?
We're here now.
Really?
We're here already?
Oh no.
How do I explain myself?
What do I do?
Hello.
Yes, good morning.
Ms. Oh Jin-shim.
Yes?
The trial from yesterday.
Can you check that the
written ruling was sent,
and whether the case 2018-327
has been filed for appeal?
Ah, sure.
Um...
Mr. Kwon?
About what I said last night...
Huh? Just what...
Well,
about how I ranted about
why you had pasta with
someone else, and not me.
Well, that was just
out of friendship.
Friendship?
Yes.
Girls are like that.
Even in high school,
when your best friend goes for
teokbokki with someone else
and not you,
you just get so mad, you know?
And it feels like she's been
stolen from you.
I mean, let's be honest.
We're like best friends
at Always, right?
"Best friends?"
Yes. We are the best of friends.
I mean, I work closest to you,
and we have lunch together.
And we solve cases together!
Who else is a better
"best friend" than you?
So... I was a tad bit mad that
my best friend seemed
more intimate with
someone else, and not me.
Just a tad bit.
It's childish, right?
Not only do I look
young for my age,
but so is my mentality...
So please forget about
what happened yesterday.
- Alright?
- Yes.
Alright.
Mr. Kwon.
Mr. Yeon wants to see you.
Alright.
I'll be back.
Sure.
What am I doing?
What did you want to see me for?
Did I mention this yesterday?
I did, right? Yes, I did.
I said we may have
some good news, right?
That Always may take on
a big case that will have
the whole world know about us?
So it's come to us, has it?
Well, you know.
Here.
Have a read.
And this, too.
Isn't this the Lim Yun-hee case?
It's the hottest case
there is right now.
I want to hear not guilty, based
on the grounds of self-defense.
I can't.
Why can't you? Why not?
I've put you in charge of a big
case, so you should say thank you.
Why are you rebelling again?
This isn't rebelling,
I simply can't.
The number of cases
I'm handling right now is...
...thirty-two.
Hey, still.
Everyone's eyes are on this case,
so it's too good to pass up.
If that's what you think,
then why don't you take it?
Besides, you're not
all that busy these days.
And we know you won't get any more
offers for TV appearances.
Let's not talk about that.
Even if I did get an offer,
I'm not doing it anymore.
I've been traumatized
after that incident.
All it was, was that
it wasn't my best day,
but there were
all these hate comments!
"Did he really pass the bar exam,
because he was
stuttering like an idiot.
Maybe he's just a representative,
and not a lawyer?"
It... It really was embarrassing.
So from now on,
don’t even mention the word
TV again to me.
But Mr. Yeon, you...
I said, don't even
mention that word!
- Cushion.
- I said, don't!
Your cushion.
You think this is a cushion?
This is a blanket!
Anyway, you're taking
this case, alright?
You've taken a lot of cases
with high public interest,
and so the women's rights advocacy
asked for you especially.
Alright?
(Lim Arrested On
Suspicions of Homicide)
(From a DV Victim to
a Murder Suspect)
(Her Ex-husband Also
Perished in Fire, 5 Years Ago)
Please have a read, and
see if you can find
any more relevant articles.
Sure.
Huh?
I saw this on the news.
So you'll be defending her,
will you?
Somehow, it turned out that way.
Great.
If someone as competent
as you can represent her,
maybe her claims of
self-defense will be accepted.
Ms. Oh Jin-shim,
do you believe this was
on the grounds of self-defense?
Sure.
From what I heard,
it was on a spur
while she was being beaten
badly by her husband.
But it's not as simple
as it sounds.
Besides, for the Court to judge
it was self-defense,
there are some pre-conditions.
Pre-conditions?
(Yu Yeo-reum, Prosecutor)
Prosecutor Yu, Ms. Lim Yun-hee
will be here soon.
Alright.
I won't take so long
with her today.
Here she comes.
For the establishment
of self-defense,
a pre-condition is that there was
an attack against you,
or a third party.
And that attack must have
happened before your eyes,
at the time of action.
How do you feel?
And finally,
even if you were exercising
action to defend yourself,
it can't be at an extreme level.
Put simply,
even if you were taking
action to defend yourself,
there is a limit to
how far you can go.
For example, if someone slaps you,
you can't hit them back
with a weapon.
That won't be recognized as lawful
exercise of right to self-defense.
There were similar cases
in the past,
but none were accepted as
it was based on the
grounds of self-defense
by the High Court.
And the Prosecution will probably
refer to these cases.
Then why don't you make
a new case example?
By winning this case.
But it could be that she may have
murdered him intentionally.
Anyway, please search up
more articles for me.
Sure.
Ms. Lim Yun-hee?
From here on, I will address you
as "suspect."
You have the right to
remain silent,
and right to refuse to
answer specific questions.
Choosing to remain silent will not
disadvantage you in Court,
and you may seek assistance
from your attorney.
Ms. Lim Yun-hee, you have been
notified about
the right to silence,
have you not?
Will you seek assistance
from your attorney?
Or shall we begin?
Why did you want to see me again?
Ah, are you busy?
I was reviewing that
Lim Yun-hee case.
So, do you think you see a way?
Well.
I'll have to go to
the detention center
and meet with her first.
As I thought!
Once you're on it,
you give it 100%.
So... You're here to check
whether I'm on it, 100%?
Hey, come on!
Do you really think
I called you to check up on you?
Hmmm?
Pick out a tie for me.
This is homme fatale look,
and this is the
innocent, shy-guy look.
Which do you think is better?
What are you doing?
You see,
I've been contacted by the media.
They're coming for
an interview tomorrow!
But not so long ago,
you said you were
traumatized by that incident
and that you'll have nothing to
do with the media again.
Confucius once said,
"The best of glory is
not about never failing,
but getting up every time
after each failure."
Though my first appearance had me
nervous and ended as a failure,
I'm going to overcome it
and get up.
And should I fail again,
I'm going to get up again.
Then I guess it's time for me to
get up as well.
I'm really tired now,
and I desperately need coffee.
Can you get me one too,
with extra shot?
Wait, about Yun-seo!
What about Yun-seo?
The director told me
they're a bit behind
so they're not sure what
time they'll be here.
If they catch her
walking around here,
it might make her
feel uncomfortable.
But it's not like we can make her
stay at a cafe all day.
Oh well. I'm sure it'll be okay.
I mean, there has to be somewhere
for her to hide in this office!
Right?
Homme fatale.
Innocent.
What do you think? Is this better?
- Go with homme fatale.
- Homme fatale.
This is better.
Ah.
Would you like
a cup of coffee as well?
No, it's alright.
I can get my own.
Ms. Oh Jin-shim.
I'm going to the detention center
to meet Ms. Lim Yun-hee.
Would you like to come with me?
- What, me?
- Yes.
Though you won't be able to see
her since you're not her lawyer,
a trip to the detention center
could help you out in your career.
Of course!
It'll help way more than
not going at all.
Thank you,
for thinking about me.
Have your coffee, then.
Detention center...
That means a long drive.
Then it's just us two, and...
Since we're going far,
let's be prepared.
After all, this is work.
Yep!
What should I wear tomorrow?
If I don’t like my outfit,
I'll feel depressed,
and won't be able to
concentrate on work, so...
If my skin feels dry,
I won't be able to
concentrate on work, so...
I really must be a workaholic!
Good morning, Mr. Kwon.
Your tie.
It suits you very well.
Your necklace suits you
very well, too.
Please get in. It's cold out.
It's so nice, going for
a drive in a long time.
We're not going for a drive, but
we're off to the detention center.
To work.
Well, we're in a car,
so that's going for a drive.
Yes, this is Kwon Jung-rok.
Yes, alright.
That was from
the detention center.
My visit's been delayed
by two hours.
Really?
It's almost lunchtime,
so why don't we go
somewhere for lunch?
Um, actually...
I packed lunch for us.
Lunch?
It's a waste of time,
trying to find a restaurant.
I wanted to avoid that,
so we can focus on work.
Besides, it's always been
my dream to
eat lunch out in a nice place.
Well, we've time to kill,
so let's do that.
Sure.
Shall we just eat in the car?
No, let's just eat here.
But why? It's cold out here.
You said it's your dream.
I didn't expect you to
be a good cook.
Hey, what did you
think of me, then?
I once played a Korean
food chef in a drama.
For that role,
I learned from professional,
and now I can cook up
anything in a second!
As an actress,
you get to experience
many lives, don't you?
It sounds interesting.
I was really happy, back then.
What makes you feel happy?
Pay day?
Oh what?
You said you became a lawyer
because lawyers make money,
so it must be true
that you love money.
Actually, no.
Let's go in.
It's my loss if you catch a cold.
Sorry?
Why would that be your loss?
Huh?
Well, you're the ace attorney
at our law firm,
so if you come down with
a cold because of me
and can't come to work,
imagine what I'll have to
deal with for that whole day!
That'll be a huge loss of
manpower for the firm.
If you're cold, put your
hands in the pocket.
Really?
Thank you.
I meant, in your pocket.
I'm sorry.
Pocket...
Prosecutor.
Isn't it uncomfortable,
crashing at your friend's place?
It is, extremely.
He's so fussy, too.
Then it must be uncomfortable
being home all day on the weekend.
How about you watch
a movie with me, then?
That sounds even
more uncomfortable.
That's Prosecutor Yu.
Prosecutor Yu must be
stressed about that
Lim Yun-hee case.
Why?
It's not going well?
That Lim Yun-hee case...
Prosecutor Lim had been after it,
but Prosecutor Yu took it instead.
Prosecutor Lim's known for
holding a grudge,
so I hear he's been bullying her.
Ah, so that's the new girl
who came.
Assigned under Kim Se-won.
But why are they always together?
Are they going out?
I hear her father's
someone high-up.
A son of a hospital director, and
a daughter of a high official...
Not a bad match, I must say.
Right?
I agree.
Isn't the new girl a great match
for Kim Se-won?
They were both born with
silver spoons in their mouths.
But then again,
A son of a hospital director, and
a daughter of a con...
It just doesn't make sense.
But you know, I must say
you are something.
First your father commits fraud,
next your ex-boyfriend
chooses not to indict him
and gets transferred to Chuncheon!
How could you still
hold your head up high,
despite all that?
If I were you, I would be
too ashamed to be here.
What is it that
you're trying to say?
That you can't hide low birth.
Even if you get greedy,
a prosecutor is as
far as you'll go.
But then again,
I guess you know that, which is
why you're trying so hard.
Right? So you can try
climbing up the ladder.
- Please stop.
- Do you think
the Lim Yun-hee case went to you,
because of your competence?
It's because you're a woman,
and they wanted to
make use of that.
If you now know,
then know your place already.
Would you like to wait in the car?
No.
I'll take a look around.
As I explained before,
you won't be allowed in with me.
I know that much.
So everyone here...
Are they all waiting for
their trial, like Ms. Lim?
That's not always the case.
they may be convicted already,
or be a prisoner on trial.
Oh my, it's 2 o'clock already.
You should get going.
It's cold out, so I think
you should just wait...
Why? Are you worried?
Yes, I am.
Because it's also my loss
if you ever catch a cold.
But why...
If you catch a cold,
everything will slow down,
and that means I'll have
more to do myself.
And on top of that, if I ever
catch it from you...
Ha, you're so unbelievable.
Happy now?
It's very cold today.
Don't be stubborn,
but wait in the car
after you take a look around.
Oh what?
So is he worried about me?
Oh what? Oh what?
Ms. Lim.
Could you tell me
just what happened, on that day?
I understand it's painful to
recall the incident,
you need to tell me what happened,
without leaving out
even the tiniest detail.
Do you admit to the
charges brought against you,
that you killed your husband?
Then do you have remorse for
your actions?
I fully understand that
you had long suffered
from your husband's violence.
However,
the fact that you are
a domestic violence victim
does not justify your
actions of homicide.
Then...
What else should I have done?
Should I have died, instead?
(Case file)
No matter how I think about it,
it has to be self-defense.
So, how was it?
It was self-defense, wasn't it?
I don't think we should come to
a hasty conclusion just yet.
I guess meeting with her has
left you with more doubts.
Then while you're driving,
I'll read this through once more.
There may just be a way,
if I go over it carefully.
Just trust me.
Sure.
You said you'll find a way.
Oh my!
I must've dozed off
while contemplating.
You should've woke me up
if we're here already.
You were sleeping
too soundly, so...
Did you wait long?
No.
I didn't make any mistakes
while sleeping, did I?
I'm not sure if you can
call it a mistake,
but you snored. A lot.
Me?
Oh Yun-seo?
No way. I don't snore!
Just kidding.
How could you tell a joke
with a straight face like that?
But is it so wrong to snore?
Of course!
I want you to see
only my best side...
What, me?
Yes, because...
You're stricter than
any other person!
Otherwise, you might
pick faults with me, so...
Thank you for today.
Have a good night.
Are you crazy?
Why did you say that just now?
Ah, hello.
Yes.
There's something I need you to
look urgently into.
Ms. Lim Yun-hee's father
was also abusive,
so her mother walked out
when she was little
and it was just her and
her father from then on.
But her father too,
has been missing
since ten years ago.
Ten years,
since he's been missing...
Then he must've been
determined dead, then.
That's right.
Her mother walked out on her,
her father deemed dead
after missing for so long,
her ex-husband perished in fire,
and now, her current husband...
What a life.
I must say so myself.
Ever since she graduated
from high school,
she's been working odd jobs
including as a cashier
and a salesperson
at department stores.
Oh, she was also in insurance.
Did you say insurance?
Do you think there's a way
with this case?
Well...
The main arguments will be
that it was on impulse versus
that she'd been after the
insurance payout.
There's the fact that
she was in insurance,
so they'll be
even more suspicious.
About Ms. Lim Yun-hee.
Her file said her ex-husband had
also exerted physical violence.
So why do you think she
married another guy like him?
Shouldn't she have known better?
But then, I played a psychologist
in a drama once,
and one of my patients was
a woman who
forgave her DV husband every time
he begged for forgiveness.
But apparently, that's
a mental issue.
I have requested that
she sees a psychologist, yes.
(Yu Yeo-reum)
I don't know what to say.
You knew how hung up
I am on this case,
so did you have to
choose to oppose me?
It's against ethics to
reject a client
when she asks you to
defend her, isn't it?
If I have to take every factor
into consideration
before taking a case,
I'll have to reject them all.
I know.
But there's something
you should know, too.
The Court has never recognized
a case as being
a lawful exercise of
right to self-defense.
That's not so important to me.
Anyway, I'm going to do my best to
reveal the truth,
and if she is found guilty,
I'll make sure
she isn't over-penalized.
And if she isn't, I'll make sure
she receives a not guilty ruling.
Because that's what my job is.
She will never be
sentenced not guilty.
Because that is my job.
- ...The Prosecution...
- Today,
Ms. Lim Yun-hee will be in Court
for her first hearing.
The Prosecution has charged
Ms. Lim Yun-hee,
who had supposedly murdered
her husband on impulse
as an act of self defense,
not for the crime of injury
but for homicide.
Ms. Lim Yun-hee is the
legal spouse of
Mr. Kim Hyung-tae, the victim,
and while being physically
abused by him in their home
on January 21st, 2019,
she went to the kitchen
and took up a kitchen knife,
threatening to kill him
before stabbing him once
in the chest and in the abdomen.
Our victim, Mr. Kim Hyung-tae
was a long-time DV offender
so the defendant's actions
may be viewed as
an act of self-defense.
However, if you see the
autopsy report that was submitted,
it becomes clear that
this is homicide with
clear intentions.
What is the chance that
this knife ended stabbing him
where it would prove fatal?
For this reason, the
prosecution has charged
Ms. Lim on the crime of homicide.
You may begin your defense.
According to the testimony by
the paramedic who was
present at the scene,
my client had suffered
severe injuries,
including two broken ribs.
Even if she did
stab him intentionally,
what is the chance of
a fragile woman,
with severe injuries requiring
9 weeks in hospital,
stab him once right at the spot
where it would prove
fatal for him?
For this reason,
we plead not guilty, on the
grounds of self-defense.
At the time, Ms. Lim had
no other intention
or no other plan whatsoever,
except for her desperate
will to survive.
Ms. Lim. You said your mother
walked out on you
when you were ten.
What was the reason?
She hit her head hard on the floor
while being beaten by
my drunk father.
There was a lot of blood,
and while father was searching for
something to hit her again with,
she fled.
Probably to live.
And ever since then,
your father started
abusing you as well.
Is this true?
Yes, it's true.
Your ex-husband, and
Mr. Kim Hyung-tae too,
were also abusive.
The memories of your father
must have been painful enough,
so why did you marry men
who had the same
violent character?
Your Honor.
I'd like to call
her psychologist to stand,
who may better help us
grasp her situation.
Though you may be
so convinced at first,
but when you're exposed to
an abnormal situation for long,
you come to accept that
this is the norm.
Could you expand on that?
Those who have been
abused since young
fail to realize that abuse is
something that's wrong.
And at one point, they come to
accept that this is the norm,
and even find themselves
psychologically unstable
if this abnormal environment
doesn't hold up.
In the end, you're left with
a vicious cycle.
If you look at
our psychologist's report,
it reads, "Based on the fact
that the patient has been
exposed to an abusive environment
since childhood,
it can be said her sense of
judgment is distorted."
Is this true?
Yes, that was my conclusion.
In other words,
according to your analysis,
we can conclude Ms. Lim was not
mentally sound
at the time of the incident.
Do you agree?
Yes.
I rest my case.
Counsel,
will you cross-examine?
Yes.
Ms. Lim Yun-hee.
These are the applications for
the insurance payouts
for your ex-husband, and
also for your father's death.
Did you submit these
papers in person?
Yes, I did.
You were also aware that
Mr. Kim Hyung-tae had
- life insurance?
- Yes.
Do you know how much
the amount is, in total?
No, I do not.
The total payout of the insurance
plan for Mr. Kim is...
...4.94 million dollars.
Isn't the amount too large to
simply say you did not know?
I rest my case.
Going with abnormality of
mental functioning, are you?
But then again, even if
self-defense is not accepted,
it's not bad business for you
if you can reduce her sentence
by claiming she isn't
mentally sound.
Don't put it like that.
Whether it's self defense or
poor mental functioning,
they're both valid reasons
under the Penal Code.
I won't ever let the
Court accept your argument,
so don't even try.
Because this is
something you can't win.
Why are you so hung upon
that Lim Yun-hee case?
Because this is the only way.
Though you'll never understand,
since your starting line was
so far ahead.
You're back.
- Welcome back.
- We're back.
Um...
What about Mr. Kwon?
He told me to go ahead first,
because he needs to speak
with the prosecutor.
How did the trial go today?
It's all over the news!
From your expression...
Does that mean it didn't go
so favorably for us?
No. It was all fine
when Mr. Kwon argued that
she was not mentally healthy,
but when the topic of
insurance came up,
everyone was bought.
How much is the payout anyway?
4.9 million dollars.
4.9 million...
No wonder the
audience was convinced.
Right.
Even I'm starting to suspect that
she did it for the money.
Poor Mr. Kwon!
The media is following
this case closely,
so if he loses,
that'll mean a lot of damage.
The ruling's not out yet,
so don't say that.
Mr. Kwon...
I'm back.
Um,
Mr. Kwon?
Don't mind too much
what other people said.
I won't.
Because based on today's results,
anyone would think the same.
Sure.
But you know,
I think you'll win.
I'll be honest.
I thought lawyers were people
who were all about
logic and principles,
but now I see some lawyers with warm hearts.
Just like you, Mr. Kwon.
Because you're warm-hearted and
considerate, even though
you look like you don't.
There was a time in the past
when I felt like I was the
only one left in this world
and that no one was
there by my side.
It had been so hard for me.
Now I'm thinking about
how nice it would've been,
if I had someone like you
by my side, back then.
Because you're that amazing,
I'm sure you'll solve
this case beautifully.
It's already...
Why haven't you gone home already?
I was searching up some
relevant case examples.
In case they might help.
Would you like to
join me for dinner?
Sure. You know, I'm really hungry.
Then let's go.
To be honest,
I became a lawyer because...
Rather than to punish people,
I wanted to be on their side.
Oh.
Then why did you say it was
because lawyers make
lots of money?
Because... It's kind of
embarrassing to say it honestly.
Hmmm?
Then why are you being honest now?
Because...
I just wanted to, after
what you told me.
Thank you for telling me that
you believe in me.
And... If you
find yourself in that situation,
where you feel like you have
no one else in this world...
then I'll be on your side.
Mr. Kwon...
There's something
I need to tell you.
But...
But not just now.
However, this feeling...
What I'm feeling now,
I'm going to tell you someday.
Ms. Oh Jin-shim.
Do you...
...like...
What?
(Thank you to Hwang Chan-seong for
his special appearance)
(It's alright, anytime)
(Touch Your Heart)
Working girl,
workaholic!
You're so sexy.
Aren't you slaving
my Yun-seo around?
"My" Yun-seo?
- Hey, I...
- "Oppa?"
Would you like some coffee?
Didn't he tell me not to
slave you around?
Your boyfriend, I mean.
You've never had
a girlfriend, have you?
Because I don't think you have
talent in that field.
Someone once told me,
that she thinks I'll win this case.
So please believe in me.
This has taken a new turn.
This person could be
our only witness,
or even a whole new suspect.