President Gu
Why are you here?
Why are you back so late?
Is something wrong?
I...
I have a question for you.
And this question...
Is a very serious and earnest one.
Let's talk upstairs.
It's not raining anymore, why the umbrella?
I think you're really out of your mind.
Tell me.
What is it exactly?
You and Du Zheng,
and Feng Ziang,
have known each other for over 20 years?
Yeah.
We've known each other for 24 years.
Because our fathers knew each other.
Then Director Feng has been...
pursuing you lately.
Any thoughts on that?
To me,
Du Zheng will be in my heart forever.
No one can ever replace him.
Let me ask... ask one more question.
You must answer it carefully.
Back when I had my heart surgery,
right after I was discharged,
the first time you saw me,
did you have any special thoughts?
What special thoughts?
I mean, when you saw me,
did you feel I looked a lot like...
someone?
Like someone?
Did you feel I looked a lot like...
someone you know?
No.
Wait.
Isn't it a good thing she didn't think of anyone else?
It means in her heart,
I'm not a replacement for Du Zheng.
Besides,
there are very few people with a personality like yours.
You're so handsome,
and so refined.
The refined type
is very popular right now.
Right.
I think,
compared to looks,
what's inside is more important.
So you're saying,
the police didn't find any blood
in Tan Feng's car?
Right.
That's what my source said too.
This Tan Feng,
has been cleared of suspicion for a long time.
He might be an accomplice,
but he can't be the real killer.
How did it end up like this?
All the suspects
have been cleared of suspicion.
I wonder what the police
will do next.
Is this Lin Yaoyao
actually doing her job properly?
The first time I saw that woman,
I thought she was unreliable.
Makes sense.
Useless.
Stupid.
Makes sense.
Let's drive.
Because he's a murder suspect now,
the police will be watching him closely.
So you must be careful.
Also, help me check
when the police surveillance will be looser.
I don't care what method you use,
you must complete this mission.
Okay.
Got it.
Hello, Dad.
Ziang.
When are you coming back?
I'm out discussing business.
It might take about two hours.
Well...
I want to go back for a bit.
Before I return to Tongzhou,
I have some things
I want to talk to you about.
If you're not in a hurry,
how about waiting for me at home?
We can talk when I get back.
Ziang,
I'm quite bored alone at home.
I was just thinking
you could keep me company and chat.
Then I'll head back now.
The unqualified raw materials incident...
Don't you want to explain it to me?
As the son of a factory guard,
if I want to fight the chairman,
I must find a
more powerful backer.
Are you out of your mind?
You weren't like this before.
How did you become like this?
People change.
I did it.
Because you're my brother since childhood,
I'm admitting it to you.
Now you only have two choices.
Either turn yourself in for leniency,
or
wait for me to report you.
Gaoming,
you said Du Zheng's phone
suddenly has a signal?
What's going on?
The telecom company sent a message.
They said Du Zheng's phone was turned on at night.
And the base station that received the signal
is a new one.
Yuhe District, Tongzhou City.
Yes.
We also found an important piece of information.
Within a one-kilometer radius of this base station,
is someone's hometown.
Guess who?
Who?
Feng Ziang.
Dad,
I'm back.
Ziang,
those things you did,
I know all about them.
Tomorrow I'll go find Yaoyao
and tell her about this.
Even if you cut ties with me.
Wake up!
Save him quickly!
He'll die if we don't save him!
Call 120!
You can't call!
He'll die right away without rescue!
Only one can live between Du Zheng and us.
Choose for yourself.
What are you thinking?
Have you forgotten?
I paid off hundreds of thousands in gambling debts for you.
Your wife's living and medical expenses...
We need to calculate it all.
Du Zheng already knows everything.
We caused the unqualified raw materials incident.
He knows it all.
If you revive him,
we'll have to go to jail.
Go to jail?
I won't go to jail!
Then listen to me now.
Listen to me.
Just pretend nothing happened.
Don't tell anyone anything.
I promise you,
after this is over,
I'll take your wife abroad for treatment.
And your child,
I guarantee they'll be well-fed and clothed for life.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Understood.
Let's go!
An untaught son
is the father's fault.
I feel ashamed of you,
and sad for myself.
If you still have a little conscience left,
spend the rest of your life
paying for your blood debt.
Treat Jiaqi and old Du
a little better.
Feng Wei!
Keep up.
Go check inside.
Feng Wei!
Is anyone there?
Senior!
Hurry!
Call an ambulance!
Hurry up!
Hello, is this the hospital?
This is Yuhe District, Tongzhou City.
We have someone who needs emergency care.
Secretary Peng.
I'm here.
Is your last name Peng?
Help me send the data over.
Okay.
Secretary Lin.
It's time.
Let's go to the Tongzhou factory.
Okay.
What about me?
You...
change the flowers in this vase.
Such a difficult job.
Excuse me.
Hello, Yaoyao.
I'm at work right now.
Let's talk later.
What did you say?
Yaoyao!
How is it?
Mr. Du,
the phone has been recovered.
The truck involved in the accident is scrapped.
This is the only evidence we have right now.
And we've done a blood test.
It proves it's Du Zheng's phone.
But...
how did he hit my Du Zheng?
I saw in the confession letter that
he was on his way to deliver a wallet to Feng Ziang
when he hit Du Zheng.
The phone kept ringing at the time.
He was afraid someone would see it,
so he took it away.
Mr. Du,
right now,
all the evidence
points entirely to
Feng Wei.
I'm afraid the case will be closed.
I'm sorry.
Could he really be the killer?
Did he just have a driving accident,
or did he intentionally use the car to kill?
Who are you?
No.
I feel like it shouldn't be him.
Something must have gone wrong here.
Hello?
Who is it?
Officer Lin,
this is Gu Tiancheng.
I'm at the police station right now,
waiting for you in the garden next door.
Come see me immediately.
Right now, immediately.
What is this guy doing?
Being so mysterious late at night.
What do you want from me, kid?
I asked you here
to tell you
that the hit-and-run,
the case of Du Zheng's murder,
wasn't done by Feng Wei.
What are you talking about?
At the time, I felt
there was something wrong with that truck.
The vehicle probably wasn't a truck.
Your police department
wouldn't close the case so hastily, right?
You'll reopen the investigation, right?
What does this have to do with you?
Psycho.
Don't go yet.
Fine.
Then I'll tell you.
But you must not tell anyone else.
If I tell you this,
you'll definitely think I'm
very weird and crazy.
But everything I'm saying is true.
Inside my body,
lives another person.
Lives another person?
Are you possessed by a ghost?
That's exactly how it feels.
Anyway,
after that incident happened,
my body changed.
I always have a special feeling
about certain things.
So my intuition tells me
there's something wrong with this case.
You have to believe me.
Okay?
Hello?
Okay.
Got it.
You're very lucky today, kid.
Let me tell you,
if you come looking for me again,
I definitely won't let you off.
Psycho.
Officer Lin!
Then you'll definitely reopen this case,
right?
You have to believe me!
Officer Lin!
When I found out about Uncle Feng,
I rushed over immediately.
I felt I should
bid him a final farewell.
And a final farewell
between you
and me.
I can't ignore all this
and continue to face you.
I don't know
how we're going to get along in the future.
Just like you said,
we can't even be friends anymore.
I didn't expect the words I once said
to become a sharp blade stabbing me now.
To think I dug myself
such a trap.
Thank you for taking care of me all these years.
From now on, we don't owe each other anything.
What is Gu Tiancheng doing?
Acting so weird all day.
Hello,
the number you have dialed is powered off.
Brat.
Her phone is off whenever I look for her.
To deal with the bond maturity issue now,
we need to produce new products by the first of next month.
And the quality inspection
must be completed within two weeks.
Jiaqi.
Why is your phone turned off?
Also,
Gu Tiancheng,
he's just an idiot, right?
Is there something wrong with him?
Jiaqi.
No.
It's nothing.
Um, sorry.
I'll turn it off right away.
Weiwei,
turn off the projector.
Today's new product presentation ends here.
Next,
everyone think about it,
does anyone have anything to say?
I'm really sorry.
President Gu.
I'll leave you two to talk.
For such a problem to occur on this occasion,
I feel really bad about it.
And...
thank you.
Why are you thanking me?
Thank you for helping me out.
It's nothing.
By the way,
these past few days,
how have you been feeling?
I'm fine.
Liar.
You clearly look like something's wrong.
You're a girl,
why do you have to pretend to be strong?
Why do you insist on carrying everything yourself?
Can you even handle it?
Aren't you tired?
You always make people worry.
Why are you just standing there?
I'm heading home.
I'll drop you off on the way.
That's not necessary.
I'm sorry, President Gu.
Because a lot has happened lately...
Stop, stop.
On this whole ride,
you've already apologized
I don't know how many times.
I'm sorry.
Lin Jiaqi,
is your life
just about saying sorry?
You always say
I'm like a child who won't grow up,
that I don't understand others' feelings,
can't take care of people,
and that I'm annoying.
But at the very least,
I think I live quite happily.
What about you?
If a person acts too much like an adult
and cares too much about others' feelings,
then are you happy yourself?
Every one of us
only has one life.
We must treat it well.
If you dedicate your life
entirely to others,
making everyone else happy,
and making everyone think
that Lin Jiaqi is a great person,
then what about yourself?
How much time do you leave for yourself?
Before, you had Du Zheng
to care for you
and comfort you.
But after Du Zheng left?
I know you just try desperately to bear it,
desperately enduring it.
Lin Jiaqi,
stop pushing yourself so hard, okay?
Du Zheng died on that cold ground
not that long ago.
Why do I feel like
you've forgotten him so quickly?
Do you understand?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'll get going.
Lin Jiaqi.
Silly girl.
You don't have to pretend around me anymore.
You can lean on my shoulder anytime.
If you're sad, just cry it out.
From now on, everything,
I will share the burden with you.