THE POTATO LAB
Oh my!
There we are.
Come out.
Come out before I make you.
Ten.
Nine.
- Eight.
- Oh, gosh.
Holy moly.
I was so focused on cleaning
the floor that I forgot where I was.
By the way, is all that hair
on the floor yours?
You need to be careful
or you might start balding.
No worries. I'm planning on pulling out
my brother's hair for transplants.
Hey, I can also hear you breathing
through your nose, Ms. Lee.
What you just said
is a clear insult against
the 30 million Koreans with rhinitis--
So sue me.
What are you doing?
Did you watch a spy movie?
What is this, an ambush?
How is it possible that you two
are getting more and more childish?
We were just curious, that's all.
Did you make up with Ward B?
If you did, then how?
Was there anywhere…
Anyway.
What did you expect
from a stakeout like this?
Did you think I'd stand here
and deliver a monologue?
Most rom-com leads do that.
Enough already! I'm going to burn
every copy of those dramas…
No, never mind.
I'll let it go.
I'm in too much
of a good mood to get angry.
So just get out of my sight,
if you please.
Why?
What put you in such a good mood?
She was smiling to herself
while looking out the window just now.
There's nothing there.
Jesus…
Oh, Buddha…
Oh, for heaven's sake! Move!
What in the world? Are you serious?
Even if you guys like each other,
you shouldn't be peeking like that!
I know I'm always talking about
risqué things,
but this isn't the way, friend.
No, that's not it. I just…
Just a moment ago, he wasn't…
Why does he walk so fast?
SOFTIE SWEETIE
- Is it him?
- Hey.
Wait. No, hold on.
Can you guys talk to him?
Tell him it was an accident!
What are they called? Oh, right, herons!
Tell him we were watching
a flock of herons pass by.
- Come on!
- Right.
Hey! Where are you going?
God damn it, those demons.
Damn it.
Hi, Baek-ho.
What happened just now
was a misunderstanding.
I wasn't trying to see
you shirtless or anything.
Okay, so I did see a tiny bit,
but it wasn't on purpose at all!
- I--
- It's all right.
At any rate,
you'll see it soon enough, anyway.
What--
Wait.
What?
Sleep well.
Wait, just hold on.
Did you say…
soon enough?
Not "later" or "someday,"
but "soon enough"?
Why?
Why did he say, "soon enough"? Why?
I think I've been bitten
by something lethal.
How could you say something like that…
and expect me to sleep? So Baek-ho!
Oh my gosh!
What do I do?
EPISODE 8
LETHAL
Let's have a toast.
- Drink up!
Oh my gosh, this is so good.
- What is this? Why is this so good?
- It's so good.
- It's amazing.
- Let's take a selfie.
- A selfie?
- One, two, three.
Marry me!
- Is he proposing?
- Someone's proposing.
Oh, wow.
- Say yes. Say yes.
- Oh my gosh, I hope she says yes.
- Say yes!
- She said yes!
- That was wonderful!
- Congratulations!
I'll be right back.
A vodka, please. Neat.
X
MOBILE
Should we just get married?
Excuse me?
Let's get married. You and me.
Here you are.
Well.
Love it! It's great!
Gracias.
Hey, what's going on?
Kim Mi-kyung. So Baek-ho.
Kim Mi-kyung, So Baek…
For heaven's sake.
Why did you style your hair?
We're just eating braised monkfish.
Do you think you'll get noticed?
Do you think you're famous or something?
The owner
is a huge stickler for punctuality.
Because of you, the bean sprouts
are losing their freshness in real time.
Okay, okay.
I apologize for looking fresh.
- Don't talk back to me.
- Put your shoes on.
What is it?
Why are you making that face?
You little--
Why? What's going on?
Come here! Dog Mi-kyung, you traitor!
How could you freaking do this to me?
You promised me first!
You should go with me!
I'm your bestie, your wifey!
So Baek-ho's just a mistress!
You freaking jerk!
What is going on right now?
Just wait until she stops.
She'll wear herself out.
Damn!
Good grief!
Freaking…
Oh, good! Kim, come here.
What's it called, a master key?
Get that for me.
No, we'll just break it down.
Bring the sledgehammer.
You owe me big time!
What are you doing?
- Gosh.
- Hey!
You can't freaking do this to me!
Put me down, you idiot!
Dog Mi-kyung, Dog Hwan-kyung!
You're both freaking dead!
You! Put me down! Whoa!
Are they gone?
Yes.
Did you have a previous engagement?
Gosh.
That's too big of a word for it.
We did make reservations
to eat a large braised monkfish.
You should've told me.
But it's our first time.
It's the first time you've offered
to make something for me.
And it's our first date at home.
This counts as a date, right?
- Yes, it does.
- Okay.
It's not the first time you've seen me
with unwashed hair,
so please bear with me.
So,
what delicacy do you have planned?
Do you like tofu salad?
I'll add in chicken breast.
How much do you have?
Well…
I'm not sure. Hee-jin bought it.
But I'll put in this and that
and some other stuff…
Then throw in everything you have.
Yes, ma'am.
Gosh.
You're really not going to talk all day?
When we get there,
you're not going to happily shout,
"It's so good, so spicy!"
and get all giddy?
Fine.
Let's go back, rip down the door,
and bring Mi-kyung with us.
No! We're already running late.
It won't be good if it's cold.
Then what should we do?
I don't want to see you upset, Honeybun.
You're so adorable when you smile.
I'm not just upset.
I'm feeling bereft of human relationships.
Did I ever stop her
from hanging out with So Baek-ho?
I'm saying there's an order to everything!
Dog Mi-kyung doesn't know jack
about the beauty of friendship.
But are you in a position to say that
about my sister, Honeybun?
Who's the one getting it on
with her best friend's brother
and keeping her mouth shut?
Come on, that's--
I told you not to try
to win an argument with me.
I'm pretty ticked off right now.
- Want a kiss?
- No!
I won't fall
for your physical temptations…
Pull over up there.
Just three kisses and we'll go.
What?
What is that?
What's a car like that
doing in Youngeul-ri?
That license plate is giving off
rude vibes for some reason…
Hey.
- You should get out.
- Right now?
Come on, get out!
Why? What's going on?
Ong-ju!
What are you doing?
What?
Lee Ong-ju!
Oh, man.
You.
So you do value your life?
I thought you came here
because you didn't!
What do you think you're freaking doing?
- Who taught you to drive like that?
- Who freaking taught you to live that way?
You sold off your loyalty,
conscience, and shame
by becoming a mooch
for your wife's rich family!
How dare you try to school me?
Are you a professor
of Introduction to Leeching?
- Is Mi-kyung inside?
- Hey.
Get her name out of your dirty mouth.
Her parents named her that
so she could live a beautiful life.
How dare you use it, you bastard?
You're lower than dog crap!
Watch your language.
You're not some immature--
Hey.
You should be grateful
I'm letting you live.
If I could, I'd break every single one
of your ribs and use them as toothpicks.
But I won't. I don't want Mi-kyung
to suffer while I'm in prison.
- I'll kill you, you filthy bastard!
- Whoa, Ong-ju! Ong-ju!
Whoa! Come on, breathe. Calm down.
Why are you here?
Never mind.
Please leave.
You're not welcome here.
Can you butt out, please?
You don't know anything
about what's going on here!
Then what do you know?
If you knew even a smidgen
of what she went through
after you dumped her,
if you even took a second
to think about it,
you wouldn't dare show
your face like this!
Lee Ong-ju!
Let's be real.
You have no right to say that to me!
You had a part in Mi-kyung and me
breaking up like…
- Hwan-kyung.
- Yeah?
Promise me.
That you'll send balanced meals
in my prison care packages.
What? Ong-ju?
Get the frick over here!
- You jerk!
- Oh, for goodness' sake!
Are you insane? What are you doing?
Hades, Lord of the Underworld!
Today, I'm sending you a soul!
I pray that you will let him burn
for all eternity
in the pits of eternal fire!
Ong-ju, please calm down! Please!
If possible, I would like
to have him quartered once a day
by a four-headed dog,
with each head holding
a limb in its mouth!
- Sorry for the wait.
- No problem.
Damn it. You!
Get the frick over here.
I'm going to pull out all your hair,
make voodoo dolls,
and place them in shrines
all over the damn country!
Oh, there you are!
Hey, over here!
Damn it.
- Ki--
- Ki-se?
God damn.
I'm so angry that it's driving me crazy.
This is why I said
we should buy a crossbow!
If you two hadn't stopped me,
I could've prevented that bastard
from strutting through Pyeongwon.
Oh, I'm so pissed!
Are they super close?
They're not just coworkers?
I don't know.
But he's not the type
to be friendly with just anyone.
It doesn't seem like
they're just coworkers.
So what if they're close?
Just storm in there like he did
and tell him everything
Park Ki-se has done!
Tell him he's the worst bastard ever
and that he should cut him off now!
She can't!
Don't you dare tell him.
Think about it.
If it were you,
do you think you could just date someone
who used to be engaged to your friend
but is now her sworn enemy?
You two just started dating.
This is your honeymoon phase!
Why drag the past into it?
If that bastard runs his mouth,
he'll end up knowing anyway.
It's better for you to come clean first
than to wait anxiously.
He's not going to tell him. How can he?
He's the one who mucked it up,
no matter how you slice it.
And Ki-se's not an idiot. There's no way
he'll blab about it first.
Why are you still nice to him?
Don't you know
what kind of a douche he is?
Just freaking thinking about what happened
makes my damn blood boil.
Guys.
You can stop now.
Stop bringing that up.
Please.
Mi-kyung…
Damn it.
How dare that Park bastard
freaking show up like that?
Damn him!
That son of a…
What is this?
Why does it say Park Ki-se on this?
Just so you know,
that was a slight altercation
with the driver who was behind me.
That's all it was.
There's nothing else to it.
Have a seat.
Would you like something to drink?
No, thanks.
Did I interrupt something?
I would have to say yes.
I didn't think you'd come
all the way here on a weekend morning.
Why does that sound like, "Do you
not have anything better to do?"
I was implying that I'm uncomfortable.
Ki-se.
Let me ask you directly.
Have you been acting strangely
towards me lately…
because of Hee-jin?
What?
Oh, yeah, that's right. It's Hee-jin.
How could you not say anything to me
when you had Hee-jin here the whole time?
You knew I was looking for her everywhere.
What happened is between you two.
I'm just Hee-jin's friend.
I can't be in the middle
and play messenger.
I hope you'll understand.
All right. We'll talk about that later.
Anyway, I guess it's true?
That you're seeing Ms. Kim?
Did you hear from Mr. Lee?
Is that important right now?
It seems like you've put a tail on me
and are getting reports
on everything happening at the lab.
It's not like that.
It's because I'm worried about you.
Wonhan's already chock-full of people
spreading rumors about you.
So how could you
cause a scandal like this?
I can't believe you're dating
a subordinate you're planning to fire.
Do you realize you're creating
your own Achilles heel?
This is going to follow you around
throughout your career!
I've considered every aspect.
And it doesn't matter anymore.
I'm serious about her.
- What?
- Thank you for worrying about me,
but I'd ask you not to go beyond that.
If you do, I think it would
definitely feel like interference.
How… how serious, exactly?
Are you…
You're really taking things
seriously with Ms. Kim?
You can't be talking about
marriage already.
Ki-se.
Can I give you a word of advice?
Pick up a hobby.
Something you can spend your energy on.
INCOMING CALL
SOFTIE SWEETIE
Man…
- Hello?
- I'm sorry, Mi-kyung.
That was a long wait.
I'll have the food ready soon.
Well…
Actually, it's fine. I have…
something urgent to review right now.
So I need to get this done first.
Then I'll bring the food to you.
No, it's all right.
What was it…
You know Oheung-ri?
The Crop Team at Oheung-ri also called,
so I have to head over there.
I don't think I can make it today.
Goodness, I'm so busy right now.
Oh, I see.
Don't tire yourself out too much.
Then what about later?
Maybe at dinner, I can…
Honeybun, are you still mad at me?
I was so mad that I ended up
raising my voice at you as well.
I'm very, very sorry.
I have an order. I'm busy.
Okay.
I mean, why did you have to nitpick
about something like that?
I may be lax about many things,
but manners are not one of them.
Why? As a 14-year-old in puberty,
I yelled at Mi-kyung once
and got beat up with a washcloth--
Gosh, how many times are you
going to bring that up?
- Let it go.
- How can I?
You helped her beat me up
with a shampoo bottle!
Back then, you were smaller than me.
When did you grow up to become
such a big cutie?
Don't treat me like a kid.
By the next year, I was taller than you.
Let's get it over with.
I bought a new brand of highballs
because I've heard they're good.
I can't wait to let my lips touch them
and feel them course down my throat.
Regarding what Ki-se said earlier…
What did he mean by that?
What?
When he said you had a hand
in their breakup.
I can't stop thinking about it.
It's all bullshit.
I was just…
always on Mi-kyung's side.
You know what?
Kiss time! Let's go!
Wait, be careful! This is going to spill!
I can't freaking believe it.
That jerk,
telling me I need to get a hobby.
I have a ton of things to do!
And it doesn't matter anymore.
I'm serious about her.
Is Mi-kyung serious about him, too?
Whoa.
Oh, no. Myungsu. Myungsu!
Oh, no. Oh, no, what do I do?
Oh, my goodness. What do I do?
Oh, my goodness. Myungsu.
Myungsu!
- Ah, ah.
- What?
To all Youngeul-ri residents.
This is an emergency announcement.
Man.
Did you hear?
Myungsu ran away from home again.
What is wrong with him?
He needs to learn
how scary it is out there.
It's a phase, you know that.
I'll get the flashlight.
Oh, dear.
Goodness.
We'll find him soon.
She had dinner.
Yes, she found out then.
This is crazy.
Oh, gosh!
You're all here!
Of course! It's for Ms. Hong.
How long has he been gone?
Well, the specifics will be
given to us by Mr. Byun in a bit.
- Grab some water first.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Take a lot, okay?
Mi-kyung!
Wait, why is he…
What's happening right now?
Are you okay?
You look like the one who's not okay.
What is all this? Are you seeking asylum?
Oh, this?
This is my emergency survival kit.
I thought this was an emergency--
Did you not hear the announcement?
Ms. Hong's baby ran away from home,
so we're going to go find him.
Did you only hear "emergency"
and rushed to pack
before running out here?
Is he a genius or a dummy?
Come on. It just means
he's got great survival skills.
Come closer.
To all Youngeul-ri residents,
thank you so much
for gathering at such a late hour.
As I said before,
Ms. Hong's youngest
has run away from home.
To speed up the search,
I'll relay the information
about the missing kid.
Name, Hong Myungsu.
Born in January 2023.
What does this say?
Here.
How does a one-year-old
run away from home?
Weight, 150 kg.
On the slim side.
Myungsu is a calf.
- Did you not know?
- What?
Wait,
then the whole village is out here
because of an animal--
Be quiet.
Do you want them to close the road again?
He gets frightened easily
and is very wary of strangers.
Please call the village hall
the moment you find him
so that Myungsu can safely
come back home.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Yes! That was great, Mr. Byun!
- Hey!
- Come with me.
All right, let's go find him.
Myungsu!
Please search thoroughly.
- Myungsu!
Hurry up, let's go find him.
- Oh, my Myungsu.
- Where are you, Myungsu?
Since we've decided to search
near the house first,
- Ong-ju and I will go right--
- Oh, who are you?
You look awfully similar to my ex-spouse
who abandoned her wifey
for her mistress.
I knew you'd still be holding a grudge.
Fine, then it's me and Hwan-kyung.
You and I walking together
under the moonlight?
I don't know about that.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Oh, those little…
Do you have a flashlight?
How many lumens?
Myungsu.
- Myungsu.
My goodness. Myungsu.
Myungsu.
- Where are you, Myungsu?
- Where could you be?
Myungsu.
Wow, there are so many stars.
Oh! You're right.
Hey! What the heck?
Be careful.
Oh, my goodness. What is this?
Did you get this from a baseball stadium?
This high-performance searchlight
can go up to 25,000 lumens
and go as far as 550 meters.
It's from overseas.
Why do you even have this?
Because it's useful
in multiple situations. For example,
I could signal my location
if I get lost in the mountains.
This isn't just a signal.
This is basically the sun.
You'll have everyone in Gangwon-do
up and ready for work with that.
Do you not have anything normal
that a normal person might use?
How can you be so thorough all the time?
Isn't it exhausting to prepare
for every single possibility?
It's an old habit.
I was my own guardian for a long time,
so I had to prepare myself for anything
so I wouldn't be afraid.
Even then, life isn't
any kinder to you.
Being alone so much
must have been scary for young Baek-ho.
For a bit. Not anymore.
Why? Because you're all grown now?
I realized
that sometimes, a variable I can't predict
or control…
could bring me joy.
Gosh.
So… about yesterday.
I know. You were avoiding me on purpose.
What?
How did you know?
You said you were going to Oheung-ri
but spent half the day napping
with the curtains wide open.
Wow.
Wow, dating my neighbor is so scary.
I can't deny anything or run away.
Aren't you…
going to ask why?
The Kim Mi-kyung I know
gets angry when she's angry
and makes it clear when she's upset.
But if it's neither of those,
it means there's a reason why
you don't want to tell me.
So I didn't ask.
And I'm not going to ask now.
Baek-ho.
To be honest, years ago…
Myungsu?
Oh! Myungsu!
Wait, Mi-kyung.
Mr. Byun said he scares easily.
So let's be quiet
and move as little as possible.
- Okay?
- Yes, of course.
I'll make the call first.
Myungsu.
You remember me, right?
When you hit 100 kilograms
and we threw a party,
I bought you straw, remember?
Hey!
No, wait, Baek-ho!
Hello? Mr. Byun?
Yes, the path on the left
of Mr. Yang's lettuce field.
He went up toward the mountain.
Yes!
Why did you run off after him like that?
What were you going to do alone?
There's a highway entrance
just 300 meters to the right.
It would be bad if he got on the highway,
so I decided to appease him
as quickly as I could.
Wow. You made a plan that fast?
He could've picked
a better place to run off to.
Did you call them?
Yes, but it'll take them time to get here
since we're in the mountains.
I hope he stays put until then.
Oh, man, I bet Hong Myungsu
was a meerkat in his past life.
He's so jumpy and alert.
- Mi-kyung.
- Yes?
Do you know why goats climb cliffs?
That's what you want to ask me right now?
Sodium is an essential mineral
in our daily lives,
but herbivores rarely have
the opportunity to ingest it.
That's right, since grass
and grains don't contain sodium.
That's the reason why goats climb cliffs,
risking their lives.
They're trying to find rock salt to lick.
Similarly, there are herds of elephants
that dig through
cave walls for salt water.
Right. I got your point.
Herbivores are obsessed
with getting their sodium intake.
But why is that important right now?
If that's the case…
wouldn't it apply to cows as well?
I mean, yes…
Wait.
No way.
MYUNG-SU'S HOUSE
Ms. Hong!
Oh my! Oh my goodness.
Myungsu.
Oh, Myungsu!
- Ms. Hong, it's Myungsu.
- Oh my goodness.
Myungsu! Myungsu, my dear.
My goodness, you silly thing.
Where did you go?
I really thought I lost you
for good this time.
He went all the way up
that mountain there,
but Seoul Guy here
lured him with some salt
and brought him back.
I never would've imagined
that you'd know such things.
Gosh.
It's amazing what you did,
and I can't thank you enough.
My goodness, my dear Myungsu.
Wait, what…
what is this supposed to be?
What is this black thing?
It's a mini tracking device
for professional use.
It sends coordinates every 3.7 seconds
- and the receiver speed--
- Well…
It's a location tracker, Ms. Hong.
If Myungsu runs away from home again,
his location will pop up on my phone.
We'll be able to find him
and bring him back.
How can I ever repay you?
Goodness me.
- My dear Myungsu.
- Yes, that's good.
Goodness me, thank you.
Oh my goodness.
Gosh.
At any rate, Mr. Seoul Guy,
you were a bit aggressive
at the beginning,
but now that I've gotten to known you,
you're the real deal.
If Chang-sook was just 20 years younger,
I would have set you up with her.
Gosh.
Oh, what a shame!
It's just too bad
that turning back time is impossible.
- That's true.
- You must be exhausted.
You should get home
and get some rest, Mr. Byun.
Sure. Take care.
Whew.
Who's Chang-sook?
It's his younger sister.
She recently got divorced again
and is now on the search
for her third or fourth husband.
If Mr. Byun says he'll buy you food,
do not go with him.
That's a blind date.
I'll go eat,
then say I like someone else and run out.
How's that?
Oh, shucks.
Is that what happened? My sweetie.
My little sweetie.
My dear Myungsu.
He's not just livestock to her, right?
You're right.
The truth is, Ms. Hong
was diagnosed
with stage 2 dementia last year.
There was a whole ruckus over whether
to place her in a senior care center
or have one of her kids take care of her.
But then one day, she suddenly
brought home a calf from the market.
She basically declared
that she doesn't want to lie in bed
waiting to die, but to keep living
as she always did, at her home.
Since then,
Myungsu has become like a son to her.
You need to change the batteries
about every 210 days.
Make sure to check it on time.
Okay. Seven months?
Man, I'm not sure.
I might be exhausted
from job hunting by then
and be roaming the East Sea
on a fishing boat.
Speaking of which,
I should go search for jobs.
Wait.
Mi-kyung, wait.
Come on, don't be like that.
Goodness me.
I knew these two would slip out
in the middle of everything.
Jeez.
Hey, you lazy bums!
I was roaming the mountain and fields,
sweating my butt off
in order to uphold
our guesthouse's honor--
Mi-kyung, wait!
Some owner you are!
Whoa.
No way.
No freaking way.
Ong-ju. Ong-ju.
This is one for the books!
Hey, it's on right now!
Hwan-kyung's brought a girl home!
Hurry up, get out here!
What in the world are you doing?
What?
Where did she dash off to now?
She needs to see this!
Wait a second.
What?
Where is it?
It's here. I found it.
Hey, Mi-kyung.
Right now, I'm…
You two…
Why…
Why are you two…
Are you two…
Are you okay?
Do you want some hot water?
Do you think I'm okay?
Is that even a question?
Is it?
Do you think I'm okay right now?
You two…
Wait. I can't even…
The two of you?
Am I dreaming?
How?
You're Kim Hwan-kyung.
You're Lee Ong-ju.
You two…
you're family.
Wait a second, isn't there a legal…
Is this right?
Is this allowed in civilized society?
Aren't you afraid of what people will say?
Just because we live together
doesn't mean we're actually family.
We aren't even related--
"We"?
Did you just refer to yourselves
as "we" in front of me? "We"?
Don't yell at Ong-ju.
- It's not her fault. It was all--
- Why is it not her fault?
You.
I can't believe
that you actually did this!
It's okay for him!
We'll say he's a child
who can't tell right from wrong.
But you can! How could you?
Just because there aren't any men around
is not an excuse to get with Hwan-kyung!
Hey.
If you get hungry on the road,
do you pick up animal poop and eat it?
No!
We're intelligent adults.
But with him? How could you--
Hey! There's nothing wrong with him.
You may not know it,
but he's not a bad boyfriend.
Damn it! Stop talking!
This is disgusting. So disgusting.
So every time I wasn't here, you two…
I can't eat anything now.
I can't sleep.
I'm afraid of dreaming about you.
Oh, this is freaking gross!
I can't live here anymore.
What?
- Come on, Mi-kyung.
- No!
Hey, Mi-kyung!
Oh, man.
Can you give this to my sister?
Tell her it's some necessities.
Why are you giving this to me?
Is she not inside?
Her car's still here,
so I thought she came to you.
Hwan-kyung. Is something wrong?
Angry when you get bitten…
Wrong!
Angry when you get bitten. Keep going.
It seems like…
I have a knack for searching.
I found two runaways in one day.
Gosh.
You scared me.
How did you know I left?
Did Hwan-kyung tell on me?
Actually, he asked me to give this to you.
He said he packed
what you need for tomorrow,
like a blouse, laptop, your bag,
and other necessities
since we're going to Headquarters.
If he cares enough for me to do this,
he shouldn't have done that
behind my back.
Are you that upset?
This can't simply be described
as being upset.
I mean, think about it.
Hwan-kyung is my baby brother.
Ong-ju is like my twin sister.
The three of us
basically grew up together.
Since Hwan-kyung was a baby, we saw him
when he learned how to write,
got his first pimple,
got dumped by his first love
and bawled his eyes out.
Gosh.
So how could they like each other?
Siblings can't do that.
They need to be arrested.
I see.
They may be siblings and family to you,
but perhaps they didn't feel
that way toward each other.
I'm worried that it's not even that deep.
They open the bathroom door
while one of them is using it
to call for more toilet paper.
One time,
I saw them drinking beer together
and having a burping contest.
There was no room
for any feelings to grow.
Both of them are just lonely and bored,
and they just happen
to be around each other.
So they're playing with fire
to sate their hunger.
They're out of their minds.
Still, wouldn't it be better
if you let them explain?
Hwan-kyung looked like
he had a lot to say.
I don't want to hear this anymore.
Just thinking about it makes me furious.
I can't look at them.
I can't erase the image from my mind.
So you won't go home either?
How can I?
I don't want to see anything else.
You seem to be still in shock,
so take all the time
you need to calm down.
But…
I can't let you sleep here alone.
What do you mean?
That I'm joining you.
And running away from home.
Oh, gosh. Baek-ho.
Thank you for being such a softie sweetie.
I really am grateful.
But right now, I don't think
there's anything that would help--
I'm not being soft or sweet.
I'm making a move.
Do you not want me to?
Do you?
TRYING TO JUSTIFY THE FACT
THAT JUST 20 MINUTES AGO
SHE WAS CONDEMNING HER BEST FRIEND
AND BROTHER'S RELATIONSHIP AS LUST
BUT IS NOW AT A HOTEL
ENTICED BY HER SITUATIONSHIP
All right. Okay.
Damn it.
I should've bought some bras
when Ong-ju told me to.
Damn it.
It doesn't matter now.
How do you get the mood going again?
Here.
Oh, okay…
Should…
I…
wash… wash up?
If you'd like.
Right. Then…
I'll be off now.
What?
Wait a second.
You said we'll be runaways together.
Then aren't you also staying…
No?
Oh, I see.
That was to lure you.
Like how I used salt with the calf,
I used So Baek-ho with Kim Mi-kyung.
What?
Why?
The rest area is hot, stuffy,
and uncomfortable,
but you insisted on not returning home.
But if I said I'd book you a hotel room,
you wouldn't have come so willingly.
Why are you--
why are you treating me like an animal?
I'm very emotionally vulnerable right now.
I'm not in the mood to play games
or have my heart toyed with.
Were you hoping for something--
I wasn't hoping…
Jeez.
Forget it. Just go.
If I throw another fit,
I think I might blow
a blood vessel somewhere.
Just go. Go.
Not tonight.
Because I know
you're emotionally vulnerable.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't trying to play games
or toy with your heart.
Okay?
Can I order room service?
Yes.
I'm going to order enough
for three people.
Are you going to pick me up
tomorrow morning?
Yes.
Try luring me again
like this next time, I'll--
You won't have time
to get angry next time.
Get some sleep.
Call me when you wake up. Okay?
Yeah…
okay.
I'll be going now.
He's so lethal.
He's such a pro at this. Oh my gosh.
INCOMING CALL
YOON HEE-JIN - MOBILE
Hello?
It's me, Hee-jin.
I was just thinking of you.
It's…
our wedding anniversary tomorrow.
Where are you right now?
This way.
- Hello, Mr. Park.
- Hello!
Where's Mr. Bu?
He went out to the self-irrigated fields.
May I ask who you're with?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Section Chief Lee Seung-hoon from
Wonhan Retail's Strategic Planning Dept.
Oh, I see.
Hello, I'm Lee Chung-hyeon.
I'm Kwon Hee-dong.
Hello. I'm Section Chief Ko Jung-hae.
- Thank you for all you do.
- Thank you.
Well…
I think right here should be good.
Oh, sure. Yes.
It seems nice. You have the A/C there.
Let's see…
Could you give me a hand here?
- Excuse me?
- We'll put Mr. Lee's desk here.
His desk? In our office?
OMG RIGHT NOW
Could I get a cup of coffee, please?
Black.
Me?
Is there…
anyone else here?
Oh!
My firm skin must have made you think
I was one of the younger employees.
I'm Section Chief Ko Jung-hae.
Section Chief Lee.
- Yes?
- Yes.
I am well aware.
Section Chief Ko Jung-hae.
He knows, yet he still…
Oh, you must not know
where the break room is.
Right. So here's
where we have our break room.
I don't have much time to spare
juggling work from Headquarters and here.
You wouldn't happen
to have an ice maker, would you?
Then I'll have a hot coffee.
- Oh, Director Kim.
- Wow.
Yes. How have you been?
Gosh, I'm actually in Pyeongwon right now.
Of course, I would love to help…
Ms. Ju, this way.
What's going on?
Why can't I go to the office?
Mr. Ko! What's wrong with you?
- He was ordered to make coffee.
- What?
Do you know anything, Ms. Ju?
About the Strategic Planning Dept.
Section Chief and why he's here.
We have another one?
Here? At Potato Lab?
He's even got a desk in our office.
The Production Dept. said
they had no space.
Gosh, he lied through his teeth.
Chief So downsized that whole team,
so all they have are empty desks.
They tossed him to us
because they're uncomfortable.
Damn Park, that traitor.
Wait, he didn't even say
what he's doing here
or how long he's staying?
He just arrived and settled in?
Yes, he barged in
and said, "Clean that up and make space."
Then he said, "Make a cup of coffee--"
It's all right. It's all good.
Can't you just tell him to go work
somewhere else, Mr. Bu?
You rank higher than he does.
Hey, Hee-dong.
Even Mr. Bu can't say anything to him.
Why not?
If you look at the organization chart,
the Strategic Planning Department
is right next to the Chairman's Office.
And Potato Lab is two levels under R&D,
which is under F&B,
which is under Food.
We're shoved in a corner.
You didn't have to point that out--
That's why I don't get this at all.
Is there a crude oil deposit
hidden underneath our lab?
Why are they coming here and meddling?
Mr. Bu. What did Chief So say?
He went to Headquarters
with Ms. Kim today.
At any rate, be careful of what you say
in the office, all right?
I'll look into how this happened.
What?
What does this mean?
They're saying someone
from the Strategic Planning Dept.
has taken a desk
in the Research Team's office.
Oh, that. Well…
Headquarters sent someone
to help me with my work.
I'll be sending him back soon.
Wonhan sure does work strangely.
Like that Park Ki-se…
I mean, Executive Director Park.
What are you all coming to Pyeongwon for?
Your department must not be too busy.
But I bet your pay is super high.
Man, I would've given him a super
uncomfortable welcome if I were there.
Let's go.
Let's go outside and talk.
Okay.
Give me a hug.
Hug me.
Right now.
What are you playing at--
Hee-jin?
WEDDING INVITATION
GROOM PARK KI-SE, BRIDE YOON HEE-JIN
- Come in, come in.
- Yes.
The weather's wonderful today.
This place is beautiful.
You don't have to buy me a meal.
I wasn't much help at all.
No, don't say that.
Knowing how much
you contributed to Youngeul-ri,
I should've treated you
a dozen times over already.
Here we are.
- Go on in.
- Oh, okay.
Who is…
Oh, this is…
the most beautiful woman
Youngeul-ri produced.
Byun Chang-sook.
Hello, I'm Byun Chang-sook.
And this is the person I told you about.
Mr. Kim Hwan-kyung.
Oh, right.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, yes. Nice to meet you too.
- Yes, have a seat.
- Thank you, brother.
I remember now.
- Yoon Hee-jin.
- Baek-ho!
When I think about it,
I was happiest six years ago.
Mi-kyung.
When I notice you're lying,
I'm supposed to act like I don't, right?
Ong-ju ran away.
We have to sneak Ong-ju out
as quietly as possible.
Someone stop her.
Stop her.
No! I mean…
Are you… my boyfriend?
I never agreed to that.
Subtitle translation by Grace Kim