Have you been taking your medication?
I threw them up.
Why are you punishing yourself like that?
Because my mom cherishes me the most.
If something you cherish becomes ruined, it's painful.
Miss Hwang Bo Young, if you continue like this
not only will your body suffer from extreme nutrient and hormonal deficiency,
your brain could become damaged as well.
If you want to punish your mother,
what about we look for alternative methods?
Is there a CCTV in here?
No, there isn't. You can speak comfortably.
I...
Did you just sexually assault me? I can post this on social media.
- Miss Hwang Bo Young!
- Tell my mom
that she doesn't need to keep sending me to the hospital.
I really don't like coming here. I hate it!
Sexual assault?
She says she's done whatever her mother told her to do for 25 years.
What to eat, what to wear, everything. She went to the college her mother wanted her to go to.
That all built up until it exploded, in the form of self-abuse.
I think that patient needs psychological treatment first.
Endorphins increase a lot in anorexic patients.
They're people who are happier starving rather than eating.
My theory is that the lack of 'happy hormones'
is being revitalized in a paradoxical way through starvation.
That's an interesting theory.
It's a theory that can help figure out why people become addicted to starving themselves.
So you want to try rebalancing the hormonal levels of this patient with medication?
Yes, and then psychological treatment follows after.
I'm looking forward to it.
I heard the source of the pica patient's condition is due to a fear of his father?
I think this approach may help that patient as well.
I went to see my dad early this morning.
I realized for the first time today that his back was so small.
On my way back, I kept thinking,
"How did my dad become that way?"
"We all become weak as we grow old."
I wonder why I ran away so much from my father.
I don't know what kind of story patient Sung has,
but wouldn't figuring that out solve it?
Doctor, Sung Min Ho just cancelled his treatment session for today.
With whose permission?
The menu here is to die for; it looks really good.
Is it always this way?
Doctor,
why are you here?
Are you surprised? Seeing how you're stuttering.
Since you cancelled today's treatment session, I thought you must be busy, so I came here myself.
Sometimes changing the location like this is good for a change of atmosphere and can be helpful also.
Go ahead and eat, you must be hungry.
I feel good. I'm full, and the weather is nice too.
By the way, how tall is your dad?
Why?
I guess you don't know.
Then, what about his shoe size?
You must not be close with your dad, since you seem to know nothing about him.
Is my dad a friend that I should be friendly with him?
I should respect him.
Let's start by fixing your stammering.
This wasn't the first time you ate paper, is it? When was the first?
Why are you being this way to me?
Because I want to treat you.
- Why?
- Because I'm a doctor and you're my patient.
I know how hard you tried to fix it.
You've probably been to the hospital and probably practiced  looking at the mirror every day.
You told me last time that you didn't want to chew on the house.
I understand that feeling.
At one point, I feared my dad the most in the world.
Trust in me this once.
Can y-you r-really f-fix me?
Are you still angry?
No. I was just about to go help you.
That's fine. You know the musical "Cinderella," right?
The music director is a senior from my school.
I talked about you, and he said he'd like to work with you.
- Really?
- He said it's not really a big role.
Hey! What— How come you didn't tell me you had these kinds of connections before?
Thank you, I really won't forget this favor.
Are you that happy?
♪ How I grew up, no, no ♪
♪ I sigh as I breathe... ♪
♪ Where is your love? ♪
♪ Don't forget your fate ♪
♪ Waiting for your prince on a white horse... ♪
♪ White horse ♪
♪ Waiting for your first love... ♪
♪ Let's all go! ♪
♪ Dance time! ♪
♪ This is your destiny ♪
Okay, let's take a 10-minute break.
Thank you.
You've all improved.
Hello.
Miss Han Woo Joo, I heard about you from Ji Sun.
It's an ensemble, will that really be okay for you?
Of course. I can do whatever you tell me to do.
I'm sure your skills are great, judging from how you won the rookie of the year award.
You can practice right away, right?
Thank you. Thank you.
You should thank Ji Sun.
She begged me, even saying she would pay for  our team's dinner, so I said okay.
What?
You didn't know?
Oh you must have really not known.
Oh then,
you are hiring me because Ji Sun said she would buy you all a meal?
Well, we're just being of mutual assistance to each other.
Excuse me, I can't do it this way.
I will not do it.
Even though I was a national embarrassment
and was fired from projects,
it wasn't to the extent of being sold out for a free meal.
What do you want?
I just barely convinced the director.
Anyway, I'm not doing it.
You're failing every audition, and you still can't grasp the situation you're in?
I'm saying I won't do this because I do understand my situation!
(T/N: informal speech.)
Just as the rumors said you are really a big freak.
Look here, do you think you're failing auditions because of drunk driving?
Not at all! It's because you are such a crazy b*tch!
- Do you know the rumors have spread in this field?!
- Ahhhhhhh!
It seemed like I was someone else.
In the mirror,  there was someone I saw for the first time.
Why could I have suddenly felt that way?
Maybe you wanted to deny it, the Han Woo Joo you've been lately.
I didn't know
that I made people so uncomfortable.
When they get angry, I always apologized first.
Even though I did nothing wrong.
Then they all told me it was fine,
but I guess it wasn't.
No matter how small a wound, it doesn't always heal that easily.
I must really be a crazy b*tch.
Doctor, I'm going to leave this field for the time being.
Do you have plans on what you will do?
Someone recommended a part-time job to me.
What part-time job is it?
- What are you doing here?
-  Oh my.
Perhaps are you here to meet me?
Yes.
Let's go in.
Have you decided?
On what?
- Didn't you come to get treatment?
- No.
Then?
I came because I was wondering if I could do the part-time job you suggested the last time.
You called it... theatrical treatment, right?
Yes, that's correct. Theatrical treatment.
I sometimes get reminded of acting in front of Mr. Cha Dong Il.
It strangely made me feel good.
I would like to do it. Can't I?
This works out so well.
I was worried. You are my savior.
Really? That's a relief.
These are documents on theatrical therapy. You can start immediately, right?
Of course.
What's wrong with treating their team to a few meals?
Are you running a charity?
That's your specialty.
Didn't you think of my pride?
I thought  you standing on the stage was a priority.
Pride is something you can protect once you're standing on stage.
I'll accept your thoughtfulness thankfully.
But I'm not going to look that way for the time being.
What are you talking about?
I agreed to work part-time at the hospital.
What work can you do part-time at a hospital?
Theatrical therapy.
What is that?
Sick people have something called "trauma" and  the job is about  finding  their trauma through theater.
I'm having a really rough time.
Is this the time to be doing this here?
You've worked hard.
Well done.
Hug me.
Don't say that, won't it get better on its own?
Be quiet and let me be! I'll live how I want!
How dare you speak to your mother that way, you little punk! Do you want to die?
You're going to college?
I told you that I can't send you to college, didn't I? I don't have the money to send you to college, also.
Do you think I'm made of money?
You're not going to some law school like your older brother.
If you just act a bit smarter,
you can make a living for yourself like I did, even without going to college.
How could someone like you go to college?
Hey! If I had the money to send you to college, I would rather buy your older brother an extra steak!
Stop thinking about useless things and get a hold of yourself!
Min Ho, you have something you want to say. Don't hold it in and say it.
What kind of person is "someone like me"?
Are you asking because you don't know? Gosh, this worthless punk.
If I was able to raise you this well without your mother,
you should be grateful and try to live a bit more properly.
Is there even one thing that you can do properly?
Do you have any interest in what I'm good at?
Dad, I''m also a person.
I'm a person.
I'm also your son!
That's right, you're also his son. You have something you want to say to your father, right? Go on, say it.
Why do you only look at my brother? Why don't you see me?
I'm not a ghost. Stop making a fool of me like I'm not there.
You have to be more concrete. Your father doesn't understand you.
When I was 12, you didn't know that I ran away because I felt so lonely, did you?
I thought you would come looking for me.
After struggling out on the streets for a week,
I went back home because I couldn't stand it anymore. But you...
You didn't even know I ran away.
You just took my brother out to eat because he had come home with an award.
I was so hungry... but I had nothing to eat...
so I ate tissue papers with water.
"Let's eat this and die."  I ate it thinking that!!
People who hurt others are typically not strangers.
A family member, significant other, or friend. They are those who are the closest to you.
Doctor, hello.
Han Woo Joo, you really did well today.
I'll be heading out.
Doctor, we are going to get a drink, would you like to join us?
Next time.
Alright.
There are approximately 100 billion neurons inside a person's brain.
The neurotransmitters that are released from these neurons influence our state of consciousness.
When we are stressed, adrenaline is released.
Oxytocin strengthens relationships with others.
Thank you.
- Shall we do a cheers?
- Sounds good.
- Good work, everyone!
- Good work!
Dopamine excites us, and GABA calms us down.
Hello.
What I wonder at this point,
is where these neurotransmitters come from?
They come from the mind.
But where exactly is the mind?
In Anglo-Saxon times, they believed the mind could be in the brain,
in the diaphragm, or in between your ribs.
Judging from the phrase 'My heart broke', I guess they could have thought it was in the heart as well.
Greek philosophers believed that the mind was not matter, thus did not exist in the body as flesh and blood.
Thus, they said the mind did not die along with your body.
I agree with the Greek philosophers.
Thus, the mind lasts forever,
and I am the fixer.
I'm sorry I called you so suddenly.
I was thinking of calling a substitute driver but since I also have something to tell you...
It worked out fine, we are going in the same direction after all.
You know Hwang Bo Young, right? She's a patient of yours.
Is she someone you know?
She's practically family with our hospital.
- Oh you didn't know.
- Yes.
How's the treatment going?
It seems she wasn't taking the drugs prescribed to her, so we're not seeing any effects.
Shouldn't anorexia first be treated psychologically, instead of with medication?
I am changing my approach.
Anorexia is incurable. You know that, right?
I know that.
I think anorexia... should be solved using Lee Si Joon's methods.
I'm sure you'll be able to do well yourself,
but family members always find the smallest things upsetting.
Of course I trust you. You know that, right?
Yes, I understand.
Yes.
Right, about the meeting of patients with eating disorders,
I heard there is one today.
Can you find out if patient Hwang Bo Young can participate in that?
Yes, I'll do that.
Okay.
What is it?
Why is he suddenly interested in theatrical therapy?
Let's go in.
Do we really have to meet my father?
You said you have something to say to him. You should tell him in person.
Psychiatry? You must be rich. Do you have money to waste?
Min Ho has something he really wants to say to you.
Listen.
If you have something to say, say it quickly, I'm busy.
Min Ho.
Dad, when I was 10 years old,
you woke me up during my sleep to scold me.
You asked me why I stole money from your wallet.
Even though I kept saying I didn't, you said I should not lie.
It really wasn't me.
I didn't steal the money.
You crazy punk.
You came all the way to say that?
How long ago was that?
Because I feel wronged.
That's been stuck right here,
all this time.
I say I feel wronged!
This pathetic punk.
Your brother confessed that he was the one who stole it.
Just how old are you that you're holding on to that?
That's why you are in this state.
Whether it's back then or now, just when will you become a person?
Doctor,
I didn't think my dad would be using things like dentures.
You really had no idea?
I couldn't even imagine.
All the dads in the world
slowly get smaller backs, whiter hairs,
and their teeth start to fall out.
Your dad is also not your dad from back then.
I won't tell you to understand your dad.
This is the beginning of the treatment.
Starting from finding your lost self-esteem.
Before we start to talk,  let's close our eyes for a couple seconds,
and feel the air in this space.
Han Woo Joo is also here.
She must be here to help out.
That's fun.
Alright, please open your eyes.
Everyone's face seems a shade brighter.
Then, shall we begin?
I... have anorexia nervosa.
I'm a model but  I've been cursed with a body that tends to gain weight by just drinking water.
It started out with a fear of not being able to stand on stage because of my weight,
but now I feel fear even when I look at food.
Adding weight by just drinking water is  just all crap.
If that were true, why would there be food scarcity in Africa?
They can gain weight by drinking water.
Thank you for sharing.
Next.
I'm a job seeker getting treatment for bulimia.
I think I must've submitted over 100 applications by now.
I developed a habit of overeating.
Once I grab my spoon, I can't put it down.
When I see food, I want to just put it all in my mouth and eat it.
If you don't lose weight, you'll probably be unable to get employed forever.
What are you— saying?
The both of you, thanks for being courageous.
Shall we all applaud?
What about you?
Anorexia.
I eat, then throw up. Eat, then throw up.
Why are you doing that?
My mom treats me like a doll.
But I'm not a doll.
In order to show my mother I am not her doll,
I just throw it all up in front of her.
Agonizing my mom is my goal.
You're really spoiled.
- What did you say?
- You don't even know how precious that is.
You said agonizing your mom is your goal?
What do you know about me? I was abused!
That's immature of you.
- Doctor, I think they're going to fight.
-  There are people who live without something like that forever.
Shouldn't we stop them?
There are tons of people in the world who float around this world like a speck of dust,
just trying to be noticed and be cared for.
That's why you shouldn't do anything you'll end up regretting,
and live properly with gratitude.
Alright, shall we all applaud now?
Woo Joo, are you already finished?
I was on my way to go take a look.
I guess I'm late. How was it today?
What is it, did something happen?
I'm sorry, I ruined it all.
Huh?
I don't think I'll be able to keep doing this. I'm sorry.
There are people who have to live that way forever!
Welcome.
Please give me one chicken.
Are you going to keep coming here?
I still haven't been able to find a chicken place as tasty as yours.
I'm someone who adopted and then ditched you.
Why do you keep coming here? There's nothing good to be gained from us seeing each other.
Are you doing that on purpose to make me uncomfortable?
From when I was 6 until I was 12,
you raised me for 6 years.
I want to see you sometimes, Mom.
Who are you calling Mom?
Mom,
about that time back then,
I'm really sorry.
Stop it. I've been so busy trying to survive, so I've forgotten things of the past.
Eat and leave.
♪  Would it be better just to smile and pretend I'm okay?  ♪
♪  Would that protect me from this world...  ♪
Ms. Woo Joo, what are you doing here?
How did you come here?
If I don't say it now, I will never be able to. That's why I came.
♫  Goodbye, the memories I want to forget  ♫
What you said was right.
I'm a patient.
Please treat me.
You can treat me, right?
♫   Will I finally be able to erase it?  ♫
♫  I'm fine. I'm so fine   ♫
♫  Stay by my side just like this  ♫
Miss Woo Joo, you are someone who will change the lives of others.
Ru... Ru Oh!
Transfer Park Ru Oh to Dong Hyuk's care.
- He's my patient.
- You ignore every protocol.
What's the reason you're so attached to all your patients?
Wha-What... Wait!
Why are you still wearing the watch I gave you?
What will you do if Han Woo Joo has borderline personality disorder?
Starting now, we will start the search.
You don't have any idea why they brought a search warrant?
Someone must have planned this.
Do you want it to be buried, scattered, or cremated?
What?