Oh my, you scared me.
What are you doing here?
Did you come to see me?
- Well, technically not that but...
- Ah...
Because you were worried?
I'm not worried. Why would I be worried? You didn't do anything wrong.
Well, you could worry a little.
You see, that thing called worry,
the more you worry, the more it piles up. So it's better to not do it in the first place.
On a day like today, if you consider this and that, I thought you might find things complicating.
I felt you might need this.
If there's someone you want to curse at, do it here instead of holding it in.
Well then, I'm off to collect my watch.
- Strike two.
- Excuse me?
After I become the Hospital's Director, there is something I decided.
Whatever situation arises, let it go three times.
Whatever the wrong, forgive it three times max.
Because a Hospital Director should be a little generous and use benevolent speech.
However, Doctor Lee, you have two strikes. What do you want to do?
I'm sorry about the foregoing investigation. I will take responsibility for it.
Responsibility? Are you going to take off your doctor's coat?
No, not that.
Then are you going to use the 'Chief Park card' this time also?
It has no connection with Chief Park.
Then what does it have to do with me?
Thanks to you, the person who has to be investigated is me as the Hospital's Director.
You?
Look at this. I see you have zero knowledge of the law.
But like I said earlier, I will let it go up till this point.
Because I'm the Hospital Director.
But the next time is strike three. You know very well what happens then without me saying it, don't you?
I was also reported when I opened the hospital.
By whom?
The neighbors sued me. Saying that the hospital made them anxious and made the neighborhood  ambience gloomy.
Talking nonsense about psychiatric clinics being bad for the public health or something...
That darned punk. I still get mad thinking about that.
Hey, she must have been so angered.
I sued him right back and made him crawl out of there.
You did well.
Si Joon, you look depressed today. Are you alright?
Well, it doesn't matter what happens to me but I never thought that the Hospital's Director would be investigated.
That's because all legal problems are her responsibility.
Regardless, if you could return to that time, you would still make the same choice. Wouldn't you?
How is Han Woo Joo these days?
She finally admitted that she's a patient.
Oh that's a huge development.
We're in the process of psychoanalysis.
Are the results out?
Not yet. But it's definitely not just an Intermittent Explosive Disorder.
- Then?
- Impulsive human relationships,
anger, unpredictability, mood disorder.
What has these characteristics?
There is one thing comes to mind.
What is that?
No way. It can't be.
There's no way you would've introduced me to a patient with borderline personality disorder. Right?
What happens if by chance, she has borderline personality disorder?
- It's been a while but these green-onion pancakes are really good.
- Why are you avoiding it?
-  What?
- Why would a person who ignored all administrative procedures and forcefully admitted Park Ru Oh, avoid this topic?
Stop it, Dong Hyuk.
Okay. Let's leave it.
How could you be so fine?
About what?
You put a star up in the sky last year.
You call yourself a doctor, but how can you be so fine when something like that happened to your patient?
- This punk really—
- Me?
Because of a star I put up in the sky 8 years ago,
I can't go to sleep unless I run around like crazy giving it my all during the day.
I just can't fathom how  you could be so fine, that's all.
This jerk really—!
Please stop.
Don't make a mockery of me, you punk.
Just because the wounds are  healed doesn't mean I'm fine.
Is it something to brag about, that he can't forget what happened 8 years ago?
Dong Hyuk, I must have made a mistake. I shouldn't have introduced Han Woo Joo to him.
I had no idea he had this hard a time forgetting about it.
Hey, Ji Young Won.
- Why are you always worrying about only Si Joon?
- What?
Isn't it time for you to stop?
Who is the informant?
He said no one comes to mind.
So even psychiatrists can be put in situations like this... Ji Soo needs to be careful.
By the way... he told me to go get my watch back from Hwang Min Wook, but what should I do?
What do you mean? You should do as you were told.
Do you think I really need to show that person the rock bottom of my pettiness?
Hello? You already showed it. You said you called asking for it.
Gosh... why do I hit rock bottom so often?
I'm sorry but we're clos—
I'm sure you didn't come to eat. Did you come to see me?
I didn't come to eat nor did I come to see you.
I came to give this to you. You said you were coming yesterday but since you didn't...
I was coming to get it anyway. Thank you.
Hey, why are you thanking him?
You have nothing else to take from me, right? If there is, say it now.
I don't know, what else could there be?
The one year I  lost?
I do have something. The bills for food. You ate a lot of free food at my house.
- Get that from her.
- What?
The money to fix my car,
do you know how much it amounted to? Couldn't we break up a little more beautifully?
Hey! The moment you cheated, that beauty was already destroyed.
This is outrageous. This is exactly what they call gaslighting!
It's not the first time your breakup was caused by your boyfriend cheating on you.
When the same thing keeps repeating itself, there's a reason why.
I was a coward, but there is a problem in your life.
Look at him pretending to be so powerful! Oh my!
Hey, what's with you again?
He's right, though. The guys I dated before also cheated on me, that's why we broke up.
Don't cry. Don't waste your tears.
I'm not crying.
I'm a crazy bastard. What am I doing here, at this time?
Do I have nowhere else to go? Pathetic.
Woo Joo, what are you doing here?
I didn't know what to do with this.
That's right.
You told me to call but why didn't you answer? I called you many times.
I'm sorry, I didn't know.
I felt like if I took this home, I would stay up all night staring at it.
I was going to throw it in the trash but I felt that wasn't right.
- Do you want to bury it, scatter it, or cremate it?
- Huh?
Throwing it in the water would be bad for the environment, and it also wouldn't burn properly.
I'd like to bury it.
Let's do that.
You could consider this a ritual.
That's right.
Alright, throw it now.
While we're at it, throw it to the very top with all your strength.
You throw very well.
Are you a shot put athlete?
It felt refreshing, though it wasn't much.
- I did well, right?
- Nice.
Nice!
All I did was throw  one of my old memories in a garbage dump,
but it felt like my wounds were also buried in the garbage dump.
Three months ago, Ru Oh sent me an S.O.S. through my podcast.
I was doing a live broadcast that day, but he said he heard hallucinations
that kept telling him to jump in front of a car.
I had no choice but to admit him.
We couldn't get in contact with his guardian for a couple days.
We eventually did, but he said he was in Vietnam and couldn't come immediately.
I couldn't send the kid back to the little study dorm  he was living in alone,
so I admitted him and I guess that turned out to be forceful hospitalization.
And that's how the investigation came about.
Why is that forceful hospitalization?
How could you have just sent him back to such a dangerous place?
He can only be without a guardian for a maximum of three days.
I knew it would become a problem one day.
So what do you do now?
You said the more you worry, the more it piles up.
I'm not worried.
Go in.
Goodnight.
Shall we do some exercises?
You prescribed them to me last time. They were really effective.
The moon is so beautiful today too.
Let's do it.
What are you doing? Why are you doing it  roughly?
Even if it's just one move, you should do it precisely  and  with discipline.
- Try it.
- Alright, waist exercise. Here we go.
1,2,3,4. 2,2,3,4.
3,2,3,4. 4,2,3,4.
Alright, shoulder exercise.
2,3,4. 2,2,3,4.
3,2,3,4.
Okay, cross your fingers and reach above your head.
1,2,3,4.
All the way.
- Refreshing, right?
- Yes.
Shaking the body. Let's go!
Okay, shake your body!
As if your arms are not your arms! Not yours!
- Shake them!
- What kind of exercise is this?
Shake your body!
I knew you would cause trouble one day.
The legal team will contact you, so wait for that.
The Gwangsu regional police office conducted the investigation.
They said they couldn't find any evidence of physical violence in the CCTV footage.
It seems they only found out about you ignoring all the procedures and forceful hospitalization.
I'm sorry.
You knew everything and did it regardless, didn't you?
There was nothing else I could do.
You will be investigated at the police station soon.
The Hospital's Director is also being investigated, right?
Of course.
Why are you so headstrong?
I don't regret it.
If I had just sent Ru Oh back, he could have died.
Transfer Park Ru Oh to Dong Hyuk.
He is my patient.
Should we just send him to a completely different hospital?
Alright.
You ignored all the procedures.
Exactly why are you this obsessed with your patients?
You know, don't you, why you are being this way?
- Obviously—
- Don't give me the obvious answer like  you were thinking about the patient.
You know that there is another reason.
- Start consultation with me.
- Chief.
Also, keep in mind that for the time being, you will have no outpatient care.
Why?
Consider it a relief that this is how the incident is ending!
Why aren't you leaving?
They took away my patients from me.
They're my reason for living, though.
Doctor.
What are you doing here?
It's going to be a while before the theatrical therapy starts, though.
I was just looking for some quiet.
You don't have any appointments today?
Oh, perhaps are you slacking off?
Do you want to drink this? I just bought it.
It's fine.
Did something bad happen?
I definitely told you yesterday
that  the more you worry, the more it piles up.
Tell me, I'll listen to you.
There's nothing to say.
What was that?
Why is he being that way all of a sudden?
Today is my daughter's birthday.
Because she has a mother like me, she can't even eat a bowl of seaweed soup on her birthday.
She's doing part-time jobs to earn money.
Still, you can't go out according to the rules.
You know the convenience store in front of the hospital, right?
She works part-time there.
I'll call her for you.
I said it's her birthday.
Don't you know what a surprise is?
You can't.
You have exactly 10 minutes.
I said I got it.
Welcome.
Hello.
What are you doing?
- Give it back.
- I can't.
- I said give it.
- I said no!
- I said give it to me!
- I said I can't.
What are you doing right now?
Give it to me!
No!
What are you guys doing?
What are you doing? You should stop your mom!
What? I'm not her daughter.
- What?
- Give it to me. I said give it to me!
Give it to me!
Oh no, what do I do?
Yoon Ji!
Doctor...
If a patient has let go of their sanity and is drinking alcohol,
you should do everything in your power to stop it, but you sit there crying.
You're a doctor.
I'm sorry.
Here in psychiatry, just because you do something with a good heart doesn't mean it will yield good results.
I got it.
Yes, Chief.
Yes, alright.
You should treat Park Ru Oh from now on.
Si Joon agreed.
Chief, is there any reason to take Si Joon's patients from him?
I'm not taking patients from Si Joon. You're the only eligible doctor.
I understand.
It's going to be hard for Si Joon, so you should help him a bit.
Of course, I should.
Alright. You may leave.
But Chief, who is the informant?
You know, don't you?
I don't know either.
People call me a wild rabbit. They say I'm  a rabbit because I'm always going for walks.
They must be mistaken.
Wild rabbits are fast but you're slow.
That's why you always get caught by me.
Ru Oh,
from now on, your doctor will change.
Why?
You're upset, aren't you?
I understand. You're taken aback and sad.
I'm fine.
Really?
I'm about to be upset.
I heard from the nurse in the ward
that the police were here because of me.
Who said such absurd rumors? That's not it.
I'm alright.
Park Ru Oh, I told you to say it hurts if  you're hurt, didn't I?
Have you forgotten why you became ill?
Because I was scared but didn't say I was.
Because I felt lonely but didn't say that I felt that way.
So why are you holding it in?
I won't hold it in.
I documented his condition from the first day he was admitted up until yesterday, so refer to it.
In Dong Hyuk
Lee Si Joon has gone crazy.
He's the craziest doctor I've ever seen.
Are you really going to be this way?
- What are you talking about?
- Are you asking because you don't know?
Why have you been like this since earlier?
Did I do something wrong? Did I make a mistake?
You didn't do anything wrong nor did you make any mistake.
I've just got a lot on my mind, that's why. Let's talk later.
Why did I cut my wrists?
Because I want to receive attention.
When I was younger, I wanted to receive attention from my adopted parents, so I started a fire.
Of course, it resulted in my adoption being dissolved. However, I never felt like dying.
I just wished they would look at me.
♫  Goodbye  ♫
♫  The memories I want to forget   ♫
Why did you send Han Woo Joo to me? You knew from the beginning and sent her, didn't you?
Do you really know who the informant is?
The culprit is—
Why did you needlessly interfere?
I'm going to quit the theatrical therapy.
How could someone who harms the patients do theatrical therapy?
What is with me seriously?
Doctor Si Joon!
Ru Oh has been in an accident.
What the—
I can't believe our country's best cardiac surgeon is a criminal who plants hidden cameras.
How great would it be if I could turn back time just one day?
♫  Stay by my side just like this  ♫