Episode 16
Hello.
- I'm the Vice President of this hospital.
- I see.
Are you the actress helping us with theatrical treatment?
How did you know?
I saw you last time, leaving with Dr. Lee Si Joon.
I just wanted to introduce myself to you, since I saw you while I was passing by.
But what are you doing here? Are you waiting for someone?
- I'm waiting for Dr. Lee Si Joon.
- Oh...
Have you two known each other for a long time?
I met him because of a patient named Cha Dong Il.
Right, right.
You really suffered because of Cha Dong Il, didn't you?
Yes, but I met Dr. Lee Si Joon thanks to that incident.
Is that so?
I heard the operators didn't come today.
Yes. We're working to resolve that issue right now.
What's so difficult about that?
Forget about that. Follow me.
Where are you going?
What? What kind of nonsense is that?
That's what I'm saying. It made so little sense to me that I came here.
Is he crazy? Dating a patient?
Vice President, Dr. Lee is not dating Ms. Han Woo Joo.
I confirmed it myself! I asked Han Woo Joo directly!
What is it that you really want to say?
What do you mean, what is it? A psychiatrist is dating a patient that he's supposed to be treating.
If rumors start going around, our hospital will be humiliated!
The director is already upset about the incident with Congressman Koh!
It's true that Dr. Lee made a mistake in his treatment of Congressman Koh.
But still. Don't you think this is a bit unfair?
Unfair? What's so unfair about it?
What's unfair about it? Do I seem like I'm just making an issue out of nothing?
Dr. In, tell him! You saw it too!
You saw them linking arms and walking around the hospital!
- Vice President, that...
- Did you see it or not?
Did you see it or not?!
Is it real?
Yes.
Good work today.
Woo Jung, go upstairs and check on the wards.
Yes, I'll do that.
You've worked hard today.
Ms. Woo Joo?
When did you get here? I've been watching the door this whole time.
Were you waiting for me?
I couldn't go home.
Why couldn't you go home?
My finger... stings and just hurts so much.
What's wrong with your hand?
Earlier, when you passed by me,
your clothing brushed against my finger.
That's just cloth, but it stung and hurt
as if I had been grazed by a knife.
As if I had really been cut by a blade.
After that, my feet wouldn't move.
Have you ever experienced something similar before?
When was it?
When my adoptive mother dissolved my adoption, she took me back to the orphanage I was from.
Then, she turned around after handing me one last $5 bill...
A part of her skirt brushed against my finger.
Then, my hand stung and hurt like I had been cut by a knife.
What are you doing?
Touch this, and see if your hands get cut.
I mean, I'm just saying it felt like that. I'm not saying I actually cut my hand.
Are you happy now?
Feeling like that is because of your painful memories.
Dr. Lee. Am I a really sick person?
Tell me honestly.
I heard that Dr. Ji Young Won introduced me to you.
Dr. Ji said she just decided to collaborate with you.
Am I someone so broken that doctors need to collaborate to fix me?
Ms. Woo Joo,
I am also sick.
Where?
My mind frequently catches the cold, for no reason.
I get treated by the patients that I treat.
While I treat them, I get consoled.
Do you know how much the sounds of those drums you made me listen to last time consoled me?
Whenever I feel down, I think of your performance,
then my mood immediately brightens.
Yesterday, I mentioned this in my podcast as well,
but there's nobody who isn't sick.
They just haven't been diagnosed yet.
While treating you, I'm also being treated.
Wait a minute.
I just sent you those drumming sounds as a file to you.
Whenever your mind catches a cold, you should listen to it.
I read somewhere that this is actually super effective.
Oh and, whenever you listen to it, you should imagine my performance too.
I'll tell you more things next time.
Okay.
Then... shall we as patients
high-five?
Sure!
What was that?
One more time?
One, two...
I knew you would do that!
- One, two—
- Three!
- This is the last time.
- One, two, three!
Dr. Lee Si Joon is really incredible.
How could he think of visiting the patient?
Dr. Lee never only meets his patient in his office.
Whether it be at their homes or their workplace, he goes to visit his patients.
I want to be on Dr. Lee's team. Should I ask Dr. In to send me?
Se Chan! If you say that, Dr. In will get pissed!
I've heard that even the patients recently
have been comparing the two doctors.
I got rejected by Si Joon before I could even confess. Before I could even say anything.
Dong Hyuk. I really feel horrible these days.
What's wrong this time?
I got rejected by a patient. Han Woo Joo.
She found out that introduced her to Si Joon, and hates me now for abandoning her.
She's a BPD patient. Isn't it a given that she would feel angry about such a thing?
She's totally transferred her emotions to Si Joon right now.
She relies on him a lot.
Is Si Joon aware of this?
Of course he is.
I'm sure it's hard for him too. He can't do anything about it.
Then I guess I don't need to worry about anything.
Why? Is something going on?
The Vice President is under the impression that they're dating.
So? Is there an issue?
Did a rumor start?
It's bad if rumors start circulating.
Well, it's fine for now.
If something happens because of that, you should take initiative and dispel the misunderstanding.
Why should I?
I'm going to stop standing behind Lee Si Joon.
What does that mean?
I'm going to send a patient to you. She's an attending in our department. She has sociophobia and anxiety.
Don't change the topic. What do you mean by what you just said?
What kind of patient is Ms. Han Woo Joo?
She's a BPD patient.
What?
You asked a BPD patient to take care of theatrical therapy?
I found out after I had asked her to do it.
So what if she's a BPD patient? She's doing well with the theatrical treatment.
We can't discriminate against the sick, after proclaiming that sick people should not be discriminated against.
Is Han Joo Woo experiencing transference towards you?
How did you know?
The Vice President said the two of you were dating.
You're not dating her, are you?
Why would you say such a thing?
I'm aware of it.
If you just wait patiently, it goes away on its own.
I'm just waiting for that to happen.
Then why did you link arms with her?
That's because she just suddenly linked her arm with mine,
and if I reject it, she might feel embarrassed.
Then what if... that resurfaces as another wound.
Please be more careful. The Vice President is watching you carefully,
and the Director is sensitive about the issue with Congressman Koh!
If the Director finds this out at a time like this, nothing good will come of it.
I understand.
Draw the line, so there are no more misunderstandings.
Under no circumstances should you meet up personally, outside of your office.
Why aren't you answering me?
I thought for a second you were my father with dementia.
Am I being like this for no reason?
If you're going to mention the incident from 8 years ago, don't.
This is different from back then.
A little too much.
How did you think of personally visiting the operators?
Vice President, Dr. In is quite clever!
Dr. In is quite eccentric.
He went out on a patient visit. It's difficult to see that these days.
You used the emergency telephone to carry out the consultation?
The person who went wasn't me, but Dr. Lee Si Joon.
Dr. In told him to go.
Whoever it may have been, it's more important who came up with the idea.
My reputation had hit rock bottom because of the incident with Congressman Koh,
but thanks you Dr. In, it's been revived.
Chief Park! Did you see the news? Dr. In really did something great for our hospital.
Yes, I just saw the news.
Dr. In cleaned up the crap that Dr. Lee Si Joon left.
Chief Park, have you confirmed what I asked you about yesterday?
He says it's not true.
What are you talking about?
About that...
I think that Dr. Lee Si Joon has personal relations with a patient that he is treating.
I'm telling you it's not true.
The patient is experiencing transference. I confirmed it myself.
Transference? Then that's more of a reason not to link arms in the hospital.
Link arms? Inside the hospital?
Please don't misunderstand, Director.
Well, to know if it's a misunderstanding or not, we can just ask directly.
Did you sleep well?
We injected Patient Yang with medication that has high anxiolytic effects late at night to help her sleep.
Since there are variances amongst all patients in their responses to the effectiveness of medication that helps them sleep,
so why don't we use these concurrently with antihistamines?
That sounds good.
Ever since her guardians visited yesterday, she's been sleeping.
I'll call you again once she's awake.
Okay.
Hello?
Was the Vice President the one that snitched?
What do I need to explain?
Okay.
Why didn't you just call me?
Can I tell a busy man to come whenever I want him to?
I've been hearing about some awkward things. Do you know what I'm talking about?
I wonder... I don't think so.
I heard that you had personal relations with a patient you were treating. Is this true?
You're laughing?
I think you're talking about Ms. Han Woo Joo.
She's just a patient. Of course, there's nothing going on between on.
I think it's ridiculous that I have to explain myself to you like this.
Are you being like this because of what happened to Congressman Koh?
Dr. Lee! Are you crazy?
Anyone would get pissed if they had to hear about things like this when nothing's going on!
I don't regret my judgement.
It was the best decision I could make as his primary physician.
This attitude of yours right now. Are you challenging me?
Fine then. Vice President, starting from today, Dr. Lee will get no funding for research.
If he says he'll go to another hospital, then let him go.
I understand.
If rumors like this circulate again, I won't forgive them.
Please tell the patient who is in charge of theatrical therapy to quit.
When did you get here?
Just now.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Then I'll be heading out.
Wait, Ms. Woo Joo.
I'm sorry,
but I don't think I'll be able to consult you today.
Something suddenly came up, so I have to cancel all my appointments.
That's a relief. I was wondering if I should reschedule my appointment anyway, because the restaurant is really busy today.
Then I'll reschedule your appointment.
Okay.
I thought Lee Si Joon would be different,
but it's not me. He's the same as everyone else.
I...
I... was abandoned again.
I— I really...
I really bring nothing but misfortune.
Even Lee Si Joon experienced misfortune because of me. I feel so bad.
But I really dislike him right now!
Ji Sun, I'm sorry.
I— I really tried not to cry in front of you again.
I really didn't want to cry in front of you.
I'm sorry.
The treatment we'll start now will be done using simple objects
to try mimicking the fear you feel
at the onset of your panic disorders and getting exposure to that.
First we will start with exposure therapy to nausea and fatigue.
Are you feeling okay?
There is one minute left.
Please stop. You can stop now.
Okay take a deep breath.
Once a recurrence happens, you'll feel nauseated as you are feeling right now.
However, please remember this one thing.
No matter how nauseated or suffocated you feel, like right now,
you will not die.
Please remember this.
I've been trying to brush it off using whatever means necessarily.
If I can't brush this off, then I will become a slave to that incident forever.
For a while, I prayed every day.
To please make them all experience what I went through.
Did you feel better, once you did that?
Not at all. I think I actually felt worse.
What do you feel the more angry and wronged about?
That of course would be that I was secretly filmed.
I think there's something else you feel worse about.
What do you think it is?
I lost my first patient.
I was looking forward to it so much. I feel that's unfair.
- What else?
- The economic loss is pretty significant as well.
I have to ride the taxi instead of riding on the subway.
The thing you are the most upset about, beyond all those things you just mentioned,
is the fact that you went from being a successful doctor to being a patient.
Because of those pitiful jerks, you missed your opportunity to treat your very first patient.
You even developed sociophobia and are struggling financially.
Isn't all of that just so unfair? I'm getting vicarious trauma from just listening to that.
That's true.
You had to study so much to meet your first patient.
How could it be that a doctor became a patient because of people like those that victimized you?
I can guarantee this.
If you're able to overcome this, when you meet a patient experiencing what you're going through right now,
you'll be the best at treating that patient.
I'll regain my confidence.
I'll help you.
What are you doing?
I heard you're not eating well again these days.
I just wanted to stop by. I didn't have anywhere else to go, either.
I want to fold an airplane, but it's not going well.
Why do you want to fold an airplane?
I have a 6-year old son. He's asking me to fold one for him.
Can you fold one for me?
You have a son?
He's so smart.
I think my son will like this!
Do you know how to fold a boat, too?
I guess you'll forget whatever I tell you today.
How are you so good at folding these?
I learned it from my father.
Is that so?
I'll fold you a boat, a turtle, and a rabbit. All of it.
But in return, can you listen to what I have to say?
Sure.
I... think I'm experiencing transference.
Towards a patient that I'm treating.
Oh, gosh!
Do you even understand what I'm saying?
You said you turned into a fish.
He says he's a fish!
So what happened?
To be honest, I've known for a while but I kept denying it.
I didn't want the same thing to happen again. I even tried not meeting her again.
I tried to avoid her, but ultimately...
I've come all the way here, like some sort of fate.
Wow, you're so good at folding those.
What should I do?
Should I... keep running like this?
Or should I choose a different path?
Life is short.
Just go. Don't go back. Life is straight forward.
Exactly.
My son will probably grow up in no time. Straight up.
Of course.
Once your son gets older,
he'll...
there will come a day when he folds papers for his father like this.
What's that one?
This is delicious!
It's good.
You should have some too.
It's so good!
Come on, eat some.
What's this?
Why is nobody here? They told me to come.
Kang Noo Ri!
We love you, Kang Noo Ri!
Sunbae,
you said your favorite food is home-cooked food, so we prepared it for you.
Ta-da! Yay!
Sunbae.
Sunbae, you've been through a lot.
Oh no! Don't cry.
Why are you crying?
Eat up!
This looks so good.
Eat lots!
It's good!
Would you like to try some of this?
Thanks.
Thank you! This is so good!
It's totally delicious!
Be quiet. Let me eat.
Please.
I'm sorry.
It's really good.
♫  The endlessly dark evening road is narrow and far.  ♫
♫   When you don't know where to go,  ♫
♫  I'll be there for you, on the corner of the road.  ♫
♫  It'll all be okay, so don't worry.  ♫
♫  I love you.  ♫
♫  I always have.  ♫
Fix You
Why were you good to me then? Why did you confuse me?
My brother has been diagnosed with PTSD.
PTSD is quite bad for Lee Si Joon as well.
There's a fire! A fire!
Why do you keep laughing?
You shouldn't use that friendly face of yours to scam people!
S-Scam?
You can't just cast someone away like this.
Do you think of Ms. Woo Joo as special?
Ms. Woo Joo, you've always been different from other patients.
Why are you leading such a difficult life?
♫   When I think of you, it gets better.   ♫