Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series
are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
(I never thought working on a holiday would make me so happy.)
(No matter what,)
(I want to see Karan succeed in life.)
(Even if he likes someone else other than me.)
What’s that sound?
It sounds like a fire alarm.
She’s so lovey-dovey.
She must be his girlfriend.
I want to take over his condo for a while.
Even though you’re my big sister, I won’t let you mess with everything.
(What? This is his older sister?)
It’s a good idea for Karan to stay here.
You’re sick.
You should have someone to take care of you.
Bye.
(Does this mean Karan is moving into my house?)
Achi.
I’m sorry for my sister causing you trouble.
Don’t worry about it.
Make yourself at home.
Get comfortable.
Actually, I can stay at a hotel.
I don’t want to trouble you.
You let me stay at your place before.
And it’s getting dark now.
At least stay here tonight.
Let’s talk about this again tomorrow.
I’ll make the bed for you.
Achi.
Are you alright?
Your temperature is still very high.
You might want to hurry upstairs and rest.
Let’s go.
Get well soon.
Please don’t disappear.
I won’t go anywhere.
You sat here all night?
You’re awake.
Let me see.
Thank god.
It seems like your fever has gone down.
But from now on, you must take care of your body
so you don’t get sick easily again.
I’ll go down and make you something to eat.
Then you can take your medicine.
Are you sure you feel okay to work?
Yeah.
I feel better now.
Don’t worry.
I can go to work.
Hey, Achi.
Are you going to work?
Come here.
Bring Khao Tom Mud to eat.
Thank you.
Eh?
Who’s this young man?
I’ve never seen him before.
Is he your friend?
This is Karan.
He’s my coworker.
Hello.
Oh my.
He looks handsome and great.
I’m relieved you have a friend who seems reliable, Achi.
I thought you’re only friends with clumsy people like you.
Honestly, I’m so worried.
You’re already 30 but still clumsy.
At this rate, when will you get promoted?
Please don’t worry, Auntie.
Achi is not irresponsible.
He’s always helping others at the office.
He works harder than anyone.
The company’s latest big project came from his idea.
He’s more talented than you think.
Really?
Achi, why haven’t you ever told me that?
Achi is a humble guy
and doesn’t like to take the credit.
Actually, I think he’s the good person he is because of you.
Thank you for taking good care of him.
Oh, you’re too kind.
He does well on his own.
Achi,
you have such a good friend.
You must take good care of each other, alright?
Okay.
We should go to work now.
Please excuse us.
Alright.
Safe trip.
Two people, please.
♪ Just a soft I love you and I’d give in all the way ♪
♪ Forget heaven and earth for the day ♪
♪ Say you love me when we’re together ♪
♪ With only a whisper from your heart ♪
(Even when singing in his head, he’s singing off key.)
This is the first time I’m on a boat like this.
I wish I could ride it often like you do.
It’d feel like I was on vacation every day.
If you ride it every day, you won’t think that way.
This morning, it’s crowded and a little uncomfortable.
Hang in there.
(Being on a boat feels so romantic.)
(Since this is my first boat ride with Achi,)
(I want to have something as a keepsake.)
(What should it be?)
(Would asking him for a selfie be too suspicious?)
Karan, this is for you.
It’s a souvenir for your first boat ride.
Thank you.
I’ll keep it carefully.
Moo Ping, anyone?
Thank you so much.
Try it.
It’s really tasty.
It’s good, right?
It’s my secret go-to place.
I usually don’t tell anyone about it.
I’m afraid the Moo Ping will sell out and I won’t get to eat any.
(Wow. Am I the only one who knows about this place from him?)
(So nice. I feel like I’m special to Achi.)
By the way, Achi.
Don’t forget to take your medicine.
Oh, right.
You forgot it at home
so I brought it for you.
Thank you.
Drink this water too.
How was last night?
Did you get any sleep?
I did.
I slept comfortably.
Then you can stay longer.
Can I really?
Of course you can.
Your sister is going through a tough time, isn’t she?
I’m happy to help.
I’ll take you up on it then.
Okay.
(Strangely, I’m not scared of being around Karan like I used to be.)
(I actually even feel comfortable.)
(I feel safe somehow.)
(I don’t know yet what this feeling is,)
(but it feels so good.)
(So this is what a person feels when they’re about to start a married life.)
(What?)
(I’m about to live like a couple with Achi?)
(I can’t wait.)
(A married life?)
(How could Karan’s imagination go so wild?)
He’s so cute, Madam Noi.
Even in the video, his aura shines through.
If I get to watch Min dance live, how much cuter is he going to be?
Look.
Let’s dance along.
Are you listening to music?
I could hear it from in front of the room.
(Oh, no. If Min finds out I’m secretly watching his practice videos,)
(he might think I’m a suspicious psycho fan.)
What music?
The ad video just randomly came up.
I can’t watch any videos.
I’ve been so busy lately.
I don’t have time for that nonsense.
You must have been busy.
Yes.
Here’s your package.
(I want to invite him to watch me practice)
(but I better not.)
(I don’t want to take away his work time.)
What?
Oh, here you go.
Keep going with your work.
I should get going.
Wait.
Damn it, Jinta!
I shouldn’t have talked too much.
Please don’t patch my tires yet.
I’d rather wait for the imported tires.
Yes.
I can wait even if it takes a long time.
I don’t need to use the car anytime soon.
Alright. Thank you so much.
Achi.
Do you want to go home together after work?
(Ever since Karan started thinking about married life,)
(I don’t know how to act when I’m alone with him,)
(even though I feel good when we’re together.)
Sure.
But we might have to wait for a while.
Boss hasn’t left yet.
(Luckily, there’s a rule forbidding us from leaving before our boss.)
(I should have some time to find an excuse.)
I’m leaving, everyone.
See you tomorrow.
Huh?
Guys, Boss left early today.
Let’s go.
How lucky.
Shall we leave now?
♪ For me to stop loving you, just stop being lovely first ♪
♪ You’re too cute to handle, not loving you is impossible ♪
♪ I’m already yours ♪
Are you guys leaving already?
I’ve never seen you leave together.
I have to stay at Achi's house for now.
What? Why didn’t you invite me?
I want to stay over too.
Then come and stay with us.
Can I?
Are you sure?
You don’t want too many people troubling you.
You won’t be troubling me.
My house has a lot of space.
But I don’t think you have enough beds.
I have a picnic mattress.
What about the bathrooms?
Hey.
Is this yours or Achi’s house?
You can come and stay over, Rock.
Don’t worry.
No take backs.
Yes!
Since all three of us are staying together tonight,
shall we hold a Mala Shabu party?
Do you have all the ingredients?
Shall we go shopping first?
(Just like that, I don’t have to worry about being alone with Karan anymore.)
(Gosh. His aura is shining even brighter than in that video clip.)
(I want to watch closer, but I don’t want Min to notice.)
Jinta.
What are you doing, sneaking around here?
Didn’t you say you were busy with work?
Yes, I’m busy.
I’m writing a novel about idols
so I’m here to do some research.
Damn.
A writer.
So cool.
Shall we let him join us for dancing?
Since he’s already here.
He’ll understand idols' lives better.
Not a good idea.
He never danced before.
Look at him.
He doesn’t look like he can pull it off.
Listen, kids.
I’m not that old.
I sometimes work out at home.
Dancing will be just a piece of cake.
He has the guts.
Alright, dude.
Turn on the music.
Bring it on.
Easy peasy.
Come on, man.
Just wait and see.
Easy peasy.
(I need to use this opportunity to impress Min.)
Watch me.
Jinta.
Whoa.
And this is Rock Rock Pork.
This Mala pork with cheese is my special recipe.
It’s so delicious.
Try it.
It’s hot. Let me blow on it first.
It’s really delicious.
I know, right?
I’m glad you like it.
I’ll make you another one.
It’s okay, Rock.
I’ll do it.
And this is my Mala specialty.
Ran Ran Mala.
Do you want to try it, Achi?
I’ll get some for you.
Try it.
Help yourself to it, Rock.
Okay.
It’s so delicious.
It’s so satisfyingly spicy.
It’s amazing.
Do you want more soup, Achi?
Let me give you some more.
(I won’t let him compliment only Rock.)
(That ‘so delicious’ compliment should be given to me.)
(Is he jealous?)
(I didn’t think he had this side of him.)
(It’s kinda cute.)
♪ What do I do next? ♪
♪ What if I just left ? ♪
♪ I can only ask ♪
♪ All you say is “umm-umm” ♪
♪ The mood’s low, it’s undone ♪
♪ This isn’t right ♪
♪ I ask “what’s wrong?”, you say “nothing’s wrong” ♪
♪ I ask “what’s wrong?”, you say “just move along” ♪
♪ All you say is “umm-umm” ♪
♪ But I’m undone ♪
You know how to sing this song?
Of course.
I’m still young.
I had a band when I was in university.
I’ll show you.
You guys seriously formed a band?
That’s so cool.
We didn’t get far.
We quit before we could.
Why did you quit?
We were just bored.
It’s nothing.
Forget it.
Do you want anything? I’ll get it for you.
(Actually, we didn’t want to quit, but we saw no future.)
(We had a band for many years, but didn’t get to debut.)
(It would’ve only been a waste of time to keep fighting.)
Is Rock asleep already?
Yeah.
I feel bad for Rock.
Even though he said “forget it”, I think he still hasn’t gotten over it.
(Why am I feeling so upset?)
(Achi is rightly worrying about another person)
(but I can’t help feeling unhappy)
(when I hear him talk about someone else.)
(I’m so bad.)
Karan.
Sorry.
I probably drank too much.
Please excuse me.
Your mattress was so comfy to sleep on.
Can I come again next time?
Sure.
You can come anytime.
Please get on the boat.
Get on.
Get on, guys.
Excuse me.
The boat is full.
Please wait for the next one.
It leaves in about 15 minutes.
But we came together.
Let’s wait for the next boat.
Come on.
I have to meet Pai for a product promotional video shoot at 8 a.m.
I don’t want to be late.
Don’t you have to help too?
You’re right.
You guys can go first.
I think I’ll visit a client before going to the office.
You may leave now.
Okay.
Off you go.
I’m sorry.
See you at the office.
Pai,
is everything alright?
Achi.
The writer we asked to promote the pen just canceled out of the blue.
I don’t know where to find his replacement in time.
Can it be someone with a different job?
Writers these days don’t use pens anymore.
They write on their computers.
If you think like that, then don’t sell pens.
If you want a writer,
I might be able to find you one
but he’s not very famous.
That’s totally fine.
As long as he’s a real writer.
Can you help me, Achi?
Sure.
I’ll keep you updated.
Okay.
I’ll go check on everything.
Alright.
Thank you.
Karan’s here.
Karan.
How was the trip?
Was it inconvenient?
Don’t worry about me.
Did you guys make it here in time?
We almost didn’t.
This morning, we went to queue up at Achi’s secret Moo Ping place.
It’s so good.
I want to eat it again.
Let’s go there again some other time.
Sure.
Is something wrong, Karan?
Nothing.
Excuse me.
(I thought I was the only one Achi told about that place.)
(I flattered myself.)
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
What the hell?
Jinta.
Oh, hey, Min.
Where are you going?
I’m going to film an ad for my friend.
Wow.
That’s cool.
You’re a model now.
I’m no model.
It’s just a small promotional video.
Are you going to model with that thing on your face?
Come here.
Let me help you.
Where’s your friend’s office?
I can give you a ride if you want.
I don’t have work today.
Are you sure?
Why not?
Are you embarrassed to ride with a motorbike delivery rider like me?
No, I’m not embarrassed.
I just don’t want to trouble you.
You’re not troubling me.
I’ll be your rider today
to make up for being the cause of your injury.
Here.
Get on.
Achi.
Hmm?
Can I talk to you?
What’s up?
Achi!
Here I am!
You’re here!
Thank you so much for coming.
No need to thank me.
I’ll do anything for you.
Oh.
Hello, Mr. Karan.
You know me?
Of course, I do.
You…
It’s almost time.
We should get ready or we’ll be late.
Let’s go.
What were you going to say?
Nothing.
Let’s go.
Writing is serious business.
It must make your heart race.
All good.
Feel free to change your clothes, Jinta.
Hey.
Do you remember the young rider I told you about?
He’s going to pick me up this evening.
The guy named Min?
Yes.
That’s cool.
Has your relationship developed already?
Not really
but I think I’m falling for real.
I knew it.
I feel the same way.
Then this evening…
(When you ride on his motorbike, why don’t you hold him like this?)
(Like this?)
(No.)
(Won’t he think you’re being handsy if you do that?)
(What if I hold onto his shoulders?)
(Will that look bad?)
(Won’t he think you’re being handsy?)
(I’ll do this then.)
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
I’m not doing anything.
We’re just talking.
Nothing is going on.
He’s right.
We’re really just talking.
We’re not doing anything.
I’m sorry.
I misunderstood.
I’m really sorry.
What’s wrong with him?
I almost got punched.
Excuse me.
Are you Min?
You know me?
Jinta told me you’d pick him up.
My name is Achi.
I’m Jinta’s friend.
He’s still filming the last scene.
You can wait upstairs.
Come.
Okay.
Take a seat and wait here.
I think Jinta is almost done.
Duj,
please let Min wait for Jinta here.
Oh.
Your name is Min?
You’re good-looking.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Are you tired from sitting here?
If so, you can sit in my heart instead.
Achi, can you help upload the footage we shot earlier?
Sure.
Let me handle it.
Thank you.
Min.
Oh?
You two know each other?
We’re friends from university.
I see.
Then you must have seen Rock’s dance band.
What was he like during that time?
Was he handsome?
Probably not.
I think I should wait outside.
Oh?
Please excuse me.
Min.
Hold on, Min.
Rock, what’s the problem between you and Min?
Hey.
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
I’m just thinking about the past.
That employee is your friend, right?
He was
but not anymore.
Min and I were in the same band.
We graduated without getting to debut.
At that time, I thought there’s no future in becoming idols
so I thought of quitting.
I thought it’d be better to have a stable job
so I applied for different companies
and ended up working here.
But I didn’t know what to tell my friends.
I was afraid of being accused of abandoning the band.
So I decided to cut contact with everyone.
I’ve never been mad at Rock.
I’m actually happy that he has a good job.
But now he’s in a different league from me.
He probably doesn’t want to be friends with me anymore.
These past several years,
I’ve always wondered
if I gave up too easily.
Was I selfish?
Did I disappoint my friends?
Rock made the right decision.
I’m still stuck in the same place.
Sometimes I think that if I hadn’t chosen this path,
my life might be better.
That’s not true.
No matter how many more times you chose,
you’d still choose this path.
You know, every time I watch your practice clips,
I only see your effort and determination.
If you didn’t really love it, you wouldn’t be working so hard for it.
You didn’t choose the wrong path.
You just chose to follow your dream.
So, even if you could turn back time and change things,
I believe that in the end, you’d still choose this path.
I’m such a bad person.
It’s good that Min stopped being friends with me.
We feel bad for Rock, don’t we?
No way in hell.
You idiot.
What’s wrong with you?
I’m in a sad mood. Why did you slap me?
To help you pull yourself together.
Are you out of your mind?
You feel guilty and want to apologize to him
but instead you’re sitting here going on about it.
How would he know how you feel?
Huh?
Come with me.
Come on. Get up!
Pai.
Duj.
I think ever since Pai went off on her ex,
she has seemed a lot scarier.
Agreed.
She’s sweet like a sugar glider on the outside
but aggressive like a bengal tiger on the inside.
She’s crazy.
Let’s quickly follow them
or Rock will be dead.
I forgot my phone.
Go talk to your friend.
Go.
Come here. Come on.
Let’s stand here.
I’m sorry.
It’s my fault.
I’m despicable.
I’m selfish.
I’m the reason our band broke up.
I abandoned you all.
You can kick and punch me all you like.
You can do anything to me.
I only ask for one thing.
Can I be your friend again?
Yes.
I was angry.
I was angry you didn’t tell me you were going to apply for jobs.
I would’ve supported you more.
Min.
But I was never angry that you left the band.
Stop feeling guilty already.
No matter what your dream is,
I’ll always support you.
I’m sorry.
Actually, there’s something I regret.
What is it?
I regret I didn’t get to dance with you one last time.
If you see me dance, you’ll be horrified.
Guys.
Would it be possible for you to help film a little something more?
Are you sure you still remember the moves?
We’ll see.
Achi.
Let’s go.
Yes!
(All’s well that ends well.)
(Rock and Min are friends again.)
(Even though they’ve chosen different paths,)
(I believe both will keep supporting each other.)
Come on.
Well done.
Thank you, Pai.
If it wasn’t for you, I wouldn’t have made up with Min
and I’d still feel guilty.
No need to thank me.
But don’t think that being an office worker is easier than being an idol.
Alright.
It’s okay though.
I know you can do it.
Hmm?
No matter how hard it is, I believe you’ll be successful one day
because I’ll always support you.
Got it?
Got it, Senior.
Very good, Junior.
Let’s go.
You can hold onto my waist
so you don’t fall off.
(I’m surprised this uncle knew how to say cool things.)
(Wait. Did Min say I was cool?)
(Yes!)
By the way,
since when did you watch my dance practice clips?
Don’t tell me you’re my secret fan.
I just came across them.
Really?
Are you sure you’re not my fan?
Hold on tight.
Today was so hectic
but it was buzzing in a good way.
Filming the dance was so much fun.
Too bad Rock isn’t coming home with us tonight.
If he was, we’d probably get to eat shabu again like the other day.
That was fun, wasn’t it?
Karan?
Is something wrong?
I like you, Achi.
♪ Message from my heart, want you to hear ♪
♪ My heart shouts out loud, I love you ♪
What a waste.
I put him in this team
because he’s good-looking
so he’d attract the client.
You’re drunk. Will you get home okay?
I feel so useless.
No.
At least you helped me.
The office is so lonely without Karan.
Pai.
I have something very important to talk about with Karan.
Achi, follow me.
I wouldn’t be able to make it in time.
[You didn’t choose the wrong path.
You just chose your dream.
Even if you could turn back time,
I believe that you’d still choose this path.]