Uncle.
How many times have I told you?
All you know is fighting and killing.
Put the gun down.
My nephew's young and hotheaded.
He's got a temper.
Dawa.
Apologize to the two bosses
right now.
I'm sorry.
That's not very sincere.
I was too impulsive just now.
Please forgive me.
That's a better attitude.
Now that's more like it.
Come on.
Do me a small favor.
Let's just let this
slide this time.
Hong Ye has spoken.
You're forgiven.
Hong Ye.
Where's Lao Zhang?
Lao Zhang?
Lao Zhang is...
Dr. Zhang.
Don't worry.
Right now,
he's at my place having tea.
I've got nothing but good tea.
Wanna see him?
Come.
Lao Zhang.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Of course I'm fine.
Hong Ye's been very hospitable.
He invited me here specially
to talk about working together.
I emailed you guys.
We didn't get it.
We got it.
What did Hong Ye invite you for?
Hong Ye's got great vision.
He wants a long-term partnership with us.
To a great partnership.
As for me,
I want to work with your company.
I know President Shen
has been making high-end chips.
And I happen to need them too.
High-end chips.
No problem.
But Lao Zhang
is our company's chief scientist.
If you want the chips,
he has to come back first.
But time waits for no one.
I hope to get your answer
by tomorrow.
Otherwise, what if Dr. Zhang
ends up liking it at my place?
I'll wait for your answer tomorrow.
Let's go.
Uncle.
I don't get it.
Why work with her?
Why not just kidnap her and be done?
Idiot.
How many times have I told you,
use your brain.
Do you know what I want?
I want their chips.
Chips are used to make high-tech weapons.
Once we get high-tech weapons,
beyond Dongba,
in all of Sanjiepo,
who would dare stand against us?
Use your head.
Go.
Hong Ye grabbed Dr. Zhang to threaten you
so he can get the chips
to make high-tech weapons.
Wars from now on will be different.
No more soldiers charging the front lines.
From now on,
it'll be robots
and smart drone warfare.
So the demand for high-tech chips is high.
So for now,
we need to stall Hong Ye,
and figure out a way to save Dr. Zhang.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't deliver on what I promised.
And I dragged you into all this.
Don't worry.
As long as I'm still standing,
no one's gonna hurt you.
Hello, Hong Ye.
Working together's fine.
President Shen is a smart woman.
I believe
President Shen would see reason.
But you also know
this deal is highly profitable.
Our company happens to need massive funding
for R&D and production.
So once the money comes in,
I want a 50-50 split.
Looks like President Shen knows
how much risk is involved in this business.
A 70-30 split.
You get 30 at most.
Fine.
But the chips
are under global scrutiny right now.
We can't afford any mistakes.
So I need time to clear the channels
before we can ship the chips.
Time's not a problem.
But I need to see first
who's in charge of the shipment.
Okay.
I'll arrange for him to come over ASAP.
Uncle, you're really splitting with her?
That woman is sharp.
She figured out our goal right away.
So what if she did?
This is Dongba.
She's gotta play by our rules.
What the hell do you know?
I'm not just after their chips.
What I want more is
their channels for shipping the chips.
We
use huge profits first
to reel her in.
Once the deal's done,
then
we call the shots.
Bro Xingchen.
Ma Liu.
You just got here, or you're leaving?
I'm going upstairs to grab something.
All right.
Do you know anyone reliable around here
who can pose as a distributor?
Hong Ye is sly as a fox.
Anyone we find in Dongba
won't be able to fool him.
How about this.
If we're putting on a show, we go all in.
Find someone from back home,
and bring them over.
Bro.
Send someone reliable on a trip to Dongba.
I need someone to pose as a distributor.
Sis!
Something's wrong!
Shen Xingyu's teaming up with Hong Ye.
Isn't Shen Xingyu's a tech company?
What are they teaming up on?
High-tech weapons.
Is that confirmed?
One hundred percent.
Shen Xingyu's sending people to Dongba right now.
What do we do?
Send people to stop them, now.
We can't let them work together.
Okay, okay.
They're already late.
Why aren't they here yet?
The rule of thumb in Dongba:
when things are unusual, something's fishy.
Looks like we
need a backup plan now.
Something must've happened.
President Shen.
President Shen!
Ma Liu.
What are you doing here?
What happened to you?
Lao Tian and I were on our way to find you.
The moment we stepped out, we got jumped.
Lao Tian's still laid up in the hospital.
Doc says he won't wake up for four or five days.
A woman called Sis Fei
told me to pass a message to you.
She said Dongba needs "balance."
And she said if certain things happen,
you won't be able to handle the fallout.
President Shen...
I saw Wu Di's ghost.
He's sitting right here.
If only you were still alive, Bro Wu Di.
Then I wouldn't have been beaten up like this.
Bro Wu Di...
I'm not used to men being this close to me.
He's not Zhao Wu Di.
They just look alike.
Alright.
Back to business.
Why's Sis Fei stirring things up?
If we team up with Hong Ye on arms right now,
then Sis Fei
will lose her foothold.
Of course she won't just sit back.
I won't let a few of her words
intimidate me.
Enough.
With Sis Fei,
we'll send someone to explain later.
Our top priority right now is
to find someone to pose as the distributor.
If it's someone who's been laying low
in Dongba, wouldn't it seem
more convincing to Hong Ye?
Me?
You've gotta be kidding.
Hong Ye and Dawa have both seen me.
You can do it.
You look so much like Bro Wu Di.
You could pretend to be him.
Be President Shen's temporary husband.
Everyone here knows I'm a waiter.
They won't buy it.
That's why we need
to spin a good story.
Miss Shen.
Hong Ye sent me to collect the debt.