Break!
I didn't expect you to really be Zhao Wudi.
You're actually still alive.
Not only am I not dead,
but I also got my memory back.
Xingyu.
How could Xingyu be you?
Useless trash.
You don't seriously think
that you've woken up from the dream, do you?
That was just the appetizer.
Starting now,
begins the real hellish nightmare.
So what if you got your memory back?
Your combat instincts
have only recovered to
fifty percent.
In my domain,
you're as weak as a bug.
Didn't you want to protect Shen Xingyu?
Too bad.
You can't do anything.
Wudi.
Xingyu.
Save me.
No... save me.
Xingyu!
No!
Zhao Wudi.
Watch the woman you love
die because of you.
Xingyu! Wudi!
Wudi!
Zhao Wudi,
this is your fate.
Impossible!
You're a monster.
Now you can tell me
who hired you, right?
It was...
It was Dawa.
General.
That hypnotist,
is he reliable?
I looked into it.
He's extremely good.
Even if Zhao Wudi doesn't die this time,
he'll end up a vegetable.
He'll never wake up again.
Who says I won't wake up?
Guards!
Somebody, get in here!
Stop yelling.
They're all asleep.
How are you okay?
The hypnotist.
Who found him?
I did.
I found him.
With that pig brain of yours,
how could you possibly find
a hypnotist that good?
Talk.
Who's been calling the shots behind you?
You dare look down on me?
Yeah, I look down on you.
I'll talk.
It's...
Welcome back.
Zhao Wudi.
A Li.
Xingyu
Someone's messing around behind the scenes
Trying to sabotage tomorrow's deal
Dawa's already been silenced
Dawa's dead
He's not far from it.
Laiya
Also known as A Li
She injected him with a neurotoxin
We don't know if Dawa
Will ever wake up
But
Doesn't A Li just work for money?
Then someone else must be behind it
Why are you looking at me?
Even if there is a mastermind
It must be someone you guys know
What does that have to do with me?
A guy like Dawa has enemies everywhere
It's completely normal for him to be set up
Besides
The time A Li went undercover beside Dawa
coincides with when you came to Dongba
So wasn't this your doing?
No way
The first time I met her, Xingyu was with me
You're just making it more obvious
A guy who doesn't even know who he is,
How am I supposed to trust you?
Enough
Stop arguing
Let's worry about
Tomorrow's deal first, okay?
As long as our people don't have ulterior motives,
The deal won't go wrong
I don't care who's behind this
Tomorrow's deal
Must succeed
and cannot fail
Dr. Zhang's life depends on it
As do all of our lives
Xingyu's right
Xingyu
I should go with you tomorrow
I don't trust this kid
Bro
Hong Ye only recognizes him
It's best you don't show your face
No,
Why is it bad for me to show my face?
Then why does Hong Ye insist on seeing him?
What Hong Ye cares about is
Whether the deal goes through
What does that have to do with him?
How am I worse than him?
Bro
You're our ace
You're the best brother in the world
But you also have to know
An ace should be held close to the chest,
so at the very end,
it can be played.
Right?
If you want to go with him
Why not just say so?
I'm your brother
You think sweet talk will brush me off?
But I have to run perimeter support tomorrow
Otherwise, I'll be worried
Fine
And you
Keep a close eye on my sister tomorrow
If she loses even a single hair
I'll make you pay
Don't worry
As long as I'm here
I won't let anyone
harm a single hair on her head
Hong Ye, they're here
The roads were rough
Sorry to keep you waiting, Hong Ye
Have a seat
The chips are here
The first batch
Eight thousand in total
Any more
would be too hard to transport
Hong Ye
To a pleasant partnership
No rush
I just want to ask
About my nephew, Dawa
What happened to him?
General Dawa
You don't know, President Shen?
Didn't you
see him yesterday?
Yes
I did see General Dawa yesterday
Because someone tried to kill me,
I went to ask the general about it
What I didn't expect was
for his housekeeper to suddenly attack him
I tried to catch her
But unfortunately, she got away
Then how do you explain this?
Hong Ye
You suspect she and I are accomplices
Laiya, also known as A Li
The relationship between her and me
is that of assassin and target
Someone as smart as you, Hong Ye,
wouldn't fail to see
the flaws in that logic, right?
Are you saying what I just said
Was wrong?
A Li
is someone who only cares about money
As long as the price is right,
She'll do anything
Besides
If Wudi wanted him dead
Back when General Dawa
first attacked me,
he would've killed him already
He wouldn't be alive today
Then this is
clearly a frame-up
What's the motive?
Isn't that obvious?
They obviously don't want our deal to happen.
Look at this.
Hong Ye.
Given how things look,
are you trying to end the partnership?
No, no, not at all.
Put it down, put it down.
The weather in Dongba,
it changes in the blink of an eye.
But my deal with President Shen
will absolutely not change.
Then I've got an idea.
Wait till Dawa wakes up.
Hong Ye, you can ask him yourself.
It won't be too late to make the deal then.
It's a misunderstanding.
President Shen.
Let's proceed with the deal.
Let me introduce someone to you all.
This gentleman here
is
the renowned chip expert,
Dr. Martin.
He's been in the global market
for decades.
He's a leading authority in the field.
So,
for this deal,
we'll have
Dr. Martin
verify the goods.
The renowned Dr. Martin.
I didn't expect to meet you on such an occasion.
Xingyu Optoelectronics
is just
a small mainland company.
The brand's not well-known.
Its technology is
average at best.
I don't think they can make
any good chips.
They don't have anything good.
Dr. Ma,
Jumping to conclusions without testing them
is a bit too hostile, isn't it?
It's not Dr. Ma.
It's Dr. Martin.
Dr. Martin.
Got it?
So pretentious.
Sorry about that.
My English isn't very good.
I can't remember the names of those who worship foreigners.
Hong Ye.
Let's just get started.
Let's see.
Crap.
The chips in the case,
except for the one I'm holding,
are all fake.
What did I tell you?
It can't even power up the machine.
Hong Ye,
I advise you to switch partners while you still can.
This one
is way too low-end.
Is that so?
What's the problem?
Let me take a look.
Dr. Ma,
you've been abroad too long.
You can't even read Chinese characters anymore.
It says "unlock" right here.
After you unlock it,
it starts right up, see?
Take another look.
For the test,
I have to do it myself.
That last one
doesn't count.
Hong Ye,
Such a big deal,
and you're keeping it all to yourself?
That's not very fair, is it?
Sure is lively here today.
Feifei.
Are you turning against me now?
Do you know what it'll cost you?
Of course I know.
And I know even better
the price of letting you take
all these weapons away.
I'd be dead for sure.