Set the bait first
so we can cast the net for a big catch
Captain Cangming
Black Bat Special Operations Team
Here to provide backup
Black Bat Assault Team
Black Bat Defense Team
Here to provide backup
Black Bat Demolition Team
Ma Liu
Leaving without even saying goodbye
That's not very brotherly of you
Brother Wu Di
Our run ends here
Ends here?
So let's part ways here
Brother
Even if I wanted to let you go
would the people you killed
agree to it?
Brother Wu Di
I'm just messing with you
Look, I've got nothing now
I can only go back to being a lowly guard
Just let me go, okay?
Let you go?
I came all the way to Dongba
and suffered through so much
just to hunt you down
And now you're telling me
to let you go?
Let you go?
So you can go out and harm more people?
Zhao Wu Di
You really think I came
completely unprepared?
I've already injected myself
with ten times the Wushuang
Now I'm faster than you
and stronger
Zhao Wu Di
That's cheating!
I told you
what era do you think this is?
Still using your fists?
Why not use a gun?
But you're Zhao Wu Di
the toughest of them all
Zhao Wu Di!
You wanna get hit, huh?
Fine
Then I'll give you what you want
Baring his teeth
Local police will be here soon to take over
Wu Di
You did a great job this time
Not at all
Brother Xingchen
It's thanks to you guys
arriving in time
Oh, right
the Death Jungle lab
what do we do about it now?
I've already sent a Black Bat
squad over there
Death Jungle is in the middle of nowhere
It's perfect for
illegal activities
I'm worried that after we leave
that place
will start up again
So I told them specifically
to raze it to the ground
We were thinking the same thing
Fatty
You're awake
Zhao Wu Di
Even if you caught me
you think this is over?
Don't you worry about that
Zhao Wu Di
Even if you catch me
someone stronger will come for you
None of you will get away
Then let them all come
We'll be right here waiting
Zhao Wu Di
You have no idea
how powerful the force behind me is
how terrifyingly strong they are
They're not people you can mess with
You talk too damn much
Mission accomplished
Pack it up
Let's go home
Heading home
How was the banquet
this afternoon?
Nice having cute guys around, huh?
Yeah?
I added tons of cute guys on WeChat
Tomato
The whitening products are ready
Ladies
Are these crappy shoes even wearable?
Nida
We're eating
Ma'am
What?
Nice legs
Mind taking them down, please?
Fine
Let's drink
Come on
Cheers
Nida
Do you want to pick
a local name?
Sure, sure!
Sister Xingyu, you're the most educated
Why don't you give me one?
Wu Di brought you back
Let him name you
I'm just a lowly guard
I don't know how to name people
What's wrong with being a guard?
Since you call him your master
you might as well take his last name
Okay, then what should I be called?
Just call her
How about Zhao Wuqing?
That's a good name
Perfect for your savage bloodline
That way, if someday
you run into a scumbag
and he tricks you
so you don't beat him to death again
Okay!
Then from now on I'll be
Zhao Wuqing
Zhao Wu Di
When a few women get together
the whole world goes quiet.
This is insane.
You attracted all these girls yourself.
I'm meeting your needs.
Isn't that good?
I swear.
I really didn't know
it'd turn into this.
I didn't mean to invite this many people.
But...
somehow more and more just showed up.
More and more.
Then I guess...
I wrongly blamed you.
Zhao Wu Di!
Listen to me.
I'm Shen Xingyu.
I'd rather be widowed
than divorced.
Cut ties with all your little flings
completely, right now.
Shen Xingyu...
Whether I'm Zhao Wu Di
or A-Di,
I'll fall in love with you again and again.
Fine.
I'll trust you one more time.
Protect me.
Five million.
Until I go down,
no one can hurt you.
Right now, you're playing
my husband.
You need to get used to
being intimate with me.
Wu Di, you're back.