I will kill the baby.
I can't do it.
How will I ever take revenge?
You're being so loud. Shut up.
Shut up! Shut the hell up!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Hello? Makoto?
Yep.
What time will you be back?
Okay. See you soon.
So she doesn't love her child at all.
Unbelievable.
This changes everything for us.
Well, she's a true monster, no doubt.
I guess there's no point
in killing the baby.
I agree.
Are you relieved?
What?
"No matter the reason,
I feel awful killing an innocent child."
Is that what you think?
No!
That's not…
Did you forget how much you suffered?
SUSPECT OF MURDER CASE RUNAWAY
POSSIBLE SUICIDE BY JUMPING…
That's terrifying…
-What is that?
-I'm scared!
So creepy…
Geez, she made me jump! What the hell?
She'll hear you!
-What a freak!
-Creepy!
-A mummy?
-Right?
-It's a mummy!
-Terrifying…
RECITAL
FEBRUARY 8TH, 2014
A NEW CLASSICAL PRINCESS
LIKE PARENT, LIKE CHILD
Our ultimate goals
are to expose all of Rena's crimes
and make her atone for sins,
and also…
I know!
I'll show her what true hell is like.
I'll find another weakness of hers.
Okay.
I do wonder though…
Why hasn't she killed Kokoro already?
What?
She's murdered so many people
and managed to cover up all of them.
She definitely could've done
the same with Kokoro.
So why keep her alive?
It's probably…
because she knows
she as a mother can be blamed
or become a prime suspect.
Not anymore though.
She can blame it on you.
Don't let that monster out of your sight.
I won't.
I've reached my limit.
I was playing the piano
when the bed rail fell off.
Kokoro fell off the bed and died!
Good morning.
Oh, right!
I'm so sorry!
I shouldn't have left it here.
My apologies.
Yeah. If it fell,
it could've been a disaster.
I'm very sorry.
Hello? Yuki?
I'll come out.
I need to go pick up my dress.
Okay. See you later!
Recently…
she calms down when I hold her.
I guess Kokoro likes me.
Rena's most prized possession…
Her assets and income?
If I take all that away…
No. Her family is rich anyway,
and she'd easily find
another income source.
What about her social status and value?
What if I just expose her
as a murderer online?
I truly regret
the trouble and confusion…
No.
She's too good at lying.
What about her husband, Makoto？
Although, she doesn't even love
her own child.
Does she actually love her husband?
Would she truly despair if she lost him?
Rena?
No. It's not…
Welcome home.
Is something wrong?
Uh, no.
Rena told me I can use
the record player anytime.
Oh, yeah. That's totally fine.
Sorry to worry you.
Ah…
Hey, Kokoro!
You're awake!
Oh, Kokoro…
You seem happy!
Look! What's this?
Makoto absolutely loves that baby to bits.
A very devoted dad.
That's normal. It's his own daughter.
But Rena once said
Makoto is incapable
of genuinely loving someone.
Is it possible
that Makoto's just like Rena?
Or having a child
made him capable of love?
Hm? What's wrong?
Uh…
Hang on.
Wait…
Did you just roll over?
Kokoro rolled over by herself!
Oh, wow! That's great.
Is something wrong?
No… Nothing.
I'm back!
Makoto! Welcome back!
-You won't believe this!
-Huh?
Kokoro just rolled over by herself
for the first time!
-Really? That's amazing!
-Right?
A cake to celebrate?
Sounds good.
Shall we order takeout as well?
-Yes! Like a little party!
-Yeah.
Would you like to join us too,
Ms. Tachibana?
Uh…
I'd love to.
-Yay! How exciting!
-Yeah.
-I'll go arrange stuff now!
-Okay.
Well done, Kokoro. You did it!
Do you think we have enough cake?
We should! Kokoro can't eat it yet!
True.
-I'll call when I'm done shopping.
-Okay!
Ask for a message on the cake, too!
How about…
"She rolled over!"
Will do!
We should go, too.
Okay.
What would you like to eat?
Tell me what you like!
No, I feel bad.
-Please choose what you two like!
-But…
I want you to be part of the celebration!
Okay. Well…
-In that case…
-I know!
There's a new Italian restaurant
that opened last week!
I heard it's very popular…
Sorry! Are you okay?
Yes…
Thank god.
Makoto! Makoto, are you okay?
-I'm fine.
-Can you move?
-Yeah…
-Thank goodness!
-Are you sure you're okay?
-Yeah, thanks.
I'm just glad that
you're okay!
Makoto…
I knew it.
RENA HANAI
So her most prized possession
is her husband.
She had the baby
just so he loves her more.
Rena's love for Makoto
seems genuine.
I realize now that Rena lied to my face.
Because…
she didn't want him to get taken away.
Makoto's incapable
of loving someone.
He never can.
A living hell for Rena…
is to live without Makoto.
Makoto Hanai, 30 years old.
A florist.
Has known Rena for over 20 years.
When he was 11,
his mother died.
He was adopted by his relative after that.
Fastest way of getting rid of Makoto
is to kill him, you know.
Wait…
We can kill him anytime if needed.
But what would be worse for Rena
is probably if he told her
he wants a divorce.
In that case,
we'll make him hate her first.
Show Makoto proof that Rena is actually
a vicious killer.
No, not yet!
I'm not ready.
Sorry for the wait!
That looks great!
I have good news.
Thankfully…
With Botanical has asked us
to do another product collaboration!
-Yes!
-Amazing!
I'm so relieved!
-Hey, Rena.
-Yes?
-Look over there.
-There?
This is a present for you.
Thank you, Nao!
You said you wanted some
when you came to our place, so….
I hope you like them!
Tomomi, you remembered that?
I'm so happy!
-I'm glad!
-Thank you, Nao!
Wow, look at that!
Can you catch them, Nao?
Can you? Oh, Almost! Try again!
Ms. Tomomi,
could I ask you about something?
Yes. What's up?
Rena's feeling down
since the With Botanical incident, and…
I was thinking about planning
a surprise party for her birthday.
That sounds lovely! Let's do it!
I need to know her schedule
so I was wondering
if you could ask Makoto about it?
Okay!
I'll ask him now!
-Makoto!
-Yes?
For Rena's upcoming birthday,
we want to surprise her with a party
to cheer her up.
-Wow, really?
-Yes!
She would absolutely love that!
Great!
Was it the 26th?
Yes, it is.
-Start from noon?
-That's quite early!
Rena! You made me jump!
Don't do that!
Tomomi, what were you talking
to Makoto about?
What?
Oh, it was nothing!
Uh, it was…
about flowers!
I want to send some to my friend!
Oh, Makoto!
Thanks again for helping me
with my friend's bouquet.
Thanks for the order.
I hope she likes it.
Me too.
-Oh, that's it?
-Yep!
That's all?
Good morning.
Ms. Tachibana?
Can I help you?
There's something…
I want to talk to you about.
It's regarding Rena.
Ms. Tachibana.
Yes?
I'm sorry but…
I need you
to quit.
-I'm Bando from class A, third year.
-I'm Hanai.
Please let me keep the job!
So that was a lie…
Subtitle translation by: Emily Johnson