Professional Single
Episode 12
Are you OK?
Keep it up.
You need to grow higher,
or you'll be our burden.
How could you say that?
Look at Qin and me,
am I right?
Essence is made from concentrate.
Didn't sleep well?
I thought about it thoroughly last night.
What happened between us
wasn't the arrangement of fate.
You may have missed your chance
and can't get it back,
but I still have a chance.
I can change my fate.
That's what you reckon?
Right.
Am I wrong?
You're really pig-headed.
What?
Why did you make personal attack?
Yuan Qian.
Qin Shen.
Why didn't you come to the party yesterday?
You should've been the stars of it.
I was tied up yesterday.
Yuan Qian,
just tell me
if you are busy next time.
I wasn't familiar with them,
I wouldn't have gone there
if I have known you weren't show up.
I was forced to drink too much.
It was horrible!
Well...
It has nothing to do
with her.
I didn't mean that.
It sounds like that to me.
The teacher's coming.
Time for class.
You did that to cover up what happened last night,
or
to protect me?
Take a guess.
How could I get it?
What's the hurry?
Yuan Qian,
I know you really want to help me,
and I appreciate that.
But I can't
take the money.
It's for your mother,
not for you.
What's the difference
between giving it to her or me?
You don't have to do this,
I have money.
Keep it for yourself.
I'm lending it to you,
not giving it to you,
you'll give it back with interests.
Then I have another reason to reject it.
Why should I live with a loan
when I'm not short of money?
Take it,
keep it safe.
By the way,
your new electives are all on weekends,
so is the coming orienteering.
You now have the money,
so stop doing your part-time job
and concentrate on your classes.
Are you sure you don't need it?
I'm sure.
Trust me.
Stop pulling my hair!
See you.
Be a good student.
Bye.
Mom,
did you sell your grandpa's watch?
Sorry, mom.
I'm sure
I can redeem the watch
when I get the prize money
after the competition.
It was my fault,
I shouldn't have accepted Yuan Qian's money.
You're friends,
it would hurt your pride
if we use her money.
I didn't mean that,
I have confident in myself,
I'll win the competition.
It was all my fault.
It's OK to sold the watch,
I just feel so bad
that I can't help you.
If I wasn't so capricious
to kept you with me...
No!
Mom,
thank you for always supporting my dream.
I miss your Braised Spare Ribs in Brown Sauce,
can I have it tonight?
Then I'll come home tonight.
OK.
So it's settled.
Bye.
I still remember we were carefree and happy
when we were in high school.
Sometimes I really hope
nothing changes when I wake up,
and we're still in high school.
Right.
But there's no going back.
There is,
if we want to.
Will you come to my birthday tonight?
Will Qin Shen come too?
You didn't invite him?
I wanted to,
but I'm afraid he won't come.
Do you mind if I invite him?
How could it be?
It's fine.
We can celebrate together.
Isn't it?
That's what I'm thinking about.
We can have a good talk
by this chance
to resolve our misunderstandings.
But I don't know what to do
if he refused me,
could you invite him for me?
That's out of my capability.
But...
But what?
Qin Shen's close to Yuan Qian lately.
If we couldn't find Qin Shen during activities,
we'd look for Yuan Qian.
If Yuan Qian show up,
Qin Shen will come, too.
Why don't you invite Yuan Qian then?
You mean Qin Shen likes Yuan Qian?
I'm not sure.
You have to ask Qin Shen.
I see.
Hey, Yuan Qian,
I heard you've quit the job.
I got too many classes recently,
I don't have time for it.
I see.
By the way,
have you lost a book on oil painting
in the training school?
I saw the stamp of our library on its back.
Right, I was wondering where it is,
so I've lost it there.
I knew it's yours,
so I've brought it back.
Ling Wei, are you in the dorm now?
I'll go for it
because it'll expire tomorrow.
I... I'm outside now.
It's fine, I'll go tonight.
Tomorrow's also fine.
I won't go back tonight,
and I don't know when will I tomorrow.
Can you come out to take it?
OK, where should I find you?
Windsor KTV.
Seven o'clock tonight.
OK, see you tonight.
Why's she in a KTV?
Qin Shen,
my classmates will come
to celebrate my birthday tonight.
Why don't you come to?
I'm busy.
Yuan Qian will come, too.
What're you planning for?
Do you think
there's a plan in everything I do?
Yuan Qian is my friend,
I just want to celebrate my birthday with her.
Am I wrong?
Seven o'clock tonight.
Windsor KTV.
You had dinner?
Yes.
What?
I mean supper.
You're inviting me for a supper?
It's two o'clock, how could we have it now?
Shall we have supper together?
I can't.
I'm engaged tonight.
Maybe tomorrow?
Engaged in what?
You're so interested in me suddenly,
are you...
See you.
Order as you like, make yourselves at home.
I'm putting on weight.
You haven't changed a little bit.
You're flattering me.
No,
you're as cute as before.
Yuan Qian.
Come here.
I'm here for the book.
I'll give you later, come on in.
Ling Wei,
it's your birthday today?
I'm sorry, I didn't know!
I didn't bring you a gift.
I didn't tell you because I didn't want you to make a cost.
I'm so happy you're here.
Have a seat.
I'll meet the others.
OK, I won't bother you.
Yuan Qian!
Jia Sicheng?
Why're you here?
This way, here's a room for you.
Come on!
Hold on.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Sit here.
I don't think it's proper.
Really? Are you sure?
I've no idea.
It's fine.
I'll sit here.
Sit there if there's a room.
Next time when you dragging me,
could you tell yourself this's a person, not a sack?
Sorry.
Why're you here?
Haven't I told you I'm engaged?
Come on, cheers!
Cheers!
Take whatever you like,
it's a treatment for accompanying me.
Then I should thank you.
By the way,
why're you here?
Qin Shen, Ling Wei and I
were classmates in high school.
You're their classmates, too?
Yes.
I thought you'd be surprised
that they were classmates.
No.
Ling Wei has told me about it.
Actually I'm pretty surprised that Qin Shen came.
It's normal for Qin Shen to come
since they were classmates.
I'm sure it's normal since he used to
care about her.
Yuan Qian,
take whatever you want.
Make yourself at home,
it's Ling Wei's treat anyway.
She won't change her frayed wallet
because it was a present from Qin Shen.
Qin Shen has sent Ling Wei a wallet?
Yes.
She's always taking it with her.
I'm sure there's something between them.
She'd believe those words.
Here're snacks!
Take some.
Boys! Bottoms up!
Thanks.
Open it yourself.
Have some snacks.
Jia Sicheng, hurry!
Hurry up!
All right.
Have some snacks.
I just want to put the card back.
I can do it, thanks.
There he comes.
Drink it first.
OK.
Then it's Ling Wei's turn.
Ling Wei's turn?
I'll try this.
Here's your juice.
All right!
Ling Wei,
the one on your left should play Truth or Dare.
Then I'll ask.
Listen,
who's your favorite person?
My parents.
They don't count,
I mean boys.
Then
it's Xiao Jing.
He doesn't count either,
you admire him at most
since he's popular.
Then I've no idea,
maybe I don't have one.
My favorite thing is study.
Yuan Qian, can you be serious?
Stop beating around the bush!
OK, let her be.
Maybe she doesn't want to say
because he's here.
She'll be embarrassed to do so.
Who's this guy here?
Maybe it's me!
Forget it, give me a break!
Actually I think it's normal
to have no one to like.
Let's go on.
OK, the next is Dai Yaqing.
My turn?
Yes.
Let's go.
OK.
All shall drink up.
Come on!
I told you I'm not planning for anything!
Qin Shen,
you never came to my birthday party before.
If I didn't tell you Yuan Qian would come,
you'd never be here!
I know you're here for her,
but why're you so concerned?
You think I'll eat her alive?
You know it clearly
what you're planning for.
What can I do to win your trust?
Like I told you, I'm not planning for anything!
I like Yuan Qian,
I'm taking her as my friend.
I just want her
to join my birthday party!
I just want
to make up with you
by inviting you here.
We don't have to be enemies.
Can't we even be friends
if we can't be a couple?
You should leave Yuan Qian alone,
she's not good at your games.
Have this.
Thanks.
All right.
Hi,
I'm leaving.
Come on!
You should drink less.
Ling Wei,
it's late, I should go back.
Yuan Qian.
Yuan Qian, I'm sorry.
I lied to you.
Do you know it?
I still like him.
I've been liking him for three years.
I've lost myself in this affection.
I...
I really afraid
that you'll say
you like him, too.
But
I... I know...
I know I should wish you two happy.
But I really can't do it.
Why wouldn't he look into my eyes?
Why did he always wrong me?
Did I do anything wrong?
Yuan Qian.
Could you tell me
what should I do
to make him like me?
Dai Yaqing!
Ling Wei, let Dai Yaqing take you back.
Have a good rest, OK?
She's so drunk?
I'll handle this.
She's yours.
You can go back.
Are you alright?
Let's go back, OK?
I won't go back.
I don't want to.
What?
Nothing.
Split it out.
Have you
being with Lin Wei before?
No.
Then did she like you so much
and chased you for long?
Does that matter you?
No.
Then why're you asking?
I...
I'm just curious.
You know it.
He's so changeable,
what's in his mind?
He has nothing else to do?
Whatever!
I'll be a fool if I talk to him!
Are you asleep?
No, you?
No, not decent.
Seems like a perfunctory answer.
What if he won't reply?
I am.
Sorry to bother you.
That's it?
Forget it,
I shouldn't have expectations on a straight man!
Good night!
He's not totally naive.
What're you doing now?
Sleeping?
So early?
I'm too tired today
and I had some beer.
Why did you drink?
It's Ling Wei's birthday.
By the way,
I've got good news for you.
Have a guess?
I'm sleeping, let's talk tomorrow.
I’m gonna let you go.
Song Siyi is so annoying!
So childish!
Where's Song?
I'll go find him.
All right,
thank you for achieving
such a good result,
I'll propose a toast for you on behalf of the company.
Come on.
Cheers.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
Talking to your mother?
The company wants to know
the date you go back.
Tomorrow then.
Tomorrow?
There's only one early flight tomorrow!
It's fine.
I'll take that early flight.
Won't you sleep?
It'll be dawn when we go back!
I really want to see someone right now,
though she's ungrateful.
Part-time sister?
Hurry, we're all waiting for you.
Qin!
Come here!
Your rival in love is awesome!
Congratulations on Song Siyi
for winning the sculling!
It's unexpected
that Song Siyi could win this time,
the audience there went crazy!
No just them,
so will the school leaders!
First, I want to thank my coach and teammates,
then,
I want to thank a girl.
Yuan Qian!
Get down here! Big news!
Come here, all of you!
Check this out!
What's the fuss?
Come on!
She even did part-time job
when she was free.
Come on.
Without her,
I don't think I can achieve this result.
What's your relationship?
She's your girlfriend?
Tell us, Mr. Song!
What's your relationship?
Yes, tell us!
She's
a very special person to me.
Mr. Song,
did you attend
this competition for her?
Yuan Qian?
Sculling's boring, forget it.
He's ordinary.
Just an ordinary guy.
Qin?
Yuan Qian!
You're the one he was speaking of!
Right?
Oh, no!
I'll change my side.
Song Siyi, you're so romantic!
He's purely expressing his love!
Could you think for my clothes?
Qin Shen, I'm sorry.
I'm standing on Song's side now.
What's the big deal?
Isn't it just a live love-expressing spot?
Choose Song Siyi, I back you up!
What're you talking about?
We're good friends
since childhood!
This is normal.
You've grown up together!
That's an innocent relation.
I even saw him wearing open-backed pants then,
we're just like relatives!
But I didn't expect he'd win,
that's awesome.
Qin,
is it Yuan Qian your rival in love referred to?
She has been active in part-time job.
Didn't she work as
a teacher with you?
Why should I care?
Go on.
You'll be regret
when she's with your rival.
Nature’s calling.
Don't guess if you don't want to,
I'll tell you now.
I...
I've seen your interview.
Congratulations! Champion!
Could you stop saying
such things to set me up?
I'm afraid I'll be killed by your girl fans!
Sorry!
The subscriber you dialed is busy now...
Come on, pick it up.
Why did he call me?
Sorry!
The subscriber you dialed is busy now,
please redial later. Sorry...
Let me take this.
Thanks.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Song Siyi, the guy from the Sports Department,
did he mean Yuan Qian in the interview?
I knew you were planning something
when you helped me!
Did he?
Yes.
I knew it!
Song Siyi was so cool!
The girls of our room
were so excited that we yelled
when we were watching his game video yesterday.
We almost became his fans.
To think you're a classmate of Qin!
Is that Song prettier than Qin?
Song Siyi's pretty, OK?
The most important thing is
Song Siyi has an advantage
which Qin Shen doesn't have at all.
Impossible!
Our Qin has every advantages
Song Siyi possesses!
Absolutely impossible!
Activeness!
Ac...
activeness?
Girls are easy to chase.
Guys need to constantly
draw their attention.
Being pretty alone won't work.
Speaking of drawing attention,
our Qin
draws more than that Song!
It's hard for him to see Yuan Qian.
But our Qin
can show up in front of her every day.
You're all brawn and no brains!
It's really boring
to talk gossips with you!
Stop beating me!
What're you doing?
Why're you on my seat?
I've got more mud,
here's some for you.
Thank you, bro.
I've learned something
when I'm talking to her.
I think she has the point.
You should be more active.
You need the mud?
I'm good.
This guy's really hopeless.
What're you doing?
Homework.
I mean what're you making?
Two swans rubbing their necks.
Now the mud cake's ready,
so are the paper fillers.
Pack the cake with paper.
Mind the shape,
then bend the iron wire into the shape of swan necks.
Qin Shen,
I don't have to be No.1.
Why don't you do yours now,
I'll ask you if I have any questions.
You're giving me
enormous pressure by standing here.
How could I make a good work then?
You're giving me more pressure
than Prof. Jin.
Girls are easy to chase.
Guys need to constantly
draw their attention.
Being pretty alone won't work.
Junk science!
Wait a moment.
You're not together yet,
why're you going to separate?
The neck won't stand,
I did it like Qin Shen said.
Hello?
Song Siyi,
what's up?
Relax,
I won't forget your treat.
Wait, I'll call you later.
I've got something to do.
Wait!
My...
my male swan's neck
just won't stand.
Can you help me?
I make it as what you told me.
This's swans rubbing their necks,
but this one won't stand.
You've used wrong type of wire.
It's too thin to hold the neck.
What shall I do?
Don't tell me I have to remake it.
You may if you have time.
I'm so busy lately,
how could this happen to me?
I...
You took part-time jobs for Song Siyi?
Well,
something happened to him recently.
I have to help him.
You're friends since childhood?
No.
Well, sort of.
We grew up together.
You quite cares about him.
We're good friends,
we should help each other.
Is that so?
Easy!
You!
It's broken!
This...
I want to make swans rubbing necks,
now it looks like a Spiced Duck Neck!
Sorry, I was trying too hard.
What shall I do?
I have to hand in it this afternoon!
Rubbing necks has another meaning: mating.
It's indecent.
Why don't you call it The Death of Swan?
It's touching and beautiful, and elegant.
They're same.
In which way?
Aren't they?
Take your hands away.
What's this?
Will Prof. Jin think
I'm too perfunctory?
Yuan Qian,
do you think he won't kick your ass?
What's this?
Putting a dead swan with a living one?
This's two swans rubbing necks!
Yuan Qian,
you may insult my grade,
but you can't insult my eye sight!
I've passed the English test
by peeping multiple-choice questions
with these sharp eyes!
I...
Professor!
We're ready!
Please check these.
I think it's hard to see
this kind of immature work
with a good shape.
I can tell
No.1 will be Qin again,
no surprise.
Tell me.
Why did you break my swan's neck?
Now one's dead and one's alive,
it's ridiculous!
Didn't I tell you?
Knock it off!
That's absurd.
Who knows rubbing necks means mating?
Besides, even it means mating,
it's noble
because it can produce lives.
I saw it from the prospect of art.
Yuan Qian, come here!
Is your swan died?
It... it...
Nice work, you've made progress.
The Death of Swan.
Swans are strictly monogamous.
If one dies,
another will fast
to die for its lover.
Yuan Qian
has grabbed this emotion
to create the work.
It's striking.
It has more pathos
than normal rubbing necks.
Good!
Very good!
What's that expression?
Did I explain it wrong?
Right!
Quite right!
That's what I'm thinking about!
Very good,
good job.
Who made this pig?
Me.
You made it for bakery?
No.
Isn't it good?
Look at its smooth skin.
Smooth skin.