The Long Ballad
Episode 18
That's weird.
Aunt Ping's mouth is broken.
I'm afraid she'll see Wan Yin Xing's misunderstanding.
That's bad.
The Long Ballad
I gave you the hairpin before I went out.
Why didn't you take it?
Who are you?
Go away!
Why did you get up so late?
Aunt Ping has gone out.
She asked me to give it to you.
My hand is hurt.
It's late.
I'll go back to my room.
Chu, do you really like her?
The Long Ballad
I can't go on like this.
Since I know it's a bad omen,
I should have made an early decision.
So you've got the general of the Li family.
Mother, go and get the matchmaker to propose to her.
Don't worry.
Girls don't know how to be reserved.
Besides, Li Zhen has a bright future.
He has a lower family background.
Even if he wants to propose,
he has to let them propose first.
Don't worry.
Okay, I got it, mother.
Mother, I like the second lady of the Li family.
Please help me.
You mean that girl?
She's the daughter of the Li family.
The second lady, Li Chuchu.
Why does this girl look familiar?
I think I've seen her somewhere before.
It's okay to marry her back.
But the girl's face looks really familiar.
I mean,
I want to marry her as a wife.
Are you crazy?
As long as I'm alive,
you can't decide your marriage.
Chu, what should I do with you?
Brother, do you have to go to war?
I can't bear to leave you.
I'll be back when the war is over.
Okay.
Chu.
Brother, take this hairpin back.
You want to draw the whole world for me, right?
Yes.
You're so cruel to me.
Just for Lin Xiaoguo.
If I lose you,
I won't allow you to be together.
If brother is a guest,
and teach us to separate,
I'll miss him all my life.
You know that.
Lin Xiaoguo
Do you really hate me so much?
Then why do you keep this hairpin?
I just...
I just want to return it to you.
If you really hate me so much,
then kill me.
Let's go.
Kill her.
Chu,
what do you believe in?
You still need me.
Give me your hand.
I beg you, don't leave me.
Only if you marry Lin Xiaoguo,
can you really feel safe.
I'll never
betray you.
Miss.
Is the news reliable?
The people in Zhuangzi received the good news
that we sent in time.
It won't be fake.
I'll go and check.
Okay.
I'll go now.
It won't be fake.
General.
You're hurt.
It doesn't matter.
What happened?
We found the general's assistant general.
He has something important.
Sister,
please find a way to save my mother.
What happened to her?
She's seriously ill in Zhuangzi.
There's no doctor there.
She's going to die.
But...
But it's so far away.
What can I do?
Now that you're happy with your brother,
and you're taking care of Young Master Lin,
how can you not have a good solution?
I'm afraid you're the only one in your heart.
You don't have a mother.
You...
You're so selfish.
I didn't think you and Aunt...
No.
Now that you're sick,
you should go with those
who are useful to us.
No.
I won't go even if I die.
Don't pretend to be so serious.
You should think about your sister and aunt.
If you don't want to go,
you'll have to sell out all three of them.
I...
I won't go.
I will go.
But you have to...
I will sell...
I will sell my body.
Otherwise,
I'd rather die.
If it wasn't for you and Aunt,
how could I have lost you?
You're so stupid.
Sister,
I'm sorry.
No matter what,
I'll just die.
Peike,
I...
Take me to my home.
I've been here all day.
But you still saw me.
At this moment,
we are all the concubines of the General's Mansion.
Peike,
where are you going?
If you want to save your mother,
you should take something important with you.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.