The Long Ballad
Episode 17
Yu Niang, you hit me!
You are really going to kill your second sister!
It's my second sister and your big brother!
I'm not talking nonsense!
You still say that!
You hit me! You hit me to death!
You came to me
because you think your second sister is more important than me.
But why do all of you like Li Chu Ci?
Then what am I?
No, no, no, no.
I don't want to see you!
Sister.
From now on,
you only have one daughter.
Choose her or choose me.
Make a decision as soon as possible.
Sister.
What happened?
Long Ballad
Hong Ling, take Chu away first.
I'll handle this.
General, you go first. I'll wait.
This is the military order.
You can't disobey.
Brother Bu, if you want to go, we'll go together.
If you want to die, we'll die together.
Don't be afraid.
I won't let anything happen to you.
Stop talking nonsense!
No one can leave today!
Get out!
Go!
Brother.
Kill them!
Brother!
Brother.
Are you okay?
Chu, don't be afraid.
Brother.
Brother is alive.
Your Highness.
Li Zhen's sister was seriously injured and was not sent.
But I think it's too dangerous.
This Lin Ansheng.
Why didn't he say that Li Chuchu also dared to come?
Forget it.
I was just trying to get a position.
I need a role to play as a partner.
I've checked.
Li Zhen never participates in the war on the surface.
He actually had a deep relationship with the Crown Prince.
If he finds out that the Crown Prince died for his own purpose,
the consequences will be unimaginable.
Although Li Zhen is a talent,
it's a pity that he's an old man who doesn't know the truth.
In order to avoid a long night,
I had to take the initiative.
Doctor, how is he?
This young man is seriously injured and has lost too much blood.
Fortunately, he is strong.
If he can recover from the injury tonight,
he should be fine.
Thank you, Doctor.
Achi, hurry up.
Hurry up.
It turns out that he has been helping me to kill him more than his own life.
Achi.
If we're not brothers,
how good would that be?
Brother,
don't leave Su'an.
Don't leave me.
Brother,
what are you going to do?
A'chu,
I know you're going to save me.
You pack up slowly.
I'll go get something to eat.
Who is the mastermind behind this?
Who is so bold to kill his neighbor?
If I'm not wrong,
it's not the Third Prince.
The Third Prince?
A'chu,
I've been suspecting that
the Third Prince was the one who killed Father.
I came to Jiangling to find evidence
and expose his real identity.
Now,
the enemy is in the dark.
I'm afraid that he's not going to be able to escape.
Now,
the enemy is in the dark.
You must be careful.
You'd better not get in touch with him again.
Okay, I understand.
The people in front are so hungry.
What are they doing?
They're probably celebrating the Flower God Festival.
Rumor has it that the lovers who get the flower god blessing
can have a heart of gold.
The time has come.
You're so impulsive.
I'm sure you're here to pray for the flower god blessing.
Niu, we are...
That's right.
We're the newlyweds from the outside.
I'd like to ask you a question.
Do you know each other?
Come on.
Please.
What do you want?
Madam.
What do you think?
I've checked the city.
Master went to Jiangling this time
for official business.
But he didn't say when he would come back.
It's really not a personal escape?
Madam, don't worry too much.
Master has always been well-mannered.
He will never come back.
But when it comes to Li Chu Chu,
he's like crazy.
He doesn't care.
Chu,
why did you lie in the daytime?
We are not a couple.
How do you know we are not a couple?
Do you know
we are not a couple?
Chu,
what did you say?
Chu Chu Chu,
Chu Chu Chu Chu,
Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu,
Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu Chu
Mai
he
c