The Long Ballad
Episode 18
Qianqian.
Today is Madam's big day.
You usually go to her place to have fun.
Why are you so slow today?
You are not fast enough.
Madam.
Just wait until the banquet is over.
Have you finished your work?
Does it make me look like a stranger?
Madam.
If you are in a hurry,
you can go by yourself.
What's wrong with you?
Forget it.
I'd better go to the kitchen to keep an eye on her.
In case something happens,
Madam will be angry again.
Mother.
I embroidered this Songhe Yan Nian Ping Feng.
I wish you a happy and prosperous day.
Thank you, Madam.
I should have prepared the Qibao Geng for you.
I'll go and get it for you.
As long as you solve Li Chuchu's problem,
I will officially appoint you.
You will be the daughter of the General's manor.
You will be the daughter of the Qing family.
I wish you a long life and a long life.
It's hard for you to think about the Qibao Geng
after a long time.
Wait.
Madam.
You are so filial.
I was just trying to stop you.
Are you dissatisfied with me?
No, I dare not.
Then get out of here.
Madam, what's wrong with you?
Is there something wrong with the Geng?
Wait.
If there is something wrong with the soup,
then I will be the one who will be accused.
Today is Mother's good day.
Madam, don't be confused.
Let go of Second Sister.
General, this is the letter from the General.
I have found out that
Third Prince and the spy of the enemy have secretly returned.
This will collect evidence.
Soon, we will have a progress.
General Li.
How dare you break into the military camp?
Someone has accused you of robbing the camp
and corrupting the society.
His Majesty is furious.
He ordered the Dali Temple to investigate.
His Majesty means
that before the matter is clear,
you should not interfere with military affairs.
You should go home and rest for a while.
Is it His Majesty's intention
or Third Prince's?
Yuzhan,
you should not offend someone.
It is better to be aware of the situation.
Young Lord, you should take good care of your family.
Don't be too careless.
Be careful not to get caught in the fire.
You!
Also,
you should not be so careless.
you and A'chu have not left the city yet.
Your marriage will not be accepted.
Madam, please forgive me.
I am very sick.
I haven't had such a delicious soup for a long time.
I have a mouthful of it.
Since you are sick,
you should go home and rest.
Thank you, Madam.
I...
I will go and see Madam off.
Madam!
Why did you do this?
For Li Chuchu,
you even give up your life?
I did not do this for Chuchu.
I did it for you.
Thank you.
Madam, please forgive me.
Madam,
please do not do this.
You two are...
You are my children.
Li Chuchu!
Only I am your biological daughter.
Only I am your stepdaughter.
Only I will get rid of my own daughter.
This is all your fault.
Li Qianqian,
are you still a human?
How can you say that?
I am stronger than you.
Li Qianqian,
Li Chuchu,
you are a shameless scoundrel.
You seduced your own brother,
and now you even hurt Madam.
I hate you.
I hate you!
Qianqian!
Madam!
Someone!
Someone, please go and get a doctor!
Madam!
I am sorry.
Your sister is young.
It is all your fault.
Madam, do not say that.
There must be a way.
Wait for me to find a doctor.
Wait for me.
Madam,
I have never done anything to you.
Please go away.
I want to give you a chance
to get rid of your sister.
Okay.
I will do it.
As long as you are alive,
I will do anything you say.
Madam!
Someone, please come!
posts
crab
Flower
OrNow
You shouldn't have funeral.
I am The One Initially.
A'chu.
I told you to get out!
A'chu!
Miss, don't be too sad.
I'll serve you to change your uniform.
Go and guard the tomb for Madam.
Shouliang?
She doesn't have a daughter like me.
Why should I give her a horse?
Miss,
are you possessed?
Madam, she's a bastard.
She's a bastard!
Oh no!
She's possessed!
No!
Don't die.
Brother,
I don't have a mother.
Don't be afraid, A'chu.
I'll protect you for Madam.
I always thought that Madam was biased towards me.
She didn't love me much.
Although she didn't tell me,
she kept a grudge in her heart.
I only understood it when she died.
She had already made me a daughter.
A'chu,
I can understand your feelings.
For you,
Madam is not only a benefactor,
but also a mother in real sense.
Madam is poisoned.
Madam died of poison.
She poisoned her sister to frame her.
But she couldn't be so bold.
There must be someone else behind this.
I must investigate this matter.
I'll avenge Madam.
Okay.
Just tell me what I should do.
No matter who I investigate,
will you help me?
Of course.
What if I investigate Madam?
You're so cruel.
You almost killed Li Chuchu.
Madam, don't be angry.
Don't be angry with your body.
You're not the only one who died.
You didn't get the whole body.
Now we've cleaned it up.
If we want to do it again,
it will be difficult.
We must get rid of the antidote we prepared.
I'll do it.
Yes.
Mother, you're asleep.
Zheng, why are you here at this time?
There's a death case in the family.
I want to ask you
how to deal with it.
Madam is very ill.
She's been sick for a long time.
I feel sorry for her.
I want to read more of her soul-destroying porridge
and read it.
Madam didn't die because of illness.
She was poisoned.
Is that so?
Aunt Ping,
you must investigate it carefully.
You must investigate it carefully
so that the evil person won't have any trouble.
Yes.
I'll do it.
Zheng,
what do you mean?
Mother,
Chu is not my biological daughter.
I've decided to marry her.
What?
Not your biological daughter?
Even if she's not your biological sister,
she's also a sister of your brother.
If this is known,
the General's Mansion will be broken into pieces.
I can't agree to it.
I'm not here to ask for your opinion.
Something happened in the court recently.
My son has been suspended.
If anything goes wrong again,
if someone catches you and makes a complaint,
I'm afraid you can't get over it.
You're a traitor.
How dare you threaten your mother?
Didn't your mother say
that the future of the General's Mansion is in my son's hands?
Then don't force your son to do something unfilial.
You...
Your Majesty,
I'm sorry.