The Legend of Chuchu
Episode 16
This jade pendant is for you, Miss Chuchu.
Just take it as my apology.
In the future, if you encounter any trouble,
the jade pendant will come to me.
No one will stop you.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I also thank you on behalf of my sister.
Your Highness.
Your Highness,
will you promise me to go to my house for tea?
Sure.
I'll go right now.
Miss Chuchu,
please rest assured.
I'll definitely be there.
Young Lord,
I'm willing to wait for you no matter how long it takes.
There are many people here.
You should go back first.
Congratulations, Sister.
You've won the Third Prince's favor.
Let's go back first.
Chu, let's talk.
You're so mean.
You're harassing my brother,
and you're seducing Young Lord.
You even want to go to Third Prince.
Li Chuchu,
why should all men be after you?
I'm not as weak as you.
That woman has been caught.
She said she was just using her skills.
Why?
Someone else knows.
Although she did this,
she's determined to find out.
You know who she is?
Chu is just talking nonsense.
Third Sister is still waiting.
I'll go back first.
Wait.
Third Prince is not a good person.
Don't go too close to him.
Be careful not to be caught.
In my brother's eyes,
no matter which man approaches me,
he's not good.
Chu,
I know you've been through a lot.
When you're close to Third Prince,
you're just looking for a backer.
But it's really dangerous.
Don't jump into a fire pit.
Jump into a bigger fire pit.
Chu chose this path himself.
Even if it's a mountain of knives and fire,
I don't regret it.
I really don't.
This Li family of Anping Jun
is really capable of killing people.
Now Li Zhen is like the sun in the sky.
The two sisters are also extraordinary.
It's a little interesting.
I'm willing to serve you.
If you need me,
why must you do it?
I'm not talented.
I'm willing to serve you.
With my relationship with the old Prime Minister,
I'm the first to choose you.
In a few days, I'm going to Jiangling.
You take care of Anping Jun.
If anything happens, report to me at any time.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
General, please wait.
What's the matter, Miss Lin?
General, when are you going to come to my house to propose?
General, what are you doing?
I have a secret.
I'm not a good girl.
I don't want to waste your time.
So I don't want to be a part of this marriage.
Please forgive me.
What did I eat?
I have a stomachache.
I'm also feeling a little stuffy.
But last night,
Mingyue went to the kitchen to get porridge for me.
Mingyue?
Chunriyan was supposed to be attended by Li Tiantian.
But I accidentally got a stomachache.
I can only let Second Sister go.
I'm sorry.
She went to the kitchen.
And Her Highness remembered her.
What a sisterly love story.
Ask someone to take care of Ange.
Her Highness is the royal family's most important.
She must not be neglected.
Don't worry, Madam.
I've already told her.
Mother, I don't want to marry Li Zhen.
What happened to you?
Li Zhen looks like a...
What?
A silver-medicine-pillow.
A useless embroidery pillow.
I don't want to be a guard for my whole life.
Forget it.
Just don't marry him.
Otherwise, I'll ask Ange to marry Li Tiantian, the legitimate daughter of the Li family.
In this way,
I can also prevent Li Chuchu from being a little demon.
Big Sister.
What are you doing here?
I just want to tell you something.
What?
Li Chuchu, this bitch.
How dare she trick me?
But what can I do?
I think I'd better forget it.
After all, the second sister is now protected by someone.
She is easy to move.
Especially after the Spring Festival.
Big brother sent several people to watch her.
That's not necessarily.
Big sister.
You want to see me?
Second sister.
Tonight is the lantern show.
Come with me to go out.
We take this opportunity
to dress up more.
Thank you for your help.
But...
You don't want to go out with me?
No.
Then let's go now.
Sit.
This is even more beautiful.
Let's go.
Second sister.
There is a very good clothing store in front.
Let's go and see.
Let's go.
Wait a minute, big sister.
What? There's something on your face.
Wait a minute.
Really?
Let's go.
Madam.
Someone just reported that
the second girl was kidnapped
and went to the church.
I know.
Let her go.
Do you want to
or send someone to tell the doctor
so as not to hurt the mother and son?
Amitabha.
After the two are born,
send someone to the military camp to report.
Little beauty.
Master.
You are so bold.
You are really a little crazy.
You will be fine in a while.
You caught the wrong person.
Wrong person?
We are looking for this hairpin.
I really don't know.
I will give you a lot of money
when you get married.
Let's go.
You can't go in.
You are the girl who was caught by the police.
I am in your room.
Wait a minute, big sister.
What? There's something on your face.
Wait a minute.
Really?
Okay.
Let's go.
Please go to the general's mansion to report.
Tell them that Miss Li
was caught by the police.
Tell them to come and save her.
Big sister.
I gave you a chance.
What a pity.
Miss Li.
Tingting.
How could it be you?
I am sorry.