CRAZY LOVE
THE CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS AND
EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE WORKS OF FICTION
EPISODE 9
Was it your first time?
Kissing someone.
No. I've done it before.
That's my point.
My point is that it was just a show
to play our own roles.
Simply put, show time.
Since I made you put on a show,
I should pay you for it.
I'm not without common sense.
I'll write off your debt.
How does 100 million won sound?
The most expensive three seconds
in the whole world.
-But--
-Of course, you would want my apology too.
According to the contract,
you agreed to faithfully play
the role of my fiancée,
and it happened to be a moment
I needed to show that you were my fiancée.
I had no intention of violating
your rights or insulting you in any way.
In the event you felt insulted
regardless of my intention,
I deeply apologize.
That's not how you apologize to someone.
This is how you do it.
I'm sorry.
It was my mistake.
Please say hello.
This is my fiancée Lee Sina.
You knew?
Why didn't you tell me…
about Mr. Noh's engagement?
I'm sorry. I was going to tell you
after you attend the KPEDA event.
Did you also know
that his fiancée was his secretary?
That I really had no idea.
Okay. You may go now.
I'll drive you home.
I want to stay here a little longer.
Okay, ma'am.
Hello?
The police station?
Sir.
This is the chairman's message.
From my father?
Next time, it won't end
with just forgery charges.
He'll kill that punk.
He also wanted me to tell you
that your wedding date has been set.
Your fiancé will arrive in Korea tomorrow.
POLICE WHO UNDERSTAND CITIZENS
I didn't do it.
I never deceived anyone.
I never forged my academic records.
I know you didn't do it.
I believe you. But…
we can't be together anymore.
What do you mean?
I'm getting married.
I have a fiancé.
-What?
-It's time…
for us to wake up from this dream.
We shouldn't have dated from the start.
We can never be together.
If I stay with you,
your bad reputation will follow me
for the rest of my life too.
Noh Gojin, a fraud instructor
who forged his academic records.
I'm not a fraud!
Today is the last day…
I'll be standing in the rain with you.
No. I won't let you go.
Please don't do this, Sooyeong.
Let me go.
No, I can't.
I…
can't live without you.
That's not true.
You'll be fine without me.
You've always been alone.
Let's break up on a high note.
I went through so much to protect you.
It's okay.
You'll remember me in the end,
and we'll fall in love again.
That's right.
It was just a show.
It was all an act.
What else would it be?
But why did he have to bring up money
in that moment?
Why bring up the debt write-off?
What? The most expensive three seconds
in the whole world?
What does he take me for?
It's fine since I got to pay off
some of my debt.
He wrote off 100 million won for me.
But still. He needed to apologize first--
He did apologize.
He apologized very properly.
Then why am I so upset?
I'm sorry.
It was my mistake.
Mistake.
It was a mistake indeed.
I wonder if she's very upset.
Why did I have to mention
writing off her debt?
What's going on?
What's wrong with me?
What are you doing so early?
Gosh! Did you go
on a shopping spree again?
I need to return these.
What for?
I'm going to be late. I'll wash up first.
Return them?
That's nonsense.
I know you're going to donate them again.
I won't let that happen this time.
It's so pretty.
I'm going to wear them
for my audition tomorrow.
-Hello.
Why is he getting out of the car
by himself today?
Aren't you going in?
What… What are you doing there?
Sorry?
And why are you so late?
As a secretary, you have to come to work
right on time. Don't you know that?
At this rate,
when will you pay off all your debt?
If you had sent me a text letting me know
you were going ahead of me,
I wouldn't have gone
all the way to your house.
Then I would've gotten to work earlier.
Besides, I still have
20 more minutes until work begins.
There's no official work start time
for a secretary.
Why did I have to mention
her debt again? Why?
-What's that?
-It's the dress, shoes, and accessories
I wore to the KPEDA event.
What about them?
I'm returning them to you.
When did I say you need to return--
So are you asking me
to carry them home myself?
My goodness. I've never seen
a debtor putting a creditor to work.
I'll take them to your house.
Wait.
Take these too.
I'll read them at home.
What?
Do you have a complaint--
There was a strand of hair…
on your jacket.
Why did you close your eyes?
I just…
got something in my eye.
Okay, then.
How embarrassing.
Gojin.
I TRUSTED THE TOP INSTRUCTOR…
ILPUM EDU, ERRORS FOUND
ILPUM EDU MATH STUDY GUIDE CONTROVERSY,
ILPUM EDU STUDY GUIDE WITH ERRORS
Right, I heard something about…
a spy.
-Spy?
I heard that
Mr. Park planted a spy at Gotop.
And that spy stole Mr. Noh's study guides.
No way. I doubt that.
Right, that's too absurd.
We'll see if it's really absurd or not.
It'll soon be found out
once they investigate it.
Mr. Noh isn't the type
to just take it lying down.
He'll discipline his research team first.
Oh, no. Are you not feeling well?
You look pale as a ghost.
No, I'm fine.
Someone might misunderstand
if they see you like that.
Don't you agree?
What nonsense are you talking about?
What… misunderstanding?
How could you do this to me?
Ms. Ma!
Misunderstanding, my foot.
I meant someone might
misunderstand her to be sick.
Why did she get so upset?
Gosh, watch what you say.
It's not nice to tell someone
they look sick when they look pale.
You crossed the line, Ms. Michelle.
What? Gosh.
Oh, right.
Ms. Michelle, you graduated
from Virginia State University, right?
Well… Yes…
Why do you ask?
My nephew is applying there.
Oh, I see. Is he?
If I have any questions,
I'll just ask you directly.
I have relatives living in Virginia.
Just ask me.
Why don't you take care of
your skin problem? It looks terrible.
You even have age spots.
I saw you.
What?
I thought hundreds,
no, thousands of times over again
to confirm who I saw was really you, Segi.
I'd rather have real amnesia
because this is such a horrible nightmare.
Why'd you do it?
Seriously, why?
You saw me?
I saw you on your way to work.
Let's have some tea.
What's going on?
Well.
You saw the articles on Ilpum Edu, right?
I was wondering if you knew
anything about that incident.
It's certain that the study guides
you put together were leaked.
But how could there be so many errors?
How would I know?
I have amnesia.
Right.
By the way, you said last time
that it's going to be very interesting.
So you really wanted to attend
the KPEDA event.
Oddly, what you said
kept ringing in my head.
I felt as if you already knew
what was going to happen there.
How could that be?
Take care.
Have a good day.
BALANCE 5,920 WON
JINHAN BANK
SAVINGS ACCOUNT
What's this?
I brought everything I have.
You have to look after me now, sir.
Have some coffee.
MONTHLY CALENDAR
Okay, now to find the relative maximum
and minimum points,
I'll draw a graph of the f prime of x.
Excluding exponential x…
One second.
Are you ready?
I'll check it now.
Gojin!
Look!
GOTOP EDU NOH GOJIN
EASY CSAT MATH
VIEWS
-We did it!
-Good job!
I knew we could do it!
Was it all a lie from the start?
Why?
Seriously, why?
Mr. Noh.
Sir, are you okay?
Just ten seconds.
No.
Just for a minute.
GOTOP EDUCATION
DIRECTOR MA EUNJUNG
Ms. Ma, are you going somewhere?
I'm not feeling well,
so I'm going home early.
Ms. Ma.
Do you have a minute?
I understand you, Ms. Ma.
I know you used to be
a very promising instructor.
If you hadn't quit after getting married,
you would've become
an amazing top instructor by now.
But after getting married,
because of the career gap,
you had to come back here
as a teaching assistant,
not an instructor.
I can fully understand…
how sad you must've been.
On top of it, as a mother,
you had to take on your ex-husband's debt
to maintain custody of your son.
I don't believe anyone has the right
to criticize you for this incident.
They don't understand even 10%…
No, not even 0.01% of the pain
you've endured.
I didn't mean to do it.
I was harassed by creditors every day,
but I didn't have any money.
I really needed to do something.
Just at that moment, Mr. Park…
promised me an instructor position
at Ilpum Edu…
I would've done the same too.
But, Mr. Noh
won't ever forgive you.
Ms. Ma.
If you help me,
I'll help you too.
What…
SUPPORT CENTER
NO WONDER WHY EVERYONE LOVES GOTOP,
CAN'T EVEN MAKE A PROPER STUDY GUIDE
I think we need to…
refund all our study guides.
Refund? All of them?
Yes.
Ms. Ma.
Ms. Ma, that idiot!
Where is Ms. Ma?
Tell her to come here now. At once!
Sir.
What? You really showed up…
Well…
I…
What?
Speak of the devil.
What now?
How will you pay for all this damage?
Say something. Say it!
Ma Eunjung. How dare you!
Hello, Mr. Park.
I'm Oh Segi,
the deputy CEO of Gotop Education.
Ms. Ma, you may go now.
I'll talk to him on your behalf.
Sir,
I did my best.
Don't go! Ms. Ma! Darn it.
Can you give us a minute?
Well…
Okay.
You have a nice office.
Ms. Ma told me everything.
No, I don't know anything.
Do you have evidence?
Do you have evidence that I took them?
You always find evidence
if you investigate.
Don't get cute with me.
Hey, you stay out of this.
Tell that janitor thug Noh Gojin
to come here.
If I stay out of this,
it won't do you any good, Mr. Park.
You know Mr. Noh's temper.
It's going to be a litigation battle.
Will you be able to handle it?
We already secured
Ms. Ma's confession.
But if you and I
become good friends,
such an unfortunate situation
won't happen.
Your sandwiches are ready.
Thank you.
Have a good day!
Something seems different about her.
Right?
She used to have no presence
like dust in the wind,
but now she has an air about her.
Like she carries a certain ambience.
She gives off the vibe
of a rich Cheongdam-dong housewife.
She seems so elegant.
Isn't that heavy?
Do you want me to help you carry it?
Ms. Sooyeong!
We were both very surprised that day,
weren't we?
Yes.
I didn't know you were Mr. Noh's fiancée.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No need to apologize.
I didn't tell you
that I was the CEO of Baek Edu either.
Thank you for your understanding.
What do you
like about this girl?
Is something wrong?
I met my first love.
First love?
The one who got you
the dress that you lent me?
Yes.
I waited for 12 years to see him.
For 12 years?
Wow, you're so amazing.
But…
he has a fiancée.
He must've been so lonely alone.
But I was so heartbroken
actually seeing another woman with him.
On top of that,
it turns out that I know the woman.
Seriously?
What would you do if you were me?
Of course, you shouldn't give up.
You could die tomorrow.
"I could die tomorrow."
Good advice.
You're right. I won't give up on him
no matter what now.
He's the only one who can make me happy.
Okay. I'll root for you too.
You can do it.
Please take your medicine.
How do you plan on
getting your money back if you're sick?
TOP PRIVATE INVESTIGATOR
Here you go.
No, not yet.
I guess you don't trust me.
You're Mr. Noh Manners' underling.
How could I trust you?
But the underling is
usually the one who cooperates.
What's this?
M&A CONTRACT TERMS AND CONDITIONS
Mr. Jang of Think Academy is
in critical condition.
These are the M&A terms and conditions
that Mr. Noh worked hard on for six months
to acquire Think Academy
after Mr. Jang fell ill.
If you have a look, Ilpum Edu
might be able to take over Think Academy.
So,
what do you want from me?
Where should I put this?
Well, just put it anywhere over there.
I'll go home now.
I cooked side dishes
and put them in the refrigerator, so--
I don't eat day-old side dishes.
Make fresh ones again.
Then I'll go home now.
Wait.
Who will do the dishes then?
Should I do them?
Of course, I should.
Then I'll go home now.
You're going home already?
Sorry?
But…
the living room is so dirty right now.
How can you leave?
Please clean it now.
Right now?
Yes. Right now. At once. Immediately.
All done.
What about the dressing room?
I can't sleep
if the dressing room is dirty.
Okay, sir.
I'm all done now.
The study is dirty too.
I can't sleep if the study is dirty.
I cleaned the study,
the bedroom, and the bathroom too.
And it's past 11 p.m. now.
Where did the time go?
With that kind of mindset,
when will you pay me all back?
And from now on, you won't
be able to go home until midnight,
so come prepared.
That darn money!
The only thing he cares about is money.
Where are you going?
To buy cola.
Cola?
But you don't like cola.
I can't drink it if I don't like it?
Well? Aren't you going home?
Yes… I'm going now.
Aren't you going to go buy cola?
Goodnight.
Why isn't he going?
His focus…
Once he's fixed on something,
he wouldn't notice the end of the world.
Was my house always this big?
Drink this.
Thank you.
Actually, I was waiting for you.
If you had something to say,
you could've called.
My fiancée might feel uncomfortable,
so I don't like to meet
with other women outside.
I guess Ms. Sina is the jealous type.
I'm friends with her.
So, to be honest,
I was very surprised that day
to find out Ms. Sina was your fiancée.
I met her for the first time in Gangneung.
I even lent her the dress
that my first love got for me.
What a small world, right?
By the way, how about dinner
all together this weekend?
I want to congratulate you guys
on your engagement.
The day is also my birthday.
It's your birthday?
Yes.
Since it's my birthday,
you wouldn't turn it down, right?
Fine. I'll come with my fiancée.
I'll treat you to somewhere nice.
It's 75 degrees Celsius.
I confirmed it.
Ms. Lee Sina.
Please make yourself available
for dinner this weekend.
Pardon?
Let's have dinner together.
-Me?
-Yes.
Why?
Ms. Baek Sooyeong invited us.
Oh, I see.
What?
Wait, that means
you want me to pretend to be
your fiancée
in front of Ms. Sooyeong again?
What? You don't want to?
-Of course, I don't.
-Why not?
Why don't you want to pretend
to be the fiancée of a man
so great like me
who is handsome, smart, and rich?
What a narcissist. Seriously.
I'm sorry, but I won't be going.
I'll let Ms. Baek know.
"Article Two of the contract.
The debtor will become
a hostage of the creditor
and offset
the financial liabilities with labor.
First,
the debtor will faithfully act
and fulfill the role of a fiancée
even better than a real fiancée would."
Did you forget already?
With that kind of mindset,
when will you pay me all back?
By the way, we're the only ones here.
I rented the place for you two.
The entire place?
Yes.
Is this your first time here?
Yes, it's my first time.
This is on another level
since you're rich.
I feel so uncomfortable
that I might get indigestion.
I didn't do this because I'm rich.
I wanted to do it for you.
I pre-ordered the most famous dish
from this restaurant.
Please enjoy.
It looks so delicious.
Thank you for the food.
I asked them to remove the onions…
Why?
Don't you hate onions?
Oh, right.
I heard that I used to be like that.
But I enjoy them now.
My honey told me that
if I keep eating things I didn't like,
perhaps I'll learn to like them.
Open your mouth.
Honey, open your mouth.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
But you don't seem like someone
who was born in spring.
I don't?
I'm so curious how you met.
Ms. Sina, what made you fall for Mr. Noh?
Pardon?
Well…
What made me fall for him?
It's his personality.
He really had no manners--
He's so great and kind, you know?
What about you, Mr. Noh?
What made you fall for Ms. Sina?
Although I can't really remember,
perhaps it's her beauty.
I've never seen someone
so pretty in my whole life.
The moment I saw her in the hospital room,
I thought my heart was going to explode.
But…
what made me really fall for her
was the fact that she stayed by my side.
I had always been all alone,
but she never left my side.
She didn't abandon me.
Can we have more coffee, please?
Pardon me.
-Ow, that's hot!
-I'm sorry, ma'am. Are you okay?
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
What are you doing?
You need to be careful!
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry, ma'am.
I'm all right.
Did you get burned? Are you all right?
I'm going to use the restroom.
I'm so very sorry.
Why did he get so upset?
People might think I'm really his fiancée…
I had always been all alone,
but she never left my side.
He must've been lonely.
We've come here together before.
We sat at this table too then.
Is that so?
I don't recall at all.
When your memories do come back,
what would you do?
What if…
you loved someone else?
Even if
I loved someone else who I don't remember,
it would be like the wind.
A wind that blew away without a trace.
Even the wind might have its own reason.
An unavoidable reason--
An excuse, I suppose
or an obsession.
What's taking her so long?
I wish my hand got burnt instead.
Since you can't see my heart.
Can't you see…
my heart that's been burned?
Please try to remember.
What's this?
For the cost of the handkerchief.
It's pretty.
These look pretty.
-Do they? Let's see.
-Yes.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, my dear Sooyeong
What is it?
I'm about to go home.
But this box has been
just sitting there for a few days,
so I'll put it in the storage cabinet
before I head out.
It's okay.
I'll put it away before I go.
-Just leave it.
-I'll put it away.
I said, just leave it!
I'm sorry.
What happened to the earrings?
Deceiving me wasn't enough
that now you even steal from me?
-What are you doing?
-Apologize.
-Let go now.
-Apologize!
-I said, let go!
-I said, apologize!
Apologize!
Apologize! I said, apologize!
Apologize to me now! Do it!
-Hey!
-Are you really out of your mind?
Are you completely out of your mind?
You're dead meat now.
Hey! Stop!
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
-Hey!
-"Hey"?
I'm not going to put up
with a scumbag like you anymore.
What?
I'm no longer your secretary or a hostage.
I'm… me!
You make no sense…
So what?
I'll repay you for the damages.
I don't have money right now,
but I'll pay you back before I die, okay?
If you don't like it,
report me to the police,
sue me, or send me to prison!
Do as you wish.
I guess I've been too easy on you lately.
Do you have a death wish?
I already experienced
what it means to die, you jerk!
Live until you're old and gray?
That's a delusion.
You might die tomorrow. That's life.
I'll never live like this again.
I'll never live like a fool again!
You never know when you might die.
I'm going to live my life
happily without regrets.
Your nose is bleeding.
Darn it.
Hey! I guess you must be
out of your mind right now,
so you don't realize what you've done!
You made a mistake.
It's over now!
Look at this.
She didn't come to work?
Yes?
Mr. Noh?
You need to leave by half past
for the advertising shoot.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
-Hello?
-Ms. Lee.
You're coming to the studio today, right?
After Mr. Noh's advertisement shoot,
we want to quickly shoot
the mock exam review video.
I'm sorry to ask, but could you please
bring the mock exam monitoring files?
I'm not going--
Yes, ma'am.
Ms. Ma.
Isn't the lighting not enough?
If you look from here,
I think they'll turn that lighting--
Forget it.
-Director.
-Yes?
That lighting isn't enough.
Let's add some more.
-Really?
-Yes.
-And that lighting…
It's too dim. Mr. Noh likes it bright.
He likes it very bright?
Yes. Just turn them all on, please.
-All of them.
-All of them?
-These too, then.
-Yes. He likes attention. It's a must.
-Understood.
-Great.
That's already set up.
Please don't touch it.
Mr. Noh.
-Hello, sir!
-Hello.
Make sure to put up the slides properly.
I'll do it like a real lecture.
Don't make dumb mistakes
and waste my precious time,
not even a minute.
Yes, sir.
We'll start filming him
giving a lecture in ten minutes.
-Hello.
-Hello. Thank you.
Is this all the materials?
Okay, got it.
Mr. Noh, please come up to the stage.
Can we have this cleaned up, please?
-And also turn on this screen?
-Yes, thank you.
-Okay. Good.
-Please turn the lights that way.
Yes, over there.
Hello. I'm Noh Gojin.
This year…
What the… My goodness.
Oh, no. What happened?
Sir.
Sir, are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Are you?
Are you okay?
Sir.
Are you hurt?
You're the one who got hurt.
But why am I… the one that's hurting?
What's…
with you?
Translated by Ji-young Hwang