(This series was being filmed
under the regulation of Emergency Decree)
(Footage is used according to preventive
measures for infectious diseases)
The following program is suitable
for people 18 years of age or older.
It may contain disturbing
content and graphics,
violence, sexual activity
and coarse language.
Viewer discretion is required.
People under 18
should view with an adult.
(This series is fiction. Names and/or
events are created for entertainment.)
(Viewer discretion is required.)
And will you be able to enter the match?
I will. Easy.
That community member interviews
this weekend. Let me look for a community.
Okay, let's assign roles.
We can use that court near your house.
You do some with Torn.
Does that mean you like Torn?
And what was wrong with you today?
Please tell me.
Okay.
Better if you don't know.
(Tupfa)
(Torn)
(Saen)
(Aai)
(Dome)
(Vee)
(Pete)
(Tupbok)
(Special Guests)
(The series was adapted from
'You're My Sky')
I don't understand why
they brought their girls to the match.
I lost focus
and then jammed my finger.
Maybe love?
Love?
Is it love? Does love
make you good at basketball?
No, but practice does.
I'm so bummed.
I want to play basketball.
I haven't asked my uncle.
I'm afraid he'll say no.
Go-no-go.
A critical moment when you
have to decide whether to go or not.
If you go, you might score,
or you might lose.
My teacher said it is a go-no-go moment.
Think about it, Torn.
If you ask him, you might have a chance.
But if you don't...
I definitely won't be
playing basketball with you.
So? Go or no-go?
Hey, out again?
Where are you going this time?
I have basketball practice.
Why is it so often?
Stay at home for once.
So? Go or no-go?
Go, of course.
(Municipality Pier)
What? You've been
aiming for this scholarship.
Pete even booked
a place for the celebration.
Why do you suddenly hesitate?
(You know...)
(You know... About Saen...)
I'll feed you
so your hand won't get dirty.
Tsk. Almost got it.
One down, one day left to go.
Are you tired?
We'll go to the car for our stuff,
then to the hotel.
- It's just right next from here.
- Uh-huh.
- Let's wash our hands and eat ice cream.
- Yay!
Back then,
I envied the families in TV dramas.
I've been eating dinner alone
since elementary school.
My parents are busy with
the restaurants.
Is it ironic? They open restaurants
but don't have time to dine with me.
You know? Some kids want their mom
to stop telling them to eat.
You are one of them?
Mhm.
My family is bossy.
They order me around.
So, I'm not comfortable
while being at home.
When I see another family,
I'm not feeling that way.
And when I was interviewing those people,
I mean, I didn't know how to act around them.
What the heck. I want that.
I asked my parents to stay
with my grandma every summer.
I got into soccer because
I wanted to be home late.
I did everything just not to be alone.
That bad?
It isn't fun when you have to
sleep alone on the couch every night.
Take your time.
Think about it.
You can tell us everything.
This is where we're going to stay.
Where have you taken me?
It doesn't look like a hotel.
Is it a homestay?
Nope.
It looks like someone's house.
Oh! You're here, Saen.
And who's that lady?
She's too old
to be a hotel staff member.
Seriously, Saen, tell me now.
Easy, bro.
It's a homestay,
the home which is a house.
My grandma's house.
- Saen!
- Ouch! It hurts.
You tricked me into your house?
I just told you that I'm not
comfortable around seniors.
- How sneaky you are!
- Ouch! Ouch!
- I'm off.
- Where are you going?
- Get back in here.
- Off to my grandma.
No! Get back.
- Grandma.
- Saen.
- I missed you so much.
- I missed you too.
Ow! Enough!
Enough with the hug.
Where is your "friend"?
The one you'll introduce me to.
Well, he is... What?
Over there.
Hello.
What are you standing here for?
Why don't you wait at the restaurant?
I want to wait until you're done,
so we can go together.
Let's go.
Are you excited about the competition?
How are you with Vee?
Well, it's okay.
Is it really okay?
Vee also gave me that answer.
Normally, he wouldn't stop talking.
It is really okay.
Your brother is a good boy.
We all like each other as a team.
That includes you?
I'm glad.
You two have been in the same club for
a year but don't talk about each other.
I thought you didn't get along.
Let's take a selfie.
Here.
Hold on. Okay.
One, two...
Here.
Let's eat.
Yeah.
Grandma.
Why did you go by yourself?
Oh, I can walk.
What if you get in an accident,
who's gonna help you, huh?
Not gonna happen.
I am still in good shape.
You listen to no one.
I don't know. It's my house.
What I do is my business.
If you want to complain,
move to be here with me.
Aai, wait a second.
He's changing the bedsheet.
Could you believe it?
He nagged my ear off
just right after we met.
Saen is a nagger,
he nags the whole family.
Aai, have you ever gotten annoyed by him?
- No.
- Really?
You can stand him?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Even though he's a nagger,
when his grandpa was stationed
near the frontier,
if Saen didn't fuss around
every summer, I would've been lonely.
When you were far apart,
did you miss him?
The missing part was nothing.
When you had been together,
and then had to be apart,
it makes you worry about everything.
You worry if he is well-fed,
who does his laundry...
And in my day, Aai,
there was no phone,
only letters.
It takes days to get one.
The day you read the letter,
we couldn't know for sure that
"I'm fine" in the letter...
was still "I'm fine".
Aai, they've announced the scholarship.
You've fulfilled your dream.
Lesson learned.
When I had a daughter,
I told her to find someone
who can always be with her.
If that person has to be stationed
at another province or get deployed,
you shouldn't be together
from the start.
Well, you mean
if you could turn back time,
you wouldn't marry grandpa.
I would.
I was just whining.
I would marry his grandpa again.
Grandma.
What have you said to Aai?
Hey, can't I just talk to you friend?
Oh, yeah, Aai.
There's a dip in the mattress.
You sleep on the right side.
And let Saen sleep on
the left side where the dip is.
Huh? Where is Saen going to sleep?
Left side, and you on the right side.
No, I mean which room
you're gonna sleep in.
In your room.
Huh?
- Is it okay?
- Yeah...
Uh, yes.
And, Aai,
if you need that thing,
I'll leave it on a nightstand.
That thing?
What is that thing you're talking about?
The pointy thingy that you use at night.
I'll get that for you.
- I don't think I need, uh...
- You're definitely gonna need it.
You can't get sleep easily
when you lie next to Saen.
You're gonna need those earplugs.
He's a loud snorer. Take a couple?
Yes, please.
Tsk, tsk. Keep that in your mind.
Ing is free today,
so she dropped by.
I've told her not to come.
But she said she can watch
while waiting.
So I took her with me.
You can play even with her watching?
Torn.
Why can't you stop asking?
If you're going to be this worried,
you shouldn't have brought her.
- Ouch.
- Oh, hey, bro.
Fa.
Oh my.
What's going on?
Is it jammed?
Want me to buy some ice for that?
It's okay, Ing.
It's gonna be swollen.
I'll go get some ice.
I said no.
Please look after him, Ing.
It isn't her business.
It doesn't hurt that much.
Why do you have to be so stubborn?
Is it a good thing
that you two will be alone?
I'll go.
Is there something I should know, Torn?
No, nothing.
I feel like I'm a bother.
Sorry.
Not to worry.
A boy brought his girlfriend
to practice,
it's very common.
Not a girlfriend.
But soon-to-be.
I don't think he has a feeling for me.
Maybe he did,
but I think he no longer does.
What makes you think that way?
It's just a hunch.
Actually, I just felt that today.
- Torn, do you think...
- Ing.
I don't think I can go on playing.
Do you want to go now?
So we won't be home late.
Let's go.
You can move if you want to,
don't be afraid.
Whoa, my grandma doesn't love me.
She made me sleep on a saggy mattress.
Your grandma told me
that you're a nagger.
Yeah.
But you've never nagged me.
I nag because I don't like what I see.
But I don't nag you,
because I like it all.
You're rolling eyes at me, aren't you?
And you just changed
your facial expression, right?
Whoa!
I like everything about you.
Is there any part of me that you like?
You can tell me if there isn't.
I can't tell if you're being silent.
I don't dislike you.
- Hey.
- Huh?
Nothing.
You asked me to say what was in my mind.
But now you're being silent?
I want to kiss you.
But it's alright, forget about it.
It's late anyway.
Saen.
I won't mind.
Pete.
Can you press my back?
Huh? What about Dome?
Dome is too soft,
he doesn't press hard enough.
Well, okay.
Be careful what you wish for.
Ugh!
Why do you have to say "Ugh"
when passing the baton?
Actually, you can say anything.
So let's change it to
a thing that you like.
How about Pan? You like her.
Vee.
Fa.
Do you still want to be with me?
Hey...
Don't you feel guilty.
I'm sorry, Ing.
Why?
I don't like you that much.
Can I say that out loud?
It hurts you no more, right?
Ing...
I'm the one who feels guilty.
I didn't like you but...
still didn't let you go.
You really treated me well.
I just didn't want to lose someone
who had a feeling for me.
Aren't you mean?
Sorry.
So...
Let's be friends.
Friends.
Aren't you relieved?
Hey.
Mhm.
Well, goodbye. Thank you for the ride.
And...
Won't you tell me who it is?
Just messing with you.
Torn.
Get in the car. I'll take you home.
What?
I'm sorry.
Why did you say that? You did nothing.
Let's go.
You can go by yourself.
Torn.
About Ing...
Well...
I don't like her anymore.
And have you told her that?
Yes, I have.
We were just talking.
What did she say?
To tell you the truth,
Ing never had a feeling for me.
It was one-sided love.
- Lame.
- Uh-huh.
How is your finger?
It doesn't hurt that bad.
A critical moment when you
have to decide whether to go or not.
Torn.
Can I ask you something?
Why did you draw a picture
of me in your cheer-book?
(Poker Face Fa)
Done.
Try moving your fingers.
Can you do that?
I'm going.
Torn.
I'll take you home.
No, I can go by myself.
How will you go?
I've told you that a good relationship
is important for our relay team.
It's almost the day.
You've been doing a good job.
Will you sink your ship just
because of this, Dome?
I'm done talking.
You're grown-ups.
I let you decide what you want to do.
Aren't we gonna talk?
What to talk about?
Want to clear things up?
What is it?
I'm sorry.
Even when I'm with Pan,
all I can think about is Vee.
I can't stop.
I want to see you all the time.
Mhm.
Aren't we gonna talk?
How do you really feel about me?
Well...
Why do you want to
know about my feeling?
I just want to be sure.
That isn't one-sided.
I'm sorry.
I really have no idea.
Bye.
Fa.
Breakfast is ready.
So?
Did you use that thing last night?
Well, not the same thing as yours,
but we used it.
Get a shower
and come down for breakfast.
Today, I'll show you the market.
- Don't smile.
- Ouch!
Why didn't you lock the door?
Whoa.
How can I go down there
and face your grandma?
So don't go down.
Saen, don't! Don't.
Whoo! Woo-hoo!
Go away, Saen!
Go! Don't come near me!
Enough! I'll kick you!
Bro.
Should we tell our teammates?
Win over Coach Tuan's team.
And get the gold medal.
As we promised.
How is it going? Won his heart yet?
Are you crazy, Oak?
But the way I know from someone else.
I feel bad anyway.
I have decided.
I might break up with Pan.
♪And I won't let you go♪
♪I don't care whether
you let me love you or not♪
♪You are my good story
which I will never share♪
♪And only you who makes me so sure♪
♪That I want to be with you
till the end♪
♪Because love is love,
you make me feel that inside♪
♪It's better than what I've been told♪
♪And I won't let you go♪
♪I don't care whether
you let me love you or not♪
♪You are my good story
which I will never share♪
♪And only you who makes me so sure♪
♪That I want to be with you
till the end♪