Sun Jae!
No way...
Sun Jae, maybe we should have never met from the start.
No, we should have never met.
Hey, Im Sol!
Wake up!
34-1.
I think they delivered it wrong.
♫  I fall asleep missing you tonight  ♫
♫  Your low and deep voice  ♫
♫  The traces of you that I can't forget  ♫
♫  If I could stop, even just for a moment  ♫
♫  I would embrace you right there and then
♫  All day, I miss you  ♫
♫  I want to go back to our time together  ♫
♫  No matter what happens, I will remember you  ♫
♫  Your name is painted deep in my heart  ♫
♫  You're getting far away, out of reach  ♫
♫  At the end, please come back to me  ♫
Sun Jae, listen to me. I can really see ghosts.
You really have to be careful around water!
I don't need to be consoled.
Did I ask you to take care of me?
Honestly, when I look at you, I feel like you can see through my despair.
It's embarrassing and uncomfortable.
- Here.
- This isn't worth singing in front of all those people!
Why are you worried needlessly about me?
Why? Am I not allowed to worry about you?
No, don't.
Let me ask you one last thing.
In all the times you've lived, did you ever like me?
No. Never.
Sol, stop running away from me. You can just like me.
If I die saving you, I'm okay with it.
I don't care.
Im Sol, what are you doing? Get in the car.
Okay.
♫  Please come to me again  ♫
♫  I will hold your hand tightly  ♫
♫  Like fate  ♫
I guess they are moving.
♫  You can just embrace me like nothing happened  ♫
♫  No matter what happens, I will remember you  ♫
♫  Your name is painted deep in my heart  ♫
Here is the winning title.
Don't open it ahead of time.
Got it.
What a beautiful night!
Sun Jae?
Who are you?
I saw everything.
You stole that.
Are you a thief?
Oh, no, no.
I'm sorry.
Where are you running off to?
Want me to call the cops?
Why are you crying?
I didn't make you cry, did I?
You think I'll go easy on you if you cry?
Ryu Sun Jae, you're here!
Please go to the waiting room now.
Please give this to CEO Lee of Bon Cinema.
Also, the security here is very inadequate.
- I saw a petty thief go around.
- A petty thief?
I avoided him like the plague. How did we somehow meet again?
I didn't hear that Sun Jae was coming to the film festival.
Why is he here?
Is he here to present an award?
She's...
I'm honored to participate in the White Dragon Film Festival again since last year.
- I'm home.
- This year was especially...
Hey, you're home. Have you had dinner?
I'm not hungry.
First, these films lit up the screen this year.
- Did you retrieve your resignation letter?
- Yeah.
Here are the best picture nominees.
Why did I ever write this thing?
A Survival Story in Seoul
In Search of Utopia
To Study Good and Evil in the Human Nature...
Among these outstanding nominations, which film will win?
I can't wait to see, either. I'm holding the result here.
- The 45th White Dragon Film Festival.
- Oh, no, no...
The award for Best Picture goes to...
What do I do!!!
"Get it Done; Do it Right; Make it Work!" Congratulations!
Wow, this is crazy.
- Won't you turn that off?
- Just one more time.
There's an article about it already.
"The highlight of the festival, Ryu Sun Jae, left the crowd in disarray."
They even rhymed it!
"He muddied the occasion" vs. "It was a hilarious accident."
"Netizens are debating."
"Do it Right, Get it Done, Make it Work wins Best Picture?"
"Is Ryu Sun Jae's brain not right, not working?"
- Will you read that all night?
- Hey, Hyung.
You can tell this looks wrong right away. How can you make a mistake like that?
Let me see.
You think I'd notice that while I'm on live television?
Who cares if someone stole CEO Lee's bag?
Why butt in and cause all this chaos?
How can I see something unjust and sit back?
Congratulations on being a man who won't sit back.
- Seriously!
- Wow...
Someone obviously wrote this drunk.
Sounds like a terrible workplace, though.
No wonder she quit!
Give it back. Whose side are you two on anyway?
I became a national embarrassment because of a weird woman.
Are you going to sue her or something?
Don't do it, Hyung.
She's just a sad office worker.
Besides, everyone has a version of this letter inside their hearts.
Give it now. I'll get it. I said I'll get it for you.
Hyung!
Should we release this resignation letter to the press and explain?
Forget it. People will lose interest in a day or two. It'll die down.
That's right, go easy on her.
- Who said I'd go easy on her?
- Then what?
She will have to pray that she will never run into me ever again.
So scary.
He's scary.
It's the white puffer girl again.
I'm sorry.
The investors want to decide once they see who we will replace Park Do Jun with.
But everyone in the industry knows he'd be replacing Park Do Jun.
I'm sorry, Sun Jae.
- Why am I alive? I should just go die.
- Wouldn't it be tough?
- Hello, Bo Ah's mom.
- Who'd want to step in for Park Do Jun?
Bo Ah threw up, and I can't get in touch with her dad.
Im Geum, where is he, doing what?
Any ideas on who?
Oh, well...
I mean...
How about Ryu Sun Jae?
Sun Jae? It can't be Sun Jae.
Ryu Sun Jae?
You think Ryu Sun Jae wants to be Park Do Jun's replacement?
It might still be worth sending him the script.
When he passed on our offer for "Hero" last time,
he said, "I hope we can work together next time."
I'm sure he just said that to be polite.
But if Ryu Sun Jae wants to do it, the investors will love it!
Yes.
Then send Ryu Sun Jae the "Shall We Kiss?" script right now.
Okay? I'll get in touch separately.
Hey, Producer Im, did you edit your pitch?
Producer Im!
What?
Oh. Yes. I uploaded it on the team mail.
I'll read it.
Okay.
- Okay!
- There's no way...
he'd say yes. Right?
- Thank you!
- Good work!
Hello, Teacher.
I am so sorry.
I'm at work right now. I'll tell my husband to go right away.
Yes, I'm so sorry.
Goodbye.
I don't think this was the title.
The story of a man whose life tragically ended
and a woman who went back 15 years into the past to save him.
A fantasy romance following them as they meet again in time
and fall in love traveling back and forth between the past and the present.
When I knew I would never walk again,
I prayed every night that the morning would never come.
That morning, the sunlight pouring through the hospital windows felt desperately sad.
Then, a man told me, through a random call on a radio show.
Stay alive today.
Because it's too nice outside.
I hear it's going to rain tomorrow.
Then wait until the rain stops, and stay alive again.
Then, someday, a day might come when living doesn't seem so bad.
In the middle of the Han River bridge,
I was shivering in the cold in the endless snow.
He marched toward me and put an umbrella over my head.
Sometimes you know the consequences but make the same choice anyway.
You can't help it because of your feelings for her.
I love you.
The man falls off the edge of the cliff.
He dies once more while saving her.
In 2009, the past.
Maybe we should never have met from the start.
No. We should have never met.
As she realizes that meeting her is what leads to his death,
she's determined to never cross paths with him...
by erasing herself from his life.
Having lost all memories of her, he lives his life in this world.
As she watches his brilliant life from afar, she thinks...
This is right.
We should have never met from the start.
A song that only exists in her memories...
"Rain Shower" softly plays.
What is this?
Hyung! They sent that as a mistake.
They sent this one instead...
- Hyung.
- Dong Seok.
What?
Am I... crying right now?
I think so.
These are tears, right?
The water's coming out of your eyes, so it's not snot.
I can't stop crying.
Dong Seok.
You're treating me to lunch somewhere this expensive?
Is this a special occasion?
And is someone else coming?
So, instead of "Shall We Kiss?" we accidentally sent him your pitch.
What?
So?
Ryu Sun Jae read your pitch and is interested!
What?
What? It's her?
Do you know her or something?
"Do it right, get it done, make it work!"
She's the one who wrote the resignation letter!
Really? Wow.
- Go in.
- Tell them I'm not doing it.
- Wait! Just like that?
- Yes, just like that; I don't want to do it.
Hyung, even if you are angry, don't bring your personal feelings into this.
It's not about my personal feelings.
This pitch doesn't have mainstream appeal. I don't like it.
Wait.
No.
I'll turn it down myself.
She has to pay for humiliating me, right?
Gosh, welcome, Sun Jae!
- No.
- Gosh, it's been a while.
We can't meet like this.
Have a seat.
Over here.
Nice to meet you.
Actually, no, we've met.
Oh, my, you've met already?
Where?
Maybe not.
I think I got it wrong.
So, Mr. Ryu, you must have really loved the pitch.
You even brought these flowers.
Actually, I think the wrong message went through.
- I'm here to turn it down—
- I'm sorry.
Ryu Sun Jae, I don't want you to star in this movie.
What?
- I'm sorry!
- Why are you joking...
- Sun Jae, sorry to scare you!
- I'm not joking.
You're far from what I imagine the main character to be.
The pitch wasn't meant to go to you in the first place.
Please just forget about this project.
Are you... rejecting me right now?
Yes. I'm sorry if I hurt your feelings.
Are you out of your mind?
You didn't hurt my feelings at all.
I came here to turn it down anyway.
I got flowers so your feelings won't get hurt after I turn it down.
Thank goodness we're on the same page.
Also, if you ever see another pitch with my name on it,
please just filter it out.
Are you saying you never want to work with me?
If that's what you think, and I hurt your feelings,
that's even better.
I'm sure you never want to associate with me again.
I'll be off, then.
I have work to do.
Oh, my, w-what's with her...
I'm sorry. Give me a minute.
Sun Jae, just give me a minute, please.
Just wait one minute. Sol...
Sol! Sol! Sol! Im Sol!
What? What?
I think she rejected you.
Let's go.
His ego must be bruised.
He must have been really offended.
But...
I did the right thing. This is right.
I'll never see him again anyway.
Hyung, you haven't been rejected to your face since your debut. Right?
No, even back then, no one trampled all over you like this.
Maybe this is an opportunity to rethink things a bit.
You might be stuck in a rut without knowing.
What? In a rut?
I mean, you kind of deserved to be rejected.
That company is romance-focused. I've been watching you for years.
Despite your looks, your love life kind of sucks.
It's not your forte.
N-Not my forte? What do you mean?
What do you know about my love life?
- Pay attention to driving!
- Oh, right.
So, will you let her reject you like this?
Who's rejecting whom? In my mind...
I rejected her first.
I think she rejected you a million years ago.
- What?
- The pitch.
It seemed to hit home with you.
If you don't want to miss out, go and try to convince her.
Convince her? No thanks.
Is that the only project I can do?
Why do I need to crawl back to someone who passed on me?
Can we talk for a second?
I have nothing to say to you.
I think you do.
If it's about the movie, I already told you.
You can talk to my CEO.
"Do it right, get it done, make it work."
You said that was the type of employee I am.
If I'm that kind of employee, how can you treat me like this?
Seriously, I'm getting the ick."
What does "getting the ick" mean?
Oh, no! My resignation letter!
You really want me to talk to CEO Lee?
Cover your face when you leave just to be safe.
I'll call you.
Of all places, why here?
You're going home quite late.
Do you really do it right, get it done, and make it work?
Get to the point. I'm busy.
I want to know why you're so against me.
You waited for me to get out of work for that?
You think I waited for you to have a cup of tea at a bar?
What relationship do you think we have?
Is this because I thought you were a thief at the ceremony?
That's not fair.
You're the reason I had an incident on live TV.
The envelope switch was a mistake.
I'm sorry.
I accept your apology.
I'm sorry I mistook you for a thief.
Sure. Well...
Good, then.
Now, you have no reason to be against me.
That's not true.
That was that. I have plenty of reasons to be against you.
Let's hear them.
As I said, you don't fit the image of the main character I thought of.
If not me, who were you thinking of?
What?
Well, that is...
well...
S-S-Sung Jae Kyung.
Who? Sung Jae Kyung?
You're just pulling that out of thin air.
He's almost 50. He can't do a youth romance.
W-What's wrong with being 50? Who says he can't?
He has to play a high school student 15 years ago in the past.
Isn't your company producing it?
CGI is very advanced these days!
Besides, Sung Jae Kyung still looks really young!
If we airbrush his wrinkles, he could even play a middle schooler.
Fine. Let's say he can.
And what else?
To be honest with you,
I would prefer an actor who's better at the romance genre.
What else?
I'm looking for a fresh face.
- I'm an old face?
- You're not all that fresh, I guess.
Are you grocery shopping? Are you picking out fish?
- Fresh?
- And most crucially!
The heavens are against it. They say "never" to Ryu Sun Jae.
- Who?
- The Heavenly Granny!
She's pretty accurate.
My natal chart says if I associate with a man born in the Year of the Horse, three generations will be doomed.
And the family of the man, too.
You were born in the Year of the Horse!
Year of the Horse?
Looking at compatibility? Are we getting married?
Compatibility is important to this business!
Im Sol, do you believe in fate, that kind of thing?
Yes, I do.
I'm not doing anything fate doesn't want me to do.
I trust you've understood plenty. I'm leaving.
♫  The clear picture of myself is fading  ♫
Unbelievable. I'm going to lose my mind.
♫  The dreams that filled countless nights  ♫
Im Sol, do you believe in fate, that kind of thing?
Yes, I do.
I'm not doing anything fate doesn't want me to do.
♫  I was swaying and flowed down to somewhere while I cried  ♫
♫  My sighs are collecting, and I couldn't see the happy days  ♫
♫  I'll get them back, I won't let them get away  ♫
♫  I'll hold onto them, never let them go  ♫
♫  Even when the night is gone  ♫
What kind of dream was that?
- That girl must really hate you.
- What?
Unless she truly hates you as a person, she wouldn't reject you like that.
Why would she hate me? She's never met me.
Why does she have to like you? She's never met you.
Buddy, stop assuming everyone in the world likes you.
Anyone has the right to dislike us.
Geez. Seriously.
The Year of the Horse thing is a little ridiculous.
Sung Jae Kyung was born in the Year of the Horse, too.
What? He's a horse, too?
Yeah. He was born in 1978.
Wow, I thought that was a crazy excuse.
This is how she's going to play it?
Hello?
It's Ryu Sun Jae. Can we—
Why is he calling me?
- What was that?
- What else? She hung up on you.
Wow, she hung up on you hearing your name.
She's really icing you out.
Dong Seok!
You call her.
You want to invest in the film?
You must have more money than you can spend.
Yes, I think so.
No thank you.
We can make the movie on our own.
It's not a blockbuster or anything.
She says no thank you.
Say they can cut my fee in half.
- His fee—
- Wait.
Tell her I'll do it for free.
He'll do it for free.
Again, no, thank you.
Please tell him that puts us in an uncomfortable position.
I did.
I'll cancel my vacation and clear my entire calendar.
I'll devote myself to the movie. Tell her!
Enjoy your vacation. Please tell him he can devote himself to the rest of his calendar.
- Can we talk in person?
- Goodness, I have a meeting. Bye.
She hung up.
- Hyung.
- Why?
Why does she hate me so much?
Maybe because you were born in the Year of the Horse?
That's not it. Don't ever say "horse" in front of me ever again.
Hyung, just give up before things get uglier.
Sometimes, you get rejected.
Why are you insisting on humiliating yourself?
You must have your reasons.
Your makeup looks great today.
Hey! Stop right there!
Hey!
When did you sneak in here again?
Let's go. Careful.
Mom, stay right here.
Stay right here. I'll be right back after I throw this out.
Yes, ma'am!
Mal Ja!
I'm going home.
Get home safe.
Yeah, Mom.
Sol! Grandma disappeared in the blink of an eye.
What do I do?
Hey. Come.
- Grandma!
Grandma!
Boss, the old lady by herself at table 5.
She's eaten five orders by herself. It's weird.
I think her mind isn't fully there.
Okay, let me go see.
Watch the counter.
Ma'am, how is everything?
I've only had a bite. How would I know?
Let me judge after I've eaten some more.
Oh, sure, of course.
Gosh, you've eaten five orders by yourself.
Do you need anything else?
Oh, I... Gosh, thank you.
Blue door?
What?
That's right! You're the guy across the street.
I'm from Gold Video &amp; DVD.
Don't you remember me?
Gosh! The grandma across the street!
Gosh, what a coincidence!
How have you been?
My goodness, your son turned out so well.
I don't like bragging about my child.
But my son is just famous enough that
1, no, 11 out of 10 people in Korea know who he is.
He's just as popular as Na Hoon Ah in his heyday.
No, he has a long way to go until he can catch up to Na Hoon Ah.
But there were 50,000 people at his last concert.
That's like a neighborhood kid's birthday party.
Grandma, we haven't seen each other in years. Let's do cheers.
May you live long and healthy! Cheers!
Gosh, stop, stop.
Wow, speaking of the devil!
My son is here!
Son! Come on!
Dad, how much did you drink?
Hey, I'm not drunk.
Also, I still have the side dishes you gave me last time.
I don't want to take more home.
Stop it, brat.
Hey! Say hello.
Remember the video place across the street when you were young?
She's the grandma of that family. Say hi.
- Hello.
- My son.
Husband!
(Sounds like "stand up")
Stand, stand. Stand up straight.
My man, where have you been all night?
You were gambling again, weren't you?
Grandma, let go of him.
You reek of women's makeup.
Maybe you weren't at the gambling house. You were at the coffee shop.
Which bitch were you with? Was it that Kkot Bun girl?
Was it Cho In? Which bitch were you with?
- Grandma...
- Gosh, falling for this smooth face,
I'm the fool for marrying you at 18.
Sun Jae.
She must have dementia.
Grandma. Grandma.
Hold on, maybe she took the bus.
Wait.
That's it. The 27 bus.
Check the CCTV along the bus line and see where she got off.
Hey, Mom.
I'm watching the CCTV footage with Tae Sung.
Sol, we found Grandma.
What? You found her?
Where?
Someone read her ID tag.
She was eating at a restaurant.
The owner is going to bring her home. Come home now.
Thank goodness.
Sol.
Thank you for today. I know you're busy.
I have time to take you home.
And try to drive your car.
It's dangerous out there.
- Did something happen?
- Attempted kidnapping of a woman.
There's no evidence, so we haven't narrowed down a suspect.
So, when the sun goes down, go home right away. Okay?
If you're working late, call me.
If I have time, I'll pick you up.
No thanks. Save that for your girlfriend.
I thought you were my girlfriend.
Why am I your girlfriend?
Are you a boy, then? You're a girl.
I'm a friend to you. Not a girl.
Yes, Chief. Right now?
Go, go.
I'll be right there.
Get home safe. Let me know how your grandma's doing.
- You, too.
- Bye.
Bye!
That must be your boyfriend.
How did you know...
- What a sweet boyfriend.
- He's not!
Also, if you show up at my house like this,
I feel a little taken aback.
Oh, really?
What are you doing?
I'm not getting in that car.
I have nothing more to say to you.
So, please go.
You're really letting me go?
- You won't regret it?
- Of course not.
I already said no.
We don't ever need to see each other again.
I'm not getting in!
Why? Are you going to threaten me with my resignation letter again?
Is this funny to you?
Yes. It is.
Are you having fun toying with someone's livelihood?
Why don't you just tell the CEO everything?
You keep coming to find me. I can't take this anymore.
I might as well get fired!
His whole personality is different.
Let me go! I'm not a doormat!
I don't care how much you beg and plead. It won't work!
Unni! Where are you going?
I thought the owner of the restaurant was driving you home...
My dad has a restaurant.
That must have surprised you.
I hadn't visited my dad in a while.
This surprised me quite a bit.
Gosh, you're here!
I should have gone over there.
Thank you so much for bringing her home.
I should thank you before you leave. Would you like to come up?
That's all right. Have a good night.
Unni, I need to pee.
Okay, okay.
It wouldn't be polite to just let you go.
My bladder is going to explode.
Okay, Mom, just hold on a second, Miss Mal Ja.
Sol, get him a warm cup of tea before he leaves. Okay?
We'll go upstairs, then. Thank you so much.
Thank you!
Let's go. Let's go, Miss Mal Ja. Let's go.
- I'm going to explode!
- No, no. Hold it, hold it.
Take it.
I misunderstood.
Thank you for bringing my grandma home.
Don't you need to get me a cup of tea?
Here's the tea.
Is this how you thank someone?
Nothing around here is open this late.
If we sit out like this and rumors start about us dating,
will you be responsible for it?
- No one's around.
- We have to be careful.
I don't want a scandal.
Romance is my specialty as an actor.
Since when?
(It means "sweet")
- What about it?
- All right.
Look into my eyes.
I hear that I have the "eyes for romance" a lot.
What?
Huh?
Good timing.
You saw that, right? Advertisers approved. I. Am. A. Fresh. Face.
Are you trying to convince me to cast you in my film?
No, not at all.
I'm just spitting facts.
I'm still fresh, and I can do romance.
If you let me go, it's your loss.
Oh, really?
Darn, they recognized me.
We could be in an unnecessary scandal.
- Just pretend like you're my stylist.
- What?
It's not like you have style, but...
Hey, girls! Don't be shy, come over here.
Oh, my god!
You want a photo? An autograph?
Mister, could you get us a pack of cigarettes?
You don't know who I am?
- What?
- What is he talking about?
Oh! I get it!
You can get yourself a coffee with the change, Mister.
It's a tip.
You're too young to be smoking!
Go away!
Go! Now!
- How annoying.
- Let's go.
Is this funny to you?
Yes, it is.
I've never seen you laugh before.
- Are you done laughing?
- Yes.
Good night, then.
My dad mentioned that we used to be neighbors.
Your mom used to run a video store. Right?
I lived across from your house.
Did you ever see me back then?
No, I didn't.
Maybe I've seen you before.
I thought maybe that's why you looked familiar.
I've never seen you. How would you have seen me?
Right.
By the way, that Heavenly Granny might be a quack.
Whether we've met before or not, it might be fate at this rate.
I think... it's just a coincidence.
Coincidence.
I won't change my mind just because we were neighbors once.
Even if my CEO offers you the movie, please say no.
I'm asking you.
What if I want to do it, whether you approve or not?
What happens then?
I hope you won't do that.
I'll get going now.
Look into my eyes.
Is this funny to you?
Yes, it is.
I don't care how much you beg and plead, it won't work!
I'm home.
You're home already?
Did you just let him go?
Yeah. He said it was okay and just left.
Oppa and Hyun Joo are home, too. Right?
They're putting the kids to bed.
Hey, he's not the owner of the restaurant. Right?
It wasn't him on the phone.
He's probably an employee or something.
No way. He had a lot of charisma.
His face, height, and voice...
Plus, I feel like I've seen him before.
I've seen him...
Right! The TV drama!
Ryu...
Ryu Sun Jae! It was him. That's right! Ryu Sun Jae.
Of course, that wasn't him. That's crazy.
It totally was.
Mom, stay here for a second.
I'm hungry.
Grandma, Grandma.
Stop going places by yourself.
How did you even know that BBQ restaurant anyway?
Don't ever go there again. Got it?
Yes, ma'am.
Grandma did a good job, though. Right?
- What?
- You missed him.
Mom! Get in here!
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, you are right, Grandma.
I missed him.
It might be fate at this rate.
I shouldn't do this.
But the more I see him... the more I miss him.
She's a runaway middle schooler.
I think it's the same perp as the attempted kidnapping last time. Same method.
Thankfully, she yelled at a passerby for help and ran away.
Are you feeling better?
Should we talk when your parents get here?
No.
I can tell you now.
Okay.
Did you get a chance to see his face?
Yes.
I know it might be hard to remember, but can you try to describe it in detail?
Honey! Honey!
Honey, Honey, Honey, Honey!
I got Bo Ah ready for school already!
I did a good job braiding her hair. Right?
Hearts! Heart on the cheek!
Want a shoulder massage? You must be so tired!
Bo Ah! You are so pretty.
Bo Ah, Mommy's busy today, so Daddy's taking you to daycare.
Okay.
Daddy, I don't think Mommy can see you.
It's because Daddy is wearing an invisibility cloak.
Only pretty people can see me!
Bo Ah, let's go. Say bye to ommy.
- Bye-bye!
Give Mommy a kiss.
- Have a good day!
- Daddy wants a kiss, too!
Fighting, Honey!
Geez! So frustrating.
Where could my scarf be?
What is this?
He spent money on something useless again.
Hyun Joo, are you going to work?
I'm coming.
What? Why?
What do you mean, why?
Ryu Sun Jae wants to do it. Why do you need a reason?
He likes your pitch.
I'm still going to say no.
Then what? What are you going to do?
You think it's easy to get a top star cast in a romance film?
I heard you kept saying no.
Not to mention last time.
What are you doing without discussing it with us?
Is this a joke to you?
Especially after what happened with Park Do Jun,
we need to get Ryu Sun Jae, no matter what.
It doesn't matter if you're against it.
Sure. Then please go ahead with the movie.
I'll leave the company.
What? Are you protesting or something?
It's not that.
I really can't work with Ryu Sun Jae. I mean, I shouldn't.
So, I'll just give up this project.
I'll let it go and leave.
What? H-Hey, are you serious?
Thank you... for everything.
Hey!
Sol.
Sol!
What are you doing? Are you thinking clearly?
Yes, I am.
Why did you do what you did?
If you hadn't sent him my pitch, this wouldn't have happened!
Hey.
But wasn't that a good thing for you?
No.
You have no idea what it took to cut him off. What it felt like to end it!
I can't cross paths with him again.
Sol.
What's wrong? Is something going on?
It's the middle of winter.
Why are they filming a commercial outside?
Today might be a little warmer, though.
Hey. Do you know a song called "Rain Shower"?
It's a common title.
There must be quite a few like that. Which one?
Never mind.
By the way, CEO Lee from Bon Cinema wants to set up a meeting.
But someone else is the producer in charge now, not Im Sol.
- Why?
- She doesn't want to be a part of this movie.
It's her movie. She doesn't want to be involved?
No. What is this movie about? Why are you being like this?
A woman travels 15 years to the past to save the man she loves.
It's not a novel concept.
Right. It's not very novel at all.
It's strange.
Her phone is off, too.
She's not going to actually quit. Right?
There's no way.
I don't think the CEO is taking it seriously, either.
Let me talk to her at home later.
She said her dream was to be a film director. How can she throw this opportunity out the window?
It's so strange.
Did something actually happen between her and Ryu Sun Jae?
She's not the kind of person to dislike someone for no reason.
What?
What's wrong?
This place hasn't changed at all.
When we meet again in the future, we can come together.
♫  So I had to let it go  ♫
It's too bad I don't even have a photo of it.
I guess there can't be one.
♫  I call your name, I can see a little clearer  ♫
♫  Maybe I was waiting for this, in these lost times  ♫
Oh, my.
I must have been here for hours.
♫  One moment, your scent came to me  ♫
♫  I won't let it disappear, I won't let it get away  ♫
♫  Don't let go of my hands  ♫
Sol!
♫  This moment, everything  ♫
Hyung, I think the shoot's going to be canceled.
- Why?
- The actress got into a collision on her way here.
- Is she okay?
- Yeah.
Oh, well. There's not much we can do about it then.
It's cold. Let me get the car out.
I'll take that. I'll be right back.
It's this bastard.
Senior!
- Here's the sketch.
- Let me see.
It's him.
Just wait a moment.
You can get in now.
- Closing the door.
- I'm with her.
What? How did you...
Are you worried I followed you or something?
I'm here to film a commercial, but the shoot got canceled.
I was thinking about the Ferris wheel scene in the pitch.
We meet again.
I told you that Heavenly Granny is a quack.
At this point, I think the heavens are setting us up.
Fine, let's say you happened to see me.
You should've gone on your way. Why follow me?
Riding a Ferris wheel car together? We're not that close.
You want to run away, but you can't just hop off.
That's what you are thinking. Right?
You can't run away until we've done a full circle.
Do you really hate me that much?
I heard you're not going to be involved in the production.
Yes.
- I quit the company, so...
- Why?
I don't want you to.
Why does it matter to you?
Are you sick?
No. Let's just sit in silence until we get off.
So, is that really how it ends?
- What?
- The ending.
Does that man really forget everything about the girl he loved
and goes on living like that?
Yes.
What a sad ending.
From her perspective, it's a happy ending.
She saved his life.
But lost her love.
After she loses her love, is she happy?
See? It's a sad ending.
I don't like how it ends.
If you don't like it, just don't do the movie.
Why are you being so pushy?
I was being pushy before, but now I'm sincere.
I really want to do this movie.
Why do you want to do this movie so badly?
You must have many more great pitches, directors, scripts, and writers who want you.
♫  'Cause I'm falling slowly love with you  ♫
I...
feel a little weird these days.
After I read your pitch, something weird happened to me.
I keep tearing up.
I have dreams, too.
Vivid dreams as if they actually happened to me.
And, this place...
♫  I'm dreaming again  ♫
♫  No matter what happens  ♫
♫  I will find you  ♫
♫  'Cause I'm falling slowly in love with you  ♫
♫  I've been waiting for this for so long  ♫
It's my first time here, but it feels familiar.
Like I've been here before.
Sun Jae...
Maybe that's why I'm drawn to it more than any other project.
Is that not allowed?
You might die.
If I told you,
you might die if you get involved with me,
would you still want to do it?
In order to be close to you, do I need to be ready to die?
What if I said yes?
Why aren't you saying anything?
It's so pretty.
It's so pretty that I'm at a loss for words.
♫  If I miss you this much, will it come true?  ♫
♫  I want to tell you someday before it's too late  ♫
♫  I never let go, not even a moment  ♫
♫  I never forgot all this time  ♫
Maybe we might die together right here.
♫  When you fall like petals, like I've been waiting for  ♫
At that moment, I thought...
our fates are like this Ferris wheel, going round and round.
♫  Will you remember my heart?  ♫
♫  Crossing over all of time  ♫
♫  I'll find you  ♫
♫  I'll run to you  ♫
♫  I remember you  ♫
♫  Maybe this time  ♫
Sun Jae...
You'll feel better soon. Get some sleep.
He's really famous.
I heard you're starring in my Sol's movie.
She told me she doesn't have a boyfriend.
I got it then came this way, I mean, I was passing by.
Producer Im left the company.
Ryu Sun Jae, please stay healthy and be well.
I'm leaving now.
I think it's him.
- Is there such a thing as fate?
- Sol!
A certain destiny you can't change or cross?
♫  The day snow fell like petals  ♫