Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
✨ The Marvellous ✨ Team @ Viki.com
♫  I wished the rain would never end  ♫
This is DJ Ham's Ten-Ten Friends.
I'm with Sun Jae here, headed to part two.
It's the rainy season.
And it's raining today as usual.
Which is why we're listening to "Rain Shower" by Eclipse.
Did you know? This song was
voted number one as the "Song that reminds you of your first love."
Sun Jae, I just found out that you wrote this song before your debut.
Yes.
Were you thinking of your first love when you were writing?
Whoa, from your reaction, I think I'm right.
Your movie that's about to come out is also about first love.
- Yes.
- Could you tell us about your first love?
I promise your secret is safe with me.
My first love?
♫   You came down like a rain shower one day  ♫
It was raining the day I met her.
Mister!
Holding a yellow umbrella over me, she smiled at me.
I was so nervous that I couldn't breathe.
As if I had forgotten how to breathe.
- Oh, my! When was that?
- He used to say his fans were his first love.
That... is a secret.
Who could she be? I'm so curious.
This isn't worth singing in front of all those people!
Why are you worried about me?
Hey.
Come with me.
Have you seen Tae Sung?
Choi Ga Hyun dragged Im Sol somewhere!
Who is that?
- He's hot.
- He's so tall!
Hey!
Let Kim Tae Sung deal with it.
How can I just do nothing?
What if she's somewhere getting beat up?
What's going on out of the blue?
I told you you're not allowed to break Sol's heart.
- What?
- I heard you don't actually like me.
You just dated a random girl to get Choi Ga Hyun off your back.
And I happen to be that rando...?
- Who said that?
- Does that matter?
I didn't know you were that much of a shitface. I'm so disappointed.
I'm just glad that I found out first.
Anyway, you and I are over, dude! Do you understand?
I know you're just acting your age... but don't live your life like that.
Oh!
By the way...
even if I come back and say, "I don't remember breaking up,"
saying some nonsense and beg you to take me back, don't ever take me back.
Geez, seriously.
Yeah, this is for the best.
High school seniors should focus on studies, not romance.
It's my number one treasure.
Here we go again.
Let's go. We're late.
What?
- This is still...
- You can talk.
Wow, you walked right out of an advertisement.
You came alive.
Yeah, you are so funny.
How do I delete this?
Sun Jae.
You told me to only think about myself. Right?
Can you break up with him?
If that's what I want, can you do that?
I like you.
Then break up with Kim Tae Sung.
I... like you.
Why?
Why would Sun Jae like me?
- Did you get beat up?
- No way!
Did somebody hit you?
Im Sol!
♫  I think I do  ♫
I like you.
Why do I keep thinking about it?
What's wrong with me?
What is wrong with you?
- What?
- Why are you yelling at the onions?
You've been crying this whole time. Is something wrong?
No. It's nothing.
My eyes hurt so much.
It's because you've been smashing the onions with your bare hands.
Put this in your mouth.
It still hurts.
Look at you ugly crying.
Stop peeling them and go get some makgeolli from the store.
I forgot to get some.
It hurts!
I didn't know you were that much of a shit face.
I'm so disappointed.
Anyway, you and I are over, dude!
Do you understand?
What are you thinking about instead of eating?
It's weird.
What is?
- In here?
- In there?
How do I say this?
Something... Something is...
- What?
- ...hurting.
- Your heart?
- My heart.
Hey, if you got hit in the head, your head should hurt. Why is your heart hurting?
I know, right?
I know. You're pissed that Im Sol kicked you to the curb.
You're all worked up and pissed, aren't you?
Hey, do you have a death wish?
You are so careless.
What right do you have to tell her to break up with him?
Then, should I just sit and watch her date a jerk like him?
You can't say that before properly telling her how you feel.
You're like a candle, you know.
You always blow it.
I'm going to go insane.
Hey, don't just sit there. Want to go on a blind date?
- Hey! Let's just go.
- No.
Let's go.
A blind date?
That dude...
- Hey! Hey!
- Is she on your mind?
Not at all.
Should I say yes?
- Don't do it.
- Sure, set it up.
Yeah, if you got dumped, just go out with someone new.
I'm going to go, too.
What's up with you?
Did you get dumped?
Are you making fun of me?
- Wow.
- Have fun on your blind date.
Fighting!
Wow, he got d-d-dumped?
Hey, Ryu Sun Jae!
Is he insane?
He's insane.
How much did you cry?
What?
Hold on. Ow!
Stop crying!
Why are you crying over that SOB?
What?
What are you talking about? This is because of onions.
Onions?
Kim Tae Sung is an onion?
What?
What's with the alcohol?
You're already trying to cope with alcohol?
Just lean on me instead!
Why do you keep drinking?
I mean, this isn't it, Sun Jae...
Give it to me.
What? Let go.
No! I can't see you fall apart.
I'm not going to fall apart. What the heck? Give it back!
No! No matter how hard, this isn't it.
Give it back, Sun Jae!
Give it back!
Are you going to keep doing this? Are you really?
Are you really?
What's going on with you?
What?
I'm going to pour this out.
What the heck? I was picking it up for my grandma!
That bastard...
Get your hands off her!
Crazy bastard, how dare you do that to my sister?
Sun Jae!
Brother! Are you crazy?
Shouldn't you have taken him to the hospital?
Hospital?
How could he be like that with a little bit of makgeolli?
Hey, he's kind of pathetic. Right?
It's your fault!
Makgeolli doesn't sit well with Sun Jae.
He'll pass out after just one sip.
Sun Jae must be burning up!
How can you sleep like you're dead?
I like you.
I... like you.
What was that?
Where am I?
This is crazy.
Sorry.
What? You...
Oh... that...
The fan. I wanted to turn the fan on for you.
Oh, no.
Why is the fan here again?
What? Did he fall off the bed?
Geez. Whatever.
Geez! Why is it so cold all of a sudden?
He's strong even when he's asleep.
I'm so cold.
Is he asleep?
What are you two doing?
Oh, I don't know why I'm sleeping here!
Maybe I sleepwalk.
You two, seriously...
Come here! Come here!
Hey, let go!
You bastard, how dare you do that move on me?
Why aren't you coming in?
Did you get a confession of love or something?
How did you know?
Really? From whom?
Wait, from Ryu Sun Jae?
How can Sun Jae like me?
Why does such a dazzling boy like me?
Girl, you seduced him.
I did? When?
Think about it.
You broke into the swim arena and told him you loved him.
You kept skipping study sessions to follow him around.
You went to his match to cheer for him.
When he got shoulder surgery, you brought him food every day.
That's because I had a reason to.
A reason? Please.
Then why did you crawl into his room when he was asleep?
You know he likes you.
You're an old vixen.
I'm not a vixen.
I am older than nineteen, though.
I think he's been so into sports and single his whole life.
Guys like that have a weakness for girls who approach them like bulldozers.
Really?
Anyway, I can't stand people who dangle it in front of you.
Whether I'm pooping or not, why take your clothes off?
If you don't want to give me your heart, don't dangle it in front of me.
Poop? Who did?
What?
Don't get distracted. Come inside and study.
Did I just confuse him when he did nothing?
So loud.
Sun Jae!
Oh!
What are you doing here?
- I came to see you.
- Don't come on too strong
right after her breakup.
Don't be obvious. Don't be clingy. Be cool.
Not.
I'm at the library to study.
Oh, okay.
Studying. Yes.
Wow, I got the seat next to you.
What a coincidence.
R-Right.
Then... good luck studying.
Oh, okay.
Y-Y-You, too. Good luck.
Those two are here to romance each other.
- Lee Seung Yuop bats...
- Hit! Hit!
A grounder for second base.
- To the second base.
- Is it a double play?
Right. She lost her phone.
Oh, I heard that Choi Ga Hyun is still bullying Im Sol.
She keeps dragging her around.
What? Why are you just telling me this?
Because I just heard it today.
Dude.
You bastard.
How are you going to go to college?
You got level 8s on everything.
How many levels are there?
Is that really low?
It's not just low. It's on the floor.
I'm applying with special skills, so I just need to meet the minimum.
What is the minimum?
Level 5.
You're level 8.
We're already at the 8th inning.
Can they start scoring?
You got 8s on everything.
8, 8, 8, 8.
Wow, he looks good.
Lee Seung Yuop is playing very well.
But the collegiate exams are coming up soon. Don't you think this is a bit too much?
- You said you'd help me.
- I did.
But it's been a while since I studied for the collegiate exam, too.
I can't even remember the quadratic formula. What do I do?
Spit it out!
Hurry! You'll burn your mouth!
Isn't it hot?
I'm okay.
Score.
What? What do you mean you scored?
Look! He scored.
Lee Seung Yuop! Lee Seung Yuop! Lee Seung Yuop!
He scored twice. Wow.
Lee Seung Yuop!
Republic of Korea!
Oh? Is it going to rain?
I have an umbrella. I brought it with me today.
Wait! Where is it? The library?
I might have left it at the restaurant.
Where are you going? You're going to get soaked.
I don't know who's dangling it in front of whom.
You almost broke your skull.
It's working, seriously.
Huh? We must have won the baseball game.
I think we did.
Wow, I didn't think we would make it to the finals.
What are you thinking about?
What? Nothing.
Is she still heartbroken over Kim Tae Sung?
Should we go... cheer on the streets for the finals?
- On the streets?
- Yeah.
I can't stand people who dangle it in front of others.
The exams are soon! We need to be studying.
Hey! How can you study all day, every day, in that cramped room?
You need to clear your head and get fresh air once in a while.
It's just one day. Can you go?
You know the English vocabulary book you were looking at?
- If you memorize that whole thing.
- The whole thing?
Wow, so you don't want to go.
So, focus on studying.
What if I memorize the whole thing?
You said you would go if I did.
I'll memorize the whole thing in a day.
Let's go.
What the heck is he doing?
What is wrong with him?
It stopped raining. Why are you sharing an umbrella?
Standing so close?
- Did you go somewhere together?
- None of your business.
What are you doing here?
We need to talk.
- I don't have anything to say to you.
- I do.
You just listen.
- She said no.
- Why don't you back off?
You butted in first.
Oh, should I have turned on my blinkers?
Okay, okay.
Let's hear what you have to say.
Wait.
What?
Be cool.
Good luck with the talk.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Night.
Stop. Just forget about me.
What does that mean?
- Just forget me!
- How do I do that?
You're crazy.
Yes, Kim Tae Sung is crazy.
He is a criminal.
His crime was loving one woman to death!
Tae Sung!
If loving someone was a crime, I would be sentenced to life.
This is crazy.
Im Sol!
You are my star!
No way.
What do you want to say?
I don't have a lot of time, so spit it out.
I heard Choi Ga Hyun was bullying you.
I didn't know.
Did you get hurt?
You cried a lot. Right?
No! I didn't cry at all.
You didn't? Why not?
I was used. Do I need to cry over that?
No, I guess.
But for some reason, I'm sad.
- Why are you sad?
- Exactly.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
That's what I came here to say.
I'm really sorry.
I guess you're not a total shitface.
Also, I wasn't using you.
- Then why did you ask me out?
- You said you liked me.
Do you date everyone who says they like you?
- No.
- Are you talking or farting?
- Huh?
- What?
Did...
Did I like you?
- What the...
- That's right.
- I did like you.
- Wow!
Wow, y-y-you are ridiculous.
How can this be?
I think I liked you a lot.
No thanks.
If you came to give that back, hand it back and go.
It's not like that.
Then what? Are you going to throw it out? Give it to me.
Let go! I said it's not like that!
It's my favorite stuffed animal. I cuddle with it all the time.
What nonsense! Give it back!
It's mine!
Tae Sung! Our love is forever!
Should we just be together forever?
No!
The biggest villain of my life is me in the past.
Huh?
What's wrong?
My legs are cramping.
Huh?
Goodness, you are such a good son.
Bending those long legs to help me pull out the weeds.
Gosh, you are all grown up now.
My son, you know what?
Plants can hear us.
So, if you caress them like this every day,
and tell them, "You're so pretty," and say nice things,
- they grow much faster.
- Where is she? What are they talking about?
So, Sun Jae...
I'll only say nice things to you.
Goodness, my son...
You lowlife bastard!
Do those look like weeds to you?
Why are you pulling out healthy peppers and shit?
Go away! Go away!
Are you helping or screwing me over, you little turd!
Gosh, my poor little peppers, so sorry...
Goodness, my babies...
- Dad!
- My goodness...
You were born with the wrong older brother.
Stop getting into fights.
You should graduate from high school, at least.
You'll regret it later.
Is it good?
Forever, my ass.
Mom, are you going somewhere?
I told you.
I'm going to Jeju Island with my friends.
- Jeju?
- Yes.
Her trip with that guy must have been today.
You're leaving your high school senior daughter behind to go to Jeju Island?
It's with the guy who drove you home last time. Right?
Who cares?
Plus, you don't get a crown for being a high school senior!
I busted my ass to raise you guys alone. Am I not allowed to go on vacation?
I feel bad for Dad. That's why!
He was worried about you until the day he died.
He couldn't even rest in peace. I feel so sorry for him!
Hand wash your uniform shirts every day.
Don't just throw them in the hamper.
Don't ask for new ones when other colored clothes bleed on them.
Okay, I got it.
And soak your dishes after you eat.
You always leave them with food still stuck on them
and we get maggots and fruit flies. So disgusting.
And tell your brother.
If he drinks and falls asleep on the streets
and gets caught, I'm disowning him.
Lock your doors, and don't sleep with your windows open, even if it's hot.
Okay, I said I got it!
Mom, we're not toddlers, you know.
You two might be older, but you're still clueless.
It's because you keep coddling us.
If you're not here, we'll do even better.
Goodness, really?
You'll be fine without your mom, huh?
Of course!
See? You raise a child all for nothing.
Did you just realize that?
They say when you're old and sick, turn to your husband, not your kids.
So, find a new husband soon.
Hey, when I get old and sick, I should die. Not find a husband.
Enough! Stop spewing nonsense and go inside.
I'll be back. Go study!
Have fun, Mom!
So, what you're saying is, not today, not tomorrow,
but on September 1st, something may or may not happen to you.
You want to tell me what that is, but you can't.
Yes. Exactly.
Student, if you think something's going to happen at the reservoir that day,
just don't go near it. Right?
That's true, but...
Okay, okay.
Okay. Have one of these and get home safe. Okay?
Okay.
Go home.
Something might happen, so don't come back!
She's normal looking for a crazy girl.
Hello, Detective Kim.
What do you mean? Something might happen?
Oh, it's just crazy talk.
What brings you here?
You know the night patrol logs from last month?
Can I see them organized by the hour?
Lee Seung Yuop hits the ball high...
- It gets above the right fielder!
- We won, we won.
It flies over the fence!
Hello?
If you called, you need to say something.
Excuse me.
I picked up a cell phone.
Oh, yes! That belongs to my granddaughter.
You must have found it.
How should I get this to you?
I'll come pick it up from you.
Where do I go?
Oh, no! I'm in the countryside.
Oh, then, could you mail it to us?
I'll give you the address.
Should I?
Study?
♫  That night, when everyone's gathered  ♫
♫  When you're not sitting in your usual seat  ♫
When did you get here?
♫  When I catch your scent, the one that I liked so much  ♫
♫  I turn my head, wondering if it's you  ♫
♫  When I find myself in your neighborhood  ♫
♫  When I keep thinking of your face  ♫
♫  I think I do, I think I like you  ♫
It's my number one treasure.
♫  Day by day, all I think of is you  ♫
♫  I want to see you, I can do better  ♫
♫  I want to be brave and pick up the phone, but I can't  ♫
♫  Like a fool  ♫
I like you.
I... like you.
"My friend is h-hardworking."
Hardworking. Hardworking.
This is crazy!
What is?
N-No, nothing.
But... why is your face so red?
Huh?
B-Because it's hot.
Hey.
- Do you know?
- What?
Have you noticed?
W-What?
I...
- I memorized everything.
- What?
You said we'd go cheer for the baseball finals if I memorized all the vocabulary.
If you don't believe me, test me.
Oh, no, it's not that...
Then, you're coming with me tomorrow.
I have to tell you something.
Republic of Korea!
We can feel the passion of the citizens who have gathered to cheer for the national team.
8 games, 8 wins.
Our national team is writing their own legend with every match.
Can our national team take us all the way to the gold?
- Im Sol! Over here!
- Republic of Korea!
Republic of Korea!
Excuse me.
Excuse me...
You're early!
Yeah, I wanted a good spot.
I think we'll get a good view here.
Really? Weren't you hot?
♫  Will it be embarrassing to say, "I miss you"?  ♫
That feels amazing.
I was burning up.
♫  Even if I close my eyes  ♫
♫  I really miss you  ♫
Right. It's really hot.
♫  I can't hide my feelings, can you hear it?  ♫
♫  Could I tell you how I feel inside?  ♫
♫  Didn't you feel it a little, too?  ♫
That helps, right?
♫  These are my true feelings  ♫
♫  I hope you know, I hope you see me  ♫
Hyun Joo is here!
Is that you?
Oh, you're here too!
Where's Sol? Is she out?
You'd know better than me.
You brought chicken, Hyun Joo!
I brought it to share with Sol while we watch baseball.
If Sol's not here, I'm leaving.
Don't go.
Or if you do...
leave the chicken with me.
This is the men's baseball finals at the 2008 Beijing Olympics.
Octopus?
Oh, this?
Stop! Stop!
How many times will you play Choi Min Sik? How boring.
That's why you never get it.
Just because you dress up like him doesn't mean you can move the people the same way.
You need authenticity in your acting.
Maybe you're right.
I get rejected at every audition, so I wanted to stand out.
But I think you're right.
Why is he pulling at my heartstrings? I want to protect him.
Get it together! You can't fall for this!
Oh! Hit it! Good! Damn...
Hey, why aren't you eating?
Here. Have some.
He's unexpectedly sweet. I'm getting butterflies in my stomach...
Get it together! Don't you dare fall for this!
Hyun Joo, look.
Clean!
If someone looks at the bone,
they shouldn't be able to tell if you had fried or sauced.
Why am I falling for lines like that?
He's Im Geum. The kind of person I hate the most.
Gosh, but he's still cute!
No. I can't fall for this.
- Lee Seung Yuop hits to the left...
- I can never fall for him.
I can't. Never...
Is it going to make it? Is it?
- No, no!
- It's gone!
Yes! He did it!
Lee Seung Yuop, a home run!
Hyun Joo!
We can win! We can win!
Lee Seung Yuop hit a home run! This is crazy!
I fell for it.
Hi, sweetie baby.
Geum is watching baseball right now.
I thought you were busy, Princess Chae Won.
Yeah.
Yeah, see you tomorrow. Kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss.
- What?
- Do you have a girlfriend?
Yeah.
Why?
Am I not allowed to have a girlfriend?
No!
Why are you just telling me this now?
Hey! Where are you going?
The score is 2:1!
Lee Yong Gyu! Lee Yong Gyu!
Lee Young Gyu scores a double!
Lee Yong Gyu did it!
- Lee Yong Gyu! Lee Yong Gyu!
- It's 3:1!
Hey, how busy can your dad be?
His son is in the hospital, and he hasn't even shown up.
Korea is leading by a point...
The streets are hot with passionate fans who are gathered.
Hey, that was Im Sol and Ryu Sun Jae. Right?
Wow, I guess she's educated and smart.
She got it together to date a wholesome guy.
Right?
Get out. Go home.
Take this and go home.
- I'm still eating!
- Get out.
- What's wrong?
- Get out, you bastard.
- What's wrong with you?
- Hurry up, dude.
I'm out!
The game isn't even over yet.
We are at the end of the 9th inning with one out...
Guriel at the plate, Jung Dae Hyun is the pitcher...
No ball, two strikes!
Oh, is it a double?
It's a gold for South Korea
A gold medal!
Republic of Korea wins the gold medal!
A gold for South Korea's baseball team!
♫  All those hidden seasons  ♫
♫  Are calling us back again  ♫
♫  Wherever I am... ♫
Republic of Korea!
- Republic of Korea!
- I have to tell you something!
What? What did you say?
- A gold medal for Korea!
- Republic of Korea!
♫  I've been waiting for this for so long  ♫
♫  'Cause I'm falling slowly in love with you  ♫
Republic of Korea!
♫  All my life, it's you  ♫
What?
What's going on?
I was going to wait a bit longer.
- But I don't think I can hide it anymore.
- What?
You know what I used to hate the most?
Rain.
After being in a swimming pool all day long,
going outside, getting wet again in the rain pissed me off.
But... it rained the day I met you.
I liked the rain that day.
I hated it all my life, but I liked it overnight.
I thought it would just be that day.
But no.
I still don't hate it.
I don't think I'll hate it again.
Rain... or you.
Sol.
I... like you a lot.
Y-You don't need to answer right away.
Sun Jae!
I...
Take it.
Maybe it's urgent.
Hello?
It's Kim Tae Sung.
Are you with Im Sol right now?
Why are you calling me?
- Let's go.
- What?
What's going on?
Your mom.
She's in the hospital.
What?
Doctor, a patient named Park Bok Soon—
Are you Sol?
I almost didn't recognize you.
I saw you a few times when you were little. Don't you remember me?
We did a biopsy during an endoscopy, and it wasn't good.
But thankfully, we caught it early. She should be okay after surgery.
I had no idea.
Why did I not know?
If you're not here, we'll do even better.
Mom, we're not toddlers, you know.
You'll be fine without your mom, huh?
Of course!
I told her I'd be fine without her.
I didn't know she was sick.
It's not your fault.
Don't think like that.
Thank you for calling.
If you hadn't, my mom would've gone into surgery by herself.
- How is she doing?
- She just went into the OR.
She's going to be okay.
But how did you break your arm?
- You didn't get into a fight, did you?
- No.
I don't know what kind of person you think I am.
That's a relief.
Tae Sung, I don't know what kind of scars you have...
or what kind of pain you're in,
but I don't want you to have regrets later.
I want you to get through this time in your life.
That's the one thing I want to say to my first love.
So please, try to change your destiny, too.
I'll be earnestly praying for you.
I'll be going now.
Why is she acting like that?
Like it's the last time I'll see her.
The painkiller is going in now. If it hurts a lot, let me know.
Thank you.
- Where's Grandma?
- I told Brother to take her home.
She should get some rest and come back tomorrow.
- Don't worry and sleep, Mom.
- Good job.
Why did you come back?
Did the surgery
go well?
Did you get any sleep?
You look tired.
You're going to pass out at this rate.
I'm okay.
You haven't eaten, right? Want me to bring you something?
I'm fine, really.
You can go.
Okay. Then I'll watch you go in and come back tomorrow.
No.
Don't come.
Sun Jae, I can't accept your feelings.
I mean...
I wasn't expecting anything. Don't be so cold.
You're confused because I gave you mixed signals.
- It's not like that.
- I'm sorry I hung around you and led you on.
- I said it's not like that.
- You know...
If you continue like this, I'll feel uncomfortable and pressured.
So, just
stop liking me.
♫  Your low and deep voice  ♫
I forgot to ask you the most important question. How do you feel?
What does it matter? I'm leaving soon anyway.
Where are you going?
Whether you go to a rural school or go abroad,
besides that, what does your heart want?
♫  I would embrace you right there and then  ♫
♫  All day, I miss you  ♫
♫  I want to go back to our time together  ♫
♫  No matter what happens, I will remember you  ♫
♫  Your name is painted deep in my heart  ♫
My dear sister, could you bring my phone charger?
- I forgot...
- At this hour?
Mom will be discharged tomorrow. Just stick it out for the night.
I auditioned for a movie, and they said they would call me. Huh? Please!
You skipped the first day of school and are staying home. Can't you do it for me?
I'm sorry, Brother. I really can't go anywhere today.
So, come get it or buy it somewhere nearby. Figure it out.
Yes. I just need to stick it out for the next two hours.
I'll be fine. Nothing will happen.
Your umbrella is at the library.
Are you not coming anymore because of me?
I won't make you uncomfortable. Can we talk in person?
Just for a minute.
I'll wait for you at the playground.
I'm sorry. I can't go outside today.
Don't wait for me.
Where is he going? Didn't he see my reply?
He's not waiting for me, is he?
Did you ever see me before the practice game?
I did. You thought I was the package delivery guy.
I don't think you remember.
Mister!
It was raining the day I met her.
Holding a yellow umbrella over me, she smiled at me.
I was so nervous that I couldn't breathe.
No way...
It rained the day I met you.
I liked the rain that day.
Sol.
I...
like you a lot.
Since then?
♫  When I find myself in your neighborhood  ♫
♫  When I keep thinking of your face  ♫
♫  I think I do, I think I like you  ♫
♫  Day by day, all I think of is you  ♫
♫  I want to see you, I can do better  ♫
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
✨ The Marvellous ✨ Team @ Viki.com
She kept saying, "I can't go outside today." She was totally overreacting.
I know everything. I can change it.
- Here, here!
- Excuse me, your name?
If you have willpower, you can change your fate. Right?
- What happened?
- Come quick!
He doesn't want to do the movie because of you. What are you going to do about that?
Sun Jae has to be cast.
Who are you? Do we know each other?
No. It can't be...
Sun Jae, don't come.
♫  Inside scattered sense of time  ♫