=The Rise of Ning=
(Adapted from Wen Tan's novel "Chancellor
Training Handbook" from Jinjiang Literature)
=Episode 16=
Second Uncle wouldn't even let him
enter the home academy.
How could Luo Shenyuan...
Pay no attention to others.
You
just need to think about
why you couldn't write good poems
despite the efforts
Mother put in for you.
My dear sister,
literature isn't my ambition.
If it were about martial
or military knowledge,
I'd triumph over everyone.
Shanyuan.
Yiyu.
Your guzheng playing earlier today
was elegant and refined.
Even a fairy musician
couldn't compare to you.
Thank you for your compliment.
We haven't met in a few days.
You seem to be cold toward me.
Are you drunk, Mr. Cheng?
We are merely connected
through our elders.
We are not that familiar.
Why would you say that, Mr. Cheng?
Also,
please stop saying things
like the fairy musician anymore.
People might
misunderstand it.
Shan,
Yixiu isn't feeling well.
Mother wants us
to return to look after her.
To think
that the Luo's Residence
illegitimate son
will soon rise to fame in the capital.
He has such great patience.
The third son of the Luo Family
is not someone to be trifled with.
Seventh Lady.
Your pipa playing earlier
doesn't seem to have been taught
by a female master.
What do you mean, Marquis Lu?
Such ferocious ambiance
shouldn't belong to a woman.
Have you not heard
about the story
of Lady Duchess of Qiao State?
Female generals
haven't been a rare occurrence
since ancient times.
Also, the ferocious ambiance
is not exclusive to men.
What a spirit, Seventh Lady.
Ladies usually play songs
that are peaceful and elegant.
You played a song
with such profound sadness
as if you had experienced it yourself.
Is that a compliment, Marquis Lu?
If that's not your favorite song,
you better not play it.
Isn't that too much to ask,
Marquis Lu?
Whether I like it or play it
has nothing to do with you.
The Literary Feast has ended.
You may take your leave soon
as you have many official duties
at hand.
Are you trying to send me away?
I wouldn't dare.
The Luo's Residence
has a century-old garden,
but I suppose it holds
no interest for you.
I need to go return gifts to the guests.
Please excuse me.
Your Lordship,
is Seventh Lady
the person you have been looking for?
She's like her,
but not entirely.
By the way, any luck with Chen Daoyan?
Not yet.
Come with me.
(As humble as hollow bamboo)
Be gentle with it.
Congratulations.
These are precious.
Put them to...
Congratulations on seeking
a great apprenticeship.
This Literary Feast is a success.
I didn't expect to see
such a fruitful occasion
after so many years.
This is truly rare.
It's all thanks to you, Mr. Sun.
Not at all. Please stop here,
Registrar Luo.
Please wait a moment, Mr. Sun.
Butler Bai.
Yes.
Your Lordship, this chest of gifts
seems a bit suspicious.
Examine the chest.
Yes.
No.
No, Registrar Luo.
Mr. Sun, these are
some writing supplies.
It's a small token of appreciation.
Registrar Luo,
attending the Literary Feast
has been a great pleasure for me,
as for this...
Mr. Sun, to be honest,
my mother was glad to hear
that you accept students
regardless of their status
and refuse gifts.
This is just a small gesture.
Please accept it.
In that case,
I will accept this.
I shall thank Old Madam Luo
on behalf of students from humble roots.
Hurry and carry it to the carriage.
I will take my leave, Registrar Luo.
Take care, Mr. Sun.
Hold on!
I apologize
for startling you,
Mr. Sun and Second Master Luo.
Commander Ye,
what is this about?
There's a criminal at large.
The Imperial Guards
have been ordered to arrest him.
Someone spotted
the criminal here,
so Marquis Lu commanded us to search.
Please forgive us.
Since this is an official duty,
please help yourself.
This is my duty.
Come.
Open the chest.
- Yes.
Hold on.
Commander Ye,
this chest
is a gift we return to Mr. Sun.
Commander Ye,
this chest contains the writing supplies
Old Madam Luo gave me.
I think it should be all right.
Mr. Sun,
this is my duty.
I wouldn't dare overlook anything.
These are elegant objects.
How could you...
This is humiliating.
Please pardon me.
You dare defy me?
Search!
How dare you!
Don't be rude.
Greetings, Marquis Lu.
Please pardon
their disrespectful actions.
Marquis Lu,
your subordinate
is very diligent.
We are decreed
to capture the criminal.
I'm doing this in regard to laws.
I'm truly sorry.
Marquis Lu, this chest
only contains writing supplies.
It's better not
to ruin such an elegant gesture.
They certainly are elegant,
but the one who ruins them
isn't me.
I'm also
protecting your reputation, Mr. Sun.
What will you do if you don't
find the criminal inside?
If that's the case,
I will send you a gift of apology.
Come.
Yes.
Open the chest.
It would be better not
to open the chest
and sabotage this elegance.
Pay no mind to my impudence.
Please pardon me, Mr. Sun.
This is ridiculous.
I bid you farewell, Marquis Lu.
Please see your way out.
We have plenty of time ahead,
Third Young Master Luo.
Your Lordship.
How was it?
I followed Sun Jie's carriage
to the academy
and watched them unloading all the gifts
until the carriage left.
We didn't find anything suspicious.
All guests and carriages
leaving Luo Residence
were thoroughly searched.
Aside from Sun Jie,
did the Luo's Residence return gifts
to anyone else?
Return gifts?
They returned gifts
to Cheng's Residence.
It's said
that Mr. Cheng brought
plenty of fine gifts
to Luo's Residence.
This time,
they also returned
a few chests of gifts
to Mr. Cheng.
Did you search
their carriages thoroughly?
I ordered them
to search all the carriages.
However, concerning
Mr. Cheng's relationship with you,
they wouldn't dare
disturb the Cheng's Residence carriage.
Careless.
Are you saying
that the man left together
with Cheng Residence's carriage?
I will send my men to pursue him.
No need. It's already late.
Be that as it may,
just as I expected,
we are up against
a rival to be reckoned with.
It seems
I have underestimated him.
(Cheng)
Come
and unload the chests.
(Cheng)
(Jimo House)
Congratulations, Third Brother.
You made an impression today.
You will surely achieve your goal
in the future.
I believe Senior Daoyan
must've escaped by now.
For this,
I must thank you, Seventh Sister,
and Qing Qu.
My brilliant mind
is certainly because of
my intelligent third brother.
Of course,
thanks to your strategy as well.
Your prediction
of Lu Jiaxue's suspiciousness
gave us this opportunity.
Lu Jiaxue will
figure it out sooner or later.
We can't fool him for so long.
Do you suspect
that he will target you?
Well, he and I
will eventually
end up in a desperate fight.
What I'm worried about is you.
Me?
Somehow,
Lu Jiaxue
is paying extra attention to you.
Perhaps you played
"The Conqueror Disarms"
too impressively.
Maybe
the song is filled with killing intent
that resonates with him.
That's why I caught his attention.
If so,
I won't play that song again.
By the way, Third Brother,
where
did your senior hide
when he was here?
This is a secret chamber.
Third Brother,
what is this secret chamber for?
Of course, it's to prevent
another incident like today's.
You are telling me now.
Aren't you afraid
that I will tell others?
Aside from Shao'an,
you are the one I trust the most.
Ouch.
So in your heart,
I'm not as important as Shao'an.
Uh, let me put it this way.
I trust no one more than you.
That's better.
Oh, right.
Ms. Zheng wrote back the other day,
saying that she would be returning soon.
There are some things
that should faced head-on
rather than avoided.
Yining,
trust me.
I will stay with you
through everything
you are going through.
(Luo Residence)
Father?
You are awake.
The physician said you are fine,
it was just exhaustion.
It seems
you have worked very hard
for the Literary Feast.
Thank... Thank you
for your consideration, Father.
I couldn't sleep well
these days,
that's why I made a mistake.
Shut it.
Hardworking
is the least a scholar should do.
Going all out to study despite hardships
is simply common.
The literary gathering
is the battleground for scholars.
You should charge forward bravely
when confronting strong enemies.
Yet you fled in fear.
That's cowardice!
Do you know
that your behavior
has made the Luo Family
a laughing stock?
This is merely
a small literary feast,
but you couldn't even handle it.
How are you going
to deal with the upcoming
imperial examination?
Tell me!
I will definitely do my best
and not
fail...
I used to think
that you were a driven person
since you were a kid,
but it turns out
you are so immature.
Useless fool.
Father...
Send for a physician to check on him.
Are you all right, Xuan?
You are the one to blame!
You always urged me to study
day and night,
that's why I became nervous and made
a fool of myself
in front of many people.
How could you say that?
I'm doing this for your own good.
For my own good?
All you care about is yourself.
I became a joke in the entire capital.
Even that fellow
from Jimo House
outperformed me.
Happy now?
Xuan...
Let me alone!
That boy
truly caught me off guard.
This Luo Shenyuan is strange.
How could he be able...
I have noticed
something different about him
a long time ago.
He may be quiet
and looks like a pushover,
but his eyes
give off a stubborn feeling.
I just didn't expect him
to hide his talent so deeply.
He's just a lowly person
who made up a nonsense poem.
I don't think
he's any better than Young Master Shan.
Still, the second home
got lucky
at the literary feast this time.
If Mr. Sun said it's good,
then it's good.
I just can't tolerate this.
The second home
has always had the upper hand
over these years.
It's merely because Second Master
is an official in the capital,
while First Master has been posted
outside the capital.
I received news
from my maternal family.
First Master
is soon returning to the capital.
That's good.
Madam Chen,
you no longer have
to be alone
and suffer quietly.
(Haitang Abode)
Young Lady,
Qing Qu went to the gate to fetch her.
They will be arriving soon.
Ms. Zheng.
You're finally here.
I have been waiting for you.
Please come in.
Ms. Zheng, there's no need
for formalities.
You were with my mother
since she was little
and accompanied her
to marry into this family
until she passed away.
You don't have to bow to me.
When I left the Luo's Residence,
you were a baby,
but now
you have already grown
into a young lady.
Qing Qu wrote to me,
saying that you are not feeling well.
Allow me to check on you.
Before this,
let's visit Grandma.
My apologies.
I have already forgotten the rules.
Yes, Young Lady.
Grandma.
I, Zheng Rong, offer my greetings,
Old Madam.
Get up.
Thank you, Old Madam.
It has been many years.
How's your health?
Indeed, it has been many years.
I don't understand.
Yining was just a baby that year,
and you were the most capable
and reliable maid besides Minglan.
I implored you
to stay to look after Yining,
but you left the Luo's Residence
without turning back.
But why
are you back now?
Grandma,
I invited Ms. Zheng back.
I thought that Ms. Zheng
had looked after my mother
until her passing
and also cultivated Qing Qu for me,
so I asked Qing Qu
to invite her back
to have some fun in the capital
for some days.
Old Madam,
I had my reason back then.
Please don't blame me.
Well.
I don't want to rake up the past.
Thank you, Old Madam.
The past
is in the past.
(Liuhe Tavern)
"I would rather die
than crouch in shame.
Eagles do not blend with the flock,
standing alone, proud and lofty."
Daoyan, your calligraphy
is as strong and peculiar
as it were.
"To depart from trouble
is to depart from suffering."
Daoyan.
You just got rid of trouble.
Why don't we
relax a bit tonight?
Senior Daoyan,
Shenyuan is here with us.
Come try my cooking.
It has been years
since we have all gathered together.
What's wrong, Daoyan?
Perhaps he hasn't recovered
from his old injury.
Daoyan, I will send a physician for you.
No need.
Just a throat issue, nothing new.
Seventh Lady.
Ms. Zheng.
Seventh Lady,
you still keep
your mother's belongings.
When my mother passed away,
Mistress Qiao
sold all of her dowry.
Even the Minglan Hall was torn down.
Now,
these are the only things left.
Mistress Qiao is indeed wicked.
Grandma must've told you
not to tell me too much.
Mistress Qiao
has received her retribution.
We will let bygone
be bygone.
Yes, it's all the past.
As long as you are well,
Madam Gu will rest in peace.
Young Lady,
let me take your pulse.
Qing Qu wrote in the letter
that you are not feeling well.
Though I'm not inept at healing,
I will try my best
to heal you.
Ms. Zheng,
I was
feeling unwell before,
but I have recovered
these past few days.
But Qing Qu said...
I lied to you.
I asked Qing Qu to lie to you,
so that you would return here.
Ms. Zheng,
to be frank,
I have something to ask you.
How much do you know
about my mother's death?
I will tell you
as much as I know.
Back then, Father favored Mistress Qiao.
My mother couldn't endure
such humiliation,
so she moved to the side yard
and asked Father for a divorce.
Is this true?
Yes, it is.
Your father favored the concubine
and neglected his wife.
Besides, Mistress Qiao
often used cunning tricks.
She spread rumors
and slandered Madam Gu
for endangering her.
Madam Gu had a lofty character
and didn't want to compete with her.
If not for you,
Madam Gu
wouldn't have returned
to the Luo's Residence.
If so,
did Father visit her
after Mother returned?
He came once.
It was when you were just born.
At that time,
your father bought some tea leaves
that your mother liked.
Tea leaves?
Yes.
I remember clearly
that your father
was unexpectedly friendly
that day.
He played with you.
Your mother noticed that,
so she didn't turn him away
and took a few sips of the tea
he brought.
Yet after a brief conversation,
he was actually coveting
the dowry Madam Gu prepared for you.
He wanted Madam Gu
to buy him a position in the court.
Madam Gu was furious
and poured the tea
into the hardy begonia.
Unexpectedly,
the root of those hardy begonias
withered.
Hardy begonia?
But Grandma told me
it was because
of the Mongolian milkvetch
and peony tonic.
That's an excuse
your mother told Old Madam
as she didn't want to drink
the tea your father brought.
Tea leaves?
Yes, this is that one.
This is the tea
Second Master gave to your mother.
I can't believe it still exists.
Will my mother's death
be related
to Father?
Of course, it's related to him.
If not
for his cruelty,
your mother wouldn't have fallen ill
and passed away
at such a young age.
Send Senior Daoyan away
as quickly as possible.
Don't let Lu Jiaxue's men find out.
Yes.
Qi An will handle that.
No, I will do it myself.
Daoyan is the proudest student
of Master.
He passed the exam
when he was a teenager
and was personally appointed
as an official by His Majesty.
Yet he has to live on the run now.
It's my fault.
It has been three years,
and I still haven't achieved
anything yet.
Young Master, you run Liuhe Tavern
and the sea transportation business,
have protected all your
seniors and juniors,
found Li Yinglong and Lu Jiaxue,
and even obtained the statement
from Old Madam.
How could you say
you have achieved nothing?
Third Brother.
Seventh Lady, the tea is ready.
Have you made up your mind?
It seems
everything is all right.
(No animals were harmed
during the making of this series.)
It's poisoned.
Yining.
Father.
Where's your handmaiden?
Why aren't they with you?
It's already late at night.
What are you doing here?
I was on my way to see you, Father.
Lately, I have been sorting things out,
and saw Mother's belongings.
They bring back memories of her,
so I came out for some fresh air.
She's already at peace.
It's all in the past.
Digging up these things
will only add to your sorrow.
Have you already forgotten
the people and things from the past?
But I still can't forget
Mother's voice and face.
So
I would like to ask you...
Seventh Sister,
what are you doing here?
Father.
That's rude.
Don't think that because you wrote
a good poem at the Literary Feast
and people
started calling you
"Third Young Master Luo",
you can act as you please.
Know your place.
I'm now
Mr. Sun's student.
I don't have any other identities
other than that.
You are talking back to me?
Stay in Jimo House
these days
and don't leave.
Am I under house arrest?
But Mr. Sun told me
to attend a literary gathering with him.
In that case,
I won't go.
Go.
You have to go.
Perform well.
Yes.
Yining, what was it you wanted to ask?
Get rest early.
I understand how you feel.
But the poisoned tea
doesn't prove anything.
If it was him,
he wouldn't tell you
the truth
if you had no evidence.
Third Brother,
what should I do?
I thought
my heart was cold enough
to bear every consequence,
but...
♪Stirring up trouble, loneliness,
stirring up a sky full of fireworks♪
♪Through the trials, who set it,
and who bore the consequence?♪
There, there.
You still have me.
I'm with you.
If it's truly him,
just follow your heart.
♪Afraid of missing out and mistakes,
of begonias blooming and withering♪
Even if you go against the entire world,
I will definitely
be on your side.
♪Your gentle presence leaves
a trace of ink in my heart♪
♪An overlapping shade of us
spreads across my life♪
♪Though countless faces pass me by,
I seek only you♪
♪Love is a lifelong promise,
regardless of what may come♪
This is my mother.
Is she pretty?
She's pretty.
So, am I pretty as well?
Yes.
You are the prettiest one
in this world.
Third Brother,
until I figure out
whether Father
was involved,
I won't be able to rest easy.
Please.
Sorry to disturb you again.
Physician Zhao,
I have a doubt.
I'd like to seek your guidance.
Have you discovered
any new clues, Seventh Lady?
I asked the old maid who used to serve
my mother before.
She said before my mother passed away,
she was in great pain.
Her mouth and tongue were numb,
her whole body was stinging,
and she couldn't speak clearly.
Are these symptoms of certain illnesses?
I have never heard of Madam Gu
having such symptoms.
From your description,
it sounds more like
she took the wrong medicine
or was poisoned.
This is the tea leaves
she drank before.
I tested it.
It's poisonous.
Please help me to find out
what poison it is.
Daoyan,
we are parting ways now.
Please take care.
Yuan,
I hope the next time we meet
will be the day
when Master's case is reopened.
Rest assured, Daoyan.
I'll make sure
all the seniors and juniors
get rid of the life on the run.
Qi An,
stay alert along the journey.
Look out for my senior.
Yes, Young Master.
Young Master,
the thing Seventh Lady needs is ready.
(Luo's Residence)
Father.
You are here, too, Yining.
Mother.
I came to pay my respects.
Sit.
She came here early in the morning
for breakfast.
I really like the food prepared
by Grandma's kitchen.
I heard they had served
the seasonal osmanthus cake recently,
so I came to try it.
If you like it,
I can have the cook
send some for you.
But it tastes better
when I come here to enjoy it.
It tastes better to eat it here?
This girl.
You make such a mischievous excuse
for the food.
Grandma,
I didn't come empty-handed.
I brought
some fine tea here.
It's already roasted and ground
into tea powder.
Since Father is here too,
let's try it together.
Xue Zhi.
I have something
to attend to later,
so I'm not drinking the tea.
Since you are all right,
I will take my leave.
Father, please stay.
This tea is special.
I hope we can savor it together.
I have tried all kinds of tea.
Chengzhang,
just stay and drink it.
It won't affect your appointment.
I wonder
what she's going to show us.
♪South wind weaves
a brocade tapestry of lives♪
♪Begonias lean on each other
in front of a turquoise pond♪
♪The tea fragrance wafts
along the long street♪
♪A bright heart will radiate the world♪
♪Family is the safe haven
surrounding me♪
Grandma,
this is the smallest portion,
so it won't affect your nap.
Father,
I know
you are a tea expert.
This cup contains
the tea's original taste.
Please try it.
♪Red strings on the eaves,
bind two devoted hearts together♪
♪Through half a lifetime
and sweet dreams♪
Father,
what do you think about this tea?
This is the Dragon-Phoenix Tea Cake.
You still remember this?
You gave this tea cake to my mother
back then.
This tea is
left by Minglan?
Grandma,
when I found this tea
from Mother's belongings,
I was so excited,
so I immediately brought it to Father
to ask him about it.
You came to me that night
because of this tea?
The Dragon-Phoenix Tea Cakes is rare.
It's also hard for the royals
to even get one.
It took me a lot of effort
to get just a little.
I remember
Minglan and I had a fight that day.
I thought
she had already
thrown this tea away.
Unexpectedly,
she had kept it for over a decade.
Why did you fight?
Was it about
Mistress Qiao again?
No.
At that time,
I encountered some problems
in the court.
Father was upright
and refused to help me,
so I thought
about spending some money
to resolve the issue,
so I asked your mother
for some of her dowry.
How foolish!
How could you think about bribery
and even using
Minglan's dowry?
Mother, you are right.
I deeply regretted it.
I wouldn't dare
think of doing it again.
If your father were
to find out about this,
he would definitely punish you severely.
I wasn't thinking straight at that time.
But fortunately,
I didn't disgrace the family.
Thank you for getting
this decade-old
Dragon-Phoenix Tea Cake for me.
Without it,
I wouldn't have had the opportunity
to test Father's reaction.
You feel relieved now, right?
Father didn't seem like
he was behind this.
If he feels guilty about it,
he will surely show some signs.
But
if it's not him,
who could it be?
Perhaps the situation becomes clearer
after Physician Zhao
uncovers the poison.
Even if it was him,
I don't think you could bring yourself
to sever ties with him.
As terribly wrong and disappointing
as he may be,
he's still
your father.
What about you?
Do you hate him?
I did,
but children
can't choose their parents,
so I just do
what I should do.
The autumn examination is nearing.
Your name must be registered
in the family register soon.
Even though
Father has softened toward you,
it's only because
of Mr. Sun.
If we want Father to allow you
to be registered in the family register,
we will have to give it a push.
Mother, you are good at doing business
and managing accounts.
If you hadn't married
into the Luo Family,
you might've become
a successful businesswoman.
At this age,
even if I hadn't married
into the Luo Family,
I would have married someone else.
Women obey their fathers
before getting married
and their husbands after.
No one could tell
which fate could've been better.
Compared to other places,
marrying into the Luo Family
has been pretty good.
At least you are with me.
Besides,
Old Madam has been nice to me.
Mother,
do you plan to continue living like this
with Father?
Your father and I
both live separate lives
and don't interfere with each other.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Why are you asking this all of a sudden?
Of course, I will support
any choice you make,
but I think
it's better
to plan for the future.
What if
I get married
and Mistress Qiao
returns here?
What do you mean?
Mother, ever since the Literary Feast,
even though Father
doesn't like Third Brother,
he has had to acknowledge
in front of everyone
that Third Brother
is part of the Luo Family.
If you take him as your son,
you will have a legitimate son.
You can rely on him
in the future, right?
Besides, Third Brother is kind
and knowledgeable.
If he successfully passes
the triennial palace examination,
you'll be the mother
of a palace graduate.
If he tops in
the final palace exam,
you're the mother
of the honorary principal graduate.
You make it sound
like passing the examination is easy.
Besides, he's an adult now.
I don't think
I can be a good mother to him.
If you can't
do it well,
no one else in this residence can.
Ever since you took over
the household management,
you have always left a share
for him in everything.
Being fair to everyone
is the way it should be.
Besides,
when you sprained your foot
at the estate last time,
Third Brother offered to carry you
all the way back.
That's how a mother and a son do.
Well,
I used to think he looked gloomy,
but this time,
I realized that he's actually kind.
Besides,
he's a grateful person.
He will surely be nice to you.
Regarding this,
I need to discuss it with your father.
As you know,
your father
might not be easily convinced.
♪It's complicated but I'm not afraid♪
♪There's light in my heart♪
♪Following the river of time♪
♪I dive into the whirlpool♪
♪For the sake of you and mine♪
♪In search of an outcome♪
♪I'm willing to risk my life♪
♪To break the chain of nights♪
♪I'm willing to fall into the abyss♪
♪In order to reveal the fate♪
♪Forget about the outcome♪
♪Let me be your shoulder to lean on♪
♪Even if things go south, so be it♪
♪Love is a voyage with you by my side♪
♪The dust eventually settles♪
♪No matter how fragile and trivial I am♪
♪I will dance and shine bright♪
♪I overcome all kinds of doubt♪
♪And obstacles♪
♪For the sake of you and mine♪
♪Committing to my promise♪
♪I'm willing to risk my life♪
♪May my existence shine on more♪
♪Let go of everything♪
♪Let the longing fade♪
♪Forget about the outcome♪
♪As long as it fulfills
the vastness of love♪
♪Even if things go south, so be it♪
♪Love is you being by my side♪