=The Rise of Ning=
(Adapted from Wen Tan's novel "Chancellor
Training Handbook" from Jinjiang Literature)
=Episode 34=
Is that Marquis Lu?
Did you invite him?
No.
What a great prestige
for Duke Ying's Residence.
Marquis Lu actually came
to attend the Flowers Festival.
But why did Marquis Lu
come to the garden?
Obviously, His Lordship came
to deliver a decree.
Didn't you see the two palace servants
following him?
Old Madam, the guest is here.
Greetings, Old Madams.
Old Madam Wei,
everyone admires the famous flowers
during the Flowers Festival.
The Empress has gifted you
this Bingdi Lotus
as the grand prize
for the Flowers Festival.
Thank Her Majesty.
Why's there lotus in this season?
Is that a dried flower?
There are flower caretakers
in the palace
who study flower-forcing techniques,
using water at different temperatures
to tend to flowers outside their season.
Grandma and I saw this
when we entered the palace.
They are rare and precious.
Duke Ying's Residence must be proud.
Even Her Majesty sent the prize over.
I didn't expect you
to come here, Marquis Lu.
Today is the Flowers Festival.
I entered the palace
to present flowers to Her Majesty.
After learning
that this year's Flowers Festival
is hosted by Duke Ying's Residence
and that it's the first appearance
of County Princess of Qingcheng,
Her Majesty specifically
instructed me
to deliver the grand prize.
You're thoughtful, Marquis Lu.
In that case,
please do away
with the formalities.
Show all the male guests
in the front yard
to the main garden
to try their luck
for the grand prize.
Yes, Old Madam Wei.
Ladies, please come this way.
Ladies and gentlemen,
whoever retrieves the Bingdi Lotus
will claim the grand prize.
If we can get
this Bingdi Lotus in our store,
Yanrong Pavilion will definitely
become famous.
Do you want it?
Yu,
I want the grand prize.
Please help me.
Don't worry.
It's a piece of cake.
Forget about
the grand prize.
I didn't know Shenyuan could shoot.
When did Third Brother learn that?
He knows a lot.
You were trying so hard to hide
your martial arts skills
that you got injured that day.
But you're not hiding it today.
Thank you for your compliment,
Marquis Lu.
I only practice some moves
that help strengthen my body.
I want to get it for Young Lady Wei
to celebrate her title.
I wonder
if you have the same intention as I do.
That's what I thought.
Very well.
Why don't we use this grand prize
to present it to Young Lady Wei
together?
How does that sound?
That's good.
You got it, Yining.
Let me see.
Imperial Scholar Luo always seems
to be gentle.
I didn't know
his skills were on par with Marquis Lu's.
Do Minister Luo and Marquis Lu...
Isn't that obvious enough?
Young Lady Wei is really something.
You've got most of the attention today.
Today's the Flowers Festival,
and you're the host family.
Plus, two men competed
for the grand prize for you.
Why?
Marquis Lu and Third Brother
gave it to Yining willingly.
Do you have any problem with that?
No.
Young Lady Wei is lucky.
Just ignore those who gossip
behind your back.
The feast hasn't begun yet,
but I think she's already full now.
Butterfly!
My father
intends to betroth me
to Third Young Master Luo.
I saw a butterfly flying over here,
so I accidentally
stepped on your garment.
It's all right.
Young Lady,
the seats in the garden are all set up.
Old Madam Wei wants you to usher
the other young ladies to the seats.
She'll have meals with other madams
in Jing'an Hall.
Yining, why don't you get changed first?
Young Ladies, please take your seat.
Make yourselves comfortable here.
Please have some pastries.
This liquor is nice.
This pastry is delicious.
All right.
You may go.
- Yes.
Yixiu, do you think it's tasty or not?
It's tasty, of course.
Come on, Yining.
Come here.
This is really delicious.
Come. Have a seat.
Can you tell me
what ingredient did you use?
It tastes different
from those sold outside.
Tell me, please.
I'll have my chef make this later.
We added chestnuts.
No wonder.
The flavor is very different
from those outside.
It's really nice.
You can't stop eating it, right?
- What's wrong with my hand?
- Look at it.
- It's so itchy.
- Me too.
What's going on?
There's something on your neck.
Why is this happening?
Why are my hands so itchy?
Me too.
My neck is also itchy.
It's all red.
What is this?
It's so itchy.
Why am I starting to itch?
Why is there redness there?
I don't know. So itchy.
Stop scratching.
It'll be worse.
Don't you feel itchy?
I...
I think I'm fine.
Why is everyone starting to itch?
My hands are so itchy.
Me too.
Look at here.
What should I do?
Physician,
are they all right?
Please don't worry, Old Madam Wei.
It's the rash
that caused the redness and itching.
They'll be fine after a rest.
Remember to remind them
not to scratch too hard.
It might leave scars.
Physician,
do you know
what triggers this?
It's hard to say.
The young ladies are
all staying outdoors,
and there are many plants.
It's very likely to be in contact
with things that trigger itching.
How is that possible?
It's not our first time
attending the Flowers Festival.
This has never happened
in the past.
- That's right.
- Exactly.
It never happened before.
That's right.
Yes.
Young ladies,
did you use anything
that you've never used before?
Did we?
What?
The floral dew.
The only thing we didn't have before
was the floral dew
brought by Young Lady Wei.
Right. I also used that just now.
This is impossible.
Yanrong Pavilion's
products have no problem at all.
Why not?
Look at the redness and itching.
We all used the floral dew.
This can't be just a coincidence.
Yanrong Pavilion?
It's more like a disfiguring store.
The floral dew is extracted
from fresh flowers.
It doesn't contain other substances.
Right. I've also tried many products
from Yanrong Pavilion.
There's no problem so far.
Enough said.
You two sisters are defending it.
Is Yanrong Pavilion yours?
Don't talk nonsense.
Physician, please check on this.
This is the floral dew.
Take out yours too.
This is hard to say.
Natural products
aren't always harmless to humans.
Besides,
this floral dew is highly concentrated.
I brought this floral dew here.
If something's wrong with it,
I'll take full responsibility.
Please give me some time.
I'll get to the bottom of this.
Marquis Lu,
let me offer you a toast.
This bunch of snobs.
They're lining up to offer toasts
once Marquis Lu has arrived.
That's pretty good.
It's quiet now.
Come. Let's drink to Marquis Lu.
Young Master,
I noticed
a physician was sent
to the garden just now.
I went to ask around.
They said the ladies in the garden
suddenly broke out in rashes.
Is Yining all right?
This is weird.
Only the Seventh Lady is fine.
I'll go and check on Yixiu.
Uncle, there are all ladies
over there.
It's not appropriate if you
suddenly show up there.
Sixth Master Lin, since they've sent
for a physician,
it should be no problem.
I don't think the physician
can do better than me.
Send Qing Qu to bring Yining out.
Yes.
Third Brother.
It's good that you're fine.
I'm all good.
I'm relieved, then.
You know what happened in the garden?
I think they're after you.
That's what I thought.
Try to recall
if you did anything
different from others
before the incident happened.
Is there any?
One thing does come up to me.
Qing Qu,
go and investigate.
Yes.
Hey.
Yes?
Young Lady Wei wants to wash her hands.
I need to prepare it for her.
Please come with me.
Are there any cloths?
All are used.
Laundry Division
hasn't delivered the clean ones yet.
Have all the basins and cloths been
delivered from the Laundry Division
after cleaning?
Yes.
What should I do?
It's all right.
I'll find another cloth for Young Lady.
Thank you.
Where has Young Lady Wei gone?
Has she investigated anything yet?
She should at least send someone
to explain.
What's there to investigate?
I'm sure that something's wrong
with the floral dew
from Yanrong Pavilion.
Young Lady Wei actually brought us
something from an unknown source for us.
What exactly is she up to?
Tell me about it.
Nothing is clear yet.
Don't talk nonsense.
Mother, I'm not wrong.
That little store
is indecent,
and their products
aren't up to par either.
I understand
all of you
have concerns.
But if this is really done
by the Wei Family,
I'll give you an explanation.
However, if it's not
and someone slanders us,
I won't spare them.
Hold on.
It's you, Qing Qu.
Are these the cloths
the young ladies used at the feast?
Yes. Why?
My young lady might drop
her accessory into this
while washing her hands.
Let me see.
It'd be hard to find it
if it dropped in the water.
You should try searching for it.
Young Lady Wei's things are valuable.
I can't afford it
if it's lost.
Not at all. It's not worth much.
It's just that my young lady
cherishes it very much.
You are in charge
of these cloths?
That's right.
I'm the maid in charge of the laundry.
We wash the used cloths.
Who delivers them to the feast?
The maids who serve at the feast.
Did six maids
- go to collect them just now?
- No.
It was Young Lady Zhao's maid.
There were not enough attendants,
so she offered help.
Young Lady,
this is what it is.
Do you need my help?
If I were to pursue this incident,
it would embarrass Grandma
as well as the Wei Family.
I didn't expect you to value
the Wei Family so highly.
I didn't expect that either.
It seems they have treated you well.
Father is very kind to me.
Grandma may be strict,
but she also cares for me sincerely.
I don't want to disappoint them.
All right. Point taken.
I'll handle this myself.
You'll return first.
I'm sorry
for letting you worry, Grandmas.
Yining,
what have you found?
Young ladies, do you remember
what you all did together
before the itching started?
We were drinking floral liquor
and floral pastries together.
What about before that?
Before that,
we washed our hands.
Shortly after that,
my hands started feeling itchy.
You didn't wash your hands.
Those maids left
when you arrived, right?
Young ladies, do you remember
if your palms started itching,
and then you
touched your neck
and cheeks with your palms,
which then
started to itch as well?
Exactly.
I think so.
That's right.
It started to feel itchy
wherever my hands touched.
Qing Qu.
These are the cloths
we used earlier, right?
Physician,
could you please take a look
and see if there's anything on it?
This cloth is stained with yam sap.
Yam sap?
Right, it's yam.
What's wrong with yam?
It's often cooked in soups.
I've never seen symptoms like this.
Eating cooked yam
is fine,
but the sap on its skin
can trigger redness and itching.
If you still have doubts,
there's another method.
Qing Qu,
bring hot water and salt here.
Don't apply the salt water directly
to your face.
You can apply heat with the towel.
The hotter the water, the better.
The itching is gone. What about you?
Right.
Old Madam Luo.
It's not itchy anymore.
I wonder
why there's yam sap
on these cloths?
I don't know either.
Today's Flowers Festival
is held by the Wei's Residence.
While it didn't cause serious harm,
this was clearly someone's doing.
Duke Ying's Residence
will investigate this thoroughly
and give everyone an explanation.
♪To break the chain of nights♪
Ning, tell me.
Did you find out
who did that long ago?
Grandma,
I've been through
some ups and downs.
This is only trivial.
Well.
I should get going.
Take good care of Grandma.
I'm leaving.
Send Qing Qu or Xue Zhi to inform me
if anything happens.
I'll come to give you lectures
a few days later.
Just take good care of yourself.
What's wrong with me?
Thank you for coming uninvited,
Marquis Lu.
Did something happen in the garden
just now?
This is our own business.
I don't want to trouble you with that.
There's one thing
I'd like to ask of you.
No matter what favor it is,
I'll say yes.
Did you request
for the grand prize earlier today?
This is your first appearance
on an important occasion
as the daughter of Duke Ying.
It certainly needs to be decent.
Marquis Lu,
please don't do that again.
As long as you like it,
I will do anything for you.
In that case, Marquis Lu,
please leave.
Mingzhu.
Did you hurt yourself by scratching
earlier today?
No.
Thank you for your concern, Yining.
Ting,
you just returned from the academy?
I heard
you got the grand prize just now.
May I borrow it?
The Bingdi Lotus
isn't quite interesting.
If I come across something fun tomorrow,
I'll buy it for you.
Why are you unhappy?
I noticed one of the guests
brought a dagger as a gift.
I thought you would like it,
so I brought it to you.
Really?
Suxi, give it to him.
Do you like it?
I'm sorry, Suxi.
I'm panicking.
Ting is in a rash again.
I need to inform Young Lady.
I'm sorry.
What?
He gets a rash?
Ting only gets a rash
when he touches yams.
Have you cleaned up
everything in our place?
Yes.
Those bottles that carry yams
were all thrown away.
I also washed my hands
when I returned.
And...
The dagger. What about the dagger?
Did you clean it
before sending it over?
You know Ting gets rashes
once he touches yams.
It's my fault.
What if something bad happened to Ting?
I shouldn't have done that.
Even Ting got involved.
Mingzhu,
where are you going at this hour?
I was told
that Ting breaks out in rashes.
I'll check on him.
Ting is all right.
This is a misunderstanding.
Grandma always dotes on him.
Even if this is a misunderstanding,
she'll be worried sick.
I need to go and visit Grandma.
Grandma and Ting are fine.
However, I have something
to talk to you.
Seeing how caring you are
for Grandma
and Ting,
I'm truly glad.
That reminds me
of my days in the Luo's Residence,
even though
I'm not
part of the family.
Yining,
what are you getting at?
I used to think
that they would treat me less friendly
after knowing
that we had no blood relation.
To my surprise,
they treat me like their own family
as they always have.
Only then did I realize
that the relationships between people
don't rely solely on blood relations.
Sincerity is what matters.
True.
Sincerity is precious.
The identity of being
the legitimate daughter of a Duke
isn't what I want.
To me,
this is nothing but an identity.
When I was in the Luo's Residence,
I suffered a lot
due to my birth mother.
As for now, I only wish for an easy
and simple life.
Human hearts are
complicated and suspicious.
Instead, I feel
that one will get something
they believe in.
As long as
hearts are together,
home is there.
Mingzhu,
do you understand
what I'm trying to tell you?
Yining,
you don't have to imply that.
I know why you came here tonight.
What happened
during the Flowers Festival
is my doing.
Grandma and Father want me
to accept you,
which I'm reluctant to do,
but I still tried.
However, everyone
has their selfishness.
To be honest, I'm wary of you.
You're the legitimate daughter,
and I'm only an adopted daughter.
It was a moment of weakness,
and I did something foolish.
I didn't know
you were so outspoken.
Please don't say that.
I know I did it wrong.
Truth be told,
I regretted it later.
Since you're being frank,
I won't beat around the bush.
Honestly, to me,
whether it's a prestigious family
or commoners, it doesn't matter.
I only hope that the family can
care for one another
sincerely
and have
a place to settle down.
I understand now.
Well,
you know I did that,
but you didn't expose me.
I know what kind of person you are.
Don't worry.
I won't do that ever again.
Since we've cleared this up,
Yining...
♪Along the long street♪
There's something
I've always wanted to tell you.
Yes, please.
I once invited ladies
of the Luo Family to the residence
and brought you
to the Marquis Anbei's Residence.
They were
all from Godbrother's order.
I know.
That day
at the Marquis Anbei's Residence,
if it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have been able to escape.
So you knew it all along?
Of course.
That's why I know
you have a kind nature.
Besides, Grandma and Father
wouldn't raise an unruly child.
♪Bind two devoted hearts together♪
♪Through half a lifetime
and sweet dreams♪
Old Madam Wei,
Young Lady Mingzhu is here.
Leave us.
Close the door.
Yes.
I've committed a grave mistake.
Please punish me, Grandma.
What have you done wrong?
What happened earlier today
is my doing.
And I wanted to shift the blame
to Yining.
Why did you do that?
Because I'm insecure.
Yining receives most of the attention.
Besides, you've grown fond of her.
I feel that the only one I can rely on
is soon gone.
Oh my.
You were being foolish.
I like Yining,
but does that mean I don't like you?
It's my fault.
I barely even recognize myself
after doing something like that.
Get up.
I've embarrassed you, Grandma,
and the Wei's Residence.
I'm too ashamed to get up.
I knew it was you all along.
I was waiting for you to admit it.
I knew I could hide nothing
from you, Grandma.
Since you've owned up to your mistake,
it shows you can tell right from wrong
and are willing to make it right.
It's all right.
Get up.
This bottle of floral dew
is guaranteed pure.
I've tried countless times
before extracting this pure fragrance.
Give it a try.
The scent is clean and refreshing.
By the way,
I heard maidservants
at Duke Xu's Residence say
that their young lady loves
the plum fragrance.
- Really?
- Yes.
Give me two bottles of that.
I want two bottles of that!
- Me too.
- I want two bottles of that.
Shopkeeper, check, please.
All right.
Judging by your temperament,
you're elegant, personable,
and beautiful.
Why don't you take two bottles?
It's a double blessing.
Sir,
this is bad!
Everyone wants the rose floral dew.
- But it's sold out.
- Are you the owner?
Sir, we want the rose floral dew.
That's right, sir. We all want that.
Ladies,
I'm very sorry.
We're out of stock.
How about this?
We can sign a pre-order form.
If you want one, pay a deposit
and take the product
five days later.
I'll take your word for take.
Five days later.
Right. Don't break your promise.
Of course.
Come. Let's sign pre-order forms.
This way.
I want two bottles.
Wait up.
How's it?
The figure we've earned today
is more than those of previous months.
I didn't know
you were good at making money.
My sister didn't realize
I inherited the Lin Family's
business acumen.
Sixth Uncle,
we received so many orders today.
Can you prepare the products in time?
Right. You only have five days.
It's money.
Money opens all doors.
I wish for more orders to wear me out.
Very well. Go ahead.
I'm leaving, then.
(Marquis Anbei's Residence)
Young Master Cheng took action
before Yang Ling boarded the ship.
Chen Long and Chen Yang were shot dead,
but Yang Ling was abducted.
Your Lordship, do you think
the person who abducted Yang Ling
could be Luo Shenyuan?
It seems we've underestimated him.
Who else could it be except for him?
Tell Cheng Lang
to monitor the area closely.
You'll stay on guard
outside the capital.
Inform me immediately
if there's any movement.
Yes, Your Lordship.
You're awake, Official Yang.
Who are you?
Don't be afraid, sir.
You'll know after reading the letter.
(Vice Minister Yang boarded
a smuggler ship and he may have been framed.)
Shenyuan sent you?
Yes.
Young Master worried
that Wang Yuan's men would harm you,
so he urgently sent me here.
Official Yang,
they're accusing you
of being a smuggler.
You'll have to
conceal your identity
if you want to go out for now.
This is utterly absurd.
I don't know those smugglers
at all.
The priority now is
to send you back to the capital
and then find a way to clear your name.
All right.
This is simply a frame-up.
I don't believe
Yang Ling is this kind of person.
Calm down, Master.
The truth will only be uncovered
if we can find Senior Yang Ling.
But...
But the yamen
has issued
a marine warrant everywhere
to arrest him.
Where's he now?
Greetings, Father.
Third Yong Master Luo.
I've prepared some pastries
for Father.
I didn't know you were here.
Put it there.
I won't disturb you here, Father.
I'll take my leave.
Shenyuan,
you've reached the marriageable age.
I discussed this matter with your father
when I visited
the Luo's Residence last time.
I know your ambition
has yet to be realized.
However, men should start a family
before establishing a career.
You can get engaged now
and marry later.
I already have someone I like.
I'm thinking of proposing to her
once I achieve something.
Which family is this lady from?
Your father didn't mention it.
I haven't told my family about it yet.
Master, I've made up my mind.
I will marry no one but her.
Well, then.
You two aren't mean for each other.
Young Master,
Qi An has already rescued Official Yang
and is escorting him back
to the capital.
But why did they
kill all their people?
Chen Long and Chen Yang
were Wang Yuan's henchmen.
This is too much of a price to pay.
Cheng Lang left the capital
and has likely gone to Quanzhou.
So Lu Jiaxue intends
to eliminate all of them
to get rid of Wang Yuan's control.
They gather for profits
and disperse when there's nothing left.
He's always ruthless
when it comes to situations like this.
Understood.
Let's go to Duke Ying's Residence.
Yes.
(Huanjing Pavilion)
Young Lady, are you drawing
the Yanrong Pavilion?
Who are these two people?
Young Lady,
Madam Shen just came.
Was it because of the Flowers Festival?
Old Madam Wei told her
everything frankly.
Madam Shen didn't say anything.
Grandma is an honest person,
so they wouldn't pursue it.
Aside from this,
Madam Shen came here
mainly because of the proposal to you.
Proposal?
Duke Ying just returned,
and Old Madam Wei sent for him.
What?
The Shen Family also wants
to marry Yining?
What's with that face?
You seem like the enemy
has arrived on your doorstep.
It seems that my daughter
is too outstanding.
So many people approve of her
just as she returns.
Yining has reached
the marriageable age.
The Shen Family is an earl.
They're considered a prestigious family.
I don't care who they are.
Mother, I've made up my mind.
I won't consider
Yining's marriage for now.
Besides, if I were
to choose a son-in-law,
I only have a request.
Yining has to like the man.
As long as she likes him
and he has good character,
I won't reject him even if he comes
from a humble root.
Children's marriages
are decided by parents
and arranged by matchmakers.
Daughters can't decide for themselves.
That may be what other families do,
I won't comment on that. But my daughter
has to marry a man she likes.
She will decide for herself.
I know
you're worried about Yining's future.
But I'm afraid
that if you're too picky,
you'll delay her marriage.
I don't care.
If Yining has a man she likes,
I don't mind personally proposing
marriage to him.
But if she doesn't have any, I'd rather
provide for her
for her whole life.
Did you hear yourself?
Mother,
I've heard something
about Young Master Shen.
He's not knowledgeable
and incompetent.
How could our Yining marry him?
Right?
Shen Yu
is a bit lacking.
That's not a bit.
But you haven't even asked Yining,
how do you know she doesn't
like the Shen Family?
There's no need to ask.
Everyone in the capital
knows what kind of a person he is.
Mother,
if you don't believe me,
you can call for her.
Grandma, Father.
I've heard your conversation
from outside just now.
That Young Master Shen...
Don't worry, Father.
I'm not interested
in him.
See?
I told you.
My daughter won't like him.
Yining,
your father
really can't bear to leave you.
Even so,
you're of marriageable age.
Your grandma has a point.
You've reached marriageable age now.
I'd like to ask you
if you have anyone
you like now.
Right.
What kind of man do you like?
Tell us.
Your father and I would like
to listen about it.
The man I like
should be dashing,
have excellent character
and talent,
not just book-smart,
aware of the world
but not overly sophisticated,
skilled in martial arts,
resilient,
and must cherish me.
When I'm with him,
he'll understand what I truly want
and make me feel secure.
♪It's complicated but I'm not afraid♪
♪There's light in my heart♪
♪Following the river of time♪
♪I dive into the whirlpool♪
♪For the sake of you and mine♪
♪In search of an outcome♪
♪I'm willing to risk my life♪
♪To break the chain of nights♪
♪I'm willing to fall into the abyss♪
♪In order to reveal the fate♪
♪Forget about the outcome♪
♪Let me be your shoulder to lean on♪
♪Even if things go south, so be it♪
♪Love is a voyage with you by my side♪
♪The dust eventually settles♪
♪No matter how fragile and trivial I am♪
♪I will dance and shine bright♪
♪I overcome all kinds of doubt♪
♪And obstacles♪
♪For the sake of you and mine♪
♪Committing to my promise♪
♪I'm willing to risk my life♪
♪May my existence shine on more♪
♪Let go of everything♪
♪Let the longing fade♪
♪Forget about the outcome♪
♪As long as it fulfills
the vastness of love♪
♪Even if things go south, so be it♪
♪Love is you being by my side♪