=The Rise of Ning=
(Adapted from Wen Tan's novel "Chancellor
Training Handbook" from Jinjiang Literature)
=Episode 3=
(Liuhe Tavern)
Chen Jiuheng,
Vice Minister of Revenue,
was assigned
to a disaster relief mission,
but he embezzled the funds.
His crime is unforgivable.
Take him away.
Master!
Young Master, you are finally awake.
Get up now.
It is almost noon.
Hurry and take your breakfast.
You must've drunk a lot
with your seniors last night.
I will let some fresh air in.
Young Master,
isn't that Seventh Lady?
Young misses.
Di Suite, please, sir.
Di Suite?
Bring the two misses there.
This way, please.
Who sent this?
I couldn't see that person's face.
Second Master,
this letter concerns
Seventh Lady's chastity.
Perhaps
this is a false alarm.
Whether it is or not,
prepare a carriage. I'm going out.
Yes.
Young misses, how may I help you?
Is there a vacant room beside Di Suite?
There's this Ren Suite.
- I will take that.
- All right.
Show them the way to the Ren Suite.
Young misses, this way, please.
Please.
Father has received the letter.
I'd like to see how Luo Yining
will react when Father shows up here.
Sir,
where is the Ren Suite?
Ren Suite?
This way.
Show him the way.
This way, please.
Welcome.
Sir, are you here for a drink
or a performance?
I'm looking for someone.
Looking for someone?
(Ren Suite)
Young Lady,
Second Master
and Young Master Jiang are here.
I doubt Seventh Lady
can get away this time.
(Di Suite)
Father?
There you are.
Where is he?
Who?
What are you talking about, Father?
Come out!
Second Master.
What are you doing here?
Seventh Lady and I
came to Liuhe Tavern
to try their new dishes.
Where is Mr. Jiang?
Mr. Jiang?
Why would I meet a man in private?
Don't try to hide it.
I knew
you arranged a meeting with Mr. Jiang
to call off the engagement.
Why are you here?
This noon, at Liuhe Tavern.
In the Ren Suite.
I asked to meet you?
Aren't you meeting Luo Yining
in the Di Suite?
Yilian,
I don't understand
what you are talking about.
You sent someone
to deliver a note to me.
(Meet me in the Ren Suite
of Liuhe Tavern at noon.)
I know you are still mad at me.
Later, I will tell my mother
I won't marry another woman.
Even if I'm to marry the daughter
of the Luo Family,
I will marry only you.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I'm not marrying you as a concubine.
Don't worry. I will be kind to you
despite your status as a concubine.
Father.
Why are you doing this?
Are you trying to disgrace me?
Mr. Luo,
Yilian and I sincerely like each other.
Please marry her off to me.
There's no need to tell me that.
I...
Father,
nothing is going on
between Mr. Jiang and me.
It's her!
She intentionally lured me here.
Yilian,
what are you talking about?
I don't understand.
It turns out that Mr. Jiang
and you are in love.
I...
I sincerely support you.
Nonsense!
Support them?
Marriage isn't a reckless decision.
Do you have no respect for me?
Mr. Luo,
anyway, I'm going to
marry one of your daughters.
Since you have already learned
of the situation,
I will return to tell my parents
that I will only marry Luo Yilian
and no other Luo's daughter.
Father,
have you forgotten what my mother
has been through at home?
I'm your daughter.
Do you bear
to see my whole life ruined?
Father, I do not want to be a concubine.
Yilian,
although I can't go against
my parents' decision
to take you as my principal wife,
I will never let you suffer.
Mr. Jiang,
I have already made myself clear.
Why can't you let me go?
Father,
if you insist on marrying me off
as a concubine,
I will take my life
right in front of you now.
- Yilian!
Yilian.
Father,
since you can't bear to see her suffer
and want to maintain
the Luo Family's dignity,
there's only one solution.
That is to meet with Madam Jiang
and cancel the engagement.
Fine.
The marriage between the two families
is off.
I will pick a day to formally
break off the engagement.
Listen.
Mr. Jiang,
you are going to marry a noble lady
and take the imperial examination soon.
Do consider yourself.
I believe
you will keep it secret.
You are right, Mr. Luo.
The two of you, come home with me.
Young Master,
we just witnessed a great show.
That was interesting, indeed.
Women don't have a say
in deciding their own marriage.
Seventh Lady
is really something else.
She pressured Luo Chengzhang
to cancel the engagement
with the Jiang Family.
Tactical and reasonable.
We should be discreet
when searching for evidence from her.
Understood.
Young Lady,
the marriage pact
with the Jiang Family is off now.
Why are you not happy?
Father
treats me like a stepping stone
and insists that I marry
into the Jiang Family.
But he won't do that
to Yilian.
Old Madam and Madam Lin
are on your side.
Right.
I only have them.
I have to get my hands dirty
to protect Grandma.
Qing Qu,
do you think I went too far?
I'm doing something I once despised.
Before this,
I truly despised her dirty tricks.
But now,
I have become just like her.
She wouldn't have walked into your trap
if she hadn't harbored an ill intention.
Don't overthink, Young Lady.
Why are you so foolish?
Mother,
what should I do now?
What if... What if Father
punishes me?
Enough. Stop whimpering.
Mother...
Stop it.
Stop crying.
Lian,
do you know how dearly
your father holds you
and how he hates the idea
of you becoming a concubine?
Do you know that?
But you made silly mistakes.
And I have to
clean up after you.
Come.
Twenty strokes on her palm.
- Yes.
- Mother.
Father didn't punish me.
Why are you beating me?
That's his own decision
whether to punish you.
But you need to show
that you are reflecting on yourself.
No, I won't.
Hold out your hand.
Hold out your hand Now.
Beat her.
(Xingfang Abode)
What are you doing?
Yuechan,
what has happened?
Why was Lian
so bold?
It's my fault.
I failed to control her.
Before, she told me
that she and Mr. Jiang
had feelings for each other,
so I...
I didn't discipline her properly.
She has been losing weight.
It reminds me of
the days when I was missing you.
I couldn't see her upset,
so I didn't stop her.
But when I found out Mr. Jiang
was going to be betrothed to Yining,
I warned her
to break things off with him.
I was being careless
and failed to discipline her properly.
Please punish me, my dear.
How could I bear
to punish you?
Yuechan,
you are too kind.
But sometimes, kindness can ruin things.
You've been managing household affairs
while looking after Lian and Xuanyuan.
It has been tough for you.
My dear, it's not tough at all.
I have already
punished Lian.
She learned the lesson.
It's also my fault
that Old Madam fell sick.
I'm willing to chant scriptures
300 times
to pray for her well-being.
Fortunately,
this matter is kept contained.
Besides, Mother's condition
is stable.
But
that's the last one.
My dear,
I will teach Lian properly.
She won't repeat the same mistake.
Yuechan.
You, Lian, and Xuanyuan
are the most important ones to me.
Don't worry
about Lian's marriage.
I will take care of that.
Mother.
Yining, you are here.
I investigated all the servants
and found that the person gossiping
in Old Madam's place was
Yue from my abode.
What was your maid doing
in Muxi Hall?
Yue always tends to the plants,
so I sent her to Muxi Hall
to look after Old Madam's peonies.
She was talking nonsense there
and annoyed Old Madam.
Maids in your abode
are very reliable.
Why was she gossiping in Muxi Hall?
Something seems fishy.
Are you saying
that she was being used?
It must be Mistress Qiao.
I must go and confront her.
Mother, don't go just yet.
Please sit down and calm yourself.
Think about this. Mistress Qiao
went through all this trouble
just to set up your maid.
It's because she intended
to rid herself of blame.
If we confront her now,
she will definitely pretend
to be innocent
and make you look bad.
You have a point.
I can't fall into her trap.
But what should I do?
Who was talking to Yue at that time?
She said
it was an old maid
who served in Muxi Hall. She's called
Ms. Lyu.
By the way,
I had someone transcribe
Yue's confession. Take a look at this
and see if it's suspicious.
Ms. Lyu is strange.
Her topics seem to revolve
around the marriage
between the Luo and Jiang Families.
She kept mentioning
that Grandma holds me dear
and that I would marry
as a principal wife.
She seems to be tempting Yue
to retort against her by saying
that I'd actually marry
as a concubine.
Yue also mentioned that Ms. Lyu
kept broaching the topic that Old Madam
was worried about your marriage,
which is why she responded to her.
Also, why did Ms. Lyu
choose the moment
just when Grandma showed up
to bring up this topic?
The problem is,
there's nothing
to nitpick
from this conversation per se.
They would only be punished
for gossiping about the master.
Do you mean
that someone
brided Ms. Lyu?
That's possible.
Qing Qu,
go and investigate Ms. Lyu.
Yes, Young Lady.
Ms. Qing Qu,
what are you doing here?
And what are you doing here?
I'm looking for Ms. Lyu.
I went to several places
but couldn't find her.
Is she in this room?
Why are you looking for Ms. Lyu?
Young Master sent me to ask her
if Old Madam likes the plant
he gave.
Don't look at me like that.
Everyone in this residence
wants to please Old Madam.
Besides, Ms. Lyu is the only one
who's amiable.
Not just us,
but others also seek her help.
In that case,
Ms. Lyu is quite popular.
Indeed.
I also heard that Mistress Qiao
recommended Ms. Lyu's son
for a job under her brother.
Really?
By the way, Ms. Lyu isn't here.
Then, I will try other places.
Young Master.
Have you got the message through?
Yes.
Young Master,
you helped Seventh Lady
since you returned.
But she doesn't know this at all.
We won't have a chance to borrow
Old Master's paintings from her.
Are you purely trying
to help Seventh Lady?
Keep an eye on Li Yinglong.
Yes, Young Master.
It's oriental sweetgum.
Mistress Qiao is so cruel.
She dares to harm Old Madam.
Mistress Qiao.
Why are you afraid?
Even if they detained her,
as long as she doesn't admit it,
no one can accuse her.
You are right, Mistress Qiao.
Mistress Qiao, Madam Lin wants you
to head to Muxi Hall now.
Did she say why?
She only asks for you.
Second Madam is there, too.
Tell her I'm coming.
Yes.
Father,
Grandma's health
is an important matter in the residence.
We have been
a scholarly family for generations.
We are well known
for being an example
of adhering to ethics and rules.
However, someone in this residence
is spreading rumors,
causing big trouble.
I hope you can investigate this
thoroughly
and give Grandma an explanation.
Of course.
However,
isn't Yue
the maid from Madam Lin's abode?
I heard she has been punished.
Why? Is there another story behind it?
There's another clue
I wouldn't dare to hide.
It concerns Mistress Qiao,
so I invited her here.
What does this have to do with her?
Whether it relates to her,
we will find out later.
Greetings, Second Master.
Greetings, Madam Lin.
Yuechan...
Yue!
Yue,
were you and Ms. Lyu there
when Old Madam fainted?
Yes.
But I didn't mean for that to happen.
Ms. Lyu brought up the topic.
She insisted on bending my ears
about Seventh Lady's marriage.
I didn't want to respond to her,
but she kept talking,
especially when Old Madam came
to check on her plants.
I didn't. You are lying.
You were talkative.
Don't blame me for that.
Ms. Lyu,
this bag of silver taels
was found in your room.
There are over ten silver taels.
How could a maid
have so much money?
Did you steal it?
No, I didn't steal it.
Or did someone bribe you
to pass the message to Grandma
through Yue
and cause her to fall sick?
That's not true. The money...
The money was given by my son.
He learns to do business outside
and has made some money.
- Your son gave you this?
- Yes.
Why did this pouch
smell like oriental sweetgum?
I remember
Mistress Qiao's abode
uses this incense, right?
Father.
I'm wronged.
The oriental sweetgum
isn't exclusive to me.
Why are all of you
suddenly accusing me now?
If I have wronged you,
let me ask you this.
Is Ms. Lyu's son following
Fifth Master Qiao to learn to do business?
Is Fifth Master Qiao
your younger brother?
He is my brother,
but I have no idea
about his business.
But I heard
that you recommended Ms. Lyu's son
for a job under him.
What do you mean?
Father,
to get to the bottom of this,
we can ask a few people to find out.
There's no need to make a fuss
over something without evidence.
The priority now is
for your grandma to wake up soon.
Father,
perhaps someone
is secretly plotting this.
It may seem unintentional,
but in fact, everything is well-planned.
I'm innocent.
It's my fault
for not disciplining the servants.
But I would definitely not
commit such a ridiculous mistake
to harm Old Madam.
Perhaps Seventh Lady
still holds grudges against me
for what happened back then.
Still, you can't
slander me.
You seem guilty.
You won't stop bringing up the past.
You know very well
what the truth is.
Enough.
Father,
we must adhere to the family rules.
Grandma's safety is at stake.
Please investigate this thoroughly.
♪I'm willing to fall into the abyss
in order to reveal the fate♪
It's far-fetched
that Mistress Qiao
egged on Ms. Lyu.
However, Mistress Qiao
failed to discipline the servants.
She should be held accountable
for this incident.
Mistress Qiao
is to be confined for a month.
Well.
That's all for this matter.
Father,
I'm afraid it's inappropriate
for Mistress Qiao
to continue managing household affairs.
This matter
may be pursued
when Grandma wakes up.
Second Master,
I also think it's inappropriate.
We must give Old Madam
an explanation of this.
Mother is seriously ill.
We can't disturb her
over a trivial matter like this.
As such,
I will hand over the authority
of the household management to you.
What did you say?
I say I'll hand over the authority
of the household management to you.
All right.
Second Master...
Yuechan,
sort out the ledgers.
Once Mother wakes up,
hand over the keys
to Madam Lin.
Listen carefully, everyone.
If anyone dares to gossip
or spread rumors in Muxi Hall
to disturb my mother again,
they will be punished with fifty flogs
without mercy
and sent to the farm.
Yes.
(Caifu Abode)
Mother, stop pacing.
Yining,
pinch me.
Is this a dream?
Did your father really give me
the authority to manage the household?
It's true.
Oh, heavens.
I can't believe
this will happen to me
at this age.
Mother,
I believe you are more than capable
of managing the entire residence.
Honestly, I had never thought of
competing with her over the years.
But I didn't expect her
to bring harm to Old Madam.
Besides, she even tried
to frame Caifu Abode.
I'm not incompetent.
I just think
the competition
is pointless.
Since we have a new head,
new rules should be established.
♪South wind weaves
a brocade tapestry of lives♪
♪Begonias lean on each other
in front of the turquoise pond♪
♪The tea fragrance wafts
along the long street♪
♪A bright heart will radiate the world♪
Grandma,
you are awake.
Is this a dream?
No.
I'm watching you.
Help me sit up.
Slowly.
I want to get up now
to ask your father.
I want to ask him if
he was out of his mind
to agree to marry you off
as a concubine.
Grandma,
the Jiang Family intended to take me
as a concubine.
But Father personally went
to turn it down.
Really?
Yes.
Finally, your father
is behaving like a father now.
Think about this.
The legitimate daughter
of the Luo Residence
is going to be someone's concubine?
If this gets out,
we will become a laughing stock.
Shame!
Grandma,
don't always believe
in everything you hear.
You can wait for me
and explain it to you,
all right?
All right.
You must be thirsty.
Grandma,
Ms. Lyu from your abode
isn't honest.
I have sent her away.
Mistress Qiao failed in her duty
to keep the servants in check.
Father has handed over the authority
of household management
to Mother.
He favors Mistress Qiao very much.
I can't believe he changed his mind.
Wonders never cease.
You have always worried that Mother is
on the downtrodden side
in this residence.
Given the current situation,
Father can't deny it.
If Hairu takes control
of the household management
and handles this job perfectly,
it would be a crutch for her
in the future.
That's very good.
Yes.
Mother is frank
and sincere,
and she cares about you.
That's more reassuring.
My Yining has really grown up.
You are no longer the little girl
anyone can manipulate.
That's right.
If Mistress Qiao hadn't gone overboard,
I wouldn't have been so harsh on her.
Ning,
I'm concerned about you.
You have endured so much alone.
Sweetheart, listen.
Let the past be the past.
Before your mother passed on,
she told me
that she only wanted you
to have an easy life.
Grandma.
Ning, sit here.
Ning, dear,
I only hope you can
have a peaceful life.
Find a fine man
who cherishes you,
and to have children by your side.
Even if I were to die tomorrow,
I have no regrets.
Grandma,
don't talk nonsense.
I would rather not marry
and stay beside you
to take care of you.
My sweet girl.
(Chengjing Hall)
Get up.
Previously,
Madam Lin has been
looking after me.
That's why the household management
was temporarily entrusted
to Mistress Qiao.
From now on,
this authority
should be returned to Madam Lin.
Having a concubine
to manage household affairs
is simply ludicrous if people find out.
In the future, all the ledgers
and expenses
must go through Madam Lin.
All the maidservants,
if you need anything,
you must report to Madam Lin.
Yes.
Get up.
Hairu,
it will be a tough task for you.
I will try my best
not to disappoint you, Mother.
Hairu,
since the keys have been
passed on to you,
we can dismiss the meeting.
As you entrusted me with the task,
from today on,
I will establish new rules for you.
What do you think, Mistress Qiao?
You are right, Madam Lin.
I shall do as you say.
Let's begin
with daily greeting practice.
You may start
the daily greeting practice
once your confinement ends.
Daily greeting practice?
You are right.
I should've done this earlier.
But I'm weak,
and Chengzhang is concerned for me,
so he permitted me to skip it.
Mistress Qiao, you are weak
because you lack exercise.
This is Madam Lin's
daily routine schedule.
Please follow everything on it closely.
At three-quarters past the Yin hour,
the concubine must prepare water
for washing up.
Three-quarters past the Yin hour?
The sky is still dark,
and the rooster hasn't even crowed.
Madam Lin wakes up at the Mao hour
every day.
If you don't wait
at the Caifu Abode earlier,
do you expect Madam Lin
to serve you instead?
Starting from Mao hour, the concubine
will assist the principal wife
with washing up, getting changed, and having
breakfast until the latter retires for the night,
and the former is free to return to rest.
When the principal wife is attending
to household affairs,
the concubine must wait upon her,
serving tea, filling empty cups,
massaging, and fanning.
When the principal wife
goes out on a carriage,
the concubine needs
to follow her on foot.
When the principal wife
scolds the concubine,
the latter must kneel and listen to her
and not talk back.
Without the principal wife's permission,
the concubine is not allowed to leave
the residence or meet any guests.
Madam Lin...
This is too much, Hairu.
I believe Mistress Qiao has predicted
this day would come
when she chose this path back then.
I was too generous to her,
and that made her forget
how to behave like a concubine.
My dear,
have you forgotten it, too?
Whatever.
Do you have any objections,
Mistress Qiao?
No, I don't.
Keep the book well.
You can study it carefully
while you are being grounded.
Ms. Li.
Yes, Madam Lin.
Bring all the ledgers to my room
first thing in the morning.
Don't miss a single ledger.
Yes, Madam Lin.
(Caifu Abode)
Yining, thank you so much for today.
I finally can get my resentments
off my chest
after being oppressed by her
over these years.
I'm also happy for you.
What do you want to eat?
I will order the kitchen to prepare.
What else do you want?
I can bring them to you.
Mother, there's nothing I want.
But I have a favor
to ask of you, Mother.
What's it?
I want to send Shenyuan's allowance
to him.
Third Brother,
are you studying?
Why are you calling me that?
You are also Father's son.
Naturally, I will call you brother.
Do you not like it?
Seventh Sister.
How's Old Madam?
She is out and about.
This time, I came here
to bring you this month's allowance.
Mother is in charge now,
so you will receive a sufficient amount
from this month onward.
That's very thoughtful of you.
A favor for a favor.
Mother is fair.
If anything is lacking here,
just tell Mother.
I will. Thank you.
I will take my leave.
It seems Seventh Lady
has noticed we helped her.
She keeps calling you brother just now.
So?
Young Master,
why don't you take this opportunity
to borrow Old Master's paintings?
You are indeed a daft...
Young Master.
Get ready for tonight.
Where are we going tonight?
Bring the tea.
Young Lady,
what do you mean
by "a favor for a favor"?
Do you really think Shao'an
went to see Ms. Lyu that day?
Did he purposely tell me that?
But why would he do that?
I'm not sure.
But the person in Jimo House
isn't an enemy.
From now on,
I will treat him as my brother.
(Luo's Residence)
(Haitang Abode)
Young Master,
I found the late Emperor's handwriting
on this painting.
Will it be here?
If you were Old Master,
would you put it here
when everyone knew you were good
at painting trees
and the late Emperor even left
his inscriptions on them?
You have a point.
Are you sure Seventh Lady
won't come back now?
She always serves
at Ximu Hall at this hour
until the Xu hour.
Just in case, let's make it quick.
Yes, Young Master.
You must be tired, Young Lady.
Didn't you say she should be serving
in Ximu Hall now?
This is unexpected. What should we do?
Young Lady,
Old Madam is concerned about you,
that's why she didn't let you serve her.
It has been tough for you these days.
Please rest early.
I wonder
if they have found Physician Du.
Second Master and Madam Lin
should be working on it.
Hopefully, they can find him soon
and heal Grandma.
Well,
let's go to Mother's abode tonight.
Tell the kitchen
to send almond soup over.
Yes, Young Lady.
They mentioned Physician Du just now.
Send someone to look into it.
Yes, Young Master.
Let's continue.
(Bilian Pavilion)
Let me out!
- I can't stay here anymore.
- No.
It's late at night.
Also, you are under house arrest.
You can't leave the room.
I want to see Father.
He hasn't come here
ever since I was grounded.
This has never happened before.
Young Lady,
Mistress Qiao told us
to endure even more
during a time like this.
She can endure, but I definitely can't!
Young Lady, you are
no match for Luo Yining.
If she finds leverage against you...
How can I be no match for her?
Father has always doted on me
and treated me as a legitimate daughter.
Also,
my brother, Xuan, has bright prospects.
Father has placed all his hope on him.
What does Luo Yining have?
Aside from the sickly Grandma,
does she have anything better than me?
Young Lady, keep it down.
If this gets out,
you will be deemed disrespectful.
Yes, you are right.
You are far better
than her in every way.
It's just that
Mistress Qiao doesn't want you
to be bothered by her.
Mother has overestimated Luo Yining.
The more you all think highly of her,
the more I want to
take her down a notch.
Young Lady.
Spread this
around the Haitang Abode.
What's this?
Don't smell it.
Don't act clumsily.
Also,
don't let my mother
find out about this.
Mother.
You are here, Yining.
I heard you were still busy
at this hour,
so I brought you some almond soup.
Daughters are sweethearts.
I didn't know
I would have such fortune now.
I can't understand
how Mistress Qiao managed
the accounts all these years.
If any of my shopkeepers
made accounts like this,
I would've kicked them out.
Mother, did you handle accounts before?
I used to help my father
manage a dozen shops
before I got married.
When I was a kid,
every time I read or wrote,
my head would hurt.
But I was elated
to use the abacus and do accounts.
Are you going to finish
all those ledgers tonight?
They are only part of it.
Butler Bai said there was
another chest of ledgers outside.
Mistress Qiao has been
managing the household for years.
It's impossible to finish crunching
all the numbers in just a few days.
How about you teach me?
Perhaps
I can help ease your burden.
You are intelligent.
You will pick it up quickly.
Also, I need a helper.
♪It's complicated but I'm not afraid♪
♪There's light in my heart♪
♪Following the river of time♪
♪I dive into the whirlpool♪
♪For the sake of you and mine♪
♪In search of an outcome♪
♪I'm willing to risk my life♪
♪To break the chain of nights♪
♪I'm willing to fall into the abyss♪
♪In order to reveal the fate♪
♪Forget about the outcome♪
♪Let me be your shoulder to lean on♪
♪Even if things go south, so be it♪
♪Love is a voyage with you by my side♪
♪The dust eventually settles♪
♪No matter how fragile and trivial I am♪
♪I will dance and shine bright♪
♪I overcome all kinds of doubt♪
♪And obstacles♪
♪For the sake of you and mine♪
♪Committing to my promise♪
♪I'm willing to risk my life♪
♪May my existence shine on more♪
♪Let go of everything♪
♪Let the longing fade♪
♪Forget about the outcome♪
♪As long as it fulfills
the vastness of love♪
♪Even if things go south, so be it♪
♪Love is you being by my side♪