(Lee Eun-Chun as Kim Hye-In and Kim Ye-Rin as Baek Jin-Na)
(Kim Min-kyu as Cha Chen-wook, Lee Jong-hyuk as Seo Do-yeon)
(Park Si-woo as Min Yool-hee, Jang Deok-soo as Park Woo-jin, Jang Sung-yoon as Kim Hae-in)
(Yuan Kui-bin as Lee Sa-rang and Yoon Jae-hyun as Hwang Bo-seok)
(Oh Ji-ho as Seo Hee-kwon)
(Cheongdam International High School 2)
(This drama is purely fictional and the characters, places, organizations, groups, events, etc. have nothing to do with reality)
Hello Wu Shien
I really beg you
I'll be dead if that video gets out
Really? Then... just go die.
I beg you
What should I do to make you let me go?
I can do anything you want me to do.
That video...really can't be shared
Forget it, I'm going to explode everything I have.
Whatever the case, Diamond Six is all over.
Wu Shien: My video has nothing to do with them.
In conclusion
Come over to my side first.
Where are you
Me? I'm at school.
There's not much time left. You didn't arrive before 12 o'clock.
This video will be the first to be released
Hello Wu Shien
Wu Shien
Hello…
Hello Wu Shien
What about your cell phone?
what to do
Hello…
(Scientific Investigation)
(police)
Wu Shien is dead
(Over 1 billion Wu Shien)
(Park Woo Jin)
(Wu Shien)
And I…
Became the murderer of Wu Shien
Suspect
What are you doing?
You really are...
Chairman's recall...
(Emergency Council of the Seiji Foundation)
I am the chairman Xu Xiquan and I hereby declare clearly
Future Cheongdam International High School
We will continue to maintain our status as Cheongdam International High School
Any behavior that interferes with this
I absolutely...
Absolutely will not tolerate
Question 39 requires you to select a sentence with a participial particle forming a subsidiary component.
Then we need to first have the concept that the subordinate components are the article and the adverb
To solve this problem
What happened? It seems to be related to the necklace
It seems so. Huiren, come here for a moment.
Hey, I heard that she pushed Wu Shien to find a special recruiter. Why?
Really? She's crazy.
Special recruited insects actually kill people?
Are we still living in the same room with a murderer?
Did she really kill someone? Damn it.
It's really too scary. Are you crazy? That's what I mean.
Poor her. What on earth is she thinking?
Does the special recruited insect kill people?
I already knew she had no quality.
Did the special recruit bug kill someone? Is she crazy?
It's really not me
I didn't kill anyone
I am just accepting the investigation as a related person.
You don't have to worry too much
It's not me anymore
You have the right to refuse
But the school asked to complete the investigation as soon as possible
The special insect can actually kill people
Kim Hye In killed Oh Si Eun
Have you seen that video?
Kim Hye In Nude Videos
I heard that she took off all her clothes in front of Li Demin
It seems like he received 10 million?
Crazy woman really does everything. If you need money, you should beg for it.
(Cheongdam International High School 2)
(Statement)
According to call records
You are the person she contacts most recently.
Even the last call was to you
Why do you go to school late at night?
Because... I have an appointment with Shien
Are you being threatened?
What
I saw that the dead classmate sent you a threatening text message
so
Did you push her down?
I don't
I didn't go up to the rooftop at all. It's true. Please believe me.
Let me tell you first.
You were threatened because of something?
It's like this...
I heard that it was Kim Hye-in who pushed Oh Si-eun down the stairs
How could she do something like that? It's horrible.
Min Yool Hee
What
I sometimes... want to kill someone.
Don't you think so?
right
I wouldn't think so
Is there a typo?
(Seo Hee-soo, Representative Director of the Cheonggi Foundation)
There is a typo here
There is a typo... There is a typo above
I said I hate the name Xu Xixiu the most, right?
I'm really sorry about everything that happened with your brother.
I'll check them all again.
elder brother
Is that guy my brother, Mr. Kim Jin-seop?
I'm really sorry
Please give me more advice in the future.
Please take care of me,
You can go now
Wu Shien Case
The family believes it was suicide
Don't you want things to get out of hand?
Yes
The witness is Kim Hye-in
This is the student who enrolled last time to cover up the incident of Kim Hae-in falling from the building.
She testified to police that she saw nothing.
I also want Wu Shien's case to be closed as suicide.
Two suicides have occurred in one year
And it's all related to Kim Hye-in
That's a bit of a headache.
You go out
(Cheongdam International High School student information card Kim Hye-in)
That?
I'm asking
Lawyer appointment fees are more expensive than expected
But this is about the life of the child.
Just get the security deposit back.
Should be able to afford
Just change your place to live
I'll sleep with you.
Let Huiren have her own room
(Cheongdam International High School)
Cheongdam International High School
Not really good...
I have to study here for three years?
I'm really going crazy.
That was the case last time.
It's been so long now and she's here... It's crazy
Look at her
Sit down...
So funny
Damn, this is hilarious
Hey, are you scared?
What's wrong
Aren't they your friends?
You will be afraid
It's just a tapeworm, but it dares to kill people
You worm...
Should be killed
Like this
Damn, my hands are dirty.
Do you have wet wipes?
Sorry, I thought it was a bug.
It seems that you can't even feel the pain now
Wu Shien is really pitiful
When you pushed me off the roof and broke my head
It must be very painful.
If you want to save your head, stop it.
What
Are you going to kill me too?
Damn it, she's trying to kill us. We really need to be careful. We might die.
You're all equally disgusted
When did you become so concerned about Wu Shien?
and
The investigation results are not out yet
I am upright and I am innocent.
By then
I will never forgive you
Hey, I really don't understand
You are different from other special insects.
Why are you so confident when you have nothing?
Because you are at the bottom of the special recruitment circle.
There's nothing to lose, right?
No money and no background
No parents yet...
Pu Shuo, are you okay? Damn, you've gone mad, you crazy woman
You are dead
Damn, catch her.
Damn it, catch him!
You stinky bitch
Crazy woman
Go catch the damn thing
Not allowed to leave
Damn it, if I catch you, I'll kill you, you stinky bitch
Get in the car quickly...
Who is that person?
Get going
This is our school uniform.
Li Silang
Who are you?
You're asking now?
Special recruitment of bug bucket Jin Huiren, right?
What did you say
hateful…
I've heard a lot about you.
I am Silang
Li Suwang's younger brother
Lee Su-wang…
Because you want to spend more time with me?
's younger brother?
But you... don't say I am...
Don't say I'm a special recruiter
worn out
Coffee is ready
So cute!
It's the type I like
I was a little worried because I couldn't contact Brother Suwang before.
He went to study abroad
Said to go to study abroad, but was actually kicked out
Our Pastor Li is not someone you want to mess with.
I didn't know he had a brother.
Seeing that you all like motorcycles, you are indeed brothers.
Feel sorry
I just hit you
My head still hurts.
Please give me something delicious
I didn't hit that side.
No matter what, I'm definitely on your side.
We just met and he said he was on my side
Bai Zina
You will receive a gift today
Gift
Hope you like it
Dad is me
Going to the company?
OK, I know.
Facing the Fourth Industrial Revolution
(Expanding the future of biotechnology, core healthcare, new drugs, gene therapy evolution)
The future development of the biotechnology industry is attracting much attention
Especially the most advanced biotechnology in the development of new medical drugs
(Company Overview: Chesei Pharmaceuticals is a leading company in the next-generation biotech industry representing Korea)
(Merged Briefing: The new generation biotech industry has achieved rapid development by combining digital technology)
Especially the most advanced biotechnology in the development of new medical drugs
It will greatly improve our quality of life in many fields such as gene therapy.
Yes, President.
As stated in the information sent to you
Although they are currently the first in Kosdaq market value
But the funds don't seem to be sufficient.
If we can do a share exchange
It can also be a springboard for us to enter new businesses.
Are you saying we should adopt a friendly strategy rather than a hostile approach?
Yes, President.
Okay, let's do it. I know.
(Cha Myung-gyu, Strategic Planning Department)
Daughter, what are you doing now?
(Mother)
You are here. Please sit down.
There will be a report coming out soon.
You have to pretend nothing happened
What report
About divorce
Please don't divorce
This is an adult matter. I told you not to get a divorce.
How can we get divorced because of that unknown woman?
She is even a contract teacher at our school.
Speak politely
What about mom?
Who caused her to become an alcoholic and suffer from depression?
Is that my fault?
Blood relationship really can't deceive people
You're just like your mother, always blaming others for your mistakes
You said blood relationship can't deceive people?
Am I not your daughter?
I'm not here to discuss this with you.
You go back
I will kill them.
The woman and her unborn child
Damn guy
Even family members cannot cross the line
How can a successor to the group be so reckless?
Zina is going back to prepare the car
Now the one who crosses the line...
It's you
(The divorce between Hanming Group Chairman Bai Zhuyuan and Xi Zaijing was an agreement, please do not speculate)
(Chairman Bai Zhuyuan of Hanming Group filed for divorce and stated that the two divorced by agreement)
(Xi Zaijing is currently hospitalized. If you spread unfounded rumors without reason, legal action will be taken.)
Bai Zina
Is she crazy?
Hey...are you crazy?
I'm going to find my mom
My mom doesn't answer the phone.
Wait a minute, I'll call a taxi for you.
With the attention of many economic experts...
Then reported the divorce news of Hanming Group Chairman Baek Joo-won
It is rumored that Chairman Bai's mistress is pregnant
(Mother)
Hanming Group said this was Chairman Bai's personal issue.
No response was made on behalf of the group
In addition, the situation of Hanming Group's successor
It is also expected that it will be affected by Chairman Bai's divorce.
Currently, Chairman Bai... Mr. Driver
Could you please turn off the radio?
(Hanming Hospital)
Hey Bai Zina
Bai Zina
mom
Why don't you answer the phone?
My baby girl, you are here.
How much alcohol did you drink?
Are you drinking again?
Isn't it said that if you drink again, it will be dangerous?
Why divorce?
Does it make sense to talk about this?
Mom is rich Zina
It's not because of money.
What should I do if you give up so easily?
Haven't you ever thought about me?
It turns out that Zina is feeling uneasy.
I'm sorry
sorry
I should protect Zina...
You can't fall like me.
Don't hand over anything
Don't let others snatch it away.
No matter what
don’t worry
I will never...
Let no one take my things
No matter what
Hello, are you okay?
What…
I must be crazy to wait for her for hours.
Why should I worry about her?
(Cheongdam International High School)
(It is true that Bai Qina's mother was admitted to a mental hospital)
Did you see this?
There's this rumor going around.
Your mother is in a mental hospital.
What about this kind of rubbish post?
but…
You were in front of everyone that day
Didn't you spread this kind of rubbish?
Said Woojin had sex with other people before
That guy was also threatened.
Kim Hae-in slept with your boyfriend
Everyone always has...
A secret you want to hide
But did you receive the gift I gave you?
Gift
It was delivered later than I expected.
(We hereby inform that Bai Qina has committed school bullying by spreading false information in school)
False news...
(If you are subject to review by the Student Disciplinary Committee, please attend this week's committee and explain yourself)
School violence
What are you going to wear to the Disciplinary Committee?
Why would you do such a stupid thing?
How could I be punished?
Who knows?
You want to live with that dirty guy?
I have made my words very clear.
but…
I'm not spreading rumors.
I uploaded it because it's real.
It's you.
People who upload that kind of spam
I also know one thing about you that is not a rumor
Kim Hae-in
Who pushed her off the roof?
I think I know
Kim Hye In's dad is so pathetic
what are you doing here
So you didn't know
Your dad...
Kneeling and mopping the floor in the school office
Kim Hye In's dad is here and he did a great job
Please forgive me once...
Are you here, you bitch lady?
Dad, what are you doing? Stand up!
Hurry up, I'm speechless.
You still don't understand the situation?
Even if you kneel down and beg for mercy, I may not forgive you
Please, just once. This is related to the child's life.
She's done for now, I'll file a lawsuit for school violence
Let me drop her out of school
Madam...you can't let her drop out of school, Dad.
Where are you touching? It's so dirty.
never mind
I don't want to talk to this uncle any more
Call your mother
Even if your whole family kneels down and begs for mercy, it's not enough.
Where is your mother? Call your mother over
I don't have a mother
I said I don't have a mother
My mom is dead. What the hell are you doing looking for her?
Huiren, come with the teacher.
Huiren
The teacher also knows your mood. The teacher knows everything.
But if you are labeled as a school bully in your current situation
At least 4 years of records will be left in the student register
You won't have to take the certification exam then.
And you will not be able to find a job for several years. Do you understand what the teacher means?
Huiren
Okay?
I understand now
Ma'am... this is my reality
It will never change...
My Future
I was wrong
I don't want to live like this
Is it a crime to have no money?
I was wrong
No
I will let you know that being rich is also a sin
(Cheongdam International High School 2)