[This drama is fictional, and any similarity
with reality is purely coincidental.]
Ah!
Are you keeping what I gave you well?
What?
Don't you remember?
The necklace I gave you.
You…
You remember everything?
While I was suffering,
you gained quite a lot.
You shouldn't use someone else's misfortune
to make deals.
I had no choice, either.
That's impressive.
If I had just died,
would it have been better for you?
No!
I've never thought that way.
But why did you act like you didn't know me?
Oh.
Was it
because you became a Diamond 6?
Hey!
If you have a conscience,
disappear from this school tomorrow!
Then we'll all die together.
Wait!
I was not the one
who pushed you.
- What?
- I genuinely
feel sorry for you.
I also struggled to death.
I fought and endured much to achieve this.
Even watching me dying,
you closed your eyes and mouth
to get what you wanted.
What?
Yours?
Yeah, mine.
Look,
now I'm a Diamond 6,
and you're not.
Is that what you should be saying to me right now?
Yeah, Equal Opportunity Leech…
For Equal Opportunity Leeches
like us to become Diamond 6
is a great achievement in this school.
You know better than anyone.
But I accomplished it
and I have the power to help you.
So, if you want to stay in this school,
you should know what's important.
Think about it carefully.
Ah…
So now,
are you asking me to
yield to you?
Think carefully!
If Min Yul Hee finds out that
your memory has returned,
do you think she'll leave you alone?
What?
Hey!
Who do you think you are?
I'll kill you!
Die!
Who do you think you are?
- Why are you doing this?
- Hey, come here!
Hey!
- Die!
- Stop it!
Stop it!
Hey!
Do you think anything will change by doing this?
Stop it! Get a hold of yourself!
And you…
It'd be best if you keep
pretending to have amnesia.
Don't give yourself away unnecessarily.
Hey!
Get over here!
Let's go together.
Still, we're somewhat together
as the Diamond 6 members.
I didn't say it.
That I'm your fiancé.
You know you're really unlucky, right?
Yeah, I know.
But,
still, you seem to have developed
some feelings for me.
Isn't she cute?
Hey, let's go together!
What?
Cha Jin Wook is an illegitimate child?
What a waste.
Good-looking face, nice body.
Totally my type.
Regardless of his background, he's still handsome.
- Go for it.
- Are you crazy?
Still, that's not right.
Hi!
Aren't they funny?
Just until yesterday, they were
trying hard to be friendly.
Do your best, illegitimate.
Wow!
Everyone ignores me now.
Don't you think I'm pitiful?
Because you're a bastard?
Bastard…
Wow! You're so cold-hearted.
Aren't you being too self-pitying?
If we're talking about being pitiful,
those who were quietly victimized
are more to be pitied than you.
Like me.
Marriage?
If it helps my life, well,
I can force myself into it.
But there will never be a day in my life
where I come to like you.
Really?
Isn't that
being a little too definitive?
Huh?
Hye In, why…
Can you not ask?
[Cheongdam International High School]
It's cold.
Ta-da!
Hye In, after playing in the water,
you need to replenish calories, right?
I didn't play in water.
- What is that?
- Tteokbokki, sundae,
I even added intestines.
When you eat,
you look like a rabbit that
hasn't eaten for three months.
Is that a compliment or an insult?
Of course, it's a compliment.
You should eat some, too.
It's embarrassing if I'm the only one eating.
I'll just watch you eat.
Ah, excuse me. I have to take this.
Yeah.
Hello? Just a moment.
I'm at school.
I don't care.
Why is he carrying two phones?
What is this?
Cell phone…
This…
Why is this here?
[Cheongdam International High School]
Hey!
Did you see the video Black Dog
posted about our school yesterday?
Yeah, I did.
No wonder that punk Woo Jin,
even though he goofs around so much,
got accepted through the international selection.
Ah, darn it, really.
Because of that, my mom
went completely crazy yesterday.
I heard all of the Diamond 6 kids'
secret accounts got completely exposed.
[Privileged School Admissions
of Conglomerate Heirs Sparks Controversy]
[Admissions Fraud, and Exemption from Punishment?]
But there are also photos that seem like
they would be on a private Instagram account.
Where did they get all of this?
Isn't Black Dog a student from our school?
Nah, if they were from our school,
why would they self-destruct like that?
You never know.
Maybe some leech wants us all to go down together.
We seriously need to exterminate them.
Hey, call the exterminators to catch the leeches!
We have to get rid of them quickly, don't we?
I met with our friendly reporters
and cleaned up the articles.
However,
[Truth about Cheongdam International High School?]
Reporter Lee Ho Jong, from SBN,
is demanding more money.
What should we do?
He only knows where to get money from,
but he doesn't know any limits.
Just give it to him.
But,
how are we going to catch this punk?
Since the video server is based overseas,
it might take some time to identify.
Seeing as most of the material
consists of private photos,
it appears to be the work of an insider.
Whoever it is, handle it quickly
so it won't become a nuisance.
Aren't you taking the tray away?
Goodness…
Did you hear that story?
What story?
When Oh Si Eun died,
her phone disappeared.
And on it, there were videos
she used to blackmail other kids.
But among them…
Among them?
That…
What is it?
Why do you stop talking
in the middle of a sentence?
I was being blackmailed by Oh Si Eun too.
That pervert Lee Deok Min
told me to change clothes right in front of him.
So?
What?
Hey!
Who do you think I made that video for?
To pay off the dress you ruined.
Because of that 8 million won…
That's why.
You took off your clothes
for a measly 8 million won?
To you, it might be just a measly 8 million won,
but don't you think I stripped
because that's how desperate I was?
What?
You're having a private conversation,
and I just barged in cluelessly?
Should I leave?
No need.
We're planning a party this weekend.
You'll come, right?
Do you want to come too?
Me?
I'm not really interested in parties.
Really?
The others seem to have high expectations.
Like, "let's see Cha Jin Wook's
scale" or something…
You'll come, right?
Fine, I get it. So go away.
We were in the middle of a conversation.
No.
The conversation is over.
I'm off now.
That's unexpected.
You have friends too.
Friends?
What?
Did you hear that too?
This is Oh Si Eun's voice,
right? The laughing part.
Yeah, that's right, Oh Si Eun.
So creepy.
What are you talking about?
Why do we hear her voice here? It's scary.
Hey, listen.
This is 100% Oh Si Eun's laughter.
Right?
Crazy, did Oh Si Eun record this then?
Take this out.
Sorry, did I scare you?
You don't know me, right?
I'm Park Woo Jin.
I have something to say.
Do you have a moment?
I wanted to talk somewhere quiet.
I was really surprised you came back to school.
I was really worried,
so I'm glad you're okay.
Do you maybe not remember me?
Yeah.
Sorry.
Then,
you don't remember this, either?
What are you doing?
What could it be?
You blackmailed me with the hidden
camera video you got from Oh Si Eun,
you dirty girl.
No, I…
I almost hit rock bottom because of you!
And you get the convenient out of having amnesia?
Do you really not remember?
You don't remember sleeping with me, either?
After we slept together,
I even bought you expensive things.
It makes me curious…
if I buy you expensive things now,
is it still possible?
Ah, what should I wear this weekend?
You look like a goddess no matter what you wear.
Goddess, my ass.
Just a girl, right?
Just a girl.
What?
Ah…
You're jealous because
you don't have to choose clothes.
Why doesn't Bo Seok choose clothes?
He found a partner for the party.
Oh, I see.
I thought you wouldn't come
because you'd be too embarrassed,
since the Diamond 6 member
Kim Hye In will be there.
Do you wanna die?
Hey, Equal Opportunity Leech,
when you see someone,
you should greet them before leaving.
Move.
Move?
Ah, these annoying leeches!
Did you both go crazy together?
Hey, just because Kim Hye In became
a Diamond 6, do you think you're something?
Oh, darn, really!
Hey!
You said it was amnesia.
For memory loss,
you need to stimulate brain cells.
Will that be enough?
Exactly, surely,
you have to do it strongly.
- Like this…
- Hey!
Stop it!
Let's go.
I have organized the dress for you to wear
at the party of Mr. Cha Jin Wook.
I've checked off the ones that
the kids of other esteemed families
are paying attention to.
This dress,
send it to Kim Hye In's house.
Yes.
Well…
Cha Jin Wook
is throwing a party this weekend.
Why didn't you ask me to go?
Ah, it's just that…
- me and them now…
- I want to go too.
As your partner.
They say we used to date secretly.
It was like that in the past,
but not anymore.
Hae In, you
still don't know, right?
What?
Never mind.
Alright, let's go.
Yes.
Why aren't you eating?
It's delicious, though.
Here.
- Isn't it tasty?
- Eat it all.
Shall we go?
Okay.
Wait a moment.
It's cold.
Thank you.
It looks good on you.
Let's go.
Hey, Kim Hye In!
Ah, I told you to knock!
- What is this?
- What?
I don't know. What is it?
Do you think I'm your delivery man?
What is it?
Baek Jenna.
Do Un, can I go look in the mirror?
You can enter first.
No, I'll wait here.
Go and come back.
I'll be back quickly.
Okay.
Huh?
Seo Do Un,
you're here?
Yeah.
Wow!
This place is really nice!
How is it?
Do I look a bit weird?
Wow!
You can't find the old Kim Hye In anymore.
Old?
Are you insulting me right now?
No, it's a compliment this time.
Thanks.
Let's go together. Aren't you going in?
I came with Hae In.
I'm waiting while she went somewhere for a moment.
Ah.
Kim Hae In.
Hey, isn't that Kim Hae In?
Why is someone like that here? It's disgusting!
Ah, seriously!
So, you're out of your mind.
What makes you think you can come here?
Why? Can't I come?
I was invited too.
You were invited?
Ah, seriously!
What a load of nonsense.
I don't know who invited you,
as a partner, or whatever…
Seo Do Un?
Are you really naive now? Really…
Hey, get a grip!
Seo Do Un isn't a Diamond 6 anymore.
His dad was ousted ages ago,
and you're still sticking around?
Moreover, that guy's dad
must be in a bad position, as he was
completely pushed out by his younger brother.
So what?
I don't care.
You don't care?
That's hilarious.
Hey,
I don't know what kind of
trick you're trying to pull,
but you should just live quietly.
It'd be even better if you
transfer to another school.
Park Woo Jin,
you don't know
who pushed me, do you?
Someone who knows
that you and I had sex.
Someone who knows that
and wants to kill me.
Why are you suddenly talking nonsense?
I wonder if you get it after I've said this much.
How is Hae In these days?
What do you mean, "how is Hae In these days"?
What does that mean?
Uh… well…
Does she talk about me,
or has her memory returned, or anything like that?
No.
Does Hae In recognize you?
No, what are you talking about?
There's no way.
I was just asking.
I'm off now.
Do Un.
Have you been waiting long?
No, let's go in.
Cheers!
What is it?
Hey, are you okay?
Hye In!
Would you like some champagne?
Lee Sa Rang,
I have something to ask you.
Can you step outside for a moment?
It's the first time we're properly
introducing ourselves, right?
Huh?
You transferred too, didn't you?
I heard it was really hard to transfer here.
I paid a lot of money to get in.
How did you get in?
Besides,
even up to Diamond 6?
I just got in because a spot opened up.
What do you want to talk about?
Should we move somewhere else to talk?
- Sure.
- This party today is
hosted by Cha Jin Wook.
For a short while,
we will now begin the couple's dance event!
The winning couple
will be gifted the highest-quality champagne,
Cristal!
Now, make some noise!
Okay, the first couple,
please raise your hands!
- Me!
- There?
- Come here.
- Hye In, come out.
- What?
- Come out, now.
- Me?
- Let's go!
Why me?
Come out!
Wow, Sa Rang!
Wow!
Oh, it's hard!
See?
You can do it.
Those guys,
got so excited since that video of Black Dog
came out.
Did you see it too?
Black Dog?
Isn't it disgusting how they pretend
not to care on the outside but get all excited
about trashy gossip like that?
Are they crazy?
Hey!
Who wants to see something interesting?
My video?
Then, did Oh Si Eun film this?
This crazy girl…
Jin Wook,
your mother is really a beauty.
Looking closely, I see
you got your pretty looks from your mom.
This bastard is crossing the line.
You brat! Hey, say that again.
- Let go!
- Say it again!
- What are you doing?
- Say it again.
- Hey!
- Huh?
Come out.
What are you doing?
This bastard did this to me first.
I'm a bit late, right?
Let me introduce you, my fiancé, Cha Jin Wook.
That's right.
We're engaged.
Don't be mistaken.
What, Baek Jenna?
You put the Equal Opportunity Leech in Diamond 6,
and now you're even engaged
to an illegitimate child?
How did you end up like this, Baek Jenna?
I don't think this is the time
for you to worry about me?
But, Yul Hee, you need to develop better taste.
Your eye for dresses is really quite poor?