​
Stop right there!
Stop!
Move!
Are you okay?
I am okay.
Ms. Han.
Where did she go?
No way, right?
It can't be. No way.
How could he be scared of me? I'm so small.
No. Calm down.
I can't run to him like a zombie.
I need to show him that I'm cute.
I won't hurt you. I won't bite you.
I pay taxes and make donations. I'm a good dog.
Isn't this it?
It was definitely around here.
She must've changed already.
Did she break the curse?
Gosh, seriously...
Gosh, I'm going crazy.
What are you doing over there?
Hyung.
- Mr. Bo Gyeom?
- Are you drunk?
What are you doing up there?
There's a rat.
A rat? A rat?
A rat?
My gosh.
All right, let's see.
Where did you come from?
Gosh, you're so cute.
Where's your owner?
You're my owner.
Is it the owner's dog?
No, you can have me.
Jjong!
Gosh, where were you?
Gosh, where did you lose your collar?
Well, I'm not sure, but it looks like things are resolved.
Right, Jjong?
Let's go.
Hyung, a rat this big was jumping up and down here.
He was going to eat me. It came from there.
What do you mean, a rat?
How much did you drink, anyway?
Why did you drink so much you lost your mind?
Which one was the math teacher?
The one that was perched up.
How do you know?
She was drooling over the one that was standing.
He's a Korean history teacher.
Do they hire teachers based on looks these days?
Unlike vets, right?
Seriously...
Where did Ms. Hae Na go, by the way?
Huh?
Mr. Jin Seo Won is calling.
Don't answer for now.
Don't answer. Don't answer.
I should text him, at least.
Mr. Jin, I'm sorry, but something urgent came up.
I'll see you later.
The first attempt was a total failure.
Don't count my attempts.
There won't be second or third ones.
I'll make sure to get it done next time.
You don't have control over it.
Isn't Mr. Jin kind of weird?
Why is he afraid of such a tiny dog?
I suppose he had a traumatic experience.
But I'm so ridiculously cute.
What do I do now?
What do you mean, what do you do?
You have to kiss him and break the curse.
So how am I supposed to kiss him?
He hates dogs so much.
Just do it while he's sleeping.
- How?
- You can just date him.
Who said she would? Does Hae Na want that?
Come on. I have Mr. Bo Gyeom.
Yesterday, Mr. Bo Gyeom was like, "You're so cute."
He held me like this. Like this. Did you see that?
It's because you were a dog. He won't do that to a human.
Uncle, don't worry.
I'll make sure to get it resolved.
I'm sure you would.
The situation got worse now.
What do you mean?
You kissed him by mistake.
You said you'd treat him to a meal to apologize, so he went out,
but you dashed without paying.
- The math teacher thinks you're-
- A dine and dasher.
- Yes, a dine and dasher.
- Yes, you dined and dashed.
That's exactly it.
He'd think you're basically a scum.
That's right. A scum.
I'd be annoyed just to see her face.
Dine and dasher.
Come here, come here!
Stay calm!
Did she see that?
Hello.
Good morning.
Won, you didn't forget about us hanging out after work today, right?
What are you hanging out for?
He made me come out and drive last night.
So I want to make him pay for it.
Mr. Seo Won, did you drink?
Yes.
What did you talk about with Ms. Hae Na that you drank so much?
Did you drink with Ms. Hae Na alone?
Why?
There was a bit of a situation.
What situation?
Ms. Hae Na forced you to drink with her, right?
I see her all the time since we both teach Korean literature. So I know.
She's kind of immature.
It's kind of tiring to be with her.
- Ms. Yoon.
- Yes?
I'm not sure about talking behind her back when you don't know her well.
Right? I don't normally say stuff like this, either.
I should get ready for the class.
You said Ms. Hae Na suddenly disappeared last night.
Did something happen?
I'll go to the printing room.
Okay, okay.
Did you take care of the urgent situation last night?
Yes, my sister suddenly called me.
I'm so sorry.
Did anything else happen by chance?
L-Like what?
Never mind.
Give me your bank account number.
I said I'll treat you, but I ended up dining and dashing.
Send it to Mr. Lee. He's the one who paid.
Right, why did he suddenly come?
- Did you see him?
- No.
I didn't.
You said he paid, so...
I see. You called him to set us up, didn't you?
Yes.
If so, since you decided to help me,
how about we meet regularly so I can get tips from you?
- Regularly?
- Yes.
Is that too much?
Yes, it is.
Just think of it as a charity and doing good deeds.
Please help me out.
I'll just help you once, then.
Really?
I'm going somewhere with Hyung tonight.
Do you want to go instead of me?
Aren't you coming with us?
- Of course not.
- Why not?
Why do I have to go?
If it's just the two of us, it'd feel too much like a date.
I thought you wanted to go on a date. No?
Well, yes, but...
What if I die of a heart attack while hanging out alone with him?
I didn't know you liked him that much.
Well, I'm just wondering, what if?
Okay.
I'll come with you, but
feel free to do whatever afterward.
Thank you.
Two men are meeting at a place like this?
Ms. Hae Na.
- Ms. Chae Ah.
- What brings you here?
How about you?
Did Mr. Bo Gyeom invite you?
No, Mr. Jin did.
Did he invite you, too-
No, Mr. Bo Gyeom did.
- Ms. Hae Na.
- Yes.
You're interested in Mr. Bo Gyeom, right?
Pardon? Well...
It's just the two of us. You can tell me.
Well, um...
I'll help you so you two work out.
No, it's okay.
Why not? You make a nice couple since you both look like puppies.
Mr. Seo Won.
This place looks so fun.
Have you been to an escape room before?
No.
Ms. Chae Ah said she wanted to come, too.
Did you invite Ms. Hae Na?
- Yes.
- I see.
I thought you two weren't very close.
You're wrong. We're very close.
Right?
Yes.
Put these on, put your hands on each other's shoulders, and follow me.
Do we put it on like this?
Walk slowly.
- Are we doing okay?
- During the set amount of time, solve the mystery
using hidden clues and escape the room.
It's scary.
The code can't be just 1234...
No.
Let's look.
There must be a clue.
Should we look?
Are these clues?
Are they? Try solving the problem, Mr. Jin.
You're definitely a math teacher.
Over here. I think there's something here.
But it's too high up.
Seo Won, could you prop me up?
I think there's something up there.
I don't want to. You're heavy.
Forget about the math problem. I think we need to open this. Right?
- This is definitely it.
- Yes.
Could you prop me up, then?
Well...
Ms. Hae Na.
Yes?
Oh? There's something.
Let this go!
Hold on, hold on.
Are you okay?
We found it. We found it.
You have five minutes left.
We really don't have much time left.
We need to hurry. Hurry.
Ms. Hae Na, is there anything there?
No, there isn't. I really have no idea. What do we do?
We're trapped.
No, it's four.
It opened.
We're escaping. We're escaping.
We're escaping!
What?
I think I could stretch it to midnight.
I'm breaking the curse today. Just wait and see-
Ms. Han.
Why are you coming out alone?
They went to the bathroom.
I'm so sorry about earlier.
I was so scared.
It's okay.
Should I buy you fried chicken and beer to make it up to you?
Deal?
The three of you should go. I'll get going.
Huh? Why?
I'm a bit tired.
Just sit with us for a bit and leave, then. Okay?
No, I'll get going now.
No.
Just one beer, please?
I actually don't like drinking that much.
You get better as you drink. Please?
- No, I don't like it, I said.
- Don't be like that. Just a tiny bit.
Drink just a tiny bit, please?
Can't you hear what I'm saying?
How many times did I say no just now?
I just wanted to get close to you-
Why all of a sudden?
Because of Mr. Lee Bo Gyeom?
Yes, you said you'd set us up.
That's why I came all the way here.
Yes, you must've done a lot for us from your perspective.
I happened to hear it before.
That you feel uncomfortable with me.
You said there's a reason why.
Why do you feel uncomfortable with me, anyway?
I didn't mean it like that-
What are you, a nutcracker?
And am I a walnut?
You keep crushing me over and over and over again.
I need to know why so I can do something about it.
Never mind. I'll get going.
Ms. Han, the thing is...
Bye, then.
Why did I have to flip out, then?
I've been clinging to him a lot lately.
He must've thought I was like a leech.
Huh? Why are there three glasses?
Wow, he told me he was tired.
Does he feel energized because I left?
Ms. Hae Na, why did you leave?
Come back if you change your mind.
It's not about how I feel.
Huh? Hold on.
Excuse me.
♫  Nature is complete, enchanting night for our love  ♫
♫  We will be in sweet meadows in the enchanting night  ♫
♫  Graceful together  ♫
♫  Timeless memories that love will sustain from now  ♫
♫  Forever dancing in each other's minds  ♫
♫  But a loving...  ♫
♫  Forever hearts, timeless melodies  ♫
♫  As the sun rises, the sun will remain  ♫
♫  It will transcend  ♫
The math teacher is so harsh.
Why is he playing so hard to get?
Even the neighborhood dogs would get pissed off if rejected repeatedly like that.
Right?
Why does he hate me so much?
I really have no idea.
I really didn't do anything wrong to him.
Didn't do anything wrong...
Did you say he's afraid of dogs?
I don't know if it's because of the curse, but since you were kids,
the dogs in the neighborhood used to follow you.
Right. Why do dogs like us so much? We don't do anything for them.
I know. But you said he's really afraid of dogs.
But I'm sure all dogs in the area flock around her.
Let's just say you're really afraid of pigeons.
But imagine someone with ten pigeons on his shoulders is next to you.
Sometimes, one of them comes up on his head and flaps its wings.
Sometimes, it poops, too.
Daebak.
Come to think of it, back then...
Let's see. Tteokbokki...
Gosh, we forgot soondae.
What? Where did he go?
And in that moment, too.
I heard the mango one is good.
But that one looks good, too.
What do we do?
Right. It happened then, too.
I'll leave now.
That's it.
He's so afraid of dogs, but I keep attracting them.
He can't always do that since people can see him.
Woo Taek, you're a genius.
No, no. Go ahead and eat.
Genius.
You guys aren't allowed to approach me anymore.
Let's go to Kona.
I love it, I love it.
- Did you form your music group?
- We have a performance assessment?
I told you, you dummy.
Huh?
What's with this smell?
They're smoking.
Gosh, in their school uniform? How confident.
Let's go.
Ms. Han, Ms. Han!
Ms. Han, Ms. Han, Ms. Han!
Ms. Han, please yell at the Gyeonghoon High School students.
They're smoking in front of our school.
- Really?
- They do this all the time.
The cigarette smell drives me crazy.
Okay. I'll talk to them.
Really?
It's them, right?
Guys.
What kind of students smoke in front of a school?
Just keep going where you were going, Ahjumma.
I'm a teacher at Garam High School.
What? You're not even a teacher at our school.
You guys go to Gyeonghoon High, right?
What year and class are you in? Put out your cigarettes right now.
I'll just smoke this one and put it out, Ma'am.
Gosh, you punk. Hey.
Are you crazy?
- What, you idiot?
- Are you smiling?
She's about to cry because you mocked her.
You can't make a woman cry. Right? Right?
Ma'am, are you crying?
What are your names?
Why don't you wear your name tags?
Ma'am, you just touched my chest, didn't you?
Gosh, isn't this sexual harassment?
Is it okay for a female teacher to touch male students' chests like that?
Should we report her?
Daebak.
No, let's just touch her and call it even.
Excuse me for a second, Ma'am.
She asked what your names are just now.
You'd better let go of this.
What's your name?
Sir.
They're Seo Chang Soo, Min Gyeong Seok, and Do Jae Min.
Move. Move!
Are you okay, Ms. Han?
Huh? Yes.
Kids these days aren't afraid of teachers.
Yes. Thank you.
See you later at school.
Okay.
Ms. Hae Na.
Is something going on? Why do you look so upset?
What? What's wrong with you?
Hello.
Is it because I went to bed late last night? I don't feel so good.
Why did you go to bed so late?
Why did you suddenly disappear yesterday?
Because of you, I just ate chicken talking about the weather.
I'm sorry.
If you're sorry, get me a souffle cheesecake.
Okay.
I love souffle cheesecakes, too.
I'll get you one.
You like tiramisu.
Ask for it now.
I'm okay.
Hello.
"Peace Under Heaven" is a full-length novel.
Back in the day, full-length novels were published with subheadings.
Page 243. The third paragraph.
"It's Ho who destroyed the Qin dynasty."
Wow.
It's so hard to become a dog every night.
Mr. Jin.
What are you doing here at this time of day?
I don't have a class now, either.
Are you feeling better now?
I was a bit in shock this morning,
but I'm okay now.
It's so pathetic.
What kind of teacher is afraid of a student?
No.
It was enough to be afraid of.
Whoa, the kids were watching, and I had to discipline them.
But I wasn't sure what else to do.
I would've peed my pants if it were a dream-
Anyway, I'm okay now.
If it were a dream,
I would've peed my pants, too.
Right. Sorry about last night.
I'm sorry I suddenly lost my temper.
I'm sorry, too.
Thinking about it, I could see why you were mistaken.
Because of the situations that occur whenever I'm with you...
I gave you the impression that I'm avoiding you.
But...
To be honest, I...
Show him what you got.
Block properly. You'll break your bones otherwise.
Mr. Jin.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what it is,
but you don't have to tell me if it's too difficult.
You're trying so hard to explain.
So I don't think it's because you dislike me. And...
everyone is in unique situations
and it's natural to have at least one secret of their own.
I'll get going now, then.
Ms. Han.
Thank you for understanding.
Sure.
And...
I'll do my best trying to set you up with Hyung, too.
Okay.
Fighting.
Mr. Jin, I have a question.
You figured out the passcode in the first room. How did you do it?
Another word for King is Imgeum*. So "Im" as in Imgeum.
(King in Korean)
The character for the dragon in Earthly Branches is "Jin."
Reverse a word. W.A.R.
It spells "war."
So you're left with the clue "Imjin war."
Gosh, daebak. Imjinwoeran.*
(Japanese invasions of Korea)
By the way, they really made you want to escape the room.
Why did Hyung want to go to a place like that with just me?
It gives me the chills.
Jeonggye Monument at Mt. Baekdu
is a monument to create a border between the Joseon and Qing dynasties.
The monument says the Western side of it is the Yalu River
and the Eastern side of it is the Tumen River.
This might be in the exam. So make sure to memorize it, okay?
Okay.
That's it for today's class.
We'll have a fun debate in the next class.
The theme is, "If you can go back in history and reverse something,
when and where would you travel to?"
Okay?
Sir, are we being graded for this?
I'll make sure to grade you, at least.
I'm in trouble. What do I do?
Sir, how about you?
When and where would you travel to?
I'd choose...1592.
Why?
Because a tragedy you can't escape from started then.
Catch him!
How should I make it?
So, have you picked the date to meet yet?
Not yet, but I should.
Did you get to talk about dogs at all?
But...I think he wanted to hide that he's afraid of dogs.
Why?
I saw Mr. Jin smiling today.
I've never seen him smiling before.
Why make such a big deal out of it?
Hey, you'd better get close to him and break the curse.
Yes, hello?
Hey, why is it so hard to reach you?
Everyone is in unique situations
and it's natural to have at least one secret of their own.
We ran out of ramen.
Uncle, I'm going to a convenience store. Do you want something?
What? Where did he go?
I'm getting expelled if I get caught smoking again.
Just get expelled, you idiot.
Geez.
Do some research on that bastard.
I want to beat him up with the kids sometime.
Should we mess up a kid from Garam High?
Don't just talk about it and do it.
Gosh, you're so frustrating.
Geez, they're all pictures of themselves.
Wow, she's so pretty.
Huh? Is this it?
It's this bastard, right?
Doesn't he look kind of like me?
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Huh?
What?
Hey, buddy.
You want to come over here?
Please call the police.
Yes. Hello?
Is this Ms. Han Hae Na of Garam High School?
Yes, this is she.
This is Hyeonseo Police Station.
Yes, I see.
You're Choi Yul's homeroom teacher, correct?
Police Station?
What do we do with this?
Gosh, seriously.
I told you to call your parents.
Why won't you answer?
You should answer when an adult is talking to you.
Don't you have parents? Are you an orphan?
Ma'am. Ma'am. Please calm down.
Apparently, your son and his friends started it first.
You should be apologizing to him.
I didn't hit him. I just dodged the punches.
He fell on his own because he tripped.
Stop lying.
My baby. What do we do with your face?
Baby?
Gosh, you're embarrassing me. That's enough, Mom!
You'd better stay put.
Hey...
where are your parents?
Where are they?
I don't have them.
See?
The ones who weren't disciplined at home always stick out.
You beat people up because you weren't taught at home.
Excuse me.
You're being too harsh.
Ms. Han.
You're a young female teacher, and you can't seem to discipline the kids.
You'd better teach them well.
Don't cause harm to other kids.
I know. I guess he thought I was easy because I'm a young female teacher.
I was threatened by him this morning.
It's a civil offense, and I can bring criminal charges, right, Officer?
Yes, that's correct.
I caught your son smoking this morning.
I think that's why he took revenge on my student.
If you find it so unfair,
should we settle through the school violence committee?
School violence committee, my foot.
Is there any evidence? Is there?
Excuse me for a second.
He still has what he smoked this morning.
Kids can do stuff like that.
They should not.
And it's the teachers' and...
parents' job to teach them that.
How could you do that, punk?
Why did you hit me?
- Thank you.
You didn't get hurt, right?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
It's okay.
I feel bad that you got dragged into this because of me this morning.
But why didn't you call your parents?
Were you afraid you'd get scolded?
Well, it's because I really can't reach them.
They live in Australia.
Why didn't you tell me?
You should've told me during our counseling session.
Well, I don't know...
Do you live alone, then?
No, I live with a relative.
Why didn't you call them, then?
I'm sure he'd flip out.
He'd make a big deal out of nothing.
But you still should've.
Next time.
How do you get home from here? I'll drop you off.
The buses must've stopped running.
Gosh, when did it get so late?
I'm so sorry, but you can go on your own, right?
I forgot I have something to do at home.
I'll get going now. Bye.
Ms. Han.
D-D-Don't come.
Don't come.
Bye.
Pick it up.
Hello? Oppa, I'm in trouble right now.
Ms. Han, what's going on?
I'm sorry.
Your phone... What do we do?
I'll take it out real quick.
No, it's okay. I threw it away on purpose. I was going to.
You were talking on the phone just now. I'll take it out real quick.
I'm really okay. I never liked this phone.
I was going to get a new one. What a relief.
But if you throw it away here like this-
No, it's okay.
You should go home now.
Bye.
It looks fine, though.
See you.
Why won't she say anything?
Your sister is totally drunk.
Come pick her up, please!
Gosh, what's wrong with you?
It's midnight... Why are you so heavy?
- Gotta go. Gotta go.
- Go home. Hurry up and go home.
No, no. She's a friend.
Why are you still here?
Ms. Han, I got your phone.
W-What time is it?
It's 12.
Dog... Ms. Han...
Gosh, I wanted her to take her sister. Why won't she...
Gosh, it's past 12.
I don't want to kiss.
But my lips are sticking out.
Did you eat pickled garlic?
Yul, wake up.
Wake up.
Are you awake?
Let's run away for now.
It's a dog.
Ms. Han is a dog?
Hold on!
Ms. Han, hold on.
Hold on, Ms. Han.
I caught you.
These damn stubby legs.
It's definitely a dog.
She's a dog.
How could a person turn into a dog?
No, I was mistaken.
Yes, you were mistaken.
No.
She definitely changed in front of me.
Is this really Ms. Han, then?
Is it you?
No.
No. This makes no sense.
This is just a dog. It's not her.
Yes, I'm a dog. Ruff ruff.
So please just let me go.
What do I do?
Do I have to go to the police station?
No, they'll think I'm crazy.
Should I call 911?
A hospital?
A lab?
Ms. Han, what do I do?
Say something.
You can just let me go.
What a well-behaved dog.
Yes.
It knows how to open the window.
Hold on a second, Ma'am.
Just wait a moment.
How do I get out of here?
She's still at my place.
I should get her some tea...
Do dogs drink tea?
Won't you have any?
I don't want it.
Ma'am, do you live alone?
Your family must be worried.
Should I call them for you?
I brought all of your stuff.
Your clothes, purse,
and your phone.
It's locked.
I-It unlocked.
M-Ms. Han.
I-It's really you.
Ms. Han.
How did you turn into a dog?
What if you could never go back to normal?
Say something. Please?
Ms. Han!
Hello?
W-Why is a man answering?
Ms. Han.
Is she asleep?
She's so cute.
There's a puppy on my bed.
A photo.
No. This is Ms. Han.
It's illegal to take one without permission.
But it's just one photo.
It's such a cute dog,
but this is Ms. Han.
She must be tired.
Pretend to be sleeping
and get out of here when Yul falls asleep.
What?
Is he asleep?
My gosh...
What do I do?
Okay. Nice.
My best trait is that
I give up quickly.
I'll wait until it's six in the morning
and leave when I turn into a human.
Never, ever fall asleep.
Never fall asleep...
Who's that?
​
Ms. Han?
Is this a dream?
♫  Please don't pretend not to know  ♫
♫  I know exactly how you feel  ♫
♫  Even if you act like you don't, don't, don't, don't, don't care  ♫
♫  It's so obvious  ♫
♫  Don't play ignorant, our love won't die  ♫
♫  Stop acting cautious, tell me everything  ♫
♫  No matter what other say  ♫
♫  Why does it matter?  ♫
♫  You're too shy, too shy  ♫
♫  Let's not waste time anymore  ♫
You got caught?
By a student of yours?
Not only that, he's the math teacher's nephew.
What's with the dog?
Man Deuk will hang out here just for a day.
Huh? Man Deuk went home?
Ms. Han, are you free this evening?
Didn't you say you haven't graded the performance assessment yet?
Did you wait for a long time?
Thank you for today.
I know you helped me in many ways.
What's with those two?
Are you saying there's nothing going on?
You have no feelings at all?