​
Our family has an unusual secret.
I think someone once said, "There are no bad dogs in the world."
Unni.
I won't be able to kiss now?
Only...
bad curses exist.
Hae Na!
Hae Na! Hae Na, come on!
Hurry up!
We're here!
Ta-da!
Hae Na, happy one-year anniversary.
- I'm so jealous!
- Thank you, Oppa.
Hey, you even passed the certification exam. You should just live together.
Oh, my!
The cake is shaped like lips.
- Congratulations!
- Congrats.
We're probably the only couple to have the first kiss on their one-year anniversary.
What?
Did he say, "Kiss"?
Gosh! What do I do?
This one's going to be tough to get out of.
What the heck?
Oppa, I'm sorry!
Once again, this is how my relationship ended.
- Hello.
- Ms. Hae Na!
Oh, hi.
Daebak!
Jun Woo sunbae's getting married!
Hey, Hae Na's in this chat, too.
-  I know.
Hae Na, you're okay, right?
- I'm okay-
- Why wouldn't she be okay?
Hae Na, I'm really worried about you.
Will you grow old and die alone?
What can she do about her extremely high standards?
- That's not the-
- Anyway, who's the bride?
The bride looks familiar.
Who wants to drink tonight?
Sorry, I'm watching a movie with Oppa tonight.
It's my one-year anniversary today! This is what I'm getting.
Sorry, I also have plans today.
These traitors.
Hey, kids!
Hello.
- Hello.
- Good morning, Mr. Bo Gyeom.
He's so handsome.
Hey, girls.
Here.
Today's our first day, then.
Today's the 24th.
What? You want a calendar?
Out!
Hello.
Guys, do you see this?
My love for you guys is starting to crack...
down the middle.
Good job.
Not everyone has applied for the duties on the list back there.
Phone collector, waste sorter, and blackboard manager. There are still many open spots.
I'm trying to make your school records look even the slightest bit prettier,
so diligently apply for a duty while I tell you nicely.
- Okay.
- Okay!
Ms. Hae Na,
shouldn't you make yourself pretty, not just our school records?
This is me dressed up pretty.
I mean, C.C.K. You'll stop C.C.K.-ing once you start dating.
What's C.C.K.?
"Cutting off couples who kiss."
Ms. Hae Na, seriously, what's wrong with you?
Hey!
Is it because you're envious?
Envy is ignorance, Ms. Hae Na.
Ms. Hae Na, hang in there.
Hey, come on.
Fighting!
All right, I'm taking attendance.
- Min Ah.
- Here.
- Soo Jin.
Hey, C.C.K.
Can you not call me that?
So, why did you go around cutting off couples who kiss?
You should've just passed them by.
It's reprehensible. They're at school doing something I haven't even done yet.
- Reprehensible, or are you just envious?
- Huh?
You said so before. "Yes to dating. No to kissing."
But you got dumped right away when you tell the guys about "no kissing."
I can truly do anything for them except kiss them.
That's weirder.
If kissing isn't allowed, everything shouldn't be allowed. Why is only kissing off-limits?
Don't tell me you've really never done it before.
Really?
Do you have some kind of illness?
I guess you can say...
Uncle, I got 100!
It is an illness.
What?
Geez, what is it?
Gosh, I don't know- Oh, my.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Are your hands okay-
That jerk.
Why do you hate Mr. Jin so much?
He's a bit blunt, but he's handsome.
And he's popular with the students.
It's not that I don't like him. He doesn't like me.
Why?
Hey, give it back!
Daebak!
- Whoa.
- Wow.
Hello, ladies.
Hello, Mr. Bo Gyeom.
Oh, we're all going to get together later
and have a drink. You'll be there, right?
Of course, we'll be there.
- Okay.
- You said you have plans-
Of course, we'll be there. It's not often that we meet.
That's good to hear.
We're going to eat meat, so have a light lunch. Okay?
Gosh, he's so sweet.
I come to work for Mr. Bo Gyeom.
Good for you. At least you have a reason to come to work.
When will they get here?
They'll be here soon.
Hello, ladies.
Gosh, he's handsome.
Ms. Yoon Chae Ah isn't here?
Oh, she told us to go first because something came up.
You're hungry, right? Let's go.
As if. She's probably busy doing her full makeup.
Oh, my.
Oh, my gosh! This is heaven. They're so pretty.
Why are they all here?
So cute.
Do you also like dogs?
Of course. They're so cute, right?
You're cuter.
That's right.
Let's get going.
Let's just watch them for a bit.
Whoa, they're so cute!
Earlier, that was the hand-
I'll go on ahead.
Gosh, that jerk.
They're all cooked.
You guys did a good job being handsome today.
Eat up.
I'm a bit late, aren't I?
This looks delicious.
Calm down. You're sensitive because you're hungry.
Why is everyone holding back on the alcohol?
Oh, here.
We, younger teachers, should meet often
and have dinner and go on trips, too.
That sounds great!
Staying at home after work gets lonely. Right?
I'm not lonely.
Oh! Mr. Jin, you're more like the chic cat type, huh?
This is my baby. He looks like you, right?
This is your cat?
It's so pretty!
You must like cats, too.
Yes, I guess. But I like dogs more.
That's because dogs are just really kind. Right?
Like him.
Goochie goochie goo. You're so kind.
Don't you think?
One, two!
Whoa!
That was so cool!
Hold on.
I'm going to use the restroom.
- She's so cool!
- So cool!
Ms. Chae Ah is so cool!
Daebak! Jun Woo sunbae's bride is Doo Na!
Your best friend is marrying your first love.
These jerks.
Ms. Hae Na, is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Mr. Bo Gyeom, you don't have a girlfriend, do you?
Do you think I do or not?
If I had a girlfriend, I'd be on a date right now.
I'm the type to go all-in on my girlfriend.
Then what's your ideal type?
I don't really have an ideal type.
But still. You must be attracted to something.
I just...
like someone who likes me.
I hate that pre-dating flirting phase.
I appreciate it when they tell me first, "I like you."
"Do you want to date me?"
- I'm going to get this call.
- Sure.
Hey, Seo Won! It's cold outside. Wear this.
He hates complicated things.
Just simply go!
Go?
Ms. Hae Na?
Guess what I like more than dogs.
It's you.
Really?
So...
tell me first.
Go.
Mr. Bo Gyeom.
Mr. Lee.
Ms. Han!
Yes, it's me.
Are you okay? You seem really drunk.
No, no. I'm not drunk at all.
I came to tell you something.
You said so before. That you...
appreciate simple things.
Which is why you like women who like you. And that...
you'd like...for them to be honest with you.
So what I want to tell you is...
I like you, Mr. Bo Gyeom.
That's right.
If it's Mr. Bo Gyeom, he'll accept a woman like me, too.
Ms. Hae Na.
Whoa! Mr. Bo Gyeom can even talk while he kisses.
Whoa!
Are you okay?
Mr. Jin, what are you doing here?
Sorry?
Your lips...
Why are you wearing this coat?
Whoa!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Ms. Han. Ms. Han! Ms. Hae Na!
Hey! Your bag!
Where's Ms. Hae Na going?
Oh, well...
Her family must be strict. Something about a curfew?
Doesn't she live with just her older sister?
I only have one minute left.
If I kiss a man,
I turn into a dog.
Because of that damned curse.
Shit!
What do I do?
Hae Na, aren't I handsome today?
No.
- I'm more handsome than your dad, right?
- No.
You rascal.
I'll be back.
Okay, see you later.
My uncle was fine when he left in the morning...
Uncle! I got 100!
returned as a dog.
What's with this mutt?
It's not a mutt. It's my uncle.
His name is Uncle? Uncle, give me your paw.
Don't touch my uncle. He's really my uncle.
No way. Stop bluffing.
She's not. Our mom said our family turns into dogs when we kiss someone.
Then you'll turn into a dog if you kiss someone, too?
Yeah.
I'll believe you if you show me.
What the heck?
You haven't changed!
I'll change after one minute.
Mom! It's not working!
What's not working?
I kissed him, but I haven't changed!
What?
♫  Going home with, but instead of me  ♫
♫  Unless I forget myself, it feels complete  ♫
♫  Inside my head, I remain the same  ♫
♫  If you'd still love me, too  ♫
♫  Going home with, but instead of me  ♫
♫  Unless I forget myself, it feels complete  ♫
♫  Inside my head, I remain the same  ♫
♫  If you'd still love me, too  ♫
♫  So, here I am...  ♫
This is Hyunseo Station. This is the last train from Hyunseo Station.
♫  We'll embark on the love still  ♫
♫  Now, I'm going home  ♫
♫  You're by my side, now I'm going home  ♫
♫  Going home  ♫
♫  My heart remains true, now I am going home  ♫
♫  Still I hear you  ♫
When we come across a dog without its owner,
we go through a confirmation process.
Zero...
Seven...
Han Yoo Na?
You just left like that last time. And now...
Who was it this time?
Which bastard did you kiss this time, Han Yoo Na?
- What about me?
- Geez, you scared me!
You...
y-you're not...
Who's this?
This is Hae Na's shoe.
You're Han Hae Na?
Han Hae Na, what will you do?
- What will you do?
- What's going on?
What the hell? What happened?
What is she saying?
She has to talk, so I understand! She's barking right now.
What do I do now? What do I do?
All right, so be quiet!
She'll be naked when she wakes up tomorrow.
When will she turn back into a human?
Six in the morning.
And she'll turn into a dog again at midnight.
For how long?
For 100 days.
If she can't undo the curse by then, she'll live the rest of her life as a dog.
Like your uncle?
She's still able to sleep in her situation?
You've never turned into a dog, have you?
Of course not.
It's exhausting.
You're a tenth of your normal size, but the world is the same.
The world is 10 times bigger.
I guess your food expenses are reduced by a tenth, too.
That must be nice.
I mean, she can just undo the curse like you did back then.
You think that's easy?
Gosh, why did your family have to be cursed like this?
If your children have a lover and they kiss,
their appearance will turn into something that is not human.
They must be able to prove their outstanding love
in order to change back into a human.
My curse will pass down to generations, and they will not escape the cycle!
Are you okay?
What is it?
What? What, what?
Resignation?
Are you crazy?
I can't go to school. I'd rather die than go to school.
Why? What is it? Go on and tell me the details.
I must've been possessed. I was sure it was Mr. Bo Gyeom.
What are you saying?
Unni.
Yeah, I must've been possessed. Yeah, I must've been possessed, Unni.
I was possessed.
- I must've been possessed.
- I'm scared.
So, you thought you came onto the sweet Korean history teacher,
but it was that jerk of a math teacher?
Because they switched clothes?
Hey, how'd you pass the teacher certification exam?
These problems don't come out on the exam!
What do you think? Does it look like I'm atoning?
Are you going to a funeral?
Gosh, why did it have to be Mr. Jin, of all people?
I'm the most awkward with him at school.
- Whatever the case, you got your wish.
- What?
Your first kiss at 28 years old.
- Congrats.
- That wasn't a kiss.
It was just a collision between lips.
No, no.
Rather than a collision, wouldn't it be sexual assault?
Physical contact without the other party's consent.
I'm trash.
Whatever, just get to school.
Mr. Jin is at school.
Hey, get it together.
If you can't undo the curse, you know you'll turn into a dog every night, right?
Gosh, seriously!
Hey, put this on your face and-
What are you doing? Hey, get out of there.
- I'm not going to school.
- Go to school!
No, I won't!
This wench! Go to school!
Hello.
Good morning.
I have...your bag.
I'm going to homeroom now.
Have a good one.
Thanks.
Ms. Yoon.
- Yes?
- One moment, please.
Did you get home okay last night?
Yes.
- About last night...
- Oh, yes.
It's a secret.
People make mistakes when they're drunk.
Yes.
It was truly a mistake.
Not an ounce of emotion involved.
It was truly, really just a pure mistake.
That's right.
But it was totally a kiss-
Okay, okay. I'll stop.
Seo Won told me...not to say a thing about it.
- Really?
- Yes.
Seo Won may be a little blunt, but he's a decent guy.
Huh.
Anyhow, I think you should apologize to Seo Won properly.
It looks like he was really shocked.
Yes, I should.
Of course, I should.
I want to preserve this sight.
How is he so handsome?
You started out right, but
I think it went wrong from here.
Look closely.
All right. You get it, right?
- Yes.
- Yes!
- Hey, did you see Mr. Seo Won's face?
- Of course!
Gosh, I think he's getting more handsome by the day!
Just when I think he can't get more handsome, he becomes more handsome the next day!
- He looks the same every day.
- And he's Garam High School's brain.
- I'm sure he's better than most top tutors.
- Totally.
He's popular among the kids and close to Mr. Bo Gyeom.
But why is he only like that to me?
Are your hands okay-
Your house is in the same direction as Ms. Hae Na's, so you can go together.
I feel uncomfortable with her.
Huh? Why uncomfortable?
I avoided him because he finds me uncomfortable,
but why did it have to be him?
I'm sorry.
Even when I think about it in your shoes, I really...
Anyhow, thank you so much for keeping it a secret.
Honestly, I didn't know you were this generous.
Are you sure you're sorry?
I'm sorry. It was really a mistake.
I know.
You mistook me for Mr. Lee Bo Gyeom.
Oh! How did you know?
It was impossible not to know in that situation.
So why were you wearing Mr. Lee Bo Gyeom's jacket?
Was that a question?
I'm sorry.
Nonetheless, it's okay.
It's not like you committed a grave sin.
Let's just say it never happened.
Thank you, thank you.
Let's forget about it.
Excuse me, Mr. Jin!
Do you happen to like dogs?
The solution to undo this damned curse.
Woo Taek,
it's all right.
It's kissing the other person again as a dog.
Yoo Na!
I must kiss this man again today but as a dog this time.
Why are you asking me that all of a sudden?
I mean, it's because I like dogs, so I was wondering if you also like dogs.
But why are you getting annoyed with me?
When did I?
Right now.
Not at all.
M-Mr. Jin!
I'll buy you a meal as an apology.
Sorry?
Hey!
Isn't that our homeroom teacher?
Why is our homeroom teacher...
She must have something to tell him.
Please let me buy.
- It's okay.
- Gosh,
I'd feel really uncomfortable if I didn't.
There's no need to feel uncomfortable.
No, it's...
My sense of guilt and my conscience...
They hurt too much.
I'm sorry.
Why did she ask about dogs all of a sudden?
Mr. Jin!
Mr. Jin?
Are you dating my homeroom teacher?
What?
I'm asking because I saw you talking to her lovingly over there earlier.
Did that look loving?
Well, sort of?
Please throw this out for me!
Hey-
Hey!
Was she talking about crabs, not dogs*?
(Dogs and crabs sound similar in Korean.)
Easy.
What a good boy.
- Be gentle.
- It's okay, it's okay.
A little further in.
Dong Cheol...
Let's go home together. Let's go to Noona's house, okay?
What should I do? I'm so sad...
It's okay.
BUN, creatinine... all kidney levels are bad.
I think dialysis is needed,
but he's too old to get surgery for his brain tumor.
How much longer...will Uncle be able to live?
Don't worry too much.
They do live six more months after getting told one month.
That's why you need to undo your curse quickly.
Didn't you see Mom crying her eyes out earlier?
Ask that guy out to dinner and make him drink alcohol until midnight.
When he's all drunk and confused, kiss him in your dog form, and that's it.
Gosh. It's easier said than done.
Ask him out first, for now.
We'll also come since you need to cover up if you fail.
Yes, you do need to cover up.
"We"?
Woo Taek,
you know what?
After my curse was undone and when I feel sad or disappointed,
I get this urge to bite.
Do you want to get bitten?
I-I got you.
I'm going inside first.
Okay.
Good night.
Don't worry too much.
She'll undo the curse soon.
Woo Taek.
You should... do something with me...
Hey, did you discuss this with her?
Even if you're family, doesn't she have the right to privacy?
Go turn her face a little to the left.
Gosh, I'm sure she'll get mad.
This will be a good memory once her curse is undone.
Okay.
My!
Isn't Hae Na so cute? Look at this.
Even if you're family, this is- Whoa, she is cute, though.
Right, right?
I'm naturally terrible at flattering someone.
Hello.
What are you doing right now?
Oh, my! There was so much dust on your desk.
It's not good for your lungs, right?
I was just worried about your health.
I'll take care of my health.
Of course, you should.
Are you eating properly, by the way?
Should I buy you some meat? Meat with a shot of soju.
Gosh, we really don't click.
I still need to try.
Don't you hear your dry hands screaming?
Sorry?
When it's dry, wouldn't your life be better with a glass of moist alcohol?
I don't like humidity.
You must hate the rainy season.
So, shall we make plans to prepare for the upcoming rainy season?
With some beef intestines and soju, yeah?
Class dismissed.
Thank you!
The kids just don't listen, do they?
When you're stressed, pig feet and soju are the best.
Gosh, you're picking at your food so much.
When you don't have an appetite, have chicken feet with soju.
Dang it!
Why are you in a bad mood this time?
This evening works for me.
My goodness.
Operation launches this evening.
Whoa, finally.
Mr. Song Woo Taek, today's the day.
Excuse me, two bottles of soju for us, please.
Please give me the lukewarm ones, not the cold ones.
- I won't be drinking alcohol.
- Sorry?
How can you not drink soju with spicy stir-fried chicken? That's the unwritten law.
- I still don't-
- Still,
you should abide by the unwritten law since it's still a law.
I'll just have a glass of beer, then.
Excuse me! Please give us a bottle of beer
in addition to the soju.
Beer tastes smoother when mixed.
I know the killer ratio for somaek*. Should I show you one?
(Soju and beer.)
I'm fine.
I get drunk too quickly when I drink soju.
I'll take this call.
Oh, okay! You can go ahead. Hurry!
Get him totally plastered.
So he won't even realize if it's a dream or not
when a dog he just kissed becomes human.
You got it?
Even that bastard who said he loved me thousands of times
treated me like a monster when I became a dog in front of his eyes.
Worse off, you've got an awkward and uncomfortable coworker.
Make sure no one catches you.
More, more, more.
More!
Cheers.
Sure.
I'm getting so drunk.
Gosh, why are we leaving this early when she turns at midnight?
You have nothing to do anyway.
Get a girlfriend or something if you don't want to do this.
Y-You think I can't get a girlfriend, huh?
Well...
I kind of know why you insisted on wanting to see me tonight.
Sorry?
Since I'm close to Bo Gyeom,
you want me to connect you both, isn't it?
Oh, you're right. That's right. The connection.
But I don't know if I could help you because I'm very clumsy at this.
Come on, what's there to be clumsy about?
You just need to be there in that place.
If you'll just stay there in your spot,
I won't think twice and go to him with your help.
By the way...
why do you hate me, Mr. Jin?
Why would I hate you, Ms. Han?
Exactly! Why do you hate me?
What did I ever do to you?
But I never hated you.
Whoa! You make me laugh.
I've got an upset note in my heart, okay? I remember everything.
During fifth period's free period on April 20th, last year,
when the teachers chipped in to buy snacks.
Whoa, gosh.
We didn't buy soondae.
Whoa, you disappeared in a split second.
Did you use an invisible cape or something?
- Do you remember or not?
- I remember.
And also, on Ms. Song's birthday last year,
when we went to buy the cake together.
They say the mango flavor tastes good,
but Ms. Song likes matcha flavor.
But that one looks tasty, too.
What should we do?
Do you remember or not?
I remember.
See?
I mean, why on Earth do you hate me?
Why do you find me uncomfortable?
When I'm with you, it's really-
I have my reasons.
So, tell me about those reasons.
Anyhow, it's true I avoided you because I was a bit uncomfortable,
but it wasn't because I hate you.
I'm sorry if I made you misunderstand.
Wait, what's that supposed to...
And...I think I also misunderstood.
I also like them.
Like what?
Crabs*.
(Sounds similar to dogs in Korean)
Oh, really?
They taste good.
Sorry?
They taste good steamed and also
taste great stewed.
Is he picking a fight with me right now?
Do they have a stew here?
Five minutes left. Hurry up and come out!
Whoa! M-Mr. Jin, please excuse me for one moment. Sorry.
Where are you-
Yes, Mr. Jin! I'm at the alley right outside.
Can you come outside for a minute?
There's a really cute...
Boss, one bottle of soju, please.
What?
What the heck?
Do I need to call Bo Gyeom or something?
Calling Bo Gyeom.
What?
My goodness.
Gosh, I really can't get used to this alt character.
This sorrowful doggy life.
I'll get over with this soon.
Ms. Han?
Ms. Han!
Hi.
Hey, you're cute.
♫  Whatever I say, it's for you  ♫
♫  Learning all the lessons I taught you  ♫
♫  Whatever the language, I don't mind  ♫
♫  Million words I need to describe it  ♫
♫  Ooh, there are blue moons in the sky  ♫
♫  And the stars light the eternal light  ♫
♫  Ooh, the waves are crashing in  ♫
And it'll be game over.
Ms. Han!
What?  Dogs* taste good?
(Sounds similar to crabs in Korean)
What a jerk. I'm done with you once the curse is lifted.
What in the world...
I'm cute, right? You know I'm cute.
Great. Now, to put things to an end.
Huh?
Don't come.
What's wrong with him?
Did he see a ghost?
There's nothing there.
Don't tell me. He's not afraid of ghosts,
but afraid of dogs?
No way, right?
It can't be. No way.
​
He is.
It really was me!
Gosh!
I'm totally doomed!
All right, attention.
It won't come out on the test, but we'll do a review.
Number one.
You turn into a dog within one minute after kissing the opposite sex.
Number two.
You become a dog from midnight to six in the morning every day.
Number three.
If 100 days pass before you undo the curse,
you live as a dog for the rest of your life.
Lastly, number four. The most important one.
How can you lift the curse, then?
Yes, that's right. Number four!
You need to kiss the same person you kissed again as a dog.
All right, everyone got it now, right?
Any student with a question, please post it on the bulletin board
and that's it for today's class.
♫  Please don't pretend not to know  ♫
♫  I know how you feel  ♫
♫  Even if you act like you're nonchalant  ♫
♫  You make it obvious  ♫
♫  Don't act like you don't know, it's love  ♫
♫  Don't walk on eggshells, tell me everything  ♫
♫  Who cares what other people say  ♫
♫  What does it matter?  ♫
♫  You're too shy  ♫
♫  Too shy  ♫
♫  Let's not waste any more time  ♫
I heard Ms. Hae Na suddenly disappeared last night.
- Did something happen?
- Did she see?
Like hell, you'll take care of it.
You kiss him by mistake,
make him go out to dinner with you to apologize and run off without even paying.
From Mr. Jin's perspective, you're...
Dine and dash. Yes, you're a dine and dasher.
Since you agreed to help, can we meet regularly, and can you give me some good tips?
Regularly?
- Is this Ms. Han Hae Na from Garam High School?
-  Ms. Han!
The buses probably stopped running.
Hello? I'm in big trouble right now-
Whoa, you dog...
Just one glass of beer, please?
Don't you even hear what I'm saying?
How many times do I have to say no?
I have been very clingy lately.
I'm sure he thought of me as a leech.
Ms. Han, you see...
♫  Take care of your image  ♫