(Cha Eun Woo, Park Gyu Young)
(Lee Hyun Woo)
(A Good Day To Be A Dog)
(Production sponsors)
(Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, KOCCA)
(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(All animals were filmed under expert supervision.)
She's a returning student who's three years older than us.
She became a shaman just a month ago.
I hear she is right on the nose about things.
Do you have no intention of becoming friendly with Cocoa?
You have to stay on your toes.
Don't get caught by anyone.
This time, things may work out between those two.
I think she changed her night watch time so they could be partners.
It's a swallow.
A welcome guest or a reunion.
Hey, how come the girls aren't here?
That's what I saw after I was done with my shower.
You couldn't find them, right?
I couldn't. This is bad.
It'll be midnight soon.
- Are you unwell? - I need to go number two.
Don't follow me.
Hey. You girls are from Garam High School, right?
Stop right there! Nice.
This is where she transformed.
Where did she go?
Who is that old lady?
Ms. Han!
Ms. Han hasn't come back yet?
Where is she?
What's going on right now?
If you can hear me, say something.
Please wait there. I'll make sure to get you out of there.
- Help! - Ms. Han!
Grab my hand.
Two, three.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
You were lucky. I was worried.
Mr. Jin.
I don't have feelings for him anymore.
My lord.
Han Yu Na's sister. This is interesting.
I wonder if he knows...
his girlfriend is a monster.
Gosh, are there any fun stories to cover?
"This Woman Turns into a Dog Every Night?"
(This Woman Turns into a Dog Every Night)
(The whole family is cursed.)
(So my ex's sister also turns into a dog when she's kissed.)
He sure wasted his time, writing this detailed post about nonsense.
This crazy jerk.
I think I recognize him.
Who is he?
Isn't this Jin Seo Won?
You know what? I never liked you the moment I saw your face.
She turns into a dog...
Wait. She's the woman?
(Episode 7)
I don't have feelings for him anymore.
It just happened that way.
That's it.
Guys, your class is starting.
Get back inside.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Ms. Han. - Mr. Jin.
- You can go first. - You can go first.
Did you rest up?
Yes. Thanks to you.
What about you?
- Me too. - Hey.
You should already be in class.
Get back inside.
I should get to my class now.
Mr. Jin, shouldn't you be in class?
I'm on my way.
I'm working as a journalist now.
I'd like to cover your story on my channel.
Please write back.
(Name of my channel: Mystery Hwani)
(Inbox, Hwani)
(Mystery Hwani)
(Modern Cinderella, How Actress Enters Pyeongchang-dong)
This is Hwani from Mystery Hwani.
I would like to reveal a shocking personal life...
of an actress who's beloved for her pure and innocent image.
What about my mom?
Yu Na went out with her.
She couldn't eat anything all day.
I told you not to play with my uncle's face like that.
Your uncle loves this.
- Right? - Uncle.
Don't wag your tail.
Is he okay?
There was blood in his stool because of pancreatitis.
He has been low on energy for the past few days.
But he's doing a lot better after getting the IV fluids.
So don't worry.
He doesn't have much time left, right?
Time flows differently for humans and dogs.
I'll go out and clean up the shop.
Hae Na.
You know that you need to break the curse soon, right?
Uncle, you can't get sick this often.
You're worrying Mom.
Uncle.
I think I finally understand how you must have felt then...
and how tough this must have been for you.
My feelings right now are precious that I want to protect them.
But to do that,
I need to tell him the truth.
I'm really scared.
What should I do, Uncle?
He and I have finally gotten close now.
We had a heart-to-heart talk.
We joked around too.
Will I be able to tell him the truth?
Yes.
I will talk to him for 30 minutes...
and show him my transformation.
Okay. I'll make sure to tell him today.
(Mr. Jin Seo Won)
Seo Won.
Do you still live here?
I have no interest in catching up with you.
Is that so?
I'm here as your friend because I'm worried about you.
- I got nothing to discuss with you. - Hey.
Are you still upset about what happened in the past?
Are you that petty?
Right. I saw your picture online.
Your girlfriend is super gorgeous.
What?
I heard what you've been doing with your life.
You create trashy videos.
Are you not busy?
You must have a lot of time on your hands.
Look at this punk. You grew up a lot.
I had always been taller than you.
Why don't you live a proper life now?
You're a grown-up too.
Gosh. The residents might file a noise complaint.
How does it feel to hear that after such a long time?
Does it jog your memory?
Hey. You know what this is, right?
(The guy next to her seemed like her boyfriend.)
You're doing well now. You got a girlfriend.
Now that you have a girlfriend,
things must get rowdy with you two like some horny dogs.
It's like that, isn't it?
Stop this nonsense, and leave.
Fine. I should do what you say.
See you around, my friend.
Darn it.
What is this?
(Mr. Jin Seo Won)
Hello, Mr. Jin.
I fell asleep early last night. So I missed your call.
It's fine. Did you get home safely last night?
I saw you leave in a hurry.
Pardon?
When you got off work.
I was wondering if you got home safely.
Gosh, of course. I got home safely.
Have a nice weekend then. I'll see you around.
Hey, are you sure it was here?
Did someone take my clothes overnight?
I made sure I hid them.
Gosh. They were one of my favourite outfits.
They were my clothes.
Exactly. I wanted to come back last night to find the clothes.
But you went clubbing, so I couldn't.
Come on.
What is it?
- It's Mom. - What about her?
- She's at our house. - Why?
Well, remember?
When you kissed Math, you didn't turn back because he was asleep.
So I asked Mom why it was like that.
Then she asked me who was under the curse and got suspicious.
- What do we do? - Let's go home.
- This way. Let's go. - We must go home. Let's hurry.
Mom.
Gosh. You should have called if you were coming over.
Where have you two been in the morning?
- We went out for a walk. - Yes.
We love going out for a walk in the morning.
- Right. - I feel so refreshed.
What?
So you didn't go back to retrieve...
your clothes on the street from last night?
- What? What are you talking about? - No.
Spill it. Which one of you is it?
- What do you mean? - What? Which one of us?
So you're not going to talk.
Fine. Then I can wait here until midnight.
- Mom. - Mom.
You!
Who is it? Did you get a boyfriend? When did it happen?
No, Mom. I don't have a boyfriend.
I'm so tired. I'll go inside and get some sleep.
- Gosh. - Who is it?
- Just tell me. - No, Mom. You got it wrong.
Who is it? Tell me.
- Who is it? Just tell me. - No, Mom.
Who is it?
I knew it.
- Mom. - You know who it is, right?
- Who is it? - No. I don't know him.
Bring him home tomorrow.
Bring whom?
Who do you think? Her boyfriend!
What?
She kissed a guy who wasn't her boyfriend yet?
No! Of course, he's her boyfriend.
I have so many questions for him.
Tell him to come here tomorrow. Got it?
- What's this? - What?
Is this a celebratory party for my first kiss? Or...
is it my last meal?
Hey, try this.
How is it? The seasoning is perfect, right?
What on earth are you thinking?
Don't worry. I already handled it.
Yul.
Ms. Han.
How did you know where I lived?
What's up with the suit?
Gosh. You're here, my future brother-in-law!
"Future brother-in-law?" Hey, go back home now.
- This is a huge mistake. - Gosh.
- Mom! - Wait, Yul.
My future brother-in-law is here!
- No! - He's here.
Wait. I...
Welcome.
Welcome. Come inside.
This way.
Hello, Mother.
It's nice to meet you.
Welcome.
Right. Here.
You didn't have to.
Gosh. No way! He got your favourite!
Seriously. This is crazy.
How thoughtful you are.
- Thank you. - Sure.
Come inside.
Have you gone mad? You've really lost it.
What choice did I have?
Have you gone mad?
I'll be arrested. He's a minor.
He's not your real boyfriend. He's just acting as one.
But still!
What? Why is he sitting at the table?
Come. Let's eat.
I wonder if the food is to your liking.
This is very good, Mother.
School lunches...
"School lunches?"
He works at a company that provides school lunches.
You must be sick of school lunches...
since you eat that all the time. Right?
Yes. That tends to happen.
A company that provides school lunches?
What exactly is your position in that company?
Mom, it's not good manners to ask such personal questions now.
Gosh. She's so nosy.
Well,
your name is Yul, correct?
Yes. That's right.
How old are you?
Okay.
Didn't you say...
you were born in the Year of the Dog?
Yes.
- In the Year of the Dog? - Yes.
- He's the same age as you? - Yes, we're the same age.
You're 30?
Yes.
Gosh. You don't look like you're 30.
You look so much younger than your age.
- Seriously. - Gosh.
Right.
He looks ten years younger than you.
Everyone, would you believe me if I told you there was a line...
that made girls say yes when you ask them out?
You're too afraid to ask them out?
Then your dating life will go nowhere.
Single people with zero activities will get nowhere.
We're supposed to make our own chances.
You talk about the weather a lot when you go on dates, right?
Open the conversation by talking about the weather.
"The weather is great."
Then the girl next to you will be thinking this.
"Gosh. Come on."
Then say this line when they least expect it.
Sit comfortably.
Okay.
How did you meet my daughter?
- We met at school. - At school.
Well, his company provides school lunches.
- That's how... - Okay. Be quiet.
How long have you known her?
We met at the beginning of the school term.
You're dating her even when you know everything about her, right?
Yes.
What do you think about people turning into dogs?
It's super fascinating.
And she's so cute.
I'm not weird out by that. I'm really fine with that.
I'm sorry to bring you here at the last minute...
and ask you so many questions.
It's okay.
As her parent, I'm bound to worry for her.
On top of that, my girls are very different from other girls.
Well, when things are going well, you will be happy together.
But if things were to go south between you two...
and you have a bad breakup,
there are so many things we have to worry about.
Actually, it's beyond worrying.
I'm afraid that...
their ex-boyfriends might expose my girls' secret to other people...
or that they might show up...
and pick on my girls when my girls have finally met someone great.
Love life is a complicated and difficult matter to handle.
So it feels like...
I've given my girls such a big disability to deal with.
So...
even if you say that you're completely fine with this,
we'll have a hard time accepting...
or trusting you.
I understand.
But...
I only told you that because it really didn't bother me.
That's how I truly feel.
It's fascinating that people can turn into dogs.
But I don't think it's weird.
Actually, it's the opposite.
I don't want Hae Na to feel insecure about this.
A while ago,
she said no man could possibly like her...
because of who she was.
But I completely disagree.
She has a warm heart.
She's funny and cute.
She certainly deserves to be loved.
I guess you love Hae Na very much.
"Love?"
My heart suddenly feels...
Are you all right?
Oh, yes.
"The weather is great,"
"and I like you."
And it's game over.
You can start dating.
You can do it too.
Like my videos, and leave many comments.
And I'll be your dating coach...
(Ms. Han Hae Na)
(Ms. Han, the weather is great, and I...)
Happy birthday, brother.
I really wanted to visit you guys in Korea this time,
but I can't take off enough time.
I think I can take some time off next month.
Yul is doing well, right?
All right. Just visit us when you can.
Yul is doing well.
(Uncle Seo Won)
Someone's calling you.
Please excuse me for a moment.
You can take the call in that room over there.
Okay.
Ouch, my legs.
Hi, Uncle Seo Won. What's up?
What time will you be home?
I'm not sure. Why?
I was thinking of going out for dinner.
I'll eat alone if you'll be home late.
Hey, Uncle. Are you kidding me?
You shouldn't have dinner alone on your birthday.
All right, then.
- Call me when you're on your way. - Will do.
Ma'am.
You and your uncle must be very close.
Hae Na is close to her uncle too.
Yes, we're close.
There's something I want to check with you.
Sure.
You and Hae Na truly love each other, right?
You two are in a relationship, right?
I think so. Yes.
Then why is it that Hae Na...
hasn't been able to break the curse yet?
Pardon me?
- You guys have kissed, right? - Yes.
- When she was in her dog form too? - Well, that's...
- Sleep here tonight. - Sorry?
She must break the curse tonight.
Only then can I stop worrying.
Ma'am, that's...
Please do it for me.
No.
Ma'am.
Ma'am!
You truly love Hae Na, right?
So would you please do it for her, just this once?
Just for one night.
Mom.
This is just wrong, Mom.
- Mom, please... - What do you mean it's wrong?
Mom, I have something to tell you.
Be quiet.
Mom, I'm sorry.
The guy I kissed...
is someone else.
He doesn't know anything.
What?
Then who is he?
- My gosh, I'm really sorry. - No, it's okay.
I'm so sorry again.
It's okay. Please don't be sorry.
I feel so bad. My goodness.
Gosh, get home safely.
It's all my fault for raising my daughters wrong.
I raised my daughters wrong.
My daughters...
Ms. Han, hold on.
I'm really sorry, Yul.
You can go home now.
I'm really sorry. I mean it.
Anyway, I'm really sorry for everything. And thank you, Yul.
What on earth did I do to you? I'm too embarrassed to face you.
No, Ms. Han.
It's really okay.
It was fun.
And it was nice.
I know she's my sister, but what was she thinking, bringing you here?
I really had a good time though.
Do you want to take a taxi?
Can you go home by yourself?
Ms. Han, I'm not a kid.
It's not like you're in your 30s or 40s.
Just cab home. I'll give you money for your taxi fare.
I have a lot of free time today.
Oh, right!
It's my uncle's birthday today.
He wants to go out for dinner.
I see.
- Do you want to join us? - Can I come too?
Yes, that'd be great!
But it's a family dinner.
Wouldn't it be weird for me to tag along?
Ms. Han.
You have to break the curse.
Do it today.
Okay.
Then I'll go in and get changed quickly. Wait here.
Sure.
Take your time and hurry.
Nice.
(Han Hae Na, Teacher)
(Garam High School)
What?
They work at the same school?
(Garam High School)
"Faculty Forum."
(Faculty Forum)
Uncle Seo Won!
Ms. Han.
What are you doing here?
I ran into Yul over there.
And my plan suddenly got cancelled.
I see.
Hey.
What's with that outfit?
This style is hip these days.
Where shall we go?
Enjoy.
Thanks to you, I get to enjoy this delicious meal.
I hope you enjoy the food too.
Uncle Seo Won.
If it weren't for Ms. Han,
we'd be spending your birthday alone again.
I know.
Ms. Han, thank you so much.
This really feels like a birthday party, having you here.
I was getting sick and tired of having meals with just my uncle.
Had I known it was your birthday,
I would've prepared a gift in advance.
Here, I got you something!
Ta-Da.
I bought it in a rush on my way here.
Next time, I'll buy you something nicer.
This is nice.
There's something else we prepared.
- Happy birthday - Happy birthday
- Happy birthday, dear customer - Happy birthday, dear my uncle
Happy birthday. We hope you have a great time.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Uncle Seo Won, make a wish.
You're good!
You saw that, right?
Let's take some pictures.
Let's take some pictures together.
(The Best Photos of Your Life)
- How do they look? - They're all so cute.
Isn't this such a great photo?
(The Best Photos of Your Life)
Look at that face.
That's too bad, Mr. Jin.
Oh, wait. Hold on.
You lose.
Gosh. I can't remember the last time I let loose and played like this.
Same here.
Gosh, I'm hungry.
Hey, we ate earlier. Why are you hungry already?
It's about time we got hungry.
Yes.
Then...
Ms. Han, do you want to check out this place?
Yes, I'd love to.
But it's not the best place since we have Yul here with us.
Right, it's not the best place for Yul.
It's fine. I'll just go home.
- Really? - Really?
No, Yul. Hang out with us for a little longer.
Mr. Jin, why don't we find someplace else?
Yes, somewhere where we can go with Yul.
I'm off.
Get home safely, then.
Call me when you get home.
Yes. "Han Pan Dong."
My, they look like such a happy family.
A woman who turns into a dog.
Oh, my. How should I go about this?
That's right.
(A female teacher's secret)
Oh, right.
Yul is not mad at us, right?
He hates hanging out with me anyway.
Thank you for everything today.
Thanks to you, I had a fun birthday.
No, don't say that. I should thank you, if anything.
I had so much fun today.
Oh, here.
Okay.
- Well... - Well...
Go ahead.
It's nothing important.
It's your birthday today,
but I couldn't even prepare a proper gift, so I feel bad.
But I like this.
Actually,
I was going to call you separately.
Why?
There's something I want to tell you.
What is it?
You see, I...
Ms. Han, I thought...
long and hard before deciding to tell you this.
Ms. Han,
I think I...
Ms. Han.
Wait.
Yes?
Can I tell you something first?
Sure.
Let me quickly run to the restroom first.
Mr. Jin.
Please listen carefully to what I'm about to tell you.
Don't be too surprised.
Please listen carefully and make your decision.
I...
turn into a dog.
That's too depressing. Gosh.
That's right. I turn into a dog. So what?
I sound like I want to fight.
By any chance,
have you seen a person who turns into a dog?
That's me.
I sound like a crazy woman.
Just be honest.
Pluck up your courage.
I turn into a dog,
and I...
like you.
Hurry up. Finally, she's out.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Jin.
There's something I want to tell you.
Okay.
The thing is, I...
I'll drink this and tell you.
Well...
Mr. Jin.
I...
The thing is, I...
The truth is...
- I turn... - If it's hard for you to tell me,
you don't have to say it.
So I am...
not an alien,
and I'm certainly not a ghost.
Ms. Han, where did you say your place was?
Oh, my.
How pretty.
Hydrangeas...
change colour depending on where they're planted.
Hey, hydrangea.
What will be your new colour?
Let's find out what your new colour will be.
The colour isn't changing.
Guess what my colour is when I change.
No matter what colour you are,
I'm sure you'll still look pretty.
Hello, welcome in.
Can I get a whole chicken to go?
What flavour?
Whatever's the most popular.
Our three-flavour set is good.
Then I'll get the three-flavour set.
Okay. Coming right up.
- One three-flavour set to go! - Okay!
That'll be 21 dollars. Thank you.
How is your restaurant doing lately?
I guess we're doing fine.
Do your children not help you?
They're busy with their own lives.
I guess I'm not that great of a son either.
- You must have a son. - I have two daughters.
But they're a pain in the neck.
Why?
It's hard to explain, but they just are.
But if they resemble you, they must be beautiful.
Goodness. You're handsome yourself,
but you have a good eye.
Do you happen to have any pictures of them?
Don't a lot of parents with daughters...
have them as their wallpaper?
Jeez.
Do you want to see?
Yes, I do.
My daughters are so pretty.
Since a handsome guy like you is asking,
I'll show you.
Let me find...
Why do you want to see my daughters' faces?
I just asked because I thought they'd be pretty...
if they resembled the both of you.
That is true.
I hope you sell a lot.
- Thank you. - Goodbye.
- Bye. - Take care.
Ms. Beautiful.
Goodness. You're so unwary.
Anyway, your younger daughter is in serious trouble.
Why?
Why are you taking that?
I'm going to give it to your brother at the hospital.
He's too old now, and he has weak teeth.
How is he supposed to chew on those?
Do you think he can eat it if I soak it in water...
and mix it in with his feed?
Maybe.
Her brother?
Hey, Yo Sub,
do me a favour.
(Nana Animal Hospital)
Yes, I arrived.
But is this okay? I...
Okay. You don't have to curse.
All right.
I'll call you later.
- How may I help you? - Hello.
My dog keeps dry heaving.
I think an examination needs to be done.
Is that so?
- Let me take a look. - Okay.
All right.
- Let's go. - It's okay.
- We'll take a look. - Okay.
Come on.
How cute.
What are you doing here?
Something's in here.
What?
I don't know.
I can just sense something.
But why do you keep using informal language?
You're younger than me.
What's wrong with being young?
By the way,
how did you know I would be summoned somewhere...
and beg on my knees?
I could just see it.
What you said before...
You know, about how getting too involved...
when it's not even real will lead me to trouble.
Did you run into trouble?
Okay.
Then have fun handling it.
You need to teach me how to handle it...
to call yourself a true shaman.
Can you unlock this?
Move out of the way.
I'll ask Mr. Lee.
Mr. Lee.
What are you doing here?
This is no fun.
Let's go.
Linked arms...
Hello. Can we ask...
- No. - We're not buying anything.
I have a religion.
They're a part of that generation after Generation Z,
Generation Alpha, aren't they?
- They're so rude. - There's such a thing?
You idiot.
Like this. Gosh.
Hey.
Hello.
Can I ask you guys a question?
Do you know Ms. Han Hae Na?
Yes. Why?
I'm a reporter, and I'm here to gather some information.
Here.
Do you have Ms. Han Hae Na's contact information by any chance?
(Kang Eun Hwan)
What is the topic of the story?
Society...
and the economy.
Yes, we will be covering various social problems...
Why aren't you going home?
- Hurry home. - Goodbye.
- Good job today. - Goodbye.
Get home safe.
May I help you?
Well, we are...
The thing is, I am that student's...
uncle.
Who are you talking about?
The one with long hair.
So tell me who exactly you're talking about!
Hey!
I heard yesterday...
- Mr. Jin. - Mr. Jin.
Hey, what did that man say?
He asked about Ms. Han.
- Show him. - Here.
Mr. Jin.
What? You think I'll be pressed for charges?
Go ahead and report me.
I'll be acquitted anyway.
The worst that could happen is a suspended sentence.
(Mystery Hwani Live: Waiting for My Food)
My food is ready.
(Wondeung Central Church)
Do your best to block our kicks or your bone will break.
Block well.
Why did you run away?
Who is it?
Hey, Jin Seo Won.
How did you know I was here?
You're one scary punk.
Did you tail me?
Come in for now.
I'll make you some hot cocoa.
Don't ever come back to the school that I work at.
Did you come all the way over here to say that?
Hey.
I didn't go there to see you.
I went to see your girlfriend.
I don't know what you're plotting,
and I don't even want to know.
But if I see you ever again,
I won't let it slide.
That jerk.
He's making things more interesting.
(Nana Animal Hospital)
You don't have much time left.
How many days are left?
Ten.
Gosh, time flies.
It has already been 90 days?
What are you going to do?
Should we call Yul over for a meeting?
I don't want him to get involved because of me.
Then what are you going to do?
I have a plan.
Though it'll be hard.
What is it?
I should tell him.
Is he...
trustworthy?
No matter what colour you are,
I'm sure you'll still look pretty.
Yes.
I think he is worthy of my trust.
I'm scared.
I don't want you to go through what I did.
I'm here.
What's the room number?
You're actually going to help me lift my curse today, right?
Sang Soo.
I don't have that much time left.
Okay.
Sang Soo.
What? He said he was here.
I put in more than you would have expected.
Please...
kiss my daughter properly.
Also, just to be sure,
if you have been filming any videos in secret,
you better delete everything.
If you don't,
I'm going to chase you to the ends of the earth...
and cut you to pieces.
Darn it.
My poor...
Yu Na.
It's okay.
- Mom. - It's all right.
Gosh.
Sang Soo, that jerk.
Hey, the dogs are listening.
I wasn't talking about them.
No, he wasn't talking about you.
- Not you guys. - It's okay.
Aren't you so pretty?
I wasn't talking about you guys.
That was real?
Hello, I'm the reporter who contacted you before.
Do you have any videos?
I want to buy them from you.
Mr. Hwani?
Just out of curiosity,
how much can you make from videos like these?
Well, it's different every time.
I think I'll need more money paid in advance...
in order for me to rest assured.
I am being threatened right now.
Then we'll just get a recording for now.
Manager?
Record what he says.
Me?
Then should I?
Okay.
One second.
Please disguise my voice.
Of course.
You may start talking.
So the thing is,
turning into a dog runs in their family.
I think I'm going to get sick. Let's get out of here.
Darn it.
My goodness.
Sir.
Thank you.
But what's making you spend this much money...
to reveal all of this?
If I see you ever again,
I won't let it slide.
Just because...
I think it'll be fun.
Hey.
I didn't go there to see you.
I went to see your girlfriend.
(A Good Day To Be A Dog)
Jin Seo Won, that jerk, must not know yet,
seeing how you still have the curse.
Jun Seo, why aren't you turning in your phone?
I will after I feed Cocoa.
Be honest with me.
Where and who did you bring Cocoa from?
Will he go and tell Mr. Jin?
I should go to him before then...
No.
Just worry about yourself right now.
Isn't he the man from the other day?
I'm sure you have never heard of a person turning into a dog.
Come to where we met yesterday this instant...
or else I'm going to kill him.
Today is the day.
I will introduce her to you. She is right here.