Producers: Zhan Haifeng, Zhao Ziyu, Yao Dongqin
Executive Producers: Zhang Jincheng, Zhang Youquan
Written by: Fengdu Brothers
Producers: Huang Yanqing, Zhang Hua
Associate Producers: Chang Le, Yang Nuoxi
Starring: Zheng Chuchen, Zhao Adong
Special Appearance: Heizi
Co-starring: Zhang Zhen, Xiao Ziming, Wang Xingyue, Zhang Jincheng
Associate Director: Xing Shuaibiao
Post-production Director: Zhao Zhiqiang
Produced by: Zhang Jincheng
Directed by: Zhan Haifeng
Haotian,
what's wrong?
Did something happen at the company?
No,
I just don't have much appetite today.
Why do I feel like
you're not very happy?
How could that be?
When I'm with you,
no matter what happens,
I always face it with a smile.
Me too.
When you're happy, I'm happy.
Nothing is more important than that.
By the way, Haotian,
we've been busy with company matters lately,
and haven't gone out for quite some time.
After this busy period is over,
shall we go out and relax a bit?
Sounds good.
Wherever you want to go then,
that's where we'll go.
Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry.
Zimo, you're here.
It's been so long since you've been back.
Has this place changed much?
Quite a bit.
Haven't you looked around?
No.
I don't want to go anywhere.
What's wrong?
You look so down.
What happened?
Tell me.
I want to cheer up too.
I just got back and you're already teasing me.
I'm just
trying to make you feel better.
Look at you,
you don't even look pretty anymore.
Well,
the person I like got married.
Who could be so blind?
My dear sister is so elegant
and graceful.
Another business elite,
right?
Back in the day, you had suitors lining up.
Let me tell you,
if you like him, that's his good fortune.
I see.
Tell me,
who is he?
What does he do?
You might know him.
I know him?
Who is it?
Long Haotian.
Long Haotian...
Long Haotian from Long Corporation?
That's right.
What's wrong, Zimo?
How did you two
meet each other?
We met when
he came to the orphanage
to do charity work,
that's how we got to know each other.
Then why did you
break up with him
and how
did you become Uncle Li's adopted daughter?
I don't want to talk about that anymore.
Okay.
Let's drop it then.
What if I could help you get him back?
He's already married,
how could you possibly help me?
What if Long Haotian
doesn't actually love Chu Ruoyun,
but the child in her womb?
Yiran,
you still have a chance.
If you want this relationship
to continue,
we can work together.
How would we work together?
We each get what we want.
You get Long Haotian.
And Chu Ruoyun...
Chu Ruoyun.
Actually,
I don't know why,
but every time I see her,
I really want to get to know her.
Maybe
she reminds you too much of Nono.
I understand,
emotional attachment.
You're still as smart as ever.
So for this matter,
I need your help too.
Do you have any plans?
Well,
let's go to his company tomorrow.
Mr. Zhong, please wait a moment,
I'll inform the chairman.
Come in.
Chairman,
Mr. Zhong is already waiting for you in the conference room.
Okay,
I got it.
Mr. Zhong
this Mr. Long is really too much,
making us wait for so long.
Why don't we leave now
and reconsider the cooperation later.
No rush.
It's business.
Take it slow.
If we leave first,
it would make us look bad.
Mr. Zhong.
I'm sorry,
I've been so busy I lost track of time.
It's fine,
our business discussion won't take long anyway.
Great,
let's make the most of our time then.
Here's the project proposal
and the contract.
10 billion.
Mr. Zhong,
that's quite ambitious.
However,
I notice the products in your proposal
could be manufactured by companies other than Long Group,
so why choose us?
Other companies can do it,
but when it comes to capability
and quality,
it has to be your
Long Group.
Of course,
if you have any concerns, Mr. Long,
we can always work together another time.
Well,
Mr. Zhong,
if you're in such a hurry to give me money,
how could I possibly refuse?
But since this is our first collaboration,
we need to follow proper procedures,
can't skip those.
We'll do as you say, Mr. Long.
Good.
It seems there's no problem.
Since Mr. Zhong is showing such sincerity,
let's work together this time.
Alright.
Mr. Zhong,
here's to
a successful partnership.
I hope we can collaborate frequently in the future.
We certainly will.
Well then,
I'll take my leave.
Take care.
You're Chu Ruoyun, aren't you?
And you are?
I'm Li Yiran.
Let's find a place to talk.
Well...
Is that a problem?
Do we know each other?
We don't.
But we both know
Long Haotian.
Cast
Zheng Chuchen as Chu Ruoyun
Zhao Adong as Long Haotian
Zhang Zhen as Xiao Ai
Xiao Ziming as Zhong Zimo
Wang Xingyue as Li Yiran
Guo Jing as Lin Xiaoxin
Zhang Jincheng as Li Xiaohan
Zhang Yanhua as Chairman Long
Zhang Zhiwei as Uncle Zhang
Zhang Xinglan as Zhang Hui
Jiang Hao as Boss B
Huang Yanqing as Assistant Zhong
Wu Guoshan as Boss A
Mao Zhu as Chu Yulan
Theme Song "No Debt No Regret"
Performed by: Banxia Cc
Arrangement: Qiu Muyang
Harmony Arrangement: Chen Xiaoquan
Producer: Shengyu
Exclusive Distribution
Zhejiang Fengdu Film and Media Co., Ltd.