Producers: Zhan Haifeng, Zhao Ziyu, Yao Dongqin
Jincheng Welfare
Executive Producers: Zhang Jincheng, Zhang Youquan Welfare
Screenplay: Fengdu Brothers
Producers: Huang Yanqing, Zhang Hua
Associate Producers: Chang Le, Yang Nuoxi
Starring: Zheng Chuchen, Zhao Adong
Special Appearance: Heizi
Cast: Zhang Zhen, Xiao Ziming, Wang Xingyue, Zhang Jincheng
Executive Director: Xing Shuaibiao
Post-production Director: Zhao Zhiqiang
Supervising Producer: Zhang Jincheng
Director: Zhan Haifeng
What's wrong, Ruoyun?
Uncle,
I see my husband at the beach every day,
I can see him there,
still waiting for me.
I didn't expect this guy
to be such a devoted lover.
Come,
sit down.
What are you thinking?
I can't bear to see him like this,
I want to go back to him.
Ruoyun,
if you go back now,
you might temporarily ease the pain of separation,
but what about
the future? Have you thought about that?
I...
Mom!
Mr. Li,
you wanted to see me?
Find a buyer,
keep it quiet.
Yes, Mr. Li.
Xiaohan.
Yulan,
you're here.
Yulan.
Come on, it's time
for us to end this relationship.
Why?
Weren't we doing fine?
I'm going to be a father.
Yulan.
To keep my family intact,
we can't continue like this anymore.
You can't do this to me.
Yulan.
I'm sorry.
Madam.
The company just sent news that
Li Yiran is
secretly acquiring shares of the company,
and several directors
have already transferred their shares to her name.
This Li Yiran
is quite cunning.
In the future,
whether Long Corporation remains with the Long family
or becomes Li's,
depends on what Haotian does.
Huihui.
I found our other child.
I'm sorry, Xiaohan.
Only Nono can be with you now.
We originally had two children.
She lost one.
Now only Nono is left.
Her health is poor.
You must take good care of her.
I will.
Meeting you in this life
has been the greatest happiness
of my entire existence.
Don't overthink things.
You'll get better,
you'll definitely get better.
I hope in our next life
we can be husband and wife again.
It's all my fault.
We've been separated for so many years.
To the point that
you didn't even know she existed.
This child
is naturally kind-hearted.
She's especially lovable.
But I
can't protect her forever.
So
I want to raise her to be
a strong, independent person.
Huihui.
Don't worry.
I will definitely
bring her to see you.
Cast
Zheng Chuchen as Chu Ruoyun
Zhao Adong as Long Haotian
Zhang Zhen as Xiao Ai
Xiao Ziming as Zhong Zimo
Wang Xingyue as Li Yiran
Guo Jing as Lin Xiaoxin
Zhang Jincheng as Li Xiaohan
Heizi as Grandpa Li
Jiang Jiaxin as Zhao Zi'ang
Zhang Yanhua as Chairman Long
Zhang Zhiwei as Uncle Zhang
Zhang Xinglan as Zhang Hui
Jiang Hao as Boss B
Huang Yanqing as Assistant Zhong
Wu Guoshan as Boss A
Mao Zhu as Chu Yulan
Theme Song "No Debt, No Regret"
Performed by: Banxia Cc
Lyrics by: Shengyu
Arranged by: Qiu Muyang
Mixed by: Liu Chenghan
Harmony Arrangement: Chen Xiaoquan
Producer: Shengyu
Exclusive Distribution
Zhejiang Fengdu Film and Media Co., Ltd.