(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh my gosh!
A boss-employee relationship
is definitely challenging.
There should be clear boundaries
between your work relationship
and your couple relationship.
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
I'm sorry.
I know my position
complicates our relationship,
but what can I do?
I just want to make you
feel special all the time.
Well, I'm just not
used to it yet.
- Kimberly!
- Little sis!
- It's my sisters.
- I thought you're proud of us.
No, just hide here.
I'm coming!
Why are there two plates?!
Where is he?!
Your boss is rich.
Why is he only
feeding you pares?
So there is something
going on between you.
My goodness!
The nerve of that guy!
Remember this, Kim.
I don't approve of your boss.
He should get to know us first.
And he should never put you
in a difficult position.
Brandon?
Your sisters are right.
I'll show them how serious
I am about you.
What are you doing here?
I came here to give this to you.
I promise I'll never make you
cry again, Secretary Kim.
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
- Oh.
- Hi, Secretary Kim.
Good morning, madam.
Good morning.
Can you be a darling for me?
Could you ask the Parks
their shirt sizes?
Sure, ma'am.
I'll have sweaters made for them
as my way of welcoming them
to Prime Alpha family.
Copy, ma'am.
Shall I coordinate this
with Sir Gab Poblete?
Yes, please.
You know, since Donny
and Cyrus were kids,
we've been ordering
custom-made clothes from him.
Let me show you.
Here.
Aren't we cute?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
You convinced boss to wear that?
Oh, I insisted.
Because I wanted us to recreate
our old family picture.
Wait, I'll show you.
Here it is. Look!
- (UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING)
- Cute, right?
(YOUNG KIM) Promise me that
we'll get married.
If you don't, I won't go inside.
Okay, fine. You're persistent.
(YOUNG KIM) You promise?
I promise.
(CARLOTA) Oh.
Well, speaking of things,
Secretary Kim, I heard that...
(BRANDON) Mom!
(UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES)
Good morning!
Hey.
(MUG, COFFEE MAKER CLINKING)
(QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING)
Good morning, guys!
(STEPH) Good morning!
(KIM MARIE) Hey, Steph!
I finally moved into
my new place.
- Wow!
- You better come
to my housewarming party, okay?
Thanks to you, the landlady
gave me a discount.
- Of course I'll be there.
- (GIGGLES)
Can I come too?
Sure. You can go with Steph.
Nah. He can find your place
on his own.
Let's go over there.
(QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES)
(KIM MARIE)
Are you two okay?
(STEPH CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY)
Here's your coffee.
- Thank you, dear.
- You're welcome, ma'am.
Excuse me, boss.
(BRANDON INHALES DEEPLY)
Mom. (SIGHS)
You could always call Sec. Kim
if you need anything.
So, tell me. What's the real
reason for your visit?
Am I not allowed
to check up on my youngest
after that IdeaEx fiasco?
The nerve of that Iñigo!
(SIGHS)
But I'm okay, Mom.
Also, I'm able to cope
because of...
someone.
(PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
You're seeing someone?
(SQUEALS) Who's that
lucky girl?!
To think I came here
to ask Secretary Kim
who her boyfriend is.
(CARLOTA SIGHS)
Cyrus was broken hearted.
Well, at least one of my sons
is looking very happy!
Mom, I'm always happy.
Anyway, I need your help
with something regarding
the Park family.
Well, of course!
Anything for you.
So, what do you need?
Do you want to send them
on a trip to Boracay or Palawan?
Play golf with them perhaps?
Ma'am Carlota showed me an
old picture with my boss in it.
He was wearing the same sweater
as Ninja Boy.
Kim, we already closed
that case, remember?
We've established
that his older brother
is Ninja Boy.
But the evidence
doesn't match Cyrus.
(KAT SIGHS)
Little sis...
You keep suspecting
that your boss is Ninja Boy.
Are you sure this time?
Don't tell me you like him
because you associate him
with Ninja Boy.
Kat, I'm sure about my feelings.
Then all the more reason
for you to move on.
It won't be good for your
current relationship
if you're still carrying
baggage from the past,
especially now that
you just started dating.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
Oh my.
I felt that sigh
all the way from here.
Good thing we're going
out of town tomorrow.
You badly need a breather.
You're right.
See you. Bye!
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
- Here's your coffee, Sir Walt.
- Thank you.
- This is good to go.
- Okay.
(WALTER) Thank you.
(QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING)
Damn it.
Why is he being mysterious?
Hey, who are you
stalking this time?
My future hubby.
Oh, really?
- Let me see.
- Wait, Sir Walt.
I'll show you
when we're official.
Official, huh?
(WALTER) Whatever.
OMG! You finally moved in?
Huh? Can I see?
Here.
Aren't you going to invite us
to your housewarming party?
Well, I plan to, Sir Walt,
once I've settled in.
Invite me too, okay?
Of course, Miss Sarah.
You two.
- It depends if he's going.
- It depends if she's going.
(QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES)
I should go. I've got errands
to run for Sir Philip.
Oh, okay.
- I'll step out for a bit.
- You too?
- Okay.
- "It depends if he's going"?
Guys, I swear.
Can you feel it too?
Tension, tension, tension!
Tension across the board!
Hey! Steph.
What?
Are you still mad?
What do you think?
You walked out on me.
Why? Are you the only one
who has the right to walk out?
Yes!
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
So...
Are you still mad?
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
You?
I can't get mad at you.
Then...
Should we go to the
housewarming party together?
Oh. Why does my opinion
suddenly matter now?
Well, what are we?
(CLICKS TONGUE)
We don't want to be
anything yet, right?
So, what are we?
We're...
getting to know each other.
Hmm.
Okay.
Rule number one: We must go
to events as a package deal.
Why are you suddenly
enforcing rules?
We're getting to
know each other, right?
Then I'd like you to know
that I'm a rule-oriented person.
I'll send you
my list of rules later.
(WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Um, boss-
("TO BE WITH YOU"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING)
Will you give me a raise?
- Sorry.
- Sir Philip.
I didn't notice you enter.
Um...
Ninja Boy?
Ninja Boy.
Mm. Yes?
Ninja Boy?
(MUSIC FADES)
What are you doing?
U-Um...
I'm not trying to steal
a kiss from you, okay?
Hmm?
(GRUNTS)
Then what are you doing
so close to me?
I called you Ninja Boy.
And what did I say?
You said...
"Yes?"
- (SOBBING)
- (SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(KIM) It's Troy. It's Troy.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry...
(MUSIC FADING)
Well, Sec. Kim, I just had
the best sleep of my life.
Maybe I was talking gibberish
while I was half asleep.
Hmm.
Okay. Go back to sleep.
Hmm?
- Psst. Hey!
- (SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
Shall I make you coffee, tea?
Mm, coffee, please.
Okay, sure. Two minutes.
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES)
(KLA) Dada, everything
is ready for tomorrow!
I'm excited, Dada!
Come here.
Why isn't he speaking?
Dada!
(STRUMMING GUITAR)
(KAT) Da!
You don't look excited
for tomorrow.
Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
This could be the last time
we'll do this together.
(STRUMMING GUITAR)
W-Why, Dada?
Don't tell us...
Are you sick?!
Hey. I'm strong as a bull.
I'm not dying, okay?
(KLA) Stop talking nonsense!
Well, if he's not sick,
then why is he sad?
And why is it the last time?
Da.
- What's wrong with him?
- What happened?
It's because Auntie
has a boyfriend!
- (QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING)
- Huh?
- Did you hear that?
- A boyfriend?
Yes.
(CHUCKLES)
You really take after me, huh?
You Little Miss Chatterbox!
- (KLA) Katrina.
- Sis?
The last I heard,
they were just flirting.
But now they're a couple?
They're together?!
It hasn't been a month!
Calm down, sis!
Their love story has been
nine years in the making!
(KLA) I see.
- Right?
- Trying to be smart, huh?
You think you're so clever?
- But, sis-
- Maybe Dada was right.
This should be the last one.
I don't think I can stop myself
from pinching you!
- You asked me!
- How annoying!
You asked me a question,
so I answered you.
You're such a loudmouth,
it's rubbing off on the kid!
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
(LOUNGE MUSIC PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
Philip.
Hon.
Uh, sorry. Laura. Sorry.
Uh, you're here?
I mean, you're here, of course.
Are you with someone?
- (PHILIP) You see, I have-
- Oh, sorry. Uh...
I don't know
if you've met... JB.
JB. Hello. Nice to meet you.
Oh.
Peter, right? Peter?
No, it's Philip, actually.
Oh, Philip. Philip. Yeah.
- Philip?
- (PHILIP) Yeah.
I'll just go to our baby.
- (LAURA) Okay. I'll stay here.
- (JB) Philip.
- Nice suit, nice suit.
- (PHILIP) Thank you.
- See you, hon.
- Yes, yes. I'll wait for you.
(LOUNGE MUSIC CONTINUES)
"Baby"?
(CHUCKLES) Yes.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Who are you with?
I'm with...
L-Lana. Lana.
- Lana.
- (PHILIP) Right.
Y-You will like her, actually.
I-If you catch her.
- I think she's running late.
- Sir.
- Sir? Sir Philip?
- Yeah?
Your table for one is ready.
B-Before. But now it's for two.
L-Lana couldn't come at first.
She messaged 10 minutes ago
that she was coming.
She's coming h-here
from her thing.
Uh...
N-Nice to see you, Laura.
Enjoy the rest of your day.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(KIM) Thank you.
(CAR DOOR SHUTS)
Oh, by the way,
I'm on leave tomorrow.
It's Mama's birthday.
Uh, yeah. I know.
You go on leave
on that day every year.
(INHALES DEEPLY) Um...
If you want to come, it's fine.
But it's a long ride.
I don't want to impose
on you and Baldo.
Of course I can drive.
If it's really that far,
I can always check in-
"Check in"?
Check in the GPS app of the car
for faster routes.
What were you thinking?
(QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING)
The same thing.
Faster r-routes.
Okay.
And besides,
I heard your sister Klarisse.
So, until they give
their approval,
I won't enter your apartment
or any place where you sleep.
Copy, sir.
Uh, alright. I'm going inside.
Good night.
(CLEARS THROAT)
And where's my good night kiss?
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
Okay.
Good night.
And what about my goodbye kiss?
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES)
Goodbye. (GIGGLES)
(KIM) Okay?
And this is my good night kiss.
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES)
Good night and goodbye.
Good night.
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES)
(PHONE CHIMES)
(SOBBING) And now
they have a baby, bro.
What?
I didn't know Laura gave birth.
No! It's a fur baby. Look.
(PHILIP) Its name is Charlie.
Charlie, bro!
We were going to name
our firstborn Charlie!
They should've named it JB.
The guy looked
like a dog anyway!
What's so funny?
Um...
Nothing. (CLEARS THROAT)
I was just surprised,
that's all.
"Surprised?" You're laughing
while I'm feeling regretful.
If I did not prioritize
my ambition,
we'd already have a baby by now.
I'd probably be carrying
baby Charlie right now, bro.
But no.
Even her family is mad at me.
They said I only cared
about my career and myself.
They were right.
Um, Philip...
Do you like her?
"Like?"
I still love Laura so much, bro.
But there's nothing
I can do now.
I can't blame her if she's tired
of defending me to her family.
To think that at first,
her family was on the side
of our reconciliation.
But no, I wasted my chance, bro.
It's because I'm selfish.
I'm so selfish.
Why am I selfish?
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(BRANDON) Let's meet
your fam tomorrow?
- (PHONE CHIMES)
- (KIM) Are you sure?
(BRANDON) Yes, boss.
(SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES)
(PHONE CHIMES)
(KIM) Copy that. See you, boss.
(QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING)
(QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES)
The Castillos were like family
to me.
That's why I was hurt they
didn't give me a second chance.
I can see why.
But...
Are these bribery
allegations true?
I thought we will just talk
about the kidnapping.
We... We are.
I'm just being careful, sir.
You might be doing
this interview
because of a personal vendetta.
Of course not.
Right.
So what I need are facts.
I need details
about the kidnapping.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Their family doesn't leave
any trace, Troy.
You see, the story didn't
resurface until now.
So...
Are they hiding something?
The kidnapper was the wife
of the man they sent to jail.
A wrongfully accused man.
(STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES)
- (KLA CHUCKLES)
- (KAT) One, two, three...
Wow! Good job!
- Do you want to join them?
- Of course.
- Yes. Here we go.
- With feelings.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
- I love it!
- Let's turn.
Is something wrong, Dada?
Are you happy?
Huh?
Yeah, I'm happy.
Oh. We have a visitor, Dada.
Kat, Kla, we have a visitor.
(KAT) Let's go. Come on.
- (KLA) Who's that?
- (KIM) Come in.
(KLA) Oh.
(KIM) Um, Dada...
Kat, Kla, Kring...
This is my boss. Um...
I mean, Brandon, my boyfriend.
Hi, Uncle Handsome!
Good morning, Liwanag family.
Sir.
Uh...
We have to go somewhere.
We'll be back before lunch.
- Alright.
- Bye, Dada.
- (KLA) Psst.
- Let's go.
Excuse us.
(KAT SQUEALS)
Your daughter really takes
after you.
What's wrong? We were just
being polite.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
Ma, this is Brandon Castillo.
My boyfriend.
I promise...
I'll take good care
of your daughter.
I won't make her cry.
I promise...
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES)
I'll always take care of her.
I'm planning to have
a housewarming party.
No, you can't.
What do you mean I can't?
- Just cancel it.
- Whatever.
Kim Marie? Kim Marie!
- Kim Marie.
- Surprise!
- (SQUEALS)
- (LAUGHS)
What's happening?
We will...
You know, catch some tilapia.
(CHUCKLES)
Tilapia?
Why is he even here?
This is our family tradition.
Kla, can we work in teams?
Sure. It doesn't have
any bearing yet.
Ow! That hurt!
- Look!
- Stay energetic.
(QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING)
(SQUEALS)
(GRUNTS)
- Are you okay?
- Yes, he's okay.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Watch your step.