Why did you ask to see me?
I have to tie up the loose ends
between us.
Do you really remember it now?
I already know the truth.
There must be something.
What those scumbags did to Indy.
There must be evidence.
Are you sure he did it?
And what are you going to do
with the evidence?
I miss you.
I want to see you.
Nothing will happen
if I take it to the police.
Or maybe we tell the public
and let the public deal with him.
When it all started that night,
I used classical music
to bring myself to him,
to be in the same circle as him.
Classical music is falsely believed
as belonging to the rich.
They're obsessed with using it
to enhance their taste
and present themselves
as superior to others.
And this time,
I'm going to use classical music
to bring myself to him
one last time.
Because I've now realized
there's no other way.
And this should be
the end to everything.
I'm the last-minute replacement for
the musician who called in sick.
Can I see your credentials?
May I check your bag?
Are you the musician for tonight?
This way, please.
The event's about to start.
All done?
Risa will be unhappy if she's late.
Please proceed.
Why the long face, It?
It's a night of merriment.
It's also a celebration of us
joining forces.
Just don't forget what you said.
I lost a fortune.
Of course, I won't forget.
You can rest assured.
If someone digs up your past
and uses it against you,
I'll help you sort it out.
I'm doing everything
for my daughter's sake.
She's getting married after all.
So I want to be sure
I can guarantee her
stability and happiness.
You're lucky to have a daughter.
Apparently, she can be used
as a guarantor
to demand an ample amount of money.
Oh, you.
You're still yourself
after all this time.
Well then. I hope your luck is
as sharp as your tongue.
What are you doing here, Risa?
Oh, I'm about to head inside.
My daughter's very beautiful.
You've spoken to Treetep,
haven't you?
The deal I have with him
is going smoothly, I hope?
Of course I have.
Let's wait until after tonight.
It's not the time.
Oh?
Risa, you look
very beautiful tonight.
You're the bride of the year,
you'll be the talk of the town.
Thank you, Parnkeaw.
This is such
an occasion to celebrate.
It has brought
people of equal status
from our families together.
Maya!
Keep it together.
People are watching.
Escort this uninvited guest
out of here, please!
Don't worry.
I'll leave.
But I have to speak to It first.
What's the matter?
You said you missed me.
So I came to see you.
Let's wait until after the wedding.
I'll speak to you later.
Of course. I'll leave.
But you have to tell me first.
Why did you do this?
I asked you who you're working for!
If you don't talk,
you'll never talk again.
Who do you work for?
How did you get your hands
on that clip?
Tell me why you did it!
I don't think it's the time
to discuss it.
And why would you be angry with me?
This man is a friend of mine.
The person you tried to murder is
a friend of mine!
I didn't know he was your friend.
More importantly, I had to do that
because he did something to me
he shouldn't have done.
What was it then?
Was it about you ordering the slums
to be burned down 15 years ago?
Burning down the slums?
I don't know anything about that.
Maya, let's talk later, okay?
This is what I'm going to make you
admit to everyone tonight.
You did it.
I've been waiting for 15 years.
I'm not going to wait any longer.
Don't go anywhere!
Stay here and listen, all of you.
Or I'm going to shoot him.
- Maya?
- I knew it.
You wouldn't admit
anything that easily.
Spit it out.
Say you made the order
to burn the slums down.
Say it. The same thing
you said to me.
Say that the lives
of the poor are worthless.
That we're just dirty rats.
Say it! Exactly like
when you said it to me.
What's going to happen
once the slums have burned down?
Spit it out.
Just like you did
to that little girl.
You killed my dad, didn't you?
You good-for-nothing scumbag!
Why did you burn my house down?
My dad died because of you!
Let go of me!
So what if I did?
What can you do to me?
You don't deserve to be there.
You were lucky you didn't die.
Let me go!
You're...
that filthy little brat
who came into my house?
It was you?
I can't believe it.
You came into my life
and seduced me because of this?
How pathetic.
Because it's all in vain.
I did nothing wrong.
Even if you kill me now,
it would be in vain.
People will come
to my funeral in droves
and praise me
for all of the wonderful things
I've done.
As for you,
you'll be in jail.
You're going to rot in jail.
And the past will
finally be forgotten
because it's only
a pile of trash.
Shoot me.
- Do it!
- Do you think I won't?
Shoot me if you dare!
- Maya, stop!
- Say it now!
- Enough!
- Kin!
Kin, don't!
Maya, enough.
It's over now.
(A Few Hours Ago)
Did you get it?
Yes, sir.
You fool. Your search for evidence
led you to your death.
It will just be...
a rumor now on.
Why are you here?
You don't remember anything at all?
No.
All this time, I've been
following your father's orders.
I always believed
I was serving a criminal.
In here,
there's important data
I was able to recover.
I believe you might find it useful.
I've transferred
all the data to this.
It's over, Dad.
What are you talking about?
Play the clip for me.
What clip?
What is it about?
No, what is this clip?
Kin, what are you doing?
Do you think I've forgotten?
In fact, I haven't.
What do you mean by that?
I told you
I have to tell everyone.
Akin, you...
You... don't play it!
- Don't do it!
- I saw you hurting them,
and my memory became even clearer.
Because I used to be
on the receiving end as well!
I meant to wait
until after the wedding.
But since it's come to this,
I can't wait any longer.
Play the clip!
- No!
- Play it!
I said no!
You can't burn down their houses!
Come here, young master!
Come on!
- No, you can't!
- I said let go!
Don't!
- How did you find this?
- No!
- Where did you get it?
Please stop!
Who took it?
No, you can't do it.
What are you doing here?
I've been looking everywhere
for you. What are you doing?
What are you doing?
We have to go to the airport.
You can't burn down
those people's houses.
And how does it concern you?
Do you want to be a good person?
Remember.
There's no place for good people.
Are you sure
you want to reveal
the truth to everyone
after this?
If you're still going to be weak
and too much of a coward
to do anything,
you'll never get anything from me.
Because you'll ruin
everything I've built!
No!
Kin!
I don't want to!
If you don't burn it down,
I'm going to kill them all.
Burn it!
No, Dad!
Burn it.
Burn it!
- I don't have that much time!
- I don't want to!
No!
Don't!
I'm sorry.
- Hey!
- Dad!
- Calm down, Dad.
- Step back.
- Let her go.
- Step back!
- All of you, step back!
- Dad!
Step back!
Step back, all of you.
- Kin, don't!
- Dad!
- Let her go, please.
- Step back!
- You've done enough! Let her go!
Risa!
Don't go after them!
I forbid you to be involved with
these people ever again.
Come on. Let's go home.
We're done here.
Come on.
Your husband's ruined everything.
I didn't have any part in this.
I... I didn't...
I've never known
about anything It did.
Dad, wait! Dad!
Let me go!
Oh? Ma?
What's wrong? Why are you crying?
What happened? Why are you crying?
Oh? Dear!
She's bleeding!
Oh dear! Look at her!
See what's wrong with her!
Huh? It's just a small cut.
- Are you okay?
- You'll be fine.
You're not going to die.
What? She's crying. She's hurt.
Look at her. Is the cut deep?
Does she need stitches?
What are you thinking, Bua?
We can't afford that.
Let me see.
I'll blow on it.
Oh, it's okay.
I'm sorry for telling you off.
Okay? But you have to remember
to toughen up,
or we won't survive.
We've still got
a tough life ahead.
We're poor.
The poor will keep getting bullied.
I want you to be strong
so you'll be able
to keep fighting in life.
I love you, Ma.
Ma?
- Mom?
- Ma.
Dad?
Maya?
- Maya?
- Ma'am, are you okay?
- All done.
- Thank you.
- Can you give us a moment?
- Of course.
Are you okay?
I'm all right.
You said you were sorry.
Please don't blame yourself.
You didn't do anything wrong.
But at least, we've found out
what the wound in your heart is.
Your method worked.
It helped me remember everything.
But it wasn't right.
It hurt you.
It made you feel horrible.
It's me
who should be apologizing.
It's okay.
I also remember you were that girl.
You ran into my house to demand
justice for your family.
I understand
why you did everything.
That little girl...
was named Mayawee.
She's also known as "Ma".
You met her
when you were younger
before the terrible incident.
You were very good at soccer.
You're so good!
That girl.
Thank you so much
for helping a girl who had no hope
of finding happiness.
You helped her feel
like she had a brother.
And if that brother of hers would
keep her in his heart forever,
she'd probably be very happy.
I'm sorry
for coming into your life,
lying to you,
and hurting you.
There's nothing truthful
about what's happened,
even our feelings.
I wish you a good life
from now on.
Let's get you to a hospital.
Sure. But...
can you drop me off
at a different one?
Of course.
Akin.
You don't have
to come with me anymore.
And after this,
please go and enjoy
your life without me.
All done. We're ready to go.
Ow. Ow!
Ow!
Let go of me!
Let me go!
Argh!
Help!
Anyone, help me!
Why would you tie me up?
I'm in pain all over!
Anyone, please help me!
Where is everyone?
Hey!
Anyone, help me!
Anyone, please!
Please! I'm in agony!
Dad?
Dad.
Dad!
Please, help me!
Help me!
I want to die!
Mom, Dad, it's all over now.
The person who did this to us
has faced the consequences.
You don't have to worry anymore.
I believe you're both
always with me.
And someday,
we'll see each other again.
I'm not running away from you.
I just moved, that's all.
Besides, I have to take care of Indy
and look for Kongkwan.
Ma,
have you seen the news?
What news?
Someone found a burned skeleton
in the forest.
The police have
a lead on the culprit.
There are comments on social media
saying he works for Saksit.
Don't tell me it's Kwan.
I don't know.
I couldn't bear to keep watching
when the skeleton appeared.
I'm scared.
I'm scared I'll see something that
confirms it's Kwan.
And have the police arrested Saksit?
I have no idea.
It's so obvious, but I don't know
if the cops can do anything to him.
Ma,
we have to try and do something
before he gets away.
Saksit,
you didn't kill your ex-wife
like they're saying online, did you?
What are you doing?
Are you running away?
Then you're admitting it.
You're leaving me with the backlash
that I'm a scumbag like you?
Are you criticizing me right now?
As if you're a good person!
Saksit!
It's always been the two of us
since we were young!
I'm on your side no matter what!
Please don't go!
I'll have no one else left
if you go!
- Please!
- Hey!
Be with your husband!
Aren't you two very much in love?
He never loved me!
Let him die for all I care!
Saksit!
Even if you're behind it,
I'll still be on your side.
- Don't go! Let's start over!
- Ugh! Get off me!
Like how we always do!
- Don't leave me!
- Let go!
Are you going to be a burden
until the very last second?
Let me tell you!
You'd ruin it all again
if we started over!
You're a loser!
I'd rather have a koala
for a sister!
From this moment on,
we have no ties to each other!
We'll go our separate ways!
Saksit! Please don't go!
Saksit!
Please come with us
for questioning at the station.
And why do I have to go?
I didn't do anything wrong.
And even if I was in the wrong,
you wouldn't be able
to lay a finger on me.
I'm close to the top brass.
But I don't think
you'll get away this time.
It's made national headlines.
And the whole country is
keeping a close watch,
Saksit.
And how is this
any of your business?
All right. Let's do it this way.
I'd like you all to leave my house.
I'm afraid not.
According to the forensic
examination of the burned skeleton,
the results show that the deceased
was an ex-wife of yours.
We've also received a lead that
you might've murdered her here.
And we were able to trace
her phone's signal to this place
when her relative came
to file a report.
Our speculation is that this is
the last place she visited.
Where's my friend?
I asked you a question!
Officers, please hurry
and search the house.
I believe my friend is here.
We'll have to search the house.
Here's the warrant.
This has nothing to do with me.
I'll see myself out.
Where do you think you're going,
you stuck-up snob?
I believe you're
directly involved in it.
I hate her so much.
I hate her, so, so much.
I really should've just killed her.
I should've just killed her!
I shouldn't have just asked you to
send someone over to beat her up!
Are you hard of hearing?
Try listening to it closely.
That's it! Now, are you going to
insist you're not involved?
You sent someone
to beat my friend up,
and you intended to kill her too!
- You harlot!
- Is that so? Bring it on!
Come on!
Maya, you!
You!
You made me lose everything.
You made me lose everyone I love!
You destroyed everything in my life!
- Now I have nothing left!
- Calm down!
You!
- Let go of me!
- Get her out of here!
- Let go of me! Maya!
- Get her out!
- Maya!
- Come with us.
Go and be a snob in prison!
Officers,
please search the house.
I'm very worried about my friend.
- Let's go then.
- Okay.
And remember, both of you!
If anything happened to my friend,
I will never let this go!
Jerks!
- Kwan!
- Have you found her?
- No.
- Captain.
- Yes?
We've located Saksit's wife.
You've found my friend?
Kwan? Kwan!
- Kwan!
- Sofia!
Maya!
- Where have you been?
- I'm sorry.
I'll get you out of here, okay?
Don't leave me again, okay?
Don't leave me, please!
Please!
Don't leave me!
Don't go anywhere!
I promise!
We've patted her down.
She's unarmed, sir.
Have a seat.
After everything you've done,
you still asked
to meet me in private.
I really respect your tenacity.
I'm not surprised you were able
to put It in his place like that.
All right. How can I help you today?
(A List of Names of the Slum Victims
Affected by the Arson)
Here's a list of names
of all the people in the slums.
I asked you to help improve
the quality of their life
according to the policy
you proposed.
But it seems that it never happened.
And do you really think that
one minister, like myself,
can make an order
and that society will
instantly improve?
You have to give it time.
But you can't wait
when it's people's lives.
I know we can't just rely
on those in power.
Anyway, while I wait
for you to do your part,
an individual like me will
do her best
to improve their lives as well.
I want to give them hope
that their lives don't exist
just to help politicians win votes.
This has been an undeniable fact
for many years.
Okay. I'll receive your request.
And if there's nothing else,
please.
I'd like everyone's life to be
hopeful.
And I hope that someday,
you'll feel the same way I do now,
Mr. Minister.
Mom,
I'm afraid I'll have to break
the promise you asked me to keep
because I couldn't protect anything.
In fact, I had no right to do that
because we shouldn't have possessed
those things in the first place.
Both the land
and the mall were built
at the cost of human lives.
They shouldn't have been ours.
I, Akin Itsarapat,
would like to resign
from all positions at Itsara Group.
The resignation is
effective immediately.
Why did you have to
since you're not in the wrong?
What happened?
That's right. And who's going to
take over from you?
That's right. Who?
- Give us an answer, please.
- Akin?
I believe you'll agree
with my decision
because choosing to do what's right
is the type of courage
you wanted me to have.
I did it, Indy.
Right now,
those crooks have faced
the consequences of their actions.
It is in agony,
like he's in a living hell.
I did it.
Right now,
it's almost a happy ending
for everything.
There's only you.
I want to talk to you,
like how you used to talk to me.
I want you to open your eyes
so you can keep living a happy life.
Wake up, Indy.
Please!
Indy?
Nurse!
Indy!
I got lucky, thanks to my beauty.
That's why he kept me alive
and didn't kill me.
That's true.
You're lucky you're pretty,
or you would've been
another dead body in his house.
Are you trying to jinx me?
It sounds like it, doesn't it?
But I didn't expect him
to be such a scumbag.
There's probably a lot more
about him we still don't know.
But I'm curious as to
what's on his ex-wife's phone.
She used it to blackmail him
for money but got killed instead.
There were photos and videos
when he slept with children.
They were still young.
There were many too.
- He's evil beyond all reason.
- Oh gosh.
What are you going to do now?
I don't know.
I'll think about it later.
I'm worried if I asked Sofia
to find me another rich man,
she'll bring me
another psycho again.
Okay. I guess the fault is all mine.
- Indeed.
- I'm really sorry
for finding you such a scumbag.
But when I let you try on your own,
you couldn't find anyone.
Sofia.
That's the second time already.
Anyway, we still have a lot of time
to think about it.
Judging from the kind of crimes
Saksit committed,
he'll probably be
in prison for a while.
But I do know
where he hid his money.
Once things quiet down,
I'll secretly spend his money.
Easy-peasy.
You can call me Maharani.
You almost got beaten to death,
yet you still...
The worst person in this
is really you.
Just don't come to me
and beg for a new bag.
Anyway, I'm happy you get to
turn over a new leaf.
Thank you so much
for not abandoning me.
And congratulations for your success
in dealing with It's family.
I guess I didn't do anything.
- Aw!
- I'm sorry.
I didn't expect
I'd land you in such a mess.
I love you.
I've learned a lot from it.
Nothing can be gained
without giving something away.
And I won't take the easy,
sneaky way to earn money again.
Our lives are going to be full
of good things and happiness now!
- Whoo!
We're going to be rich!
Ma, thank you so much
for everything you've done for me.
And what are you going to do now?
You're not going
to leave me, are you?
Gee, where would I go?
All I did was move.
I think I'll do things
I can handle from now on.
I want to help kids in need.
I might go and give
free music lessons in the slums.
At least it might provide them
with an opportunity.
That's probably all I can do.
An opportunity can
help change a lot of people's
lives for the better.
As for me,
I won't go anywhere either.
I'll stay here and look after you
for the rest of our lives,
no matter our relationship status.
I promise I'll never leave you.
Thanks so much.
Oh, right.
This is for you.
- Thanks.
- Mm.
I think it's time
you moved on from him.
His family is
facing a lot of lawsuits.
We shouldn't risk
our family's reputation.
It's good that things
turned out this way.
I'm actually happier.
I'm finally getting
to live the life I want.
I hope you'll finally stop using me
as leverage in business dealings.
But I'm doing everything
for your sake.
If you really want
to do things for my sake,
then can I ask for one thing?
Please give me freedom in life.
If you choose someone compatible
with me based on their wealth,
I might end up with someone
who doesn't love me again.
I'm tired of it.
I'm sorry.
I... I thought
you were happy.
I was never truly happy.
Please let me have my freedom.
I love you.
I love you very much.
Hello?
Why did you call me so many times?
Can you take me somewhere?
Where?
Anywhere you want to take me to.
Risa?
Where are you going?
You promised
you'd let me live my life freely.
Let's go.
(One Year Later)
(Psychological Assessments)
- Akin.
- Yes?
Your condition has improved a lot.
And I believe it's going to
keep improving.
Thank you.
I admire that you've
started new things on your own.
As for the young patients
receiving psychiatric treatment
as part of your project,
their lives have
improved a lot as well.
I think childhood is
the most important time
because it's the starting point
of everything.
Right, I completely forgot.
Do you mind if I have
a look at your hand?
Oh, sure.
That's great. There's no mark.
- All right. I have to get back.
- Sure.
It was coincidental when we met
for the very first time as kids.
But the reunion was my intention.
But from now on,
I guess it's up to destiny.
I hope that
if we get to see each other again,
it won't be to hurt each other
and leave our hearts wounded.