Evil
is always more stubborn and cunning than humans imagine.
But humans also possess gentleness and precious qualities
and emotions capable of overcoming evil.
They're researchers.
Ah, forget it.
Just a researcher.
Don't waste any more time.
The shell-changing lab is just ahead.
Everyone, hurry!
Go!
Run!
Stop!
We'll hold them off.
You go stop the shell-changing.
You really are a persistent rat, aren't you?
Perfect.
It's time we settled the score between us.
Settle the score?
Do you really have what it takes?
This body is actually quite useful.
Hurry, go! Go!
Go, quickly!
Hurry, hurry!
Enough.
Blue Team No. 12 is out.
Red Team No. 7 is out.
Old Huang, you're serious about this.
All this just for a small outpost.
Why?
You want to take me down with you?
The situation on the battlefield changes in an instant.
Sometimes, it's even for a tiny outpost.
It can be the key to victory or defeat.
Alright, alright, alright.
You're impressive, you're a hero.
You'd sacrifice yourself for victory.
You owe me a drink later.
Otherwise, I can't let this go.
Then you have to get over it.
If we ever meet on the battlefield one day,
would you strike so ruthlessly?
Hard to say.
How is it going?
Wait a moment.
Let's keep a memento.
Do you want it?
I really...
Do you want it or not?
It's already at ninety-eight percent.
Is there a way to stop it?
I'm constantly refreshing the backend code.
I hope I can find an overlap.
So I can reverse and shut down the system.
Is it done?
Found it.
How much longer?
How is it going?
That's impossible.
I've already shut down the machine.
Qingyun.
He's dead.
You promised me you'd save him.
I'm sorry.
Save him, please save him again.
Qingyun.
What should we do?
What are we supposed to do?
Do you know how serious this is?
Don't worry.
Huang Hai's goal is clearly different from theirs.
What exactly does he want to do?
And who's behind him?
He won't even let me go.