♪By the small window♪
♪She is grooming herself♪
♪A fleeting dream at night
brings me back home♪
♪Through willows glows the sinking sun♪
♪Over walls so still and bare♪
♪A few faint strokes remain,
shadows of words♪
♪In my twilight years,
I yearn for what is lost♪
♪I try not to remember♪
♪How far we were apart♪
♪But forgetting is hard, with nowhere
to talk my cold thoughts out♪
♪We looked at each other, silent,
lines of tears coursing down♪
♪Now I gaze alone at the full moon,
entranced by its wistful beauty♪
[Agarwood Like a Dream]
[Episode 16]
You asked me to come back today.
Is it because you know Buhan
didn't return to the mansion last night?
Wearing winter clothes in autumn,
it seems you've truly been living
a lonely and bitter life
in Ye's Mansion.
I lack both the authority
to manage the household
and Buhan's love,
so life in the inner chambers
is lonely and helpless.
But I didn't painstakingly arrange
for you to marry into Ye's Mansion
just for you to be consumed by jealousy
and waste away in the inner chambers!
Without the love of Buhan,
how could I possibly find my footing
in the Ye family?
Even if this strategy doesn't work,
there are other ways.
There are many ways to win.
But I've been in love
with Buhan for many years
and have tried everything.
If you have a solution,
then take care of it yourself.
Do you know
why I must acquire Qixiang Pavilion?
Of course, I know.
The Bai family may currently
be the richest in Shangjing.
But just because our wealth
was built in only two generations,
we are seen as less
than those with century-old enterprises.
What my father and I
strove for but couldn't achieve,
they were born into.
How is that fair?
Our father chose Qixiang Pavilion
after much consideration
as an opportunity to change our destiny.
After all, Qixiang Pavilion
has lasted over ten generations
and is one of the Five Great Businesses
in Shangjing.
Among them,
only fragrance materials
are something the Bai family
can strategically control.
Given my situation in the Ye family,
how could I possibly talk about
taking control of Qixiang Pavilion?
If someone of the Bai family's lineage
inherited Qixiang Pavilion,
we would be able
to improve our status much sooner.
But Ms. Chen is a master
at captivating hearts.
Now that she's back at Qixiang Pavilion
making incense,
if she bears Buhan's child before me,
how could I possibly control
the Ye family?
All you need to do
is hand this letter to Madam Ye.
After staying up for several nights,
you and Master
have finally created
the incense Her Highness wanted.
No,
don't go.
Don't leave me.
He's burning up.
I'll go get a physician.
Don't leave.
Okay.
I won't leave.
The weather is really nice today.
Please take a seat.
Anyuan,
it's such a relief to see you and Buhan
back on good terms.
If you can have a child with him,
I'll feel at ease
handing the family business over to you.
Grandmother.
I...
Are you feeling unwell?
I might have caught a chill.
Madam, bad news.
What's going on?
Just now, we received news
from Lord Wen's Mansion.
After Lord Wen
used the medicinal incense
sent by Ms. Chen,
he suddenly fainted.
Now, Her Highness is furious,
the imperial physicians are
with Lord Wen, diagnosing his condition.
Hurry,
get the carriage ready.
I'll go to Lord Wen's Mansion.
Yes, Madam.
Grandmother,
I believe you should not intervene
at this moment.
From what I can tell,
since he collapsed suddenly
after using the medicinal incense,
if the issue
really lies with the incense,
it's most likely that someone's trying
to harm the Qixiang Pavilion.
The priority now
is to find out who this person is.
I've suspected something was off
ever since the incident
at Ye's Mansion.
Confess now!
What exactly did you put
in the medicine incense for Lord Wen?
I hold no grudges against Lord Wen,
so why would I harm him?
It's you
who have repeatedly
made things difficult for me.
We've inspected it.
The medicinal incense
sent to Lord Wen's Mansion
is the same as the one you have left.
It's the incense you made.
Now, you can't say that it was me
who added musk to harm you.
If you're set on blaming me,
there's always a pretext.
I didn't do it,
so why should I confess?
Because you are Ying Hemeng.
Your mother took her own life
in this very room out of guilt.
This is why you resent the Ye family
and have caused trouble over and over.
My mother was killed by the Ye family!
If it weren't for the tricks
you used back then,
how could she have never had the chance
to step into the courtroom
and die here of illness?
Torture and forced confessions
are exactly
what the Ye family excels at!
Shut up!
Use the wet paper.
Meng!
Madam,
Master is here.
Where's Meng?
What's the matter?
I just need to ask her
a couple of questions.
Grandmother,
Ying Hemeng
is your granddaughter.
I named her Hemeng,
and gave her the surname Ying,
after my beloved.
The full name of my daughter
is Ying Hemeng.
This is a handwritten letter
from your father.
♪Familiar yet strange sights♪
♪The tale's first light♪
♪Growing with time's flow♪
♪Somber and mournful grief♪
♪The final act, my swan song as a bait♪
♪Has freed the heart from all desires♪
♪As I dance with wolves,
love lies hidden deep♪
♪The scented sachet,
a memory that never fades♪
♪With every passing day,
our love simmers and ignites♪
♪The ache born
from our ephemeral meetings♪
♪Etched upon the canvas of my heart♪
♪How to untangle
this lasting, aching desire♪
♪In the face of such a bewitching gaze?♪
♪Soft melodies caress locked windows,
reaching out to the setting sun♪
♪Gently adorning with twilight's charm♪
♪My remaining breaths,
the thoughts that they bear♪
♪The vision of you,
the one that fills my mind♪