♪By the small window♪
♪She is grooming herself♪
♪A fleeting dream at night
brings me back home♪
♪Through willows glows the sinking sun♪
♪Over walls so still and bare♪
♪A few faint strokes remain,
shadows of words♪
♪In my twilight years,
I yearn for what is lost♪
♪I try not to remember♪
♪How far we were apart♪
♪But forgetting is hard, with nowhere
to talk my cold thoughts out♪
♪We looked at each other, silent,
lines of tears coursing down♪
♪Now I gaze alone at the full moon,
entranced by its wistful beauty♪
[Agarwood Like a Dream]
[Episode 10]
This is the weapon from that day.
No murderer
would leave a weapon
engraved with their name
at the scene.
[Ying Ling]
Why didn't you expose me?
I was worried
that if you knew the truth,
you would insist
on finding the real murderer.
The murderer
killed my father unguarded
and then escaped.
They must be someone the Ye family knew.
If you act rashly,
the enemy will be alerted
and target you.
Your speculation is right.
It's from the Bai family.
Where did you get this from?
Do you remember an incense maker
called Wen Zhong when we were little?
After your father died
and my mother was framed,
the rest of the Ye family
was driven out.
Wen Zhong left with this secret.
He kept it until I met him again.
How did you go through
all these years?
When I left Ye's Mansion,
I was adrift
and begged for a living
until one day,
I met a smuggler
who sold me into a pleasure house.
I was too young
and had to stay in the backyard
doing the drudgery.
Laundry, boiling water,
cooking, and cleaning the yard.
I did all the hard work.
Meet me next time.
See you.
I am sorry.
If it wasn't for me,
you wouldn't have suffered so much.
Look at me now.
I'm living quite well.
The top courtesan in the pleasure house
thought I had a talent
for incense making
and kept me by her side.
Life became easier.
Later,
I started to make fragrances
for the girls.
Backflow incense was an invention
during that time.
Here.
That was the best meal I had ever had.
Right,
it's from the well-known
Qingyun Restaurant in Shangjing.
What you missed,
I'll make it all up to you.
That day,
I merely raised my voice a bit
when speaking to Ms. Chen,
and Buhan told me
he was going to divorce me.
How could I stay in the Ye family?
The Ye family is not for him
to make the decisions.
Grandmother,
Buhan has his struggles
and I don't wish
to make it difficult for him.
You and Buhan
grew up together,
and you are his wife
with a proper marriage
arranged by our family.
But his heart is only with her.
On the wedding day,
you saw how calculating
Ms. Chen could be.
Buhan is still young
and can be unsure about his feelings.
I shouldn't ask
about your intimate life,
but it's been months
since your wedding day.
Have you spent any nights
with Buhan?
A woman's status rises with her child.
The priority now
is to bear a child.
But Buhan won't even enter my room.
How could I...?
Do not worry.
I have my plans.
Egg yolk pastry,
Osmanthus cakes,
Drunken Crab in Huadiao Wine,
and steamed smoked venison
are all signature dishes
of the Qingyun Restaurant.
The delicacies were once out of reach,
and now,
I can finally taste them.
The pastry looks lovely.
It's sweet, not overwhelming,
but it breaks easily.
That's like
all the beautiful things in life.
They always slip away too quickly.
The crust is flaky,
but the inside is soft yet resilient.
Just like
how Chen Rumeng appeared
after I searched for Ying Hemeng
for ten years
and found she had died.
You hid the box on the lower floor
of the Southwest Pavilion
and carried the key with you every day.
I thought it was
a secret Qixiang Pavilion formula.
I didn't expect it
to be the Ruyi seal I put in the coffin.
I remember us making incense together
when we were children.
The way you smiled
was adorable.
Turns out
you had your eye on me all along.
It was you who bumped into my arms
and enticed me with incense powder.
Did you not fall for it?
I was playing along.
I've long admired you.
Would you do me
the honor of becoming my wife?
Would you bear children
and grow old with me?
Would you be willing
to drink this couple's toast with me?
Master,
Ms. Chen,
Madam would like to speak with Master.
Wait for me.
The meal is ready.
Madam is detained
but will be here shortly.
Please have a rest
in the room.
Where's Grandmother?
Buhan,
it's been months since we married.
You haven't dined
alone with me.
Let's get a divorce.
If you have someone you like,
I can help you arrange a match.
I only wish to be your wife.
What did you put in the tea?
You really...
have no feelings for me at all.
I didn't expect Grandmother
to make this happen for us.
♪Familiar yet strange sights♪
♪The tale's first light♪
♪Growing with time's flow♪
♪Somber and mournful grief♪
♪The final act, my swan song as a bait♪
♪Has freed the heart from all desires♪
♪As I dance with wolves,
love lies hidden deep♪
♪The scented sachet,
a memory that never fades♪
♪With every passing day,
our love simmers and ignites♪
♪The ache born
from our ephemeral meetings♪
♪Etched upon the canvas of my heart♪
♪How to untangle
this lasting, aching desire♪
♪In the face of such a bewitching gaze?♪
♪Soft melodies caress locked windows,
reaching out to the setting sun♪
♪Gently adorning with twilight's charm♪
♪My remaining breaths,
the thoughts that they bear♪
♪The vision of you,
the one that fills my mind♪