You smell of cigarettes.
Should we continue after I brush my teeth?
What?
The others must be waiting. Let's go back.
I did it.
EPISODE 3: IT HAS ALREADY BEGUN.
NEVERTHELESS,
What is this emotion?
I hope it's just love.
Not childish jealousy.
Something seems to be going on
between Na-bi and Jae-eon, right?
-Why do you say so?
-Those two
disappeared for a while last night.
And it seemed like something happened
between them.
I could tell from her expression.
And I saw them whispering something
by the door early in the morning.
I couldn't hear what they said though.
Are you the only one who saw?
Yes, and I didn't tell Bit-na.
Good thing I didn't, right?
-Good thinking.
-I'm starving.
The noodles are here.
It looks so good!
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
And don't say anything to Na-bi.
Don't worry.
I'm going to steal this from you!
Would it be okay though?
What? Your belly fat?
No! I mean Na-bi.
She's probably having a hard time
after breaking up with her ex.
She could get involved in gossip
by hanging out with him.
I don't think
she should be seeing Jae-eon.
Really?
I think Jae-eon is better than her ex.
What? Really? Why?
I don't know. I can just feel it.
They look good together.
Got drunk and kissed…
RECENT SEARCHES
KISSING SOMEONE BEFORE DATING
I GOT DRUNK AND KISSED MY FRIEND
WHO I HAVE NO FEELINGS FOR
I MADE A MISTAKE WHILE DRUNK
EVERYONE THINKS WEIRDLY OF ME
I GOT DRUNK AND KISSED MY FRIEND
WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
WE NEVER TALKED ABOUT IT AFTER
WAS IT JUST A DRUNKEN MISTAKE?
THERE'S NO TURNING BACK
ONCE YOU'VE TOUCHED FIRST BASE
YOU'LL END UP BECOMING SP
OR DRIFTING APART
"SP"?
"SP"? As in…
"Sex partners"?
Na-bi.
You startled me.
What were you looking at?
Just looking for some references.
Sol.
If you want to kiss someone,
does that mean you want
to sleep with them as well?
Are you asking about me?
Or is it about you?
What? Me?
No, it's not about me.
I mean, generally. I just want to know
how people usually feel.
I'm just trying to come up
with an idea for my assignment.
I'm not sure.
I guess it'll depend on
who the other person is.
The other person…
SEOL-A
I just got on the plane!
One-night…
I'm not sure.
I guess it'll depend on
who the other person is.
"The other person"?
You may want to kiss and have sex
with someone,
or you might kiss someone
and not want to go further.
So in the end, it depends
on who the other person is.
Then what kind of person
am I to him?
ONE-NIGHT STAND?
PARK JAE-EON
SHOULDN'T WE TALK ABOUT YESTERDAY?
Would I seem too clingy?
-Hey!
-Hi!
Hey, Na-bi.
Hi.
My battery's dead again.
Maybe I should get a new phone.
-Where's Ji-wan?
-She's meeting someone.
-What are you doing?
-I need a charger.
She's watching a movie
with her blind date.
She doesn't care much about school.
Let's see…
I want to ask
what I should say to get Jae-eon
to tell me how he really feels about me.
Do you really like that guy?
-Yes.
-You don't look that way.
Do you dance excitedly
whenever you like someone's post?
That's different though.
Why would you sleep with someone
you're not even dating?
Isn't that meaningless?
Gosh.
Why do you always associate sex
with dating? Are you that old-fashioned?
-Watch your mouth.
-Lower your voice!
-Someone might hear you.
-I'm not saying anything wrong.
I can say it even louder! Should I?
Let's begin class!
All right, let's begin class.
-Hello, Professor.
-Hello.
Try this.
-You're not with your cute friend today.
-She's hanging out with someone else.
She must be having fun.
I'll get you your food right away.
Thank you. Give us a large serving.
All right.
You must be a regular here.
Yes. My friend loves this place.
But this place is quite famous
in this neighborhood.
Danpunggol was the most popular
when I was in school.
You went to school here?
Yes. I was an Economics major.
-I graduated two years ago.
-I see.
I'm really sorry about last time.
I put in an estimated amount.
Tell me if it's not enough.
It's really fine.
It's okay. Keep it.
This isn't why I asked to see you.
Sorry? Then why…
Here's your food.
It's hot, so be careful. Enjoy.
Thank you.
-What's wrong?
-You're really strong.
Do you work out?
Oh, I major in sculpture.
I always work with clay,
so I have a lot of strength in my hands.
Just buy me this meal. That's enough.
I wouldn't feel comfortable with that.
-Then buy me coffee, too.
-I'll buy dessert as well.
Okay.
-Like this?
-Yes.
-Do it like that.
-Thank you.
That's it for today.
-Thank you!
The weather is so nice today.
You should all go on a date.
-Okay.
-Come on.
Why aren't you answering?
Don't tell me you guys are all single.
You should at least
have one proper relationship at your age.
What they say about art
coming from loneliness is nonsense.
Dating is the best way
to get inspiration for art.
She's at it again.
Didn't she say class was over?
Love is what can make
even the roughest person become
as soft as sand on a beach.
I can't believe you guys.
You guys are art majors, you know.
They have no inspiration.
One student told me a while ago
that he doesn't want a relationship.
He just wants to flirt and date around.
Basically, he wants to have fun
with no strings attached.
He should have one-night stands instead.
It's so sad, isn't it?
Goodness.
Find your inspirations, all right?
-Yes, ma'am.
-That's what art is.
-Thank you.
-Goodbye.
-Thank you for today.
PARK YE-SOM, KANG SEO-YEON, LEE YE-HWA
YU NA-BI
I'M BUYING ART SUPPLIES.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING NOW?
Jae-eon.
Welcome back.
You've gotten more handsome.
You must've enjoyed it, Ji-wan.
Yes, it was so fun.
It was much better than I expected.
-I want to watch it again with my friend.
-Your friend?
-It's not a guy, right?
-It's a girl, of course.
Her name's Sol. She's been my bestie
since middle school.
I think she'll enjoy it, too.
I'll watch it with her.
Then Ji-wan,
watch it again with me next time, too.
Well, okay.
But you didn't seem to enjoy it
as much as I did.
I really enjoyed it too.
It wasn't what I expected though.
-What do you mean?
-I thought it would be about romance,
but it was about friendship.
Oh. Friendship?
I felt that it was clearly about love,
but I guess you could've seen it that way.
Still, it was good.
If you're hungry, should we go eat?
Yes. I'm really hungry.
I said I'd buy. Why did you pay?
Well, I didn't think it'd be enough
to repay me.
I knew it.
Can you pay next time?
I'd like to see you again.
Why?
It was fun hearing about your projects.
-You ate…
-I eat quite a lot.
Hey, it's Sol.
She's the friend I just told you about.
That's strange.
I'm not really a smooth talker.
No, I really enjoyed listening to you.
Who's that next to her?
Where are you headed now?
I'm taking the bus here.
-I'll come with you.
-No, I can go by myself.
Why don't you try calling her?
No, it's fine.
You two must be really close.
Yes.
Let's go.
SCULPTURE STUDIO 3
I'm so hungry.
Jae-eon still isn't contacting me.
I don't know if he just doesn't care
about me or if he's teasing me.
But whichever it is,
it sucks.
I hate to admit it,
but I can't take my eyes off him
once he comes into my sight.
Hey, Seol-a.
I knew it was you.
Hang on. I'll be there soon.
Who is Seol-a?
Seol-a.
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
-It's okay.
-Who is she…
-Should we get something to drink?
-to make him smile…
-Okay.
-like that?
-Let's go.
You're so pathetic, Na-bi.
You're acting like a stalker.
I could tell right away.
She's the one Jae-eon's heart belongs to.
Welcome.
Oh, Na-bi!
I sat next to you yesterday.
You stole my water, remember?
Oh, that's my water.
Oh, right. The freshman.
Your name is Kang Eun-han, right?
It's Kim Eun-han.
You're bad at remembering people.
Sorry, there were
so many people yesterday.
Do you work here?
Yes. Just in the evenings. I just started.
Was it fun last night?
I wanted to hang out longer,
but I had to come and work.
You haven't had dinner?
No. I was working on my assignment.
In that case. I was saving this,
but you can have it.
No, it's fine. You should have it.
It's okay.
I want you to have it.
Thanks.
I'll enjoy this.
Good luck with work, then.
Na-bi.
Can you give me your phone?
-My phone?
-Yes.
Do you know them?
You keep looking at them.
A freshman in our department.
He must work there.
Not him.
Is that girl a freshman, too?
Here's my number.
-I'll contact you later.
-Okay.
No. She's my senior.
Or maybe a friend.
-Take care, then.
-Bye.
-See you later.
-See you.
You're still using that?
-What about you?
-Me?
I lost it a long time ago.
That's disappointing.
How are your butterflies doing?
They're fine.
But I'm going to set them free soon.
Why?
I feel guilty.
They're supposed to be free,
but they're locked up
because of me.
You've grown up.
That girl…
Her name's Na-bi.
So you haven't grown up.
You just found another butterfly.
It's not like that.
She's just a friend.
You're lying.
Even her name is Na-bi.
Is it fate?
Don't be ridiculous.
You're my fate.
GRANDSON OF A NOODLE SHOP OWNER
SLICE THE GREEN ONIONS
NEW MESSAGE FROM KIM EUN-HAN
Hello, Na-bi!
It's Kim Eun-han from a moment ago.
He messaged me right away.
Right. Hi.
Are you coming to the flea market?
I'm serving at our booth!
Or you can come to the after-party.
I hope you'll come.
Okay, then.
Really? Then I'll see you there!
To be honest, it doesn't feel bad.
By the way, are there days
when you don't have class?
Oh, was that too personal?
My apologies.
Good night. See you at the festival!
Sadly, I have class every day.
Good night.
PARK JAE-EON
Jae-eon!
No way! You can do glass art, too?
What are you making?
What?
Oh, I'm making a suncatcher.
It's so pretty.
You're making a butterfly again.
You really love butterflies, don't you?
What? Do you have a cold?
Stay away from me.
I don't know. I have a headache.
Are you sick from quitting Jae-eon?
Withdrawal symptoms?
What are you on about?
You haven't been hanging out with him.
Is it over now?
I don't think we really click.
I'm disappointed.
The quiet kids usually end up causing
huge trouble.
That disappoints you?
Of course. I was looking forward to
some drama. This is so boring.
You seem to want to push me into
Hell's pit just for your entertainment.
Come on, don't say it like that.
Like when you all came to my house.
Why did you have to talk about
testing him and stuff?
What about it?
Why? Did something happen
between you two that day?
I mean, it was useless
because nothing happened.
You saw what it was like.
Do you know what you need
to catch a big fish, Na-bi?
You're going to say "patience," right?
And he's not even a catch.
He isn't?
Well, it depends.
Anyhow, are you sure he doesn't date?
I'm sure. I told you.
Why? Did he ask you out?
No, it seemed like he was dating someone.
But maybe I'm mistaken.
Na-bi! Hi!
-Hi.
Hi, Eun-han. Are you going to eat lunch?
-Yes.
-Enjoy your lunch.
-You too.
-Okay.
What was that with Eun-han?
We got close recently.
Is there something about him, too?
No. Not that I know of.
I knew it. You're receiving attention
as soon as you come out of your bubble.
Gosh, but Eun-han's a bit boring.
Leave me out of your fun, okay?
So you're thinking of seeing him?
It's not like that.
This is a bit disappointing.
Hi.
You should get some vitamins.
Thanks.
How is that going?
It's bad. I'm screwed this semester.
No way. You're so good.
What do you know?
I know quite a lot.
I actually saw your piece when I was here
for the entrance exam last year.
Last year?
Then it would have been…
LOVE
YU NA-BI
"Love"?
"Yu Na-bi."
-The one about love?
-Yes.
I got scolded for making the same thing
over and over.
I loved it. I even took a photo.
Let me see.
There aren't many pieces
that depict love just as it is.
Everyone thinks they have to
make it look cool.
Where is it?
Oh, right. I got a new phone.
Na-bi. Could I see it again?
I promise to back up my photos.
-Well…
-Yes?
I threw it away.
-Really?
-Because my ex was the inspiration.
Is it really not here?
Thanks.
For what?
To be honest, I gave up on the piece
I was working on,
and I didn't know what to do.
But you cheered me up.
He does seem pretty cute.
But it's a bit awkward
since you're talking so formally to me.
Just talk casually.
It's hard for me to do that
to people older than me.
Oh, really?
All right, then. Whatever you prefer.
No. I'll talk casually
from now on.
Okay.
Na-bi, everyone said this movie was good.
Did you watch it?
No, I didn't. I haven't been
to a movie theater in a while.
Do you want to watch it with me?
-Is it a romantic movie?
-Yes.
Hi.
Hello.
Oh, hi.
What are you two talking about?
We're going to watch a movie together.
Should we watch something else, then?
-Well…
-Hey.
You're talking casually to her?
Were you two close?
Yes. We're close.
Closer than you and me, anyway.
Let's watch this, Eun-han.
I like romantic movies.
Okay, then.
Hey.
Isn't this erotic?
That's better, then.
Let's watch it.
Right. You'll need a reference.
What do you mean?
The male lead.
He's a good kisser.
Na-bi's fussy about kisses.
Be careful because she'll push you away
if she doesn't like it.
See me outside.
-What was that about?
-What?
Why would you
suddenly mention kissing? Hey.
Stop playing games with me.
Playing games? You're the one
who pushed my hand away.
I never let you touch my shoulder.
There's nothing between us, you know.
-Why are you so upset?
-I'm not upset!
I'm not upset.
You never contacted me since that day.
You know that?
You didn't, either.
And what's so wrong about that?
I'm sorry,
but I'm not that kind of person.
What do you mean by that?
I thought you were enjoying it.
Don't worry.
I won't try anything with you.
Good luck with Eun-han.
Fine.
Well, you left your phone…
Right. Thanks.
Na-bi.
Should we go watch the movie?
All right.
Na-bi.
I like butterflies
way more than dragonflies.
You didn't eat, right?
This place is really amazing. Try it.
And you don't seem to be
in a good mood. So eat up.
You should eat to cheer up.
You should eat too.
-Here, have some water.
-Thank you.
Na-bi. That's my water.
Stop that!
-You seemed to like water.
-Stop it.
This is it.
Going on a date in the daytime.
-Right.
-Sweet and innocent attraction.
I saw it!
-"Miracle"?
-"Past"?
That's great.
-It's open.
-Yes! It's open!
Could you take a photo of us?
Thank you.
All right, then. One, two.
Can I have a combo set, please?
Which flavor would you like?
Well…
Eating and watching a movie together,
like a normal date.
Something that suits me perfectly.
Come on, just once.
One, two, three.
It's a good photo. Let me take one of you.
Let's eat.
Here.
Enjoy your meal.
This is really good.
-Is it?
-Yes.
Why do I…
still have this on my phone?
Na-bi.
I didn't know what you'd like,
so I got everything.
Oh, okay.
-Should I buy more?
-No, it's fine. Thanks.
This is really tasty.
Will things keep piling up like this?
I was a loser who was always running away.
But I can't run away from you.
I like everything about you,
and I can't stop thinking about you.
I…
I love you.
What are you thinking, Na-bi?
I wasn't thinking of anything. Why?
You didn't seem to be in a good mood
since we were in the theater.
-So I thought you didn't like the movie.
-Well…
I'm just not feeling too good.
It was a bit too cheesy, right?
Really?
I enjoyed it a lot.
It made me want to have
a relationship like that too.
I suddenly got that feeling…
Actually, I heard you and Jae-eon earlier.
Oh, I see.
-But he's…
-I know. It's over now, right?
"Over"?
You know that he only hurts other people.
Don't let someone who was never sincere
toward you hurt you.
I know…
what it's like. But it's all meaningless.
And most of all,
you two don't suit each other.
All right.
Okay.
Sorry, Eun-han.
I…
I was about to sneeze.
Forget it.
I really did! Eun-han!
He is pretty cute, but…
Are you with someone?
Because you're cute.
I just don't feel a spark with him
like I did with Jae-eon.
PARK JAE-EON
DELETE
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO
DELETE THIS CONTACT?
DELETE
PAINKILLER
What do you mean?
You heard me.
The landlord said you can't get
an extension.
But why?
I should've been notified
at least three months in advance, then.
-Whatever. I relayed the message.
-Excuse me!
What the heck?
Darn it.
Oh, my gosh!
-Na-bi!
-Hello!
Hey, you look really good in that.
Thank you, my lady.
Are you not coming to our booth?
I'm okay. How are the preparations going?
I'm sure it's going great.
They have Jae-eon.
My friends said they're coming,
but there might not be seats.
-You have friends?
-Of course I do!
So what will you do?
Can you find a house within a month?
If I can't, I'll have to find
a small studio or something.
Or some housemates.
What about all your stuff?
I guess I'll have to use
a storage service.
Darn it! What do I do?
The rent is expensive around here now.
It'll be impossible to find
another place with cheap rent.
I'm screwed!
Hey, calm down.
How much was the rent?
-Hello!
-Hi.
-Can we have more butane?
And where can we get more folding chairs?
In the clubroom.
Oh, right.
Tell Sol not to come to the booth.
She'll run into Professor Lee
and get nagged to death.
Why would she get nagged?
Don't you know?
The exchange program.
It's really exhausting for me, too.
She'll get a full scholarship.
What's holding her back?
Some people are dying to go.
It's not an easy decision to make though.
Here you go.
Exchange program?
What? You didn't know?
-No.
-How did you not know?
All the professors are going.
-Let's take these.
-Okay.
Let's go.
-I'll go with them.
-Bye.
Let's go.
What's going on?
Goodness.
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
Aren't you going to the flea market?
-Are you going to see Eun-han?
-What?
I heard something's going on
between you and him.
-I heard everything.
-From Bit-na, right?
I'm glad.
I don't know him well,
but he's way better than Jae-eon.
Last time, when the professor
called you and Sol…
It was because
of the exchange program, right?
Well…
Yes.
I see.
But Bit-na didn't hear from Sol, either.
Sol was probably thinking
of telling you first.
And I only heard when I met
the professor with her.
I don't know.
I bet she didn't tell me
because I'd feel upset.
Did I tell you before?
I started art because of Sol.
Really?
I didn't know.
She wanted to major in art
since she was in middle school.
And I worked so hard to join her.
I thought I'd at least be able
to keep up with her if I did my best.
But I guess there are things
you can never do.
I can barely get my assignments done.
I don't even know if I can graduate.
I'm so jealous of her.
That kind of presence
only comes naturally.
Right.
Some people are gifted like that.
Let's go to the flea market.
-All right. Let's go.
-Let's go.
SCULPTURE DEPARTMENT FLEA MARKET
Is everything going okay?
All right, the next two people. Come in.
She's just not my type.
Why is he here?
I know, right? He's not even here to help.
-He's not even paying.
-Right.
He's just here to watch us.
-That looks nice.
-No.
-Here you go.
-Can I…
have your number?
Sorry.
What was that? Namaste?
-I should use this gesture too.
-Where would you use that?
Hey, let's go.
Why? You wanted to come.
It's too noisy and crowded in here.
-And there aren't any pretty girls.
-But there are.
Let's just go. Come on.
Hey, they're leaving.
-What a relief.
-Why's he leaving?
-You're leaving?
-Yes!
Hey, they're gone. Go and serve the food.
Gosh. It's a festival,
but they're not selling drinks, Professor.
This is unbelievable.
-He really is popular, isn't he?
-This place is so nice.
-You're so handsome.
-Thank you.
-You must be tired.
-Can I have your number?
-Sorry.
-They're all smiling from ear to ear.
-Are you two dating?
-What? No!
Why are you overreacting?
Kids like you always end up dating.
Professor, that's never going to happen.
Watch what you say.
It could really happen.
No way. Hey, Jin-su. Come over here.
Professor, this is…
By the way,
that student over there.
He's Park Jae-eon, right?
-Yes.
I remember him since he's very competent.
I should get going.
-Have fun.
-All right.
-Don't cause any trouble.
-Okay.
-Jin-su will show you out.
-I'll escort you.
Okay. I have some work
to finish up, so I'll get going.
-Bye, then.
-I'll see you later.
-Bye.
-Don't cause any trouble.
Bye, Professor.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
I thought she'd leave
like three hours ago.
So she remembers him
because of his competency?
I bet she remembers him
because he's so handsome.
Hey, where did you steal this?
We can't sell alcohol here.
I bought it at a convenience store.
Can't I even do that?
You're going to drink at the after-party.
Can't you hold yourself back?
Seriously, you nag more than my mom.
If you get drunk today, I'm really
going to abandon you on the streets.
That looks delicious.
Hey, Ji-wan! Over here.
Hey! You got really good seats.
Why don't you join us?
I'll introduce you to them.
No, I'm fine. Have fun.
Then call me if you get bored.
Okay.
-Have fun.
-Okay.
When did you come?
You should've called me.
ARTISTS THAT SHINE
LOOKING FOR ARTISTS-IN-RESIDENCE
This is the usual serving.
But I added more
since you seemed like you'd eat a lot.
Eun-han.
Hey, Na-bi.
There are so many people.
-Our department's the most crowded.
-Right. Well…
-Are you here with anyone?
-What?
There are so many people.
I didn't think it'd get so crowded.
Maybe you should just go somewhere else.
No, I just came to see you for a moment.
As I promised.
Right.
Eun-han!
When do you get off?
We're thinking of getting drinks.
Who is she? Your friend?
She's a senior that I'm close with.
Oh, hello.
Right. Hi.
Well, why don't you go ahead first?
I'll join you after I finish.
Okay. Call me when you're done.
All right.
-I'll see you later, then.
-It's not like that.
I've liked her since I was in high school,
but she rejected me.
And she suddenly contacted me yesterday…
I'm really sorry.
All right.
Let's begin the game. Se-hun?
-All right. Let's spin the wheel!
-Spin the wheel!
-That looks fun.
-Let's try that later.
Speed quiz!
-Is it only for couples?
-I don't think so.
By the way, that guy has a crush
on Sol, right?
You got it right!
-Right or…
-Wrong.
How would I know?
I'm sure of it. I told him we were
Sol's friends,
and he gave us so much food.
Sol's not that close to him.
Well, since you two are so close.
Don't you get sick of each other?
We don't hang out as much as we did
these days.
Right. You've been dating a lot.
-Spin the wheel!
-Spin!
-But I kind of feel sorry for him.
If Sol goes to the States, she'll be
hanging out with hot American guys.
Wasn't she going to England?
It seemed like she was going to Europe.
Is she really going though? When?
How did you guys know?
What do you mean?
Can I have some of your juice?
-Here.
-Thanks.
Hey, there's Sol!
She's with someone though.
Hey, Sol!
Isn't he the guy from the café?
Hey, I think he is.
Hi, I'm Jung Ju-hyeok.
-Hi!
-Hi.
Is he your boyfriend, Sol?
No.
Have you been seeing each other
since then?
I had business nearby, and I asked her
to show me around school.
-Let's go!
-Let's go play a couple's game!
-A couple's game!
-Couple's game!
All right.
-Let's…
-Sol!
Sol! Come play…
Are you…
Are you two a couple?
-You're here to play the couple's game!
-Don't they look good together?
-Let me through.
-You have to throw a dart
and play the game it lands on.
That's all you have to do.
You try it.
-Me?
-Yes.
You should give up.
You're no match to him.
Okay, let's go.
Se-hun, spin the wheel.
All right, I'll spin the wheel.
Spin the wheel!
Oh, it's "Pop the Balloon"!
The most exciting game.
-What is it?
-You two, come over here.
I can't believe Sol's hanging out with
a guy. He's really handsome, isn't he?
I'll put a balloon right here.
-What?
-Stick together like this.
And pop it with your bodies.
You succeed if you pop it in five seconds.
All right, let's begin.
Ready, go.
You did it! Congratulations!
Take your prize.
-There's a prize?
-Take your pick.
Did Sol tell you anything?
No, she didn't.
She said they're not dating.
It doesn't seem like that.
I can totally tell from the guy's face.
Why else would he have come here?
There's nothing to see.
He just came to take a look around.
Sol's so lucky.
You know how they say
you'll get really lucky with men
after you have no one for a while.
It's an undeniable truth, you know.
She said they're not dating.
-Why are you giving me this?
-You like that character.
I don't like it anymore.
Is there something going on?
We were supposed to hang out together.
Why did you bring a guy along?
Oh…
I…
Well…
Sorry. I didn't think
it would make you uncomfortable.
If I knew, I would've brought a guy too.
Did you enjoy playing the couple's game?
I need to smoke.
-Hey.
-What's with you?
Lime?
I think you'll like it.
-Me?
-You said so at the club.
You remember that?
You must be exhausted.
Good work.
But the after-party begins now,
so let's go have fun!
You're all going to get wasted today!
-Guys, take this.
-Thanks!
-Move!
-Move over!
Gosh, my head.
I should go buy medicine.
I've liked her since I was in high school,
but she rejected me.
And she suddenly contacted me yesterday.
I'm really sorry.
So I was just a replacement?
Whatever. I don't care now.
But…
She suddenly contacted me yesterday.
I'm really sorry.
So embarrassing…
Who is this?
Hello?
What are you doing?
Park Jae-eon?
Wait.
Did you delete my number?
Well…
Why did you call?
What's wrong with your voice?
Are you sick?
I'm not feeling well.
I'm near your house right now.
So?
Why would you come here?
My friend lives nearby.
Okay. Have fun.
Na-bi.
Yes?
Do you want to meet right now?
Right now?
So cold.
Why don't they have any medicine?
There must've been an accident.
-There's even a police car.
-Is someone hurt?
-What's going on?
-Why is there a police car?
Was there an accident?
Is it a student?
-A student lives there.
-Excuse me.
EMERGENCY RESPONSE
-The third floor?
-Isn't that her?
Hey! Can you hear me?
I think something happened to her! Hurry!
Calm down and stay back.
We should open it.
-Hurry.
-Wait!
Wait, sir. Wait!
What are you doing? Who called you?
I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-It's fine. We'll get going.
You know you totally overreacted, right?
I was just worried.
You said you were sick.
Plus, you live alone.
All right.
Well, you know that I'm alive now.
Bye.
Are you really okay?
I'm fine.
You have a fever.
Let's go to the hospital.
It's fine.
I'll be fine if I get some sleep.
Bye.
Hey.
Let's go. Come on.
Everyone left.
I'm really leaving.
Get a grip.
Don't you know how late it is?
What are you doing?
Come on, let's--
Shut up.
You kind of…
look…
handsome up close.
Was I too cold?
No.
I did the right thing.
I should just get some sleep.
Who is it?
Can I come in?
Oh, sure.
There weren't any pharmacies open,
so I went to a convenience store.
Take some medicine after you eat.
Okay. Thanks.
Get some sleep, then. Bye.
You really came back because of this?
Hey, Jae-eon.
I don't like this.
Take it back.
I'm hungry.
You didn't even eat until this hour?
I didn't have an appetite
since I smelled food all day.
But I'm hungry now.
Then you can eat this here.
This is really tasty.
-I haven't had homemade food in a while.
-My aunt made all this.
The aunt who named you?
Yes.
You must be sleepy.
Yes. Probably because of the medicine.
I'm so sleepy now.
-Go lie down.
-It's fine.
I'll sleep after you leave.
I ate your food,
so let me help you.
What?
Hey! What are you doing?
Hey, let me down.
Wait!
"There was a boy in the small store.
He waited for the girl every day."
What are you doing?
Go home now.
I'll go home when you fall asleep.
Don't worry.
It's worse to see you gone
when I wake up later.
Should I stay, then?
I didn't mean that…
Right. I don't want you to leave.
You're really weird.
The way you talk, and the things you do…
You even called 911.
You mean you want to think of me
as a jerk,
but I actually seem okay, right?
You're so annoying.
To tell you the truth,
I was shocked when I saw you with Eun-han.
-Why?
-I don't know.
Maybe I got jealous.
You deleted my number,
but you seemed happy with him.
Then you would've felt good
when you saw me get rejected.
Save my number again.
I'm not such a bad guy, am I?
I don't know if it's because of
the fever or because of him,
but I feel so dizzy.
Why are you doing this to me?
Because my name means "butterfly"?
I've been attracted to you
from the beginning.
Oh, I see.
You're so funny, you know that?
What's so funny?
Why do you ask
if you won't even believe me?
You're not really trustworthy, you know.
Then will you see me in a different light
if I try to earn your trust?
Maybe he really…
Your fever's down.
You really nursed me
the old-fashioned way?
Classic methods are the best.
You're right.
I should get ready for school.
Why don't you leave your hair down?
-It's uncomfortable.
-Still.
Just for me.
Then…
I want to see your hair tied up.
It's pretty.
His touch and his scent.
I already got used to them.
I want to keep seeing you. What about you?
Jae-eon is too smooth with everything.
-Be my girlfriend.
-You're overreacting.
-Do you like me?
-Na-bi?
-The channel name reminded me of you.
-So you've thought about me?
I got you!
I have a gift for you.
We're much more compatible than I thought,
and I enjoy spending nights with him.
Is there someone else you're seeing?
Aren't you going overboard?
We're not even going out.
We should end it.
I don't want to let go.
Not yet.
I'm still attracted to him,
even at this moment.
Like crazy.