(What's Wrong With Secretary Kim?)
(AURA)
(A legendary secretary)
(Brother)
(Friends)
(What's Wrong With Secretary Kim?)
Didn't he look cold?
He's weak against the cold.
What if we catch a cold?
I'm fine!
I don't mean you, I mean me.
What if I catch a cold?
Oh…
That's right. You get cold easily.
I won't ever forget
your name, then!
Your name was… Lee…
Dummy, there you go again.
That's not what my name is.
My name is Lee Sung…
How was he?
How was my Hyeon?
Yes. She definitely said
"Hyeon," back then.
Did I remember it wrong
because I was so young then?
Because the pronunciation was
so similar?
Sung… Sung-hyeon?
What?
I clearly said 'Sung-hyeon,'
so why did you answer
to that name?
Mr. Lee, did you…
…Ever change your name?
Was your name
Lee Sung-hyeon in the past?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
When I talked to your mother
about the kidnapping incident,
I clearly heard her say…
…'My Hyeon.'
I want to know the truth.
Ms. Kim,
don't get so serious over
my sleeptalking.
I heard your voice,
so I just answered
like I always do.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
But he sounded so natural like
he was answering to his name.
When I talked to your mother
about the kidnapping incident,
I clearly heard her say…
…'My Hyeon.'
I want to know the truth.
Come with me.
I don’t want to go alone.
- Come with me.
- No!
You don’t need to know that.
No, oppa!
Don’t leave me.
I don't want to…
…Make you cry again.
(Episode 10)
What brings you here
so early in the morning, Ms. Kim?
Seems like something's up,
for you to come here at this time.
There's something I want to ask.
Go on.
Has… Mr. Lee ever
changed his name?
Sorry?
I clearly heard you say 'Hyeon'
last time,
and I was wondering whether
you meant Mr. Lee.
Just what…
You probably just misheard me.
No. I'm sure of it.
You clearly said,
'How was my Hyeon?'
While we were talking about
the kidnapping incident.
I don't know
what you'll think about this,
but I think this 'Hyeon'
is Mr. Lee.
Now why would you think that?
I know this is a difficult favor,
but if there's
something I still don't know,
could you please tell me?
The person you were with
when you were little is…
…Definitely my Sung-yeon.
I have no idea who
this 'Hyeon' is.
You simply misheard me.
- But…
- Ms. Kim?
I'm feeling a bit tired.
Can I ask you to leave?
Ah… yes, ma'am.
Then please excuse me.
What brings you here
so early in the morning?
I was just here to
see your mother.
Well, great timing.
I was just about to call you.
For what?
I need to return something to you,
don't I? Your diary.
Oh.
Wait right there.
I'll bring it right now.
Um…
Did my diary trigger anything?
Well…
I'm sorry.
That woman who abducted us…
You don't even remember
what she was wearing?
Or what she looked like,
or even how long her hair was?
I don’t remember a thing.
Any memories of
how you were abducted,
or how we made it out?
Anything?
Why do you ask, all of a sudden?
Well, uh…
I feel like my diary hasn't
done any good.
Because it hasn't
helped you at all.
Well…
Maybe it's not that
I don't remember,
but maybe I'm trying not to.
Like an unconscious
self-defense mechanism, maybe?
Because it probably was
that traumatizing.
Wait in the living room, then.
I'll bring it right over.
Why does it feel like
all of Sung-yeon's memories
were told to him
by a third person?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here, your diary.
Um…
Which one is you?
Why, I'm right here.
That's me on the left.
Don't you remember?
Mi-so, I thought hard about this,
and the reason I like you
isn't simply because we shared
that experience in the past.
I'm not asking for
an answer right away,
but I just… Want you to
know how I feel about you.
Ji-ah, did everything go
alright with your moving?
Yes! And it only takes me
5 minutes to come to work!
My place is so spacious
and it's so cozy, too.
Then when are you planning to
invite us to your cozy place?
- Sorry?
- I meant, a housewarming party!
But it's a one-room apartment
and it's so cramped!
And I'm a bad cook, and…
Sweetie!
We're not asking for much!
(Uncomfortable)
(No!)
I guess some chicken, boiled meat,
(Crunchy Chicken)
(A lump of colagen)
(Chewy sweet and sour pork)
sweet & sour beef, braised ribs…
(Braised Short Ribs
Wow~)
Just order us something,
and we'll be fine.
We're an easy bunch, right?
(Very easygoing)
You're lucky to have us
as your mentors!
Hey, it just happens that
tomorrow's the weekend!
Why, perfect timing!
- So, what do you say?
- It's on!
It's on…
Ah, Ms. Kim!
Good morning.
Ji-ah's having a housewarming
party. Can you come?
Oh, I have
a family reunion tomorrow.
Alright, then!
So, how much should we each pay
for the housewarming gift?
Well, with Mr. Yang…
That's five of us,
so what about $20 each?
But Mr. Yang is always on call,
so he probably can't come.
And what, are you not
up to date with things?
We can't get anything nice
with just $20 each.
- Our smarty pants, Mr. Park said…
- What?
Shouldn't it be at least
$24.90 each?
Alright then, tomorrow it is!
Woo-hoo, I'm all excited now.
What should I wear?
Let's all work hard today!
Oh... What am I supposed to do?
As I thought. Mr. Lee was
the boy I was looking for.
But why does everyone say
it was Sung-yeon?
Did Mr. Lee really
lose his memory?
I should just pretend
I know nothing, right?
Good morning, Ms. Kim.
You have meetings with our
affiliates from 3 p.m.,
and after that, you'll be
dining with the board.
Ms. Kim Ji-ah will
support you today.
Does that mean I won't be able to
see you until the evening?
No.
Too bad.
Then come to my place tonight.
What? At night?
What's in your head right now?
Well, I guess that suggestive
nuisance surrounding
those two words,
'night' and 'my place'
gets your naughty
imagination going.
Well, I've never been to
a creativity academy
like you did, sir,
so I'm not that imaginative.
That's too bad.
I wanted to tidy up the
documents in my study.
You can't help me?
Of course I can…
…Oppa.
What?
What did you just call me?
I just wanted to
try calling you that.
'Oppa.'
You may keep it up.
I will specially allow it.
No, once is enough.
Then please excuse me.
You can keep on…
Maybe I should've recorded that.
Mr. Lee!
Mr. Lee?
You're here early.
Ah…
Oh, I see.
It'll be too much for your heart
if you see my abs beneath this,
so let me go get changed.
Could those scars be from…
When he was tied up?
It must've hurt so much…
Why am I crying?
Hey, Sis.
Mi-so, where are you?
At Mr. Lee's place.
What? Why are you there?
Do you know what time it is?
Are you really dating your VP?
That selfish, egoistic bastard?
Sis, Mr. Lee, he…
He's not selfish.
He was a much better person
than I thought he was.
So…
Please don't worry
about us so much.
Whatever. Anyway, we leave at
12 o'clock tomorrow.
Alright? Don't be late.
Alright. Bye.
This is too hard for me…
Is she crying because
they're that against me?
But why?
When they should be putting up
welcome banners instead!
Could it because
they think I'm too perfect?
Ha…
Young-joon, you…
Why can't you be
slightly less perfect?
God, I hate myself
in times like these.
Ms. Kim.
Everything will soon be settled.
Yes, once we shred all the
documents older than 10 years,
except for the confidential files…
I don’t mean that.
I mean all your dilemmas.
They will all soon be settled.
Just what…
I overheard your
phone conversation.
Looks like your sisters are
worried for us,
but I'll make sure that
they stop worrying very soon.
You know me.
I have that aura that…
…Dazzle people.
I'll use all means and methods to
win over their trust.
So don't cry from now on.
You didn't need to take me home…
This is so we can be
together even just a bit longer.
If we said goodbye at my place,
wouldn't that be disappointing?
I mean, for you.
Yes, you're right.
My schedule's free tomorrow.
Want me to date you?
Oh, I can't tomorrow.
I have a family reunion.
Oh, is it that one weekend
you ask for leave, each year?
Yes, sir.
Heading down to
Jebudo Island again, are you?
Yes.
Then good night, Mr. Lee.
Oh, that's right. Mr. Lee?
Here you go.
What is that, Ms. Kim?
Then good night!
Ah… I can't believe
what I just did!
Good night.
'Is something wrong?'
is what you want me to
ask you right now, isn't it?
Yes.
Please ask me.
I want to let it all out.
Then go on. Let it all out.
Can I?
A few days ago, I saw my ex-wife.
She was with some other guy.
And ha… She looked so happy.
But you look unhappy.
Yeah.
If there was a contest for
the unhappiest man of this month,
I'm confident I'll rank in
the top 3.
I mean, how could she already
see someone else?
How?
You should've been good to her.
But I was!
What more could I have done?
I'd buy her new handbags regularly,
I'd buy her jewelry regularly,
and I'd even make breakfast!
I even told her she looks
beautiful without makeup on!
And not just her.
I was so good to
her family as well!
To her family as well?
So goes the saying,
be good to your wife's family
if you want a happy marriage.
So that's exactly what I did.
Her father, mother
and her siblings…
They were all like,
'My son-in-law is the best!'
'You're so good to us!'
They'd coo over me like,
'Awww! Awww! Awww!'
- Over you?
- Yes, over me.
What did you do?
What, you don't believe me?
I'm not asking
because I don't believe you.
I wanted to know your know-hows.
So her family…
Wait. You want to win points from
Ms. Kim's family, don't you?
Ha, whatever.
Man, how do I make it
simple enough so you understand?
Alright, Mr. CEO.
You know how our venders are
always doing their best to
win the bid for our projects?
They always try so hard to
prove themselves,
to appeal that
they're not so bad.
- Yes.
- That's how this is.
Mr. CEO, you are
a start-up venture that is
facing evaluation from
a large conglomerate
that is Ms. Kim's family.
You've only just gone public,
so their trust level is 0.
So from now on, you need to
appeal to them to prove that
you're really not a bad guy.
Now that you put it that way,
I think I finally get it.
So what did you do?
What I did was…
…Bow 45 degrees,
put my two hands together, and…
'Yes, yes! Why, of course!'
'Of course! Yes!
I'm all good with that.'
I said yes to everything and
did whatever they told me to!
What?
In other words,
when meeting with her family,
I left my pride back at home.
Ha… Do you really have to?
You really have to,
in order to earn points from…
Wait a second.
This was supposed to be
you hearing me out,
but why am I suddenly
listening to your problems?
Oh what?
Winning the trust of
your girlfriend's family, huh?
I just cleaned the place,
so just relax.
- Thank you.
- Ah…
- Ah, this is so relaxing!
After coming here every year, this
place feels like our second home.
So, Mi-so.
Why do you look so down?
Why the long face?
Is something up?
Nothing's up.
Is it because of
what I said yesterday?
Because I gave you a lecture about
dating the VP?
- It's not that.
- Mi-so.
Now that mom's gone,
I'm playing that role.
And here's our baby,
jumping into fire,
and I can't just
sit and watch, can I?
No matter how I think about it,
your VP is a definite no.
Ha… It's because
you've never met Mr. Lee.
He has so many good points.
Wow, Mal-hee! Did you lose weight?
You look much thinner than
the last time I saw you!
- Really?
- Yes!
But I put on 2 kg!
Wow, it must be because
I'm wearing black.
Anyway, whatever it is…
Cheer up, Mi-so.
Because we need to have
fun today, right?
Alright, let's have fun!
Let's all have fun!
- Woo-hoo!
- Ah…
Let's have a blast at
Ji-ah's new place!
Woo-hoo!
Is it far from here?
No, no. We're almost here.
Here we are.
- Oh, here?
- Ah I see.
Why, aren't you the girl
from the third floor?
- Yes, hello.
- Hello.
Looks like you have guests.
Yes, for a housewarming.
Oh, then I guess you could
use the rooftop.
Well, have fun!
See you!
Rooftop! That sounds nice.
Drinking out in the open air…
That'll call for more alcohol!
The rooftop, when it's so hot?
Let’s just…
…Go to my place.
Why not? It's a nice day,
and it's perfect weather for
having a drink outside!
Let's go, then.
Up to the rooftop,
as high as my CSAT score!
But…
We'll trouble my neighbor
who lives on the rooftop.
Come on, it's not like
we're here every day.
Your neighbor will understand when
we say it's for housewarming.
- So let's go!
- Let's go!
Uh… Wait!
Then… can you drop by to
my room and
bring all the food I ordered?
I'll head up first and
wipe the table.
It's really dirty, haha.
Please take your time.
Oh, alright, alright. Geez.
She's a good girl.
Yes, she is. Hey, don't worry!
- Let's go, let's go!
- Rooftop! Nice!
She really put
a lot of effort into this.
Grow, grow, grow!
Just because you're
cherry tomatoes,
you don't need to stay
the size of cherries!
Emergency!
What, are all your colleagues
rushing over here or something?
How did you know?
They're all on their way here!
They're here for
my housewarming party,
and they want to
come up on the rooftop!
- What?
- There's no time! Hide!
Why should I hide?
It's more like
you shouldn't bring them here!
Wow, what is all this?
Eh… Owww! Ouch!
Come on!
Oh man!
Oh no… What do I do?
- Tsk!
- Where are you going?
Wow, this is a nice place.
Ouch, my back!
Why did you come up already?
I asked you to drop by to
my room and bring the…
Hey, you think I'll be doing that
with all my underlings here?
And I'm just not fit for
carrying heavy things!
My bones are so thin…
You know me.
I'm so delicate and fragile!
Ah… I'm out of breath!
Wow, this bench is really nice!
Ah, there you are!
Whoa! Hey!
Wow, the view up here I great!
I bet you have a great view
of the night sky, too!
Then we should stay here
until nightfall!
Until nightfall?
What, until nightfall? Ugh…
Come on, have a seat.
You didn't have to
order so much, Ji-ah.
Oh man…
Let's set this up.
Hurry, mix it!
- Done.
- Yes!
Mr. Lee?
Why are you…
Nice to meet you.
I'm Lee Young-joon.
What happened?
You said you always stay
at the same inn
every year down on Jebudo Island.
And that you sprained your ankle
playing badminton
at a primary school
right next to it.
So I searched for one that's next
to a primary school and voila!
What I mean is…
Why are you here?
When my sisters are here.
That's why I'm here.
They're worried about you
seeing me,
so I came to
extinguish those worries.
I'll do my best to
- win over your sisters'…
- Mi-so.
Pil-nam.
It can't be that you're here to
give her work.
So may I ask why you're here?
Are you two really going out?
- Well, uh…
- Yes.
We're going out.
I know you're worried about her
seeing me.
But there's no need to worry.
Because it's much more
serious than you think it is.
From Ms. Kim's side, that is.
Oh, of course,
it's the same for me.
Why don't we have this
conversation elsewhere?
I prepared a suite at
one of our resorts nearby.
We're fine.
You told me not to
worry about you two,
but I don’t think I can.
Because you're from
a different world to ours.
That's why I'm not
so comfortable about this.
About you suddenly
turning up here.
Pil-nam…
You said you were hungry.
Come on, let's go eat.
Then why don't we
all go for lunch?
I booked the finest restaurant
- around here.
- No, we're fine.
We already have
a reservation, too.
Then let me join you.
What?
You'll really join us?
I'm not sure about this…
(Unlimited Marinated Crabs)
Wow.
Looks like you're in shock.
Is it because it's only $19.90 per
person when it's unlimited?
Yes. I can't believe
they still make a profit.
It's called a quick-return.
They keep the costs low
and the sales volume high.
But I'm not sure whether these
cheap crabs will suit your palate.
Because I bet you only had
top-quality ones until now.
If this is too uncomfortable for
you, you may leave.
No, I am from the
same world as you.
I don't find this
uncomfortable at all.
Mr. Lee, I think
you should go back.
No, I'm going to have
those marinated crabs.
As much as I can.
I'll do it, Ms. Kim.
You're dating, and
you still call her Ms. Kim?
And you call him Mr. Lee?
Thanks for pointing that out.
I was starting to think
we needed to fix this.
So just call me
oppa already, Mi-so.
Pil-nam, that's for us to decide.
I'm so full already!
I feel like I'm stuffed with
crabs up to here.
Guess I need to
fill them up to here now.
Why's she eating when
she just said she's full?
To get our money's worth.
Sorry?
Might as well as eat more for
the same price, right?
Oh, that's right!
Guess you'd never understand.
That feeling of wanting to
get your money's worth,
even it means eating until
you burst your stomach!
Oh, I do.
You've heard of the saying,
'The have's are worse?'
Well, that'll be me.
I'm going to get more than
my money's worth today.
Alright, in we go.
Wow, that's juicy!
Hey!
Then… One more plate!
You over there!
What, is this your last day
eating marinated crabs, ever?
You're almost risking your
life there, eating them!
Tsk, tsk…
You can stop now.
You've eaten more than
your money's worth.
Oh. Did I?
Well, let me stop here for today.
Now I feel like
I finally got my money's worth.
Ha… Did I eat too much?
I feel like all my
insides are full of crabs!
Here you go, some water.
Don't tell me
you have indigestion?
I'm Lee Young-joon,
who's talented in everything.
Including digesting food.
Since we're done,
why don't you now go…
Bleh… Ah…
What's with that fashion?
Oh, we're going digging for clams.
Every year when we're down here,
we always dig them and
eat them later.
What?
Why force labor onto yourself
when you're here on holiday?
Well, what would you know,
when you've got
all the chefs cooking up
all the freshest ingredients.
You'd never understand
why we go digging for clams.
It's because we want
fresh clam noodles!
This is why I said
he's from a different world…
Tsk.
Let me join you! For clam-digging!
What?
Forget it.
You probably only walked on
red carpet all your life,
so you think you can
handle a mud flat?
I can.
As long as I'm with Ms. Kim,
be it a mud flat or a thorny path,
I'm not afraid!
Off to the sea!
Mud flat!
To the mud flat!
Wow, this is delicious.
Yes, it's so good.
Hey, you know what?
Since this is
Ji-ah's housewarming party,
let's all drink to her!
Shall we? Woo-hoo!
To Ji-ah's happy life here!
- To Ji-ah!
Bottoms up!
Man! Alcohol tastes
so sweet today.
This place is no nice!
Hey, my bag!
Wait!
Huh?
Let me get you something to
wipe that with.
Tsk… This is an expensive purse!
Thanks, Ji-ah. You're sure great!
I thought it was going to be
nice and breezy today,
but the sun's too strong.
Shall we move over to that shade?
Yes! Because UV rays are
your skin's worst enemy.
- Let's move right now!
- Let's go!
Alright, everyone. Come down.
I think this way.
Alright, that way it is.
- Watch it.
- Yes, sir.
Alright, here we go.
One, two, three!
Let's go that way.
- One, two! One, two!
- One, two!
Oh man…
Surprise!
Mr… Koh?
What are you doing here?
I told you, surprise!
'Surprise?'
Yes. I was invited to
the housewarming, too.
But I'm such a creative person
who thinks you need fresh ideas
even when you're having fun.
So I thought
I should surprise you.
That's why
I planned this with Ji-ah,
and hid under here.
While listening in and
waiting for the perfect timing…
You just happened to
lift that bench in time!
Haha, nice timing!
Well, back to our food!
Join us, Mr. Koh.
- Let's all sit.
- Sure!
Mr. Koh, do you want some…
Oh. Looks like
we'll need more beer.
That's all we have.
I'll go get some more.
No, let me!
I saw a big supermarket
on the way.
Let me go grab some from there.
What's up with you,
volunteering like that…
If I want to drink more,
I need to take a break to
digest, you know.
Then go and digest!
Alright, I'll make it quick!
- Enjoy yourselves in the meantime.
- Alright!
Hey, that looks delicious.
- Hello.
- Can I try one?
Of course. It's buy one,
get one free!
- Really?
- Yes.
Wow, that's so delicious!
Let me have one more.
Lady, you can't take
all three for yourself!
It's not like
you're going to buy any.
She is!
One, two, three!
We'll take as much as three!
So don't you
embarrass her like that.
Let's go, Ms. Bong.
Ah, sure…
Ugh…
So is your VP coming or not?
I know, right? Why did he bluff,
if he wasn't confident?
Pil-nam!
What's with that glare?
But aren't you being
too harsh on him?
I know you're in shock because
he suddenly turned up to
announce we're going out, but…
It's not like you to
be so rude!
Mi-so! I was only worried for you.
I said, there's no need to worry!
Mr. Lee isn't the person
you think he is.
He protects me
when I get scared,
and always looks out for me.
You know nothing about him.
Oh my goodness!
I can't believe this!
Sorry I'm late.
Mr. Lee, where did you
get all that?
It's my principle to be
perfect at everything I do.
Having the right tools isn't
all there is to this.
It's all about the expertise
and the know-hows
which we built over
all these years!
Sis!
Then… How about a battle?
- A battle?
- Let's team up like this,
us against you.
The losers have to grant the
other team's wish. How about it?
Bring it on!
Whatever.
Ms. Kim,
I'm going to do my best
since this is a competition,
but what is your wish?
Oh. I'm going to
ask them not to hate you.
That just washed away
all my fatigue.
Ha! Nice!
Pebble…
Guess this is not the place.
There we go!
Clams!
Oh man…
Alright, now just the
collecting to do.
So we won, right?
Yes, yes.
Congratulations, Mi-so.
Mr. Lee?
So?
What's your wish, Mi-so?
Well, my wish is…
…For you to not hate Mr. Lee.
No,
you can hate me if you want.
But please…
Keep watching over us.
Let me prove to you incessantly
that I'm serious about Mi-so.
Alright. Let's go.
Oh my gosh!
Ah…
Are you alright?
Yes.
By the way,
why are your hands so cold?
Let me see.
Is from your indigestion?
I knew it from when you were
stuffing those crabs into you…
Well, uh…
Come on. Let's get you
some medicine.
Uh, Ms. Kim? I'm…
- Let's take those clams first.
- No.
- The clams!
- Come on!
I guess it's from
eating all those crabs to
win points from us, huh?
Well, no one told him to
eat that much.
To be honest, I'm a bit surprised.
He looked so full of himself
on the news, but...
Here he is, trying so hard,
even putting up
with your bullying!
He really must be
serious about Mi-so.
Don't you think so, too?
It's just the sexual dysfunction
part that bothers me,
but I think overall,
he's not a bad person.
Besides, his sister-in-law is
an expert so he'll get over it.
What? 'Sister-in-law?'
Come on. I like the guy!
So you try opening
your heart, too.
Whatever. Hey, it's hot.
Let's go.
- Take that.
- But this is the heavy one!
Ugh.
Give me your hand.
I'm alright.
Whatever. Pricking your finger is
the best way to beat indigestion.
But still…
Hey, a UFO!
Where?
Argh! Ouch! Blood!
Um… blood. I'm bleeding.
Go get some rest.
You're not well.
No. I'm all better now.
Let me help.
No, leave this to us.
Then can you knead this for us?
This is usually Dad's job,
but he couldn't come today
because he had a concert.
Gosh, it's so tough
with my frail arms.
Oh. Let me take that for you.
Um, Mr. Lee? Be a little gentler.
You know, I really think
that did the trick.
Then… I'll prick it for you
again next time.
Gently, a little more gently.
Then shall we all go
have some beer?
There's a bar just around here.
- Then let's go.
- Let's go!
Where are you all going?
It looked like it was
going to rain,
so we're heading indoors.
Then you should've called!
You made us spend money for…
I mean, I guess this could be our
housewarming gift for JI-ah.
What, this much?
- Then let's go!
- Let's go!
Is it because
we're the only ones here?
It's so quiet in here.
Right? Why are you
all silent today?
Anything interesting to tell?
Like there is,
when we're always
stuck with each other.
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Hello.
- Oh, hello.
You heard about a park project
just around here, right?
Can you sign here to
say you agree?
Hey, aren't you the girl
from room 301?
Can you sign this, too?
I just need your signature and
that guy on the rooftop's.
Oh, is that right?
Um… Here.
- Thanks!
- Bye.
Uh, what are you doing?
Hiding behind that squid…
Well, uh…
'Masked Singer!'
- What, 'Masked Singer?'
- Yes.
You were just asking whether
there's anything,
so I thought I should
sing a song for you.
Then here I go!
Stop, stop!
Why, what is it?
I know you're eager to
climb the corporate ladder,
but do you really have to do this?
What do you mean?
You probably heard that
the VP's Office is the
shortcut to the top, huh?
That's why you want to
transfer here.
And who do you have to
flatter to do that?
You got thinking, and then…
Eureka!
You probably came to the
conclusion to flatter me,
because I'm the boss
in this place.
Am I not right?
No way.
But it is!
I mean, I went to KORI, too!
So you probably first tried the
'I went to KORI too' card,
then tried to earn points by
singing a tune for me.
It's all to get into
my good books, isn't it?
Am I not right, Mr. Koh?
You're right, sir. Yes!
Whoa! Be careful, Ms. Bong.
No, you be careful.
What should I be careful about?
Just… Everything!
Don't try to come onto me,
picking up my pads,
and don’t buy me those
3 packs of sausages.
And don't seduce me
Why are you following me?
Because you look like
you're drunk.
In case you fall over.
There you go again!
Then come on! Protect me!
That's strange.
I have extremely high standards,
but I kind of like Mr. Yang.
Should I ask him out?
No, no.
It's too embarrassing,
so I'm not saying it first.
How can a girl ask
a guy out first, right?
Let's not throw your pride away!
Whoa, whoa!
What do you think?
With the clams we dug up,
we made clam noodles
and even pancakes.
Delicious, huh?
Yes. I'll make sure to
join you next year as well.
We'll see, not just yet.
Alright.
So… Do you always
spend your holiday here,
digging up clams?
Yes. Usually, Dad's always
here with us, too.
What a unique family tradition.
Is it?
We promised Mom.
Promise?
It was when Mi-so was 4 years old.
Dad had wanted to try out for
the beach music festival,
so we'd even borrowed
our neighbor's car.
I'm going to win
no matter what and
give that trophy to your Mom
as her birthday present!
And during my acceptance speech,
I'm going to shout out your name!
- I'll look forward to it.
- Please do.
The sea!
- Hey, it's the sea.
- It's the sea!
Wow, so pretty!
Looks like
we still have some time.
Can we drop by?
Sure.
Kids, shall we all go
drop by the beach?
- Yes!
Alright, let's…
Why? Did you lose something?
The car key.
What?
I'm the worst husband.
I wanted to give you that
trophy for your birthday,
but instead I ended up
giving you worries.
This is the worst birthday for
you ever, right?
No, honey. I'm sure you're more
disappointed about the contest.
Found it!
I found it for you!
Really? You did?
Oh, you didn't mean
you found the car key,
but a clam.
Yeah! It's my first time
seeing one for real!
Let's cook this!
But we'll need
a little more for that.
Kids, shall we all go
digging for clams?
- Yes!
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
Oops, sorry.
You keep looking for the key.
I'll look after the kids.
No. Michael J. Fox once said,
'Family is not an important thing.
It's everything.'
I can just call car service,
and always participate in that
contest next year.
So today, I'm going to
focus on my everything.
My family.
But will it really be alright?
Of course. Besides, I was too busy
recently to spend time with them.
Maybe this happened today
so we can all have fun.
You're not the
worst husband in the world,
and this isn't
my worst birthday ever.
Because thanks to you, honey,
we're all having fun.
So said the legendary
heavy metal vocalist, Rob Halford.
Pee! I need to pee!
Your daughter says
she needs to pee.
Alright, let's go!
Daddy will take you.
Shall we all come down here
on my birthday each year?
Really? Yay!
Mom kept that promise
until the following year,
and passed away.
Hold on.
Then today is…
Yes, it's Mom's birthday.
Though we still have
vivid memories of Mom,
Mi-so was too young then to
remember much about Mom.
It hurts me
when I think about that.
I'm sorry if I hurt you today.
But we could see that
you truly are a good person.
And that you love
Mi-so very much.
But I…
I want Mi-so to have
a loving family,
because she lost her
mother so early.
That's why I was worried when
I heard she's seeing
who is far from average.
I won't make you worry.
It's also my wish
as much as yours,
to see Ms. Kim happy.
That woman who abducted us…
You don't even remember
what she was wearing?
Any memories of
how we made it out?
Anything?
Which one is you?
I don't know
what you'll think about this,
but I think this 'Hyeon'
is Mr. Lee.
What are you doing?
And what's with that look?
Why? What is it this time?
Honey.
I think…
…It's time we be
honest with our kids.
What?
I don’t think we can
keep it from them anymore.
Looks like I've managed to
get some points.
It does, yes.
This makes me happier than
when I was named the
'Top CEO in his 30s.'
But there's just one thing.
If I'd known it was
your late mother's birthday,
I wouldn't have followed you here.
Because this day should be spent
just with your family.
No.
You coming here,
and doing all that for me
made me really happy.
And I'm sure
it's the same for my sisters too,
now that they know
what a good person you are.
Our family usually spends the
saddest day on
Mom's late anniversary, and the
happiest day on her birthday.
Everyone in your family are
all good people.
I bet it was the same for
your mother, too.
You're right.
She was a great person.
Shortly after
we came to this beach,
Mom suddenly collapsed,
when she was so healthy.
Dad was tied up to the hospital,
always nursing her.
So I was always alone.
Watching the other kids
play with their moms,
I used to get so envious…
Then one day…
Play with me!
You can cover that now!
Mi-so!
Mom!
Mommy!
Let's play chase!
You chase me, Mom.
- Shall I?
- Yeah!
Alright, let's go!
I was so happy that
Mom had come back.
I'd been so happy.
But it turned out…
…That was the day
she chose to come home
after hearing that there was no
more that the doctors could do.
It must've been so hard,
running around in her health…
But if not for that…
I would've forgotten
all about Mom.
I was too young,
and I didn't have
many memories with her, so…
I see.
So Mr. Lee,
if you also have
a painful past of your own,
I hope I'll be able to
hear it from you someday.
Whenever that day is,
I'll be waiting.
Because from now on,
I'll forever be by your side.
You should stay longer,
since you came all the way here.
We told you already.
He has a showcase to attend to.
I'll visit you
officially next time.
Enjoy yourselves, then.
Safe driving!
Please take good care of
Mi-so for us.
- I will.
- Bye!
You don't look so well.
What's this about?
Don't get so confused,
and don't feel so
burdened by guilt.
But just listen to what I say.
That day, 24 years ago…
It wasn't you…
…Who was kidnapped.
It was me.
It has to be.
I did go through all that.
Now introducing the
grand revolution in software.
The AI analysis tool,
B-DATA!
What are you eating?
Sorry, I was a bit hungry.
Are you done with all the photos?
Only just.
It's too crowded in here.
I just want to go home and rest.
We've just the performances left,
so hang in there for a bit more.
There's nothing
after this, is there?
No, I purposely left it blank
because I knew you'd be tired.
Don’t worry.
I knew I could count on you!
Mr. Lee Young-joon!
Have a rest over there.
Alright.
Up next is a special performance
for our UK Software Showcase!
Choi Hyun-woo's magic show!
Please give him a warm welcome!
How did you…
They told me
my memories aren't real.
Is that what you think, too?
You can't even give me
a straight answer to
my question, can you?
Alright, then. Introducing our
special guest for this evening,
Ms. Kim Na-yeon, who is
also a professional model.
Does that mean
my memories are all wrong?
Sometimes…
I dream about my childhood
which I can't quite understand.
If…
If really…
…Those dreams are…
Daddy's gone to work!
What nonsense are
you talking about?
Auntie's gone weird, oppa.
No, Mi-so. That's not Auntie.
That's a spider. A huge spider.
Oppa, I'm scared.
Mi-so, stay right there.
Don't come here.
No, oppa!
Don't leave me here!
Don't come here, dummy!
I remembered.
Mi-so! Mi-so!
Mi-so, wake up! Mi-so!
Kim Mi-so!
Ms. Kim, can you hear me?
(Many thanks to Lee Min-ki, Jung So-min,)
(and Charming Choi who guest-starred)
(What's Wrong With Secretary Kim?)
Do you know who I am?
What did you say to Mi-so?
What did you say to her that
she fainted like that?
You can't hide anything forever
in this world.