Walking here from the station
I thought I was going to die from the heat
What? Ordering only for yourself
Oppa?
Oppa!
What's wrong, why are you so dazed?
Did you get heatstroke?
Uh, no..
Why did you want to meet?
Why are you being so hurtful again?
Do we need a reason to meet?
You've changed, oppa
How have I changed?
I heard you don't meet other girls these days?
The most sociable person in our department not meeting anyone means you've changed
What's with this lukewarm reaction
I'm going to order a coffee
I'll ask you one last time
If you let go of my hand now
We're really over
Hey, you..
What are you doing!
Did that wake you up?
Don't do things like this
That's why there are weird rumors
What rumors?
Ah..
Rumors that I'm meeting this guy and that guy
That I'm dating around?
Yes
Well, that's true, so what?
But..
Do you know I had a reason for all that?
Reason?
I..
I've liked a guy for a really long time
But he doesn't notice me
So I tried to make him jealous
By dating around
And?
It doesn't seem to work
So now..
I'm going to confess
Okay.. good luck
You really don't get it
Huh?
Oppa..
What do you think of me?
What?
I've liked you for a long time
I like you
Hey Choi Sol
Oppa, you've never really dated anyone seriously either
Always meeting people out of curiosity
Stop doing that
Can't you date me? Huh?
I have a girlfriend
Sorry
Jaemin oppa and I..
Didn't you break up?
How..
How do you know that?
Ah..
You’re more persistent than I thought
How do you know that!
Did you meet Jaemin?
Yes!
I met him
What did you say to him?
I told him to break up with you
Or I’d spread rumors about everything
You really
I can't understand
Why is someone like you dating someone like him?
You should date someone at your level
And with his specs
He can’t even apply to our company
I may have gone too far
But you'll thank me later
I didn't think it would be this bad
You're the worst
What?
You
I hate to even say this
But one last piece of advice
Don’t judge other people's lives by your standards
Me?
Even though I’ve dated around
I’d never date you
You're not even worth that
What did you say?
Don't contact me again
Oppa
Oppa!
You still..
Don't know me
Ah.. right, my phone..
Well, it’s good
I wasn’t getting any calls anyway
Jaemin!
I'm sorry
Whatever Sol said, I'm sorry for it all
I'm sorry for making you handle everything alone
For not understanding your feelings
For not holding your hand till the end
I'm sorry
Why didn't you tell me?
How could I say that?
Because of my situation
How could I say I was going to give you up
It felt shameless and cowardly
I thought having you was enough
But it wasn’t
After hearing what Sol said
I was worried and scared about everything
I was worried because you were beside me
I didn't want to tell you that
And hurt you
Because of me..
For making you feel that way
I'm sorry
I was only thinking of myself
I was too selfish
No
It's okay
I was only thinking of myself too
I live impulsively and without plans
But you're not like that
You have your own plans and goals
I can’t be an obstacle to that
In your life..
I promise I'll never be an obstacle
Promise
Are you sure it's okay?
Yes
As long as you're safe
But
Just let me stay by your side
Okay
I missed you
But didn’t you say we shouldn’t in case someone saw?
Did I say that?