=Playing Go=
=Episode 19=
=Don't Cry, My Beloved=
Hello.
I'm fine.
I'll wait for you at Mazu Temple.
Let's talk about it when we meet.
What did he say?
He's waiting for us at Mazu Temple.
Can I see the stuff
you hung up?
It's nice.
Pull over.
What's wrong?
I have to pee.
You can't pee?
You like that pendant?
Where did you get it?
Did you see that pendant before?
Yes.
I didn't want to tell you
because I was afraid of the trouble.
I kidnapped his son
and wife.
This
is from his son.
This has nothing to do with you.
I've always been unlucky.
I just want to talk to him
to see if we can skip drawing lots.
You don't have to draw lots either.
Let him go.
When I get the money,
I'll send his wife and son back to him.
It's fair for all three of us
to draw lots.
Even if you're picked,
he won't let anything happen to you.
You should trust him.
I only believe in myself.
Listen to me.
I introduced you to him.
You can't do this.
Where are you keeping them?
Before he knows it,
you let them go.
I won't say anything.
I'll pretend it never happened.
Nice lighter.
Let's go after this cigarette.
I have to tie you up.
What kind of a person is that?
He's got no conscience.
♪Don't cry, my beloved♪
♪Tonight, I'm like a flower in bloom♪
♪Falling in the most beautiful moment♪
♪There's no recovery
even with your tears♪
♪Don't cry, my beloved♪
♪Do you know I'll never wake up again?♪
♪Blinking in the most
beautiful night sky♪
♪My eyes are the brightest stars♪
♪Do you remember when I proudly said♪
♪I'd been to this world?♪
♪Don't tell me what eternity is♪
♪I perish in the most glorious
of moments♪
♪Don't cry, my beloved♪
♪Tonight, I'm like a flower in bloom♪
♪Falling in the most beautiful moment♪
♪There's no recovery
even with your tears♪
♪I'd been to this world?♪
♪Don't tell me what maturity is♪
♪I ended it the moment I started♪
Hello.
Stop urging.
We'll be right there.
Cui Wei,
come in.
How's your mom?
Is she all right?
My mom had a bit of a shock
and was taken to hospital.
I'm glad she's all right.
Cui Wei,
finish the noodles
and hurry to the hospital.
Stay with your mom.
Besides,
the autopsy report
won't be out soon.
Even without the autopsy report,
I know who it is.
It can only be Qin Xiaoming.
Why was Qin Xiaoming's body
buried next to your dad's grave?
From the beginning of this case to now,
through all these happenings,
we think the most crucial person
is Qin Xiaoming.
But it's not.
He's the one hiding
behind Qin Xiaoming's identity.
Cui Ye.
Who?
My younger brother.
Cui Ye.
It can only be him.
If it's him, then it all makes sense.
Why couldn't we catch the culprit?
Because he knows me well enough.
It can only be him.
Cui Wei,
do you have any evidence
of his involvement?
I have no evidence.
You should know
that if he's identified as a suspect,
you'll have to recuse yourself.
I know.
- Cui Wei.
- I know!
I know it all!
Cui Wei, calm down.
At this point in time,
the more you have
to control your emotions.
Cui Wei,
listen to me.
You'd better go back
and spend some time with your mom.
Go back.
I know.
I
know it all.
Mom,
have an apple.
I don't have an appetite.
Mom,
you look much better.
Let me see.
Tell your mom to eat it.
You won't even eat the apple
Jiawen peeled for you?
I don't get that treatment at home.
Jiawen,
it's not that I won't eat it.
I really don't have an appetite.
If Mom says no, then no.
Jiawen,
please get me some water.
Okay.
Wei,
I've been
feeling panicky.
Who do you think
was buried on your dad's grave?
It has nothing to do
with our family, right?
No.
Why don't you
have a banana
or an orange?
You guys...
No matter what happens at home,
you guys always hide it from me.
It's like the family
is always at peace.
But I...
I just don't get it.
Why was this man
buried on your dad's grave?
The doctor said
that when we're in shock,
we tend to be paranoid.
Look, it's true.
Stop thinking about it.
Come on,
lie down.
I'll adjust the bed for you.
Lie down.
Stop adjusting it. It's good.
So that's good?
Is that comfortable?
Where is Ye?
Why didn't he come to see me?
You're thinking about Ye?
Wei,
your dad passed away a long time ago.
For everything
that happened in the family
over the years,
I've always listened to you.
With you around,
I feel reassured.
I know
when Yan has got this disease,
Ye
must be under a lot of pressure.
You need to help him.
I'm his older brother
and he's my younger brother.
If you're fine,
nothing matters.
What took you so long?
Where is Xiasheng?
Xiasheng.
He is dead.
He...
How did he die?
Do you believe me
when I say it was an accident?
I kidnapped your wife and son
because I was afraid you'd set me up.
So I got a bargaining chip.
But he found out about it.
I didn't want to do anything to him,
but he got hit by a car.
It's a car accident.
I've memorized the plate number for you.
I saw that he was in pain
so I knocked him on the head.
(Go for the deal)
I guessed right, didn't I?
He told me to trust you.
Isn't that funny?
In this situation,
we don't need to draw lots.
Next, you do the deal,
I'll take the money.
When I get all the money,
I'll tell you where
your wife and son are.
I didn't want it to come to this.
What's that you've got there?
Why do you bring so much money?
I think he's very loyal to you.
Bury him.
I picked it out for you.
I bought you breakfast.
Eat it.
Dig in.
Let's do the work after eating.
Your wife and son are still hungry.
I wonder how long they'll last.
I need to call my mom.
What are you trying to do?
You kidnapped my wife and son,
and I am not at home.
Everyone in the family is gone
without a word.
My mom will call the police.
Put it here.
Turn up the volume.
No one answered the phone.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Mom,
Shuhua
took Yan
to a friend's house.
I've gone to the province
for a competition.
I'll be back in a few days.
Yan
has made it to page 38 of his handbook.
Don't mess it up.
The thing under the Tianhou Cup
belongs to my brother.
Tell him
to get it.
What is the Tianhou Cup?
It's a trophy I won in go.
Is that enough?
Dig in
and get to work.
Go to the train station.
Yan.
Mom.
Yan, are you all right?
Yan.
Mom.
What's wrong?
I want to throw up.
Breathe.
Take a deep breath.
Are you feeling better?
Lean over here.
Anybody there?
Mom!
I'm fine.
Mom,
what is this place?
Anybody there?
Help!
♪The storm rolled in that very day♪
♪The wandering lamb had lost its way♪
♪The blacksmith's hammer
rang clear and bright♪
♪But things aren't really all that bad♪
♪A banquet feast was laid with care♪
♪But not one honored guest was there♪
♪The sleeping girl
wore a peaceful smile♪
♪And things aren't really all that bad♪
♪Tried to catch a lovely dragonfly♪
♪But broke the vase I treasured most♪
♪The swallow's back beneath the eaves♪
♪And things aren't really all that bad♪
♪Each day I watered with gentle hands♪
♪But still the orchid
drooped and sagged♪
♪A breeze drifted through
with apricot scent♪
♪And things aren't really all that bad♪
♪I climbed the hill to see the view♪
♪But halfway up, the blisters grew♪
♪I paused to sip from a mountain stream♪
♪And things aren't really all that bad♪