[English subtitles are available]
[Mr. Bad]
[Episode 12]
Mr. Cheng,
they might procrastinate.
We should
find a solution.
I
checked the contract.
They omitted some details.
Yes.
Okay.
I sense that there are problems.
We'll confirm
at the meeting
this afternoon.
No problem.
Hello.
Hello, Mr. Li.
Yes.
I know why you
call
but we cannot hire
the actor
because of our company's
future development direction.
I hope you understand.
Okay.
Please consider
our suggestion.
No problem. Bye.
The contract says
that we may take part.
If they
want web traffic,
we can sue them.
We might win.
A lawsuit
will take at least two years.
If we stop
our project for two years,
we'll miss
the golden development period.
Don't worry.
I won't hire the actor.
I know
what this role is.
I will
find a solution soon.
Have you
been working non-stop?
I rest every weekend.
What did you do last weekend?
I played golf with a business partner.
The week before last?
I visited an event venue.
You did not rest.
You need an actual rest.
How could I?
If I rest,
the whole company has to rest.
You skipped
extreme sports for a long time.
I was busy.
I forgot when
was the last time I did it.
I've lost
my former self.
What?
What are you doing?
Help you solve your problem.
I am busy.
Just go.
I haven't changed my shoes.
Where are we going?
Okay.
Let's meet up later.
During our university years,
we came here to have fun.
I have
an afternoon meeting
and
must make an appointment
with the lawyer
about the film investors' lawsuit
and...
I own the original script of the movie.
If you don't obey me today, I'll give
the project
to someone.
Your job today
is to take a good rest.
I want you
to get away from your work
and like you said,
find your old self.
Hello!
I've warmed up.
We can start.
Long time no see, Xiaogao.
Hello, long time no see.
You haven't changed.
Join us?
He is afraid of water.
Right.
Just like back then.
Come, let's adjust the board.
Okay.
I'm surprised
that you still ski.
I always like this
but was busy with work
and couldn't come.
You were the water skiing goddess
for many coaches here.
Right?
Yes.
I haven't skied for years.
I don't know
if I'll feel the same.
You can. No problem.
Let's do it.
Not coming?
I'll go first.
Come!
You can do it.
Let's go!
Let's go.
You got this!
You got this, Ye Qing.
You got this.
You can do it!
I haven't had this much fun
in a long time!
Thank you, Zichen.
What for?
For dragging me here.
Don't mention it.
You looked
excited.
Did you de-stress?
Let me tell you.
Just now,
when I fell,
my mind became clear.
It's just a lawsuit.
If it takes two or five years,
we'll sue
until the copyright expires.
I'm not scared.
Ye Qing,
I booked the bungee jump.
Okay.
Let's go.
There is a good bungee jump site
nearby.
I'll jump first
before we go back.
Let's go.
I'll go too.
Isn't it boring just watching?
I'm not watching.
I...
I'll jump too.
Don't you have acrophobia?
No.
Let's go.
You can do it.
Come.
It's so high.
Are you okay?
Really?
Are you first?
I'll go first.
I can do it.
Here.
Here. Ready. Walk forward.
[Warning! These stunts are dangerous.
Do not attempt any of the stunts.]
Turn around.
Are you okay?
Come.
When I count down
to one,
let go of both hands
at the same time.
Ready.
Three.
Two.
One. Let go!
Zichen.
Are you okay?
Lu Zichen!
I think he fainted.
Zichen.
Lu Zichen.
Wake up.
Are you alive?
Lu Zichen!
Wake up!
I was
a member of the centre.
The coach was very nice.
He was my senior
but
he quit medicine for business.
Is that so?
Sounds like
you haven't been there lately.
I've been very busy at work.
Moreover,
most of my friends
don't want to climb.
After today,
I'll regain
my passion for the hobby.
Sure.
We can go together next time.
Good idea.
The director
created a WeChat group.
I'll add you.
Okay.
You're awake.
Let me examine you.
Slowly.
Slow down. Slow down.
Let's check your heartbeat.
It's a bit fast.
Do you have
any discomfort?
All indicators are normal.
You were shocked.
After the drip,
we'll discharge you
if you're fine.
Okay. Thank you, doctor.
No problem.
Keep in touch via WeChat.
Okay.
Bye.
-Bye-bye.
How are you feeling now?
Are you writing
about extreme sports next?
No.
I know.
It's about what a suicide jumper feels.
No.
I'm fine.
Good.
After you passed out,
the company kept calling.
I must go back to do some work.
I'll pick you up later.
I'm fine.
I'm okay by myself.
I'll ask Nan Xing to pick you up.
I'll work overtime.
WeChat me if you need anything.
Isn't our story
worth writing?
How do I write the beginning
of the story of Xiao Wudi and me?
I am back.
Are you back, mum?
Is the power back?
This is so weird.
The power went on and off
intermittently.
What did the electrician say?
Nothing.
I don't know either.
Are you writing?
Go ahead.
I won't disturb you.
How should I write?
[Xiao Wudi]
[How is the progress?]
How does he know I am writing?
[Nan Xing]
[I'm getting ready to write.]
[Do you need raw material from me?]
[Xiao Wudi]
[Not yet.]
[I've decided]
[Xiao Wudi]
[to support your writing career.]
[I'll be there for you.]
[Nan Xing]
He's quite attentive.
[No hurry.]
[It's a love story.]
[When you get stuck,]
[you will]
[ask for my help.]
How do I write this?
[Then,]
[you have to practice with me]
[on the male and female leads'
interactions,]
[and learn about dating,]
[holding hands,]
[and hugging.]
[Even...]
This is embarrassing.
What will she write about me?
Why don't I ask her?
Stop.
I'm in a mess.
I shouldn't take the initiative
to see her or let her know
that I care about this.
Mum, hurry up.
I'll be late
in the rush hour.
Lock it.
Let's go.
I said I won't ask
but I didn't say
I won't peek.
She wrote it!
[Xiao Wudi, Young Master Hehuan]
Young Master Xiao,
I made breakfast for you.
[Breakfast Maid, Nan Xiaoxing]
A breakfast with less than ten courses.
Is that fit for humans?
I spent my money
on ordering takeouts for you.
I have no more money.
That's not a problem.
Lu Zichen...
No!
Why is
Lu Zichen in there?
[Nan Xiaoxing thought]
[that she had escaped,]
[but unfortunately]
[she hadn't escaped]
[Xiao Wudi's clutches.]
[Xiao Wudi is the devil.]
That's not right.
What did she write?
[My Demonic Neighbour by Nan Xing]
[My Demonic Neighbour?]
[My Demonic Neighbour]
In her mind,
I'm just a demonic neighbour.
She is ungrateful.
I am sincere with you
but how do you repay me?
Fine.
I'll also write an article about you
to remind you
about the truth.
Where should I start?
Xiao Wudi, Young Master Hehuan,
is
a great hero respected by everyone.
One day,
he was suddenly summoned
to this real world, where danger
lurks on every side.
Is
this handsome guy
sent by heaven?
Why is he still asleep?
Maybe
I'll wake you up with a kiss.
He looks dignified
and suave.
How dare you
take advantage of me
and make sexual advances?
I was
attracted to you.
Please forgive me.
Young Master, please have breakfast.
Is it unappetizing?
I just woke up and have no appetite.
Didn't you say earlier
that anything less than ten courses
isn't fit for humans?
Young Master,
please eat some.
A woman should keep her distance.
You are flirty.
No one will marry you.
My life was ruined the moment I saw you.
I have
seen your real face.
I will only marry you and no one else.
Ridiculous.
A marriage is not child's play.
I won't marry you.
Young Master,
if you can't marry me,
let me stay,
even as a maid to wash your feet.
Absolutely not.
I'll do anything!
No.
Don't leave me!
Let me stay
and you can have my car, house,
and household registration book.
If I leave,
will you kill yourself?
Yes.
If you dare to leave me,
I'll kill myself.
Fine.
I pity you.
You may stay.
Thank you, Young Master.
[Nan Xiaoxing stopped crying immediately.]
[A bright smile appeared on her face.]
[It's as if her lifelong wish]
[has been fulfilled.)
What's this?
My Hero Master.
Did you
call me home to read this?
The story I wrote
is more suitable
for our real-life relationship
and fits your real-life
fangirl character.
I'm not a fangirl anymore.
It's...
You
can't see yourself.
How do you know you're not?
Wudi Bear,
do you think
he is narcissistic?
I am just
giving you a reference.
I'm here to remind you
that when you write,
do not
deviate from the basic reality.
Hasn't he deviated
from the basic reality?
I clearly remember
what was in my mind.
I was scared of him
and wanted to avoid him.
Why would I
kneel and beg him to marry me?
Why are you afraid of me?
You are scary.
You threatened me in my dream,
followed me home,
and slept next to me.
Then you kidnapped Aunt An
to force me to cooperate.
You...
Any normal person will be scared.
Wrong.
Please explain
why is it that
when you first saw me,
you said dirty words to me when I was
unconscious?
A handsome guy in ancient costumes.
The heroine comes to his rescue.
It is love at first sight for him.
Finally, he promises to marry her.
What was that?
Casual remarks?
Yes.
He wants to hit me.
Fine.
Since we two disagree
about the direction,
we can stop writing this novel!
This was originally
written by me.
Why are you intervening?
Am I?
Don't forget
that I asked you
to write this novel.
I am the main character in this novel.
I said every word he said,
and did everything
he did.
I own half of it.
What
do you want to do?
What do I want to do?
Listen.
This story
belongs to
both of us.
Before it is published,
both of us
should reach an agreement.
You're overthinking this.
It's far from ready for publication.
I have to warn you first.
Did you
write
something not presentable?
[He mustn't know]
[about My Demonic Neighbour.]
Let me read.
No.
I haven't written anything.
I've been busy lately.
Busy doing what?
I'll go back and write.
Bye-bye.
It's pretty good.
If he sees this,
I'm dead.
I describe
the male lead as the boss.
I can't submit this.
Am I so scary?
Does she have a bad impression of me?
[Because you are scary.]
You threatened me in my dream,
followed me home,
and slept next to me.
Then you kidnapped Aunt An
to force me to cooperate.
You...
Any normal person will be scared.
That's why she misunderstood.
Indeed, I said
I wanted to kidnap Aunt An.
Any normal person would be afraid,
but I didn't mean it.
I didn't do it.
What else can I write?
I am right about
she being a fangirl.
I heard it.
I am handsome.
That should counterbalance
her impression of me.
I'll find out tomorrow.
Senior, please slow down.
It's pouring.
Find a shelter or you'll
get a cold.
Never mind.
It's urgent.
Even so,
you shouldn't catch a cold.
Slow down!
Hello, hello!
Are you okay?
Coming.
Slow down.
Don't rush.
No problem.
Hello.
Sorry for being late.
It's okay.
Okay.
Leave us.
Go.
Order food.
May I take your order?
Here.
Thank you.
Two glasses of homemade carbonated water.
Tell me something.
If your senior, Nan Xing,
meets someone
who
might have
offended her
but he is
good looking,
will she feel
slightly
neutral to him?
Definitely not.
What are you thinking?
She doesn't
judge people by their faces.
Is that true?
Yes.
Examples are
the senior she met while jogging,
a Lu Zichen fan
she met on the road,
and a nice guy
who picked up her tissue.
she was obsessed with them.
Then what?
That's all.
Nothing else.
She is
very principled.
It's true.
She likes men
not because she is
a fangirl.
These are different things.
Have a drink.
No, thank you.
I like milk tea.
Order one milk tea.
Well,
I'll make another analogy.
Let's say there is a man
who is a bit cunning
and perhaps
likes to fool people.
Do you think this guy
stand a chance?
Most likely he'll be eliminated.
Listen.
This guy
would not get her.
When she has a bad
first impression,
her mind will be set.
Let me tell you.
I feel that her ideal type
is always the same.
It has never changed.
She only likes
one type.
What type?
Suave, courteous,
and righteous warm guy,
like her novels'
main characters.
That's it.
I know righteousness.
What is a warm guy?
He is...
Look.
Like him.
He holds the umbrella,
protects her under it,
and holds her.
That's a warm guy.
In this restaurant,
he pulls her chair out for her,
places the cutlery for her,
hangs up her clothes,
and then puts those sandwiches
on the table.
Wait.
Then...
Is she
physically challenged?
That's like
having a nurse.
She likes it anyway.
Do you like it?
Of course.
Who doesn't like that?
Isn't that just acting?
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm leaving.
Leaving?
Bye bye.
Thanks for the fried chicken.
It is so fragrant.
Senior,
the coach said...
Hey,
I haven't eaten for two weeks.
Let go.
[Xiao Wudi]
[Miss Nan,]
[I cordially invite you]
[to my house tonight]
[to discuss
the plot of the novel.]
[Your warm friend, Xiao Wudi.]
What's wrong with him?
Such a weird tone.
[I'm meeting my colleague.]
[I might be home late.]
[Nan Xing]
[Xiao Wudi]
[It doesn't matter.]
[I can wait.]
[I won't]
[get mad over a no-show too.]
Weird.
Boss,
why are you here?
Aren't you on leave?
I am fine.
At first, I wanted
to take it easy today
and leave early.
Why don't you rest some more?
Mr. Lu,
how are you feeling?
Much better.
You are...
Miss Ye left her keys
in the ward.
It's my rest day.
So, I dropped by.
It was my fault.
I was perturbed
and forgot about them.
Afterwards,
we'll go rock climbing.
Come along.
No. Continue your chat.
Okay.
What's up?
Can I help you?
It's okay.
Sure?
The day after tomorrow,
are you on a business trip?
Yes.
Business meeting.
I'll meet some partners.
What is it?
You should go back early
in the next two days
and rest.
Okay.
I added you to the extreme sports group.
It held activities
but you never responded.
I saw those messages
but when I got
work-related information,
I lost my mood
and worked instead.
I was busy.
I would love to go.
Isn't it a coincidence
that I return the keys?
I can ask you to go rock climbing.
Thank you so much.
Can you climb?
I won awards before.
Awesome.
We shall see.
Boss,
are you looking for me?
No.
You can do it!
Thanks.
For many years,
no girl had defeated me.
no one called me a girl.
Is Mr. Lu interested in you?
Zichen?
Do you believe in online gossip?
I don't read that.
A few days ago,
he bungee jumped
although he feared heights
and was bad at it.
He did it bravely.
Isn't he interested in you?
Impossible.
Why?
Do you know
that we
did a lot of things together
but every time, it became
work-related.
Do you know
that he took me to the cinema
to watch a New Year's Eve love movie?
Wasn't
that very romantic?
Guess what?
His next series was
a New Year's Eve
cinema dismemberment case.
Awesome.
People change.
After knowing each other for years,
it's normal to fall in love.
Zichen
doesn't
change easily.
For many years,
he
wrote with a pen.
Others think
he is sick
but that's what he is.
After he said
he doesn't like me,
he won't like me.
Did he tell you directly?
He
has another quality.
He is very direct.
Sometimes, men
lie.
Think about
what he said.
My arm is sore.
I should go home and massage.
Take a good rest.
I need
a hot compress too.
If not, tomorrow...
My friend is here.
Okay.
Hello.
Let's meet again.
Okay.
I'll go first.
Bye-bye
Bye-bye.
Are you ready?
Mum.
I'll go across to visit Xiong.
I just created a new dish.
Bring some for him to try.
Okay.
Xiao Wudi, my mother asked me...
Why is the light off?
Is it broken?
Don't move.