♪Who gazes at the stars in the sky?♪
♪Heading towards the shore
in a broken boat♪
♪This time, I'll hold onto fate
and never give in♪
♪Family bonds are hard to maintain♪
♪Who will take me
to the fearless dream?♪
♪As the wind and rain come and fade♪
♪A lone sail sways♪
♪A flower blooms alone
amidst the thorns♪
♪Its petals are pierced by thorns♪
♪Yet it turned into a pair of wings
flying against the wind♪
♪Everything grows through the heart♪
♪Even if dreams are lost♪
♪Smoothing out the surging waves♪
♪Breaking through
the tumultuous sounds of the heart♪
♪Having the courage to resist♪
♪Embracing the chant of destiny♪
♪Only love brings light♪
♪Only love embraces the thorns♪
♪Everything grows through the heart♪
♪Having the courage to resist♪
♪Embracing the chant of destiny♪
[Blossoms in Adversity]
♪Only love brings light♪
[Adapted from the novel
of the same name on cmread.com]
[Episode 9]
Madam Xia.
I hear you cough a lot
at night.
Ms. Su is a little deaf.
I will sleep here for a few days
so I can take care of you.
Madam Hua.
Do you know about
what the yard outside is like now?
Zhi made such a mess
that there's almost no room
for us to stand.
Ms. Qin
slipped on a fruit a few days ago
and she almost hurt her buttock.
Ms. Qin
is always in a flurry.
I'm not here
to bad mouth Zhi.
We've been busy for days
as busy as a bee.
But
Zhi keeps spending our money
and there's nothing in return yet.
If she keeps going like this,
I'm afraid our money
will be gone completely to waste.
Tell you what.
I know what she's up to.
I used to be a merchant too.
I know best
how hard is it to be a merchant.
She's selling fresh food.
But in the Imperial Capital,
The members of the royal family,
or the common folk.
They have seen and tasted
every sort of food.
People can't be impressed
by her mediocre food.
Let's see.
We don't have a signboard,
and let alone a proper shop.
Besides,
this is a word-of-mouth market.
So how can we pull this off?
Don't you agree?
Madam Hua.
She fell into sleep.
Any adjustment?
Young Lady,
the recipe will definitely work.
But
who are we supposed
to bring these all the way to downtown?
They will become sticky
after a while.
I traveled with my Grandfather
back then,
and one time we passed
by the Jiuyi Region.
The people there cut their hair short
and got tattoos on them,
they sat around to eat and drink.
And they didn't have chopsticks.
They all used bamboo sticks
to skewer the food,
and roasted it over the fire.
It was very handy.
We have nothing
but bamboo in this manor.
This can work.
It looks nice this way.
Like a coral beaded bracelet.
Fudong,
Get a name for it.
I...
I am naming it?
Since it's the food you made,
of course you should name it.
Madam Wu said it resembles
a coral beaded bracelet,
but I've never seen one.
When I was a kid,
I loved to play with marbles.
They were red and round, just like this.
How about
we name it honey marble?
Great.
Let's make a few dozen first tomorrow,
and see if people like them in downtown.
We're going to sell them?
Young Lady, hawking in the streets
is quite embarrassing.
You can deduct my monthly pay.
Yingchun and Fudong, are you going?
Young Lady.
I will do everything you ask
no matter how dirty or tiring it is.
I never say no.
But hawking in the streets,
I really...
Now I know.
Animal lanterns?
I can make them.
But if we are selling,
we can't beat
Feng's Lantern Shop
and Liao's Lantern Shop.
It doesn't matter.
We're not selling them.
Alright then.
Mr. Zhong.
make the lanterns
based on these drawings.
These are animal lanterns.
But
no special festival is on the way.
What do you use the lanterns for?
Young Lady.
Will people really buy honey marbles?
Of course they will.
I'm already thinking
about the price of each string.
It was not easy for Fudong
to make a whole pot of these.
Madam Xia.
Miss Zhi.
Usually,
I won't be a buzzkill
seeing you all talking happily together.
It's just that
I still have to say something
that you might not want to hear.
These hawthorn fruits
should taste quite good.
But we're in the middle of nowhere,
we can barely ever see a soul all day.
Even if these fruits are good,
who are you gonna sell them to?
I wanna know
do you have a proper shop
that can greet customers,
or you have some connections
to sell them to?
Madam Xia is always so thoughtful.
So please enlighten me.
Do you have a plan?
I don' know what to do.
But I do know
you can't set up a stall
on the street like the last time
when you were selling
Spring Festival couplets.
That's exactly
what I have
in my mind.
Look at that arrogance.
She talked in a different tone
since she took charge of the family,
I don't have any shops
or connections.
That's why in the past few days,
I went to the city
first thing in the morning.
I observed very carefully
to see the food traffic,
and where would people
like to spend their money at?
So what is your conclusion?
Tomorrow is our
first day of opening.
We must be there
right at the gate of the Academy
when the school is over.
We're a sinful family after all,
so we'd better act in a low-profile way.
So,
We can use this flower
as our sign.
Pair up in two.
Who is with me?
Miss Zhi, you're joking, right?
We are a decent and educated family.
Let alone Ling
and the other younger kids.
Even a maid
doesn't want to lose her dignity.
Hawking in the streets?
What would people think of us?
No noble man will marry a hawker girl.
Madam Xia,
we're on the same page here.
Yingchun, Baoxia.
We will be wearing the lanterns
on our heads
to conceal one's face.
That could draw less attention.
It's just two people in animal headwears
selling the haws.
Who would know who we are?
Keep your distance.
I did.
Do you think this will work out?
Go, hurry up.
I don't know.
Time to go home.
The kids are coming.
Go.
No, you should go.
Come on.
I am not going.
What...
You...
Look, what are they?
A cat.
This is a goldfish.
I want to touch it too.
Stop.
Let me touch it.
Honey marbles.
It's delicious, go ahead.
I want a string, too.
Do you want to try it?
It's so delicious.
Give me a string.
It's not for free.
You need to pay later.
My steward will come to pay you.
Listen to me.
Okay.
My treat.
I want some too.
Okay.
I want to have a taste.
Fudong and Baoxia
brought home with a total of 117 wens
after three hours.
Let's take a ballpark number.
You can have 10 percent of the income
as your wages.
Thank you, Young Lady.
Here.
Take it.
You work hard, you earn your share.
No one can deny that.
If you hadn't been pulling my sleeve...
I would have been...
I didn't pull you.
Who knew?
We have a lot work to do.
Mr. Zhong has already made
many animal lanterns for us.
Right.
His hands are all cut up.
I'm sending him his share, too.
Let's go have a look.
Go.
Look at me.
Honey marbles.
Sour and sweet honey marbles.
Would you like to try some?
Look at the bustling street.
Honey marbles.
Sour and sweet honey marbles.
What's all this noise about?
Honey marbles.
What is that on your head?
That's rare.
They look like fruit vendors.
Let's go find out.
Look at this headwear,
Sour...
Let's go.
Honey marbles.
Sour and sweet honey marbles.
My money.
Catch that thief.
Stop right there.
A little thief.
So stupid.
Exactly.
He shouldn't have...
Agree.
He...
stole my money.
Whose money is this?
I...
Um...
You don't want your money back?
He looks
fine.
Please give it to me.
Thank you.
I...
He got in my way.
I... I... I wasn't helping you.
Don't... don't get this wrong.
Because I wasn't.
Soaking the haws
makes my hands even turn white.
Look at them.
Come on, dry your hands with this.
Okay.
Yingzhen.
Where have you been?
I can't help much.
So I went to Mr. Zhong
and helped him cut some lantern paper,
and applied some paste to them.
We're short on lanterns.
There are haws
all over the ground outside.
And now you're
moving them inside the house?
Yingzhen, Huilan.
What are you
also join their little business?
What else can we do?
Anyway, I have to earn some money
to buy stationery for Boli.
Look at you.
Money is all you care about now.
Where is Ms. Qin?
Where did she go?
She?
She went into the kitchen
first thing in the morning.
Right, Yingzhen?
Young Lady.
When will it be the end
of this kind of rough life?
Are we to set up a stall for a lifetime?
Hang in there.
We need to keep doing this
for at least three months
to take a further step.
We need the whole Imperial Capital
know about us and our honey marbles.
Three months?
Young Lady.
Hearing the beautiful sound
of the money,
three months are nothing,
I could do it for another three years.
Let's go.
Who is that annoying guy?
From the Security Bureau.
I know who he is.
Come on.
I hate this thing.
Aren't you ashamed?
Young Lady.
I've thought it through.
There's nothing shameful
about earning money.
From now on,
I'm not wearing this thing.
Let's go.
Don't you know about that?
Those girls from the Hua Family
have a lot of tricks up their sleeves.
I even went to their stall
and checked on them.
Sir.
What I'm worried about
is that those women
would stir up trouble
using food-selling as their disguise.
We can't let our guard down.
I saw them.
There's nothing on their sign
but a flower
painted on it.
My point is
Miss Zhi
is indeed a smart lady.
Why didn't she just write her surname?
[*Hua means flower in Chinese]
For one thing,
the Hua Family has been incriminated,
she doesn't wanna
draw any unnecessary attention.
For another,
their customers are mostly children,
a little pretty flower
can impress them.
Sir.
Do you agree
with what I'm saying?
That's it?
You talked for so long,
and yet you didn't buy some to try?
Do you want to eat the haws, too?
My sister wants that.
It was sold out quick.
Your sister likes it too, huh?
Well,
have you finished running 30 laps yet?
No.
Then go already.
Sir...
There's still a lot of work waiting,
I'll go...
I'll get it done.
This table is not good,
Replace it with a smaller one tomorrow,
Will do.
Come sit with me, Yanxi.
Did you remember
the time when I was a kid?
You were busy with state affairs,
imperial uncle.
Back then, during meals,
there was just a low table
placed beside,
and even if you were dining,
you would also test me on my studies.
In those days,
You grew so tall so quickly
and became so big.
Bus you still sat by such a small table,
being my accompany.
Changqing.
Bring back that tea tabl
back in here.
I and Yanxi
will still dine like that in the future,
Yes,
I'm old,
I can't eat too much meat for my health.
You should eat more.
Venison?
I remember it was your favorite.
I remember
it was you who taught me
how to hunt deer.
Start a fire in the hunting land
then we could cut the meat
and drink the blood.
Now I'm too old
to ride a horse.
Well,
Yanxi.
Ever since you took over
the Security Bureau,
you have done a great job.
It was just that
there were not enough killings.
I know
that you are a kind
and decent kid.
However,
don't show mercy to anyone
who gets in your way.
By doing so,
you will have less troubles
in the future.
I see.
An old man
just loves to preach.
I've said enough,
let's enjoy the dinner.
How is the investigation going
about your mother?
Not a clue.
Eat up.
Two wens.
Come on!
Here, take this.
Thank you.
I want one.
Two wens.
Here you go, thank you.
Here, take it.
Thank you.
I'll have a skewer too.
Here.
Thanks a lot.
Young Lady.
The man from the Security Bureau.
I don't care who he is.
You want my marbles,
you pay up.
Don't cut in line!
That person is an inspector
of the Security Bureau,
you've had a dispute with him before.
No wonder he looks so familiar.
Just take it.
You give me a stick for what?
Judging by the way he looked at you,
he probably recognized you.
Thank god he didn't
make things difficult for you.
It is you I should thank.
What brings you here?
I heard a new kind of fruit is for sale
on the Willow Street
and there's even a flower painted
on the signs.
No risk, no gain.
But it's not good for business
in the long term
if you keep putting a cover up for this.
It all depends on
what His Majesty is thinking.
I wish I could ask him in person.
Enough talk of that.
Try it.
This might just be
the ones you picked the other day.
You're not a fan of sourness, right?
I've never had it before.
Then wait three more days.
You can come back
after we make the fruits sweeter.
Daddy, I want to eat this.
Miss,
how much for the fruit?
One wen each.
I'll take one.
Just one?
Have at it, kid.
Daddy, we can share.
Daddy doesn't like it.
You go on.
Mister, please wait.
One wen for two.
This one is on the house.
Thank you, Miss.
It's our turn now.
Eat slowly.
Thank you.
Thanks a lot.
I wonder
what is it like
between the fathers and sons
among the common folks?
Probably they are just like us now.
The young kid listens
to his preachy old man
when they're eating.
I really am getting old.
How would you know
the situation amongst the common folks?
Being in the royal family,
we are meant to
be different from those ordinary people.
You come to have a meal with me
from time to time,
that's enough for me.
Won't you lose money doing business
by such a generosity?
No, the marbles don't worth much.
Then in a couple of days,
Please keep one skwer for me
when you make new honey marbles
in two days.
Wrap it up in the paper
painted with flowers.
Alright.
Do you buy that for your family?
I want my uncle to taste it.
Look.
Madam is making the fruits works of art
even though she is just pitting them.
Let's get to work.
Let me see it.
Please.
Go inside the house first.
Go inside.
Come.
Aren't they adorable?
Absolutely.
So adorable.
Three.
Four, five.
Where did all the poultry
come from?
You bought them?
That was quick.
I know I'm amazing.
We have to wait until they grow up.
Does that mean
we will have eggs to eat?
Zhi says,
we keep buying eggs of the poultry,
and it costs a lot of money.
So we can raise them ourselves,
also as a pastime.
How many chickens and ducks are there?
Don't lean forward.
You shouldn't bend over.
Mind your belly.
Baozhu.
Here's yours.
How much is that?
Come on, let me see.
Yinzhu.
Fudong.
How much did you get?
Not as much as that
before the family hit a downfall.
But it's way better than
I got last month.
Why are you running? Show me.
Stop nosing around.
Tell you what?
One of us is paid the most.
Who is it?
It's an open secret already, okay?
Fudong, of course.
Isn't that so?
She took a whole guan.
If it was not for her,
we couldn't have had our pay
in the first place.
She gets more than the rest of us,
that's because she deserves it.
Baozhu,
Let me see how much you've got.
I don't care about the others,
I only wanna know your share.
How much did you get?
Show me.
That ungrateful girl!
What's wrong with her?
Fob me off with just half a guan.
Isn't she?
Go.
Madam.
She is stealing,
I can catch her on the site.
Keep it down.
I will deal with her
when the right time comes.
How lovely!
Let's get to it.
We can head home early
after we finish it.
We can have a hot meal, then.
Young Lady, look at this.
Young Lady, take a look.
This one is pretty.
Hua Zhi.
What are you doing here?
I'm heading somewhere.
What are you picking?
The pastry we made sold well
the other day.
Fudong wants to
improve the recipe better.
She asked me
to pick these green leaves
and dye the dough.
The fragrance of the plant
will burst in your mouth.
So it's my off day
for being a hawker girl today.
I'll have a taste
of your new pastry then.
The other day,
you said you wanted to bring some pastry
for your uncle.
Fudong made a type of honey cake.
It's fragrant and soft.
My Grandmother and Ms. Su love it.
Come to Willow Lane tomorrow.
Take some to him.
Thank you then.
Do you need a hand?
No.
I am a girl who provides for my family.
I am always on my own.
See you tomorrow.
What are these?
There is a Willow Street in the city
specializing in sweet pastry.
This is their newly made honey cakes.
You have been long in the palace,
and rarely taste the food
of the common people.
So I brought you some.
Yanxi.
You earn not much
in the Security Bureau.
Uncle.
This only costs five wens per portion.
Five wens.
I have never had
the pastry that is worth five wens only.
Yummy.
Very sweet.
Go on, share with me.
Go on.
Your Majesty.
May I have one?
Well...
Yanxi bought this for me.
You don't get to eat.
Go away.
Your Majesty.
Lord Xian is here.
Greetings, Father.
Your Highness.
I heard you had a bad appetite recently.
These fruits from Ruihe House
are unrivaled in the Imperial Capital.
I told their head chef
to make some appetizing fruits
for you specifically.
They are still hot.
Please try.
Take it back.
I don't wanna eat.
Your Highness.
These cake
are made by the Hua Family, right?
You're quite discerning.
I heard a few days ago
that family of sinful women
show no repentance,
and now they've even become peddlers.
How come
bring these things
into the Imperial Capital?
What's the big deal?
Just some snacks
made by some women.
Don't make a fuss about that.
I think Yanxi is right,
Since they've given up their dignity,
and started to sell things
on the street.
That means
they degraded themselves to commoners.
Yangong.
You are just narrow-minded,
That's why you care.
I will reflect on myself, Father.
Your Highness.
The pastry?
Throw it away.
Okay.
Wait a moment.
What a waste to throw it away.
I just came back here,
and have not yet tasted
the pastry from Ruihe House.
You do have a good appetite.
Thank you, brother.
Floral cloth.
Take a look at the floral cloth.
Let's take a look.
Calligraphy and painting.
Come and see.
Up for sale.
Why didn’t you make a sound?
You were reading.
I'm killing time here.
[The Mathematical Treatise
in Nine Sections]
Were you solving math problems
to kill time?
This book is very interesting.
Here you are.
The pastry from Ruihe House.
They are very expensive.
Did you buy it?
It was a gift from someone.
Study the recipe when you go back home.
Know yourself, know your enemy.
You can learn from the best.
Fudong has always wanted to
try the pastry of the Ruihe House,
but we can't afford it.
This portion costs half a guan
if I remember it right.
This one here
might cost even more.
Look at the sky.
I'm afraid it's going to rain.
We can only take the pastry back home
and let the family shares.
Baoxia,
cover the pastry.
It's raining so heavily.
Don't push.
♪When all the lights
were taken from the world♪
♪You are my only shimmering star♪
♪You save me with everything♪
♪Protecting me by my side♪
♪Refusing to give up♪
♪Never give up♪
♪Just to seize♪
♪The light of hope♪
Stop the cart.
Smash the stall of the Hua Family.
Yes.
Smash the stall.
Your...
What?
She is the owner.
You wanna buy pastry?
I don't mind if you take it all.
Except for the cart.
Young Lady, don't...
Don't go.
Mister,
It is one guan
for this whole cart of pastry.
Would you like to pay now
or put it on the tab?
Perhaps you haven't brought
enough money.
That's a lot of money.
I cannot make change for this.
Keep the change.
That's very generous of you.
What are you up to?
Please come again
if you like the pastry.
Wrap it up.
Here you go.
What are you looking at? Get going.
Go.
Do you know who that person is?
You almost scared me to death.
I don't know.
Never mind, you'd better not know.
[Yunlai Restaurant]
Won't you have a taste?
Too sweet.
It is very sweet.
Quite tasty.
I really didn't expect this.
You even came up with
such a self-degrading trick,
fraternizing with that criminal woman.
Self-degrading?
What else?
If that's not what you wish for,
do you wish
for her pretty face?
Not even close.
No wonder Father adores you.
You don't care about the rules
and how people think of you.
You are nothing like
a careerist coveting power.
I'm afraid Father
also thinks this way.
If you say no.
Gu Yanxi.
You have no idea
how much I envy you.
I knew.
Back then when imperial uncle
taught me how to read,
you often held your ink and brush
and stared inside, longing to join in.
So I knew.
However,
I am indeed different from you.
Because I am not the heir to the throne.
No matter how I behave,
one way or another,
it makes no difference.
Look at this scar.
Something like this
would never happen to you.
Do you still remember Qi Ruhai,
Your Highness?
How could I forget?
He was a good stooge.
And he died because of you.
That's right.
Do you know who is behind
this private coinage case?
And who told Qi Ruhai
to frame me?
It wasn't me.
Many in the Court think it was you.
So you're saying,
it's impossible to clear my name now.
Alright then,
that was me.
I know it wasn't you.
Because there's only one person
that can make Qi Ruhai
to die without any complaint.
That man make you live in fear.
And he forced me to scar my face
to prove my innocence,
and leave the Northern Land forever.
I see.
So that's how it is.
Gu Yanxi.
It turns out
that you're as miserable as I am.
Don't think that way.
We both lost something,
but also we gained something in return,
haven't we?
Drink?
I never drink.
Gu Yangong.
You're so depressed
living a life like this.
It takes one to know one.
It seems that
although we were born
in the royal family
but perhaps the common folks
are happier than us.
We are rich in wealth,
but poor in soul.
Life is nothing but a temporary stay.
We are destined to wander.
You see,
even the beggars on the streets
and thieves in prison
have their loved ones.
But you and I?
We've got nobody.
What we said toda stays in the room.
I owe you a favor for that.
We
didn't say a word today.
Heading back to the palace?
I'm heading home.
Since you don't like the pastry,
I'll take some off your hands.
You're back, My Lord.
What are you having here?
My Lord,
this is the pastry
Xi bought for me.
He's been so busy.
He's just such a filial kid.
You see?
My Lord,
would you like to try some?
Alright.
How is that?
What?
He went out again?
I heard His Majesty called him back.
Why is he so busy
even though he doesn't even have a job?
Qi Ruhai is dead.
Yanxi is always absent.
I know what he did.
This old fellow.
He's put my son
in a place
that is shady and notorious.
Madam.
These past few days
I've been watching that girl.
Every three days
she takes the stolen honey
and hands it over to an outsider.
When's the next time?
Tomorrow night, I think.
She is too young
to manage a big family.
She is just too naive.
Tomorrow night
I will have her hand me over
that household ledger
with her own hands.
Wait and see
she will be embarrassed
in front of the whole family.
Chanlu.
Ms.
I...
You are
just an ungrateful lowlife.
How dare you
betray all of us?
Everyone comes out.
What's wrong, Jin'e?
Yingzhen,
you have no idea, aren't you?
This girl
is about to sell all the honey
to the outsiders.
Madam.
Madam, help.
Aunt Xia.
What is going on?
She
stole the honey of the cooked haws.
She met with someone
in the middle of the night,
and delivered it outside the manor.
Why are you coming out.
Be careful with your baby.
Go back.
They...
It's fine, go back.
She
is one of Madam Zhu's maids.
So I am
in no position to deal with her.
Since you take charge of the family now.
Tell me,
what should we do with her?
Chanlu.
Speak up.
I did wrong.
You can punish me in any ways.
If this is true,
why bother with punishment?
Just kick her out.
Since this isn't a false accusation,
you should at least tell us why.
Miss Zhi,
my...
My mother needs to take medicine
all year round.
I can pay for the medicine
with my monthly allowance
in the past.
But ever since we came here...
Miss Zhi,
I made a mistake.
Miss Zhi is too young
and Yingzhen is always nice
to the maids.
I can see why Chenlu
had the guts to steal.
Okay.
Jin'e.
Zhi is too busy.
She has to arrange
our food and everything day after day.
Let alone she has to
keep an eye on her business
in the daytime.
After she comes back,
she needs to do the accounts
until midnight.
It's normal when someone steals
under her watch.
Exactly.
You have too many things to do,
so you've got no time
for the household affairs.
Chanlu
is one of Madam Zhu's maids.
Well,
even if Miss Zhi
do know about this,
you just can't punish her right away
because she's
one of your mother's maids, right?
From what I see,
you two
seem to have planned this early on.
Stay out of this.
Madam Qi.
I'm not picking sides here.
But to be honest,
if Madam Xia is still in charge
of the household ledger
none of this would ever happen.
Miss Zhi,
do you agree?
Madam Hua said
she heard you fighting outside
so late.
You can go to her room
and figure out what to do
and make things clear.
Zhi.
Ask away.
Fudong.
You've known for a while
that Chanlu was stealing honey.
I already entrust you with the kitchen.
Why didn't you say anything?
She's one of your maids.
How dare she
get in the way of your mother's maid?
Our family now
have to work hard
to provide food on the table.
You're the peddler on the street,
and Fudong is a pastry chef
in the kitchen.
You've got so many people
looked up to you,
I understand it's difficult
to make everybody happy.
Yes.
I've heard that those maids of Miss Zhi
would get more monthly allowance
than other people.
I've got
plenty of time anyway,
I would like to share the burden,
then we can sleep tight at night.
Madam Hua,
what do you say?
Back in the day,
I would have
disabled your hands
and kicked you out.
Madam Hua, please don't.
I won't do it again, I promise.
♪Not a patch of land is wasted♪
♪No tea plant is left withered♪
♪The sky drops rain, birds eat worms,
and chickens leave manure♪
♪Using effort and sweat
to water and nourish♪
♪The tea leaves may be rustic♪
♪But the taste is of spring♪
♪Ah, in the early spring,
we pick the tea leaves♪
♪Ah, let's enjoy
the abundant spring together♪
♪Not a patch of land is wasted♪
♪No tea plant is left withered♪
♪The sky drops rain, birds eat worms,
and chickens leave manure♪
♪Using effort and sweat
to water and nourish♪
♪The tea leaves may be rustic♪
♪But the taste is of spring♪
♪Ah, in the early spring,
we pick the tea leaves♪
♪Ah, let's enjoy
the abundant spring together♪
♪Ah, in the early spring,
we pick the tea leaves♪
♪Ah, let's enjoy
the abundant spring together♪