♪Who gazes at the stars in the sky?♪
♪Heading towards the shore
in a broken boat♪
♪This time, I'll hold onto fate
and never give in♪
♪Family bonds are hard to maintain♪
♪Who will take me
to the fearless dream?♪
♪As the wind and rain come and fade♪
♪A lone sail sways♪
♪A flower blooms alone
amidst the thorns♪
♪Its petals are pierced by thorns♪
♪Yet it turned into a pair of wings
flying against the wind♪
♪Everything grows through the heart♪
♪Even if dreams are lost♪
♪Smoothing out the surging waves♪
♪Breaking through
the tumultuous sounds of the heart♪
♪Having the courage to resist♪
♪Embracing the chant of destiny♪
♪Only love brings light♪
♪Only love embraces the thorns♪
♪Everything grows through the heart♪
♪Having the courage to resist♪
♪Embracing the chant of destiny♪
[Blossoms in Adversity]
♪Only love brings light♪
[Adapted from the novel
of the same name on cmread.com]
[Episode 39]
Why are you slacking off here?
The Palace has been cleaned today.
Master Haoyue has gone
to the Chenglu Palace,
and she left me no orders.
Don't spend all day here daydreaming.
You can't possibly go outside.
Ma'am, do you know
where Shen Pavilion is?
Just walk a few hundred steps
to the north.
But with four tall walls blocked,
no matter how hard you crane your neck
and stand on your tiptoes,
[Astronomy Institute]
you won't see a thing.
He came to hear me sing every day.
Every time he arrived,
he would fly his kite.
Then I would know he was outside.
♪When all the lights
were taken from the world♪
♪You are my only shimmering star♪
♪You save me with everything♪
♪Protecting me by my side♪
♪Refusing to give up♪
♪Never give up♪
[I hope the wind delivers my love to you]
♪Just to seize♪
♪The light of hope♪
♪We're like walking
in the opposite direction♪
♪We keep missing each other
day and night♪
♪Destiny keeps us wrapped
around its finger♪
♪Twilight is the sun's gentleness
bestowed upon the moon♪
♪They permeate into each other♪
♪If you nod, I'll never look back♪
♪I will go against the flow of time
to be by your side♪
♪I once had a rift in my heart♪
♪Waiting for you to light up my world♪
♪When all the lights
were taken from the world♪
♪You are my only shimmering star♪
[I hope the wind sends my love to you]
♪You save me with everything♪
♪Protecting me by my side♪
♪Refusing to give up♪
Yanxi.
When you see this kite,
you will know
that within these high walls,
I am thinking of you every moment
and wondering how you are doing.
♪The light of hope♪
Hua Zhi.
Night after night,
I hope you can appear in my dream
and reunite with me.
There's not even a single cup of tea
in this Palace.
That's how you work
as a maid?
I can prepare tea for you,
Master Haoyue.
But do you really want it?
You're reluctant to do that.
I'll go prepare right away.
Please enjoy.
Why is it so bitter?
What have you put in there?
I probably added too many tea leaves
and brewed the tea for too long.
Are you showing off
that you're a pampered daughter
from a wealthy family,
so you feel aggrieved to be my maid?
I don't blame you.
In the Imperial Capital,
who doesn't know you
as the Jade God of Wealth?
Your business
has even expanded to Jinyang.
But I really don't get it.
In your family,
isn't there any man
who knows propriety
to teach such a spoiled girl
who is pushy like you?
There are no men left in my family,
but only women and kids.
With so many people to provide for,
if I were to continue
to be a pampered daughter,
I could only watch them starve to death.
My grandfather and uncles
are in Sanbai City,
which is thousands of li away.
The men of your family
are all in Sanbai City?
You've been there?
What if I have?
You're from the northern land?
It has nothing to do with you
whether I've been there or not.
They have all been exiled.
Don't you hate the Emperor?
What's the point even if I hate him?
You really think so?
So you just push it all out
of your mind,
focus on making money,
and be a lucrative business owner?
I have to make money.
I need money
to support women and children at home
and I also need it
to redeem those exiled ones.
I couldn't redeem them as I wished.
The money I earned
has all been spent
on the construction of the Grand Canal.
But the farmlands of three provinces
get irrigated
and the people get to live.
It was well spent in some way.
I am even a bit envious of you.
I would never be in a good mood
to have such a servant like you.
Starting from today,
you don't have to
do those maid tasks in this Palace.
You know how to read and write.
I will have Haining
arrange a transcription job for you.
What are you still standing there for?
Get going now.
Get me a smart maid.
I don't want a pain in the neck.
[Fengtai Shop]
Ladies.
Come on.
Please come inside.
We have all sorts
of rare and exotic treasures.
Help yourself.
All fine stuff.
Sir.
These past few days,
we have searched every shop out there
that was owned by foreign merchants.
About a dozen shopkeepers
said that
before they entered Daqing,
someone asked them
to bring things
into the Imperial Capital.
But soon after,
Haoyue came and bought those things.
What did she buy?
Most were ritual implements.
Their shapes were somewhat peculiar,
but none of them
were of real practical use.
She also bought more than a dozen types
of Western Regions' medicinal herbs.
Physician Zhang has looked
into the herbs,
but none of them had a particular use.
Except for one thing.
Some strange red powder.
Don't know what it is used for.
Physician Zhang couldn't recognize it,
so I had a death row inmate try it.
Nothing happened to him.
Take this
and go to a person.
They won't come back.
They will come back.
Well, what happened
to her?
They won't come back.
She has been like this
since what happened to
Young Lady and Mr. Yan that day.
As soon as night falls,
she will ask the moon
when Yanxi and Zhi
will come back.
And in the daytime,
she just stands there,
not eating or sleeping.
They will come back.
Let's go.
They won't come back.
Shaoyao.
Your brother sent me.
Really?
Yes.
He said
Shaoyao was the smartest.
When it comes to
rare and peculiar medicines,
you are the only one
who can recognize them.
Take a look at this.
This medicine,
I can't recognize it, either.
If I can recognize it,
does it mean I could help Yanxi and Zhi?
Yes.
If you can recognize this medicine,
perhaps your brother and Miss Zhi
can come back.
I see.
Don't leave.
I'll go back to Lord Ling's Mansion
and check the medicine books.
Why did you lie to her?
It wasn't lying.
I was just giving her some hope.
She can hold onto that.
Well...
Don't feel so sad.
I... I've asked around.
Miss Zhi is doing quite well
in the Palace.
Don't cry.
Haoyue has been secluding herself
to refine pills these past few days.
What ingredients is she using?
And what kind of pills is she refining?
It's last night's
astronomical observation record.
Ms. Haining asked you
to transcribe it into the report,
so I can present it to Master Haoyue.
Wait a moment.
There's a mistake here.
Where is it?
On the day of Yisi,
two moons appeared at the same time
in the southwest.
Yesterday was the fourth day
of the lunar month.
After sunset,
the new moon rose from the southwest.
The appearance of two moons
must have been an illusion
caused by the blurry clouds.
If you present such a report,
Master Haoyue considers the change
as an inauspicious portent,
and chaos is caused,
there will be serious consequences.
When you transcribe it,
remember to make a correction.
Thank you so much for mentioning this.
[Astronomical Observation Record]
Why was the appearance of two moons
not recorded in the report?
The transcriber Miss Zhi said
the moon didn't change last night.
It was just an illusion
caused by blurry clouds.
She thought it might cause you trouble
if His Majesty noticed that.
That was why she didn't record it.
Why did she know about astronomy?
Your eyes must become tired now.
How about
we take a rest for a while?
I can't.
The sooner I find it,
the sooner Yanxi and Zhi
can come back.
I miss them so much.
It's you.
It surprised me
that you would have a sleepless night.
You do know how to entertain yourself.
You spotted the mistake on the record.
Was it because you sneaked in here
and observed the stars last night?
I can't predict things like you.
Of course, I saw it with my own eyes.
This armillary sphere is identical
to the one in the Seven Stars Mansion.
It must have been made
based on Mr. Mengxi's design.
You know about Mr. Mengxi?
Should I not know?
He measured the pole star
with an armillary sphere,
and after observation
for over three months,
he drew hundreds of star maps.
I've read all of his notes.
You can read star maps?
No wonder in the daytime,
you noticed the mistake on the record.
Yes.
There are 1460 stars
on the star map of Su Song.
I remember them all.
You memorize them by rote.
Aren't you tired?
I am interested in it,
so I am willing to learn.
How could it be tiring?
It's just a pity
that I can't travel far and wide
like they do,
chasing the stars and watching the moon.
What about you?
Why are you so proficient
in celestial events?
I was not like you,
who could only learn from books.
Ever since I was a child,
I learned to use
the Star-Orienting Board
from my parents.
During the day, I would observe the sky.
At night, I would observe the moon.
I have seen so many times
when the sea met the sky.
Gradually, I had a grasp on it.
You've been out to sea?
I grew up on sailing boats.
I know everything
about the sky.
When I was young,
I took a ship once
with my grandfather to Qiongzhou.
And I saw the waves at sea.
It was so splendid
that it took my breath away.
The seas in the south
can be considered splendid?
You really should see
the icy sea of my hometown.
The sea is frozen over thousands of li
and meets with the sky.
When the waves rise,
even the most solid ice
would break apart.
It seems like the sky and the earth
are shattered into pieces.
When the sun goes down,
the sky and the earth are crystal clear
and it looks like a crystal world.
Unfortunately,
I don't get to see it anymore.
The icy sea?
Ice sea only exists on the land
where is extremely cold.
You come from the northern land.
Shut up.
Mind your words.
You are already
miserable enough now.
You'd better mind your own business.
You are now a hostage.
The Emperor
is your true enemy.
You surely don't
want to become his pawn
or his spy, right?
It's a lunar corona.
It is mostly obscured by clouds,
but I can't be wrong.
It is a lunar corona.
The weather is changing.
You succeeded once again.
This time,
how shall I reward you?
I am just a mortal.
To pray for rain,
we have to choose
the favorable weather conditions
and geographic advantages.
Today, all five elements are present,
so we succeeded in praying for rain.
In five days,
it will be your Longevity Festival.
I am willing to partake
in the fireworks show
and pray once more for the rain
to wish Your Majesty a long life.
[Astronomy Institute]
What are these bamboo poles for?
For setting up the fireworks rack.
Master Haoyue wants a firework show,
so she can pray to heaven for rain
on the Longevity Festival.
Before the Longevity Festival,
fire is not allowed within the Palace.
This batch of fireworks is valuable.
We can't afford any mistakes.
Yes.
It's the smell of sulfur.
Hua Zhi.
What are you trying to tell me?
[Shen Pavilion]
Zhi.
You really are here.
Did Gu Yanxi send you?
He wanted me to ask you
if anything abnormal came up.
Come take a look at this.
This...
[Lord Ling's Mansion]
Shaoyao.
Today is the Longevity Festival.
Many ingredients need to be purchased
for the kitchen of Zhiming Building.
I need to hurry over and help.
- Is that so?
- Here.
Fill your stomach with this.
When I come back tonight,
I'll bring you something delicious.
Tasty.
Aren't you busy? You'd better hurry.
I still haven't found that medicine.
Alright.
Then I will leave you to it.
Don't touch my head.
I can't grow taller if you do that.
I am leaving.
Wait for me.
Don't be too late.
A stone is produced
in the Western Regions,
named red stone.
It can remove phlegm and relieve asthma.
If it is calcined with realgar,
it will turn into a green stone.
Green...
[Renji Pharmacy]
Sir.
Is there any realgar available?
You come for realgar again.
That's really unfortunate.
The newly arrived realgar
has all been bought by that young lady.
[Lord Ling's Mansion]
Her hands are stained
with red stone powder.
[Lord Ling's Mansion]
And she also bought realgar.
Has she already
known about that?
Then she can't be alive.
She might be from Lord Ling's Mansion.
If we kill her,
it might draw attention
and jeopardize the master's
greater cause.
If that's the case,
we have to make her death
look like an accident.
We haven't been too busy recently.
Only some new death row inmates
came into the prison.
Have Shaoyao
found what kind of medicine that was?
You go and ask her.
Yes.
I'll go ask again.
If it is calcined with realgar,
it will turn into a green stone.
Green.
So this is the green stone.
It is highly toxic.
Fire! Fire!
- Need help here!
- Come on!
Fire!
What happened?
Lady Shaoyao's room is on fire.
Go get water.
Shaoyao.
Hurry.
Coming.
Shaoyao.
Get out of here!
Is she still inside?
Yes.
Shaoyao.
Shaoyao, where are you?
Are you alright?
Why didn't you run outside?
I... I'm scared...
Come on, I'll get you out of here.
Shaoyao, go!
Shaoyao.
Get out of here!
Mother!
Shen Huan.
I couldn't save my mother in that fire,
but now,
I can save you.
Is there anyone still inside?
- Yes.
Shaoyao.
I was so useless.
I wanted to play the hero
and go in there to save you.
- No.
- But...
You were incredibly brave
and amazing.
The fire was so huge,
but you rushed in to save me
without hesitation.
I'm glad you said that.
Shen Huan.
I've always thought
that I was terrified of fire
because it took my mother away.
All these years,
I couldn't even bear to look at it.
But
just now
when you were lying on the ground
covered in fire,
I thought
the most terrifying thing
was that you would also disappear.
My affection for you
overcame my fear.
I seemed to have gotten over a hurdle
and over a mountain.
You like me?
Yes.
I like you so much.
I...
I am all dizzy now.
You'd better not lie to me.
I mean every word of it.
Love story.
Stop it.
Where should we go now?
Go back to the Security Bureau?
We can't.
His Majesty has already sent men
to spy on the Bureau.
Let's go to the Hua Mansion.
Giddy up.
Illuminate one's bright virtues
and cultivate the populace.
Jian.
Why are you reciting like this?
Yanxi told me
that I wouldn't feel sleepy this way
and also could strengthen my body.
Good.
Hurry.
What happened?
Close the door.
What happened really?
Come on.
Get them settled.
The three of them
are out of strength.
Go.
Well,
Miss Shaoyao.
What happened?
Did you set the house on fire
when making medicine?
No.
When I was making medicine,
I was knocked out by someone.
And then,
I woke up in the fire.
That powder
is from red stones,
which is non-toxic.
But
after being calcined with realgar,
it would turn into
highly toxic green stones.
Highly toxic?
Today is the Longevity Festival.
His Majesty has prepared a banquet
in the Palace.
This is bad.
The medicinal powder is from the Palace?
Then you must hurry there
to report this.
We are just nobodies,
so we don't have the opportunity
to meet His Majesty.
But...
The Commander is still locked up
in the Shen Pavilion.
I mean...
What should we do?
What about the Empress Dowager?
Can you get to meet her?
She is in the Shanhua Temple.
It is heavily guarded there.
We can't get in.
I'll go with you.
Grandmother
knows who I am.
Jian,
don't be afraid.
I'll go with you.
I will go with you
to see your grandmother.
I'll come along too.
You need to rest.
Go now.
I'll take care of Huan.
Let's go, Shaoyao.
Let's go.
Come on.
Father.
The wind is getting stronger.
Please keep warm.
I am not cold.
I am glad that you concern me.
Father.
I will toast to you.
Changqing.
Yes.
How is Yanxi doing?
Your Majesty.
How about
I bring him here to keep you company?
Do you want him
to cause a scene again
at my Longevity Festival?
Let him reflect
in the Shen Pavilion.
As you command.
Stop there! Who are you?
Chen Qing and Zheng Hu
from the Security Bureau.
We want to see the Empress Dowager.
The Empress Dowager is on a retreat now.
She cannot be disturbed
by anyone.
If you do want to see her,
let the Commander come in person.
I recognize you.
You used to serve at Gongchen Gate,
didn't you?
I am Gu Yanzhao, the Sixth Prince.
I'm here to send greetings
to my grandmother.
Greetings, Your Highness.
- Greetings, Empress Dowager.
- Greetings, Grandmother.
Zhao.
How could you...?
You are still alive.
Grandmother.
I will explain to you later
about what happened.
This lady here has something important
to tell you.
Empress Dowager.
Shaoyao.
Child.
You...
You're Shaoyao, aren't you?
How do you recognize me?
When your mother was still alive,
I had seen you and your mother.
You look just like your mother.
You look like her so much!
Child.
Tell me.
What has happened?
His Majesty has set a banquet
in the Palace,
but...
The Dubhe Envoy has arrived.
Your Majesty.
The auspicious time is approaching.
You shall begin.
The auspicious time has arrived.
Begin.
Heaven creates the mountains and rivers
to stabilize all quarters.
It bestows food upon the people
with rain and sunshine.
The deities provide for the people.
The officials serve the Emperor.
The officials attend to
agriculture and sericulture.
The deities
control the rain and the sunshine.
Heaven creates the mountains and rivers
to stabilize all quarters.
May the Emperor long live.
You two can make haste.
Take my decree and hurry.
Yes.
Get the carriage ready.
I am going back to the Palace.
You looked dumbfounded.
Are you wondering
why those fire caltrops of yours
have all lost their effectiveness?
You've known all along?
Daqing is my realm.
There's nothing
that can be hidden from me.
You have filled the inside
with saltpeter, sulfur
iron filings, and fire caltrops.
Once ignited,
it will burst into flames.
The power can pierce the skin
and penetrate the armor,
not to mention the flesh and blood.
Even the war chariots
aren't strong enough to withstand them.
Back then,
we had a war with the Zhao Empire.
In the battle by Kushui River,
they used fire caltrops against us
and caused heavy casualties.
Over half my soldiers died.
No matter how many years pass,
I will not forget these fire caltrops.
Under the pretext
of alchemical practices,
you brought these materials blatantly
into the Palace
and made gunpowder.
Even if the Security Bureau
hasn't removed your fire caltrops,
I would never allow you
to ignite it tonight.
He knew the Security Bureau Guards
had removed the gunpowder.
♪Not a patch of land is wasted♪
♪No tea plant is left withered♪
♪The sky drops rain, birds eat worms,
and chickens leave manure♪
♪Using effort and sweat
to water and nourish♪
♪The tea leaves may be rustic♪
♪But the taste is of spring♪
♪Ah, in the early spring,
we pick the tea leaves♪
♪Ah, let's enjoy
the abundant spring together♪
♪Not a patch of land is wasted♪
♪No tea plant is left withered♪
♪The sky drops rain, birds eat worms,
and chickens leave manure♪
♪Using effort and sweat
to water and nourish♪
♪The tea leaves may be rustic♪
♪But the taste is of spring♪
♪Ah, in the early spring,
we pick the tea leaves♪
♪Ah, let's enjoy
the abundant spring together♪
♪Ah, in the early spring,
we pick the tea leaves♪
♪Ah, let's enjoy
the abundant spring together♪