♪Who gazes at the stars in the sky?♪
♪Heading towards the shore
in a broken boat♪
♪This time, I'll hold onto fate
and never give in♪
♪Family bonds are hard to maintain♪
♪Who will take me
to the fearless dream?♪
♪As the wind and rain come and fade♪
♪A lone sail sways♪
♪A flower blooms alone
amidst the thorns♪
♪Its petals are pierced by thorns♪
♪Yet it turned into a pair of wings
flying against the wind♪
♪Everything grows through the heart♪
♪Even if dreams are lost♪
♪Smoothing out the surging waves♪
♪Breaking through
the tumultuous sounds of the heart♪
♪Having the courage to resist♪
♪Embracing the chant of destiny♪
♪Only love brings light♪
♪Only love embraces the thorns♪
♪Everything grows through the heart♪
♪Having the courage to resist♪
♪Embracing the chant of destiny♪
[Blossoms in Adversity]
♪Only love brings light♪
[Adapted from the novel
of the same name on cmread.com]
[Episode 28]
Listen carefully.
Since you are here,
you're not allowed to steal anymore.
If you do that again,
I will break your legs.
Are you a little mad dog?
You want to bite me?
If you don't behave, I will...
I'll stew you
and eat you!
I'll add something
to make you taste even better.
I'm just kidding.
These are all good
for promoting blood circulation
and relieving the pain!
The hot noodle soup is ready.
I smelled it just now.
- Sit down.
- Jian.
This child knows no shame!
- Sit down.
- Jian!
- Have you sat down?
[Hua Mansion]
Today's dishes are quite good.
Lady Zhi!
Lady Zhi,
the little beggar is gone!
Did you look under the bed?
I did.
I even searched through the chests.
He ate three large bowls of noodles
last night.
I asked him about his background,
but he said nothing.
In the morning, when I went back,
he was gone.
He left!
I'll go look with you.
Wait a moment.
What?
Why are you under the bed?
The ground is freezing,
don't catch a cold.
Come out.
I'm not going to beat you.
Why are you hiding under my bed?
You want to follow me, don't you?
Then follow me.
Lady Zhi,
who is he?
Don't turn around.
Just pretend you can't see him.
Let's reconcile the accounts.
Lady Zhi.
Mr. Bai is here.
Let him in.
Mr. Bai, you've come so early.
You must have something
to discuss with me.
Facing your politeness,
no one can possibly say bad words.
Tomorrow
will be the fifth day.
Our competition will come to an end.
Miss Hua,
do you know who's winning at the moment?
After closing up shop yesterday,
we were just three votes short.
No matter who becomes
the final owner of Tangxi Restaurant,
tomorrow will be the last day for sure.
Mr. Bai, do you have
another plan already?
These days, with so many diners
rushing into the restaurant,
I learned that every moment
is as precious as gold.
So, Mr. Bai, you don't want it
to end just like that, do you?
You want to get the most out of this.
Do you have any ideas then?
Back when you and I
set up this competition,
I believe we were
thinking the same thing.
This five-day cooking competition
is enough to make Tangxi Restaurant
famous throughout the imperial city.
This last day,
why not make it even more lively?
Let's hold a competition on the spot.
We present a cook each
to compete in knifing skills,
cooking skills,
and the taste of their dishes.
Two out of three.
How about it?
What are you hesitating for?
If we have to choose someone
for this competition,
our family will surely
send the head chef.
But I can't make that decision for her.
After I ask her about it,
I'll reply to you.
Young Lady.
You don't need to ask.
I'll do it.
Miss Fudong.
On one condition.
I want to challenge Liang Fugui
from your crew.
The winner will be one of us.
Also, regardless of winning or losing,
all three rounds must be completed.
Why him?
Young Lady,
I want to
defeat him honorably.
Good.
The decisive battle
between Hua's and Bai's
will happen tomorrow!
The final owner of Tangxi Restaurant
will soon be revealed.
By that time, each customer
will receive...
Take a look...
Every customer present is entitled to
complimentary appetizers!
What does this say?
Between Hua's and Bai's,
it's finally time
to determine the winner.
[Bai's, Hua's]
The red one is for Hua's
and the green one is for Bai's.
[Hua Mansion]
You and the baby are going too?
Today is such an important day
for our entire family.
How can I just sit at home?
Madam Wu,
Qin and I will look after you.
Zhi's still in the room?
Your daughter
will never leave the room
until she finishes accounting.
Indeed.
She's busy.
Let's go without her.
Fudong left early in the morning.
Let's hurry to Tangxi Restaurant
and grab the best seats!
Children,
there will be a lot of people today.
Don't you kids run around!
Alright, Mother.
Let's go.
Don't run around.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Do you have any further instructions?
This matter is of great importance.
You must handle it well.
Understood.
Who's there?
Kill him.
Don't kill me!
Your Highness,
please forgive me!
Blame yourself for seeing
what you shouldn't have seen!
Don't kill me.
Don't kill me!
Lady Zhi, it's done.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
Young Lady.
I kindly covered him with a blanket,
but he guarded against me
as if I were a thief!
I don't even know
when he took the knife from the table
and hid it under the pillow.
He nearly cut me with it!
If you need this knife
to help you sleep tight,
you can keep it.
But I assure you
that in this family,
you don't need this
to get a good sleep.
This child is...
Now, apologize to Baoxia.
You did wrong just now.
No need.
He's like a puppy, biting everyone.
He doesn't need to apologize.
Why did you throw things everywhere?
What are these?
These are...
Well...
Jian,
are you worried
that you might get hungry?
Baoxia.
Go to the kitchen and prepare some food.
Prepare as much as possible.
Jian,
I'm going out today.
But I will be back before dark.
Wait here for me,
okay?
In the future, whenever you're hungry,
just let me know.
If you need anything,
you can tell Baoxia.
When I get back,
I will bring you something tasty.
Young Lady,
Mr. Zhong wants to know
if it's time to set off.
Let's go.
Be good.
Mr. Zhong.
Lady Zhi.
How come you're wearing
the new clothes today?
Of course, I am.
Today is a big day!
I want
to look good for you!
Let's go!
Get in, Lady Zhi.
Come on.
Eat up.
Just eat to your fill.
Look at you.
Slow down.
I'll go get you some water!
I can't believe him.
He really knows how to tire me out.
I heard the Security Bureau Guards
put in great effort
to catch a child.
Is that so?
What could a child
possibly do wrong?
I don't know.
They caught a little kid.
Why would they capture a child?
The one in that carriage
must be the Sixth Prince!
They really found him ahead of us!
You, go and report to our master.
The rest of you, follow me.
We cannot let them take the Sixth Prince
back with them.
Yes.
Make a way.
The carriage is coming!
Yes.
This is Miss Hua!
Miss Hua!
Please, come in.
Please.
Miss Hua.
How wonderful!
This way.
Indeed.
Good.
Good to see you, Miss Hua.
Prepare this private room.
Clean it up nicely
and get the tea ready.
Later, after Miss Hua
visits the kitchen,
she will take a seat here
to watch the competition.
- Move quickly.
- Yes.
Today
is already the seventh day.
Who is there?
He's with me.
Commander,
it's done.
Are you sure?
I've been following that man in black.
He went into a small courtyard.
And as soon as he got into the house,
he knelt and apologized to his master.
Did you see his master's face?
At that time,
his face was half-covered.
I couldn't see it clearly.
But I remember his voice.
Who is it?
Eunuch Wei.
Lord Xian's trusted man.
Commander,
let's take action.
I've never raided
a lord's mansion before.
To bring down a lord,
we need solid evidence.
I saw it with my own eyes!
What exactly is solid evidence?
We'll have it soon.
Fools!
You've sold yourselves out.
And you're not even aware of it!
Please, Your Highness,
enlighten me.
You think the Security Bureau
really found the Sixth Prince?
They only did that
to lure you out!
You think they tried
to capture you alive for interrogation?
Don't they know
that my death warriors would only
commit suicide once they got caught?
That fool
thought he had escaped to safety.
And he ran to report to you!
The inspectors from the Security Bureau
definitely followed him.
Most likely,
they've already discovered you.
I...
I am so sorry!
Now,
it's like holding
the arrow on the bowstring.
It must be released!
Go and call up fifty good fighters.
Have them get armed
and follow me to the Palace immediately!
I'll show some concern for His Majesty.
Your Highness,
but in the Palace,
the Security Bureau is on guard!
In the end, the Security Bureau
is no more than a dog
by His Majesty's side.
Now even the owner is nearly gone.
Can't we kill the dog?
They sealed the Forbidden Palace.
Merely for that, I can accuse him
of plotting treason.
I'm leading troops into the Palace
to eliminate the traitors.
Who would dare to object?
Go tell those in the Court
to get their reports ready
as a foolproof preparation!
I will
follow your order!
Commander,
do you think Lord Xian will really come?
What if he doesn't come?
Someone else
might hesitate and hold back,
but Lord Xian won't.
Someone like him
is naturally cruel and suspicious.
He only moves forward
and never retreats.
He will lead troops into the Palace.
Can we defeat him then?
Don't you know
exactly how many men
the Security Bureau has?
What should we do then?
Attack them when they're unprepared.
We'll win by striking quickly.
Why are there so many people?
Make way!
My Lord,
there is news about that child!
Is the information reliable?
An old beggar
saw him clearly!
It was a boy with bruises on his neck.
He never speaks
and tries to hide from everyone.
He got onto
the Hua Family's carriage that night
and left with Miss Hua
and a maid.
What a coincidence.
Where is Miss Hua at this moment?
Today, the Hua Family
is holding a contest at the restaurant.
Miss Hua is at Tangxi Restaurant.
You take half the men to the Hua Family
and search the place thoroughly.
If you let them
run off again,
all of you
should not come back to see me anymore.
Yes.
The rest of you,
follow me to Tangxi Restaurant!
This darn child!
Where did he go again?
Oh, I'm so angry.
The whole family
went out to watch the competition,
leaving me alone to watch the kid.
If he's gone missing, then let it be.
No, I can't.
I must let Lady Zhi know.
Why do others
get to watch the competition
and I can't?
I bet on the Hua Family!
Look!
Such a spectacle scene
is probably one of the tops
in the capital!
Just have a seat.
Don't embarrass yourself.
Alright.
[Hua Mansion]
Search!
Yes.
Search the whole place!
You, over there!
Yes!
Miss Hua.
Your Highness.
It's very lively today.
Miss Zhi.
Young Lady.
Mr. Bai,
I have a friend here
who wants
to have a private talk with me.
Would you step aside for a moment?
Yingchun,
no need to wait on us for now.
Then...
Your Highness,
how can I help you?
Aren't you the owner of a restaurant?
I, of course,
am here to dine.
Let's start with a pot of tea.
I'm really sorry.
I don't know how to make tea.
Just do it!
Cut the chatter!
This dish has it all,
color, aroma, and flavor.
You...
Look at them.
No.
He's not here.
Look, those people
have all been arrested.
No.
Sir, we found nothing.
No?
Then set it on fire.
Block both the front and back gates!
Let's see
who exactly will run out.
Move!
Yes!
Burn it!
Excuse me!
Where are the ladies?
Hurry over. It's about to start!
How did you get here?
Don't mention it.
It's a long story.
Stop asking.
Come on.
Good.
- Good.
- Fighting.
Fudong, fighting!
Fudong!
Fighting.
Fudong, Fighting!
Everyone,
silence!
Honored guests,
thank you for coming here!
Your presence truly brings glory
to Tangxi Restaurant.
However,
starting tomorrow,
this place will no longer
be called Tangxi Restaurant.
No longer called Tangxi Restaurant?
You will find out its new name tomorrow.
Let's cut the chitchat.
The first round of this competition
is a contest of knifing skills.
Now,
it begins!
- Good.
Good!
It has begun!
Look!
I'm going to take a break.
Boil the water.
What are you crying for?
I'm not dead yet!
Cry again and
I'll throw you in the pot and cook you
to serve with my drink!
Chop all these!
Or you'll have nothing to eat.
♪Who gazes at the stars in the sky?♪
♪Heading towards the shore
in a broken boat♪
Xigu.
Can't I teach you?
Father!
In this world,
you were the one I feared the most.
But now,
I am no longer afraid.
♪Its petals are pierced by thorns♪
♪Yet it turned into a pair of wings
flying against the wind♪
♪Everything grows through the heart♪
♪Even if dreams are lost♪
♪Smoothing out the surging waves♪
Fudong finished!
♪Breaking through
the tumultuous sounds of the heart♪
- Good!
♪Embracing the chant of destiny♪
Good!
♪Only love brings light♪
Look!
♪Only love embraces the thorns♪
This was too hard!
Check this knifing skill!
This is tofu?
This competition is worth watching!
♪Only love brings light♪
So impressive!
Truly amazing!
Please enjoy it.
I've told you
I don't know how to make tea.
Are you okay?
I said it's lively today.
And it's bustling indeed.
Cousin, long time no see.
Sit down.
It seems that I guessed wrong earlier.
You might
really manage to buy yourselves
half a year of time.
By then,
I'll have to add a generous gift
for you.
I'm curious.
Young Lord, what brings you here?
Whatever brings you here, cousin,
surely
is also what brings me here.
I came to eat.
I came to eat as well.
Today, you have to wait
until the competition is over
to be served.
My two honored guests,
I'm afraid you're not going
to have a meal soon.
That's fine.
Then let the competition go on.
No, no.
I must think carefully.
Think carefully.
Liang Fugui,
seventy votes.
Fudong,
a hundred and nine votes.
First round,
Fudong wins!
- Good!
Really impressive!
[Hua's]
Good!
- Good.
- Excellent!
Stop throwing things!
You lost because she's better than you.
Don't take your anger out
on my kitchenware!
Exactly!
Exactly.
Round two,
cooking-time test.
Now,
begin!
- Good.
Sir.
Is the Lord inside?
Yes.
We'll wait here.
Go tell him
that we have searched the Hua Mansion,
and found nothing.
Yes.
The old man and the young girl
looked quite like each other.
They are father and daughter.
Today was not a wasted trip.
There happens to be a competition
between father and daughter.
It's truly exciting.
- Good!
Are you happy watching this game,
dear cousin?
If the father loses,
I'll be happy.
If he wins,
this would be uninteresting.
I'm sure you won't be disappointed,
Your Highness.
Is that so?
We've searched inside and outside
the building
and found nothing.
Eunuch Wei is back.
He found nothing either.
Miss Hua,
there's something
I'd like to ask you about.
But in this place,
I think
you won't speak to me honestly.
How about we go somewhere else?
Wherever I am,
my answers to you will be the same.
Please.
She will not go with you today.
This is unlike the matters before.
You shouldn't take part.
She's with me.
How could this not concern me?
Gu Yanxi,
you are a clever person.
If we were not both
born into the royal family,
we could probably become friends.
But now,
the situation changes as it pleases.
I can tell you this, though.
After today,
whatever happens,
I, Gu Yangong,
can ensure your lifelong safety.
You'll be rich,
with no responsibilities.
I wonder
when you acquired
this kind of power.
If you truly are so capable,
then let's just talk here.
Alright.
Then let's talk.
The night before last,
in the Grass Lane,
you took away a boy of eight or nine
with your carriage.
Where is he now?
That was my little brother,
Hua Bolin.
Why are you looking for him?
Liang Fugui,
eighty-eight votes.
Fudong,
ninety-one votes!
Fudong has won another round!
Close the window.
That's fast.
Good!
It was a good decision coming here!
- Good!
Your Highness, aren't you here
to watch the game?
The winner is determined.
There's nothing left to be watched.
The father has lost two rounds indeed.
But for the last round,
who knows
if the young one will win again?
Such a large restaurant.
People are fighting for it.
It's going to be a good show.
Your Highness,
since you're already here,
why not watch closely?
Miss Hua,
think carefully about
how to answer my question.
Before the gong sounds thrice,
you still have a chance
to save your life.
If your answer is wrong,
no one
can save you.
Round three.
The two chefs
will each make a special dish
for our guests.
There are no requirements
on cooking methods or dish types.
The one with the most votes wins.
Good!
The competition
begins!
- Good.
Good!
My dear guests,
thank you all for your support.
Today,
I, Liang Fugui,
don't care if I will win
or lose.
Next,
I will present you
my family heritage,
the Roasted Camel Hump!
Go and bring me that dish.
Miss Chef,
what will you make for us?
Yeah!
Dear guests,
you will find out soon.
Also,
I'm not called "Miss Chef".
My name is Fudong.
What will you make for us?
- Right.
- What will you make?
This really is a duel of masters.
It's so intense!
Let me try it.
Delicious!
Ms. Fudong,
everyone
has tried
Chef Liang's Roasted Camel Hump.
That flavor
lingers on endlessly.
This dish of yours
must be made of
dragon tendons or phoenix marrow
so that you can never win.
What a coincidence.
This dish of mine
is called "Surpassing Camel Hump".
Surpassing Camel Hump?
How come there's
a "Surpassing Camel Hump"?
This camel hump of yours
is...
I mean,
it has not even a hint of gamey taste!
It tastes even more delicate
than Bai's camel hump!
And quite crispy, too!
Such a pity.
For a delicacy like this,
I can only have it
once in a lifetime!
Dear guests, don't sign.
In the future,
when our restaurant opens,
this dish will still be available.
Everyone,
make sure to come and try.
Our Hua's "Surpassing Camel Hump"
is not made from real camel hump.
Therefore,
everyone can afford it.
So it's actually fish!
Fish?
She can turn fish into that?
It doesn't have any fishy smell
and didn't fall apart either.
Ms. Fudong,
that's truly amazing!
Really amazing!
So impressive!
Ingenious!
Indeed ingenious!
Where did Zhi go?
Right.
Yeah, where's she?
She vanished as soon as arrived.
The winner is about to be decided.
Where did she go?
Good!
Good.
Impressive!
Really impressive!
The Hua's wins!
Good!
[Hua's]
Marvelous!
Good!
Excellent!
I gave you a chance.
Unexpectedly,
you're a pair of fools.
Guards.
Guards!
Allow me, Your Highness.
Commander!
You are the Commander
of the Security Bureau?
Yes, I am.
Take him down!
Let's go!
♪Not a patch of land is wasted♪
♪No tea plant is left withered♪
♪The sky drops rain, birds eat worms,
and chickens leave manure♪
♪Using effort and sweat
to water and nourish♪
♪The tea leaves may be rustic♪
♪But the taste is of spring♪
♪Ah, in the early spring,
we pick the tea leaves♪
♪Ah, let's enjoy
the abundant spring together♪
♪Not a patch of land is wasted♪
♪No tea plant is left withered♪
♪The sky drops rain, birds eat worms,
and chickens leave manure♪
♪Using effort and sweat
to water and nourish♪
♪The tea leaves may be rustic♪
♪But the taste is of spring♪
♪Ah, in the early spring,
we pick the tea leaves♪
♪Ah, let's enjoy
the abundant spring together♪
♪Ah, in the early spring,
we pick the tea leaves♪
♪Ah, let's enjoy
the abundant spring together♪