♪Who gazes at the stars in the sky?♪
♪Heading towards the shore
in a broken boat♪
♪This time, I'll hold onto fate
and never give in♪
♪Family bonds are hard to maintain♪
♪Who will take me
to the fearless dream?♪
♪As the wind and rain come and fade♪
♪A lone sail sways♪
♪A flower blooms alone
amidst the thorns♪
♪Its petals are pierced by thorns♪
♪Yet it turned into a pair of wings
flying against the wind♪
♪Everything grows through the heart♪
♪Even if dreams are lost♪
♪Smoothing out the surging waves♪
♪Breaking through
the tumultuous sounds of the heart♪
♪Having the courage to resist♪
♪Embracing the chant of destiny♪
♪Only love brings light♪
♪Only love embraces the thorns♪
♪Everything grows through the heart♪
♪Having the courage to resist♪
♪Embracing the chant of destiny♪
[Blossoms in Adversity]
♪Only love brings light♪
[Adapted from the novel
of the same name on cmread.com]
[Episode 32]
I won't ask who she is.
Just tell me.
Does she feel the same way?
Even if she doesn't,
does that mean
I can ignore my feelings
and marry another person?
For instance,
you still like Hua Zhi,
but if our parents require you
to marry someone else,
will you do it?
The affection,
you can hide from to the others,
but never to yourself.
Like when
Ji Zha presented a sword.
Since my affection
has already been silently pledged,
even if the other person
cannot accept it,
I would rather hang this affection
high on a tree
than retract it
and easily promise it to someone else.
[Shen Mansion]
Master Shen, please.
Huan,
to receive the favor
of Master Jiang's daughter
is a blessing
cultivated over many lifetimes.
Won't you say something?
Good.
Mr. Jiang,
Huan has never experienced
such an occasion.
Let's not make him embarrass himself.
Take a seat.
Mr. Shen, you're too humble.
Huan is truly a great young man
with extraordinary talent and virtue.
I'd like to hear
what he has to say.
Very well.
Cheers.
You are quite a good speaker.
Sit down.
Mr. Jiang,
let's eat.
The embroidery works you sent us,
I have seen them all.
Your daughter's
needlework is truly exquisite!
Those flowers and birds embroidered
seem as if they've come to life!
I was telling our master
that we can never find
another skilled young girl like her
throughout the Imperial Capital!
Our Yi
has been pampered since childhood.
It's only in the past two years
that I've started
to let her learn some sewing.
I was worried that when she got married,
she'd be laughed at by others.
Unexpectedly,
she's quite talented indeed.
Yes, that's right.
I think so too.
Her works are much better
than the purses
given to me by those misses
from Qunfang House.
If you don't know how to talk properly,
keep your mouth shut!
This...
What kind of a place is Qunfang House?
Zhengzhi,
I toast to you.
I almost forgot about this.
Yesterday, all I could think of
was today's important event.
I got overly excited
and gambled too many times.
The other boys
made me drink a lot.
So today,
I really can't drink anymore.
I apologize, Zhengzhi.
Servants,
take him away!
Mr. Jiang, come on.
No wonder Miss Jiang is so beautiful.
It turns out she got the beauty from
my future mother-in-law.
If I knew
that my future mother-in-law
had such charm,
I would have trouble
deciding whom to propose to!
How dare you!
You unfilial boy!
Take him away!
Mr. Jiang.
Please wait!
Please hear me out, Mr. Jiang.
No need.
I cannot bear it.
Mr. Jiang.
Hurry, let's go!
Mr. Jiang!
How preposterous!
How ridiculous!
Zhengzhi.
You want
to infuriate me to death, don't you?
Master, please calm down!
Look at the trouble he's caused!
Beat him severely!
I know
it's me whom you carved.
It's so ugly.
First-level offense,
colluding with Gu Yangong in secret
to plot for power and seize positions,
involving two families.
Second-level offense,
providing Gu Yangong with weapons,
military provisions,
vehicles, horses, and others,
involving seven families.
Third-level offense,
privately exchanging favors
with Gu Yangong,
[Treasury Minister]
trying to be close with him,
[Shen Zhongxing, and His Son]
involving twenty-six families.
The Shen Family.
They sent him dancing girls,
calligraphy and paintings,
several carts of antiques,
and an invitation letter.
The Shen Family has always
looked down on the insignificant ones.
They always wanted to be
part of Gu Yangong's faction.
That didn't happen, though.
Under the overthrown nest,
can there be any intact eggs?
Commander,
what did you say?
After this,
the Court will inevitably
experience another major shock.
So Commander, do you plan
to report to His Majesty immediately
or to continue the interrogation?
No rush.
The imperial examinations are imminent.
Let's wait until this period is over.
The first nine families
you just mentioned
should be thoroughly investigated again.
Yes.
What is there to fear?
We still have Qi, don't we?
If Qi passes
the final imperial examination,
then our family
will have a newly succeeded
jinshi candidate.
By then,
things will naturally
be different again.
People of even higher status
than the Jiang Family
will want to be our in-laws.
Father, you're right.
It's like a thousand soldiers
crossing a single-log bridge.
It's not that easy.
That's correct.
We can't just count on Qi alone.
Let's do this.
You should prepare
a generous gift immediately.
Tomorrow, pay another visit
to the State Finance Commissioner
and Minister Zheng,
as well as Defender-in-Chief Wang.
Go and meet with them all.
No.
As the saying goes,
a stitch in time saves nine.
Better early than late.
Don't wait till tomorrow.
Go today and see what happens.
Understood.
Good to see you, Mr. Shen.
Mr. Jiang?
Mr. Jiang,
You...
Why are you here?
I've come to return
your betrothal gifts.
Your parents and sister
must be very angry now, right?
I am truly too embarrassed to see you.
Mr. Shen,
you've already
given your heart to another.
Why didn't you tell us?
How did you know?
You made such a scene.
Even my sister has figured it out.
Mr. Shen,
you didn't have to do that.
If I had said
that I'm already
in love with someone else
and that I don't want
to marry your sister,
your sister would definitely
feel embarrassed, wouldn't she?
Also, if the word gets out,
your family will be disgraced.
So I decided
to let your parents
think that I am just
a hopeless loser.
In this case,
after your family rejected me,
I'd be the only one who got disgraced.
To my surprise,
you turn out to be
such a thoughtful man.
Sadly, my sister doesn't have a chance
to marry you.
But in fact,
the one I love
might not marry me either.
She is not the same
as the other girls.
Perhaps,
we can only be good friends.
Then why did you...
I cannot go
against my true feelings
and get married.
Moreover,
Miss Jiang is innocent.
I cannot ruin her life.
Mr. Shen,
no matter what happens
between our families,
you and I will always be friends.
As long as you don't disdain me.
Careful.
Don't blame my curiosity.
Mr. Shen,
which family is the miss you love from?
She...
She has no family.
She just lodges with the Hua Family.
The Hua Family?
The one running Zhiming Restaurant.
Then does she know
that your betrothal was called...
No, I mean,
does she know you were betrothed?
Perhaps at this very moment,
she is at home feeling heartbroken.
You're right!
She must be extremely sad!
I must go find her.
No, I can't.
Now my family
will surely not allow me to leave.
Mr. Shen,
are you able to stand up now?
You can hide in my carriage.
Shaoyao!
You...
What happened to you?
What's going on?
Why do you always get hurt?
Who knows?
Perhaps even heaven knows
that with you here,
I can take a few hits without dying.
Shaoyao,
I have something
very important to tell you.
What is it?
I don't have to get married anymore.
No need to get married?
Really?
That's great!
You don't have to...
Shen Huan.
Earlier you told me
that you have affection for me.
I've thought about it.
You're not like the others.
My brother and Zhi,
when spending time with me,
always try so hard to protect me
and indulge me.
Like, like...
Like the teacup
on Zhi's table.
Baoxia cherishes it so much
that she won't even
allow anyone else to touch it.
But then I met you.
You bullied me from the start.
Only you
don't look at me differently.
We can do bold things together.
And you're not afraid of breaking me.
♪Kaleidoscope of colors♪
So...
I... I have affection for you too.
♪The galaxy flows like a song♪
♪Lighting up the sky with fingertips♪
♪The story slowly unfolds♪
♪Nourishing warmth within our hearts♪
♪The pulsing heartbeat ticks away♪
♪Colors of the bouquet won't fade♪
♪In each other's palms♪
♪Capturing every moment♪
♪Let the beauty continue to flourish♪
♪Brewing our♪
♪love words, practiced for so long♪
♪Happy scenes are forever abundant♪
♪Your smile freely wanders♪
♪Answering the future♪
Xiaohua.
Where is it?
Little bunny!
Little cutie!
Stay still.
Don't move.
I can't let you run around.
Sorry.
I mistook you for Mr. Zheng.
Is Mr. Zheng
the one you fancy, miss?
No, he's not.
He's just a teacher
in our family academy.
Even if it were Master Mu,
I would still jest in the same manner.
And who is Master Mu?
Master Mu's hair and beard
have both turned grey.
Mister, please don't fabricate tales.
I certainly don't fancy him.
May I ask who your father is?
My father is Hua Pingyu.
Mister, what about you?
Are you also here to be a teacher?
I am here visiting with a friend.
I would like to take my leave now.
But I can't find the way out.
Our courtyard is large.
It's only your first visit,
so I'm not surprised that you got lost.
Could I trouble you, miss,
to show me the way out?
My name is Jiang Zhengzhi.
I'm Hua Rong.
No.
Qin once said
that I shouldn't
let others know my maiden name.
Miss, rest assured.
I did not hear it clearly.
Are you angry?
Don't you want to leave?
Then hurry up and follow me.
If you have the audacity,
don't come home
for the rest of your lives!
One ran away,
and the other did the same.
I'm so angry!
Earlier, your father asked you to visit
the State Finance Commissioner
and the others.
Any news from them?
Don't even mention it.
Those old foxes in the capital
are far craftier than Jiang.
They have probably heard of something
and they weren't even willing to see me.
The Security Bureau
has already turned Lord Xian's Mansion
upside down.
People associated with him
will sooner or later be listed.
But now it's uncertain
if that list
was delivered to His Majesty
and if our names
are on it.
What...
Hope our names are not on the list.
Sir,
how much is this?
Miss, you have quite discerning eyes!
This is Huizhou craftsmanship,
made of beech wood.
That won't do, then.
The building of our Zhiming Restaurant
is quite old.
If this was placed on the second floor,
I'm afraid the floor would collapse.
It's for Zhiming Restaurant?
Then you must be the owner,
Miss Hua!
I've long heard of you!
This set isn't what you're looking for.
I've acquired a new set.
Come, let me show you.
This is the set.
Check this craftsmanship.
These carvings are all freshly engraved.
They're made of brand new poplar wood,
perfect for placing
on the second floor for guests.
Are these all newly made?
Of course!
Mister,
this is a canopy bed from Jinling.
Look at these carvings
and these inscriptions.
What do you think?
No matter how many beds you will see,
this is definitely the best.
I'm not bragging,
but in the Imperial Capital,
it is only available in our shop.
The other shops cannot afford it.
It's too expensive.
What are you looking at this for?
I've heard about it long ago.
The dowry of a girl
from the Imperial Capital
must include a carved bed
to be considered decent.
Then I should buy one myself.
You're treating me like a stranger now.
If I brought this home,
they would laugh at me again.
You can do as you did the last time.
What did you say last time?
Again?
They are not fools.
Mr. Jiang,
please watch your step.
Shen Huan
has indeed been staying here recently
recovering from injuries.
I don't know what happened,
but he got beaten up by someone
so badly.
I mean, poor man.
It was painful even to look at him.
I am sorry.
I need to go to the bathroom.
I'll go find him myself later.
You go with Mr. Zhong first.
Okay, then.
You, follow me.
You again?
Miss.
You, the one who got lost.
Why are you here again?
I...
I've come to visit a friend.
Who is your friend?
Miss, please don't misunderstand.
I didn't mean you.
I meant Shen Huan.
Do you have anything else to say?
I...
Then go to your friend.
Miss, please wait.
Recently,
I heard that on Zhou Bridge,
there's this honey slush
that I have yet to try.
Have you tried it, miss?
Everyone, be careful.
Yes, Madam.
Don't leave anything behind.
Yes.
Dear, where did Zhengzhi go?
Why hasn't he returned yet?
These days,
Yi hasn't been in a good mood.
She went to bed early.
As for Zhengzhi, well...
You didn't notice it before?
What's wrong?
These past few days,
when has he ever stayed home peacefully?
He's been outside all day,
acting so mysteriously.
I have no idea what he's up to.
I hope he's not with
any indecent friends.
Father, Mother.
What is...?
Zhengzhi,
you're finally back.
Go to your room
and check your belongings.
See if they're all packed well.
Why are you so surprised?
We're returning to Jinyang tomorrow.
I've told you before.
You just didn't listen.
What's wrong again?
Father, Mother,
I can't just leave like this.
I've fallen for someone.
I need your support, Father.
So many betrothal gifts!
Are these from the Jiang Family,
the Transport Commissioner
of the Six Routes?
Yes.
Rong is truly fortunate.
I just wonder how old
is this young man from the Jiang Family.
Eighteen.
I really didn't expect
that my Rong
would have such good fortune.
How come he suddenly
offers betrothal gifts to Rong?
Rong is still young.
I don't know
if she's willing to accept this.
That family has an honorable background,
and the man is young.
Why wouldn't Rong accept it?
However,
earlier I heard that the betrothal
between the daughter of Mr. Jiang
and the second son of Mr. Shen
was called off unpleasantly.
We don't know
what exactly happened.
Jin'e, rest assured.
This has nothing to do
with the son of Mr. Jiang.
I'll explain it to you later.
Okay.
This whole thing is quite strange.
We still need to ask Rong
for her own opinion.
Marriage is a major affair.
The elders should make the decision.
We ask the girl?
Zhi, what do you need me for?
So many chests!
What are all these?
Rong,
someone proposed to you.
These are all your betrothal gifts.
Betrothal gifts?
What betrothal gifts?
Who sent these betrothal gifts?
Mother, I don't want to get married!
I want to stay with you.
They're from the Jiang Family
from Jinyang.
The Jiang Family?
Jiang Zhengzhi?
Do you know him?
If you're not willing to...
Who said I'm not?
Hurry up and tell me.
What's really going on?
Stop asking questions.
Anyway, I am willing to marry him.
Seriously,
a lot of happy things
have been happening
to our family recently.
Tomorrow, they'll post
the examination results.
How about I take you all
to the announcement site
and catch a few more
good sons-in-law for us?
Oh, right,
I heard that our Mr. Zheng
also took the exam.
Is that so?
[Announcement of Exam Result]
[Second place, Shen Qi
Eighteenth place, Zheng Zhi]
After we give these away,
if we can't get anything in return...
At this very time,
how can you still worry about money?
You're afraid of wasting money,
but I'm afraid
that no one will even accept these.
Sir!
What's the matter?
Shen Qi has succeeded!
The official envoy is right at our door!
Shen Qi got second place in the exam!
Are you saying Qi got second place?
That's right!
Great! Qi!
Wonderful!
The top three were appointed
by His Majesty himself.
This shows
that our family has not
lost His Majesty's favor!
Yes, yes!
Dear.
Our family is now safe.
Where is the official envoy?
Right outside the main entrance.
Quickly,
invite him in!
Qi, my good boy!
Father, Mother,
Qi got second place in the exam!
Master Zheng?
[Hua Mansion]
Master Zheng, Zheng Zhi!
We asked around all the way.
Everyone said he lives at your place.
Does he not?
[Good News]
[Zheng Zhi ranks 18th]
[in the second-highest class
in the imperial exam.]
Zheng Zhi?
You see.
Our family has produced its fifth
successful jinshi candidate in the exam.
I only ranked
in the second-highest class.
You're being too modest.
Only the second-highest class?
How many scholars are there in Daqing?
And how many actually took the exam?
Don't mention being
in the second-highest class.
Even being in the third-highest class
is one in a thousand.
If our Boli can be like you,
I'd be eternally grateful!
Congratulations, Mr. Zheng!
Not Mr. Zheng.
Master Zheng.
Yes, that's right.
- Master Zheng.
Master Zheng.
Master Mu,
ever since I joined this family academy,
I've been under your guidance.
Your great kindness
will never be forgotten.
Congratulations, Master Zheng.
Where is Zhi?
Why isn't she here?
Zhi probably doesn't know yet.
The eldest son of the Shen Family
got second place.
She left as soon as she knew.
Congratulations, Master Zheng.
I'll learn from Master Zheng.
I'll study hard.
In the future,
I'll follow Master Zheng's example.
I'll study hard.
From now on, he's Master Zheng.
[Yunlai Restaurant]
Congratulations!
Your dream has come true.
It can't really be called
a dream come true.
The result justifies
my ten years of hard study.
I am truly happy for you.
During my time at Jujube Tree Alley,
every month, you had Yingchun
bring me things.
Today, finally,
I didn't let down the person
who helped me when I mostly needed help.
I have another gift for you.
That's a good thing!
Many thanks.
If you had come earlier
and offered congratulations just now,
he would have been glad.
I know.
But without me showing up,
he might be even happier.
The top three
all are outstanding
young talents.
This brings great comfort to me.
This year's examination question
was about how to unite the emperor
and his courtiers,
and how should they support each other.
I created the question myself.
The answers from you all
won me over.
Speaking of exam questions,
the questions in past years
were all set by Hua Yizheng.
Regarding that person,
I would like to hear your opinions.
Your Majesty,
Hua Yizheng is learned and eloquent,
yet he was quite
conceited about his talents.
In order to be known
as a forthright official,
he even tried to tarnish
your great reputation.
I will take that as a warning
and to reflect upon myself.
Your Majesty,
the imperial judgment was final.
In my point of view,
it was indeed Hua Yizheng's own fault.
How about you,
the second-ranked scholar?
Why don't you speak?
Shen Qi?
Back then,
when Master Hua answered
His Majesty's questions,
he must have also been on the edge
between life and death
like this.
Your Majesty,
I dare not to answer your question
dishonestly.
I believe
that among all the courtiers,
if we talk about loyalty and bravery,
no one surpasses Master Hua.
Shen Qi,
I have heard
that back when you were
in the Imperial Academy,
your integrity was already known
among the Hanlin scholars.
So today,
are you emulating Hua Yizheng?
Your Majesty,
I don't want
to seek fame and reputation.
For ten years,
I studied Confucian classics,
delved into the path of the sage,
all to assist Your Majesty
in governing and promoting civilization.
Throughout history, loyal ministers
have always placed their sovereigns
in an immaculate position.
It is only because of this,
I am constantly filled with anxiety
because of Master Hua's misfortune.
I truly hope Your Majesty can avoid
public criticism.
Then what do you think
I should do?
Master Hua is honest and righteous.
Despite opposing the royal will,
he served the empire
rather than personal interests.
I pray Your Majesty will
acknowledge his loyalty
and pardon his breach of etiquette.
Shen Qi,
you and the granddaughter of Hua Yizheng
were betrothed, right?
Your Majesty,
the betrothal has already been annulled.
Then you are indeed very faithful.
Your Majesty,
since the betrothal has been annulled,
there is no longer any connection
between the two families.
What I have said
has nothing to do with that.
Come here, Shen Qi.
Take a few steps closer
and let me take a look at you.
Has anyone ever told you
that you are not
like Shen Zhongxing at all?
Your Majesty, I do not understand.
We already have a bed,
but we need to buy a few more chests.
Let me see what else we are missing.
[Purchasing list]
What is this?
The wedding is so important for us.
Of course we must prepare well.
You've become
even more annoying than before.
Apart from these,
I have to get you some betrothal gifts.
I certainly can't offer less
than the Shen Family did, right?
What's the matter?
Do you know that
the Shen Family...
Commander,
you're urgently summoned by His Majesty.
Since the list
has long been prepared,
why didn't you hand it to me earlier?
The matter involves accusations
of treason, implicating many.
I have yet to untangle
the relationships involved,
so I feared it may lead
to wrongful convictions.
Your Majesty, I earnestly request you
to grant me some more time,
so I can thoroughly examine the case.
You think
I didn't give you enough time,
right?
How come I feel
that you have quite a lot of time?
[Shen Zhongxing and his son]
Uncle.
Shen Zhongxing and his son
are just accustomed
to sucking up to the superior
and stepping on the inferior.
They flattered whoever was in power.
Those they have fawned over
are not limited to just Gu Yangong.
They are merely petty men.
To consider them
as part of Gu Yangong's faction,
I feel
that would be somewhat unjust.
Yanxi.
Just now was the first time
you attempted to deceive me.
What a pity.
The Shen Family is accused
of being in league with rebels
with the punishment
extending to the entire clan.
Their property will be confiscated,
men will be imprisoned,
and women and children
will be sold into servitude.
Do you have anything else to say?
No.
Very good.
Then go and deal with it.
Yes.
Changqing.
Last time when I went
to the Fengxiang Palace,
I didn't seem to take this path.
She has gone to the Palace?
Yes, indeed.
Just like that time
with the Empress Dowager,
a eunuch came
to deliver a verbal decree,
asking Lady Zhi to bring some pastries
into the Palace.
His Majesty arrives.
I did not summon Zhi today.
Grandmother,
I will accompany you another day.
Wait.
This is urgent.
Yanxi, you are muddled.
If you go to her right now,
this will only further prove
how important she is to you.
You should think about it.
How will your uncle treat her?
I've heard that the Hua's pastries
have become famous throughout
the Imperial Capital
and that even the Empress Dowager
has taken a liking to them.
You are very clever.
You've even brought your business
to my Imperial Palace.
Your Majesty,
the Hua Family has only
women and children left.
We're making pastries
merely to scrape by.
Receiving the Empress Dowager's favor
was an unexpected honor
and a great fortune.
What the Empress Dowager dotes on
is not your pastry
but someone related to you.
Yanxi is her most beloved grandchild.
Your Majesty, I dare not to deceive you.
The young lord and I
do share true affection.
Stand up.
Open the food box
and show what's inside to me.
The sprouting of affection
between a girl and a boy
is very normal.
It doesn't matter.
No need to be concerned about it.
I too was once young
and privately committed
to the daughter of a general.
Do you know what happened afterward?
No.
Later,
I ascended to the throne
and brought her into the Palace
according to our agreement.
It is just that her father
did not know how to retreat in time
and actually had the audacity
to speak nonsense before me.
I then annihilated her entire family.
She ultimately took her own life
in the Palace.
Hua Zhi,
you are too young
to understand
that the temperament
of those born in the royal family
is different from
that of ordinary people.
For supreme power,
there is nothing
that they cannot sacrifice.
Of course,
I also know
that since Yanxi returned
from the northern land,
his days have been hard.
Occasionally trying some sweets
to relieve tiredness
is not necessarily a bad idea.
You should be more considerate to him.
After all, if he lives comfortably,
he'll work for me more efficiently.
Alright, go home.
Your Majesty,
I am a sinner from the Hua Family.
Keeping me by Yanxi's side,
aren't you worried, Your Majesty?
Sinner?
Have I blamed you?
Your grandfather
and your father
are both too arrogant.
But neither they
nor you
are of any significance
in my eyes.
Yes,
no significance.
The word "no significance" from you
can be a devastating disaster
to the others.
Not just my grandfather and me.
Be it the Hua Family,
the Wang Family, or the Li Family,
to you,
they are all of no significance.
What a girl.
Sharp and clear-sighted.
No wonder Yanxi
is attracted to you.
As such a smart girl,
you should be able to understand
that you being with Yanxi
will only harm him.
You and the eldest son
of the Shen Family
are friends.
Am I right?
Do you know
why I value Yanxi so much
and why I entrusted the Security Bureau
to him?
It is because
he is utterly loyal to me.
Also because
he can handle matters impartially.
He has no connection
with the Shen Family,
but today he pleaded for them.
That was because of you.
He tried to shield the Shen Family
for your sake.
So you shouldn't blame me.
Do you know that originally,
the crimes of the Shen Family
wouldn't have led
to the confiscation of their properties?
Confiscation?
You didn't know it?
I can tell you this.
The Shen Family's situation
is just the beginning.
No interference shall be allowed
in Yanxi's loyalty to me.
Anything that interferes
with his loyalty
will be considered insignificant to me.
Now, do you understand?
If yes, you may leave.
The pastries you made
are indeed delicious.
Next time when you send some to
the Empress Dowager,
remember to send me some as well.
If I have time,
I will tell you
about Yanxi's childhood.
Follow them.
My lady,
it seems like
the Security Bureau is going
to raid someone's residence.
Are we really following them?
Yes.
Madam!
Search this place!
Something terrible has happened!
Madam, Madam Shen!
Madam Shen!
Search!
Stop right there!
Don't run!
- Here.
- Don't move!
My house is
a third-rank official residence
and my grandson just got second place
in the imperial examination.
You...
How dare you do this to us!
The minister of the Court
of the Imperial Treasury,
Shen Zhongxing, has been
imprisoned for his crimes,
implicating the entire clan.
The Security Bureau is ordered
to confiscate the family properties
and sell all the women and children
from his family.
Take them away!
Let go of me!
Squat down properly.
Don't move.
Don't move!
Stay put!
They really should
investigate them thoroughly.
Investigate them carefully.
Madam Shen!
♪Not a patch of land is wasted♪
♪No tea plant is left withered♪
♪The sky drops rain, birds eat worms,
and chickens leave manure♪
♪Using effort and sweat
to water and nourish♪
♪The tea leaves may be rustic♪
♪But the taste is of spring♪
♪Ah, in the early spring,
we pick the tea leaves♪
♪Ah, let's enjoy
the abundant spring together♪
♪Not a patch of land is wasted♪
♪No tea plant is left withered♪
♪The sky drops rain, birds eat worms,
and chickens leave manure♪
♪Using effort and sweat
to water and nourish♪
♪The tea leaves may be rustic♪
♪But the taste is of spring♪
♪Ah, in the early spring,
we pick the tea leaves♪
♪Ah, let's enjoy
the abundant spring together♪
♪Ah, in the early spring,
we pick the tea leaves♪
♪Ah, let's enjoy
the abundant spring together♪