♪Searching through half a lifetime,
I rest with the breeze as my pillow♪
♪The bright moon's yearning
echoes through lonely strings♪
♪Gazing across the mortal realm♪
♪She appears where lanterns fade♪
♪Storms disperse.
Drunken reunions trace past bonds♪
♪Asking when we'll meet in another life♪
♪A millennium passes in moments.
Where's today's joy♪
♪This love defies severing♪
♪Cutting a fragment of time♪
♪Shattered stars can't compare
to my resolve with you♪
♪Though countless sorrows
may fall like petals♪
♪For this stretch of time♪
♪Walk with you through life and death♪
♪Carving your essence in my heart♪
♪Creating life's fairest memory♪
♪Cutting a fragment of time♪
♪Shattered stars can't compare
to my resolve with you♪
♪Though countless sorrows
may fall like petals♪
♪For this stretch of time♪
♪Walk with you through life and death♪
♪Carving your essence in my heart♪
♪Creating life's fairest memory♪
=The Sun in the Dark=
=Episode 16=
Now, I understand.
The prophecy states
the Night Deity must be sealed
into the purest soul vessel,
where a powerful cultivator
transforms into the Divine Sword
and its spirit,
allowing the Sword Master
to slay the Night Deity.
(Moreover, someone
with supreme cultivation)
(can absorb the sealed Night Deity)
(from the soul vessel into themselves,)
(converting Night Deity's power)
(into their own.)
(This must never
fall into malicious hands.)
Then what?
What's written after this?
(His ambition
and killing intent run deep.)
(Better keep this hidden
from him for now.)
That's all there is.
(So the Night Deity's power)
(can be transferred to another's body.)
Yusheng.
I remember now.
I remember everything.
Why is this happening?
Will this lifetime end the same way?
In the end,
I'll lose all my memories again.
You won't.
For twelve hundred years,
I've finally found a way to save you.
What way?
You'll no longer
be the Night Deity's vessel
if I transfer
Night Deity's power
from your body to mine.
Transferring it into you?
What then?
Then I'll pass
all my cultivation to you.
Passing it all to me?
You want me to kill you?
Don't even think about it!
I'll never agree to this.
This is the only way.
Your consent doesn't matter.
I must proceed regardless.
I refuse!
There must be another way.
Let's find another way together.
There has to be another way.
We'll think of something. I refuse.
- No.
- We've searched Three Realms.
This is the only way.
I'm your master.
By my command,
from this day forth,
you'll cultivate here
without leaving even once.
Chen!
What's wrong?
Are you hurt?
What's happening?
Don't scare me like this.
You're scaring me.
What's happening?
I won't let you die.
I won't let anything happen to you.
I'll keep you safe.
(Why am I lying here?)
(Could it be...?)
(Yusheng.)
Yusheng.
The Night Deity's power
awakened far earlier.
Night Deity!
Wan Guchen.
The nine-tailed fox demon
loved you to madness.
To prevent your plan from succeeding,
she offered her body to me long ago.
How utterly gullible she was.
Night Deity,
didn't you hate me most?
Get out of her body now.
You can use my body as a vessel.
That's an intriguing proposition.
But
I have no interest in your body.
I prefer watching
you torment each other.
I'll make you suffer for eternity.
Yusheng.
Master,
kill me quickly.
I refuse to kill you again.
If you won't do it,
I'll have to...
No!
I transferred all my spiritual power
and demonic energy into the nine tails.
With the tails severed,
I can no longer harm you.
Why would you do that?
Do you know that losing your tails
means losing all your cultivation?
To me,
you matter more than anything.
Trying to expel me from your body?
Don't even think about it!
Yusheng?
- Master.
- Yusheng.
Kill me quickly.
I don't want to be controlled anymore.
Kill me now!
I beg you.
I beg you!
Yusheng.
♪I'd rather cycle
through a thousand lives♪
♪Remaining that very fox♪
For over a millennium,
you've endured much,
Master.
♪Inviting heaven's envy♪
♪If another life exists♪
♪How could I fail you then?♪
♪Had I not seen
through this life's haze♪
♪Would past lives
still yearn for your gaze?♪
♪How abandon this fall into you?♪
♪Had I not raced to your side♪
♪I'd rather reincarnate endlessly♪
♪Still tread that destined path♪
♪Sins and faults♪
♪I'll shoulder them all♪
♪On the road to afterlife♪
♪Through storm and upheaval♪
♪Even with another life♪
♪How could I fail you then?♪
♪On the road to afterlife♪
♪I'll keep you here♪
Why must endings always be like this?
(Do I now possess
part of the Night Deity's power?)
(The technique for exchanging
divine and demonic energies)
(can truly transfer
the Night Deity into another's body.)
(But this process requires)
(the other party's consent.)
(Without her willingness,
I cannot proceed.)
(So)
(I must wait until the next life.)
(And she must never learn
my true purpose.)
(Yixi,)
(I'll use this piece
of the Night Deity's power)
(to first become a false Night Deity.)
Wan Guchen,
you've caused immense turmoil.
What's your true intention?
From this day forth,
I relinquish
my position as Sword Master
and quit immortal sects.
Henceforward,
I'm no longer an immortal sect member.
All these years,
we've treated you well.
Yet you obsess
over Bai Yixi's reincarnation.
I gravely misjudged you.
All these years,
I kept every promise
regarding the Night Clan
and Night Deity.
For the next three centuries,
handle it yourselves.
To complete the divine-demon exchange,
the only way
is to transform myself
into the Night Deity.
Yixi,
in this lifetime,
let me suffer in your place.
(I'll endure three centuries
of heavenly thunder)
(to destroy my immortal bones.)
(I'll bear three centuries
of the Night Energy's searing pain)
(to rebuild my flesh and bones.)
(I'll endure three centuries
of Night Fire consuming my heart)
(to reforge my veins.)
Ye Chenyuan, why are you doing this?
Ye Chenyuan!
No!
(Three centuries of Night Fire
reshaped my appearance.)
(Henceforth,)
(no one in this world
will recognize Wan Guchen.)
(Only the reviled Night Deity
scorned by the Three Realms,)
(Ye Chenyuan, remains!)
(Three centuries have passed.)
(My plan shall now unfold.)
(The first step
to break this cursed fate)
(is when the next
three-century cycle arrives,)
(I shall become the new Night Deity.)
Who dares trespass
in the Night Clan's place?
My identity matters not.
You just need to know
that I am the future master
of the Night Clan
and your sovereign lord.
This is the Night Deity's power!
Welcome your return, Lord Night Deity.
- All hail the Night Deity!
(Thus begins the second step)
(of seizing the sword crystal)
(to manipulate
the future Sword Master's actions.)
Halt!
Audacious demon!
You dare breach our forbidden area?
You're audacious
to show disrespect
before the Lord Night Deity.
Night Deity?
I've dealt with Night Deity
for fifteen centuries.
Do you think me easily deceived?
(As expected,
none recognize my visage now.)
The Night Deity's power!
You are the Night Deity!
Remember,
my name is Ye Chenyuan.
From now on, this sword crystal
belongs to the Night Clan.
When I obtain the Divine Sword,
no one can pose a threat
to the Night Clan.
I
shall lead the Night Clan
to dominate all Three Realms.
- Dominate the Three Realms
- for eternity!
(All proceeds according to plan.)
(The third step)
(is waiting for you.)
(Get out of Su City!)
I've finally found you.
(So)
(it was I who killed my mother.)
Mother!
Mother, wake up!
(Forgive me.)
(In this lifetime,)
(I can't protect you.)
(I must make you hate me.)
♪Smiling without words♪
(Ye Chenyuan!)
(We meet at last.)
(Forgive me.)
(In this life, I must be the person
you hate the most.)
(To absorb the Night Deity's power
within her,)
(we must stay close for some time.)
(The Soul-Binding Rope)
(provides the perfect means.)
(Let me absorb
all the Night Deity's power from you.)
(This time, I'll bear all this.)
No!
♪No sail brings you back
across the wide♪
♪If only rain carried news of you♪
♪Like a lingering dream♪
He wasn't spewing
demonic energy at me,
but absorbing
the Night Deity's power within me.
(I must absorb the demonic energy
within you faster.)
(You'll obtain the Divine Sword,)
(become the Sword Master,)
(and then kill me.)
(No.)
(I haven't fully absorbed the power,)
(and it's already erupting.)
(Faster!)
(Or I will lose her!)
(Bai Xiaoying,)
(hold your breath)
(and focus.)
♪How dare I plead your day
across the wide♪
(This time,)
(I will never let anything
happen to you.)
♪Only fragments of memories remain♪
(It's so good to be with you.)
(Even if this is how it must be.)
(Do you know?)
(My heart truly aches.)
(I made you suffer. I'm sorry.)
Do it now.
Kill me.
I never exploit vulnerabilities.
You owe me this.
(Through countless years and lifetimes,)
(do you still love me?)
(Why did you save me?)
(Your pathetic mercy)
(spared my life.)
However,
I keep you alive
to prolong your suffering.
I won't let you die so easily here.
(Don't worry.)
(Give me some time.)
(I'll make Ye Chenyuan agree.)
(Ye Chenyuan,)
(what are you angry about?)
(You wanted her to hate you.)
(Blame yourself)
(if you must.)
(She still loves me.)
(She said you've been
in seclusion for 20 years.)
(Is that true?)
So at the Lantern Festival
ten years ago,
you never went to Su City
nor killed my mother.
So what
if it's true or not?
The world has accused me
of countless crimes.
I don't care at all.
(Ye Chenyuan,)
(you've learned nothing
in fifteen centuries.)
(You chose to deceive her.)
(But her not loving you upsets you.)
(Before awakening the Divine Sword,)
(I must fully absorb
the Night Deity's power within you.)
(If I were the Night Deity,)
(would you insist on killing me)
(like before?)
I'll find a way to prove
you're not the Night Deity.
(Yixi,)
(I'll do something
that breaks your heart completely.)
(This is the only chance
to change your destiny.)
(Just hate me.)
(Hate me.)
(Kill me.)
(Let everything end.)
So you've planned everything
while I remained oblivious.
No.
I won't let you do this.
Were you planning
to hide all this from me
until your death?
I'm sorry.
In this lifetime,
I deceived you.
For six lifetimes,
you waited alone
for fifteen hundred years
until you turned yourself
into the wicked Night Deity
people revile.
Was it worth it?
I know exactly what I'm doing.
I'm the true vessel of the Night Deity.
This is my fate.
Not yours.
I don't need you bearing it for me.
You have no idea.
It kills me, watching
the demonic energy take you,
helpless to stop it.
Watching you die in front of me,
over and over,
powerless to change it.
This time,
I won't suffer that again.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Ye Chenyuan,
don't leave me alone again.
Don't.
Bai Xiaoying,
this final step
must be done by you.
Kill me.
No.
After all we've been through,
now that I've finally
remembered everything,
how could I possibly kill you?
If you don't do it now,
the demonic energy
will consume me completely.
And all our previous efforts
will be wasted.
The Three Realms
will drown in bloodshed.
Is this what you want to see?
No.
But I don't want to see you die either.
If it requires sacrificing you
to save all living beings,
I would rather abandon the Three Realms.
Xiaoying,
I'm sorry.
Only through my death
can you survive.
♪Searching through half a lifetime,
I rest with the breeze as my pillow♪
♪The bright moon's yearning
echoes through lonely strings♪
♪Gazing across the mortal realm♪
♪She appears where lanterns fade♪
♪Storms disperse.
Drunken reunions trace past bonds♪
♪Asking when we'll meet in another life♪
♪A millennium passes in moments.
Where's today's joy♪
♪This love defies severing♪
♪Cutting a fragment of time♪
♪Shattered stars can't compare
to my resolve with you♪
No.
No!
Ye Chenyuan!
♪Carving your essence in my heart♪
I want nothing else.
I just want you to live.
I beg you, don't.
Don't leave me alone.
No!
Ye Chenyuan!
Please!
- Xiaoying.
Xiaoying,
I didn't know you were so good.
You managed to kill
the wicked Night Deity.
- I'm so thrilled for you.
- Yes.
- Exactly.
- Indeed, Xiaoying.
You're the hero of Nine Heavens.
We're all proud of you.
Congratulate our War God.
Congratulations, Xiaoying.
I mean, Lord War God.
We must learn from you.
Lord War God,
- you are the Nine Heavens' hero.
- Xiaoying!
- You are amazing!
- We're proud of you.
Xiaoying.
As the Sword Master of the Nine Heavens,
you've resealed the Night Deity again,
restoring peace to the world.
You've done well.
By right, you should become
the Nine Heavens' War God.
Do you accept?
I remember everything
of the past fifteen hundred years.
Immortal Lord,
you didn't know
that Ye Chenyuan
was Wan Guchen from the past, did you?
What did you say?
♪Withered trees bear decaying rings♪
♪Love and hate entwine in cycles♪
♪Vows unravel into parting words♪
♪The harsh mortal world
cuts like a blade♪
♪Your icy tone♪
♪Wounds across lifetimes♪
♪The bitterest tear stains♪
♪Scorch my lips♪
♪Memories pile up, tender and warm♪
♪Our fated bond clings unyielding♪
♪Fate's mottled lines on palms♪
♪Severing dawn from endless night♪
♪Bitter winds gather sparse stars♪
♪Yet still I wait♪
♪For a promise lost,
to share life's journey♪
♪Ephemeral blooms fade overnight♪
♪Drunken delusions feed this obsession♪
♪Through lifetimes of chains,
only my sighs remain♪
♪Sorrow soars over peaks♪
♪Never reaching the far shore♪
♪How could I seek you in fading lights?♪
♪Memories pile up, tender and warm♪
♪Our fated bond clings unyielding♪
♪Fate's mottled lines on palms♪
♪Severing dawn from endless night♪
♪Bitter winds gather sparse stars♪
♪Yet still I wait♪
♪For a promise lost,
to share life's journey♪