I like you, Shioya-san.
For a long time now, I have been…
Sato-san.
Yes?
Good morning.
Shi… Shioya-san?
Good… morning.
I remember now.
Shioya-san let me stay here last night.
And then…
We… we kissed.
If you want to go home before work,
it's best to leave early.
Yes, you are right.
His reaction is so ordinary.
Could it be an ideal dream born from my fantasies?
Also, if you go now, Mizoguchi is still sleeping.
I see. I'll get changed.
♫ Obviously, you already know. Hush ♫
♫ Bold lines ♫
♫ Hey, I want to say; I can't say; I won't say absolutely ♫
♫ Show me your face for the first time ♫
♫ Obviously, you already know. Hush ♫
♫ Bold lines ♫
♫ Hey, I want to say; I can't say; I won't say absolutely ♫
♫ So sweet that it's unsettling ♫
♫ About to, want to be discovered, still not discovered today ♫
♫ I just want to see the real you ♫
♫ Kiss you ♫
­[Seal My Lips with a Kiss]
[Episode 2]
Thank you so much for yesterday.
Don't worry about it.
So your roommate is Mizoguchi-san.
Yes.
When I told him I would move closer to the company,
Mizoguchi said it'd be more convenient to live close
and half forcefully moved in.
I see.
But he's annoying. I hope he moves out soon.
So straightforward.
But we agreed that whoever gets a girlfriend has to move out.
So... does that mean you're single now?
Yes.
Sato-san, you...
Yes?
Nothing.
Yes!
Shibayama, confirm again the final schedule with the person in charge.
Got it.
Mizoguchi-san, here's the presentation.
Let me take a look. Thank you.
Also, could you please prepare the proposal document for Morga Games
by the end of today?
Okay.
[What is the weapon of Morga Games?]
Is the proposal ready?
I'm almost done.
Sato-san, being meticulous is a good thing.
But it would be better if you could pay more attention to speed.
Sorry.
You just need to follow the Handover Manual instructions.
[Sales Department Handover Manual]
But…
Why not put in a little effort yourself?
Okay, I'm sorry.
I will work hard.
Thank you.
By the way,
today buy a gift box from Wagashi Store in front of the station.
"Gift box"?
The red bean paste one?
Shioya-san?
Yes.
[Sky Wave]
I'm exhausted.
I was so happy this morning and even had a beautiful dream.
Sato-san.
Shioya-san.
You've worked hard.
Thank you. You've also worked hard.
Are you working overtime today as well?
Yes.
It's embarrassing to admit it,
but my work progress is too slow.
Here you go.
Thank you. I really needed some sugar.
Also, I want to apologize to you.
"Apologize"?
I didn't consider your feelings yesterday
and did that to you.
What do you mean by "that"?
The kiss.
What?
I'm really sorry.
What? What!
Why are you so surprised?
Sorry, I thought it was a dream!
I should be the one feeling embarrassed.
What did I do to you?
You don't need to apologize.
I've already decided on no more involvement with you, Sato-san.
Rest assured.
"No more involvement" with me?
It's not here.
Of my clothes,
why only the underwear?
No matter what, I must get back my underwear!
Shioya-san, good morning.
Good morning.
You see… I seem to have left something at your place.
Then I'll bring it tomorrow—
No! Please let me get it myself.
Okay.
Thank you.
Found it.
Great, I'm relieved.
Did you find it?
Yes.
Thank you for letting me look for my stuff.
I'm home!
Why?
He was supposed to go to a dinner party today.
Shioya, you're home, right?
What? You're here.
Shioya-san, this...
Shioya.
Just stay still.
Okay.
The dinner party was rescheduled.
I'm hungry. How about you?
I've eaten.
Oh, is that so?
I'll go out to eat my fill and return.
Really, they should notify me earlier if they reschedule.
Are you okay?
Sorry for getting you all wet.
Sorry.
I'm glad we weren't caught.
You really like him.
Pardon?
Isn't that why you don't want him to see you?
What?
Don't you have a crush on Mizoguchi?
What are you talking about?
Did you say anything?
It's impossible!
No, you must have heard wrong.
Is that so?
I thought I heard a girl.
You might be possessed by something.
Don't say scary things.
Thank you for lending me clothes again.
A-Also…
the kiss.
Sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
I should apologize for giving you unpleasant memories.
It's not unpleasant at all. It's cute…
Never mind.
So...
when you said no involvement with me, was it because…
I thought you liked Mizoguchi.
Mizoguchi-san and I...
We interact a lot at work,
but I have no special feelings for him at all.
Then...
if you could stop saying
no involvement with me, I would be very happy.
I see.
Mizoguchi is very capable at work.
I cause him much trouble at work.
Do you, Sato-san?
It's all because I didn't work hard enough.
I must work harder.
Sato-san,
if you encounter difficulties at work, let me know.
Thank you.
[Shioya]
Da… daifuku? (red bean pastry)
What's wrong?
Mizoguchi, I have something to say.
Is it about my spilling coffee on your hoodie?
- Sorry.
- That's not it.
But you'll have to pay for it later.
Darn it.
I want to discuss Sato-san in the Sales Department.
I hope you can take care of her.
Please, she seems distressed lately.
Right.
You know her from General Affairs Department.
"Sato"?
Then Sales Department's welcome party
for this year officially begins!
- Cheers!
- Hooray!
Great work, everyone!
Matsuyuki, what do you think of Sato-san?
What? I'll say what I think.
Well, she's a serious person.
She does need more time at work.
After all, she is Usuda-san's successor,
and people would compare them.
You are right.
Mizoguchi-kun, you need to pay attention
to the person taking over my position.
Do you mean Sato-san from General Affairs Department?
I heard from a colleague at General Affairs Department
that she was incompetent at work.
She seems like someone who plays around.
Is that so?
But during the interview, she seemed quite serious.
Moreover, I heard she especially likes to please men.
Is that true?
So she will act obedient and cute in front of you.
Be careful not to be deceived.
If you say so…
Moreover, in this situation,
her true nature should be showing by now.
Here you go. You're the main character. Drink, drink.
I'm sorry, but thank you.
- But you don't need to look after me.
- Your glass is empty.
In the current situation, instead of saying she likes to please men,
it seems more like she struggles around men.
Those going for a second round, please follow me!
Shall we ask Sato-san to come?
They say she likes to please men so she should say yes.
Wait, Sato-san. Are you coming for the second round?
Do you want to go have a drink with me?
Well, I… that…
Sorry, I'll discuss something with Sato-san.
- I will confirm tomorrow's work with her.
- What?
Discussing work at this kind of time?
That's right. You guys go ahead.
- See you.
- Okay.
Mizoguchi-san.
I don't think I can work in this condition.
It was an excuse.
What?
Thank you.
I couldn't drink anymore; thank you for rescuing me.
You didn't have to drink so much.
But they poured drinks specially to welcome me.
I appreciate everyone's kindness.
Really?
Are you okay?
I am… so sorry for dragging you down
since I was transferred to Sales Dept.
Now on, I'll do my best to learn
and avoid such situations again.
I will also work hard to restore everyone's trust in me.
Are you handling a customer complaint?
No, I'd never treat you as a customer complaint subject.
Of course not.
But my attitude wasn't good, either.
Why do you look so surprised?
Well,
I thought you were such a person to whom apology is a loss.
That's a rude thing to say.
Pardon me.
Somehow, she is very different from the rumors.
I ask you.
- Do you truly like to please men?
- Hey!
Not at all!
I have always had a crush on the same person!
Is that so? How long has it been?
Two… two years.
That's long.
It's the truth.
But...
should I say I'm happy just looking at him?
You sound like a student's crush.
You should confess to him quickly.
Try calling him right now.
C-C-Call him?
What should I say?
What?
"I'm too drunk to go home."
"Please come and take me home."
You're laughing very hard.
You're a laugh-after-drinks type, right?
This is the first time I've seen her laugh.
I should be going.
Take care on your way home.
Okay.
Mizoguchi-san, thank you.
I will do my best to call him.
Okay.
[Kaede Sato]
Shioya-san.
Are you drunk?
No, I'm not drunk at all.
I'm sorry.
I intended to say it over the phone,
but I made you come all the way here.
It's okay. I worried about you, too.
I'm so happy to hear that.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
Your hands are so warm.
♫ Wobbling ♫
Let's go.
♫ Pouring into the empty container ♫
♫ Bare and fuzzy feelings ♫
Then I will go back first.
♫ The sky gradually fades, but I pretend not to see ♫
♫ Until everything is over ♫
You can't leave.
[Next Episode]
I like you, Shioya-san.
What kind of reaction was this?
I am here to show you my perfect strategy.
Mizoguchi-san has become more friendly.
Come to my house.
What exactly am I to you, Shioya-san?
[This drama is a work of fiction.]