Why don't we reschedule for next week?
That's good. I haven't told the staff yet.
I'm worried
they won't be able to process it.
Get Ms. Lin to change her mind
and rent somewhere else.
A ghost!
You should be talking to Mr. Pao
to find new opportunities for the staff
instead of plotting immature tricks
like a woman-child.
I need to change my plan.
Is our secret group's name adorable?
The CEO has been reeled in.
Can you tell me now what happened?
What were you so afraid of,
shaking that much?
There was a cockroach.
A cockroach?
Mhm.
You're not afraid,
so you wouldn't understand.
I'm lucky I didn't faint.
But thank you so much for saving me.
So what are you doing here?
I'm here to see you.
I wanted to ask you something.
What is it?
Do you know who sent me the balloons
and pure iced matcha?
I'll find out for you.
If you see her, tell her I appreciate it.
I love pure iced matcha.
No sugar.
Who would buy it for you?
Someone hung the balloons
at the gate again, ma'am.
Donut.
I can't believe I finally found
the one who makes me smile.
Hm?
That was quite a shock
we just had, wasn't it?
So who really was the first one to flirt?
Who do you think it was?
Me?
I'll introduce you to Ms. Lin someday.
You'll like her a lot.
However,
our livelihood is more important.
I need to stick to the plan
and not get soft, right?
Yeah?
When did you even order it, ma'am?
Should I order one for you tomorrow?
It's okay.
Alright.
It's refreshing.
So sweet.
Sweet? But that's pure iced matcha.
Perfectly bitter.
-I'll come back to help.
-Okay.
Hello.
Is that the Japanese restaurant?
Who are you trying to call?
I'm sorry. I called the wrong number.
How many times a day
is this going to happen?
I kept trying to call other numbers,
but I ended up calling this one.
Maybe I should block your number.
Block it, ma'am.
Definitely a scammer, calling you all day.
Where did they even get your number?
Oh, I almost forgot.
After the meeting, we have work to do.
Oh, Ms. Lin?
I'm sorry. I was in meetings all day.
Mhm.
Are you tired?
More hungry than tired, so I came over.
Oh? Then why didn't you call
to order from me?
I blocked your number.
I'd rather see your face.
I can't believe
that a big company like Family Nest
have a female executive this young.
I took over for my father
just a little while ago.
Why? Is your father retired?
Not really. He's not feeling well.
He's dealing with ALS right now.
Oh.
So your father took a break
and let his daughter
run the company in his place.
I know it's a little too soon,
but I want to give it a try.
I'm worried about him,
and want him to relax.
But I don't really know
how long I can keep going.
Why?
The partners don't seem
to have much faith in me.
The tutoring school project
that's going to be at Play Park's location
is a chance to prove my capability.
If it doesn't work out,
or the performance is lacking,
they'll vote for a new executive.
Maybe Dad would have to
get back in the position.
So I'm putting my all into this project
and don't plan to disappoint Dad,
so he won't need to
go back to stressful work
and risk relapsing.
Sorry for only talking
about stressful stuff.
Did I bore you?
Not at all. I'm a good listener.
When it comes to your stories,
I love to listen
and I want to know everything.
I know you really love Play Park.
It's not just a workplace.
A deep bond has been created.
In the past few days,
you've been trying to indulge me
because you've learned what I like, right?
I think I've figured out your game plan.
You're trying to change my mind.
I admit, I'm really into you.
But I'm not mad at you.
It's been an enjoyable few days.
It's not lonely.
If this all ends one day,
I'll feel quite lost.
-Let's go.
-Yeah.
Why are you yelling?!
Who told you to sleep here?
And why did you come down here?
Why aren't you sleeping?
I'm thirsty.
What's keeping you awake this time?
It's Play Park, isn't it?
I've decided.
You promised
that no one would lose their job.
I won't go back on my promise.
I'm relieved that you
and the staff have come to terms with it.
Thank you so much for understanding us.
I understand you as well.
Everyone has their own needs.
I'm sorry
for not being able
to keep Play Park running.
It's okay, Mr. Pao.
Just helping us find new jobs
is really kind of you.
-Yes, Ms. Lin?
-Let's go to Play Park this afternoon.
Mr. Pao has decided
to let us rent the place.
Really?
Kids, are you ready to board the train?
-I'm ready.
Raise your hand if you're ready.
Okay, then stand up!
Come on. Put your hands on the shoulders
in front of you to form the train.
Good job! Let's go.
Moms and Dads, please join us.
Come on, come on.
We're boarding the train now.
What sound does the train make?
-Choo choo! Good job.
-Choo choo!
Well, are you ready?
I'm ready.
The train is moving now.
What sound does the train make again?
-Choo choo!
What's the sound?
Choo choo! Good job.
-What world are we going into?
-Octopus!
An octopus.
Dinosaurs!
Dinosaurs. What color are they?
This one is pink.
And blue, and orange.
It's hiding in the water.
It's in the water?
An octopus has tentacles. What does it do?
Like this?
Hey, we're arriving at the gate
where we have to sing together
for it to open again.
Are you ready?
If not, we'll be stuck here
and won't be able to enter.
Let's sing. One, two, three.
‎Quack, quack, quack!
‎The ducks are bathing in the canal
‎Eyes wide open,
‎looking at the fish and shrimp
‎Quack, quack, quack!
‎The ducks are bathing in the canal
‎Eyes wide open,
‎looking at the fish and shrimp
We did it! Great job!
Shall we go on this ride?
Ms. Lin.
Having more fun than the kids?
How did you know?
How long have you been here?
Long enough
to see someone sing the duck song.
Ms. Lin!
I've talked with Mr. Pao.
Thank you so much for backing down.
Right.
Mr. Pao promised
that he won't let anyone lose their job.
Everyone will have new jobs,
because he's friends with the owner.
I made him an offer
that he has one month left
before we close down the park.
One full month?
So everyone has time to prepare.
Both the staff and little kids.
Thank you, Ms. Lin.
You're the loveliest.
Is this all the thanks I get?
I have to present this matter
at the board meeting too.
No reward for me at all?
That's all?
Ms. Lin!
You're cheating right now.
And don't you have
any consolation for someone
who suddenly lost her job?
That's enough, Ms. Lin.
Silly. Let go.
Walking with me this far is fine.
You can get back to work.
Mhm.
Then I'll treat you to
Japanese food again this evening, okay?
Are you tired of it yet?
I don't get tired of things. Once I pick
a favorite, it stays a favorite forever.
I won't change my mind so easily.
Okay. So, deal?
Mhm.
Ms. Lin, let's head back now.
Looks so delicious.
I wish you were here like this every day.
The table's ready.
I'm digging in!
Ms. Lin.
Come on.
Gyoza time.
Is it good?
I knew Family Nest
from the wedding studio.
That was our first business.
Then we expanded into baby clothes,
maternity wear, toys, baby products,
and much more.
Then the tutoring school
will be something entirely new.
Not that new. I'd say it's a continuation.
We take care of our customers
from newlyweds to parenthood.
So the tutoring school is for their kids?
Yes.
Parents want
the best schools for their kids,
so we aim to help prepare them.
Smells so good.
Don't touch it. It's still hot.
Did you wash the dishes or wash your hair?
Ms. Lin.
Why are you taking so long?
So this is what a "stunner" looks like.
Is it so hard to wipe it?
Can we eat now?
-Wanna taste it?
-Mhm.
Is it good?
-No.
-Oh?
Just kidding.
It's delicious.
The best I've ever tasted.
You eat it.
Delicious?
I want to hear more about you too.
There's nothing interesting about me.
I don't care what others think,
but I'm interested.
What do you want to know?
About Donut.
I knew it.
I was so shocked
to find out you have a child.
You thought Ith was the father, right?
Yeah.
Everyone thinks that.
I thought my intuition failed me there.
I almost gave up on flirting with you.
Why are you so direct?
Not always.
And…
don't you mind that I have a child?
Not at all. I love kids.
Why are you saying it
like you're in a beauty pageant?
If your family was still together,
I would have stepped away.
So it's not just me, right?
I…
I need to leave.
I'm worried Ms. Lin
is being deceived, sir.
But it didn't affect her work, right?
Just a little delay.
Ms. Lin postponed
the Play Park closure by a month
to keep that woman happy.
And what does the board say?
I still haven't gotten an update.
But Ms. Lin has scheduled a meeting
to clarify the progress and reason.
Please take care of Lin for me.
Don't let her personal matters
hinder the work.
And if you see anything
that could be problematic,
handle it immediately.
You have my permission.
Yes, sir.
Ith!
Again?
Leave some lights on, please.
The shock's going to kill me someday.
And what's with you?
Aren't you going to sleep?
Want a night guard job?
I'm considering it.
What's bugging you again?
Can you stay out of it just once?
No, because I have only one sister.
Well, well.
Relationship drama, for sure.
Smartass.
Did I get it right?
Mhm.
Do you remember Ms. Lin?
-Really?
-I didn't say anything.
Is she the one?
Mhm.
Go for it, sis.
Are you crazy?
Isn't it too soon?
What's the holdup?
You know I haven't been
in a relationship before.
And look at her.
Look at how experienced she is.
There. Why are you blushing then?
And your ears. All red.
But I really don't know
if this kind of love will last.
I'm not sure if it's right for me.
Well…
I don't know.
And I'm scared to move forward with it.
I don't want anyone
to end up getting hurt.
You're still scarred
from what Guy did, right?
Listen to me.
You need to erase
all those awful memories.
It wasn't your fault.
Also, it wasn't even your choice.
Or is it because of Donut?
No.
He'll understand when he grows up.
It's more like my problem.
Ms. Lin! Ms. Lin.
Ms. Lin.
You forgot your bag.
Thank you.
No balloons today, Gib?
I don't see any, ma'am.
Did you order them?
No.
Would you like me to throw away
the deflated balloons in your room?
No need. Keep them there.
Yes, ma'am.
I… I need to leave.
No drinks delivered today?
No. Did you order it?
I'll go get it for you.
It's okay.
They probably forgot.
They can't forget it.
Have you paid for it?
Forget it. I'll be right back.
But these documents need to be signed.
I'll be back.
Where are you going, Ms. Lin? Ms. Lin?
Play Park, for sure.
Just installed the tracker,
and I need it immediately.
I'm sorry, Ms. Lin.
Your father told me
to keep a close eye on you.
How do I use this?
"I'm coming over. We need to talk."
You had to come see me here?
-May. May.
-Yes?
If Ms. Lin comes and asks to see me,
just tell her I'm out on errands
and I'm not sure when I'll be back, okay?
-Yes, Manager.
-Okay, thank you.
Let's go. You wanna go on this ride?
Alright, be careful.
Slowly. Let's go!
Excuse me.
Hello, Ms. Lin.
May I ask where the manager is?
She told me to tell you she's not here.
I don't know. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Do you know which way Play Park is?
She's already taken.
Sorry, may I ask your name?
My name's Lilin.
Lilin.
And you?
I'm Atis.
What brings you here, Ms. Lilin?
I'm attending a business meeting here.
-A business meeting at Play Park?
-Yes.
The weather's nice today.
Yeah?
But it's so cloudy.
This is perfectly chill.
It'd be too hot if it were sunny.
Want to get coffee together?
Of course.
Have you been here often?
Not really. I've been busy,
so I rarely come.
Your order's ready.
-A dark roast Americano for you, sir.
-Thank you.
-And hot green tea for you, ma'am.
I need to head back to the office now.
I have an urgent meeting this afternoon.
Will I have a chance to see you again?
You bought me a drink today,
so let me treat you to dinner.
Gladly.
Come here, come here.
What did you hear?
They're meeting for dinner, IngIng.
Where? When?
I know this restaurant.
My friend works there too.
It's a fancy place.
Though, your boyfriend's
so handsome.
And she seems a little intense.
Stop it.
Don't talk about her like that.
You don't even know her.
Here.
Take this.
And listen, don't say anything
that would bring her down.
Get back to work now.
I thought it'd be 200.
Ms. Lin.
Is everything alright?
I can't find my car.
I'm sure I parked it here.
Maybe it's in a different zone?
The parking zones look the same.
I'll help you look for it.
So, what's the car's color
and license plate number?
It's a white car, plate number 4KT50
Okay.
It's here, Ms. Lin.
White car, 4KT50.
So it is. Thank you so much.
It's nothing at all.
And please don't forget our dinner.
Are you sure
you don't want to be an actor, Mr. Atis?
I wouldn't go that far.
If you can secure a date with Ms. Lin,
you're something else.
I should thank Coach Jane.
This is next-level planning.
How did you come up
with the parking spot trick?
I always have
a spare key to her car with me.
If I told her it was a blind date,
she would never agree to go.
It had to be a coincidence like this.
But if she finds out,
won't she be really upset?
No… I mean, no one would be left alive.
So when is the first date?
You look so beautiful today.
Thank you.
All the boys will be stunned.
I'd rather stun the girls.
Your car key.
Oh?
She already left?
Is she dressed to impress
or dressed for war?
What's this?
Ms. Lin.
Your boss has been busy lately?
If I'm not mistaken,
I think Ms. Lin is in love, sir.
So, we're dating now, right?
What would you like to order?
Please give us a moment to decide.
Prae?
Subtitle translation by:
Anan Pratchayakul