=About Love=
=Episode 2=
I'm here.
Ah.
Well,
get some rest early.
Yeah.
You too.
How about
we go grab a coffee?
Are you serious?
Not really. Maybe tomorrow?
It's a bit late today.
Let's get coffee tomorrow.
Okay.
Oh, right, I just...
When I passed by your place,
there was a cafe nearby.
How's that place?
Pretty nice actually.
But they don't have
many types of coffee beans.
The place we went to today
had a bit more options.
Alright.
Then let's go to the same place
again tomorrow.
Sure.
I'll come pick you up tomorrow.
Yeah.
I'm heading out then.
Oh, okay.
- Bye.
Hey, wait a second!
Your shoes.
Thanks for this.
You're welcome.
I'm off.
- Good night.
- Bye.
Bye.
(I once navigated)
(among those men with masterful acting.)
(There are improv performances
full of technique but devoid of emotion.)
(Never affecting
the villains' genuine performances.)
(I know this isn't a fair game.)
(But who's to blame)
(for leading them)
(to this forbidden land
of eternal damnation?)
(I've seen enough
of worldly love stories.)
(They all feel dull and predictable.)
(But when that special person appears,)
(I feel like
an inexperienced extra actor)
(before him.)
What's wrong?
Morning.
Morning!
Got you breakfast.
How'd you know
I love this shop's pan-fried buns?
You posted it on Moments.
Come on, get in the car.
Thanks.
(With his seemingly icy,)
(indifferent thoughtfulness,)
(he recklessly)
(awakened the innocent heart
I once kept hidden.)
Here.
No scallions or cilantro.
- Thanks.
- Here.
Wait a second.
I learned
a "noodle-eating hack" online.
Now it won't burn your mouth.
(He's so ordinary,)
(yet somehow truly remarkable.)
(I've never heard a fake compliment)
(from him.)
(But his care for me)
Eat up.
(is in every little detail.)
Text me when you get home.
- Okay?
- Alright.
You should head back.
- I'll get going then.
- Yeah.
- Bye.
(Love feels like such a heavy word.)
(I don't really believe in it.)
(And I'm not eager to talk about it.)
(But aside from love,)
(I can't figure out)
(what else connects us.)
(I'm growing more certain)
(that life shines brighter)
(because of a man)
(who belongs only to me.)
(I've started acting
like a student again,)
(checking zodiac signs)
(and reading the love guides.)
(I can spend two hours)
(getting perfectly dressed for someone.)
(I get restless over a late call)
(or message.)
(Bei)
(Moments)
(But I still can't help feeling scared.)
(Mingmig lets me get close to the lens.)
(Could this dazzling happiness)
(be just a dream or an illusion of joy?)
Who is she?
That little girl.
I haven't seen her before.
Her name's Mingming.
She's new at our shop.
Oh.
You really want to know the result.
Aren't you worried it might upset you?
Would it?
(Suddenly,)
(I understand those flustered women.)
(The more beautiful the love,)
(the greater the fear of losing it.)
(Who can be completely certain?)
Welcome!
Sen?
Bei hasn't arrived yet.
I'm not here for him.
I came for you.
Oh.
So, how's it going?
Having a good time here?
Yeah.
Bei's been looking out for me.
Try this cake.
The shop just opened.
Everyone says it tastes great.
I'm still working. I'll eat later.
Thanks.
Then I'll pick you up after work.
No need.
I've got something to do tonight.
You...
You're not going to see him, are you?
No.
You're starting again.
Right. Sorry.
I'm just worried about you.
Welcome!
I need to attend to customers.
Talk later.
I'm free anytime.
I'll wait for your message.
Hello.
(Mingming)
Mingming?
Yes.
How may I help you?
What kind of services do you offer here?
Let me give you a quick introduction.
This way, please.
Our main business is
luxury goods authentication.
Our boss studied
professional luxury management
and authentication techniques in the UK.
Of course, we also provide
maintenance
and repair services for bags,
as well as
recycling and consignment services.
By the way, the edge paint
on my bag came apart.
Can you fix it?
Let me take a look for you.
Sorry.
There's also a small bag inside.
Ah, your edge paint issue
isn't too severe.
If you're not in a hurry,
you can wait over there for a bit.
Ah, no rush.
Xiaoxi!
Why so early?
I came early, so I just came in first.
How is it? What about the shop?
Yeah.
Enthusiastic, attentive service.
Very professional.
Most importantly,
the boss's lady is satisfied.
Nonsense.
Mingming, come.
Let me introduce you.
This is my girlfriend,
Li Xiaoxi.
This is Mingming,
the one I told you about.
Hi, sister-in-law.
You should've said so earlier.
Hello.
Was that your boyfriend earlier?
This cake is from a trendy
internet-famous shop. It's hard to get.
Oh, really?
He treats you really well.
Sen just stopped by?
He just left.
You know him?
Of course, he's my buddy.
Ah, that explains it.
If you like this cake,
I'll take you to get some later, deal?
So this is how Bei is when he's in love?
Long live the boss!
Stop it. Who said I'm the boss's lady?
Who's this amazing person?
Got you hooked so fast?
Why not bring him out to meet me?
What's the rush?
Meeting the besties is a big deal.
It's still a bit early.
Afraid he won't pass my test?
He's different.
Oh?
Who was it that told me
that every girl says
her boyfriend is different
at the start of a relationship?
And it's because of
hormones and endorphins?
I used to think my husband was unique
and different from 99% of men.
And the result?
Now he's my ex-husband.
You got divorced?
He was cheating.
When did this happen?
Apparently, that cheating pair
has been together for a while.
Every time he told me
he was on a business trip,
I stupidly believed him
until I saw the two of them
enter a hotel.
Thanks to that vixen,
my life also got its own cheesy
"caught-in-the-act" plot.
Honey, you've worked hard.
You should've seen him
frantically pulling up his pants,
as if I'd never seen it before.
It was honestly hilarious.
So tell me, who makes you happier?
I was wrong. It's me who hurt you.
Her, or me?
Yingtao, don't be like this.
Honey,
does she please you more than I do?
That's enough!
Right then, I swore to make them pay.
But later, I thought about it again.
Why should I?
Why should I debase myself
over a man?
But I really can't forgive him.
The thought of that scene makes me sick.
So I just got divorced.
There's no going back anyway.
(I'm sorry.)
(I should've told you back then.)
(It's my fault.)
I need to use the restroom.
It's a shame Yingtao
didn't introduce us sooner.
That scum.
Why didn't you tell me then
to test him before marrying him?
If that had happened,
you probably wouldn't
have gotten married
and wouldn't be getting divorced now.
Right?
It's all in the past.
Enough about me.
Tell me about your boyfriend.
You've experienced
so much betrayal yourself.
Aren't you afraid he'll...?
I don't think he's that kind of person.
You haven't even tested him.
How do you know he's not?
Is that necessary?
Yes, absolutely.
If you truly love him,
you have to confirm he is yours,
exclusively yours.
I don't want you to repeat my mistakes.
Then...
No need to worry.
Leave it to me.
I'll take care of it.
Let's treat it
like a reality show.
(I never thought the day would come)
(when I'd be plotting my own)
(romantic suspense film.)
(But unlike before,)
(this time, I'm neither the director)
(nor the actor.)
(I'm just part of the audience.)
(I feel an unprecedented anxiety.)
(This time,)
(the ending remains just a mystery.)
(But this time,)
(I desperately hope)
(that one-in-a-million chance
might happen.)
Excuse me, handsome?
Sorry to disturb you.
Could you tell me
how to get to Huaxi Park?
Go to the end of
that intersection up ahead,
then turn left.
After that, go through
three traffic lights
and probably further...
That sounds too complicated.
How about this?
Could you show me the way, handsome?
Huh?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It's kind of rude for me
to ask like this.
It's just that my bag
and my phone got stolen today.
I genuinely don't know
how to get to Huaxi Park.
So...
Alright then,
I'll take you there.
Okay!
Here, take this.
Thanks, handsome.
I'm so lucky to have run into you today.
Otherwise, I'd have no idea what to do.
Yeah.
Come on, get in the car.
He's got a spare umbrella.
Come on, get in.
Thanks.
Do you know...?
Sir!
It's fine. I'll cover the fare.
Sir, how much to Huaxi Park?
Ten yuan.
Okay, sent it.
No, it's not about the money.
It's about...
Anything else?
Your umbrella.
Keep it, I don't need it anymore.
Wait, you...
Don't get too proud yet.
His "fortune" is just beginning.
Hold on!
Thanks.
Hello.
Hi.
What's wrong?
Don't you recognize me anymore?
Who are you?
We see each other
in the elevator every day.
Sorry, I never really noticed.
On the street,
I turn quite a lot of heads.
People say I look like
that internet celebrity,
Mengmeng. Do you think so?
Really sorry.
Many girls get work done now...
They all look pretty similar, so...
I don't really remember.
Did he just say I've had work done?
Do I even look like I did?
No. He's just...
never been good with words.
Don't take it to heart.
I mean, I'm still adored
everywhere I go,
and flowers would bloom for me, right?
Yeah.
He actually said
I look like I got work done?
I'm so mad right now.
Hey!
Calling me?
I just broke up.
He doesn't want me anymore.
It really hurts.
Can you talk with me for a bit?
Sure.
Okay then.
Wait for me a second, alright?
Gong,
there's a girl here who just broke up.
Can you come over?
Is she pretty? How's her figure?
Is she my type?
She's actually quite pretty.
What kind of type do you like?
Honestly, I'm fine with any kind.
Send me the location.
Keep an eye on her for me.
I'm on my way.
Tone it down.
I'll send you the address.
I...
I don't feel that bad anymore.
I'm much better now. Thank you.
No, my friend's almost here.
He's coming to comfort you.
No need, goodbye.
He's great at comforting people.
Don't leave!
He lets a few chances slip away.
He must be really into you.
But don't you think
that's kind of strange?
How could a man
be so resistant to temptation?
My dear,
aren't you being a bit
flexing your happiness?
Don't push your luck.
You're asking for a slap.
But the man I want
is one who stays devoted
to me wholeheartedly
and completely unmoved
by any temptations.
If he's not that kind of man,
I'd rather not have him.
Currently,
that's exactly how he acts.
But don't you feel
something's missing?
I think I get it now.
It's because it's always outside,
and it's not convenient.
We need to get inside
and use stronger tactics.
Alright,
we can give it one last shot.
We need to find someone
who has all the charm and allure,
stunning and cinematic.
A true goddess.
Who are you looking for?
Excuse me, does Mr. Bei live here?
That's me.
Hi, I'm
from the Sisters Housekeeping Team.
What do you mean?
(Housekeeper Yingtao)
Our team has deep partnerships
with major banks.
As our esteemed Gold Card member,
you'll get one "freebie" opportunity
for our
deep-cleaning service.
Fine, come in.
Okay.
I'll be cleaning
your place for four hours.
During that time,
I'll fulfill any request
from the client.
If...
you need additional services...
Wait, you...
Sir, I haven't finished speaking.
You really love to cut people off, huh?
Wait, you...
Do all housekeepers dress like this?
Just call me Yingtao,
like "cherry lips".
Ah.
♪Now we strike, defying gravity♪
♪Now we strike,
breaking galactic distance♪
moving with the beat so free♪
♪Now we strike,
reaching the highest peak♪
♪Hold up, this is a brand-new reality♪
♪Hold up, no more fantasies♪
♪Hold up, no more aches♪
♪Hold up, watch me take the lead♪
♪Step out of the car,
no going off track♪
♪I said we're on the move♪
♪No taking the long way round♪
♪Not the second place♪
♪We win, taking all the trophies♪
♪It all depends on you♪
♪One day, we'll wake up♪
No, Miss Yingtao.
You've been
tidying this spot
for nearly half an hour. Maybe...
do something else?
Alright, boss.
Do you have any other instructions?
Actually, I do.
But this request of mine
might exceed your usual duties.
No problem.
If I can do it, it's no problem.
No problem?
♪We won't stop, we'll give it our all♪
That's great.
Xiaoxi.
What's wrong?
I've been thinking for a long time.
I still had to come and tell you.
What happened?
I'm sorry.
Come on, get inside.
Go inside.
What's wrong?
I think...
testing him was a mistake.
I've fallen for him.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, how do I put this?
Can you be a little more sincere?
Put a bit more honesty into your act.
Let's do another take.
No, Xiaoxi, I mean it.
I wish I'd never met him.
Blame me, yell at me.
You can even hit me,
as long as it makes you feel better.
But can I ask you for one thing?
Give him to me.
Better.
Keep that state.
But think about it.
We've been friends for so many years.
If you were in this situation,
you'd probably feel
really guilty toward me.
At least...
shed a tiny bit of crocodile tears.
That would feel real. Just one drop.
Come on, let's try again.
Think about it once more.
Feel it deep inside.
That kind of sadness from the heart.
Xiaoxi!
Did he hit you?
I can't keep acting.
I really can't keep acting.
Not testing again?
Why didn't you stop me
from going to his place?
Do you know
how I endured
those hours
at your boyfriend's house?
So? Did it work?
Yeah, it's all good now.
Wow, you really nailed it.
Any other requests?
Actually, yeah. Come with me.
You really worked hard today.
All fixed?
You're seriously amazing.
There's nothing you can't do.
After all, I'm a pro.
I'll make sure you get
a five‑star review for this.
I can't thank you enough.
If there's more time,
he even wants me
to clean his air conditioner.
But the thing is,
do you know
what he said to me in the end?
Wait a second.
Grab a bottle of water.
Thanks.
Wait, there's more.
Can you help me take this downstairs?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
You're really good at this stuff.
Good at what? This is ridiculous.
I've never been treated
like this in my life,
so humiliated.
That guy
is the coldest person
I've ever tried to please.
I'm so mad.
It really hurts my pride.
Calm down. Have an orange and cool off.
Don't tell me you two
just didn't want to do chores,
so you tricked me
into volunteering instead?
No way, sis.
This whole plan was your own idea.
I don't care!
Our little friendship just died.
Alright, I know
you suffered.
I owe you one.
Seriously, your boyfriend is sick.
Serious issues.
You'd better look into it.
Something's off with him.
Totally off.
I'll take it as it is.
Don't you think
the world becomes lovelier
because of men like this?
Didn't expect you
to enjoy movies like that.
I love the starry galaxy at the end.
It feels a bit like Socrates,
gazing up at the stars.
Alright. If there's a chance,
I'll go with you.
Up to you.
Okay.
Two bottles of cola, please.
Bei,
isn't that Mingming over there?
And the person next to her isn't Sen.
Isn't Sen Mingming's boyfriend?
Sen's been chasing her for ages.
But Mingming still hasn't said yes.
Sen's your good friend, right?
Yeah.
One is Sen.
Then me, and Gong.
The three of us grew up together.
I've heard you mention Gong a lot.
Who is he?
Actually, tonight...
I'm meeting up with Sen and Gong.
How about
you come along with us?
I think
it's time to introduce you.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I dressed so casually today.
How embarrassing.
You look great in anything.
It's fine, don't worry.
- Let's go.
- Yeah, let's go.
That's the place. Shancheng Restaurant.
Oh, it's here?
Don't be fooled by how small it looks.
The food tastes just as good
as any fancy hotel's.
Plus,
this place holds
the taste of my whole youth.
That makes me even more curious.
They should be upstairs.
- Fatty!
- Bei, you're here!
- Yeah.
- They're waiting upstairs.
And who's this? Introduce her.
My girlfriend.
You lucky guy! Such a pretty girlfriend!
Tell you what, I'll have the kitchen
make you two signature dishes.
Go on, don't stand there.
Alright, thanks. Let's go.
- Go on up. Enjoy!
- Thanks.
Hey,
listen to me.
Your judgment's flawed.
Sitting here
is more ergonomic
than there.
The left side.
Right here.
But I should warn you in advance.
These people are all a bit quirky.
So you'd better be mentally prepared.
Okay.
Then, welcome to
the Oddball Club.
You still need to learn...
Hey, get back here!
Last time, I told you
to keep an eye on that girl in the park.
Where'd she go?
Who did that? She left on her own.
I came all this way
just to wander alone?
She was smart to leave
when she knew you were coming.
Cut the chatter.
Down this drink
as your apology.
Let us have some fun.
Hold on.
Down it!
I'm driving. No alcohol for me.
Come on.
Besides,
whether I can drink depends
on your sister-in-law now.
Sister-in-law?
Come on, Xiaoxi.
Here.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Jiang Yifan.
Sister-in-law,
have we met somewhere before?
Yeah.
Well...
We met at Bei's shop.
Right, right.
That day...
Welcome, gorgeous. Big welcome.
Hello.
Hey there.
Do you have a girlfriend?
What are you staring at?
Never seen a beauty?
This is the one I told you about,
Gong.
Hi, I'm...
I'm Deep in the Alley.
I like you.
I like you...
I've fallen for you.
You're...
Jiang...
You're Jiang Rongrong, right?
Are you out of your mind?
We always hear
Bei mention you.
He keeps going on about
how amazing his girlfriend Rongrong is.
Like she's practically perfect, right?
Now that I've met you,
I see he wasn't exaggerating.
Who's Jiang Rongrong?
Ignore him, he's just being silly.
No.
Wrong person?
My bad.
Lucy.
Got it right this time, huh?
Can you stop already?
Enough already?
What's with that face?
It surely can't be Jessica,
sister-in-law.
This really isn't on me.
He brings a girl
without warning us.
My apologies.
Don't mind him.
I'm telling you,
he looks just like Ouyang Feng.
You can befriend these others,
but keep your distance from him.
Never thought Bei
had so many nicknames for me in private.
But no matter what he calls me,
I'm still his only girlfriend.
That's no fun.
Nice meeting everyone.
Hope I can join you guys in the future.
- Not drinking today.
- Let's gather more often.
- Come on.
- Chat ideals, get wasted!
- Sure.
- Welcome, welcome.
Alright, I...
But rest assured.
I won't steal him away, except...
In bed.
Hey, tone it down. That sounds awful.
Does this mean
you can't hang
with us anymore?
Why does my heart ache
so badly
like I'm dying?
Go die then.
Ignore them, that's just how they are.
Come on, let's eat.
Sis-in-law,
do you have a twin
as beautiful
and sensible as you?
I'm not asking for myself.
I'm asking for Gong.
Yeah.
Isn't there
someone who looks
just like you?
Like you were both made
from the same mold?
Sorry to disappoint you.
I'm an only child.
Here, let me introduce you.
This dual-toned hair guy
is Xiu.
He runs a musical instrument shop
and sometimes writes songs
that never sell.
Your hairstyle's really cool.
Keep it low-key, please.
I've always admired
people with artistic talent.
I'd love to hear your work sometime.
A true wordsmith artist.
Bei, take notes.
Can you talk like a normal person?
Sure.
Aren't I learning every day?
And this beauty is Luanluan.
She's a stage actress.
We treat her like a bro.
I'm Luanluan.
- Hi.
- Congrats to you.
You found the best one
among these men.
Hey, I'm still right here.
You're awesome, too.
And this guy here.
Don't be fooled by him.
His name's Gong.
He might not look it,
but he's actually a comic artist.
My boyfriend...
is a comic artist.
Though he hasn't published
any comics yet,
in my heart, he's still
a true flirt master.
Wait, what's a flirt master?
Isn't that right?
Did you drink too much to even draw now?
I'd really love to see you draw.
My bad.
Wrong choice of words.
I should've said "indiscriminate".
Guess you don't really get me then.
I don't plan to.
I've got three rules.
First, I don't date clueless fools.
Second, I stay away from gold diggers.
And third,
never go for someone already taken.
Don't take it so seriously.
I might actually believe you.
This guy is Sen.
As in the "sen" that means forest?
Yeah, the one with three trees.
It stands for steadfast.
What part of you is steadfast?
Your hair?
These are all my best friends.
- Now you know everyone.
- Bei, is that all?
Everyone else gets a bio.
Why don't I get one?
How's he supposed to describe you?
Love repellent?
Hopeless romantic?
What's wrong with quietly
being a low-key bachelor?
Who are you calling a bachelor?
I've got a girlfriend, alright?
And she's really gorgeous.
I'd like some seeds.
Let me be straight with you.
We're getting along
pretty well right now.
Things are developing nicely.
Just no chance
to hang out with you guys now.
(Yu)
Hello?
I'm writing songs at the shop.
What's up?
How long have you two known each other?
Counting today, it's been...
96 days.
If we get more specific,
it's exactly 3 hours
and 31 minutes.
I use this trick all the time.
I can get it down to the exact second.
Nobody thinks you're mute
if you shut up.
Eat more, just focus on your plate.
And you?
How long have you been with Xiu?
Sister-in-law, you've got a sharp eye.
You noticed?
You've got it wrong.
Xiu and I are just close friends.
How could this possibly hold me back?
I already make a living writing songs.
Why do you always insist that I...?
Alright, let's drop it.
Got a burst of inspiration.
I'll head back later tonight.
Bye.
♪I admit it♪
♪My back is against the wall♪
♪There's nothing I wouldn't try to do♪
♪For this feeling to have you♪
♪I resist♪
♪Your gaze, your lips♪
♪Your touch is a gift♪
♪There's no one that
I wouldn't try to fool♪
♪For an image of you♪
♪Take my hand again♪
♪Take my mind again♪
♪Break it to my heart again♪
♪I'm falling down again♪
♪I'm on my knees again♪
♪To beg for the truth♪
♪Tell me the secret of love♪
♪Is that the secret of love♪
♪I thought I had kept it from below♪
♪Did it come from above♪
♪Tell me the secret of love♪
♪Is that the secret of love♪
♪Gentle, passionate,
charming, terrifying♪
♪What is the secret of love♪