=About Love=
=Episode 17=
(Wild & Proud Rose)
(Women's Club)
Hi, Xiaoxi.
Have a seat.
How are things with Mu?
I came to tell you this.
Lin Chen is only curious about my past.
Weren't you two supposed to try for a week?
It's only been four days.
I can tell
he's not into me.
This is just a waste of time.
Besides, I agreed to help Mu
because of her feelings for Lin Chen.
But what if
Lin Chen really is a good guy
and has been loyal all along?
How will he feel
when he finds out
that we've been deceiving him?
How is Mu supposed to face him?
Are you backing out
because you have a boyfriend?
Has it ever occurred to you?
If it weren't for all this testing,
would you have trusted him?
I don't want to be Chen Qing anymore.
If you still can't trust Liu Chen,
find someone else.
Go see him one last time.
I'll consider it as the last thing
I can do for my sister, who might not
have much time left.
Guan,
your place looks nice.
You're always welcome here.
Where's what I asked for?
(100 Little Things About Love)
Zhen.
Yes?
Can I ask you
where did you
get that money?
I borrowed it.
I told you before.
From whom?
My parents.
What's wrong?
Why that face?
You're creeping me out.
Where were you last weekend?
I went home.
I told you.
Stop lying to me.
Didn't you go away for the weekend
with that admirer of yours?
Who told you that?
Am I right?
Yes,
but I did it for Zhen Guan.
Otherwise, how would we
cover the loss from the goods?
And
he's not an admirer.
He's just a friend.
Don't you know he likes you?
That guy knows
you have a boyfriend,
and he still keeps hanging around you.
I told you to stay away from him.
I kept my distance.
I said no.
Does it make him unforgivable
just because he used to like me?
We're in trouble right now.
He helped us.
I don't need that! How could I need that?
My girlfriend went on a trip
with another guy for money
and stayed overnight with him.
How do you expect me to feel?
So, what kind of person
do you think I am?
Nothing happened between us.
Can you trust me, please?
Lin isn't a bad guy.
He just has a terrible sense
of humor and a sharp tongue.
Don't fall for his tricks, okay?
Alright.
I trust you.
Let's not talk about him.
Listen to me.
Give him his money back.
We don't need it.
Okay?
If we give it back,
what about the money we need?
I'll figure something out.
Let's not rely on his money, okay?
We're just using it to get through this.
Once Zhen Guan gets back on track,
we'll pay him back.
There's nothing shameful about that.
It's not about shame.
We can sell the inventory, and...
And we can start fresh.
Trust me on this.
Right now, give him
the money back.
I don't need his money.
You still don't trust me, do you?
How dirty do you think this money is?
Fine,
so you don't want it.
You're high and mighty.
You're so noble.
I'm the cheap one.
Then go be noble on your own.
(100 Little Things About Love)
(An Miu)
Hello?
About that thing...
I don't want to do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
I just don't think
it means anything anymore.
Gosh!
I can't believe this.
Where are you?
Sweetie?
Oh, there you are!
Were you lonely at home by yourself?
Look at this mess!
I knew he must've torn the place apart.
We can't leave him alone at home.
Maybe we should send him to a pet shop.
You trust someone else with this?
Keeping him in a cage will make him depressed.
Is that right?
What do you mean?
So, we won't travel far anymore?
Since we chose to keep him,
we have to give up some time and freedom.
Stop it. The cleaning lady
is coming this afternoon.
We haven't named him yet, have we?
What should we call him?
How about...
"Thanks"?
Seeing him makes all our worries disappear.
We should thank him, right?
And we rarely say "thanks" in daily life,
but now we can call him.
Mm.
"Thanks" sounds nice.
You have a name! You're Thanks!
Thanks.
Honey,
thanks.
Honey, thank...
(Mom)
Hello, Mom.
You're coming over now?
No, we've got everything we need here.
Xiu and I have plans this afternoon.
Buying a new car.
Didn't you say we should
get a better one to look good?
I know, I know.
It's definitely time for an upgrade.
No,
Xiu earned the money,
from songwriting.
Why would I lie to you?
Alright, you can come with us.
Okay, we'll pick you up.
Alright, bye.
Mom said she wants to come with us.
Okay.
I'll work harder from now on
and get us a big house
with a yard.
Why?
Buying a wedding home for Thanks?
No,
to give him
more space to move around.
So later, when we travel,
we can leave him home and let him go wild.
But mainly because
you like growing flowers.
This yard is huge.
I want to grow lots of flowers too.
Then our future houses must all have yards.
That would cost a fortune.
We can just stay here
a couple of days each year.
You don't think I can do it?
Once my songs start streaming big,
the money will soar.
I'll buy this place outright.
If you get rich, will you still want me?
If you want me, I'm yours.
That's way too expensive.
Let's treat it as a dream.
It'll come true.
Better to be realistic.
Getting a new car is good enough.
Have you picked a model?
I don't know much about cars.
There aren't many
good all-round cars, are there?
Then let Mom help us.
So, tonight,
let's have dinner with Mom.
Tonight?
It might not work.
I promised someone
I'd help fix a demo tonight.
I need to work on it.
They'll pay me.
Since you promised, do it well.
Try to come home early tonight.
Okay,
I'll be home as I'm done.
Thanks.
Hi there!
Why are you so late?
What's up?
I've got something serious to tell you.
I've got something serious too.
How serious?
Very.
- You go first.
- Okay.
I went to his place last night.
We had some wine.
I wanted some Baijiu, though.
Never mind.
I can fake being tipsy, you know.
Then we chatted a bit.
I don't even remember exactly what.
Get to the point.
The point?
Well, his ex girlfriend posted
a photo.
It didn't register with me.
But yesterday, I realized it's his bedroom.
You're following his ex?
It could be an old photo.
Maybe she posted it
to give you the wrong idea.
No way.
When I zoomed in,
I saw a magazine on the table.
It was published this month.
I saw it last night.
Maybe it's edited.
I mean, that's possible.
Or maybe it's simpler than that.
She went to his place,
and they got back together.
After all, that girl
hasn't moved on.
Did you ask him about it?
No.
The vibe wasn't right.
I thought I'd ask later.
Does he not even know his ex has been
harassing you?
He told me he cut her off completely.
I swear, I almost wanted to
go confront her and dig
everything up right now.
What's the point?
What would you even dig up
with his ex?
Stop staring at me.
When did you get here?
I've been here for a while.
Am I wrong or not?
Exes never say anything nice.
So why bother believing them?
If you love him,
he's the best for you.
If not, just break up.
Don't overthink it.
Who are you?
It's none of your business.
Is it fun eavesdropping?
Just giving a friendly reminder.
You've been gossiping nonstop here.
It's messing up my
foreign language practice, big sister.
Big sister?
I'm not your sister, old man.
Can you be a little gentler,
ma'am?
Ma'am?
Fine, one of us is dying today!
Wait, miss!
Please watch your manners, lady.
Open your eyes. Look at me.
How old do you think I am?
Thirty-six.
Thirty-six?
Sixteen, sixteen, sixteen!
Eight years old!
Eight it is, okay?
He's Gong, right?
Yeah.
You said I'm like him?
No way!
I meant...
your hairstyle.
Fine.
Maybe I should reflect on myself.
What terrible thing
did I ever do
to make you think I'm like him?
So, this is how you've
seen me all these years?
No.
Miss Cherry,
I was a bit presumptuous.
Let me apologize with coffee instead of wine.
Put it down!
Jiang Yifan,
you said you had something serious to tell me.
If it's really serious,
maybe Miss Cherry should excuse herself?
Actually, it's nothing that serious.
I called you both here today
just to let you know
I've come clean to Bei.
I told him everything.
By "everything",
does that mean...
I suppose...
Not my part, right?
How could you two not be part of it?
I've told him the whole true story.
Bei said, after the play,
we should grab late-night snacks together.
After the play,
let's have dinner.
Don't leave.
Look at you two.
Are you falling for each other?
Problem solved perfectly!
Why aren't you happy?
We're happy.
Very happy, right?
Right, right.
Totally happy.
But no need for dinner, really.
Exactly.
We're family...
We're not even close. No need.
You two just live your lives peacefully.
Forget all those past grudges.
Let them go!
Let them go.
You two are so alike.
Yingtao,
I was going to take you to a play today,
but I didn't get front-row seats.
It's over your head anyway.
Let's just grab late-night snacks.
It's settled.
(Scoundrel Squad)
(Tonight,)
(don't leave)
(after the play.)
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Did I...
Did I pinch him too hard?
Did I make him cry?
Ma'am,
any preferences?
I can recommend a few.
Also, we can
arrange a test drive for you.
So, ma'am,
would you prefer a sedan
or an SUV?
(You received a message on WeChat)
(Yu)
(Got held up at the studio.
Can't make it. You guys go ahead.)
Mom,
Yu can't make it here.
Let's take a look first.
This one, sir.
The latest 6 Series, a four-door coupe.
And here's the newest BMW 7 Series.
The latest BMW coupe.
Yu, what's going on?
Didn't we agree to come together?
Mom, we've got a problem at the studio.
My model canceled last minute.
Are you buying the car or not?
Xiu can't make the decision.
You decide.
Just pick whichever you like.
I've got to go.
Need to make some calls.
Hello?
- Let's keep watching, young man.
- Sure.
Ma'am,
over here, please.
Mom,
have some tea.
Oh.
You're not working today?
I usually work from home.
Yu's been pretty busy.
Yes, she works late every day.
It's exhausting.
It's good for young people to earn more money,
especially for men.
They should support the family.
Let's get down to business.
Yu's father wonders if you're okay
with your future kids
taking Yu's last name.
What do you think?
Why is that?
It doesn't matter whose surname
the kids take now.
Look at the grandson of Yu's third aunt.
He took his mom's last name.
But his parents divorced.
Tell me,
who paid for this apartment
down payment?
You and Dad did.
But we agreed it was a loan.
We'll pay you back with interest.
Pay back?
You mean my daughter should pay us back
with her own money?
What a scheme.
Mom, that's not what I mean.
I meant we'd pay it back together.
How much do you make a month?
After the mortgage and daily expenses,
how much is left to pay us back?
I'll keep working hard.
As parents, we both
want our daughter to live well.
I mean,
you don't need to pay us.
The kids will take our family name.
We'll raise them.
You can keep your earnings.
No matter the surname,
they're your flesh and blood.
Honestly, we're making the bigger sacrifice.
We just want to
lighten your burden.
Mom, you didn't
mention this when we got married.
If you'd known, you wouldn't have married Yu?
No, that's not...
I didn't agree to Yu
marrying you in the first place.
Yu has always been
strong and outstanding since childhood.
She never gave us any trouble,
until she met you.
I think she must've lost her mind.
For you, she even
lied to me and her dad.
Your parents don't even have savings.
You can barely support yourselves.
When you got married,
you couldn't even afford a ring!
Paying us back?
When will you ever repay it?
If Yu hadn't been fooled by you
and insisted on marrying you,
when you're in your forties,
you'd still be trash who can't get a wife.
The back of this car
is quite not spacious.
Once you have a kid,
it'll feel way too cramped.
Ma'am,
this car has enough space.
Bigger isn't always better.
This model
is perfect for families with kids.
Look,
windows and the sunroof
have anti-pinch sensors,
very sensitive.
Little hands won't get caught.
And the trunk is spacious,
very convenient
for trips with kids.
Ma'am,
if this one feels small,
we have a bigger model,
plenty of room for
your future grandkids.
Shall I show you that one?
Mom,
Yu and I don't want kids yet.
Our careers just started.
We'll think about it a few years later.
You say that every year.
Can you keep putting this off forever?
Honestly, Yu and I have talked about it,
and we got a puppy now.
What?
Yu didn't tell me this.
You've got the energy for a dog,
but not for a kid? Get a life!
You know what?
Dogs are dirty.
If Yu gets pregnant, she can't be around one.
It's fine, Mom. Don't worry.
Dogs get all their vaccines now.
I hate your excuses!
I'm seeing a play with friends tonight.
Then we're grabbing late-night snacks.
- I won't see you.
- That's what I told Bei.
If you two talk about it later,
don't slip up.
Got it.
I'm sorry for
asking you to keep this from Bei.
I just couldn't tell him.
Never mind, anyway.
I was going to keep my mouth shut.
What difference does it make?
Since we can't be a couple,
I might as well be
the ex who leaves
no bad mark on your life.
Though I'm not really your ex.
Jiang Yifan,
can I ask you one last favor?
Of course,
anything I can do to help.
You definitely can.
When you see Bei later,
check his bag and his car.
See if there's a hammer
a wrench or something.
Make sure they're hidden.
I don't want to make the headlines.
You're insane.
Oh dear.
Tonight is
going to be interesting.
Why?
The play.
Love story, perfect for couples.
But you'll stop
believing in love after.
Do you know the plot?
I've read the script.
It's so...
How should I put it?
It's something...
Yu should never see it.
It'll crush her.
Why?
You'll see.
But it doesn't matter.
Xiu's going to get back with Yu anyway.
What permit does he have?
Dreams don't require a permit.
Even the worst person wants a better life.
And,
how do you know the current Xiu
isn't Yu's ideal type?
Looks like you and Bei
both hope Yu forgives her cheating husband
like nothing happened and gets back
together with him.
Outsiders talk about morals and rules.
But the people involved
care about feelings and interest.
Am I right, Jiang Yifan?
(Yu)
Hello?
Xiaoxi, you're the only one
who can help me with this.
You see?
(Moshi Fashion Studio)
Those seasonal pieces were made for you.
No one else could pull off this vibe.
Oh wow.
What about this one?
I honestly didn't expect
you called me here
just for this.
Of course. Who else could I ask?
I got
what you wanted.
Jiayin,
take everyone out for lunch.
- Okay.
- Mm.
Come on, let's grab a bite!
Let's go.
I can't give you the photo now.
I'm afraid it wasn't their fault.
It was mine.
I get it.
You think
you caused our divorce.
You feel guilty.
I wouldn't have before.
But Xiu is Bei's good friend.
Bei doesn't want his friend to split.
He hopes you'll reconcile.
Thank you for the photo.
I don't need it anymore.
I do want to
start over with Xiu.
Do you really think
you can forget everything
and act like nothing happened?
Never bringing it up again,
and just live normally?
I've asked myself that
over and over.
Honestly, I don't know whether I can.
Do you know
when it hurts me the most?
When you found out he cheated?
That hurts.
But what hurts me the most
was after I knew,
Xiu lied to my face
and I couldn't expose him.
Because I realized
I couldn't live without him.
All I wanted
was to ask him why.
Did he still love me?
Isn't that pathetic?
But I love him.
What could I do?
The scar is still there.
If there's someone
who can make me happy again,
why can't it
be him?
It can be.
But only if it's worth it.
Do you believe
they've broken up for good?
♪At night, I wonder if it will go away♪
No idea.
♪At dawn, I wonder if I will be okay♪
If…
If I find out they're not over,
I'll walk away.
♪Thinking about how to stay the same♪
When the day comes,
remind me to cut my losses.
♪I lie awake♪
(Yu should never see it.)
(It'll crush her.)
♪Only to lie and lie awake♪
There's this play tonight.
I think you'd like it.
(Tonight? It might not work.)
(I promised someone)
(I'd help fix a demo tonight.)
(I need to work on it.)
(Play: Delusion Girl)
(Written by: Luanluan)
Wrong place.
Come on.
Bro,
I bought a car.
800,000 yuan.
Picking it up the day after tomorrow.
Showing off here, huh?
No, that's not what I meant.
Wanna play a round of Game for Peace?
Hurry, hurry.
Go. Wait a sec.
Hurry, thirty seconds left!
On it. On it.
Heal up. Heal up.
Okay.
I'm out of meds.
- I'll drop you one.
- Okay.
Well,
why did Yu marry me?
What's wrong?
Suddenly feel not good enough?
Come on.
I'm serious.
Definitely not for your money.
Then maybe your looks.
You mocking me?
I'm just being honest.
You were good-looking back then.
Guitar on your back like you owned the world.
Looking all goofy:
"I'm gonna make my own music!"
That posture
bluffed everyone.
Hey.
I heard men mature
after they become fathers.
Is that true?
Is Yu pregnant?
No, I was just asking.
What happens when you have a kid?
Your career's finally picking up.
Why are you looking for trouble?
Do you feel your life needs more drama,
Hamlet?
First marriage,
now "deadbeat dad" mode?
Why the sudden baby fever?
Your world is crowded enough.
You can barely handle it.
Like you even have a sense of responsibility.
What are you thinking?
Here's a question.
Say…
Jiang Yifan.
Yeah, Jiang Yifan.
If... if she wants to marry you,
and you don't want to, but she'll
marry someone else. Would you do it?
Why bring her up?
She's your true love. Answer it.
Get married?
Give me a break.
Marrying her is even more impossible.
Forget it.
You don't get it.
Having a kid might not be bad.
He could play games with me.
Did you forget someone?
What about Luanluan?
We broke up.
I ended it today.
Knowing what a
shameless jerk you are,
I need to ask you this.
After the breakup,
what are you two?
Just friends?
Ha, I knew it!
Still songwriting partners?
You compose. She writes.
Perfect duo, huh?
You really are shameless,
and sleazy.
Alright.
Hang in there. I'll be there soon.
Okay. Good.
Wine's in the trunk.
Yes, you go ahead.
Okay, bye.
Sure, bye.
- Luanluan.
- Dad.
Break a leg!
Thanks.
I thought you weren't coming.
It's your directorial and writing debut.
How could miss it?
You've missed a few before.
Yes, Director Zhao.
You're there? Okay.
I'll be right over.
Yes, Mr. Wang is there.
Sure, you go ahead.
Right, let him warm you up
to the project details.
Alright, I'll be there soon.
Okay, got it.
No problem.
Oh, right.
How's it going with that married guy?
Broke up yet?
We're in love. No way we can break up.
What can you do? Can he get divorced?
He's not you.
Your mom and I weren't meant to be.
We fought every day.
How can we live like that?
That's not the same.
You were only five years old.
What could you understand?
Four, actually.
I meant in nominal age.
I meant in nominal age too.
Look, you mom and I
are doing fine apart now.
Yeah,
you're both doing great.
Don't be like this, okay?
Everything I've worked so hard for
is for you.
Money, the company...
It will all be yours.
I've given you everything you wanted.
(Delusion Girl)
You wanted to learn music.
I found you a music teacher.
You wanted to do theater,
I invested in your troupe, right?
All for your happiness.
What are you dissatisfied about?
I'm satisfied.
I just want to be in love.
Well, at least
take it seriously, alright?
We are serious.
But...
I need him, and he needs me.
Alright, fine,
as long as you're happy,
okay?
Oh right, after tonight's performance,
treat the troupe to dinner.
You need to know basic social etiquette.
Got it?
- You're leaving tomorrow?
- Yeah.
I was supposed to leave today.
Right. Yes.
Tomorrow's flight is booked.
Booked, that's right.
Yes, that one. Go ahead and book it.
You can just clear that through finance.
Okay, okay.
Alright, alright.
How long?
Four months.
Go on in, straight ahead.
Okay.
Call me if you need.
I'll go in then.
Hello, Director Zhao.
(Good luck!)
What would I need from you?
Don't forget I have a boyfriend.
Dana.
Yes?
Come here.
What is it?
What's this?
A wedding photo.
What a mess. I can't send
this to the client.
Now you're blaming me?
When you rushed to save your little lover,
did you even think about the client?
This shoot was supposed to be yours.
I did my best.
I've trained you for half a year.
Even an animal could handle this.
Don't you think I don't know why you're mad.
Your little lover
ran off with another guy.
Take it out on her.
Why on me?
Don't bring her up.
Now you're defending her.
If you love her so much, why not marry her?
Stop acting like some devoted lover.
You've not been at work for days.
Want a suggestion?
Buy her a handbag
and smooth things over.
She's not like you.
That's right.
She's different.
She hides behind perfection
while playing dirty.
I'm not in her league.
You don't need to work here.
What do you mean?
Don't you get it?
You're breaking up with me?
Yes.
Just like that?
Is my youth worthless?
I've given you enough money.
Your salary's high for such a simple job.
With your poor skills,
no one else would hire you.
Have some self-awareness.
Hey!
Order whatever you like.
Okay.
What about this couple's set?
Great. Great.
We'll have this.
Okay, just a moment.
Thanks.
I feel you're
acting crazy today.
How so?
Crazy handsome.
Really?
I picked this suit carefully.
Not bad, right?
After the play tonight,
are you all going to dinner?
Yeah,
are you coming?
Yes.
I thought you didn't like
hanging out with them.
Love me, love my dog.
Since they're your friends,
I want to fit in as soon as I can.
But it might be a little awkward
seeing Bei.
Why?
Did he say something to you?
No.
He just worries I won't
take good care of you.
Classic Bei. He worries
himself sick over his friends.
He's kind to everyone, a total sweetheart.
Honestly,
when I recommended you for the job,
I was afraid you'd fall for him.
Me?
No way.
That kind of guy
isn't my type.
That kind of guy?
What kind?
He's outstanding,
good-looking, and stylish.
He's kind-hearted
and humble.
Always proper and considerate.
He's ambitious.
No nasty habits I can see.
He's probably your mother-in-law's
ideal son-in-law.
Just name one thing
you don't like about him.
Nothing.
Don't you think he's so good
in an unreal way,
like a character in a K-drama?
So, I can't handle
such a perfect package.
Besides,
how do I know all his kindness
is genuine and not
just a calculated move?
You're overthinking.
Just guessing.
Have you heard this before?
In a perfect relationship,
if you can't find
a single flaw in someone,
he's either an actor or a con man.
That's such an exaggeration.
Bei's just a straight shooter.
He doesn't play mind games.
It's not just him.
Bei and Li Xiaoxi,
Mr. Perfect
and Miss Perfect,
treated each other like perfection itself.
These two
took "perfect loves" to the extreme.
But,
does a relationship that perfect exist?
No idea.
Anyway, I prefer
the way we are.
See? We both get jealous.
We complain and fight.
But don't you think that feeling
is safe and comfy?
Anyway, I love it.
Oh, my steak!
Here's your steak.
- Thanks.
- Please enjoy.
Thanks.
Smells so good!
Dig in.
You must be starving.
Here.
- Sen.
- Yeah?
I want to
savor this feeling longer.
The steak?
Have some more.
Are you an idiot?
Being in love.
I feel
this love we have now
is great.
Oh, I have a gift for you.
You'll see it when you get back.
A little surprise?
This is really a gift.
What are you thinking?
Eat up.
♪I'll admit♪
♪My back is faced against the wall♪
♪There's nothing that
I wouldn't try to do♪
♪For this feeling to have you♪
♪I'll resist♪
♪Your gaze, your lips♪
♪Your touches again♪
♪There's no one that
I wouldn't try to fool♪
♪For an image of you♪
♪Take my hand again♪
♪Take my mind again♪
♪Break into my heart again♪
♪I'm falling out again♪
♪I'm on my knees again♪
♪To beg for the truth♪
♪Tell me the secret of love♪
♪Is that the secret to love♪
♪I thought it had came from
below us♪
♪Did it come from above♪
♪Tell me the secret of love♪
♪Is that the secret to love♪
♪Is it violent or warming, entrancing♪
♪This secret of love♪