"Vow to You" - Liu Yuning
♫ The flames illuminate the dark night ♫
♫ Silences surrounds the world ♫
♫ The starlight fades away ♫
♫ The living stands in fear ♫
♫ Wake me up from this nightmare ♫
♫ I see through your blushing ♫
♫ The thought of you in this world urges me to make a decision ♫
♫ Entrusted to me the gale and flame ♫
♫ This farewell leaves me in pain ♫
♫ I am fearless when I take a drive into the abyss for you ♫
♫ I'll defend death to be with you ♫
♫ Heaven and Earth resonates with the mountains and rivers ♫
♫ The world is untamed and unbridled ♫
♫ Come what may ♫
♫ I am willing to risk my life for you ♫
♫ Let's go stargazing tomorrow ♫
♫ I'll never regret my lifelong vow to you ♫
[The Starry Love]
[Adapted from "The Starry Love" by Yi Du Jun Hua]
[Episode 37]
This is?
Royal Father? Follow me to the hall and protect the Void Tyrant!
Chaofeng?
As long as the Heavenly Emperor is alive, that means I haven't avenged Kui'er.
We have no way to absorb impurity.
Conquering the Void Army is the only way if we wish to attack the Heavenly Realm.
All of you, listen up.
I've slain the Void Tyrant.
I have the Xingtian Void Token now.
[Xingtian Void Token]
- As long as you all are willing to side with me and attack the Heavenly Realm,
- Royal Father!
I will let bygones be bygones.
What's going on?
I have no idea.
How could the Void yield to the heretic of Dongqiu?
I will never bow to you even at the expense of my life!
Chief Wizard!
All of you, listen up.
The Void Realm always bows to the strongest being of the realm.
Since Yetan has slain the Void Tyrant, naturally, she's the next leader of the Void.
Stop your meaningless struggle and you'll get to live.
Shut up!
She slew my father!
She's my sworn enemy!
I will never bow to her!
Wu Dai!
Yetan, he looked after Kui'er when she was living here.
Spare him.
Jia Louluo, the Snake Saintess, and the Void Patrol Battalion will join you, Princess Yetan.
Your Highness, please let the First Prince off.
- Please let the First Prince off!
Please let the First Prince off!
Do not kneel!
All of you better stand up!
Do not kneel! Stand up!
The Void Army is mine now.
I'll spare you on account of your feelings for my sister.
Take him to the Cave of Haunted Souls so that he won't stir up any trouble.
First Prince, sorry for this.
Don't touch me!
Sister said she saw the herbs you grew for her.
Kui'er?
I swapped your carriage.
I'm your sworn enemy.
Although you'd deceived me for a long time, I never felt that your feelings for me were fake.
It's been waiting for its owner for many years.
Princess, you're its owner.
In the future, I won't go anywhere else. I will just stay by your side.
No matter if it's crushing herbs or serving tea, I'll follow your every order.
As long as I can marry you, I'm not afraid of anything.
I want to be with you, no matter in life or death.
I think she'll be the happiest if she stays with you.
Kui'er.
I once promised her that I would give her a stable and blissful future.
But in the end, I still failed.
Kui'er, our happiest days weren't the days we spent in White Bamboo Valley
or the Beast Realm.
Instead, it was the time when we tried everything we could to escape from the Void.
Kui'er,
we're home now.
From now on, no one will harm you.
Princess Yetan, Kui'er's flower spirit has a special meaning to you,
yet you're willing to hand it to Feng'er.
Words cannot express my gratitude.
Consort Xue, don't mention it.
Although the Void Tyrant had mistreated you guys for many years, you guys were a family after all.
Now that he's gone, I'm sure you're more heartbroken than I am.
Your Majesty, according to sources from the Mortal Realm,
Liguang Yetan has slain the Void Tyrant and conquered the Void.
What?
That's impossible.
Now, Liguang Yetan is a mere mortal.
How could that be?
Could it be that her twin flower spirit is still intact?
You spared Yetan from death due to your kindness.
Now, she has turned into a formidable foe.
Since it has come to this,
we must get rid of her before she establishes her foothold.
Yetan is no longer the same person she was.
The Heavenly Army might not win without the help of the reverend masters.
Why don't we send the three masters after her?
Send Youqin there.
However, Empyrean Xuanshang and Yetan are...
Youqin has been planted with the Stake of Oblivion.
His ridiculous memories with Yetan had been wiped away.
Now, he has a pure heart.
He's a sharp sword that can pierce through darkness and evil.
If Yetan does possess the twin flower spirit, once the Heavenly Army goes after her,
she might break the seal of Guixu out of desperation.
Everything will only be fine when we send Youqin after her.
Your Majesty is wise.
Summon Youqin.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Wait.
I will see him in Penglai Hall personally.
Does Luowei Grotto have this many lotus plants in the first place?
These were sent here by our tribe members.
When they heard that the Third Prince brought Princess Qingkui's flower spirit back to the realm,
they sent these flowers here to mourn her.
So, they still remember Qingkui?
Princess Qingkui opened the Crown Princess's Clinic despite all odds and saved countless of our tribe members.
The voidwalkers will never forget her kindness.
Back then, Kui'er was the one
who treated my facial scar.
Sister was a kind medical practitioner.
How could I speak to her like that?
Actually...
Actually, ever since Princess Qingkui
was sent to the Void by accident, she had been talking about you.
She said your ambition was to achieve great things in the Void.
You wanted everyone to refer to you as the Devil of the Void.
She opened the Crown Princess's Clinic to fulfill your dream for you.
Where's the Crown Princess's Clinic?
It's at the west of Luowei Grotto.
It's at Zhuoxin Hall.
Let me bring you there.
It's okay.
I wish to check it out myself.
Greetings, Celestial Father.
We are father and son. There's no need for such strict customs.
Spare the formalities.
There's a difference between our ranks.
Father, if you have any orders for me, you could've asked the immortal attendant to summon me.
There's no need for you to come personally.
I came here today as I need to discuss the fate of the world with you.
Guangtian found out that the Void had been conquered by the demoness of Dongqiu.
That demoness is the human form of Ganoderma Vein's twin flower spirit.
She intends to disrupt the four realms.
After careful consideration,
sending the Heavenly Army to hunt her down is the only way we can maintain peace within the four realms.
Celestial Father, may I know her name?
Liguang Yetan.
Tan'er.
Did you pour my medicine away again?
All medicine is bitter.
Be a good girl.
Finish it.
You get into fights all day long.
You don't behave like a lady at all.
You should keep your Beauty's Dagger away.
I know.
You always wanted to be strong and unrestrained.
That's why I made this portrait for you.
I hope you can become the Devil of Void.
Do you like it?
I like it.
I like it very much.
Tan'er, may you get what you wish for.
May you lead a carefree and happy life.
Sister.
I...
I've already become the Devil of Void.
But I'm not happy at all.
Sister. Sister!
Sister!
I miss you!
Qingkui! Come back!
Come back! Come back!
Sister!
For the past few days, Your Majesty has shown more concern for the Empyrean.
I'm sure the Empyrean is delighted.
Many things had happened to Youqin lately.
Although I bore witness to them, I couldn't do anything about them.
I could only spend my effort preparing better food for him.
Thank you for harvesting the Honey Fruit for me.
Your Majesty, you're most welcome.
[Penglai Hall]
General Guangtian?
What is he doing here again?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
His Majesty is discussing important matters with the Empyrean inside.
Your Majesty, please wait outside.
What important matters?
Your Majesty!
Such audacity! How dare you stand in my way?
Since the demoness is a threat to the four realms, I'm willing to share your burden and lead our army.
Youqin, although you possess the Perfect Celestial Body, do not underestimate Liguang Yetan.
You must practice caution.
Celestial Father, for your sake, and for the four realms' sake, such danger means nothing to me.
I will gather our troops and hunt down the demoness.
- My dear?
- Greetings, Celestial Mother.
I've failed my duty.
Youqin.
What did you say just now?
Who were you going to kill?
I've taken on the task to hunt down the demoness of Dongqiu, Liguang Yetan.
You cannot!
My lifelong ambition is to protect all living beings.
Celestial Mother, why are you stopping me?
Youqin, listen to me.
Celestial Mother, I will listen to you after I slay the demoness.
Youqin!
You used Tan'er's life to threaten us so that we wouldn't mention the past to Youqin.
But now, you want Youqin to kill Tan'er?
Not only did you go back on your word, but you also used your son as a tool.
How heartless you are!
I did it for his sake.
Once he kills Yetan, no one will criticize him.
By then, he can retain his position in Penglai Hall and be a good empyrean.
You did everything to consolidate your own throne.
In your eyes, Youqin is just a pawn.
You want him to sever his feelings and be cold-blooded
all because you're trying to groom a puppet that's willing to die for you!
Stop it.
I wouldn't have been kept in the dark for so long if you didn't protect Yetan from the beginning.
Also, don't think that I have no idea.
Back then, when Youqin and Yetan got married in the Beast Realm,
you even granted them the rainbow blessing of the Xia clan.
Soft-hearted women like you can never achieve anything.
I never wanted to be the Heavenly Empress!
I only wanted to be a mother to my children!
You're the heavenly ruler and possess absolute power.
Why can't you tolerate the feelings of the world?
Shaodian Xiaoyi!
From now on,
we cease to be husband and wife.
I would rather return to the Xia clan than stay with you in this uncompassionate place.
I still have official affairs to attend to.
Heavenly Empress, you may do what you deem fit.
Your Majesty.
Well... What should we do?
Hurry and find Qingheng. Ask him to think of something.
Yes, Your Majesty.
You'll win if you throw out Two Dots.
Two Dots?
It's this one.
This one.
I'm sure it's this one.
This one. I'm sure it's this one.
That's Two Dots? What is this then?
Two Characters.
Great.
Forget it. I quit.
Come on. You're an utter fool.
I've been teaching you the entire day, yet you still can't recognize the tiles.
I'm foolish. Let's play another round.
The three of us aren't fools, you know?
You two had joined us for several days.
I'm sure you guys have a favor to ask.
Speak up. Hurry up.
I'm getting sleepy.
Masters, please practice your wise judgment.
Although the flower spirit of Dongqiu has been destroyed, the feud still remains.
People are still suffering over this.
Masters, I know you three are compassionate and kind.
That's why you guys kept the Soul-Gathering Lamp for 10,000 years.
You wish to retrieve the lamp and help Suzhi to revive her tribe members, right?
We knew that.
But your father took the lamp away long ago.
It's no longer in the Land of Nature.
Celestial Father?
If so, I'll steal it from Celestial Father.
Qingheng, do not act recklessly.
It's impossible to steal the lamp from Father.
Immortal Qingheng!
Hurry!
Immortal Qingheng, the Empyrean and General Guangtian gathered the Heavenly Army
and went to the Void to hunt down Princess Yetan.
What?
My sister-in-law is in the Void?
Qingheng, what should we do?
Celestial Father still isn't willing to let the people of Dongqiu off.
We can't just let eldest brother kill our sister-in-law.
Let's go.
Your Highness, you're exhausted.
Why are you visiting the Empress's quarters?
We should return to Fenyuan Hall.
No need for that.
This is Yingzhao's ornate mirror.
I once desired to conquer the Void and be a devil that is feared by everyone.
But now, although I've realized my ambition, I've lost all of my loved ones.
My sister died to save me.
Youqin was captured by the Heavenly Emperor.
Now, I can only quench my longing by staring into the mirror.
Your Highness, I understand your pain.
However, the Heavenly Emperor won't kill the Empyrean.
Once we wipe out the Heavenly Realm, I'm sure Your Highness can reunite with the Empyrean.
Your Highness, please do not indulge yourself in this illusion and forget about our goal.
I know this is an arduous journey.
Since we've already taken the first step, there's no turning back.
Your Highness, to you, this may only be the first step.
However, I've waited for this for 10,000 years.
For the past 10,000 years, I'd always been thinking about why the spirit of the sacred tree
didn't appear and save our tribe from the massacre.
But now, my call is finally answered.
Your Highness, I'm begging you. Please do not just dwell on your loss.
You must wield the Beauty's Dagger and uphold justice for our tribe members, who died a wrongful death.
You said before that the Soul-Gathering Lamp was created by the branches
of the Ganoderma Vein and that it could last forever.
Since the flower spirits of our tribe members were already injected into the lamp, I'm sure it still exists.
Don't worry.
I'll definitely retrieve the lamp, revive the dead, and help you reunite with your parents.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Your Highness, we received a report from the Void Patrol Battalion.
Empyrean Xuanshang has entered the Void.
Youqin is here? Where is he?
He's at the Passage of Twilight. But...
Youqin is here to look for me. I knew he wouldn't be bound by the Heavenly Emperor.
He's here for me.
Youqin!
So, you're Liguang Yetan?
Since the Empyrean is leading the Heavenly Army, I'm sure he's not here to reunite with Your Highness.
The Heavenly Army launched a sudden attack.
Our defending army lost to them and had to retreat.
Seems like Empyrean Xuanshang is here to attack us.
I've been missing you ever since we parted ways at Guixu.
Youqin, do you not remember me?
Empyrean, do not be bewitched by that demoness!
Kill them!
Wait!
I'm here to rid the world of evil.
Since you're facing me alone, I will not pressure you with my army.
What's wrong with you?
Youqin, don't you remember me? I'm Tan'er!
Your Highness, be careful!
This is the star formation most commonly used by the immortals.
Now, I'll teach you how to dispel it.
You must remember it.
You actually dispelled my star formation?
That night, you said you wanted to reward my effort with a beautiful galaxy.
I always remembered this formation, which you taught me.
But I never expected you to be the one to use this star formation on me.
Youqin, since I could make you remember me three times, I'm sure I could do it again.
The Empyrean actually imparted his sword skills to her?
Her Highness is trying to awaken the Empyrean's dormant memories with her sword skills.
However, Her Highness is already a ball of impurity.
She cannot utilize the immortals' sword skills to the fullest.
If this continues, and if Xuanshang still cannot remember her, Her Highness will definitely lose.
Something seems off. Keep an eye on Her Highness.
I'll gather the army.
Who exactly are you?
Youqin, I'm your wife,
your Money, and your Yuexia.
I'm your wife.
Your Highness!
You're the demoness of doom.
But why can't I take your life?
Youqin, do you truly not remember anything?
Empyrean, do not let her mislead you.
Liguang Yetan is unrelated to you.
She's just trying to bewitch you.
I will assist you in dispatching her.
Heavenly generals, set up formation!
Yes, sir!
Qingheng?
- Tan'er, we're here.
- Di Lanjue?
Ziwu? You guys are...
I never expected you guys to go through so much after my royal father kept me detained in the Prince's Mansion.
We rushed all the way here after Qingheng and Ziwu got me out.
Didn't we say that we would be buddies forever?
Set up formation!
- Follow me!
- Stop.
Kill the demoness!
I said, stop!
Empyrean, we mustn't let this opportunity go to waste!
Back down.
Youqin, both Qingheng and Ziwu are here.
They can testify for me.
Sister-in-law, Youqin was injured in Guixu.
He couldn't do anything about it when Father planted the Stake of Oblivion in him.
He...
He already forgot about the past.
Qingheng, Ziwu, why are you guys helping Liguang Yetan
even if it means that you have to go against Celestial Father's will?
What exactly happened between us?
Why can't I remember anything?
Your Highness, the Void Army has arrived.
The Void Army?
I mustn't let Yetan bewitch the Empyrean any longer.
Empyrean, this was supposed to be a sneak attack.
However, Immortal Qingheng and the Prince of the Beast Tribe
turned against us and sided with the demoness instead.
Now that the Void Army is here, the situation is unfavorable for us. Let's retreat.
Qingheng and Ziwu mustn't remain here.
We have no time for them! Empyrean, please focus on the bigger picture!
The Heavenly Emperor will deal with them when we return to the Heavenly Realm.
Retreat.
Youqin!
[Qinzheng Hall]
Your Majesty, you have been weak lately.
You have to follow the imperial physician's instructions and recuperate.
How's Tan'er been doing lately?
Princess Yetan has been staying in Zhaolu Hall for the past few days.
Your Majesty, please don't worry.
It's been some days since I visited Tan'er.
I will head to Zhaolu Hall later.
Your Majesty!
What are you doing?
Don't tell me Tan'er is...
Tell me.
Is Tan'er in Zhaolu Hall now?
Princess Yetan left the palace together with Consort Xue a few days ago!
She said she would head to the Void and avenge Princess Qingkui!
Your Majesty! You had been unwell lately!
I... I dared not tell you the truth!
Your Majesty!
In the end, Tan'er still went to the Void.
I will bring her back now.
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
[Fenyuan Hall]
Suzhi, give my sister-in-law some time alone.
After the Empyrean left, Her Highness locked herself away in Fenyuan Hall.
I'm worried about her.
Suzhi,
don't worry.
Sister-in-law always had a tough personality.
She should be fine.
After Qingkui's passing, Shaodian Youqin became the person she cares about the most.
All this while, she slew the Void Tyrant and conquered the Void.
She may look determined, but in reality, her heart was already riddled with holes.
Just when she thought that her husband could return to her side, it turned out to be...
I'm here to rid the world of evil.
Since you're facing me alone,
I will not pressure you with my army.
What's wrong with you?
Youqin, don't you remember me? I'm Tan'er!
In the end, you were still planted with the Stake of Oblivion.
Even if you forgot about your soul shards,
Tianpa Hall, and everything that had happened,
you still couldn't bear to strike me down.
You still have feelings for me,
right?
But...
how can I save you from the Heavenly Emperor's clutch?
Emperor Tun?
Emperor Tun.
Where's Tan'er? How has she been doing?
Great timing.
Tan Tan is fine.
However, many things had happened lately.
Tan Tan, she...
Tan Tan slew the Void Tyrant.
And Shaodian Youqin forgot about her completely.
After that, she locked herself away in her room.
We're here to visit her.
But we dare not bother her.
What about you...
Tan'er?
Imperial Father.
Tan'er.
It's all my fault.
I had to bear witness as they harm you and Kui'er.
Even so, I couldn't even uphold justice for you two.
You had to toughen yourself up and go against them.
Imperial Father, you've always been acting for my and Qingkui's sake.
On my way here, I was utterly flustered.
I was afraid that you might act recklessly and end up being captured by the Void Tyrant due to your anger.
But I never expected you to be the leader of the Void Realm. And you even met the Empyrean...
Imperial Father, you came here to persuade me not to avenge Qingkui, right?
I wish to return to the palace and keep you company too, Imperial Father.
But look at the current situation...
I've behaved like a coward all my life.
I have to suck up to all those immortals and deities.
In the end, the Heavenly Emperor still played me like a fiddle.
I wish to kill the Heavenly Emperor and avenge Kui'er too.
But I can never achieve that.
Tan'er, you and the Heavenly Emperor are mutually antagonistic now.
If I persuade you to let go of the hatred in your heart,
that means I allow them to bully you again.
Imperial Father, thank you for understanding.
The Heavenly Emperor is known throughout the four seas for his benevolence.
However, he's 100 times more ruthless than the Void Tyrant.
I have no powers.
I cannot help you out.
The only thing I can do is ensure my safety so that you won't need to worry about me.
Tan'er, no matter in life or death,
I will stand by you and stay by your side.
Luckily, our sister-in-law still has Emperor Tun with her.
That's right.
Initially, I thought Emperor Tun was the most detestable father in all of the four realms.
But now, he's actually Tan'er's last backing.
Right now, the most detestable father in all of the four realms is the Heavenly...
The Heavenly Emperor.
He said it, not me.
The Heavenly Emperor has committed plenty of atrocious deeds.
There's no need to deny the truth.
It's been some days since we met, and you've grown quite a lot, huh?
You're better than your eldest brother when it comes to differentiating right from wrong.
Naturally, Youqin is 100 times better than me.
It's just that...
It's just that he keeps losing his memories.
The Empyrean?
The strongest being of the four realms?
He always forgets things during crucial moments.
Could it be that he severed some other nerves... when he severed his desires?
Stop your nonsense!
Fine, fine. I'll stop.
Don't be angry.
Fate sure is unpredictable.
If only Tan'er wasn't a descendant of Dongqiu.
Suzhi. Suzhi!
I know.
You're joining my sister-in-law on her quest for vengeance not just for Princess Qingkui's sake.
You're doing it for your sake too.
10,000 years ago, the immortals massacred Dongqiu and caused you to be separated from your parents.
Actually, ever since I found out that you were a descendant of Dongqiu,
I wanted to apologize to you on the immortals' behalf.
I...
It happened 10,000 years ago.
I know it has nothing to do with you.
You don't need to blame yourself for it.
Since my sister-in-law has the flower spirit power, she will definitely have a showdown with my father.
However, you're barely alive.
There's no need for you to get involved in this struggle.
Thank you for always being concerned about me.
However, reviving my tribe members was the only thing that kept me going for the last 10,000 years.
I can help you steal the Soul-Gathering Lamp and revive your tribe members.
I'm already grateful enough that you risked your life to save us.
You've already done enough for me.
Don't say that.
Actually...
- Actually, I...
- Immortal Qingheng,
I know what you're trying to say.
Thank you.
Qingheng, you're the best immortal I have ever met.
But I'm sorry.
No matter what, I won't get myself entangled with worldly feelings like Yetan.
Qingheng and Ziwu actually held a candle to the devil and went down to assist Yetan without permission, huh?
Nothing's worse than a familiar enemy.
Father, although Qingheng and Ziwu are mischievous, they can still tell good from evil.
Before this, when I exchanged blows with Liguang Yetan, I realized that she could utilize immortal skills.
This might be bold of me to ask so, but, Celestial Father, who exactly is Liguang Yetan?
Liguang Yetan is a member of the crazed Dongqiu Tribe.
She's the human form of the Ganoderma Vein's flower spirit.
She has no connection with the immortals.
Youqin, you've received immortal teachings for millenniums.
You have the responsibility to protect all living beings.
Facing a devil like her, you should've shown her no mercy.
Do not let her bewitching words fool you into questioning your beliefs.
Yes, Celestial Father.
It's a shame that you didn't manage to slay her in the Void Realm.
You must be exhausted. Go and rest.
I still need you to protect our realm.
Yes, Celestial Father.
I shall take my leave.
"Flawless World" - Sa Dingding
♫ You say, "Light swept through the twin flowers" ♫
♫ Wandering at the desolate cliff ♫
♫ Whose face has the wind comfort again? ♫
♫ When the seabed sand are flying everywhere ♫
♫ If only I can spend the sorrowful night with you ♫
♫ We'll go through the ups and downs together ♫
♫ Hair being messed up by the misplaced time and space ♫
♫ No matter how tough it is, I'm not afraid ♫
♫ You are the crescent in my heart ♫
♫ My radiant light shining through the years ♫
♫ If I do shed tears, they will turn into flowers in my heart ♫
♫ I'll always be the unchanging love in your heart ♫
♫ Even the galaxy will agree with me, love needs no answer ♫
♫ I'll shine for you ♫
♫ In this flawless world ♫
♫ I'll always be the unchanging love in your heart ♫