"Vow to You" - Liu Yuning
♫ The flames illuminate the dark night ♫
♫ Silences surrounds the world ♫
♫ The starlight fades away ♫
♫ The living stands in fear ♫
♫ Wake me up from this nightmare ♫
♫ I see through your blushing ♫
♫ The thought of you in this world urges me to make a decision ♫
♫ Entrusted to me the gale and flame ♫
♫ This farewell leaves me in pain ♫
♫ I am fearless when I take a drive into the abyss for you ♫
♫ I'll defend death to be with you ♫
♫ Heaven and Earth resonates with the mountains and rivers ♫
♫ The world is untamed and unbridled ♫
♫ Come what may ♫
♫ I am willing to risk my life for you ♫
♫ Let's go stargazing tomorrow ♫
♫ I'll never regret my lifelong vow to you ♫
[The Starry Love]
[Adapted from "The Starry Love" by Yi Du Jun Hua]
[Episode 28]
I wonder if Her Highness's plan is working.
Why is there no news yet?
This won't do. I need to enter the Void.
Wait, Consort Xue. You're the person Sir cherishes the most.
Before Her Highness left, she instructed me to ensure your safety.
If anything happens to you, I'll blame myself forever.
If Feng’er and Kui’er can't overcome this ordeal, there's no point in living alone.
Consort Xue is right. No matter if they're dead or alive, we have to check them out.
All right then. We'll see how it goes after we go inside.
Let's go.
First Prince, His Majesty said he wasn't going to see anyone.
It's useless to keep kneeling here.
Do you want me to let Tan Tan die together with Chaofeng for no reason?
Royal Father! Royal Father, I'm begging you!
[Fenyuan Hall]
Royal Father! Royal Father!
I'm begging you!
Royal Father. Royal Father!
Royal Father, please let Tan Tan off!
Please let her off!
Father! Please let her off! Royal Father!
- Your Majesty
Did you really hurt Chaofeng?
So what if I did? Could it be that you have love for Chaofeng?
Don't forget, he's the descendant of the the Fuzhu clan.
However, you are hesitating to execute him.
Seems like you were bewitched by Yetan's words!
Fine.
Since you can't make up your mind, I'll head there and deal with this rebellious son of yours!
Come back!
Let me think about it.
Royal Father!
- Stand down!
- Please let them off!
Royal Father!
Royal Father, please let them off!
Consort Xue?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Good.
All of you are here to die, huh? I'll kill all of you at once!
Yingzhao!
After going through the massacre of Fuzhu clan and years of torture under your hand,
do you think I'll still be afraid of death?
Maybe I shouldn't be soft-hearted and allowed you to live in the first place.
You weren't soft-hearted.
You were just afraid.
Back then, the clans of Void Realm were having an internal struggle.
There were feuds between clans.
You used your power to frighten the other clans and united the Void Realm.
That's how the Void, which represents the rival faction of the Heavenly Realm, came into existence.
However, you were afraid.
You were afraid that the rebel army might stage an uprising.
You're afraid a slave like me will bear a grudge toward you.
Therefore, you could only let your three sons fight for the throne.
You'll choose the strongest heir to inherit your throne.
If not, the Void Realm will be divided after my retirement.
That's the only thing I can do.
The slaves and rebel army have already put down our grudges.
We stopped trying to seek revenge.
It's not because of your power.
It's because your existence had stopped the internal struggle between the clans.
We can lead a stable life now.
To conquer the world, one may use his army.
However, to conquer the people's hearts, one may not use his army.
Just let down your guard.
No one can rule over the realm peacefully on a throne tainted with blood.
The three of you, listen up.
The one who gets rid of Shaodian Youqin will be the next Void Crown Prince.
You're full of lies!
If you don't intend to seek revenge, why did you encourage Chaofeng to fight for the throne?
I'll kill you right now!
Your Majesty!
Qingxin has stayed out of worldly affairs for many years. She has no intention of stealing the throne.
After listening to what she has to say, I've finally sorted out my thoughts.
To conquer the world, one may use his army.
However, to conquer the people's hearts, one may not use his army.
It's my fault that Yun’er is dead.
Even if we kill Chaofeng, we cannot bring Yun’er back to life.
I've already lost one son.
Why don't we put down our grudges and co-exist peacefully?
Put down our grudges, huh?
Co-exist peacefully?
Yanfang,
in the end, I was still wrong about you!
Your Majesty, I express my gratitude to you on Feng'er’s behalf.
How did it go?
His Majesty has spared Feng.
Let's head to the Cave of Haunted Souls and release him.
Really?
Come on!
- All right!
- Go now!
This is great!
Under His Majesty's order, Third Prince, Chaofeng, is acquitted of his crime!
Sir, Your Highness, His Majesty has spared you two.
[Crown Princess's Clinic]
Saintess?
Tan’er, you guys are finally back.
I've been waiting for your news for the past few days.
Luckily, His Majesty spared you guys.
Why are there weapons of the immortals inside this hall?
First Prince told me to build this hall.
After you guys left, he went to the border area to fight with the immortals.
Whenever he killed one of them, he would erect their weapon here.
He said he wanted to prove to you that he was stronger than Third Prince.
There are so many weapons here. Don't tell me he picked them up from the battlefield?
Nonsense.
First Prince is the mighty Devil of Void. Why would he commit such folly?
I was referring to First Prince, too.
Why are you panicking?
I... Who's panicking?
Enough.
No matter what, all's well that ends well.
Feng’er and Princess Yetan just got married.
Tonight, we must hold a celebration.
Feng’er, Haichao, arrange for a banquet immediately.
- Yes, Consort Mother.
- All right. Go now.
Sushui, why are you still standing there?
We'll head in and take a break.
Consort Mother, take care.
Let's go.
- We need to get busy later.
- Yes, Consort Xue.
We have to decorate the entire place, you hear me?
- Yes.
- And, listen.
First Prince
is strong, meticulous, and loyal.
No wonder you fancy him.
How did you know?
You showed us a sorrowful expression when you were looking at the weapons.
Why would you do so if you didn't fancy him?
Tell me about it. What happened between you and First Prince?
After you guys left, I came here to take my medicine. But I bumped into him by accident.
What's so good about Chaofeng?
I've lived alone for a millennium. And, I've never fallen for anyone before, except for you.
First Prince. What are you doing here?
I've gathered the most beautiful flowers in the Four Realms.
Initially, I wanted to give Tan Tan a surprise, but...
First Prince, you truly have a deep affection for Tan’er.
Controlling the fire is the key to brewing medicine.
The time and amount of water are also important to the process.
Try it.
It's so bitter.
Here, have a piece of candy.
What do you think? Isn't it sweet?
I've never had anyone care so much about me before.
Is that so?
I heard that several of our brethren refused to marry you because of your hideous looks.
Those scoundrels must be blind. In my opinion, you actually look pretty.
First Prince, are you serious?
Of course. I never lie.
First Prince, thank you for the compliment.
You don't need to thank me.
After you help me court Tan Tan successfully, I'll pick the strongest
and toughest general within the Void Army to be your husband.
In a place where force is pursued, like the Void Realm, everyone is scheming against each other.
I've never seen anyone as pure as him before.
Tan’er, I'm not jealous of you.
I understand your feelings for Third Prince.
However, he's still infatuated with you. I couldn't bear it.
I...
First Prince is a simple and honest man.
He's indeed someone you can entrust your love to.
Let me think of a way.
I'll ensure he understands your feelings for him.
What are you doing?
I’m tidying up.
Ziwu!
Di Lanjue.
Why are you so energetic today? Have you finished your homework?
I didn't touch them at all.
You didn't touch them?
I didn't come to Shangshu Academy to improve my skills.
If so, why did you come here?
- I...
- Anyway, no matter why you're here, when Knowledge Star Deity comes to question you,
I won't let you copy my homework.
Who wants to copy your homework?
Why are you staring at me?
Empyrean Xuanshang is here.
- Empyrean.
Empyrean Xuanshang is concerned about the cultivation of deities.
- What are you doing here?
- Are you happy to see me?
He shall teach us spells personally.
You're messing around, aren't you?
It's excruciating to wait for your class to be over. I have no choice.
I can only come to see you personally.
Geez.
Knowledge Star Deity alone is already demanding enough.
And now, Eldest Brother is here too? Are they trying to kill us here?
I'm afraid we have to sleep at Shangshu Academy this year.
All of you are studious and hardworking. I'm relieved to see that.
However, Knowledge Star Deity and I have come to a conclusion.
In order to reduce your burden, from tomorrow onward,
all lessons shall not have any extra homework.
The lessons shall not be delayed.
The homework you get after the lesson can be finished within an hour.
All of you don't need to pull all-nighters again.
- Long live Youqin!
This is great!
- Let's begin, then.
- Hurry!
- Let's begin.
- Let's go. Have a seat.
What's wrong with them? They weren't this enthusiastic when Knowledge Star Deity was here.
It's like they're on steroids.
They've never attended a lesson taught by an intelligent empyrean like Youqin.
That's why they're excited.
That's fine. Sitting at the back is pretty good too.
We can chat in the back.
Lessons require silence. This is not the place for you to chat.
Ziwu.
What is this?
It's for you.
Look.
[See you at Tianpa Hall after dinner.]
See you at Tianpa Hall after dinner.
All right. That's all for today's lesson.
Class dismissed.
Cousin.
I still can't figure it out. Can you stay and explain it to me?
Cultivation cannot be achieved in one day. You need to take it one step at a time.
I just said that I wanted to reduce your burden.
If I stay here, I'll be going against my word. Class dismissed.
- Farewell, Empyrean.
I'll wait for you.
Come.
Sister-in-law.
- Sister-in-law, see you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow.
I’m leaving now.
Di Lanjue, where have you been living these days?
Don't tell me you travel back and forth between the two realms.
No. Ziwu found me a new place.
So, that's the reason you're here, huh?
Don't tell anyone about it.
- Go now.
- See you.
See you.
I tried my best to reduce your burden for you, yet you're practicing again.
People could tell you did so out of your selfish desire.
You just wanted me to spend more time with you, right?
However, this is my first time attending school officially.
I would like to cherish the opportunity.
Besides, you're the top immortal who had mastered the Perfect Celestial Body.
I have to stand shoulder to shoulder with you in order to be your consort.
I'm just afraid that you'll tire yourself out.
Is there anything here that can boost my power by a tremendous amount after consuming it?
The path of cultivation is tempered by one's will to achieve more.
We shouldn't take shortcuts.
However, I think we do have something called Honey Fruit.
It'll awaken your immortal intelligence after you consume it.
I want to have that then.
You're such a glutton.
Honey Fruit trees only bear fruit once every 3,000 years. It's not that easy for you to have it.
If so, it seems like I can only train by myself.
Fine.
When you practice the techniques, you need to remember the points listed on the scrolls.
If not, you'll get half the result with twice the effort.
Since that's the case, I'll do you a special favor.
I mustn't cross the line.
He doesn't have any Jianmu Fruit with him. I wonder if he can do it.
Spending the night in Tianpa Hall? If news of this gets out, her reputation will be affected.
Why don't you head inside? I'll leave now.
Fine.
Seems like he still needs the help of Jianmu Fruit.
Princess Qingkui, your outfit is here. Please get changed.
Thank you. You can leave it there.
What's on your mind? You're salivating all over your outfit.
I... I just think that this outfit is quite old.
I want to sew some embroideries on it. It'll be as good as new.
Wait, the sun isn't rising from the west, right? You're actually doing needlework now?
What exactly are you up to?
I... I'm just afraid that I'll get bored in the Heavenly Realm.
I want to nurture my hobby.
Coincidentally, I can practice my skills by doing this.
Before this, I had no idea why Qingkui loved this.But now, I think it's pretty fun.
Give them back to me!
I know what you're up to.
You know nothing! Give them to me!
Give them to me.
Give them to me!
I don't understand what you're thinking. How could you ask other people to help you out with this?
You saw through my plan anyway. You should help me out.
Take it.
Hey.
Although it isn't as good as Qingkui's work, at least it's better than mine. I'll take it.
Give it back if you don't want it.
It's excellent.
Say, why isn't Youqin here yet? It's getting dark.
Stop waiting already.
The empyrean needs to head to the Star Observatory and set up thousands of star formations.
You should wash up and go to sleep.
You have a point. Why should I wait for him when I can look for him?
You're a lady! Can you be more reserved for once?
Youqin!
What are you doing here?
You didn't come after so long. I had no choice but to look for you.
You can resume your duty. I'll observe you.
However, I'm already done.
It's over? But I wanted you to teach me.
Our marriage contains hidden dangers after all. Maybe I can teach her the star formation.
That can be of use when she's in danger.
Here, like this.
What are you doing?
You wanted to learn from me, right?
Rise.
♫ I see a light in your starry eyes ♫
♫ The sound of the zither ringing ♫
♫ As I sing softly, you and I look at each other ♫
This is the most common star formation we use in the Heavenly Realm.
Now, I'll teach you how to dispel it. You must memorize it.
You're teaching me something this difficult already?
You did master the Revitalization Spell in one go, didn't you?
I believe that you'll master this as well.
♫ Piece by piece ♫
Come. Look at my hand gesture.
Like this.
Come. Rise.
♫ Gently flickering, illuminating the Queen of the Night blossoms ♫
♫ Protecting our promise regardless of the faults of fate ♫
♫ Gorgeous flowers and fire bloom momentarily ♫
Collect.
♫ It all turned into sweetness ♫
♫ I am you, and you are me ♫
Spin.
Unlock!
♫ As I see the stars fall ♫
♫ It's like the Queen of the Night flowers and fireworks wrapped in countless rainbows ♫
Did you get that?
Yes, I did.
♫ Smiles blooming into happiness that can't be melt away ♫
♫ It was you ♫
♫ Who sweetened my parched heart ♫
This star scenery is a reward for your hardworking spirit.
If so, I'll reward you with a gentler Yetan
for breaking through ordeals fearlessly for me.
Youqin,
- let's never part with each other, okay?
- Okay.
♫ Love and affection accompanies the Queen of the Night blossoms ♫
♫ In full bloom, you and I agreed that eternity is only a flash ♫
♫ The moment the flower and fire blossomed in splendor ♫
♫ It all turned into sweetness ♫
♫ I am you, and you are me ♫
♫ As I see the stars fall ♫
♫ It's like the Queen of the Night flowers and fireworks wrapped in countless rainbows ♫
I don't need a grand wedding. I don't need anything.
I only need your love.
You've already possessed it.
[Jade Pool Pavilion]
♫ The passion, between you and I will never be forgotten ♫
Why is today's celestial phenomenon so abnormal?
♫ Thank you for reciprocating my love ♫
♫ The silhouette of our embrace ♫
♫ The stars in the eyes of my beloved gleams with sweetness ♫
[Jade Pool Pavilion]
Celestial Mother, I gathered and made this pure air tea myself.
Please have a try.
It's rare for you to be this thoughtful.
It's nice, indeed.
Celestial Mother, I came here today because I have a favor to ask of you.
Princess Qingkui has been living in the Heavenly Realm for awhile now.
- Celestial Mother...
- Now that my children have grown up, they have their own thinking now.
On the night we observed the stars, I was intending
to help improve the relationship between you and Qingkui.
However, I never expected it to end up being an ordeal for you two.
I've straightened out my thoughts after that harrowing encounter.
Nothing is as important as your safety.
Don't worry about the wedding.
I will never urge you guys to get married.
No, no, no. Celestial Mother. I think you should urge us.
I won't urge you two.
You should.
I said...
What did you just say? Say it again.
Celestial Mother, I'm afraid we're in a hurry to get married.
Is it something urgent?
Very.
Don't tell me the celestial phenomenon last night was...
Hurry! I need to head to Ninth Heaven Hall!
Your Majesty, you haven't finished your tea yet.
What tea? Didn't you hear him? This is urgent!
These are all the scrolls I've studied.
I've included some notes, too.
Since I couldn't help you to get into Shangshu Academy,
I could only prepare these for your self-study session.
Immortal Qingheng, I do not deserve your kindness.
Thank you, Immortal Qingheng.
Don't mention it.
Immortal Qingheng, you should rest early.
I will study hard right now.
Why are you always avoiding me?
Are you afraid of me?
No.
I'm just a lowly fairy.
Immortal Qingheng, I do not deserve such concern from you.
I live in fear every day.
Immortal Qingheng, you should send me back to Tianpa Hall.
A few days ago, I inquired about you from the Five Spice clan.
The place where you became a fairy was the place I met the stalk of coriander in the Source Mirror.
You were that coriander I met before.
Why didn't you admit it?
You even tried to avoid me.
I don't remember it.
I've remembered you even though it has been so many years.
Why...
Why aren't you willing to admit it?
Immortal Qingheng, you kept wanting me to admit that I was the stalk of coriander you took care of.
What are you trying to get here?
- I...
- Qingheng,
I brought your notes.
Qingheng, don't tell me you transferred Husui to your place because you wanted to court her.
Be honest with me.
Do you have feelings for her?
- I...
- If not,
why would you treat her so well and do everything in your power to make her stay by your side?
I do like Husui. But will she like me?
When we were in the Mortal Realm, Sister-in-law braved everything for the sake of love.
Now that I've fallen for her, I should at least tell her how I feel.
Why am I still hesitating?
Husui, although I'm the second heavenly prince,
my feelings for you have no ties with my title.
Believe me. I'm willing to spend my life protecting you
and loving you.
Where is she going?
Why isn't she taking the main entrance?
[Land of Nature]
Immortal Qingheng?
You would've lost your life to this magic array if I was one step later.
Did you come to the Land of Nature at this hour and activated
the magic array the Jade Deity had cast to obtain this magic item?
Judging from its design, it's a magic item from Dongqiu.
Why are you trying to acquire a magic item that's from Dongqiu?
I...
I thought you said we would have enough members today.
In the end, we still lack one.
You lied to me.
Wait. Why is the door open?
Something's off.
And this.
We have intruders!
Immortal Qingheng?
Greetings, Masters.
Immortal Qingheng, may I know why you barged into the Land of Nature at this hour?
My magic item, Jinghong, was broken when I was searching for Eldest Brother's soul shards in the Mortal Realm.
Lately, I've been attending lessons about magic items and learned something new.
I was intending to repair my magic item using some heavenly tools and ingredients.
Master, when I came here to see you, the gate was ajar, and no one was guarding here.
I didn't know where you went.
So, may I know why the three of you are here at this hour?
- I...
- Just now, I think I heard something about a sparrow.
Sparrow?
I did keep a sparrow in the past.
However, it had already flown away together with my youth.
Rain Deity, have you kept a sparrow before?
I don't think so.
What I said just now was... You were busy.
That's right.
There have been too many blessing requests lately.
I asked both of them to help me out.
We just finished our tasks. That's why we only came back now.
- Thunder Deity, am I right?
- That's right.
Since the three of you have public duties to perform, I shall not interrupt you all.
Master, thank you for the item.
Don't mention it.
Once I've done the inventory check, I will send you the list of items I need.
No problem.
Let's go.
You can tell me now.
If you insist on keeping it from me, I have no choice but to ask the Jade Deity.
Don't!
That magic item does come from Dongqiu.
It's the Soul-Gathering Lamp, which I mentioned before.
It contains the souls of my dead tribesmen.
Tribesmen?
I'm from Dongqiu.
Everyone knows that the Dongqiu people used the sacred tree of Dongqiu, Ganoderma Vein,
in an attempt to open a path to Guixu.
That's why they were vanquished by the Four Realms.
- How could you...
- Even so, do you think it's entirely correct?
- We were framed.
- Framed?
My tribesmen and the sacred tree never intended to destroy the world.
We were massacred because the Four Realms feared us due to the ancient legend.
I would've never survived if I didn't keep the only surviving fraction of my soul
in that stalk of coriander.
This is impossible.
That's not what the late emperor said.
The Heavenly Realm will never reveal the truth to the world.
However, I witnessed the massacre personally.
The immortals were the ones who took the Soul-Gathering Lamp away.
If so... If so, did you come to the Heavenly Realm
so that you could revive the souls that were trapped within the lamp?
I intended to do so.
But I was powerless.
It was hard for me to locate the Soul-Gathering Lamp.
But I was too powerless to do anything about it.
I only gathered my courage and snuck in when I heard
that the three masters were gathering today.
I knew I had no power to erect a shelter for the people of Dongqiu.
However, I still can't help myself from bringing the lamp with me.
Now that you know everything,
you can report me to the authorities.
I won't do so.
But why?
I...
I trust you.
Maybe I can try to persuade my father and tell him to investigate the truth behind the incident.
By then, we might be able to return the remnant of Dongqiu to you.
The case of Dongqiu has already come to a close.
There's no way to overturn the result.
The day you mention the incident in Dongqiu to the Heavenly Emperor
will be the day of my death.
No matter what,
Immortal Qingheng, I would like to thank you.
"Flawless World" - Sa Dingding
♫ You say, "Light swept through the twin flowers" ♫
♫ Wandering at the desolate cliff ♫
♫ Whose face has the wind comfort again? ♫
♫ When the seabed sands are flying everywhere ♫
♫ If only I can spend the sorrowful night with you ♫
♫ We'll go through the ups and downs together ♫
♫ Hair being messed up by the misplaced time and space ♫
♫ No matter how tough it is, I'm not afraid ♫
♫ You are the crescent in my heart ♫
♫ My radiant light shining through the years ♫
♫ If I do shed tears, they will turn into flowers in my heart ♫
♫ I'll always be the unchanging love in your heart ♫
♫ Even the galaxy will agree with me, love needs no answer ♫
♫ I'll shine for you ♫
♫ In this flawless world ♫
♫ I'll always be the unchanging love in your heart ♫