"Vow to You" - Liu Yuning
♫ The flames illuminate the dark night ♫
♫ Silences surrounds the world ♫
♫ The starlight fades away ♫
♫ The living stands in fear ♫
♫ Wake me up from this nightmare ♫
♫ I see through your blushing ♫
♫ The thought of you in this world urges me to make a decision ♫
♫ Entrusted to me the gale and flame ♫
♫ This farewell leaves me in pain ♫
♫ I am fearless when I take a drive into the abyss for you ♫
♫ I'll defend death to be with you ♫
♫ Heaven and Earth resonates with the mountains and the rivers ♫
♫ The world is untamed and unbridled ♫
♫ Come what may ♫
♫ I am willing to risk my life for you ♫
♫ Let's go stargazing tomorrow ♫
♫ I'll never regret my lifelong vow to you ♫
[The Starry Love]
[Adapted from "The Starry Love" by Yi Du Jun Hua]
[Episode 22]
If that's the case, why did you need to battle the Void Empress for my sake?
For your sake?
I came to Assassin Assembly Hall just to kill the second soul shard.
She has never been this heartbroken before.
It's all your fault! I'm going to take your life!
Stop!
He was the one who caused you to nearly lose your life in the Void Realm!
- I will never forgive him!
- Tan'er!
So, everything in the past was just a lie.
Thank you for making things clear.
If that's the case,
we shall never see each other again.
♫ I'll always be the unchanging love in your heart ♫
♫ Even the galaxy will agree with me, love needs no answer ♫
♫ I'll shine for you ♫
♫ In this flawless world ♫
Right now, my powers have been sealed. And I'm trapped in a dangerous situation.
I can only protect you by making you give up on me entirely.
♫ In this flawless world ♫
Romantic Heroic Chronicles, Volume Two. Please read it.
[Romantic Heroic Chronicles, Volume Two]
[Hero Heartful wielding his sword under the moonlight, terrifying all beasts and demons.]
- What do you think?
- We're here to protect you, not to inspire you.
Don't include me in your story.
Let's talk this over.
So you've...
come back.
You did do something silly, didn't you?
You still showed him mercy even though he used you like that.
He swapped the carriages. You almost died because of him.
How could you forgive him? What gives you the right to forgive him on my behalf?
Wait. I thought Dingyun was the one who swapped the carriages. Why is it Chaofeng now?
Tan'er, it's not that I forgave him just because I didn't kill him. It's...
What is it then? Old feelings die hard?
Sister Qingkui, don't be upset. She's that kind of person.
I'll talk to her. Wait here, okay?
Your Highness?
- Your Highness.
- What's wrong with her? Man Man?
What's wrong with her? Who offended her again?
It's a long story.
What are you staring at?
Your sister was deceived by Chaofeng.
She got married to the wrong person, and had her feelings cheated.
Do you think she feels great about it?
You only cared about yourself. How could you talk to her like that?
Are you even human?
Sister,
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
I didn't say all those on purpose.
I just can't get over the fact that you let Chaofeng go.
Don't worry. I'll surely uphold justice for you.
If Father can't do anything about the Void Realm, we'll head to the Heavenly Realm then.
I'll come to Thunder Deity.
We'll ask him to kill Chaofeng with thunder strikes.
Tan'er, the empyrean hasn't been revived yet.
You must never mention the wrong instances of marriage.
If the Void Tyrant and Dingyun use it to disturb the peace of the four realms,
the third soul shard will be in danger.
Sister, when will you care for yourself?
Sister, you and Chaofeng...
Sister.
His longing and gentleness for me are fake.
However, as for all those near-death experiences, how could he fake them?
Tan'er, I'm sorry!
I've let you down again.
No, Sister. Not at all.
So, deceiving one's feelings can actually hurt so much.
If the soul shards found out why I was protecting them,
would they also be heartbroken, just like sister?
Sister, don't worry.
I'll surely do my best to revive Shaodian Youqin and end this as soon as possible.
Tell Di Lanjue to take sister to the Prince's Mansion after she wakes up.
Heartless is talkative. Sister has a pure heart.
It'll be troublesome if she found out why we came here.
- When should we depart then?
- Tomorrow.
Qingheng and us will split up and locate the last soul shard as soon as possible.
What should we do about Heartless then?
He just said that he was going to show you the new script.
I'll talk to him later.
I'm sure Money will like this.
Read it for me.
Money, come here. Hurry.
I've already written the love story between Heartless and Money.
- You made up a story already?
- It's not made up.
I just wrote down what happened between us. That's the best story.
You know what? I've already read this story to the troupe leader of the shadow play troupe.
He praised it non-stop after listening to my story.
He's also willing to spend a huge sum to buy the story.
After we get rich, we'll write new stories.
- One will come after the other.
- Heartless.
I need to be away for a moment due to certain issues.
I'm afraid I cannot create new stories together with you.
H-How long will you be away?
Maybe for a short time. Maybe for a long time.
Don't be sad. I'll come back once I'm done.
Here.
Although I don't know the details, I know you will never let me down.
This is how much I've earned from writing scripts.
We can be thrifty at home, but you need money for your trip.
You can take them.
Do you truly believe me?
Of course. Don't worry.
After you leave, I'll stay here to write scripts.
The previous wedding had made you upset, right? I promise you this.
When you come back, I'll definitely hold a sincere wedding for you.
What do you think?
Come.
Promise me. Return soon.
He still has a fever.
Sir. Sir.
Be careful. Be careful.
You... What's wrong?
Why are you resting outside Tan'er's room when you're injured?
Actually, that princess wasn't Yetan.
It was Qingkui.
This...
Due to my selfish desires, I swapped their carriages.
That's how everything happened.
You!
It's no wonder I thought she looked elegant and was different from what I'd heard.
Great.
Now, I can't even kill a soul shard, not to mention going against Yingzhao.
If Kui'er follows me, she'll only be implicated.
She won't need to endure all of this once Shaodian Youqin is revived.
I'm afraid they won't be able to revive Shaodian Youqin.
The Void Empress and Dingyun had recruited every man they could find to search the Beast Realm for the soul shard.
I'm afraid Her Highness, Di Lanjue, and the rest won't be able to stop them.
Aren't you eating?
Of course, I'm eating.
I'm a human.
I don't have powers like you all.
I'm starving to death.
But I don't feel like walking at all.
You, go and buy some food for me.
For two or three?
Of course, it's for three.
There's Qingheng as well.
Wait.
Where's Qingheng?
Didn't he say he would regroup with us after searching the eastern city?
You're right. Logically speaking, he should've returned by now.
Don't tell me that fool got lost.
Mister, pick one.
Ladies, a new batch of calligraphy and paintings will arrive soon.
You can come and choose them by then.
Sure. I'll come back next time.
[House of Colors]
All right.
I'll see you guys off.
Okay.
Miss, your painting.
Okay. Thank you.
Take care.
Sir!
Waiter, get me a bowl of noodles.
All right, sir. Please wait a moment.
This place is known as the House of Colors.
It isn't an ordinary restaurant.
Usually, we sell more than just food.
We also sell calligraphy and paintings.
Literati also hold their gatherings here.
You can take a look at them if you're interested.
Please take a look.
Wait, isn't that lady holding the Silver Moon Cypress Branch, a magic item from the Heavenly Realm?
This back also resembles Sister-in-law greatly.
Who created this painting?
This painting was created by my young master.
Sir, do you intend to buy it?
I'll take it. Besides that, I need you to do me another favor.
I thought you said you ran out of energy.
Why are you trying to find Qingheng?
He hasn't returned even though time's up.
Maybe the voidwalkers are targeting him.
- Sister-in-law!
- I'm worried about him.
- He's fine.
- Sister-in-law!
- You're back?
We were so worried about you.
So you actually came back late just to buy this painting?
Sister-in-law, calm down.
Look at this.
That back resembles you greatly!
And the cypress stick.
Wasn't this the one you gave to the empyrean after that night?
Where did you find this painting?
Who drew it? And where is he?
Sister-in-law, calm down.
The one who drew this painting is called Wen Ren.
He's a painter.
He owns the House of Colors, where he sells calligraphy and paintings.
However, he wasn't in the shop today.
According to the waiter, he'll head to Mount Linglong tomorrow to draw paintings.
Okay.
Only a few people knew about the story of the cypress stick.
Could he be the third soul shard?
Rest early.
We'll head to Mount Linglong first thing in the morning tomorrow.
We mustn't miss out on him.
That's him!
We found the third soul shard!
My Iridescent Eyes can finally be removed soon!
Hurry. Tell them to ready themselves.
I never expected the third soul shard to be a gentleman.
Qingkui, you should go and meet him.
Look at him.
He's great at drawing, and he's good-looking too.
I assume he cares a lot about a woman's appearance.
You see, my face is injured.
Why don't I doll myself up and meet him after my injury has recovered?
Sister-in-law...
Miss, you...
Mister, you look graceful.
I couldn't help but notice you.
Sorry for the interruption.
This is our first encounter.
I mustn't scare him away because of my face injury.
Miss.
Don't move.
All done.
Look.
From now on, miss, you don't need to hide away.
Both Fiery and Heartless were hard to approach in the beginning.
However, the last soul shard is so gentle and considerate.
Mister, why are you staring at me?
Sorry about that.
I thought...
Forget it.
If I tell you about it, you may think that I'm an impetuous person.
Mister, why don't you tell me about it?
All this while, I was plagued by a dream.
In my dream, there was a lady whom I fell for.
She felt ephemeral to me.
However, I could never reach her.
Miss, when I saw you, I felt like you resembled the lady in my dream greatly.
That's why I couldn't help but stare at you.
So, his dream contains shards of Heartless Shaodian's memories.
It's no wonder he drew that painting.
If I'm truly the lover in his dream, it'll be a piece of cake to win his heart.
Miss, do you not believe me?
I do.
I am Wen Ren.
I established a restaurant called the House of Colors in the Beast Realm.
It's a place for literati to gather.
Miss, may I know your name?
My name is pretty boorish.
Mister, why don't you give me a name?
Miss, you flatter me.
If that's the case,
what do you think about the name Yuexia?
Yuexia?
Precisely.
"Rowing on the West Lake under the moonlight,
getting drunk restlessly among the sea of flowers."
Since ancient times, many poems were born due to one's appreciation for the moon.
And I draw inspiration from the moon for most of my paintings.
So, Heartless Shaodian has an artistic side to him too.
That name sounds great. You can call me that then.
All right.
Miss Yuexia, are you willing to admire the moon together with me tonight?
[House of Colors]
Yuexia, I'm done.
You're done?
Take a look.
I never knew Heartless Shaodian could draw so well.
It looks gorgeous.
Aren't you going to recite a poem?
Naturally, I must.
"Staring at the flower tree, a child, sleeping under the moonlight with glee.
As one abandons his conscience, the sun sets beside the rabbit."
What kind of weird poem is that?
Each line corresponds to a single word.
Here, hold this.
Staring at the flower tree, a child, sleeping under the moonlight with glee.
As one abandons his conscience, the sun sets beside the rabbit.
[If Only We Met Earlier]
Here.
People bestow willow branches to others during farewells as a symbol of longing.
Today, the cypress stick I've given to you represents a different meaning.
Cypress tree is evergreen.
Yuexia, I hope you can stay by my side for long.
We have already encountered each other late.
May we never part with each other again.
Heartless Shaodan, which side of you is this?
You're so good at stirring my heart.
You must've been exhausted. You stood for a long time.
Sit down and take a break.
Yuexia.
You're very good-looking.
Why does that sound so familiar?
The heavenly guards only acknowledge the owners of the token.
It cannot be used by people other than their owners.
Look at you.
Look at you. How could
you look so handsome?
So, he's the soul shard Heartless Shaodian had fragmented on the night I consumed the fruit of taboo.
No! No.
This is too quick.
It's fine.
We mustn't waste our precious time.
What's going on? Let me out!
Luckily I had a trick up my sleeve after Heartless Shaodian turned me into a walnut.
I learned his magic and the way to dispel it.
- If you like me...
- Let me out!
There's no need to be impatient.
Sorry about this. You can be a walnut for now.
You'll return to normal after four hours.
I'll make a move first. See you tomorrow.
Yuexia!
[Huajian Inn]
This smells great.
The dishes here are great.
I had my fill.
Sister-in-law? When did you come back?
- Have you won his heart?
- Tell us what happened.
We had a private chat surrounded by candles.
We enjoyed ourselves.
- And then?
I told him to lie down.
This... This...
Sister-in-law, you've truly done everything for Eldest Brother's sake.
You even sacrificed your body.
I made him fall for me by lifting a finger.
Maybe the heavens were taking pity on me during our journey.
Maybe the last soul shard is meant as a reward for me.
Even so, you guys didn't need to progress that quickly.
Well... Don't tell me you fell for him.
Silly bird, what are you thinking?
He attempted something indecent tonight. I turned him into a walnut.
He's lying on his bed right now.
Wait, you turned him into a walnut?
Aren't you afraid that you'll anger him?
You silly bird.
What's wrong with me again?
This is what you call the carrot-and-stick approach.
This is how you subdue him.
Tomorrow morning, I'll buy some delicious snacks for him.
And we'll spend one more day together.
By then, I'll subdue him successfully.
[House of Colors]
The pine branches will be depleted soon.
I think it's better to use willow branches in the future.
I left early yesterday.
I guess he closed another deal.
[Hongxiuzhao | Hongbin]
Miss, our shop isn't opened yet.
I'm not a customer.
I'm the lady your young master fancies.
That means I'm your future lady boss.
How could I not remember that?
But Young Master Wen Ren isn't here right now.
Miss, I'll definitely tell him that you came by.
Miss, may I know your name?
Yuexia.
I'm staying at Huajian Inn. Tell him to look for me when he's back.
All right, Miss. Take care.
[Butterfly Valley, Liurong]
[Guests]
- Who are these?
- This... Miss, do not overthink it.
All of these are important guests of ours.
These are the guests young master told me to look after.
All this while, I was plagued by a dream.
In my dream, there was a lady whom I fell for.
She felt ephemeral to me.
However, I could never reach her.
Miss, when I saw you,
I felt like you resembled the lady in my dream greatly.
Young Master Wen Ren, seems like you dreamt about plenty of ladies, huh?
- Yuexia?
- Who is she?
Who am I?
I was the lover in his dream yesterday.
He drew a painting for me too. He even made a hairpin for me with branches.
[Wanhua Valley, Luqiao, | Yuehua Restaurant, Chunxi]
[Butterfly Valley, Liurong]
I thought you were a loyal person.
So, you're just a flirtatious playboy!
Miss!
I... Mister, you truly excel at deceiving other people's feelings.
I almost fell for your trick too.
You're already flirting with other girls even though I just left not long ago.
Even the Heavens cannot react in time to punish you.
I... I can explain.
- Listen to me.
- To hell with your explanation!
[Scoundrel]
It's so sweet.
It's so unique.
I like it.
This is so infuriating.
Have some soup and be appeased.
No!
What exactly has Heartless Shaodian kept inside his heart for him to produce a villain as his soul shard?
I know he's flirtatious.
But you're flirting with two soul shards at once too, right?
You two are the same. Why are you angry at him?
How could this be the same? I'm doing it to revive him.
Why are you concerned about whether he's faithful to you or not when he's just a soul shard?
Isn't that only an issue that someone who fell for him will encounter?
Why are you worried?
I was just saying.
I couldn't care less about him.
If so, you should head back and subdue the third soul shard and remove your stupid Iridescent Eyes.
What's wrong?
Did you do anything to let him down?
I didn't do much.
I just kicked him to the ground,
stuffed his mouth with food, and wrote the word "Scoundrel" on his face.
What did you write on his face?
What are you doing here?
My staff told me that you were staying at this inn.
I found your room after inquiring about it from the innkeeper.
What are you doing here?
Are you here to seek revenge?
Last night, you turned me into a walnut and left me behind.
Initially, I thought you would never come back.
Due to my grief, I tried to express my feelings to other ladies.
Yuexia,
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I beat you up just now. Don't you blame me for it?
Yuexia, why would you do that to me if you didn't fancy me?
Let's drop the matter.
It's fine as long as you love me.
It was my fault today.
Yuexia, please give me another chance.
I've wasted the food you prepared especially for me.
I shall cook for you tomorrow to make it up to you.
What do you think?
Is that okay with you?
It's a promise then.
You and I will meet tomorrow.
All right. It's a promise.
It's a promise.
See you tomorrow.
See you.
He was so sincere.
I'm touched by his actions.
He may have committed huge mistakes in the past, but I think he has turned over a new leaf for your sake.
Doesn't that mean he has already fallen for you?
Silly bird, it was all an act.
Now, I'm not trying to subdue him.
He's trying to subdue me instead.
What do you mean?
He has won the hearts of many girls with his flirtatious behavior.
How could he turn over a new leaf overnight?
He took a step back to get two steps forward.
His acting was pretty convincing though.
He's an expert.
I thought he was the easiest to subdue.
Now that I think about it, he's the hardest to subdue.
I'll look for His Highness now.
We still have Qingheng, Ziwu, and others on our side.
I'm sure we can subdue a stupid soul shard like him.
Over here.
Fiery,
you haven't taken dinner yet.
Rock, finish it soon.
When will my wife return?
I'm sure she's busy with her tasks.
She'll definitely come back for you once she's done.
I miss her.
I know.
Even if you try not to think about it,
he'll appear in your mind automatically.
You have someone you long for too?
Here.
Carve a flower for him.
You're the sister of my wife.
I will help you.
Thank you.
But one is enough.
I'll ask you for more after I master this, okay?
Let's take dinner then.
If not, your wife will be worried.
The number of voidwalkers is rising in the Beast Realm.
Even the Void Empress is here.
Yeah. His Highness told us to report their movements in Void to him.
But we don't even know where he is.
Fiery, you must eat up.
Your wife will be happy if she knows.
I don't know how that unlucky guy offended the voidwalkers.
Right now, they've sealed off the entire Assassin Assembly Hall.
Even the Beast King is pretending to be ignorant.
He allowed the Void Empress to get her way.
I wonder why His Highness is paying great attention to this matter.
Since when have we been able to figure His Highness out?
Forget it.
Let's just do our duty and protect His Highness's friend.
- Let's go.
If they keep this up, the Void Empress will locate Heartless soon.
I have to notify Tan'er.
However, Tan'er is trying her best to locate the last soul shard.
I mustn't distract her.
I need to come up with a way to protect Heartless on her behalf.
We only lack one more soul shard.
The empyrean will be revived soon.
Two heads are better than one.
You all should try to come up with something.
This is the last soul shard.
I don't believe that we cannot subdue him.
Although this soul shard is a womanizer, he doesn't breathe fire or spend our money.
We just need to find a way to make him fall for you.
We can learn from the books.
[How to Train Your Husband]
We can also observe the couples in the market and learn from them.
Read books?
Learn from them?
I need to see him tomorrow. You think I can apply what I've learned immediately?
Di Lanjue, do you have any good ideas?
If I must say, you should just smash him with my mace until he says yes.
What are you doing?
Let go. I'll punch you.
Give it to me!
- Silly bird!
- Don't move!
Your Highness, you brought so many things here.
I'm sure one of them will come in handy.
This?
Be gentle with them!
What about this one?
Four people will definitely come up with more ideas compared to one person.
Here, cheers.
Come.
All right.
Since you insist on doing it, tomorrow, I'll apply everything that I've learned before.
Cheers.
Here, cheers.
Wish me luck.
Yuexia.
I prepared these for you.
Do you like them?
I do.
Have you ever played tug of war?
Tug of what?
You've never played tug of war before?
Each of us will pull one side.
The one who tears the leaf loses.
That leaf won't do.
You need to pick a withered one.
Di Lanjue taught me to put this leaf into my shoes and ferment it with my sweat for some hours.
This way, I'll win every game.
What did she say again?
What did she say?
Sweat?
What have you been teaching her all this while?
How should I know that she's trying to flirt with him with her usual demeanor?
Enough.
Let's stick with the original plan.
Man Man, it's your turn.
Look at me.
When I'm happy, I get ahead of myself.
I'm a lady too.
How could I play with such a thing?
Miss Yuexia, are you sick?
Mister.
Mister,
I have a sore waist.
Where did he learn all this nonsense from?
Go away.
What exactly are they doing?
Di Lanjue!
This won't work.
- That was so inappropriate.
- I...
At this rate, she will never win his heart.
Let's try someone else, okay?
Eldest Brother wouldn't be attracted by a person like you.
Let me do it.
Eldest Brother.
Yuexia.
What did you call me just now?
How could you call him Eldest Brother?
You need to call him, "Sweetie."
Sweetie.
You have to act cuter.
Do it like this.
Sweetie.
- That's not right.
- Sweetie.
Sweetie...
Sweetie.
Yuexia, I've never seen a lady as unique as you before.
Wait. What trick are they playing?
Brother Wen Ren, I agreed to meet you today just so I could ask you this question.
How much feeling do you have for me?
"Flawless World"
♫ You say, "Light swept through the twin flowers" ♫
♫ Wandering at the desolate cliff ♫
♫ Whose face has the wind comfort again? ♫
♫ When the seabed sand are flying everywhere ♫
♫ If only I can spend the sorrowful night with you ♫
♫ We'll go through the ups and downs together ♫
♫ Hair being messed up by the misplaced time and space ♫
♫ No matter how tough it is, I'm not afraid ♫
♫ You are the crescent in my heart ♫
♫ My radiant light shining through the years ♫
♫ If I do shed tears, they will turn into flowers in my heart ♫
♫ I'll always be the unchanging love in your heart ♫
♫ Even the galaxy will agree with me, love needs no answer ♫
♫ I'll shine for you ♫
♫ In this flawless world ♫
♫ I'll always be the unchanging love in your heart ♫