(A Shoulder To Cry On)
(Episode 6. A shoulder to cry on)
What I have learned is.
10 is a safe zone.
The rest of the zones...
I thought they might kill me.
I have nothing but archery.
Da-yeol startled me…
Wow, he shot how
many 10s consecutively…?
Honestly, I thought that he
would lose by a huge margin.
I have no idea what's
going to happen.
Without it, you might mess up your match...?
It doesn't matter anymore.
Don't bother me about
giving it back later.
By the way, Tae-hyun.
Huh?
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
…No…Later.
Later? What is this about?
Return my spin feathers later. Let's go.
What is it?
My entire life had been on target.
I had put away all other things.
I had no passion and desire for winning.
At some point, I was scared of
archery. That's why I had to carry on.
There was nothing left
for me except archery.
Tae-hyun, if I didn't meet you,
I really wouldn't have known.
I've only ever seen you smile
brightly when you're doing archery.
What I truly want is...
I'd like to be honest from now on.
Without any regrets.
Cho Tae-hyun.
I…I like you.
I like you.
What do you think of me?
Cho Tae(-hyun)
Still bad at basketball.
Where is your pet?
A lucky shot… didn't
he say anything to you?
About what?
You seem to try to draw a line
between the two of you but it didn't take.
So I educated him instead.
Educated him? What the
heck are you talking about?
He likes you.
What a lunatic, you brat!
Hey, is he insane? Considering what we did
to him, is it possible for him to like me?
Hell no, he would leave you alone.
See?
Still though, why didn't he?
So odd, right?
A normal guy may try to get
you back and keep his distance.
As if...
In my point of view,
you're not (normal) either.
Poor Da-yeol…he just barely lost.
He's still amazing to
have advanced to the final.
Even so, he prepared so hard for the final.
Now that he he's sad,
he might not come to school.
Don't say things like that!
What on earth is wrong with her?
Hi.
Why are you all staring at me?
Da-yeol, are you all right?
Hmm…yes, I'm all right.
Depressed, right?
No, I'm totally okay.
You must be pretty upset.
Why are you crying instead of me?
He's fine.
(Math)
*gay gasp* Wow, math really
isn't your strong suit, is it...
Don't look...
I guess God doesn't
give with both hands...
What did you get?
'I don't know…math…is too difficult.
By the way, since you're a student athelete
it doesn't really matter, does it?
Should I have a tutor?
Me! Me! Me! Let me
do it! I'm good at math!
- Really?
- Yes, I can do that for you. What do you think?
58! Hey, Kang So-young,
you'd better take care for your studying~.
- Seeing your score, who can you teach?
- Hey, give it back.
Will you study one more year?
- Give it back right away!
- No way.
Da-yeol, if you don't mind,
can I teach you math?
- (See you at 2 in the library tomorrow.)
- (Okay.)
I'm leaving home now.
Dad, see you!
In a trigonometrical function, it's easier
to see an upper circle on the graph…
The point on the
basis of XY graph..
Hey, Kang So-young.
I wasn't asleep!
Nodding off and not studying,
why did you come here with us?
I came here to study as well.
Clean up the drool from
your mouth and tell us.
It's because I hit the books all night…
I'd better drink some coffee.
Would you like some?
No, thank you.
Me neither.
Let's carry on. To solve this question,
use the formula I mentioned just now..
Can you concentrate on this?
It's not difficult, Da-yeol.
Using the formula will be solved...
What in the world are you looking at,
not the question?
What the heck are you doing?
Sorry.
Let's take a break for a minute.
Tae-hyun.
Jang Won-kyung.
My goodness, I got to see the whole damned shit.
When did you get here?
It was great, why
didn't you keep going?
Hi, Da-yeol?
Jeez, you are so pathetic.
Da-yeol, I told you
that you're nothing but a pet to him.
Am I right, Tae-hyun?
You said Da-yeol is your pet.
Hey, watch your mouth.
Damn it. I just told you the truth.
Isn't it, Tae-hyun?
Are you serious?
Tell me, please.
So, what are you going to do now?
Hey, Cho Tae-hyun..was
when he said true?
Why did you do such a thing just now?
- That's…
- Hey~.
Why did you come out?
Don't talk to me ever again.
What's wrong? What happened?
Let's have a talk.
What's the matter?
Jeez.
You keep avoiding me.
Let go of me.
I'm sorry. My mistake.
I don't even want to
hear anything, you brat!
Are you taking revenge on me now?
Revenge?
As for what I did to you before,
is this how you're paying me back?
No…I didn't mean by that.
Then, just stay out of my sight, please!
I'm filthy because I like you?
I also know I'm
being really annoying.
That I like you..it makes me so angry and upset.
I have no clue what to do…
You..
Can you hate me for good?
Can you do that?
Even if there was someone that
committed suicide because she hated me...
I told you it was just an accident…
What if another accident happens again?
I don't care..I…
I do care.
Having hung out with you until now,
I was testing myself.
Whether I feel guilty or not,
after being such a garbage person.
In order to make sure,
I just took an advantage of you, moron brat.
…is that all you have in mind?
What am I to you?
Nothing peculiar.
So, stop liking me.
What am I to you?
Right... what kind of person was he to me?
On the surface, he's been serious every time.
Let me reveal your true face in public.
Hey.
He's been desperate in some ways.
Bullying and making fun of you,
was so much fun for a while.
With a glum face,
a picky eater like an child…
Hey, how come you picked out beans?
Are you a kindergarten boy?
None of your business.
If I didn't know he was an athelete,
he would just be a regular student.
Yummy?
I liked him in such trivial ways.
Despite being a loner without friends,
Will you not come to school?
He was the only one
that ever came to see me.
Da-yeol, did you take
notes in Life and Ethics?
Can I borrow them?
Let me treat you in a snack bar later.
- No problem.
- Are you serious?
I'll get you anything you want. I won't be
messy and I'll give it to you straight after.
Bye~.
Why did you pinch me?
I was annoyed.
What made you annoyed?
How come?
Leave me alone.
Why~.
Right. What made me annoyed?
It's useless to figure it out now...
Because I ended everything myself.
Maybe I wasn't confident enough
to be hated by you?
I don't care.. I…
I do care.
I was afraid that now you were the only one...
who came and comforted me.
Hey, Cho Tae-hyun! Cho Tae-hyun!
It was not your fault.
Afraid to...
Here?
Lose you.
Da-yeol's house?
Yes…he hasn't been in touch.
He hasn't come to school for several days.
There is his previous house address
in a school record book but…
Sure, I will let you know.
Thank you.
You are… Da-yeol's friend, right?
Huh? Yes…
After the final,
Da-yeol quit archery.
Sorry?
Do you mean it? Are you really quitting?
Yes.
Owing to the mistake you made?
No, it's not the reason.
What on earth are you
going to do instead of archery?
...Quitting archery won't
make my life ruin at any rate.
And…
There is something
I'd like to pour my heart into.
I truly appreciate what you've done for me.
Without it, you might
mess up your match...?
It doesn't matter anymore.
I have something to ask you.
Not now, later.
Did Da-yeol come to school?
Tae-hyun.
Today is the last day
Da-yeol is at school.
What are you talking about?
- You've done good work.
- Well-done.
Wait...
Da-yeol! Wait!
Lee Da-yeol! Hear me out, please.
What is it?
Better late than never…
Too late, though…
Maybe I was scared to be abandoned by you.
You may disappear just as others.
Perhaps…I like you but..
Frankly, I don't know exactly
what my true heart is.
Maybe…I need you..
Hey…hold on.
- Are you kidding me?
- Huh?
You are not sure whether you like me or not.
Even so, you need me?
You told me not to like you?
Didn't you just say you
took advantage of me?
Was it not enough to hurt me?
Da-yeol..I'm sorry. I said it wrong.
Gosh…you're damn humiliating me till the end.
Don't go.
Don't go...
What the hell…
Since you try to solve all your
problems with that sad look...
I... I can't handle you anymore.
Please don't leave me.
Cho Tae-hyun.
If there's someone else
who likes you next time...
Like him back, for once.
(TWO YEARS LATER)
Hello? I just woke up. I'm leaving right away.
Are you coming? No…well..I don't know.
It' said that selection test for National team
is harder than Olympic Games in the long run.
Just a moment.
("ARCHERY NATIONAL PREMATCH"
CHOI TAE-WOOK'S BRILLIANT PLAY)
This year, athlete Choi Tae-wook’s
play definitely stood out.
He scored X-ten in the final round,
widening the gap with his competitors.
Nothing special. See you later.
If electrons gather here, then this part, a
P-type semiconductor, this carrier becomes a hole.
- Are you following me? That's all for today.
- Thank you.
Jeez…I'm worn out. Isn't he crazy?
To change lecture time
on his own authority.
So, I filed a complaint.
Already? Creepy brat. You look like a
cold-blooded person every once in a while.
But still, I feel good
because you did that.
See?
Gosh, it's gonna take forever
to finish this assignment.
Hang in there.
Huh? How come you look relaxed?
Because I've finished already.
You should have done it in advance as well.
Such a traitor…by the way.
I heard there are so many pretty girls
among freshmen this year.
Let's go crazy at
the opening party.
I'm busy.
How come, you'd finished your assignment.
I should study for the next class.
Don’t you feel sorry for me
to mess up a blind date?
I don't get it.
Without you, girls wouldn't
go for a blind date with me.
Why are you wasting your beautiful youth?
Are you a monk or something?
Or is there anyone that you are fond of?
I'm not interested at all.
Take care of your own business.
Please…let’s go together!
Hello?
Done for the day?
Yes.
(Introduction of Police Science)
Then see you there.
Okay.
(Lee Da-yeol)
Lee Da-yeol!
Waiting long?
No, I just got here.
Tada! How do I look?
You look great.
You also look like a college student.
Really? Where shall we go?
Food or drinks?
- Drinks?
- Both. Okay?
Kang Sso.
What's up?
Cho Tae-hyun, where are you?
I'm at school.
Can you come over now?
For what?...Are you drunk?
Of course, I am…by the way…
guess who I am with right now?
I have no idea.
I'm with Da-yeol.
What?
He kept calling your name…looking for you…
Where are you?
If there's someone else
who likes you next time...
Like him back, for once.
Hey, where in the world are you?
Cho Tae!
Come on.
What's going on?
I will let you in on an amazing scoop.
Check out the tear stains.
What's going on here? What's wrong with him?
Yet another scoop is that
even though he only got 52 in math,
he could go into Police Administration
because there are no enrollment requirements!
Stop joking me. Tell me what's wrong with him?
It's impossible for me to know that.
I wont be a fool,
getting stuck between the two of you.
What the heck are you doing? Take him.
Hello?
The park across from Se-woon intersection.
Turn right and you can see the park.
Hello? Hello?
Darn it. Too heavy.
Lee Da-yeol, the reason
you're going through it like this...
is because you still like me, right?
Is that right?
Da-yeol, I also hope to like you.
If someone likes me, I hope it's you.
Even if I am still problematic…
In spite of too many things I feel
sorry for you… I'd like to go for it.
If the moment comes,
Would you be with me?
Let me walk. I can walk on my own.
I can wait for you.
I will wait for you…
Give me a proper confession
when the moment is right.
(Next Episode) In high school, it was archery.
Now it's the police exam.
When am I really free to meet up with you?
We've arrived.
No one can disturb us here.
- Stay there!
- No!
- I said stay there!
- I will not!
If it's going to disappear anyway,
maybe it's better not to know.
I want to kiss you.
You always notice me before I do.
It's not hard if you like it.
I can't believe you know how to do
such a great thing.
Don't mind me.
Would you like to eat this?