[Palms on Love]
[Adapted from the online novel,
The Age of Wind and Rain]
[Episode 16]
You fired at the Governor.
Are you out of your mind?
Is he dead?
What did he ever do to you?
How could you?
I feel bad for Governor Xue.
Do you have a conscience?
Governor Xue always defended you.
Don't you at least know that?
My gun didn't point at him.
How did that happen?
You used to study abroad.
You should be more sensible than me.
But as far as I can tell,
you're ungrateful and unreasonable!
Mr. Xue.
I don't want to die.
It seems you understand
your own situation.
Whether you live or not
depends on what you'll do next.
I can tell you
whatever you want to know.
The Ji family was charged with treason.
What exactly happened?
Who is behind you?
The hag, Fang Fei.
She colluded with Xue Zhihai.
Xue Zhihai switched the replicas
in Mr. Ji's warehouse
with opium.
Then he framed the Ji family.
Where did they get the opium?
Because
someone else is behind them.
That person is the real boss.
The two of them are merely lackeys.
Who is
the real boss?
I don't know.
All I know is that he still
runs the opium business.
He has a warehouse
in the western suburbs of the city.
I've been there once
with Xue Zhihai to pick up goods.
The exact location?
Yang Village.
Nan.
Send men to Yang Village
to find the warehouse.
Why?
The opium business is way bigger
than this.
She cannot be involved.
So, who exactly
is behind all this?
We are investigating it.
We will soon have a lead.
Fang Changlin was killed
due to my negligence in guarding.
The assassin got a chance
to kill him.
How's the Governor...
According to our investigation,
someone else shot the Governor.
Their gun was aimed right at him.
Perhaps
he won't wake up.
I want to see him.
Please, let me see him.
Nan, take me to him.
So you can shoot him again?
Please, Nan.
Let me see him.
Please.
I'm begging you.
Please, nothing more.
I am begging you.
Please let me have a look at him.
Let me see him.
Please, Nan.
I want to see him.
You old fox.
You knew
that wench might not aim at him,
so you sent someone to follow them.
What a pity.
My guy still missed.
Now Xue Dongfeng is in a coma.
And Ji Lianyun has been taken
into custody.
Changlin,
don't blame me.
In the next life,
I will repay you as much as I can.
I got a letter from Commander Qin,
saying that since Dongfeng
is unconscious,
someone else should take his place.
Someone from the Xue family.
Really?
That's great.
To you,
my dear Governor.
I knew
I chose the right man.
Starting tomorrow,
don't come to see me again.
What do you mean?
Do you know
why Commander Qin favored Xue Dongfeng?
He sees him as his future son-in-law.
That's why he can be the Governor
of Jiang City.
You're going to marry Qin Mengmeng?
No.
Didn't you promise me
that I would be the Governor's wife?
Governor's wife?
Do you want the whole world to know
that I slept with my father's woman?
Xue Zhihai.
Are you going to dump me?
Do you really take yourself
as the eldest son of the Xue family?
Don't forget.
You're just an adopted son,
a dog of the Xue family!
You've gotten this far
because of all the dirty work
I've done for you!
It's all thanks to me. Do you know that?
Before I lose my temper,
get out of here.
Xue Zhihai.
Have you cheated on me?
You said you'd only love me.
Only me.
Xue Zhihai.
Please.
I can't live without you.
I'm not leaving!
Zhihai.
Please.
Please don't drive me away.
I've done so many bad things for you.
I know I will go to the devil.
But I'm not afraid at all.
In this world,
if you dump me,
what should I do?
Zhihai.
I'll see you down there when I die.
Get lost.
Leave Jiang City for good.
Get out before I change my mind.
Scram!
♪I'm waiting for the rain
to wet the city♪
♪At dusk♪
♪As I ran into someone I missed
at the street corner♪
♪Old memories flashed♪
♪If I can shout that I miss you♪
♪I'll be waiting for the sunshine
in the rain♪
♪If your heart is as cold as ice♪
♪My heart will call for you♪
♪Are you as resolute as I am♪
♪You wake me up to see you♪
♪I'm sure your heart will be soft♪
♪You approach me in the name of love♪
♪As time goes by, I realize
there's no time like the present♪
♪I have no regrets when being with you♪
♪And you're like the rising wind♪
♪I ask you not to leave me
in the name of love♪
♪Wind blows and we part ways in silence♪
♪And you're like the cloud♪
♪Moving closer or farther away from me♪