[Palms on Love]
[Adapted from the online novel,
The Age of Wind and Rain]
[Episode 19]
I guess Fang Fei's disappearance
is related to Xue Zhihai.
But he has been taken away
by Commander Qin.
Did she fall out with Xue Zhihai?
Has Xue Zhihai killed her?
Or has she been hidden somewhere?
Isn't that Ms. Yun Lian?
Just ignore her.
Let's go shopping.
Ms. Yun Lian.
Stop there.
I told you to stop. Didn't you hear?
No.
You...
Why are you here?
Hanging around.
Are you?
Are you hooking up with someone here?
It's not even that late.
Nan.
Send her back.
Wait.
Dongfeng, you know what?
She was very arrogant
while you were unconscious.
Really?
I'll punish her later.
No, I want her to kneel
before me right now.
Kneel.
Hey, what are you doing?
Governor, Miss Qin.
You're just in time. Hit her.
Well...
Get out of here.
Even the police dare not interfere.
Go on.
You asked for it.
Never mess with me again.
Let's go.
How is she?
The doctor has checked on her.
It's not serious.
Luckily it was you.
I controlled my strength.
If I had hit her hard,
Miss Ji would have died.
In that case,
if I had spoken up for her,
Qin Mengmeng
would have made her suffer more.
You can go check on her.
The doctor gave her a sedative.
So, she won't know.
I'm sorry.
I'll find out the truth
about your family.
Why are you here?
I came to see if you're dead.
Well, I'll live.
Are you happy or disappointed?
It doesn't matter.
As long as you don't die in my house.
Otherwise, it's unlucky.
No need to provoke me.
I know
I hurt you first.
So, you can torment me all you want.
I won't have any complaints.
Anyway, you used to do the same
to me.
You sure have a smart mouth
for someone who's injured.
Why didn't you dare
to argue with Qin Mengmeng earlier?
I have nothing to say to her.
Talk to me.
Fang Fei is missing.
Help me find her.
Who are you to order me around?
You tell me.
What?
You're my ex-girlfriend
or my mistress?
You're not in a position
to be my mistress.
Qin Mengmeng doesn't know
about our past relationship.
Anyway, I can't get revenge
without your help.
If you don't help me, I'll tell her.
I'll ruin your marriage and reputation.
Let's go down together.
Ji Lianyun.
You're dooming yourself.
You know I'll stop at nothing
for my revenge.
Fang Fei is safe for now.
Now,
can you calm yourself?
You want revenge,
but you need to be alive to do it.
Don't try to challenge me again.
Now that he has Fang Fei,
maybe she will be safe.
[Sheng'an Hospital]
Sir.
To the Governor's house.
Stop, this is the wrong way.
Stop.
Long time no see.
Miss Yun.
Why are you so afraid of me?
Weren't you taken by Commander Qin?
Xue Dongfeng is indeed very cunning.
But I survived.
In fact,
I've been working for Commander Qin.
It was Commander Qin
who destroyed your family.
Aren't you Ji Xianwen's daughter?
You know what I'm talking about.
Fire.
Why should I believe you?
You don't have to.
But you'll lose someone
who can help you get revenge.
When Xue Dongfeng
and Qin Mengmeng humiliated you,
I just happened to see it.
He's trying to climb up the ladder.
You're just an obstacle to his success.
You'll help me get revenge?
Why?
Because I hate the Xue family.
Before I was five,
they treated me as one of their own.
But nothing lasts forever.
When Mrs. Xue was pregnant,
they started to ignore me
and sent me to the side room.
Xue Zhaokun never cared for me again.
Outsiders thought of me
as the eldest son of the Xue family,
but the Xue family treated me
like a wildling with no parents.
I thought you would not welcome me home,
just like before.
What makes you say that?
Congrats, Governor Xue.
Even if Dongfeng remains unconscious,
you still have me.
I'll protect us.
No need to say anything.
I've long wanted you
to be my son-in-law.
I don't like him.
I only want Dongfeng.
Xue Dongfeng took everything from me.
He should never have been born.
Don't you want
to take down Commander Qin?
Kill Xue Dongfeng,
and I'll help you
take down Commander Qin
to clear your family's name.
We are both desperate.
So, we have to help each other.
♪I'm waiting for the rain
to wet the city♪
♪At dusk♪
♪As I ran into someone I missed
at the street corner♪
♪Old memories flashed♪
♪If I can shout that I miss you♪
♪I'll be waiting for the sunshine
in the rain♪
♪If your heart is as cold as ice♪
♪My heart will call for you♪
♪Are you as resolute as I am?♪
♪You wake me up to see you♪
♪I'm sure your heart will be softened♪
♪You approach me in the name of love♪
♪As time goes by, I realize
there's no time like the present♪
♪I have no regrets when being with you♪
♪And you're like the rising wind♪
♪I ask you not to leave me
in the name of love♪
♪The wind blows
and we part ways in silence♪
♪You're like a cloud♪
♪Sometimes close, sometimes distant♪