[Palms on Love]
[Adapted from the online novel,
The Age of Wind and Rain]
[Episode 8]
Auntie.
Zhihai.
Don't.
Auntie.
Calm down.
Zhihai.
He's too young.
He's my only nephew.
Just give him one more chance.
Please.
Thank you, Mr. Xue.
Aren't you eating?
If you miss this meal,
you'll have the next one
tomorrow morning.
Untie my hand.
I need to use the restroom.
Do you need help?
If you don't tell me what you're up to,
you can't go anywhere.
Even if you don't tell me,
I know you're here for Fang Fei.
As for your plan,
I suppose
I will know very soon.
Do you really want to know?
Yes.
Untie me.
And we can talk.
I want to eat something I like.
Untie me,
and I'll cook myself.
I cook for you.
It happened before.
You cooked
while I watched you.
1,785 days.
What?
I've cooked for you that long.
You remember it so clearly.
That day,
you left right after dinner
and never appeared again.
This is my father's favorite dish.
The lotus root is my mother's favorite.
I don't care about that.
Then let's start with Fang Fei.
She was a dancer.
My mother had a kind heart.
She pitied Fang Fei
and kept her as her sworn sister.
Unexpectedly,
she slept with mf my father
when he was drunk.
Since then, my home has been a mess.
I heard of it when I studied abroad.
So, I wanted to return home.
Unexpectedly,
she falsely accused my family
of selling opium.
Yet she embezzled the fortune
of my family,
turned into a national heroine,
and married your father.
What did you put in my glass?
Dongfeng.
Thank you
for the good times you gave me.
I have never forgotten you.
If one day, it's all done and dusted,
can we get back together?
How dare you.
You drugged me.
So what?
Anyway, your life is in my hands now.
You're holding a knife at midnight,
standing outside Mrs. Fang Fei's room.
So,
you're going to kill her.
Are you crazy?
I'll die with her,
and it's all over.
Must you die?
Who will give me the antidote?
Think about it.
If you die
with Fang Fei,
you'll have no chance
to prove your family's innocence.
Mr. Xue.
I don't get it.
You knew she put something
in your drink.
Why did you still drink it?
Perhaps in that way,
she would feel more secure.
After all, she dares not trust anyone
after being betrayed.
I got more confused.
I'm sorry.
Stop hitting me.
I'm begging you.
Spare me.
I can't help.
Today,
you apologize to Ms. Yun and my brother.
You implore them.
I won't stop until you ask me to.
Mr. Xue.
Ms. Yun.
I was wrong.
Please spare me.
I was just drunk.
Please.
Stop him.
Xue Zhihai.
Stop it.
You're injured.
Auntie, I made a mistake.
Please stop him.
You mean woman.
Calm down.
Though Changlin is your nephew,
he has to be punished for his mistake.
You can't cover for him.
She's just a lowly maid.
How could you hurt Changlin for her?
This mean woman loves
to hook up with guys.
She was
in Dongfeng's room last night.
Now,
why are you siding with her?
Are you okay?
You're severely injured.
You need a good rest.
Since it's hot,
take care not to get inflamed.
I...
Mrs. Fang Fei.
I know you said those words
you didn't mean.
Actually, I don't blame Fang Changlin.
Don't be angry over this.
Mr. Xue.
I know you mean well.
Thank you.
Governor.
I am no longer angry with Fang Changlin.
Please let him go.
What is she
up to?
Interesting.
♪I'm waiting for the rain
to wet the city♪
♪At dusk♪
♪As I ran into someone I missed
at the street corner♪
♪Old memories flashed♪
♪If I can shout that I miss you♪
♪I'll be waiting for the sunshine
in the rain♪
♪If your heart is as cold as ice♪
♪My heart will call for you♪
♪Are you as resolute as I am♪
♪You wake me up to see you♪
♪I'm sure your heart will be soft♪
♪You approach me in the name of love♪
♪As time goes by, I realize
there's no time like the present♪
♪I have no regrets when being with you♪
♪And you're like the rising wind♪
♪I ask you not to leave me
in the name of love♪
♪Wind blows and we part ways in silence♪
♪And you're like the cloud♪
♪Moving closer or farther away from me♪