=Ms. Nirvana=
=Episode 4=
(Mrs. Gu has just joined the family)
(and has already won a good reputation
among the servants.)
(She also threw out Madam Li.)
(It's evident...)
Huaizhou.
Madam Li
had her tongue cut off.
She had her tongue cut off?
She's
just an old woman
kicked out by the Gu family.
What kind of person
would do such a cruel thing?
Madam Li likes to spread rumors.
Perhaps
she was targeted for revenge.
Huaizhou.
She's
Sitang's personal servant after all.
She served the Gu family for years.
She worked hard
even if she didn't achieve anything.
Now that she lost her tongue,
it will be hard
for her to make a living.
Let's help her
as much as we can.
No wonder the servants
praise you for your generosity.
She set you up.
Don't you hate her?
Haven't you
already got justice for me?
I was able to make a decision
because you have
solid reasons and evidence.
When
I was in Ping City,
I bear the stigma
of being the daughter of a murderer.
The old maids and servants
around me
bullied me,
so
I was prepared
for these.
Madam Li was wrong
to set you up.
But did the incense explode
because Father and Mother were mad?
Maybe.
Or maybe something's wrong
with the incense Madam Li gave me.
What do you think?
Huaizhou.
Qianyu.
Qianyu just returned to Hu City.
It's boring for her
to stay at home alone.
Why not
let Qianyu hold a ball
and let everyone has some fun?
Sure.
Thanks for thinking of me.
Huaizhou.
Don't worry.
I'll prepare it well and won't embarrass
you and the Gu family.
Okay.
Thank you then.
Lin Qianyu.
Go to hell!
Miss, I already informed everyone.
Now everyone knows
that this ball
is prepared
for the daughter of a murderer.
No one dares to attend it.
She will be embarrassed by then.
Good job.
Here's your reward.
Thank you, Miss.
Speaking of which,
what has this wench been doing lately?
How come I don't see her?
That country bumpkin
shops for clothes every day.
She said
she's preparing for the ball.
Shop for clothes?
I'll see who she will wear them for.
Burn that thing.
Okay, Miss.
Where's everyone?
Do you even need to ask?
Everyone thinks
she's the daughter of a murderer
and refuses to come.
If there's
any neglect in etiquette,
people will be
even less willing to come.
She has humiliated
the Gu family.
I'll tell you one last time.
Don't let me hear you
call Qianyu that again.
Come inside.
Mr. Gu.
Mr. Zhang.
You came.
Long time no see.
What's going on?
Didn't you say
that you've informed everyone?
I did tell everyone.
You're useless.
Scram.
Mr. Gu.
Sitang, you're here.
Didn't I inform you?
Didn't you say you're not coming?
Didn't you write to me
that the Gu family wants to use the ball
to find a bride for Commander Gu
and asked me to introduce myself
to Commander Gu?
Li Sitang, what's wrong with you?
You mentioned that I was the only one
and that you liked me the most
in the letter you wrote to me.
I was also the only one
you're setting up with him.
Why are they here?
Li Sitang.
How many best friends do you have?
I...
What letter?
You...
Stop pretending.
How come
I never realize you were like this?
Yeah.
Why are you here?
Where did you come from?
Does it concern you
that I return to my own home?
You...
Sitang.
Don't be rude.
Gu Manor will always be Jingzhou's home.
Jingzhou is City Defense Commander now.
It's an honor
for the Gu family that he can come.
You're too kind.
I'm here
to have some fun with the heiresses.
Go ahead.
Commander.
You're so tall.
You're so handsome.
What have you been busy with recently?
Would you like a drink?
Drink with me.
I need a dancing partner.
Which of you will help me?
I'll do it.
Me first. Let me.
Me first.
Let me.
Commander.
Let me...
Mrs. Gu is so pretty.
No wonder
Mr. Gu insisted on marrying her.
Jingzhou.
Huaizhou.
Let's dance.
Okay.
♪Your face is strange yet familiar♪
♪Time passes, but your gentleness
still lingers on my fingertips♪
♪Among the vast sea of people,
I wish you're by my side♪
♪I wish I could exchange your appearance
with my entire lifetime♪
♪The warm wind writes in my heart♪
♪Try to connect two parallel worlds♪
♪Longing
is written in our unfinished story♪
♪Awaken the passion
that is frozen within me♪
♪Our mutual connection
solves the puzzle♪
♪We are destined to meet again♪
♪I'll use up all my luck♪
♪To hold you tight♪
♪Memories are like stars of love♪
♪Inspiring me to run toward you
and bet that you're one♪
♪In this life♪
Jingzhou has been fighting in war
in the past few years,
but his dancing skills haven't declined.
What do you think?
Isn't Jingzhou pretty good at dancing?
Jingzhou is indeed
pretty good at dancing.
I guess
he often dances with heiresses.
Qianyu is also good at dancing.
I wonder
which gentleman you learned it from.
I remember
that the opening dance
performed by Commander Gu and Ms. Fu
at Commander Gu's birthday party
five years ago was a sensation.
I remember.
Ms. Fu also wore a riding outfit
at the time.
Yeah.
Let's stop talking about it.
Let's drink.
Come on. Let's drink.
I'm going to the washroom.
Okay.
Huaizhou.
We haven't danced yet.
Let's dance.
I want to take a break.
Dance with someone else first.
We haven't even danced.
I'm so mad.
You...
♪A broken heart can never be mended
to its original state♪
♪The cracks are destined♪
♪Separation that's gradually
further apart and fading♪
♪Selfish soul♪
♪Running on a twisted road♪
♪Desire has spread♪
♪Never pause between black and white♪
♪Clenching trembling hands♪
♪Eyes filling with tears
from unsaid words♪
♪Some tears aren't worth shedding again♪
♪A broken heart can never be mended.
The cracks are destined♪
♪Just like the beginning♪
♪Separation that's gradually
further apart and fading♪
♪Never hesitated
or dazzled by illusions♪
♪What tragic fate?♪
♪Emotions and fate are unpredictable♪
♪A broken heart can never be mended
to its original state♪
♪The cracks are destined♪
♪Separation that's gradually
further apart and fading♪
♪Never hesitated
or dazzled by illusions♪
♪What tragic fate?♪
♪Emotions and fate are unpredictable♪