=Ms. Nirvana=
=Episode 15=
You useless fool.
You can't even catch up
with her, can you?
I'm incompetent.
Did you see
who took her away?
The car curtain blocked my view.
I didn't see clearly.
What's the license plate number?
It was also concealed.
Ms. Zheng.
Come in.
I went shopping today
and brought you some supplements.
I'm in good health.
I don't need supplements.
I'm so envious
that you're in good health.
Unlike me, who has low red blood cells
and low blood sugar.
I faint easily.
I also almost fainted
in the garden yesterday.
Fortunately, Jingzhou helped me.
Is that so?
Jingzhou held you so tightly.
I thought you two
were seeing each other behind my back.
Ms. Zheng.
Are you kidding me?
Huaizhou
is the only one I have eyes for.
Besides,
Jingzhou is yours.
How dare I go after him?
Okay.
Since
you're not interested in Jingzhou,
why don't you do me a favor?
Sure.
I wonder
how I can help you.
I want to sleep with him.
By drugging him?
This method...
What's wrong with this method?
I told you
I, Zheng Yuzhen, will get
anyone I want,
no matter what it takes.
(Aphrodisiac)
(Hu City's City Defense Department)
Commander.
Yesterday,
I checked General Zheng's guards
as per your instructions.
The murderer who wiped
out the Fu family is on it.
Find a way to pass this list to Lu Heng.
Do it secretly.
If I'm not mistaken,
she's going to the clinic
to see Lu Heng today
for this matter.
Commander.
Why are you doing this?
You risked your life for the Fu family,
but she doesn't appreciate it at all.
You might as well...
I'll do it right away.
Ms...
Ms. Lin.
You came.
What are you doing here?
I brought you some ginseng soup.
Didn't you tell me
to stay away from you?
Why are you bringing me soup now?
You helped me.
This soup
is for you.
You don't look so good.
Here.
Let's drink it together.
It can also nourish your body.
No thanks.
You can drink it yourself.
Feed me if you mean it.
Otherwise, take it back.
I'll reach
Commander's Department at 4 PM.
You just need to deliver
the drugged soup
to Jingzhou a few minutes in advance
and leave.
Drink it yourself.
What are you doing?
Someone will see us.
Let go of me.
Someone?
Who?
My brother or Zheng Yuzhen?
Speak.
What did Zheng Yuzhen ask you to do?
What did you add in the soup?
Speak.
Gu Jingzhou.
I'm only here to deliver you soup.
Let me go.
She asked me
to drug you with aphrodisiac.
She wants to sleep with you.
So you delivered me soup
just to offer me
as a token of loyalty to her?
It's just to appease her.
I didn't mean it.
Appease?
How could you
send another woman to my bed
just to appease someone?
I can accompany you
to do anything you want.
If you want my heart and my life,
I can give it to you.
But you can't do this to me.
I didn't.
Then why did you drug me?
I just added some sleeping drugs
in the soup.
♪Selfish soul♪
I knew
you still have feelings for me.
What do you want to do?
It's almost time.
She'll see us.
We'll be doomed.
Don't need to be scared.
Didn't I tell you?
I can protect you from now on.
♪A broken heart can never be mended
to its original state♪
♪The cracks are destined♪
Why isn't she out yet?
♪Never hesitated
or dazzled by illusions♪
♪What tragic fate?♪
♪Emotions♪
♪And fate are unpredictable♪
Lin Qianyu.
Get lost!
Do you think
I would care about your soup?
I'd consider you my sister-in-law
if it weren't for my father's will?
Ms. Zheng.
Sorry.
I seem
to have messed things up.
What happened?
Why is Jingzhou so angry?
Jingzhou made a big fuss
at my wedding with Huaizhou
before.
He has been against
my marriage to Huaizhou.
He
refuses to drink my soup.
Sorry, Ms. Zheng.
I couldn't help you.
It doesn't matter, Qianyu.
I'm sorry that you suffered.
Once I marry Jingzhou,
I will
help you persuade him.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Jingzhou is in a bad mood today.
Let's not provoke him.
Come on.
Let's go back to the manor.
Stop.
Commander.
Where are you going?
Mr. Chen said that the mourning period
for Old Master Gu is over.
Mr. Gu
is moving back
to Mrs. Gu's room tonight.
He asked me to make preparations.
I see.
Okay.
Huai...
Commander, you...
Commander.
Why are you still awake at this hour?
What are you wandering about for?
Didn't I ask why you're wandering...
Wandering...
Jingzhou?
It's late.
Why are you still awake?
Aren't you still awake too?
I'm planning to go to bed now.
Huaizhou.
When are you going to talk to me
about the division of the fortune?
Anytime,
but not now.
Qianyu has been waiting
in the room for a long time.
Jingzhou.
There's no rush
to divide the fortune.
What a coincidence.
You're busy every time I talk to you.
What's the point in delaying?
I don't mean to delay it.
We can talk about it.
But I'll be frank with you.
There's no way
I'm giving you the shipping business.
Didn't I tell you?
I don't want anything else
but the shipping business.
We have nothing to talk about then.
Wait.
It's not that we can't discuss it.
Why not
come to my room?
We can discuss it.
♪Selfish soul♪
♪Running on a twisted road♪
♪Desire has spread♪
♪Never pause between black and white♪
♪Clenching trembling hands♪
♪Eyes filling with tears
from unsaid words♪
♪Some tears aren't worth shedding again♪
♪A broken heart can never be mended
to its original state♪
♪The cracks are destined♪
♪Separation that's gradually
further apart and fading♪
♪Never hesitated
or dazzled by illusions♪
♪What tragic fate?♪
♪Emotions and fate are unpredictable♪
♪A broken heart can never be mended
to its original state♪
♪The cracks are destined♪
♪Separation that's gradually
further apart and fading♪
♪Never hesitated
or dazzled by illusions♪
♪What tragic fate?♪
♪Emotions and fate are unpredictable♪