=Ms. Nirvana=
=Episode 3=
(Lu's Clinic)
Zhaoxue!
Miss, it's dangerous.
Sitang, Madam Li, save me!
Let me go.
Zhaoxue.
You can't be soft-hearted.
You must get rid
of the root of the problem.
If you save her, how are you going
to explain to the Gu family?
Let me go.
Zhaoxue!
Miss.
Besides,
Mr. Huaizhou has feelings for her.
If you save her,
how are you going to become Mrs. Gu?
Sitang.
Sitang!
Sitang, Madam Li, save me!
Let's go.
Zhaoxue.
Miss.
It's none of my business.
On your memorial day next year,
I'll burn joss paper for you!
(Memorial Tablet of Fu Zhenghe)
(Memorial Tablet of Fu Zhaoxue)
(Li Meilan, Li Sitang,
Gu Jingzhou, Gu Huaizhou, Zhao Zhong)
(Zhao Zhong)
(Gu Jingzhou, Gu Huaizhou)
(Li Meilan, Li Sitang)
Madam Li.
You instigated Li Sitang not to save me.
Now,
(Li Meilan, Li Sitang,
Gu Jingzhou, Gu Huaizhou)
I'm just giving you
a taste of your own medicine.
You're lucky
that I only cut off your tongue.
(Li Meilan, Li Sitang)
(Li Meilan)
Madam Li's injury
has been treated.
I asked my assistant to send her back.
Lu Heng.
Thank you.
You don't have to be
so polite to me all the time.
If Mr. Fu
hadn't funded me when I was little,
I would have been living on the streets.
That's why I'm willing to do anything
for you and the Fu family.
However,
why didn't you
just leave Madam Li to her fate?
Instead, you saved her.
I died once
and I realized
that
death is the easiest.
I want Madam Li
to spend the rest of her life in anger
without her tongue.
A life worse than death
is the real punishment.
Zhaoxue.
Don't call me Zhaoxue.
Fu Zhaoxue
was so stupid that she didn't see through
the Gu family's sinister hearts.
She doesn't deserve to live.
How could you be blamed
for what happened back then?
Don't worry.
I'll help you
avenge the Fu family.
Who's
next?
(Li Meilan, Li Sitang,
Gu Jingzhou, Gu Huaizhou)
My best friend,
Li Sitang.
(Li Sitang)
Although Li Sitang is willful,
Gu Huaizhou
is closer to her
than to his half-brother.
It will probably take some effort
to make her suffer.
Don't worry.
As her former best friend,
I know how to deal with her.
Gu Jingzhou.
No wonder
everyone calls you a mad dog.
I'm glad that you know.
Are you going to tell the truth
or
let me kill you?
Kill me
if you dare.
Come on!
This batch of smuggled goods
is closely related to the Gu family.
You're calling out a thief
while being one yourself.
Why pretend to be so virtuous?
Draw me the shipping route map.
The Gu family's smuggling
is done
by connecting buyers and sellers
on fixed routes.
I've only taken one route
all these years.
I don't know the rest.
Gu Huaizhou
has the complete shipping route map.
Commander.
Madam Li had her tongue cut off.
Did Lin Qianyu do it?
It's probably Li Sitang.
Lin Qianyu sent Madam Li
to the clinic and saved her.
The Gu family is quite ruthless.
Lin Qianyu.
Huaizhou.
I'm not responsible
for what happened to Madam Li.
Why won't you believe me?
Without your instructions,
would Madam Li be so bold?
Servants bullying their masters
has happened throughout history.
Why would you rather believe
the one-sided statement
of a murderer's daughter?
Besides,
she isn't a pushover.
She's my wife
and your cousin-in-law.
If you call her
the daughter of a murderer again,
I...
Mr. Gu, calm down.
In my opinion,
Ms. Li has a point.
Mrs. Gu has just joined the family
and has already won a good reputation
among the servants.
She also threw out Madam Li.
It's evident...
Mr. Chen is right.
Shut up.
You're my mother's only relative.
Since you were little,
I doted on you like you're my sister.
I didn't expect to spoil you this much.
I think
I should marry you off soon.
I will find a good family for you
and make sure you never have to worry
about food and clothing.
Huaizhou.
You know me.
I don't want to marry anyone else.
I just want to marry you.
Huaizhou!
Jingzhou.
This zipper is difficult.
Come in and help me.
♪Your face is strange yet familiar♪
♪Time passes, but your gentleness
still lingers on my fingertips♪
Here.
Does this riding outfit look good on me?
Yes.
You look good in anything.
All that matters is that you like it.
Of course I like it.
I like anything you give me.
I'm wearing this outfit
to your birthday party.
Sure.
♪Longing
is written in our unfinished story♪
♪Awaken the passion
that is frozen within me♪
♪Our mutual connection
solves the puzzle♪
♪We are destined to meet again♪
♪I'll use up all my luck♪
♪To hold you tight♪
♪Memories are like stars of love♪
♪Inspiring me to run toward you
and bet that you're one♪
♪In this life♪
You...
Have you...
fallen for me?
You're the one who has fallen for me.
You
treated me
as someone you liked.
Turns out you already have someone you like.
I wonder
which heiress is it.
It's none of your business.
Why did you want to see me then?
I'm just here to tell you something.
I want you
to sneak into Gu Huaizhou's room
and get me
the Gu family's shipping route map.
Gu Huaizhou's study
isn't accessible to anyone
if you're not summoned.
You should know this better than me.
That's why only by accomplishing this
can the pawn be qualified
to become an ally.
What can I gain from this?
I agree
to your terms.
It's really not easy
to be your ally.
But
I also need you
to help me with something.
♪Selfish soul♪
♪Running on a twisted road♪
♪Desire has spread♪
♪Never pause between black and white♪
♪Clenching trembling hands♪
♪Eyes filling with tears
from unsaid words♪
♪Some tears aren't worth shedding again♪
♪A broken heart can never be mended.
The cracks are destined♪
♪Just like the beginning♪
♪Separation that's gradually
further apart and fading♪
♪Never hesitated
or dazzled by illusions♪
♪What tragic fate?♪
♪Emotions and fate are unpredictable♪
♪A broken heart can never be mended
to its original state♪
♪The cracks are destined♪
♪Separation that's gradually
further apart and fading♪
♪Never hesitated
or dazzled by illusions♪
♪What tragic fate?♪
♪Emotions and fate are unpredictable♪