♪The gentle breeze leaves no trace♪
♪It stirs the old times♪
♪Love is gained and lost♪
♪Only then does it become unforgettable♪
♪The bamboo leaves
are rustling and falling♪
♪Fate is delayed and scattered♪
♪Only lingering hatred remains♪
♪Echoing♪
♪Old dreams are like illusions♪
♪Alas, the world is too indifferent♪
♪If there were no obsession♪
♪I wouldn't be thinking of someone♪
♪If it's destined to be alone♪
♪Like a snowstorm♪
♪When love and hate dissolve♪
♪Only a long gaze remains♪
♪A drop of tear♪
♪Falls, burning my heart♪
♪We loved without regret♪
=My Destined Consort=
=Episode 27=
Mr. Chu.
Qingqing.
If Jiangli
succeeds in taking Yanyan away,
will you leave
with them
and never return?
You heard everything?
It seems we have
finally reached the time to part.
Mr. Chu,
in just this half month,
I've seen with my own eyes
how Jingxiu cast Shen Qilan aside
like worn-out shoes to save himself.
And I've watched Jingming and Jiangli
who used to be a loving couple
go their separate ways.
It makes me feel
that all men in this world
are heartless
and irresponsible.
But Mr. Chu,
you're different.
- I know you...
- Jiangli
is just my junior now.
Right now,
I can't just watch her sink deeper
into the mire.
I understand.
Take Jiangli with you.
Don't worry about me.
I'll take good care of myself.
♪Among all the feelings,
why love someone♪
♪Unwilling to face the pain of parting♪
♪Without a word,
sorrow spreads like ink♪
♪If humans are like grass,
I'm willing burn myself for you♪
♪Forgetting youth in the ashes♪
♪Reuniting with the past
after becoming dust♪
♪Swallowing roots sprouting
in the dark, damp years♪
♪Wiping away the blooming rings of time♪
♪When fate runs out,
I'll borrow a bit tenderness♪
♪Even now, I refuse to be
an ordinary person♪
♪Living a mundane, and bleak life♪
Qingqing.
♪Fading among the masses♪
♪Breaking through the endless
worldly dust for you♪
Mr. Chu.
There's something
I would like to discuss
with you in the study.
Yao,
you came so late.
What's the matter?
Lady Shu.
Jiangli...
Lady Shu,
Jiangli would like to see you.
Take your time.
I'll take my leave.
Jiangli, you've suffered.
Come here.
Take a seat.
You've lost a lot of weight.
Thank you for your concern, Lady Shu.
You must already know
about what happened
between Master Jingming and me.
Yes, I know everything.
It was my failure in teaching my son
that led him to wrong you.
We were fated but not destined.
I won't cling to it.
I came today
just to see Yanyan.
Where is he?
He's dining with the Prefect now.
You know.
The Prefect has been attentive
to Yanyan's studies lately.
Yanyan misses you very much.
He keeps asking
when he can see you.
I came today
to take Yanyan away.
I hope you'll grant me this.
Jiangli,
I know
this whole matter
was entirely Jingming's fault.
He let down your sincere heart.
But I believe
there must be a reason behind it.
Jingming isn't someone
who is cold and ungrateful.
Perhaps,
in time,
things may take a turn for the better.
I only want to take my child.
The rest has nothing to do
with me anymore.
I told you.
Yanyan is dining with the Prefect.
This is a matter between adults.
Let's not involve the child.
What do you mean by that?
Lady Shu,
as a mother yourself,
are you asking me to be separated
from Yanyan?
Jiangli,
I understand your pain as a mother.
But Yanyan is also
our eldest grandson.
Forget me.
The Prefect would never
allow you to take Yanyan away.
You know how much the Prefect
loves Yanyan.
He is grooming him wholeheartedly.
Yanyan may inherit his position
in the future.
I don't need my child
to inherit that position.
I just want to take him away.
But
if you take Yanyan away,
then we'll never get to see him again.
If I leave Yanyan behind,
as his mother,
I'll have to part with him.
That won't happen.
Once things settle down,
I'll plead with the Prefect
on your behalf,
so you'll have a chance to visit Yanyan.
After all, you're his birth mother.
Let me be honest with you.
You absolutely can't
take Yanyan away.
Lady Shu...
Let Yanyan leave with her.
Nonsense.
Actually, it was the princess's idea.
On one hand,
she feels that if Yanyan
stays in the mansion,
as a stepmother,
if she doesn't do well in the future,
she'll be criticized.
And
if later on, she and I
have our child,
she doesn't know how to treat him.
Also,
Yanyan's character is like his mother's.
Once he makes up his mind,
nothing can change it.
If you deceive him
and force them to separate,
he'll grow distant from you.
It's better
to let her take him.
You have no more concerns now.
You should leave asap.
(Prefect's Mansion)
Mother.
Yanyan.
Be good.
Take care of your mother.
♪May you be free from a long journey♪
Yanyan.
Let's go.
Go on.
Mother,
won't Father come with us?
♪You'll think of me, in every trace♪
Your father and I
have important matters to deal with.
We must part now.
I understand. It's only temporary.
We'll be back soon.
Goodbye, Father.
I will take good care of Mother.
Be good, Yanyan.
Please.
Can I trust you?
Actually,
things aren't as you think.
I don't care
about the hidden reasons.
I only remember that you
once promised
to take care of Jiangli for life.
But now, she's enduring
the pain and humiliation.
Is this the promise you once made?
Five years ago,
I led troops to fight
in the Battle of Lingshui.
In the end, we were ambushed.
The entire army
was wiped out, except for me.
All these years,
I've been searching for the truth.
Only recently
did I uncover the truth.
The one who betrayed the country
was my eldest brother.
Not only that,
he's also allied with Xizhou,
putting the people in Dongzhou
in even greater danger.
That's why
I've been planning this wedding
with Princess Chuya.
The goal is
to capture my brother
when he acts
and secure peace for both states.
As for Jiangli,
I had to deceive her.
Only if my brother believes
I've cut all ties with Jiangli
will he not target them.
In case anything
goes wrong,
they can
escape unharmed.
Have you considered
the danger in all this?
I never thought
I could walk away unscathed.
So, I had no choice
but to use this method
to force Jiangli to leave.
Even if she hates me,
I can't let them
face any danger.
I understand.
(Prefect's Mansion)
♪However fast time goes by,
you still wouldn't know my feelings♪
♪I can't hold on;
your face is like water♪
♪Only your words remain♪
♪Watching the moonlight
gradually disappear on the horizon♪
♪There's only an incense stick of time
between us♪
♪Will you remember me
after burning away thousands of flowers♪
♪The fading♪
It's here.
Come on, let's go.
How is it?
Is the place comfortable?
It's quite nice here.
I like the setup.
And there's my favorite bush lily.
That's good.
Here.
Take this.
Zimo,
I didn't know
you had a private villa like this.
This villa...
Let's talk about it another time.
Let's not wake up Yanyan.
Rest early.
I've prepared a villa
for them.
The environment is great,
and it's very secluded.
I've also sent a team of guards
to protect them at all times.
If anything happens in the future,
please help me
look after them.
Based on Yunyi's report,
someone has been
visiting Jingxiu frequently.
It seems
he's ready to act.
We must remain cautious.
Yes.
Jingming...
Jingming.
(Divorce Letter)
Jingming...
Jingming.
What's wrong?
I had a nightmare.
I dreamed
that you wanted to divorce me
and marry Chuya.
Didn't we promise each other
we'd never part
in this life?
We've already parted once.
I don't want to part again.
Jingming.
Jingming...
Jingming, Jingming...
Jiangli.
You're awake.
My head hurts a little.
I don't even know how I fell asleep.
You've been traveling these days,
caught in the rain and a cold,
and you've been burning with fever.
Take your medicine.
Come on.
I admit.
I can't let go right away.
I still can't sever the ties.
But
I won't hold onto it forever.
Zimo,
if someone
lets go of your hand the first time,
and you choose to forgive them,
yet they choose to let go again,
will you still wait at the same spot?
This time, it is your choice.
Actually,
Jingming...
I've thought it through.
From now on,
I'll part ways with him.
Even if my heart still hurts,
I can heal myself.
In the future,
I'll live my life well.
Alright.
Then I'll be responsible
for helping you recover.
Thank you, Zimo.
(Master Jingming's Mansion)
Jingming.
Jingming, come out.
Don't stay silent in the house.
You abandoned your wife and son.
Why can't you face us now?
Come out now!
(Magnanimity)
Jingming and Jiangli are in love,
but unexpectedly,
Jingming will marry
the Grand Princess of Xizhou
to be the Young Prefect.
Forget it.
Since it's come to this,
there's no point in saying more.
Of course, we have to say it.
Come out now!
He abandoned his wife.
If I don't scold him,
everyone will think my family
is full of such cold-hearted men.
I love my wife dearly,
and I'm ashamed of him.
Yao, don't worry.
I will never
be like him.
Come out!
Jingming,
since you've made up your mind,
we will never side with you
lest Jingxing learns from you.
Let's go.
You can keep hiding here.
Shen has already left the city.
It seems Master Jingming
is really determined to marry
the Grand Princess of Xizhou.
Yes. Who would've thought
Master Jingming would be
so shameless?
Master Jingxing and his wife
stood at his door
and scolded him for quite a while,
but the door remained shut,
and he refused to meet them.
If he marries Princess Chuya,
the position of the Young Prefect
will be within his grasp.
Naturally, he won't care
about the criticism.
Yes.
We can't let Princess Chuya
marry Lu Jingming.
Otherwise,
there's nothing to gain for us.
But with the current situation,
I'm afraid it's too late to stop it.
Young Master.
You may leave.
- Yes.
Young Master, something's wrong.
What happened?
There's news from Xizhou.
Wen Du has confessed.
What?
Our spy in Xizhou reported
that Princess Chuya
tortured Wen Du so badly
that he couldn't hold on anymore.
He revealed everything.
He was rescued by his subordinates,
and now they're planning a coup.
This means
Lu Jingming has investigated everything
about the events from five years ago.
I wondered why he's been
so close to Princess Chuya lately.
She's even come to me secretly
multiple times.
So, this was all part of their plot.
This means
the wedding
cannot happen.
Such overwhelming power
is too much for anyone to bear.
If you get something
that's not meant for you,
the only end is
death before you can enjoy it.
Wen Du has rebelled.
My child said the pay was good
if he went to fight in Xizhou.
With the sudden war coming,
he is gone...
Young Master, we're at your command.
Let's go.
Let's go!
(Master Jingming's Mansion)
Jingming.
Are you waiting for me?
On the night before my wedding,
Jingxiu, did you rush over
to congratulate me in advance?
So, this was your plan
to trap me.
This so-called wedding
was just a cover-up.
The goal was to expose
the traitors who betrayed the country.
Jingxiu, are you here tonight
to strike against your own brother?
Oh, I forgot
that this isn't the first time
you'd plotted against your siblings.
What do you mean?
Five years ago,
I led the army to fight
in the Battle of Lingshui.
Master Jingxiu
and General Wen Du of Xizhou
set up an ambush,
and my entire army was wiped out.
The final order from Master Jingxiu
and Wen Du
was to kill everyone
and leave no one alive.
Did you know Shuyu was there too?
I didn't want her to go at the time,
but she insisted.
Shuyu,
come back with me.
(Lu Shuyu, Grand Princess of Dongzhou)
No, Jingxiu.
I'm going to fight with Jingming.
The situation is critical,
and the danger is unpredictable.
You mustn't risk your life.
If it's dangerous, then I must go.
As the Grand Princess of Dongzhou,
I can't retreat even a step.
You might lose your life.
Jingxiu,
let's drink when I win and return.
Go.
Shuyu.
Shuyu!
You killed Shuyu.
You failed to protect our sister.
At this point,
you're still trying
to twist the truth.
Tell me.
What else do you know?
Over the years,
you have been
in cahoots with General Wen Du
of Xizhou
and have instigated many battles
between Dongzhou and Xizhou
and exaggerated the military situation.
Wen Du wanted to amass wealth.
What about you?
Jiangli asked
Wind Pavilion to gather the intel.
They told me
all the military funds you received
were channeled into Jinsheng Bank
and then went through the bank
to several mountain villages.
At first, I was curious,
thinking maybe you were funding bandits.
But I had Qilin Guards
investigate later.
The so-called bandits
were your private troops.
All these years,
I really underestimated you.
That's right.
You know too much,
so I can't let you live.
Guards!
Let's go.
Lu Jingming,
since we're brothers,
surrender.
I might spare your life.
Is that all?
Lu Jingming,
you're overestimating yourself.
You've said it yourself.
I have private troops outside.
Now,
the ones surrounding you
are all my men.
Lu Jingming,
the force behind me is Xizhou,
the strongest military power.
What do you have to fight me with?
You've become close to Chuya,
but now she can't even protect herself.
Master Jingxiu,
General Wen Du has been
executed on the spot.
If you're short on men,
there are 100,000 soldiers
at your border.
The one who should surrender
is you.
Jingxiu,
aren't you going to repent?
Lu Jingming,
was this all part of your plan?
Fine.
You won today.
I'll make sure
the two states never reconcile.
Master Jingming...
Master Jingming.
Tell me.
What's really going on?
To the victor goes the spoils.
I have no words to say.
You...
Father,
Jingxiu orchestrated
this plague incident.
We found horse feed in the medicine.
After an investigation,
we found the coachman
who tampered with the medicine.
He has been arrested.
He confessed to everything
Jingxiu told him to do.
Jingxiu intended to frame Jingming,
but by mistake,
Jiangli ended up taking the blame.
As for what happened just now,
the dare-to-die killers
outside have confessed.
They said Jingxiu's order was
to eliminate everyone
in Jingming's mansion.
Eliminate everyone?
The dare-to-die killers outside
are soldiers from your Golden Guards.
How could you be
so ruthless?
Jingxiu,
you were the man
I admired most in my youth.
I never thought
you'd do this
to your own brother.
Not only that,
but you also disregarded
the lives of the people.
You are beyond saving.
I thought you were simply ambitious,
but now I see you are truly malicious.
I even told Danling before
that you were the only one
in Dongzhou worthy of her.
Alas, she ended up like this
because of me.
When she was still your consort,
she toiled diligently for years for you,
yet you gave her contraceptive medicine,
making her unable to become a mother.
General Wang,
you forced me to do this.
All these years,
you've held military power
and earned great merit.
If Danling had my child,
and you turned against me,
wouldn't that become your leverage?
You overestimate yourself.
You've brought all of this
upon yourself.
What a beast!
Do you know
how many innocent lives were lost
and how many people became homeless
because of what you've done?
Father,
you're a good prefect,
but you're too stuck in your ways.
If all four states agree
to let me be their ruler,
wouldn't that bring peace to the land?
Those are just a few ants.
What do they matter?
You scoundrel!
Are human lives only ants to you?
What makes you think
you can ensure
there will be no more wars?
What makes you think you're capable
of managing all four states?
It's your fault.
You refused to pass the position
of the Prefect to me sooner.
Otherwise, I would've given you
my answer long ago.
Your answer?
Is this the answer you give me?
You accused me
of treating the people's lives as ants.
But what I want is
to end war and suffering
for the people of Dongzhou.
Think about it, Father.
If I become the ruler of four states
and unify the land,
wouldn't that mean an end to war?
To achieve such everlasting glory,
how could there be no bloodshed?
Isn't that right, Father?
For your so-called power,
you've gone mad,
harming innocent people,
even your own siblings.
Guards,
detain Master Jingxiu.
From now on,
he is demoted to a commoner.
He may not leave the mansion anymore.
Father...
- Get up.
- Father...
Father...
Father.
My Lord.
Your Grace, you're here.
Your Grace.
Regarding what's happened
in Dongzhou recently,
it was because I failed to teach my son.
Sorry about this.
Please accept my apology.
Well,
your marriage with Jingming...
My Lord, no need to apologize.
Master Jingming and I are close friends
and never truly intended to marry.
This was all part of the plan.
Rest assured.
I've reported everything to Xizhou.
During my time in Dongzhou,
I've seen what Princess Qingqing
and the masters
have done for the people
and their well-being.
I believe Dongzhou
will surely stand proud
among the four states.
We in Xizhou
have no intention of losing
such a valuable ally.
Aside from the betrothal
between Master Jingming and me,
none of the other terms
will be changed.
Your Grace,
thank you for your understanding.
Are you
about to return to Xizhou?
Yes. I'll depart the day after tomorrow.
After I return,
the terms will be implemented
one by one.
Very well.
Your Grace,
allow me
to wish you a safe journey.
♪The sound of the flute lingers,
making the night more tender♪
♪Stealing a bit of the starry sky,
making the encounter romantic♪
♪The lights fade; the story isn't over♪
♪Let's continue our fate♪
♪A cup of wine
to honor courage and love's trials♪
♪For you, I'd dare to travel,
however long the journey is♪
♪The world's many twists
end in separation♪
♪I can't bear to watch♪
♪This mortal world is full of hardships♪
♪Alas, this fate is full of misfortune♪
♪But I refuse to accept♪
♪That regret is
the only natural outcome♪
♪So, I cross mountains and rivers♪
♪Just to keep you by my side♪
♪The joys and sorrows,
the partings and reunions♪
♪How profound♪
♪Whether it's to part or reunite
is not up to me♪
♪I can't escape fate's pull♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither;
there are always results♪
♪Leaving me no choice♪
♪So, I cross mountains and rivers♪
♪Just to keep you by my side♪
♪The joys and sorrows,
the partings and reunions♪
♪How profound♪
♪Whether it's to part or reunite
is not up to me♪
♪I can't escape fate's pull♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither;
there are always results♪
♪Leaving me no choice♪