♪The gentle breeze leaves no trace♪
♪It stirs the old times♪
♪Love is gained and lost♪
♪Only then does it become unforgettable♪
♪The bamboo leaves
are rustling and falling♪
♪Fate is delayed and scattered♪
♪Only lingering hatred remains♪
♪Echoing♪
♪Old dreams are like illusions♪
♪Alas, the world is too indifferent♪
♪If there were no obsession♪
♪I wouldn't be thinking of someone♪
♪If it's destined to be alone♪
♪Like a snowstorm♪
♪When love and hate dissolve♪
♪Only a long gaze remains♪
♪A drop of tear♪
♪Falls, burning my heart♪
♪We loved without regret♪
=My Destined Consort=
=Episode 23=
Over there.
Those lanterns are so beautiful.
How thoughtful.
I'm glad you like them.
Jiangli spent
several days preparing them.
This is what I should do.
Yao helped a lot too.
What I did was nothing.
It was Jiangli who ran around
taking care of everything.
My daughter helped too.
She also put in a lot of effort.
Seeing my sisters-in-law perform
at the Peace Banquet,
I believe you must've worked hard on it.
It moved me deeply.
So after the lantern event,
I prepared a floral banquet for everyone
to enjoy and appreciate.
A floral banquet?
That's unheard of
in Xizhou.
How wonderful.
Qilan also
ran around
and helped a lot.
Grand Lady, Princess Chuya,
I prepared lotus lanterns for everyone.
We can make wishes together.
Grandmother, it's so delicate.
Yes, yes.
It's so beautiful.
Grand Lady,
I had this made
by the most famous artisan
in Dongzhou.
It's perfect for making wishes.
We can make a wish?
Yes, we can.
I'm done.
I also prepared sky lanterns
for everyone.
We can release them together
to pray for peace in the four states.
That's wonderful.
What is
this lovely fragrance?
Grand Lady, you smelled it?
It's Jiangli's idea.
In Dongzhou,
the sky lanterns carry blessings.
Ordinary sky lanterns
are usually made
from flame-resistant white cotton.
The sky lanterns
Jiangli prepared for you
have different flowers
pressed into them.
Your lantern
has gladioli.
This flower
is strong and resolute like you.
Grandmother, what a beautiful meaning.
This one is for the princess.
It has dendrobium flowers.
They symbolize sharpness and courage,
just like the princess.
They also stand
for auspiciousness and purity.
It's a blessing from Dongzhou
to the princess.
Thank you, Consort Jiangli.
I really like it.
We're glad you like it.
What's wrong?
Princess Chuya, were you burned?
It's nothing serious.
Just a small injury. It's nothing.
And what counts as serious?
Chuya is the princess of Xizhou.
Is this...
Is this how Dongzhou treats its guests?
Shen Jiangli,
look at the trouble you've caused.
Guards,
take her away.
Confine her to the Prefect's Mansion
for punishment.
See?
You just said it was fine.
I saw that the consort
didn't do it on purpose.
You're the princess of Xizhou.
You represent Xizhou.
If we just let this go,
outsiders will think
Xizhou is easy to push around.
So,
whether it was intentional or not,
we must be serious about it.
Understood.
My Lady, Your Grace,
Consort Qilan requests an audience.
Grandmother,
why do you think she's here?
It must be about the rivalry
among consorts.
Be smart.
Don't get yourself entangled.
Sit first.
Your Grace,
I'm here today
to plead for my sister.
Sister?
You may not know.
Consort Jiangli
is not only my sister-in-law,
but we also share a father.
She can be
careless at times,
but she means no harm.
However, at the lantern event today,
I truly don't know why
everyone's lanterns were fine,
except for yours.
If not for your quick reflexes,
it would've seriously hurt you.
I believe
Jiangli didn't do it on purpose.
I hope you can
show her mercy.
Mercy?
I never said she'd be punished.
Your Grace, you're here
as a symbol of harmony
between our two states.
As Jiangli has hurt you,
she'll surely be punished.
Your Grace,
please plead for her before the Prefect.
This is your internal affairs.
I believe Lady Wang and the Prefect
will know what to do
with this.
You're right.
You are Consort Qilan?
Who is your husband then?
Lu Jingxiu, the Prefect's eldest son.
How old is he this year?
How tall is he?
What does he look like?
Has he been to Xizhou?
Your Grace, why are you asking this?
I'm just asking out of curiosity.
It's nothing.
Men from Xizhou are different
from yours in Dongzhou,
especially the Prefect's sons.
They must be extraordinary.
Tell me more about him.
Sure.
My husband...
Young Master,
I have something to report.
What is it?
The man in black who was tailing you
during the siege at Lingshui
showed up recently in Dongzhou,
but our men lost him.
Dongzhou?
Could it be
someone in Dongzhou has been
colluding with Xizhou all along?
Bad news!
Why in such a panic?
Consort Jiangli held
a lotus lantern event,
and Princess Chuya was burned.
She's now confined.
What?
Father.
Jingming,
why the rush?
Father,
I heard
about Princess Chuya being burned.
I believe
something's fishy about it.
Please
don't punish Jiangli for now.
No need to plead for her.
Father,
you...
I already let her go.
Before you arrived,
Princess Chuya
sent word saying
that she believed Jiangli
didn't mean any harm
and that her injury wasn't serious.
She didn't want to make
a big deal out of it.
It seems Princess Chuya
is quite magnanimous.
Thank you, Father.
Then
I'll take my leave.
Sure, go ahead.
You...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Why are you suddenly back?
I heard about the lantern event
and rushed back overnight.
Then you should rest well tonight.
Are you still thinking
about the lantern event?
White phosphorus?
Its ignition temperature
is extremely low,
and it ignites easily in air.
To be safe,
the culprit behind it
must've acted on the spot
instead of spreading it in advance.
They had access to the lanterns
and could attend the event.
It's not hard to guess who it is.
We have to make the enemy hurt.
Let's find evidence first.
Master Jingming,
the princess invites you
to the post house
for a meeting.
You've met the princess before?
Never.
Forge tit.
If she's asked to see you,
it must be important.
As for today's matter,
please thank her on my behalf.
Don't worry. I will.
Then wait here for me to return.
Don't worry.
- Let's go.
- Please.
Grandmother,
try this osmanthus cake.
Alright.
Chuya,
you look quite pleased today.
Did something good happen?
I believe
I've found the one who saved my life.
Who is it?
That day,
I saw someone
who looked just like him.
I believe
it must be him.
He looked extraordinary
and moved freely
within the Prefect's Mansion.
He must be
the Prefect's son.
The Prefect of Dongzhou
has three sons.
Which one is it?
His third son, Lu Jingxing,
was still very young five years ago.
Yesterday,
I also asked Consort Qilan
about his eldest son, Lu Jingxiu.
It didn't match.
So,
it must be...
Master Jingming is here.
In that case,
you two should talk properly.
Master Jingming.
Your Grace.
I came today
to thank you for speaking
on my wife's behalf.
Master Jingming, please sit.
I know
she didn't mean to hurt me.
But I pleaded for her
not just for her sake
but for yours.
For me?
I wanted you to come and thank me.
You don't remember me?
Five years ago,
on our border...
You want us to be rough, huh?
Get her!
(Five years ago)
Get lost!
Let's go.
Miss, where do you live?
This area is unstable.
Bandits often pass through.
You should head home soon.
Thank you for saving me.
I haven't asked your name yet.
I'm just an ordinary soldier
of Dongzhou.
You needn't keep it
in your heart.
But how will I find you again?
We don't need to meet again.
If peace comes between our two states,
countless people like us will meet.
It's you.
I never thought
you'd be the princess of Xizhou.
Nor did I expect
you'd be a master of Dongzhou.
After returning to Xizhou,
I sent people to search for you,
but I never found any trace.
Not long after that,
the Battle of Lingshui
broke out between our states.
Xizhou
sent General Wen Du.
And Dongzhou's troops
were ambushed
while pursuing him.
Our forces were wiped out,
and I
was gravely injured
and withdrew from the battlefield.
Wen Du
is a high official of Xizhou.
He's always been pro-war.
I remember
it was Dongzhou
who started the battle at Lingshui,
and he immediately led troops
to fight back.
So, he was
against my peace mission this time.
What do you mean, Your Grace?
It was Xizhou
who provoked the war,
and Dongzhou only responded.
Was it not Dongzhou
who started the fire first,
burning a whole village on our border?
It was because Xizhou first captured
over 100 hostages from our border.
What is going on here?
All these years,
I've felt there was something strange
about the Battle of Lingshui.
Since then,
Jingxiu has led
all battles between us.
I've counted.
There were
five major wars
and over a dozen
skirmishes.
Yet all those combined
didn't cause as many casualties
as the Battle of Lingshui alone.
Why is that?
Now it seems
someone was behind this.
I'll send people to investigate again
in Xizhou.
Good.
I'll look into things here
in Dongzhou as well.
Lu Jingming,
if you need my help,
just come and find me.
Thank you, Your Grace.
(Ride with Wind)
Why not stay longer, Grand Lady?
You can enjoy the sights of Dongzhou.
I do enjoy
the scenery here,
but there are things to do in Xizhou.
I dare not linger.
In that case,
I'll say goodbye to you both here.
My Lord,
I won't return with Grandmother.
I can't control her anymore.
My Lord, I'll leave her to your care.
Sure.
Since you want to stay,
you must have unfinished matters.
If you need assistance,
just let me know.
I'll do my utmost to help.
Thank you, My Lord.
I wish to stay and seek a husband.
A husband?
Sorry, My Lord.
She's been spoiled by me
since childhood.
She's headstrong
and unruly.
However,
I believe
if the two states form ties by marriage,
it would benefit both sides.
But I only have three sons,
and all of them are married.
The princess is of noble birth.
Well...
My Lord,
if I truly like someone,
I don't care about their background
or their marital status.
I just want to stay
and have a look first.
As for whether the two states
can be joined through marriage,
we'll see if any Dongzhou men
can catch my eye.
Very well.
Please take care of her.
You're too kind, Grand Lady.
The princess is a distinguished guest.
Please rest assured, Grand Lady.
See?
The Prefect treats you well.
Don't always throw a tantrum
and bother him.
Got it, Grandmother.
Mother.
We were so close.
If peace between the two states
is ruined because of Shen Jiangli,
she'll have to die.
It's too bad
that Princess Chuya
was only lightly injured,
and Shen Jiangli
got off unscathed.
Qilan.
Master Jingming.
- Qilan.
- You're here.
I heard the princess of Xizhou
was hurt at the lantern event.
Did you do this?
I knew nothing of it.
How would I dare interfere
in matters between two states?
Master Jingming,
do you suspect me?
How could I suspect you?
You're kind and clever.
I trust you the most.
Then why do you
look so troubled?
Yesterday,
I heard Jingming and Princess Chuya
stayed at the post house
for quite a while.
And today,
Princess Chuya reported to Father
that she wants to seek a husband here.
Who is your husband then?
How old is he this year?
How tall is he?
What does he look like?
Has he been to Xizhou?
He must be quite impressive.
Tell me more.
(Is she interested in Master Jingxiu?)
(I'd better stay away from her.)
If Jingming gets close
to Princess Chuya,
Father will surely hold him
in higher regard.
Then Jingming will have
the upper hand again.
I must stir up some trouble
for him.
Don't worry, Master Jingxiu.
I'll take care of it.
(Just as Master Jingming suspected,)
(there was something wrong)
(with the Battle of Lingshui.)
Mentor!
What's wrong?
Another nightmare?
Maybe it's because of the visit
from Xizhou.
It brought back some memories,
so now I feel a bit unsettled.
Let the past go.
Try to sleep.
I'll always be here with you.
- Mother.
- You're here.
Mother.
Sit down.
- Come on.
You've probably heard of it.
Princess Chuya is staying here
to find a husband.
Yes, I heard.
The Prefect has instructed
you two to look after her.
She's of noble status.
You must protect her.
Do not let any negligence
harm the relationship
between our two states.
I understand.
In my view,
Qilan should be the one
to host the princess.
After all,
at the lantern event last time,
Jiangli hurt the princess.
I'm afraid the princess
might hold a grudge
if she sees Jiangli.
Jinyi,
the princess may not be that petty.
Besides, this hasn't been settled.
How can you blame Jiangli so quickly?
You can't just blame her
whenever something goes wrong.
Xiulan,
I was only making a suggestion.
Why are you getting so defensive?
Mother.
Lady Shu.
I should be the one
to host the princess,
but I've been
feeling unwell lately.
I've caught a chill these days.
I'm afraid I can't manage.
Has the private physician checked?
Yes.
He told me to rest in bed.
Then you should rest properly.
Jiangli, you will take charge
of looking after the princess.
Yes. I'll see to it.
Very well.
Handle it properly this time.
Consider it a chance
to make up for your mistake.
Jiangli.
Jiangli,
I've looked into everything
you asked.
Muxiang and Shuixiang were
in charge of the lantern event,
but I found nothing suspicious
about them.
But white phosphorus
wouldn't appear in lanterns
for no reason,
and it just happened to be
in the princess's lantern.
Yulan, keep digging.
Yes, Jiangli.
Why are your hands so cold?
I was so caught up talking
that I didn't notice.
Were you discussing the lantern event?
There's still no progress.
Don't worry.
Everything leaves traces.
The one behind it won't escape.
By the way,
when Lady Wang and Lady Shu
asked me and Qilan
to look after the princess,
she...
Is something wrong?
Ever since Ms. Zou passed,
Qilan has competed with me
over everything.
But this time, when Lady Wang
asked her to take charge,
she claimed to be ill and refused.
I feel something's off.
You're right
to be cautious.
Just pay more attention.
However,
the princess
isn't hard to get along with.
You just need to treat her with respect.
You speak
as if you know her well.
It's a coincidence.
Five years ago,
on our border,
she was attacked by bandits.
I happened to pass by and saved her.
So, we met once.
The princess
is staying here to find a husband.
Does she already have someone in mind?
It's not you, is it?
Don't worry.
In this life,
I only love you.
Have some tea, Consort Jiangli.
You too.
(Liuyun Post House)
Your Grace,
you're our honored guest,
so I prepared
this poetic banquet for you.
How thoughtful.
I really like it.
What's this smell?
There is
a light fruity fragrance.
I made it myself.
It's the pear fragrance.
If you like it,
I can have more sent to you
and you can take it back to Xizhou.
Thank you, Consort Jiangli.
You must know
I stayed here
to seek a husband.
But the noblemen who've sent
their visiting cards these days
are quite disappointing.
No need to rush, Your Grace.
Marriage is a major life decision.
It's not just about family background
or education.
Character and personality matter more.
Whether you love each other
and can get along
for the rest of your life
is more important.
You're right.
Your Grace,
what kind of man do you like?
Maybe I can help keep an eye out.
Naturally, someone handsome,
elegant,
and manly,
like
Master Jingming.
Your Grace,
I heard
you and Jingming knew each other
from before.
Five years ago,
on the border of Dongzhou,
he once saved me.
This time, I came to Dongzhou
to find him
and express my gratitude.
There's no need, Princess.
Your identity as the princess
of Xizhou doesn't matter.
Jingming would
help anyone in danger.
Yes.
That's what makes him so special.
Truly unforgettable.
If only
I could have a husband like him.
You're so cool and sincere.
You'll surely find someone you like.
Your Grace, please enjoy your meal.
I'll take my leave.
I'll walk you out.
(Liuyun Post House)
Please stay, Your Grace.
What are you doing here?
The timing seemed about right,
so I came to take you home.
Greetings, Master Jingming.
Your Grace.
We'll head back now.
Master Jingming.
Wait.
There's something I'd like to discuss.
What is it, Your Grace?
You asked me to look into something,
and I've received a reply.
I'd like to talk in detail,
but
there are too many people here.
This is not a good place.
Master Jingming,
please come inside with me.
I need to talk with the princess.
Let Yunjiu escort you home first, okay?
Do I need to wait for you?
No need.
I'll be home once I'm done.
Yunjiu.
Master Jingming, this way.
Please.
(Liuyun Post House)
My Lady?
Let's head back.
Master Jingming, have a seat.
We've found him.
A lieutenant under Wen Du's command.
(To Grand Princess)
He confessed to inciting conflict
between the two states.
Can a mere lieutenant
have such power?
According to his statement,
he's a spy from Nanzhou
planted in Xizhou.
Everything he did
was to drain the strength
and resources of Dongzhou and Xizhou,
so Nanzhou could grow its power
while the two of us were fighting.
Your Grace,
do you believe him?
Do you think
there's more to it?
When we searched his home,
we found forged letters of challenge
and letters of close contact
with Nanzhou.
I don't think it's so simple.
The war records
start
from the Battle of Lingshui.
What does that mean?
Before that,
Dongzhou and Xizhou
had fought over 20 battles,
yet none were recorded,
and the reports start exactly
from the Battle of Lingshui.
Besides,
in that battle,
our forces were equal in strength.
Why was Dongzhou's army
completely wiped out in the end?
Are you saying
someone wanted us to see those reports
to mislead us?
Perhaps
someone leaked my strategies
to Wen Du in advance.
Or perhaps
they set up
that entire battle for me.
They wanted me
to die there.
They just didn't expect me
to survive.
But my men
interrogated Wen Du
about the Battle of Lingshui.
He only said
that all was fair in war
and that you acted recklessly
out of ambition
so you fell into his trap.
If what you said is true
and Wen Du knew your strategy
in advance,
then someone in your army
must have betrayed you.
Think carefully.
Was there
anyone suspicious?
I don't know.
Could it really be
that the Battle of Lingshui
was my mistake for being headstrong?
I know
you've never let go
of what happened back then.
But I believe
the soldiers who died
wouldn't want to see you
living in sorrow.
I hope
you can still be
the brightest young general
in the four states.
I'll do everything I can
to help you uncover the truth.
If someone really framed you,
I won't let them go.
Thank you, Your Grace.
I'll take my leave.
You can just call me Chuya.
(Liuyun Post House)
By the way, Yunyi,
any new leads
on that man in black?
Young Master,
none of our men
have found anything.
It's like he vanished into thin air.
Keep watching
Jingxiu's mansion.
Yes.
(Liuyun Post House)
Mother.
Qilan.
How's your health now?
Do you feel better now?
No need to worry, Mother.
I've gotten much better.
I just need a few more days of rest.
Once you recover,
go visit the princess more often.
Don't let Shen Jiangli
hog all the attention.
Others might think
we lack manners.
Besides,
you already know
why Chuya stayed here.
Yes, Mother.
She's looking for a husband.
Good.
Sit down.
You often stay in the inner chambers,
so you may not know
about the situation in Xizhou.
Chuya is the late Prefect's
eldest daughter.
Now,
her younger brother is the Prefect.
He's only seven years old.
So, Chuya and the Grand Lady are helping
with state affairs in Xizhou.
Chuya's status is extremely noble.
Though she says
she doesn't care
about status or background
when choosing her husband,
not just anyone
can match her.
Even if Chuya likes someone,
Xizhou might not agree.
So, I've been thinking.
Is there anyone in Dongzhou
worthy of marrying her,
the Grand Princess of Xizhou?
I don't know.
Of course, you do.
It's obvious.
Look. Jingxiu
is the Prefect's lineal eldest son.
His status matches Chuya's.
Chuya is helping
with state affairs in Xizhou.
She must be magnanimous
and sensible.
Jingxiu
has been in court for years,
helping the Prefect with state affairs.
Their experiences
are remarkably alike.
Mother, are you suggesting
the princess marry
Master Jingxiu?
See?
Qilan, you're so clever.
Of course,
this would be unfair to you.
But I'll talk to Jingxiu.
You'll still be his wife.
I understand.
I come from humble origins.
As long as I can help Master Jingxiu,
I'll do whatever it takes.
Good.
Jingxiu is the Prefect's
lineal eldest son.
His status is too high
for him to court Chuya personally.
So,
I hope
you can help them meet more often
so they can
grow closer.
I understand.
Alright.
Go back to get some rest.
Please rest early, Mother.
I'll take my leave.
My Lady,
will Consort Qilan
help Master Jingxiu marry the princess?
If she knows her place,
she should understand
that she'll rise and fall
along with Jingxiu.
Why would she be upset about it?
♪The sound of the flute lingers,
making the night more tender♪
♪Stealing a bit of the starry sky,
making the encounter romantic♪
♪The lights fade; the story isn't over♪
♪Let's continue our fate♪
♪A cup of wine
to honor courage and love's trials♪
♪For you, I'd dare to travel,
however long the journey is♪
♪The world's many twists
end in separation♪
♪I can't bear to watch♪
♪This mortal world is full of hardships♪
♪Alas, this fate is full of misfortune♪
♪But I refuse to accept♪
♪That regret is
the only natural outcome♪
♪So, I cross mountains and rivers♪
♪Just to keep you by my side♪
♪The joys and sorrows,
the partings and reunions♪
♪How profound♪
♪Whether it's to part or reunite
is not up to me♪
♪I can't escape fate's pull♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither;
there are always results♪
♪Leaving me no choice♪
♪So, I cross mountains and rivers♪
♪Just to keep you by my side♪
♪The joys and sorrows,
the partings and reunions♪
♪How profound♪
♪Whether it's to part or reunite
is not up to me♪
♪I can't escape fate's pull♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither;
there are always results♪
♪Leaving me no choice♪