[After the break, everyone gathers back together]
[What kind of person are you?
Tell the BI-LIVE members about the real you]
You can reveal your age and what you do.
[Jinwoo: Wow, finally!]
[Oh!]
[Hyeyeon: Like this? Right now?]
[Jinwoo: Exactly. We need to liven things up.]
[Yongkyu: We don't have to.
It never said we had to.]
[Jinwoo: Since we're here, let's just do it.]
[Yongkyu: Wait, did you just switch
to casual speech with me?]
[Hyeyeon: Then we'll just treat you as the youngest.]
-Right now? -Then we'll treat you as the youngest.
If someone refuses to reveal their age?
[Yongkyu: Oh, if someone refuses
to reveal it?]
[Yongkyu: Oh, if someone refuses to reveal it ?]
[Wouldn't that be better?]
[Yongkyu: That's actually better.
Feels like a plot twist.]
[Yongkyu: From the oldest to the youngest.]
[Seungho: How old is everyone,
and what do they do?]
[Chaebe: Finally, we can clear things up.]
[Jinwoo: But the one I was most curious
about and had been waiting for]
[Jinwoo: was Seungho's profile.]
[Sighs]
[Heejin: No one]
[Heejin: really caught my attention at that time.]
[Heejin: To be honest, I was not curious.]
[Chaebe: So, who goes first?]
[Jinwoo: Who's starting?]
[Should we go like this?]
[Ah, I don't want to go last.]
[Huh?]
[Yongkyu: Why did you say that?]
[Yongkyu: Why?]
[Jinwoo: This works, too.]
[Heejin: This works, too.]
[Hyeyeon: Why?]
[Yongkyu: Why?]
[Jinwoo: I respect your decision.
I respect your decision.]
[Sujin: It's okay.]
[Seungho: Is there a problem?]
[Sujin: No, really, it's fine.
It's up to you.]
[Hyeyeon: Whatever you're comfortable with,
but the rest of us want to go last.]
[Seungho: I'll go first.]
-I'll go first. -Okay.
[Seungho: I'd rather go first than last.]
[Seungho: It was less stressful for me.]
[Seungho:So I volunteered to go first.]
[Sujin: Oh, how about we guess first?]
-Okay, let's guess. -Alright, let's guess.
[Yongkyu: Alright, let's guess.]
[Chaebe: Then let's guess!]
[Jinwoo: Listen to our guesses first,
then tell us if we got it right.]
[Hyeyeon: Make a serious guess.]
[Sujin: Let's start with his job.]
[Chaebe: Aren't you an idol trainee?]
[Sujin: A trainee?
That's the only thing I can think of, too.]
[Chaebe: An idol trainee.]
[Jinwoo: After talking to him, I also think]
[Jinwoo: he seems like someone in the arts or sports.]
[Hyeyeon: Is he a teaching assistant at an art college?]
[Sujin: A TA at an art college?]
[Jinwoo: Wait, didn't you guys talk a lot
on your date?]
[Hyeyeon: Why does everyone look so confused?]
[Jinwoo: Right, exactly.]
An instructor?
[Yongkyu: I think he is a college student.]
[Jinwoo: A college student?]
[Hyeyeon: A college student?]
Yeah.
[I think he's a TA at an art college.]
[Class of '26?] [Class of '26.]
-Class of '26? -I think he's a TA at an art college.
-Class of '26? -Class of '26.
[Sujin: 21? Wait, how old is he in his twenties?]
[Jinwoo: If he's class of '26,]
-It's currently 2026. -he'd be 20 years old.
[Jinwoo: He'd be 20. 20 years old.]
[Jinwoo: '07?]
So he was born in '07?
He looks 21 years old to me, not 20.
[Sujin: He looks 21 years old to me.]
[I also think 21.]
-Same here. 21. -21.
[Hyeyeon: I guess 22.]
-I guess 22. -22.
[Did anyone get it right?]
[Did anyone get it right?] [Yes.]
[Seungho: Someone got it right.
There's a correct answer.]
[Jinwoo: Oh, then...]
[Chaebe: Please reveal it!]
[Jinwoo: I'm positive he's the youngest.]
[Jinwoo: Honestly,
age doesn't really matter to me,]
[Jinwoo: as long as he's not too young,
like born in '06 or '07.]
[Seungho: First off, I was born in '06.
I'm 21 in Korean age.]
[Shocked]
[Seungho: As for my job, until recently]
[Seungho: I was still an idol trainee.]
[Gasp!]
[Gasp!] [I knew it!]
[Seungho: I even went on an idol survival show.]
[Seungho: It hasn't been long
since I quit it.]
[Seungho: I'm figuring out my next step,
and I've gotten interested in e-commerce.]
[Seungho: My sister is going
to open an online store, so]
[Seungho: I'll probably launch
a men's clothing shop with her.]
-Launch a men's clothing shop. -Together.
[Chaebe: Amazing.]
[Jinwoo: Born in '06.]
[Chaebe: No wonder he's so handsome.]
[Sujin: Then both guesses were right.
The age was right, too.]
[Sujin: Both guesses were right.
[Seungho: Yes, exactly.]
[Sujin: And we even got his old job right.]
[Seungho: It's amazing.]
[Hyeyeon: It really is amazing.]
[Hyeyeon: I used to think being young]
[Hyeyeon: might be a dealbreaker.]
[Hyeyeon: But after spending some time with Seungho,]
[Hyeyeon: I realized age isn't an issue at all.]
[Hyeyeon: Because when I first started liking him,]
[Hyeyeon: I could tell right away
that he was young.]
[Jinwoo: First, regarding his career,]
[Jinwoo: he looks so much like an idol.]
[Jinwoo: So I already had a hunch.
And for his age,]
[Jinwoo: I was hoping he'd be]
[Jinwoo: within three years of my age.]
[Jinwoo: I am a bit pressured now.]
[Jinwoo: But I'm still not giving up on my feelings.]
[Yongkyu: I was most interested in Seungho,
and I hoped he'd be a bit older.]
[Yongkyu: But his actual age matched my guess.]
[Yongkyu: My interest in him
didn't decrease by much,]
[Yongkyu: but it did drop a little.]
[Jinwoo: Born in '06.]
[Chaebe: Next.]
[Sujin: Let's guess! We have to guess.]
[Jinwoo: Why aren't we guessing?]
[Sujin: We have to guess.]
[Hyeyeon: A chef! A chef!]
[Hyeyeon: Or maybe a dental hygienist?]
[Sujin: A dental hygienist?]
[Hyeyeon: I just picked the job
that suits him the least.]
[Heejin: I think he's a hair designer.]
[Yongkyu: A hair designer?]
[Hyeyeon: Feels like he works at a barbershop.]
[Seungho: I'm thinking a tattooist?]
[Sujin: Oh, right,
I also think he is a tattooist.]
[Jinwoo: The food industry?]
[Jinwoo: Because he always]
[Jinwoo: keeps bringing up cooking.]
[Hyeyeon: He kept saying he
doesn't want to be the main chef anymore.]
[Jinwoo: Right, because he's tired of it.]
[Hyeyeon: Even here...]
[Jinwoo: He's totally over it.]
-Yeah, he's totally over it. -Make sense.
[Hyeyeon: Make sense.]
[Yongkyu: What about age?
I'm curious to hear your thoughts on it.]
[Jinwoo: Age?]
[Yongkyu: Be honest, I can take it.]
[Jinwoo: Totally honest?]
[Hyeyeon: How honest can we get?]
[Yongkyu: I wasn't born in the 80s.]
[Jinwoo: Oh, you're not born in the 80s.]
[Hyeyeon: If you were born in 1990,
how old would you be?]
[Hyeyeon: 37?]
[Yongkyu: 37?]
Someone born in 1990 would be 37, right?
[Hyeyeon: Someone born in 1990 would be 37, right?]
Right now? Not quite yet.
[Yongkyu: 36?]
[Seungho: Yeah, 37 is right.]
[Yongkyu: Are we counting Korean age or actual age?]
[Hyeyeon: No, just Korean age.]
[Jinwoo: No, not actual age.]
[Chaebe: Let's stick to Korean age then.]
-Korean age. -American age, American age.
[Yongkyu: American age.]
-Why do you keep doing this? -Born in '96?
[Born in '96?]
I'm thinking '95 or '96.
[Hyeyeon: I think he just turned 33.]
[Yongkyu: '94?]
['94?]
['94? Correct!]
[33?] ['94? Correct!]
[Spot on!] [Correct, born in '94.]
[Jinwoo: Born in '94?]
-Born in '94? -Yes.
[Yongkyu: Born in '94, food industry.]
[Jinwoo: Oh, really? See, I told you!]
[Hyeyeon: I got it right too.
Why did you only point at him?]
[Yongkyu: Well, getting both right
by yourself is a bit much.]
[Jinwoo: I said from the start
he was in the food industry.]
[Hyeyeon: It suits you. Make sense.]
[Sujin: It suits you. Make sense.]
[Hyeyeon: He looked so anxious
watching us cook the whole time.]
[Heejin: Now I'm kind of embarrassed.]
[Heejin: I cooked right next to him.
It's so embarrassing.]
[Jinwoo: What kind of cuisine do you make?]
[Yongkyu: I do Korean food.
I used to run a gimbap place.]
[Sujin: It must be delicious.
He must be amazing at rolling gimbap.]
[Yongkyu: Exactly.]
[Hyeyeon: Please make some for us.]
[Seungho: Can we hold the cucumber?]
[Yongkyu: I don't do cucumbers.]
[Ah, really?]
[Seungho: Can we hold the cucumber?]
[Yongkyu: I don't do cucumbers.]
[Heejin: I'm literally obsessed with gimbap.]
[Chaebe: Seungho and Yongkyu
have a 12-year age gap.]
[Chaebe: I was so happy, woohoo!]
[Seungho: He's older than I thought.
I was a bit surprised.]
[Seungho: He looks pretty young
for his age.]
[Seungho: But I never pictured myself
with someone 12 years older than me.]
[Seungho: Dating might be a little tough.]
[Sujin: Yongkyu sent me a message on SBM Talk.]
[Sujin: I appreciate the gesture,]
[Sujin: but the age difference
is a bit much for me.]
[Sujin: I'm rooting for him, though.]
[Hyeyeon: My turn.]
[Chaebe: An influencer?]
[Jinwoo: Are you a beauty blogger or something?]
[Hyeyeon: Really? Wow, you guys
think so highly of me.]
[Yongkyu: A YouTuber?]
[Hyeyeon: That's a huge compliment. A YouTuber?]
[Hyeyeon: Could be, could not be.]
[Yongkyu: Finance.]
[Hyeyeon: Back at it with the least fitting jobs?]
[Hyeyeon: You all put me in that category.]
[Seungho: I have no clue.]
[Sujin: Let's guess her age first.]
[Jinwoo: Age?]
[Sujin: '01?]
[Hyeyeon: If '01, that makes me 26?]
[Yongkyu: I'm thinking ‘00.]
[Hyeyeon: If '00, then 2...]
[Jinwoo: 27. '00 makes you 27.]
[Right?]
[Right?] [23?]
23.
[Hyeyeon: You sure I'm 23?]
[Chaebe: Yep.]
[Hyeyeon: My job is...]
[Hyeyeon: Job? I...]
[Hyeyeon: I majored in fashion design
in college, and after graduating,]
[Hyeyeon: I'm launching my own fashion brand.]
[Hyeyeon: And,]
[Hyeyeon: I also run my own Instagram account.]
[Chaebe: I knew it!]
[Hyeyeon: Oh, and my age.]
[Hyeyeon: I was born in '02.
I'm 25 years old.]
[Jinwoo: Oh, you were born in '02.]
[Seungho: '02.]
[Chaebe: Wait, how old is she again?]
[Jinwoo: 25.]
[Chaebe: 25.]
[Hyeyeon: Thanks for thinking I was younger.]
[Hyeyeon: I'll return the favor.]
[Yongkyu: Born in '02...]
[Hyeyeon: What's wrong?]
[Yongkyu: Nothing, nothing.]
[Seungho: As long as she's not younger than me,
I'm good.]
[Seungho: Her career path is super similar
to what I want to do.]
[Seungho: We might vibe well.]
[Jinwoo: In a way, Hyeyeon and I work in]
[Jinwoo: the same field, so]
[Jinwoo: I didn't think revealing her job
gave her an edge.]
[Jinwoo: But she's way younger than me.]
[Jinwoo: I'm pretty jealous.]
[Eunchae: When we talked about age,
I felt like we were peers before.]
[Eunchae: Turns out I was right.]
[Eunchae: She said she's working hard
on her Instagram account.]
[Eunchae: I called it. It suits her, totally.]
[Hyeyeon: Eunchae.]
[Jinwoo: Eunchae.]
[Hyeyeon: Eunchae is 23 years old.]
[Chaebe: I'm thinking 20.]
[Jinwoo: Eunchae is 20 years old?]
[Seungho: Younger than me?]
-22. -Younger than me?
[Jinwoo: She really has that super young vibe.]
[Hyeyeon: But after going on a date
with her today, I kind of doubt it.]
Oh yeah?
[Jinwoo: Does she seem mature?]
[Hyeyeon: A little bit?]
[Hyeyeon: 22?]
[Jinwoo: Probably born in '04 or '05.]
[Hyeyeon: '04 or '05?]
[Eunchae: What about my job?]
[Jinwoo: I bet she's in cosmetics or beauty.]
[Heejin: Hair designer?]
[Jinwoo: She did an amazing job
styling Chaebe's hair last time.]
[Heejin: No, makeup artist.]
Yongkyu: I think she's a fashion e-commerce model.]
[Chaebe: Totally, I agree.]
[Jinwoo: Ah, e-commerce model.]
[Chaebe: Fashion industry, fashion industry.]
-E-commerce model. -E-commerce model.
[Sujin: It totally fits her.]
[Heejin: I'm thinking a beauty salon.]
[Eunchae: It's always these industries.]
Yep.
[Hyeyeon: Because you're so good at styling yourself.]
[Sujin: After all those guesses,
watch her be a nurse.]
A nurse.
[Hyeyeon: She's a kindergarten teacher.]
[Eunchae: That would be a disaster.]
[Hyeyeon: Come here, kids.]
[Eunchae: Oh, first of all,]
[Eunchae: I was born in '05, so I'm 22.]
[Nailed it.]
[Eunchae: And my job is...]
[Eunchae: Right now, I'm a freelance model.]
[Heejin: See?]
[Chaebe: She really is a model.]
[Jinwoo: She has such a model look.]
[Heejin doesn't look too happy]
[Heejin: The reason my mood kept dropping was]
[Heejin: that I mentioned before
that I wanted to date]
[Heejin: Seungho and Eunchae next.]
[Heejin: But they are incredibly young.]
[Heejin: Finding out their ages really bummed me out.]
[Heejin's turn]
[Yongkyu: I'm guessing '94.]
I'm guessing.
[Heejin: Stop playing.]
[Jinwoo: That's too much.]
[Yongkyu: Born in '94.]
That's too much.
[Hyeyeon: I'm thinking '99, too.]
[Sujin: Same, '99.]
[Seungho: I say '98.]
[Jinwoo: '98 or '99 maybe?]
[Yongkyu: '97.]
[Jinwoo: '97 or '96?]
[Heejin: He always...]
[Heejin: Oh, seriously.]
[Hyeyeon: Suddenly, we're in the 90s.]
'99.
[Chaebe: I think she's a teacher.]
[Heejin: A teacher?]
Yeah.
[Oh...]
[Oh...] [Oh, kind of...]
A teacher.
[Chaebe: Leader energy.]
[Jinwoo: Ah, a commanding beauty.]
[No.]
[Chaebe: Leader energy.]
[Jinwoo: Ah, a commanding beauty.]
[Hyeyeon: Oh, because she takes
such good care of her body.]
[A PT?]
[A PT?] [Shake head]
[Yongkyu: Oh, a pharmacist? A pharmacist?]
[Hyeyeon: She really suits it.]
-She really suits it. -A pharmacist.
[Heejin: You guys are way off.]
[Sujin: Feels like UI/UX design.]
[Eunchae: Are you in design?]
[Hyeyeon: That was a sudden switch.]
[Eunchae: Really?]
[Yongkyu: Has she revealed her age yet?]
[Hyeyeon: No, not yet. Ah, we...]
[Yongkyu: Did anyone get it right?]
[Heejin: No, not even close.]
-Nobody got it? -Nope.
[Jinwoo: Wait, was she really
not born in the 2000s?]
'01.
[Eunchae: Look how happy she is.
She must be a 90s baby.]
‘00.
[Right in the feels]
Looks like she's a 90s baby.
[Ah, seriously, what is wrong with her!]
-That really stung, huh? -What's with her?
[That really stung, huh?]
[All smiles.]
[Yongkyu: Are you older than me?]
[Heejin: Ah, come on.]
[Chaebe: Aren't you an '00? '00?]
[Heejin: Should I just say my age first?]
[Okay.] [Okay.]
[Heejin: I was born in '96.]
[Chaebe: I got it right!]
[Hyeyeon: So that makes you 31?]
[Yongkyu: Don't do the math.]
Wait, no?
[Heejin: I'm in graphic design.]
[Heejin: I majored in art, graduated from art school,
and it's been a while since I graduated.]
[Eunchae: I got it right!]
[Yongkyu: Got it.]
[Eunchae: Whoa.]
[Eunchae, you just said I was way off.]
-Graphic design. -Eunchae.
[Eunchae: You just said I was way off.]
[Hyeyeon: Ah, my bad.]
[Eunchae: I got it right.]
[Hyeyeon: Because you suddenly lost your confidence.]
[Heejin: I've been studying textile design.]
[Chaebe: Wow, you were born in '96.]
[Heejin: I'm a graphic designer.]
[Plot twist.] [Plot twist.] [Plot twist.]
[Chaebe: Impressive.]
[Shy]
[Heejin: Yeah...]
[Hyeyeon: Heejin shocked me the most because]
[Hyeyeon: she's older than I thought.]
[Hyeyeon: She's the second oldest here.]
[Hyeyeon: It was a total surprise.]
[Eunchae: I never thought she was that old.]
[Eunchae: I was a bit shocked to learn her age.]
[Eunchae: She said she's a graphic designer.]
[Eunchae: I actually took design exams, too.]
[Eunchae: Having that in common]
[Eunchae: is pretty cool.]
[Hyeyeon: Next up is Chaebe.]
[Jinwoo: Chaebe.]
[Hyeyeon: 23?]
[Oh!]
[Yongkyu: What?]
[Hyeyeon: I got a compliment,
so I had to give one back.]
[Chaebe: He's genuinely speechless.]
[Heejin: This feels hard.]
[Jinwoo: I'd guess Chaebe is a '99.]
[Hyeyeon: Oh, he totally does.]
['98.]
[Jinwoo: I'd guess Chaebe is a '99.]
[Hyeyeon: Oh, he totally does.]
-'98. -Yeah, total '99 vibes.
[Jinwoo: Yeah, total '99 vibes.]
[Seungho: I'm guessing '99, too.]
[Jinwoo: He gives off '99 vibes.]
[Chaebe: Really?]
[Sujin: '99 vibes?]
-Total '99 vibes. -'99 vibes?
[Jinwoo: Total '99 vibes.]
[Pigeon?]
[Jinwoo: No, I didn't mean you look like a pigeon.
(Note: "99" sounds like pigeon cooing in Korean)]
[Hyeyeon: He really gives off '99 vibes.]
[Chaebe: Oh! Really?]
[Yongkyu: What is a '99 vibe?]
[Seungho: I don't know.
He just looks like he was born in '99.]
'99 vibes.
[Chaebe: What about my job, then?]
[Jinwoo: Job!]
[Hyeyeon: Brand store employee.]
[Jinwoo: You seem into fashion.]
[Heejin: I guess hair designer.]
[Sujin: But his hairstyle doesn't
really give that impression.
[Heejin: True. So...]
[Sujin: His styling is pretty bad.]
[Heejin: A barista would suit him well.]
[Jinwoo: Working at a coffee shop sounds good, too.]
[Sujin: It really fits.]
[Sujin: A tattooist?]
[A tattooist?]
-A tattooist? -Hold on.
[Chaebe: Nobody has gotten my job right yet.]
[Jinwoo: Oh, really?]
[Jinwoo: Jobs are so hard to guess.]
[Seungho: Feels like you're in corporate marketing.]
[Heejin: A programmer? No, wait.]
[Sujin: Definitely not a programmer.]
[Hyeyeon: A coder?]
[Heejin: No, no, not a programmer.]
[Hyeyeon: A kindergarten teacher?]
[Sujin: That actually kind of fits.]
[Jinwoo: He has a super bright smile.]
[Did you take your meds?]
[Sujin: That actually kind of fits.]
[Jinwoo: He has a super bright smile.]
[Hyeyeon: Oh? I feel fine now.]
[Did someone get it right?]
[Chaebe: I was born in '97.]
[Oh.]
[Chaebe: I'm also in the food industry.]
[Nods]
-Seriously? -Oh my god.
[Chaebe: I also work as
a freelance Vietnamese translator.]
[Hyeyeon: Oh, that's so cool.]
[Jinwoo: I would've never guessed
you work in the food industry.
[Yongkyu: Some people]
[Yongkyu: might be older than me,
but look younger.]
[Yongkyu: Their age was kind of tricky to guess.]
[Chaebe: So lucky. '97 and '94
are only a 3-year difference.]
[Chaebe: I was thrilled.]
[Chaebe: The age gap isn't that big.]
[Chaebe: Just a bit of a bummer
it's not a 4-year gap.]
[Chaebe: The "perfect match" age gap
in Korean tradition.]
[Chaebe: Wait, was he born early in '94? Score!]
[Sujin: What kind of food?]
[Chaebe: Southeast Asian cuisine.]
[Sujin: Like rice noodles?]
[Chaebe: Yes.]
[Sujin: Sounds delicious.]
[Jinwoo: Sounds delicious.]
[Hyeyeon: Sounds delicious.]
[Seungho: Sounds delicious.]
Sounds delicious.
[Heejin: I love cilantro.]
[Chaebe: Really?]
[Jinwoo: I love cilantro, too.]
-I love cilantro. -I love cilantro, too.
-Really? -Really?
[Oh, really?]
[Jinwoo: I eat cilantro.]
[Heejin: Want to grab food sometime?]
[Jinwoo: Yeah, down.]
[Chaebe: Count me in too.]
[Sujin: Ah, the three of you?]
[Jinwoo: Let's all go.]
[Chaebe: Let's all go.]
[Jinwoo: Got it, got it.]
[Hyeyeon: Oh, so cool.]
[Sujin: I didn't expect Chaebe
to be in the food industry at all.]
[Sujin: I actually joked]
[Sujin: with Chaebe before.]
Medium heat.
[Sujin: Chaebe.]
[Chaebe: Huh?]
[Sujin: You don't know how to cook, do you?]
[Embarrassed]
[Chaebe: Why would you think that?]
[Sujin: Who checks the recipe
while pan-frying dumplings?]
[Sujin: You just throw them in the pan.]
[Ah, really?]
[Yep!]
[Chaebe: It was my first time making them.]
[Really?]
[Really?] [Yep!]
[Gasp.]
[Sujin: That's a bit awkward.]
[Chaebe: What? I was faking it.]
[Next up is Jinwoo]
[Hyeyeon: Jinwoo has a perfect job
I can't even argue with.]
[Hyeyeon: A Lush employee.]
[Chaebe: I think he is a YouTuber.]
[Heejin: You're an MD, right?]
[Shake head]
[Hyeyeon: Kindergarten teacher?]
[Heejin: Planner? Sales?]
[Jinwoo: I actually have two jobs.]
[Jinwoo: First, my age is...]
[Heejin: He's definitely an '01.]
[Heejin: He has a total Gen Z face.]
[Seungho: Exactly.]
[Seungho: '00 or '01?]
[Jinwoo: 0...]
[1?]
[Jinwoo: I'm an '01.]
[Seungho: Called it.]
[Jinwoo: Oh, you got it.]
[Jinwoo: Seungho kept saying
I look like I was born in '01.]
[Jinwoo: I was born in '01. My current job is...]
[Jinwoo: I manage]
[Jinwoo: a perfume brand.]
[Jinwoo: And like Chaebe said,]
[Jinwoo: I'm also a beauty blogger.]
[Chaebe: See? I knew it!]
[Seungho: Ever since the first night
in the Secret Room,]
[Seungho: I guessed he was an '01.
It's amazing that I was right.]
[Seungho: On the ride to the house,
he talked a lot about perfume.]
[Seungho: I thought he just liked it.]
[Seungho: I didn't expect him to actually work]
[Seungho: in the industry.]
[Hyeyeon: I thought Jinwoo was a '98 liner.]
[Hyeyeon: I hoped the age gap
between him and Seungho]
[Hyeyeon: would be a bit wider.]
[Hyeyeon: Turns out he's only a year older than me.]
[Hyeyeon: And Seungho said]
[Hyeyeon: he prefers a 4 to 5-year age gap.]
[Hyeyeon: I'm 4 years apart from him,
and Jinwoo is 5 years apart.]
[Hyeyeon: Bummer, our gap isn't that big.]
[Jinwoo: Alright, Sujin.]
[Hyeyeon: '04.]
[Seungho: '0... '03.]
[Hyeyeon: '03? '04? I feel like she's an '04 liner.]
-'03 or '04? I feel like she's an '04 liner. -'04.
[Jinwoo: I feel like she's exactly my age.]
[Hyeyeon: Huh? Exactly?]
[Jinwoo: No?]
[Sujin: Not at all?]
['04?] [Seungho: A 2001 and a 2003 liner
are basically the same age, aren't they?]
[Ah...] [Seungho: A 2001 and a 2003 liner
[Chaebe: And I heard her say
she's done a lot of things.]
[Jinwoo: Right, she worked tons of part-time jobs.]
[Chaebe: Tons of part-time jobs.]
[Hyeyeon: But if she started in high school...]
[Jinwoo: Ah, that makes sense.]
[Seungho: Oh, make sense.]
[Sujin: I started working part-time in 9th grade.]
[Hyeyeon: Oh, same here.]
[Heejin: A nurse?]
[Sujin: A nurse? That's a first.]
[Sujin: But I don't think you guys can guess]
-Something science-related. -But I don't think
you guys can guess
[Sujin: my job right.]
[A Pilates instructor.]
[Hyeyeon: Guess it really doesn't fit.]
[Hyeyeon: A motorcycle mechanic?]
[Motorcycles?]
Out of nowhere.
[Yongkyu: Take a break. You still look sick.]
[Hyeyeon: I'm heading back to bed.]
[Jinwoo: Is the answer in any of these guesses?]
[Sujin: My job?]
[Sujin: Nobody got it yet.]
[Jinwoo: Did anyone guess your age?]
[Sujin: Yeah, someone got the age.]
[Jinwoo: Someone got the age?]
[Yongkyu: Can we get a hint? Like the field?]
[Sujin: Arts and sports.]
[Jinwoo: Are you in music?]
[Hyeyeon: Beauty!]
[Chaebe: A dancer...]
[Heejin: A dancer?]
[Composing?]
[Yongkyu: A dancer or a choreographer?]
[Heejin: Right, like modern dance.]
[Yongkyu: She mentioned it once before.]
[Oh, really?]
Is she a dancer?
[Yongkyu: She said something like that.]
[Choreographer...]
[Yongkyu: Oh, a choreographer.]
[Jinwoo: Right? A choreographer?]
[Sujin: First of all, I was born in '04.]
[Sujin: And I am]
[Sujin: majoring in applied music
and vocal performance.]
[Whoa!]
[Jinwoo: Totally unexpected.]
[Sujin: I'm still in college.]
[Sujin: I'm a college student
majoring in applied music and vocals.]
-I'm a college student. -Still in school.
[Sujin: I am currently in college.]
[Hyeyeon: Since Sujin and Seungho
are both the cute type of person,]
[Hyeyeon: that must be it.
Getting won over by how cute they are.]
[Hyeyeon: Cute things were never really my thing.]
[Hyeyeon: But when I'm around them as my true self,]
[Hyeyeon: I find myself getting
won over by how cute they are.
[Heejin: When dating Sujin,]
[Heejin: I just saw her as a cute younger sister.]
[Heejin: But she really is quite young.]
[Heejin: It hit me pretty hard.]
[Heejin: Who am I even supposed to date here?]
[Heejin: Who should I express my feelings to?
[Heejin: Who will I spend the rest]
[Heejin: of my time with?]
[Jinwoo: Anyone want to drop the honorifics?]
[Me!] [Me!] [Me too.]
[Sujin: You too, Seungho?]
[Seungho: Yeah, totally.]
[Jinwoo: Honestly,
I want to drop them with everyone.]
[Seungho: Go ahead.]
[Surprised]
[Sujin: Okay.]
[Sujin: Okay. Seungho, go ahead.]
[Jinwoo: Alright, got it.]
[Yongkyu: So we're all dropping honorifics?]
[Sujin: Yep.]
[Seungho: Really?]
[Yongkyu: Is anyone uncomfortable?]
[Jinwoo: Hyeyeon, are you good with it?]
[Seungho: Can we drop the honorifics?]
[Whatever you want!]
[Yongkyu: Not that casual!]
Not that casual.
[Hyeyeon: It's fine.]
[Yongkyu: Looks like I'm the only one
who feels a little off.]
[Why? Why? Why?]
[Yongkyu: Looks like I'm the only one
who feels a little off.]
[Jinwoo: Don't get sick.]
[Yongkyu: Sure.]
[Yongkyu: Let's be happy.]
[Jinwoo:  Let's be happy.]
[Hyeyeon: New mission.]
[Did anyone make your heart race
with a new charm? Text their name]
[This vote decides who gets to enter the Secret Room]
[Hyeyeon: After the job reveal,
you start seeing people in a new light.]
[Jinwoo: Yeah, true.]
[Jinwoo: Being proud of your job
makes you look so attractive.]
[Jinwoo: It makes you seem more thoughtful.]
[Got to know each other better today]
[Which makes the choice even harder]
[Agonizing]
[Seungho: Now that I know everyone's job and age,]
[Seungho: they might factor that into their choices.]
[Seungho: But I was still]
[Seungho: voting for the person I'm into.]
[Seungho: I followed my own heart.]
[Jinwoo: Honestly, I struggled with this.]
[Jinwoo: Do I really have to pick someone
who showed a new charm?]
[Heejin: Now that I know their ages,]
[Heejin: I wonder if choosing younger people]
[Heejin: makes any sense.]
[Heejin: When I got the prompt,]
[Heejin: I couldn't think of anyone.]
[Heejin: It was a tough choice.]
[Who did they vote today?]
[Sujin: Who's going today?]
[Jinwoo: Who's going today?]
[Seungho: I hope it's me again.]
[Sujin: Greedy.]
[Jinwoo: With whom?]
[Seungho: No idea.]
[Sujin: So greedy.]
[Hyeyeon: I doubted anyone would vote for me.]
[Hyeyeon: Jinwoo took such good care]
[Hyeyeon: of Seungho.]
[Heejin: I thought Hyeyeon
was going to the Secret Room.]
[Heejin: At the beach, both Chaebe and Yongkyu]
[Heejin: said they fell]
[Heejin: for her charm.]
[Go Sujin chose you today]
[Chaebe: I got a vote from Go Sujin.]
[Chaebe: On Day 1 and Day 2,
I didn't get any votes.]
[Chaebe: I wondered what was up.]
[Chaebe: But getting my first vote
felt pretty great.]
[Sujin: Actually, after learning
everyone's job and age,]
[Sujin: no one really stood out to me.]
[Sujin: The person I was most interested in
at the time was Chaebe.]
[Sujin: So I voted for him.]
[Nobody chose you today]
[Sujin: Aside from Heejin,]
[Sujin: I haven't really approached anyone else.]
[Sujin: I figured Heejin
probably wouldn't choose me.]
[Sujin: Oh well. It does hurt a little,]
[Sujin: but I saw it coming.]
[Nobody chose you today]
[Heejin: I didn't let it get to me]
[Heejin: because I didn't think I gave Sujin]
[Heejin: enough signals that I liked her.]
[Heejin: I was sure she could tell.]
[Heejin: So she wouldn't pick me.]
[Heejin: Eunchae picked me yesterday.]
[Heejin: Getting zero votes]
[Heejin: wasn't a huge shock.]
[Heejin: I kind of expected it.]
[What about Eunchae, who voted for Heejin yesterday?]
[Jung Heejin chose you today]
[Eunchae: I got a vote from Heejin.]
[Eunchae: Nobody had voted for me before.]
[Eunchae: That day was my very first vote.]
[Eunchae: I voted for her before.]
[Eunchae: After the age and job reveal,]
[Eunchae: maybe she found something
she liked and voted for me.
[Eunchae: First off, I was thrilled.]
[Eunchae: I wasn't being active enough,]
[Eunchae: but now I feel like
I'm getting my groove back. I was so happy.]
[Heejin: The fact that Eunchae works as a model]
[Heejin: really stood out to me.]
[Heejin: At first, she seemed kind of reserved
and was a bit hard to get along with.
[Heejin: But over time, she loosened up.]
[Heejin: She showed her true self, and seeing that—]
[Heejin: "Oh, this is how she looks and acts
when she's relaxed."]
[Heejin: Her vibe and the way she carried herself]
[Heejin: felt refreshing.]
[Koo Yongkyu, Park Jinwoo, and Kim Hyeyeon chose you]
[You matched with Kim Hyeyeon]
[Seungho: Usually, the messages only
showed "one male and one female,"]
[Seungho: without revealing who they were.]
[Seungho: But suddenly, their names were revealed.]
[Seungho: I was a bit shocked.]
[Seungho: They were exactly the people]
[Seungho: I expected would choose me.]
[Seungho: I thought, "Just as I expected."]
[Hyeyeon: I was still into him.]
[Hyeyeon: And I could tell Seungho also]
[Hyeyeon: has feelings for me.]
[Hyeyeon: Since I didn't pick him
for the YES or NO date,]
[Hyeyeon: he could've been hurt
and avoided talking to me.]
[Hyeyeon: But what I love about him
is that he answers honestly.]
[Hyeyeon: Like, "I totally assumed you'd pick me.]
[Hyeyeon: If you did, I would've picked you back."]
[Hyeyeon: Being that honest
made me like him even more.]
[Hyeyeon: So I chose Seungho again today.]
[Nobody chose you today]
[Jinwoo: I knew this day would come eventually.]
[Jinwoo: Because up until now,]
[Jinwoo: Seungho was the only one
who had been choosing me.]
[Jinwoo: So the moment Seungho picks someone else,]
[Jinwoo: I'm down to zero votes.]
[Jinwoo: I prepared myself for it.]
[Jinwoo: So Seungho and I]
[Jinwoo: actually talked about that.]
[Jinwoo: "If you want to pick someone else,
go for it. Don't feel tied down."]
[Jinwoo: I told him that day, so]
[Jinwoo: it felt a bit bitter, but that's about it.]
[Jinwoo: No hard feelings.]
[Nobody chose you today]
[Yongkyu: I need to be more open about how I feel.]
[Yongkyu: We did go on a date that day, after all.]
[Yongkyu: We went together
because we were interested.]
[Yongkyu: But getting zero votes]
[Yongkyu: made my mind race.]
[Yongkyu: Was the date just mediocre?]
[Yongkyu: Did he think we just didn't click]
[Yongkyu: because of the way]
[Yongkyu: we talked during the date?]
[Kim Seungho, Lim Chaebe, and Tae Eunchae chose you]
[You matched with Kim Seungho.]
[Hyeyeon: We went on a date yesterday,]
[Hyeyeon: but he didn't pick me. I got 0 votes.]
[Hyeyeon: But today, unexpected people
voted for me.]
[Hyeyeon: Even Seungho and I matched.]
[Hyeyeon: Wait, what? Oh, awesome.]
[Seungho: I already knew exactly
where Jinwoo stands.]
[Seungho: But Hyeyeon
said she's torn between two people.]
[Seungho: I was curious]
[Seungho: whether I'm her first or second choice.]
[Seungho: I wanted to talk to her again.]
[Seungho: So I chose Hyeyeon.]
[Eunchae: I only had eyes for Heejin at first.]
[Eunchae: But after my first date with Hyeyeon,]
[Eunchae: someone new came into the picture,
and I found her really interesting.
[Chaebe: I chose Hyeyeon.]
[Chaebe: Even though Yongkyu is my number 1,]
[Chaebe: talking and joking around—]
[Chaebe: She was the first person I did that with.]
[Chaebe: I thought, "Oh, she's great."]
[Chaebe: So I picked her.]
[Jinwoo: Who on earth is going?]
[Jinwoo: Heart thumping]
[Anxious]
[Tense]
[Tonight's Secret Room guests
are Kim Seungho and Kim Hyeyeon,
who tied for first place
and chose each other.]
[Chaebe: Oh, so]
[Chaebe: you are going?]
[Jinwoo: You're going to the Secret Room, right?]
[Chaebe: Impressive.]
[Jinwoo: Wow, incredible. Oh.]
[Chaebe: Bring back some good food.]
[Yongkyu: We have plenty of good food here.]
[Sujin: Right, we have a lot here today.]
[Jinwoo: Yeah, we have a lot here too.]
[Seungho: My stomach hurts,
so I might not eat much. I'll bring some back.]
[Chaebe: Congrats.]
[Jinwoo: Congrats.]
[Hyeyeon: I was a bit overwhelmed.]
[Hyeyeon: Seungho got 3 votes, and I got 3 votes.]
[Hyeyeon: I was like, "Oh my god,
we even matched?"]
[Hyeyeon: What is going on?
I was totally shocked.]
[Seungho: They said a 4-year age gap
makes a perfect match.]
[Seungho: That was one thing.]
[Seungho: And career-wise,]
[Seungho: I prefer someone I can relate to.]
[Seungho: Hyeyeon probably has more]
[Seungho: in common with me]
[Seungho: than Jinwoo does.]
[Jinwoo: My heart just sank. And]
[Jinwoo: they matched.]
[Jinwoo: So did Seungho find Hyeyeon's]
[Jinwoo: age and job]
[Jinwoo: attractive?]
[Jinwoo: Or did he vote for Hyeyeon knowing]
[Jinwoo: this vote was]
[Jinwoo: for the Secret Room?]
[Hyeyeon: We'll be right back.]
[Jinwoo: Go ahead.]
[Heejin: Have fun.]
[Chaebe: Bring good food.]
[Heejin: What do I do? What do I do...
I really don't know anymore.]
[Heejin: I genuinely don't know.]
[Sujin: Even though I have a single room,]
[Sujin: private chats are still limited.]
[Sujin: In the Secret Room, you get great food]
[Sujin: and drinks.]
[Sujin: I wondered if they'd
have a more honest conversation.]
[Sujin: I want to go to the Secret Room, too.]
[Sujin: It would be great]
[Sujin: to go with Heejin.]
[Chaebe: Going there must
give off a totally different vibe.]
[Chaebe: I really wanted to go.]
[Chaebe: But now, I'm not that jealous.]
[Chaebe: I already went on a date.]
[Chaebe: No regrets. Compared to anyone else,]
[Chaebe: I had a highly]
[Chaebe: satisfying day.]
[Chaebe: Why do I need to go there anyway?
He's right next to me.]
[Hyeyeon: Does your stomach hurt?]
[Seungho: Better than before.]
[Hyeyeon: Badly?]
[Seungho: A little bit, on and off.]
[Hyeyeon: What should we bring?
You've been there.]
[Seungho: Nothing, just...
Ah, I only brought my bag last time.]
[Hyeyeon: We can always come back
for whatever we need.]
[Seungho: Yeah, let's pack light.]
[Hyeyeon: Okay, I'll pack light, too.]
[Hyeyeon: We matched today]
[Hyeyeon: and went to the Secret Room together.]
[Hyeyeon: But hearts can change.]
[Hyeyeon: I just hoped we would get closer tonight]
[Hyeyeon: by spending time together
in the Secret Room.]
[Jinwoo: We have the place to ourselves tonight.]
[Heejin: Ah, I... but it's just... it's just...]
[Heejin: Two people are missing.]
[Heejin: "Hey, I can shower early tonight."]
[Jinwoo: Oh, exactly.]
[Staring]
[Jinwoo: This is our Secret Room.]
[Hyeyeon: Um... I'm going to grab my charger.]
[Jinwoo: Go eat lots of good food.]
[Hyeyeon: But his stomach hurts,
and my throat hurts.]
[Jinwoo: No drinking then.]
[Hyeyeon: It's a hospital ward
in the Secret Room tonight.]
[Jinwoo: Then don't drink too much.]
[Seungho: But we can both hold our liquor.]
[Hyeyeon: Yeah.]
[Seungho: Just a bit.]
[Jinwoo: Got it.]
[Seungho looks a bit conflicted]
[Seungho: On the first day, I picked him]
[Seungho: to go to the Secret Room.]
[Seungho: But this time, Hyeyeon and I tied for first,]
[Seungho: so we went together.]
[Seungho: I actually felt relieved.]
[Seungho: I didn't have to worry as much
about how Jinwoo felt.]
[Jinwoo: Honestly, I minded it a lot.]
[Jinwoo: I had so many questions for him.]
[Jinwoo: And my thoughts were all over the place.]
[Jinwoo: I didn't want to show my inner chaos,]
[Jinwoo: so I just forced a smile]
[Jinwoo: and told them to eat well.]
[Hyeyeon and Seungho are getting ready]
[Heejin completely ignores them]
[Hyeyeon: Should I dress up a bit?
It is the Secret Room, after all.]
[Seungho: A... a little bit... more than this?]
[Hyeyeon: Got it.]
[Heejin: Sighs. Oh man...]
[Heejin: Ah... no one...]
[Heejin: Seriously.]
[Heejin hides under the covers]
[Heejin: Hyeyeon wasn't the right person for me.
If that path didn't work,]
[Heejin: I still had other options.]
[Heejin: But even those choices]
[Heejin: vanished one by one.]
[Heejin: I had no one left to choose.]
[Heejin: I never imagined I'd cry.]
[Heejin: Ah... seriously.]
[Heejin: Ugh, can they please edit this part out?]
[Excited] [Excited]
[Hyeyeon is thrilled
about the long-awaited alone time with Seungho]
[Meanwhile, Eunchae and Sujin
run into each other in the living room]
[Sujin: What? What? What?]
[Eunchae: Ah, what a surprise.]
[Eunchae: So interesting.]
[Sujin: Girls' night?]
[Eunchae: Down?]
[Sujin: Girls' night? You down?]
[Eunchae: This is getting so interesting.]
[Sujin: What's interesting?]
[Eunchae: The Secret Room. Huge plot twist.]
[Eunchae: Such a twist.]
[Sujin: Why? Why? Why?
Anyone watching could tell.]
[Sujin: During the Truth Game.]
[Eunchae: Ah, really? Yesterday?]
[Sujin: Yeah, yeah.]
[Eunchae: Huh? I had no idea.]
[Sujin: Seungho asked Hyeyeon,]
[Sujin: "In the arrow date,]
[Ah...]
[Sujin: if you could pick a girl,
would you still pick me?" And Hyeyeon said—]
[Sujin: He asked if she'd still pick him
if girls were an option.]
[Sujin: And she said yes.]
[Eunchae: Oh, I thought she was just being polite.]
[Eunchae: I didn't realize they were that far along.]
[Sujin: No, Hyeyeon is split down the middle.]
[Sujin: Half of her heart is for one guy—]
[Sujin: that's Seungho.
Seungho also said it was more like a 60-40 split.]
[Sujin: I feel like the 60 is Jinwoo
and the 40 is Hyeyeon.]
[Eunchae: But, this time they wanted to go together.]
[Sujin: Seungho wanted to go with Hyeyeon.]
[Sujin: If Seungho won the vote,]
[Sujin: he'd definitely pick Hyeyeon.]
[Eunchae: I get it now.]
[Sujin: Huh?]
[Eunchae: Makes sense.]
[Sujin: You got it?]
[Eunchae: What shocked me was]
[Eunchae: that during the anonymous chat room,
nobody joined mine.]
[Sujin: Seriously?]
[Eunchae: Yeah.]
[Sujin: Aw, you must've been so hurt that day.]
[Eunchae: Yeah, that's why you sent a message]
[Eunchae: asking me, "How is it?" But—]
[Chaebe: What are you talking about?]
[Eunchae: Something fun. Super interesting.]
[Sujin: Juice. Juicy gossip.
You down? Juicy gossip, down?]
[Eunchae: Something super interesting.]
[Yongkyu: What is it? What is it?]
[Chaebe: I want to hear, too.]
[Sighs...]
[Chaebe: What is it?]
[This is Day 3.]
[Sujin: The Secret Room vote...
is it who I think it is?]
[Yongkyu: Did you smoke?]
[Eunchae: Not yet.]
[Go ahead]
[Chaebe: Who is it?]
[Sujin: In the secret room, did you
vote for that person I know?]
[Sujin: Today?]
[Chaebe: Today? No.]
[Sujin: Who?]
[Chaebe: Someone else.]
[Sujin: Oh, you can't just tell me directly.]
[Sujin: No, it's fine actually.]
-No, it's fine. -It's fine.
[Chaebe: I voted for Hyeyeon.]
[Sujin: Why? Because you're curious about her?]
[Chaebe: Curious? I don't know.
It's just a little...]
[Chaebe: It was fun. During
the cooking earlier...]
[Chaebe: I thought, "Oh, it would be fun
to hang out with her."]
[Sujin: You wanted to talk to her.]
[Chaebe: I thought it'd be fun, so I picked her.]
[Sujin: How was your date today?]
[Chaebe: The date? I had a really good time.]
[Sujin: You already liked her this much. Do you
like her even more now? Your feelings.]
[Chaebe: I already had some feelings for her.]
[Sujin: If 10 is the max...]
[Sujin: If 100 is 10, and 10 means
you really like them...]
[Sujin: then what was it before? Like a 2?]
[Chaebe: Before...]
[Chaebe: I already liked her quite a bit.]
-But... -About a 5?
[Sujin: About a 5?]
[Chaebe: Yeah.]
[Chaebe: But after the date,
I liked her even more.]
[Chaebe: So I think if we hadn't gone on
a date today, it wouldn't have worked out.]
[Chaebe: So I'm really happy with today.]
[Sujin: But why?]
[Chaebe: Because I'm still curious.]
[Sujin: You want to know more.
You need to know more.]
[Chaebe: Other people too... and...]
[Sujin: Right, right, right.]
[Chaebe: Anyway, that guy doesn't seem
to like me much.]
[Sujin: Why?]
[Chaebe: You can tell right away.]
[Chaebe: Because we've been talking a lot]
[Chaebe: and he even said in front of me]
[Chaebe: that he's interested
in someone else. So I thought]
[Chaebe: he wouldn't even consider me.]
[Chaebe: So I just let it go.]
[Chaebe: I don't know. Who did you pick?]
[Sujin: I picked you.]
No, wait...
[Sujin: No, that's because]
[Sujin: I originally...]
[Sujin: I originally liked Heejin.]
[Sujin: But after today's date,
it felt just okay.]
[Sujin: It was neither here nor there...]
[Chaebe: No spark?]
[Sujin: It's not that there was no spark.
It was fun and enjoyable.]
[Sujin: But during the introduction...]
[Sujin: Heejin said she wants to date men.]
[Chaebe: Oh... Oh... really?]
[Heejin: Right now, I'm more... the gender
I want to date more is men.]
[Heejin: Even though it's men, here...]
[Heejin: I can have feelings for both men
and women. The ratio is the same.]
[Sujin: Even though she said it's fifty-fifty...]
[Sujin: it still feels a little...]
[While Sujin and Chaebe are sharing
their true feelings]
[Jinwoo: What's going on? What's going on?]
[Eunchae: How was it?]
[Yongkyu: It was fun.]
[Eunchae: I thought so too.]
[Jinwoo: Now that we know everything,
it's even more interesting.]
[At this moment, I can't help but smile]
[Eunchae: At this stage, I like Hyeyeon.]
[Eunchae: When we revealed ages
and occupations today,]
[Eunchae: I realized that the age gap
between Heejin and me]
[Eunchae: is 9 years. It's quite big.]
[Eunchae: And the things I talked about
with Hyeyeon...]
[Eunchae: are exactly the kind of
conversations I enjoy.]
[Eunchae: Plus, our ages are more compatible.]
[Eunchae: So right now, I like Hyeyeon more.]
[Eunchae: But later, if I get another chance
to go on a date with Heejin...]
[Eunchae: I might not consider age as a factor.]
[Eunchae: My feelings could change.]
[The secret room door opens]
[Hyeyeon and Seungho are about to enjoy
some time alone together]
[Run, run]
[Lively]
[Looking down]
[Seungho: I think someone... someone's coming.]
-Right? -Yeah.
Like a goat.
Could it be like that?
[Just then, they run into Yongkyu,
Jinwoo, and Eunchae]
You've heard of the Joker, right?
I've heard of it.
Looks like they're going there.
[Jinwoo: Looks like they're going there.]
[Eunchae: Oh no. This is bad.]
[Eunchae: Oh, seriously...]
Oh no. This is bad.
Oh, seriously.
[Hyeyeon: She said, "Oh no. This is bad."]
[Hyeyeon: So the secret room is that
scary of a place?]
[Seungho: The first day was fine since
it was the first day...]
[Hyeyeon: Right, because everyone didn't know
each other well yet.]
[Hyeyeon: Back then, I thought, "I'm so jealous."]
[Hyeyeon: Now that everyone's feelings
are confirmed, walking into this room]
[Hyeyeon: feels like going to prison
or something?]
[Hyeyeon: No one else is here,
and no one will come in either.]
[Hyeyeon: In this space with no time limit,
where we can talk freely...]
[Hyeyeon: I need to be more proactive
and more forward]
[Hyeyeon: so we could get closer.]
[Hyeyeon: I hope this becomes
an opportunity for that.]
[Seungho: Did something change?]
[Seungho: The cushion looks different?]
[Hyeyeon: Is it softer now?]
[Seungho: Sparkling wine?]
[Seungho: Now it's a whole bottle.]
[Hyeyeon: Isn't this wine way too light for us?]
[Haha]
[Seungho: I went to the secret room
on the first day, right?]
[Seungho: I didn't expect to get picked again.
Anyway, I'm in a great mood.]
[Seungho: This time, I want to ask more
about things I've been curious about.]
[Hyeyeon: How do you open this?]
The one from last time seems a little
different from this one.
[The two decide to have some white wine first]
-I think you just twist it open. -Really?
[Struggling]
Right.
[Seungho: Isn't there one this time? Like
a corkscrew or something?]
[Hyeyeon: It's a cork.]
[Seungho: Do you know how to do this?]
[Seungho: Actually, I didn't open it last time.
Jinwoo did everything...]
[Hyeyeon: Then I have to do it? Let me try.]
[Hyeyeon: I can't lose.]
[Hyeyeon: Oh, I got it.]
[Hyeyeon: This feels like an escape room.]
[Pop!]
[Startled]
[Seungho: Oh, wait.]
[Seungho: That was scary.]
[Seungho: I panicked. It was so sudden.]
Me too.
[Seungho: I thought it was going to hit me.]
Let's pick it up first.
[Hyeyeon: Just a little bit.]
[Hyeyeon: Seungho, by the way...]
[Hyeyeon: Do you mind if people don't call you
by your name and just say "hey"?]
[Seungho: I don't really like it.]
[Hyeyeon: Then should I call you Seungho?]
[Seungho: But that does sound more
natural when spoken.]
[Seungho: But since there's no final choice yet,
this much is fine.]
[Hyeyeon: I'll keep that in mind.]
[Seungho: Should we have a drink first?]
[Hyeyeon: Should we clink glasses?]
[Hyeyeon: Don't finish it all at once.]
Okay.
[Hyeyeon: Oh, this is good.]
[Seungho: Yeah, it has a hint of lemon?]
[Hyeyeon: 9% alcohol.]
[Seungho: Somewhere between beer and soju?]
[Seungho: Should we just talk first? For a while?]
[Hyeyeon: Today I really felt like a criminal.]
[Hyeyeon: The moment I heard Eunchae
say "This is bad"...]
[Fidgeting nervously]
[Hyeyeon: But what I find unfair is]
[Hyeyeon: the vibe of our date wasn't
so much about butterflies]
[Hyeyeon: as it was about a sense of closeness.]
[Hyeyeon: I think Eunchae just felt that.]
[Hyeyeon: We had a good time together today.]
[Hyeyeon: But Jinwoo...]
Right.
[Hyeyeon: he's been so direct in expressing
his feelings for you.]
[Seungho: So...]
[Seungho: I couldn't even look him
in the eye just now...]
[Hyeyeon: But honestly, today]
[Hyeyeon: I didn't think you'd pick me.]
So...
[Seungho: Me neither. Really.]
[Hyeyeon: The feeling was mutual? But why
did you pick me?]
[Seungho: I don't know. I just wanted to?]
[Hyeyeon: Did you just pick randomly?]
[Seungho: Not really.]
[Hyeyeon: As ESTPs...]
[Hyeyeon: so we don't make a losing deal...]
[Hyeyeon: shouldn't we be calculating?]
[Seungho: I did plenty of calculating.]
[Hyeyeon: Today I really thought you
wouldn't pick me.]
[Hyeyeon: If I confessed everything,]
[Hyeyeon: it would only make Jinwoo's
feelings for you stronger.]
[Hyeyeon: So it felt like Jinwoo
was protecting you]
[Hyeyeon: and building an invisible wall
around you.]
[Hyeyeon: I couldn't even get close to you today.]
[Hyeyeon was constantly worried
about Seungho's finger]
[Hyeyeon: Every time I tried to take care of you,]
[Hyeyeon: Jinwoo would show up!]
[Hyeyeon: When I heard you two were going on
a date alone, I felt something was off.]
[Hyeyeon: Jinwoo is very perceptive, especially
when it comes to you.]
[Hyeyeon: If Jinwoo saw the band-aid
I put on you,]
[Hyeyeon: you'd at least think for a moment:
Hyeyeon put this on. Should I tell Jinwoo?"]
[Hyeyeon: That's what I was thinking.]
[Hyeyeon: That was my plan.]
[Seungho: Yeah, I told him.]
You did?
[Seungho: Both the bracelet and the band-aid.
I told him about both.]
Haha.
[Hyeyeon: That's great.]
[Seungho: I was going to tell him anyway.]
[Hyeyeon: So it was a chance to further
confirm your feelings?]
[Seungho: You're right. And I was curious
about his reaction too.]
[Hyeyeon: Is it about the memories with me,
or the couple bracelet?]
[Hyeyeon: Or were you using it
to test the person you like?]
[Hyeyeon: Was I just a tool?]
[Seungho: No, no.]
[Hyeyeon: Right. Actually, I've been
confirming things too.]
[Hyeyeon: I thought you'd
take the bracelet off.]
[Hyeyeon: Especially when
going on a date.]
[Hyeyeon: Even if Jinwoo just said it
as a joke,]
[Hyeyeon: "Take off the bracelet since you're
on a date with me, OK?" If he said that,]
[Hyeyeon: you'd laugh and take it off.]
[Seungho: It's very likely if he said that.]
If he really said that...
[Disappointed]
[Disappointed
Seungho: But to be honest,]
[Seungho: Jinwoo isn't that kind of person.]
[Seungho: Even if I took it off then,
I'd put it right back on afterwards.]
[Hyeyeon: Really?
Seungho: I can guarantee this.]
[Hyeyeon: Did your heart flutter
during the date today?]
[Seungho: Yeah!]
I did.
[Hyeyeon: You answered way too quickly...]
You actually said yeah.
[Hyeyeon: Does your heart flutter
with me too?]
[Seungho: Yeah, it does.
Hyeyeon: Really?]
Yeah.
-Yeah, I did.
-Really?
Yeah.
[Hyeyeon: I totally didn't expect that.
Seungho: Why? Did you think it didn't?]
[Hyeyeon: I thought maybe it didn't.]
[Hyeyeon: Because I... didn't know
Seungho's feelings.]
[Hyeyeon: I didn't know.]
[Hyeyeon: Want a drink? Is this a penalty?]
[Seungho: It's not a penalty.]
[Seungho: It's a good chance.]
[Their time alone
is gradually heating up]
[Seungho: Am I close to your ideal type?]
[Seungho: No?
Hyeyeon: Actually, not really.]
[Seungho: Me neither.
Hyeyeon: Really?]
[Hyeyeon: Then among the girls living here,]
[Hyeyeon: whose appearance is closest
to your ideal type?]
[Hyeyeon: But the range is too broad.]
[Seungho: You are the closest.]
-You are the closest.
-Am I?
[Hyeyeon: Really?]
[Seungho: That means I don't have
a fixed ideal type.]
[Seungho: It depends on the person
and the feeling.]
[Hyeyeon: Yes. Everyone's ideal appearance
is different.]
[Hyeyeon: But personality-wise...]
[Hyeyeon: They have to match what I like.]
[Hyeyeon: But what I like...]
[Hyeyeon: Whether it's my bisexual,
heterosexual, or homosexual friends...]
[Hyeyeon: None of them really like it.]
[Hyeyeon: I won't say exactly what it is.]
[Hyeyeon: The type of guy I like is]
[Hyeyeon: someone with fair skin
and a higher-pitched voice.]
[Hyeyeon: I'm more attracted to someone
whose hair isn't too short.]
[Hyeyeon: Rather than a confident,
dominant type,]
[Hyeyeon: I prefer someone who stays in the back
and smiles shyly.]
[Is Seungho Hyeyeon's ideal type?]
[Hyeyeon: Then during our date yesterday,
was it Yongkyu who sent you the SBM Talk?]
[Seungho: Yeah. Jinwoo and Yongkyu sent it...]
[Hyeyeon: I see. Me too.]
[Hyeyeon: I got messages from Heejin and Sujin.]
[Hyeyeon: So I naturally thought]
[Hyeyeon: that Sujin must like me too.]
[Hyeyeon and Seungho's phones
ring at the same time]
Was it sent to us?
[Yongkyu: Go on a date with me next time.]
[Hyeyeon: I'll keep it a secret.]
[Seungho: Uh, did you get it? Just one?]
[Hyeyeon: Did you get one too?]
[Seungho: Per... personal...]
[Hyeyeon: Me too... At the same time?]
[Seungho: The same person?]
10 minutes earlier.
[Hyeyeon and Seungho
receive an SBM Talk at the same time]
We talk and sort out our thoughts.
[Hyeyeon: This is really interesting.
[Seungho: Then just say what the situation is?]
[Hyeyeon: Oh, OK.]
[Seungho: Anyway, it expressed interest.]
[Hyeyeon: Me too!]
[Hyeyeon: A little boldly.]
[Seungho: Me too!]
[Hyeyeon: Let's leave it at that.]
-OK.
-Let's leave it at that. So...
[Hyeyeon and Seungho
lost in thought]
[Who sent the SBM Talk to Hyeyeon and Seungho?]
[Yongkyu: Chaebe, aren't you hungry?]
[Yeah. Uh...]
[Yongkyu: A bit early... The last meal
was around 7 or 8, right?]
[Yongkyu: My first and second choices]
[Yongkyu: went to the secret room together.]
[Yongkyu: Go on a date with me next time.]
[Yongkyu: I sent it to Seungho,
and also to Hyeyeon.]
[Hyeyeon: What's wrong?]
[Seungho: Just guessing
[Seungho: who sent the SBM Talk to you.]
[Seungho: It must be one of those two...]
[Hyeyeon: Not sure...]
[Seungho: I'm guessing on my own.]
[Sigh]
[Hyeyeon: My thoughts are getting complicated.]
[Seungho: Will you go meet them?]
[Hyeyeon: No...]
[Hyeyeon: I don't want to waste a single day.]
[Seungho: I'm also torn.]
[Seungho: I think once...
[Hyeyeon: Go and meet them.]
[Hyeyeon: Maybe you'll find...]
[Hyeyeon: Opportunities like this
don't come often.]
[Hyeyeon: I hope you try going on dates
with others too.]
[Hyeyeon: You might discover something, or]
[Hyeyeon: it might help you firmly choose
between the two.]
[Seungho: That would be too...]
[Seungho: I'd seem too much like a player.]
[Hyeyeon: Why? That's a smart move.]
[Hyeyeon: You should get to know more people
when you have the chance.]
[Seungho: Ah... I don't get it.]
[Seungho: I don't get myself either.]
What should we do?
[Hyeyeon: I don't get myself either.]
[Hyeyeon: So do you need...]
[Hyeyeon: to face it more proactively than today]
[Hyeyeon: to have more positive feelings?]
[Seungho: The... probability... would be
higher like that.]
[Seungho: I prefer being proactive.]
[Hyeyeon: The more I know him,
the more I think he's a good person.]
[Hyeyeon: He has the charm of being honest.]
[Hyeyeon: In the secret room, Seungho also fully
[Hyeyeon: showed this kind of charm.]
[Seungho: When I came to the secret room
with Jinwoo,]
[Seungho: it was a bit awkward,
but there was some excitement.]
[Seungho: With Hyeyeon, it was relaxing
but also heart-fluttering.]
[Seungho: Let's talk for 30 minutes before sleeping?
Hyeyeon: Sure.]
[Hyeyeon: You know, saying that
is the real truth or dare, right?
[Seungho: I have a secret.]
[Hyeyeon: Really? You have a secret?]
[Seungho: Yes, I do.]
[Hyeyeon: What is it?]
[Seungho: I can only tell you
after the week of shooting ends.]
[Hyeyeon: Really?]
[Hyeyeon: Does it have nothing to do with
whether you end up together?]
[Seungho: Yeah.]
[Hyeyeon: Then why did you bring it up?]
[Seungho: Just to tell you I have one.]
[Hyeyeon: Just to say you have a secret?
[Seungho: Yes, I have a secret.]
[Seungho: Even if you knew it,
what would you do with it?]
[Hyeyeon: No, I'm just curious.]
[Hyeyeon: You brought it up yourself,
why are you saying that now?]
[Hyeyeon: I'm not good at guessing either.]
[Seungho: You definitely can't guess it.]
[Seungho: No one would imagine it.]
[Hyeyeon: Really?]
[Seungho: This is only important
to the person who dates me.]
[Hyeyeon: Really? What is it?]
[What is Seungho's
unrevealed secret?]
[Jinwoo: I have some concerns.]
[Jinwoo: Are you willing to listen?
Sujin: Yes!]
[Jinwoo, Sujin, and Yongkyu
chatting in the lounge]
Because so far I've only been with one person...
[Jinwoo: Only one person...
I've been devoted, but...
-Very devoted.
-Devoted, but...
[Jinwoo: But frankly speaking,
I think besides Seungho,]
[Jinwoo: there is no one who is interested in me]
[Jinwoo: or has feelings for me.]
[Jinwoo: The voting results proved this.]
[Jinwoo: The anonymous chat did too.]
[Jinwoo: Looking at the whole situation...]
[Jinwoo: So this situation...]
[Jinwoo: Maybe I brought it upon myself.]
[Jinwoo: Because I didn't make any effort
towards anyone else.]
[Sujin: Only made an effort for one person?]
Yes, I was only focused on chasing him.
[Jinwoo: And for me.]
[Jinwoo: I didn't actually have a second choice
like they said.]
[Jinwoo: Why is this becoming a concern for me?]
[Jinwoo: If Seungho...]
[Sujin: Doesn't choose you anymore?]
[Jinwoo: gradually stops]
[Jinwoo: choosing me and falls for someone else,]
[Jinwoo: then he wouldn't vote for me either.]
[Jinwoo: Won't give me any...]
[Jinwoo: Then I'll be left with 0 points.]
[Jinwoo: I'm riding a very fun rollercoaster
named Seungho.]
[Jinwoo: It feels like the track
suddenly breaks ahead.]
[Jinwoo: And then I just plummeted.]
[Sujin: To be honest, Seungho is the youngest,]
[Sujin: even though he's only
2 years younger than me.]
[Sujin: If it were me at 21,]
[Sujin: and everyone around me
showed interest in me?]
[Sujin: I would want to date everyone.]
[Sujin: That's how it is at that age.
Jinwoo: It would definitely be fun.]
[Sujin: If 5 people all say they like you,]
[Sujin: then you'd want to
talk to everyone too, right?]
[Sujin: If that person says they like me,
what are they attracted to?]
[Sujin: Why are they curious about me?
It's totally possible to think that way.]
[Sujin: So even if Seungho meets other people,]
[Sujin: just assume he's doing it
out of curiosity.]
[Nods.]
[Sujin: Are you convinced by me now?]
[Jinwoo: Yeah, completely convinced now.]
[Sujin: Convinced by me, right?]
[Jinwoo: Problem solved right away.]
Convinced by me, right?
[Yongkyu: And Seungho might also]
[Yongkyu: be trying to make you jealous
on purpose.]
[Yongkyu: But you're acting too much like...]
[Yongkyu: "He's the only one for me."]
[Yongkyu: You're showing it too clearly.]
[Sujin: To him, you're already a sure thing.]
[Sujin: And didn't he say his heart is 6:4?]
[Sujin: I think the 6 is Jinwoo. So...]
[Sujin: You should also show him,]
[Sujin: "Don't take me for granted."]
[Jinwoo: Don't take me for granted?]
[Jinwoo: Are you crazy right now?]
[Sujin: "Don't take me for granted."]
[Sujin: "You think it's natural for me
to be by your side?"]
[Sujin: "I can talk to other people too."]
[Sujin: Just show him this once.]
[Sujin: Because Seungho has been doing it
all along.]
It seems like a good idea.
[Jinwoo seemingly sorting out his thoughts]
[The conviction is temporary,
BI-LIVE begins to waver]
[Past the turning point.
Morning of Day 4 at BI-LIVE]
[Gather at the lounge at 8 o'clock]
[Gently]
[Hyeyeon: Time to get up.
Seungho: OK.]
[Did you fall asleep?]
[Yeah, did you fall asleep?]
[Seungho: Does it count as sleeping?
Hyeyeon: You closed your eyes.]
[Seungho: We talked until really late
before sleeping, so]
[Seungho: it was really tiring waking up.
I slept for about 1 hour?]
[Seungho: 1 and a half hours.
I guess I slept for 1 and a half hours.]
[Yeah.
Seungho: Should I go wash up first?]
[Seungho: Sure.]
[Hyeyeon: I'll lie down a bit longer.]
[Hyeyeon: Because we went to the secret room,
thinking that to others,]
[Hyeyeon: we two have successfully matched up,]
[Hyeyeon: I was happy.]
[Hyeyeon: It feels like we announced it this time,
which makes me quite happy.]
[Seungho: Although I chose Hyeyeon
to come to the secret room with me]
[Seungho: because I was curious about her,]
[Seungho: my heart still leans more
towards Jinwoo, just like before.]
[Seungho's feelings are hard to figure out.
The three-way relationship continues to tangle]
[Jinwoo and Heejin
are busily preparing]
[Someone is quickly preparing
among the two who returned]
[Heejin: Thank you for the depuffing candy.
Jinwoo: It's good, right?]
[Heejin: And I found out it tastes
really good too.]
[Jinwoo: It's really delicious, right?
Heejin: Yes, it's good.]
[Jinwoo: I hope it works.]
-Depuffing candy. -Trusting its effect,
I didn't do my skincare today.
[Heejin: Trusting its effect,
I didn't do my skincare today.]
Got it. Got it.
[Seungho: Can I use this?
Jinwoo: Yeah, go ahead.]
[Jinwoo: What time did you go to bed?
Early morning?]
[Seungho: 4 a.m.]
[Jinwoo: Oh? Really?]
[Jinwoo: Were you playing all the time?]
[Seungho: That's partly it,
but I always have trouble sleeping.]
[Heejin: Has everyone picked their outfits?]
[Yes.]
[Yes, picked.]
Have you picked?
[Jinwoo: It's quite casual today.]
[Heejin: Oh, that's nice.]
[Jinwoo: I'm wearing a beanie today too.]
[Heejin: Today's beanie is giving RIIZE vibes?]
[Jinwoo: More like a CORTIS vibe, right?]
[Jinwoo: More like a CORTIS vibe, right? Sorry...]
[Heejin: I'm looking forward to it.]
[Jinwoo: Actually not CORTIS, just TIS. TIS.]
[Seungho: I'll go put on my contacts.]
[Jinwoo: Ah... my eyes.]
[Jinwoo: My eyes hurt just now,
so I said "eyes."]
[Jinwoo: Ah, my eyes.
(Note: "Eyes" sounds like "sister" in Korean)]
[Jinwoo: That's so funny.]
[Heejin: I really heard it as "sister."]
Really sorry.
[Are you making a joke?]
[-Are you making a joke?
-No, I'm serious.]
[Jinwoo: My eyes hurt just now, so I said "eyes."]
[Heejin: Really sounds like "sister," right?]
Yes.
[Yes.
Heejin: Really sounds like "sister," right?]
[Heejin: So I thought to myself,
I have a younger brother now.]
[Laughter continues in the 4-person room today]
[The members of the 3-person room
busy getting ready]
[Yongkyu: It's 8 o'clock now? 4 minutes left.]
-What? -Incredible.
[Eunchae: Ah, really, don't do this.]
[Eunchae: Eliminated...]
[Eunchae: That might be better.]
[Yongkyu: No, Eunchae, you can do it.]
[Eunchae: Only 4 minutes left?]
[Eunchae: Can I go on camera like this?]
[Yongkyu: Will they blur you out?]
Please.
[Puts on glasses]
[Let me see]
[Yongkyu: Your outfit right now
gives off that vibe.]
[Yongkyu: You look quite good when dressed up.]
[Yongkyu: But right now, you look like
you just woke up and left without contacts.]
[Chaebe: That was my goal.
Yongkyu: Really?]
[Chaebe: The casual look of not being dressed up.]
[Yongkyu: Even though you put a lot of effort in.]
[Yongkyu: I'm going to expose your little secret.
Chaebe: Make it sound nice, please.]
Why? Help me out.
[Yongkyu: Isn't it funny?
Spending an hour doing makeup.]
[Chaebe: It wasn't an hour.]
-Just now... -Not an hour.
[Unlike Day 1's silence, this morning's vibe
in the 3-person room has grown much closer]
Like this, take out glasses and try them on.
It wasn't an hour.
Looks good. Nice.
[Sujin: There's a date selection right now.
Hyeyeon: Let's go to the lounge?]
Hello.
[Members gathering in the lounge
one after another]
The beanie looks nice. What brand is it?
-This. -It's cute.
TAS, probably. TAS.
-Really? -Come over.
[Oh?]
-What is it? -We...
[Two cards placed on the table]
Sit in the middle.
[What kind of dates await them today?]