Master Rak.
My apologies.
I'm cold.
I will serve you forever, Master Rak.
Your precious heart in my care...
I shall never allow it to be marred.
Saen...
Do you know...
when I'm with you,
nowhere else in the world
feels as peaceful.
This life...
asks no more
than to serve and be with my master.
I hope that in our next lives
we are of equal standing.
I could never...
push you away.
[Tanakorn Chuen-arom as Saen/Sand]
[Wacharathon Wongyai as Rak/Lucky]
[Worachai Areewong is Tan/Thank]
[Khitaphat Choothai as Chim/Charm]
[Kornkamon Supaseripap as Vila/ViVi]
[Rungtiva Sangngoen as Prink
Napat Seela as Rit/Ton]
[Chalisa Schaub as Kamala
Weeraachai Hatgovit as Phraya Banleng]
[Nithiroj Simakamtorn as Phraya Dechanarong
Rattanachai Phakdirat as Khon Master]
Every movement
our masters devised
was hard-won.
Go take a break.
We'll continue later.
Thanks a lot. See you.
[Khon Club Performance]
Hey!
Let me join the club.
I'm the real Thotsakan.
Are you?
Do you know the basics?
Nope.
But I can try.
And I was born to be Thotsakan.
Khon is not a toy.
You can't just wear the mask
and randomly move your arms.
Then teach me.
You'll see I'm the right one for Thotsakan.
Sure.
Meet me tomorrow morning.
Seven sharp in the club room.
Okay.
Don't back out.
Me?
Don't run once you see the real thing.
Stop!
Don't touch.
You'll go blind.
Go blind?
Superstitious much?
It's not superstition.
It's respect.
Each Khon mask has its own master.
You must not disrespect it.
You want to get going?
Didn't you say
you wanted to be Thotsakan?
Yes, I do.
I wanna know how hard it could be.
Are you serious?!
If you can't handle this,
do you still think you can be Thotsakan?
Doing this and acting cool
doesn't mean you can teach Khon!
But that means I understand Khon
better than someone
who treats it like a joke.
Then teach me Khon for real!
Stop playing around!
Who said I'm playing around?
This is basic Khon training.
Without faith,
you will never truly understand Khon!
Then you can have
your real Khon and shove it!
Good.
If you can't handle this,
go ahead and leave my club.
Get out!
May today's performance go smoothly.
Sadhu.
I need to poop.
That was fast, geez!
Thanks.
That worked out better than I thought.
You ready, Ton?
Stay mindful.
Don't make a mistake.
[Khon Club Performance 2025,
Fadarun School]
You!
What the hell are you doing?
I'm performing.
Your Khon dancing is so stiff
it's painful to watch.
You've ruined the performance.
You've disrespected the masters.
Don't you realize
this isn't just some ordinary show?
I do.
And I know that if this keeps going,
nobody will care anymore!
You have no right to talk about Khon
when you have absolutely no clue
what it is truly about!
That's exactly why...
I'm making it easier to understand!
Just wait and see.
I'll make my own version of Khon
and bring your club down!
Rit!
What have you done?!
Disgraceful!
My son and servant
committed fornication under my roof!
Prink and I are in love.
And she's carrying your grandchild!
Please stop!
She's with child.
Let her go!
That's our grandchild!
Silence!
I refuse to acknowledge it!
Release her!
Rit!
You!
Saen!
Saen...
Are you well?
Please don't punish Master Rit.
Don't punish his child.
Release me!
Punish me in his place.
Please don't do this, my lord.
Release me!
Please don't do it. It's a sin.
It's a sin.
Take her away to be whipped.
Teach her her place.
And have Rit locked up.
He shall never see another soul again!
Prink!
Master Rit!
Master Rit...
Prink!!
Was it you who told Father?
Traitor!
No, I did not.
I did not dare.
Leave us.
Mother asked me to see you.
She is worried.
You have neither eaten nor slept
for many days.
Saen.
I need to speak with you.
[Phranluang School]
In a few days, I am to perform Khon
before Phraya Dechanarong.
I ask that
you wear the Thotsakan mask in my place.
When that day comes,
I shall run away with Prink.
I...
shall help.
Saen.
What are you doing?
Have you gone mad?
Those movements...
are most certainly not Rit's.
Stop!
Prink.
Master Rit, you should not be here.
I cannot stand by.
If we remain beneath this roof,
you will die,
and I shall be dead while yet alive.
A servant's life such as mine
is hardly a beautiful one.
How could you remain with one such as I?
I should not let you suffer with me.
And yet I will.
I can endure anything,
so long as I am with you.
We shall make our escape,
whatever the cost.
Rit...
Are you truly Rit?
He has taken ill.
He grows faint and unsteady.
I fear he may faint.
I should bring him inside to rest.
If you grow faint or dizzy,
remove the mask at once.
Why persist in wearing it?
I do not think
he would prefer that at the moment.
What about when we return?
Remove your mask at once!
Saen!!
I must apologize.
Where is your wretched master?!
Go home at once!!
Do not let him get away!!
How dare you!
I alone shall take the blame.
That is not your decision to make!
I asked you where your master is!
I do not know.
Father.
- Saen may...
- Rak!
Do you know where your brother went?
Master Rak knows nothing of it.
I asked my son!!
Not you!!
Do not intervene!
Bind him and lock him in here!
Take Rak away!!
Release me!
Saen!
- Saen!
- Rak!
Get out. All of you.
Do not let anyone in until I say otherwise.
Saen...
Look how badly they have hurt you.
I apologize for what I've done.
Does it hurt?
Why did you do it?
Master Rit's child is important as well.
I fear the child
will grow up without a father.
To perform as Thotsakan
for my brother...
how could you agree to it?
I was willing to.