[English subtitles are available]
[The Heart of Genius]
[Episode 16]
Most importantly,
Ji Jiang has become my brother.
What happened?
I don't know.
Maybe it's the result
of our previous stay.
But I'm thinking
that in the Strawberry World,
Hua Juan has started
to be in commercials
and has become popular at this time.
But now,
he has nothing.
He still likes singing.
He even wants to participate in the singing competition.
How about
we talk about it
at school tomorrow?
Your parents are there, right?
Okay, I'll tell you at school tomorrow.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
Dad.
Come on, let's play cards.
What did Lin Zhaoxi want from you?
We were just chatting.
Are you going to play this round?
Yes.
Catch the landlord!
After two years,
the Super Singer is coming again.
From now on,
this music reality show
which created
idol singers
like Song Zihou and Lu Wen,
will start its audition.
Yesterday afternoon,
the director of Super Singer, Jiang Dongmei,
was interviewed.
Get up. Get up. Get up.
You're late. Get up.
I won't heat up the milk.
Drink the cold milk.
What time is it?
It's 6:30. Hurry. We're late.
Sister, what's wrong with you?
It's your turn to make breakfast today.
You got up late again.
Hurry up and eat.
Come on.
Have you packed your bag?
No.
No? Go and pack your bag.
Go. Leave after you finish eating.
Hurry up.
Have you brushed your teeth and washed your face?
No.
Go and brush your teeth. Hurry up.
Be quick. We're late.
Hurry up and finish eating.
I'm not full yet.
Hurry up.
I'll take you to the bus stop after you're done.
Hurry up. Go.
Where's your motorcycle?
I sold it.
Didn't you say it's not safe?
Come on.
Yes, hold the big seat.
-This is good too.
-Let's go.
Dad, aren't you
too slow?
Am I slow?
Aren't you slow?
Let's compete later.
You take the bus and I ride.
Let's see who arrives first.
Can you drive faster?
I...
How about I run over there?
No, no, no.
It's dangerous.
I'll speed up.
Did you speed up?
Yes.
The bus is leaving.
Look at my speed.
Look.
It's speeding up.
We're here. Don't worry.
We're here.
Hurry up.
It has left.
Did you ride so slowly on purpose?
Am I that childish?
The game begins.
Childish.
Good morning.
How did you get here?
I took the bus.
I came by bus too.
I was exhausted from running.
I rode my bike here.
Go on. Take me with you.
Sorry, sir.
I haven't been to school for so long.
Be quiet.
Hua Juan has become my brother.
But now,
he's still a poor student.
But in the Strawberry World, Hua Juan
has started to be in commercials
and has become popular at this time.
I guess this is the change
I brought to the world for the first time I came here.
Without Professor Ji’s help,
his future is in doubt.
If he can't become a star,
it will be all my fault.
The teacher is coming.
Every world
has its own unique running rules.
Chatting.
You kept chatting after I left.
The teacher left.
Senior high school students are suffering.
I have found
that feeling.
I think it's good
to have fun in bitterness.
He drew a picture for himself.
I feel guilty.
Just like the one on it,
he marked the land and the bridge.
Then he put a dot.
For Hua Juan.
He connected each of these areas.
Maybe it will be better
for Hua Juan to take part in talent shows.
I don't think so.
Lin Zhaoxi.
Stand up.
Look at you.
You've become a bad student.
But you still don't work hard.
You should focus in class.
Read the second part
of Part 3 for me.
If you stutter a little,
stand until the class is over.
If a figure
has more than two odd points,
you cannot go over it
without lifting your pencil from the page
or going over a line twice.
Quickly he went to his textbooks
to find some more figures.
He looked at the four diagrams...
Okay, be quiet.
Pay attention to the lecture.
Don't play any tricks.
Sit down.
Okay, let's continue.
Do you still have the recorder?
I want to listen to it a few more times.
Here.
Thank you.
Take it.
I've memorized
all the details.
Don't worry. I'll definitely take you back.
Xi.
What do you think of
the life
in this Cheese World?
Pretty good.
Your dad and my dad
are healthy.
The superstar, Hua Juan is here.
He is also my brother.
Do you know
what's the best?
We are
a pair of
well-known mysterious deskmates.
We can also be legends
of Experimental High School.
Have you ever thought
that it would be good
for us
to live in this world?
We're from the Strawberry World.
Why should we stay here?
Why not?
I mean,
since we can
come to this world,
we have
one more chance than other people
to choose our lives.
All our important family members
are here.
And most importantly,
you and I are still together.
We can go
to Sanwei University to study maths.
What we lost
in the Strawberry World
can be found here.
I don't understand
there's a choice question
with a standard answer.
Why should we
choose a wrong one?
Listen to me, Pei Zhi.
Yes, this world is wonderful.
But if there are rocks in our socks,
what we need to do is
taking the stones out
instead of changing the shoes.
My dad
is the sick Lin.
He needs me.
I can't lose him.
I know what it feels to lose him.
I've known it since I was young.
Xi.
If you let me
return to the Strawberry World,
that means
I need to lose my father again.
I'm not brave enough
to see my dad
disappear twice in front of me.
We still have time.
Let's think about it again.
Okay?
Now let's look at this question.
The common ratio is 2.
The summation of first five terms, S5, is 1.
Calculate the summation of first ten items, S10.
You can use this formula.
S5 equals
1 minus a1/q multiply by 1 minus the fifth power of q.
The answer is 1.
Pei Zhi's father is a traffic police.
But in the Strawberry World,
his father passed away
when he was in junior high school.
Studying maths deeply
will trigger my illness.
I'm a patient.
I don't know how to face you.
Cognitive disorder
is one of the most difficult problems
in the diagnosis and treatment
of diseases of the brain.
Many patients with cognitive disorders
don't know their family members anymore.
I'm going to resign.
I'm going to study maths.
I'll find Pei Zhi
and tell him I love him.
Even if he might reject me,
I will take good care of you
and myself.
If you don't want him to die,
don't let him study maths.
So we can calculate
a1 is 1/31.
The common ratio is two
and a1 is 1/31.
We'll take them together into the formula.
So, S10 is
33.
Sorry, we have to go back.
Guys,
it's lunch break.
There will be a basketball game in the afternoon.
I hope the players can
do their best.
But be careful with the safety.
Don't get hurt.
Come on.
Cheer for the players.
Class 13 will win!
Class is over.
Stand up.
Goodbye, teacher.
I see.
Let's go, Pei Zhi.
We'll discuss tactics while having lunch.
Let's go.
How are we going to have lunch?
Xiaomeng.
Let's go, Qi.
Let's have lunch.
You are no longer
a member of our trio.
Go eat by yourself.
Unless you agree
to be one of the cheerleaders again,
you'll have the chance
to have lunch with us.
Come on, Xiaomeng.
Give me some time.
We are such good friends.
You must know me too.
If I don't want to do it,
there must be the reason
I don't want to do it.
What's the reason?
I had heatstroke that day.
As you can see,
my physical condition
very bad now.
I will faint as soon as I get on that stage.
Forget it.
You tried to take me
to climb over the school gate yesterday.
Lin Zhaoxi.
Stop making excuses.
You started this.
Are you afraid of embarrassing yourself now?
Yes, I am.
But
I don't have time to announce
that my naive teenage period is over.
Let me tell you this.
In puberty,
people tend to be emotional
and do something impulsively.
But if you think back
these things
when you grow up,
you'll very embarrassed.
You'll even want to slap yourselves.
Oh my god.
Lin Zhaoxi.
Are you really
at the same age as us?
You look
like my cousin in her 20s
who has never been in a relationship.
You've been acting strange
after you had heatstroke that day.
You used to
to join in the fun.
When you pursued Zheng Tianming,
you were even more shameless than me.
You think we will lose our faces
after just one day?
Fine.
We're not good enough for you.
Go eat by yourself.
Let's go.
She seems to be reflecting on herself.
Should we give her another chance?
Why are you back?
I'll give you another chance.
Do you want to join us?
Or I'll tell Uncle Lin
that Zhaoxi and Xiaoxiao
are eager to buy milk tea for Zheng Tianming.
Dear Xiaomeng.
Well.
Consider it as your payment
for helping me take care of Lin.
I'll go, okay?
Great.
We'll teach you again.
Hurry up.
-Let's eat in the canteen.
-Help me, Qi.
Let's go.
Wait.
When did I take care of Uncle Lin?
-Come on! Come on!
-Good job!
Class 1 will lose!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Zhang Liang is so handsome.
Don't worry.
Are you crazy?
Are you insane?
What are you doing?
Who are you?
Come on!
Zhang Liang, come on!
Come on, Class 13!
Zheng Tianming is more handsome!
Zhang Liang is so handsome! Zhang Liang is more handsome!
Zheng Tianming is the most handsome!
Zhang Liang is handsome,
smart,
and good at playing basketball.
He isn't like you guys who are bad at
studying and playing basketball.
What are you talking about?
It's enough.
Watch the game.
We are students. What do you mean?
I mean the literal meaning.
Take a break.
Baby, let's go.
Gather around.
Great!
Gather around. Gather around.
Now we are behind in the score.
But it's okay.
We can catch up.
Let's keep an eye on them. Stay calm.
They can't win.
Get the score back.
Leave more space and let me make three-point shots.
Okay?
Come on. Three, two, one.
Class 13.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Catch up with them.
Come on.
Xiaomeng.
Qi.
Listen.
Let's
wear these later.
What are these?
These are masks.
Let's dance with them.
Look.
Am I cute?
That's the cutest way.
Right?
I have confidence in you.
But I have no confidence in me.
You can do it. Go.
Let's go.
♫Like you, like you baby♫
♫Just want to be closer to you♫
♫To hear the heartbeat more accurately♫
♫Break into your world by accident♫
♫Everything about you is attractive to me♫
♫Like you, like you baby♫
♫I really like you, like you♫
The break is over.
The second half starts.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Defense!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
What did you do?
You hit him.
You're unscrupulous.
Sorry.
I was not on purpose.
What did you do?
Get out of the way.
Do you want to play?
Yes.
The game continues.
Defence!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Wait, referee.
The score was
37 to 45.
Why is our team 33 now?
Well.
This is a good opportunity.
The fall is worth four points.
It's quite special to get three plus one points.
Referee.
The score should be
37 to 45.
Mr. Wang.
Just change it
into 37 to 45.
They can't win
even we give them four more points.
That's right.
It doesn't matter.
What do you mean by giving us four points?
We have indeed got 37 points.
Okay.
Just change it into 37 to 45.
The game continues.
Give you four points.
What do you mean?
Say it again.
What do you mean by giving us four points?
So what?
Did you fight too?
No.
What are you doing here?
When have you become
the principal of Experiment High School?
I transferred here last month.
What? Do I need to report to you
my job transfer?
No need.
I'm the witness.
Principal.
Tell me.
What happened just now?
The student from Class 1
fouled Zheng Tianming from our class
during the game,
causing Zheng Tianming
to fall down.
At the same time, Zheng knocked over the table
where the scoreboard was placed.
The game was interrupted.
Players of both sides
had some minor conflicts.
Then, the scoreboard was put back.
But our score
was changed
from 37 to 33.
Zheng Tianming found this mistake
and pointed it out.
But none of Class 1's students admitted it.
Zhang Liang said
it could be changed into 37 points.
But your attitude was bad
as if our class was cheating.
But our class really got 37 points.
Our class
raised doubts.
Then, they pushed someone of our class
and we had some conflicts with them.
That's all?
That's all.
Zhang Liang, what happened?
Principal, here's how it happened.
Chen Chu accidentally
knocked Zheng Tianming down.
Class 13 wanted to take the chance to get more points
and caused conflicts with us.
You...
Sir.
Can I say something?
Go ahead.
The score of our class was indeed
37 points.
I remember the scoring record
from the beginning of the basketball game
to the break.
You're bragging.
Here's the scoring order
of Class 13.
A lay-up. A perimeter shot. A free throw.
A rebound.
Two perimeter shots. A three-point shot.
Two lay-ups. A three-point shot.
A rebound. A tip-in.
Two three-point shots.
A three-point shot. A perimeter shot.
A three-point shot. A lay-up.
It's 37 points in total.
Sir, if you need,
I can give you
the names and numbers of the students
who scored each time.
I can also tell you
everything that was going on at that time.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Class 1.
What else do you want to say?
Sir, I...
I may not remember
as clearly as him.
Maybe the score
was wrong.
But we didn't make it on purpose.
They couldn't hit us.
You pushed me first.
I pushed you means I hit you?
The guy from your class
gave me a kick.
Are you done?
Do you want to continue to fight?
You're in 12th grade.
You shouldn't hold
any basketball game.
Some teachers said
it could relax you
and lighten your pressure.
I said it was not necessary.
Look.
Well.
Class 13 stays here.
Class 1, go back to the classroom.
Thank you, principal.
You were all good.
You even cared about the score of basketball.
But your grades are getting lower.
Why don't you care about it?
All of you
like to fight with others actively.
Everyone wants to be a hero.
A hero.
Just wait.
I'll record you serious demerits.
I have a problem, principal.
What do you think?
It's none of your business. Go to play.
Before I play,
I need to tell you the thing clearly.
It was Class 1's fault.
Why?
Why does only Class 13 get punished?
Do you have any evidence?
Everyone saw it.
It's useless.
You said class 1 started it.
But they said it was your fault.
Who should I believe?
Anyway, I think
you should ask more people.
You should find out the truth at least.
I don't have the time
to do research.
Your arguments were different.
I chose to believe
the one who performed better.
Was I wrong?
Perform better.
Does better performance mean
good grades?
Yes.
I don't think good grades
can represent everything.
It doesn't mean
good morality.
And everyone in Class 1
were all arrogant.
I think if you were me,
you should also be unable to stand it.
Lin Zhaoxi.
Shut up your mouth.
Since you were a kid,
you've been so impressive.
You can be the principal.
You're the principal,
but you can't abuse your authority.
What a serious accusation!
Let me tell you.
I didn't want to only focus on the study.
But I had to make a decision.
Just now,
both of you expressed your opinions
and wanted to stay here.
How long would it take?
Stay here until the final exam?
There are less than 300 days
to the college entrance exam.
Less than 300 days.
Everyone.
Please wake up.
Well.
I'll deal with it later.
Go back now.
Go.
Have you thought about
your future?
What if you have no college to go after the college entrance exam?
You'll be done for.
You'll be shocked.
Good job.
Class 13 never gives up!
Never give up.
Classmates.
Thank you.
My dad said
we should have integrity.
Right?
Yes.
The reason that I can fight dauntlessly ahead
is your support
behind our backs.
Good job, Class 13!
Bravo! Bravo!
You really think you're a hero?
Go back and sit down.
All of you
are getting bolder.
You just kept calm for a few days.
You're making trouble again.
How dare you fight with others?
Mr. Xie.
Class 1 started the conflicts.
That's why the following things happened.
Did I ask you to speak?
Sit down.
I have only one question.
You must answer me honestly.
Which class
started today's conflicts?
Class 1.
Okay, I trust you.
I'll go to the principal now.
Good. Good. Good.
Study quietly.
Mr. Xie, I love you.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Teacher Zhang.
I feel that you have handled
today's matter quite unfairly.
If I remember correctly,
since I came to Experiment High School,
you've been calling me Principal Zhang.
Why do you
call me Teacher Zhang again today?
What do you think?
Fighting is definitely wrong.
But both parties are responsible.
And it was Class 1
started it.
Why only my class's students
were punished?
Class 1 said
your class started it.
Teacher Zhang.
I believe my students.
The class teacher of Class 1, Ms. Ma,
also believes her students.
Teacher Zhang.
You can't draw such a conclusion
just because the two classes
have different grades.
Mr. Xie.
Of course I know
grades can't represent
one's character.
The reason why
I only criticized your students
was that I wanted to use
this opportunity
to stimulate them.
I wanted to let them be brave after they felt ashamed
and make them focus on their study.
I wanted to turn this fight
into a good thing
that could let them make progress.
Here's my opinion.
Teacher Zhang, you've done a lot.
I understand.
But I disagree with you.
You might
ruin their values of right and wrong.
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
I just think
during these years,
you look
like a dough.
Everyone can pinch it.
But you're actually a piece of iron.
Good.
Thank you for your compliment.
I'm not praising you.
How was Lin Zhaoxi?
How did she react?
She was still
the same as when she was a child.
She was so angry.
But this
had nothing to do with her.
I believe it.
Okay, it's effective.
How about this?
When you go back,
tell your students
everyone in the fight
will be punished.
I won't record it in the archives.
At the end of the semester, students with good performance
can automatically cancel their demerits.
The students include those from Class 1.
Thank you, Teacher Zhang.
You should
keep an eye on Lin Zhaoxi.
Supervise her.
She's quite good. Let her work harder.
I see.
You're all top students.
How could you fight
with those bad students from Class 13?
Sir, they started the fight.
That's right.
But you couldn't fight back.
You should come to the teacher.
The school has decided
that everyone in the fight,
no matter from Class 1 or Class 13,
should be punished.
Why?
Only those who perform well
can cancel their demerits at the end of the semester.
Okay, be quiet.
Class begins now.
How are you going home?
I'll take the bus.
My dad is on night duty today.
I'll take you home.
No need.
We both have different routes home.
Forget it if you don't want to.
I didn't say I didn't want to.
Well.
If you insist on taking me home,
I accept it.
You don't have to say that.
How do you feel today?
Quite lively, right?
I used to think
life in senior high school was hard.
But from today's experience,
it's not bad actually.
Yes.
Especially when you dance...
No, don't mention it.
Don't mention it.
I want to find a crack to go in.
No.
I think your dancing was cute.
Many movements were wrong.
Really?
I can't see.
No.
Your movements
were totally different
from the other two.
Don't tell the truth.
But when you stood in the middle
and danced differently from them,
it looked like it was your design in advance.
It was very natural.
That's more like it.
How unlucky.
Class 13 was bad at playing basketball.
They wouldn't win even if we gave them 10 more points.
This little thing
made our game canceled.
We also got punished.
What should we do?
This is my first time being punished.
What are you afraid of?
The demerits will be canceled certainly.
Liang is also
with us.
If my dad knows,
he'll beat me to death.
I have to apply to study abroad.
Will it affect me?
It will be fine.
The demerits will be canceled certainly.
If it doesn't work,
at the end of the semester,
I'll ask my dad to come to school
to talk to the principal.
My dad knows
the director of the education authority.
Liang, I'm counting on you.
It's okay.
When will the audition
that Hua Juan signed up start?
Maybe on the weekend.
Look.
Lin Zhaoxi and Pei Zhi.
Can we watch it on TV?
Zhang Liang and his friends.
Pei Zhi.
I'm so disappointed in you.
I thought
although you went to Class 13
for this girl,
your heart was on Class 1's side.
But today,
you helped outsiders.
Actually, I always think
Zhang Liang is quite interesting.
I've never seen a man
who could keep his naive teenage period
for such a long time.
Was he always like this
in the Strawberry World?
Yes.
Did you hear me?
Zhang Liang, this afternoon,
I just told the truth.
I didn't mean to side with anyone.
You're quibbling. You should be punished.
Traitor!
No, no, everyone.
You just got punished today.
Do you want to be expelled from school?
Liang, I think what she said
makes sense.
We should be more cautious.
Don't be afraid.
This is not the school.
Teachers can't control us now.
Pei Zhi.
How about this?
I'll give you another chance.
Go back to Class 1.
There's nothing good in Class 13.
If you really go there
for this girl,
I can tutor her
with you,
so that she can come to Class 1.
No, no, no.
You don't need to tutor me.
-You might as well beat me.
-You have no right to speak.
One against six.
Can you defeat them?
Yes.
But I don't want to hurt them.
After all, they are just children.
What should we do?
Let's leave.
Are you two in tune with each other
like doing crosstalk?
He don't let us go.
Let's run.
Liang.
Wait.
Can you still run?
Yes.
What are they playing?
Chase them!
Okay.
Wait for me.
Young people nowadays
can run so fast.
If we can't escape,
we have to beat them up.
Don't fight. Don't fight.
We're friends. We're friends.
Who is your friend?
Zhang Liang.
I've known you for so many years.
Aren't you angry with Pei Zhi
that he don't play with you?
Pei Zhi.
You can talk to him.
He's not a bad guy.
I'll beat you up.
You just pay lip service to that.
When did you ever hit me?
Let me tell you.
Have you been punished
already?
If anything happens again,
I'll tell the school tomorrow.
Nobody will have a good result.
Are you a member of Class 1?
How can you betray us?
Lu Zhihao.
It's none of your business.
I can handle it.
Don't do that.
Calm down. Calm down. Calm down.
Listen to me.
Some of you wants to be recommended to colleges
or go abroad, right?
If you're punished seriously,
it's all over.
Yes, Liang.
I think Hao is right.
We are classmates.
We don't have much hatred of each other.
Right?
Yes.
Liang, when we were young, we were in a team
and won the gold medal of Olympic mathematics competition.
I forgot about it.
Xi.
I haven't played billiards for days.
I miss you.
Tell me if you're in trouble.
I'll protect you.
Look at
the friends she makes.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
Sorry, brother.
We are classmates.
Who is your brother?
This friend,
I don't know you.
If you don't leave,
I'll call the police.
Call the police?
Try it.
Xi, tell me, Brother Da Tou.
Are they your classmates?
Who told you to tell the teacher?
Xi.
How intimate they are.
Do you want to be hit?
Stop fighting!
Stop fighting! Stop fighting!
He's my friend in the welfare home.
Stop fighting!
Stop!
Let's go.
Something happened.
Lu.
How long will you
sit here?
Until you
promise me.
I said I would think about it.
Don't be ignorant.
I'm not doing this for you.
These two kids
are going to college soon.
The annual tuition and living expenses
will be about 40,000 to 50,000 yuan.
Why don't you open a cram school?
Is you salary enough now?
I told you.
My research is just one step away from being finished.
Zhaosheng, let's be realistic.
On the way of fundamental mathematics,
many people
have almost reached the end
in just a distance of hair.
But he probably
can never shorten
such little distance.
Even the finishing line
is wrong. It doesn't exist.
What you are studying
is a part of P=NP problem.
Even if you succeed,
you can only gain
recognition from the academic world.
It's still far from gaining fame and fortune.
You can't get these.
I don't think so.
I have stuck to one thing for 20 years.
You want me to give up now?
I don't want to.
I don't ask you
to give up on your research.
You should focus on your teaching.
You can do whatever you want
in your spare time.
If I teach students every day,
I won't have any spare time.
I'll support their tuition.
Will you accept it?
Xi.
Hello?
The patient has an ulnar radius fracture
and multiple contusions.
He needs a timely incisional composite
and an nternal plate fixation surgery.
My son
wants to be a surgeon.
Will it affect him?
It's hard to say.
It depends on the recovery.
I'll get ready.
Thank you, doctor.
Actually, no one saw
how Lu fell down.
You can't
only blame our family for this.
Mom.
Actually, it was my fault.
If we hadn't
gone to Pei Zhi,
the latter things wouldn't have happened.
Look at you.
Are you out of your mind because of hard study?
Zhang Liang.
Where are the other students
who participated in the fight?
Principal Zhang, they all went back.
This has nothing to do with them.
If there's anything wrong,
I'll take the responsibility.
Principal Zhang.
Why are you here?
Actually,
they were just playing.
They were definitely not fighting.
Absolutely not.
I think it was just an accident.
An accident?
Zhang Liang’s mom.
If your son
is lying on the bed,
can you
be so casual?
-Mom.
-How could you say that?
It was an accident.
It's okay, Zhang Liang.
We're still friends.
Your arm has been hurt.
How could it be an accident?
Everyone saw it.
They saw it.
Well, Zhang Liang’s mom.
Actually, our family
-is willing to pay medical fees.
-I don't want to hear your explanation.
-Mom.
His arm has been hurt.
Is this about medical expenses now?
Do you think you can just give me some money?
Did you do it?
Everyone saw it.
-Auntie.
-Don't worry.
Mom.