[English subtitles are available]
[The Heart of Genius]
[Episode 34]
[Faculty Apartment]
[Boys' Apartment]
Sister.
Let's go. I've been waiting for you for a long time.
I'm here now.
In the Cheese World, Lin Zhaoxi didn't choose
to be in school again.
She paid to go
to the art college Hua Juan was in.
[Tomorrow's Film]
She studied for two years
in the adult art management class.
Hello, Ms. Lin.
Remember to iron all the clothes.
Okay.
Hua Juan became popular soon.
Lin Zhaoxi in the Cheese World
became the agent of Hua Juan
and entered the entertainment industry.
She set up a company two years later.
Ms. Lin, please sign it.
[Look forward to the future]
With Hua Juan's popularity,
the company was growing.
Okay. Thank you, Ms. Lin.
Hello, Ms. Lin. Hello, Ms. Lin.
Ms. Lin.
She worked harder than everyone else.
She only slept for four and a half hours,
ran for half an hour,
and spent one hour each for lunch and dinner every day.
The rest of her time was working.
Lin Zhaoxi and Hua Juan in the Cheese World
were rising like comets.
In the second year of my postgraduate studies,
[The 23-year-old Queen of Entertainment, Lin Zhaoxi]
she had become the youngest president
of large entertainment companies.
[The 23-year-old Queen of Entertainment, Lin Zhaoxi]
And I had been working with my master
who kept healthy.
We successfully proved
[2018 National Math Academia Commendation Ceremony]
the graph isomorphism problem was NP-Complete.
To celebrate for us,
Hua Juan gathered all friends of the Lin's class
to enjoy hot pot.
Everyone had graduated.
Hua Juan and his makeup artist
were in a relationship.
Bao Xiaomeng opened
a small pet clinic.
Zheng Tianming was a high-speed rail attendant.
Lu Zhihao, who failed to be Hua Juan's agent,
became a medical postgraduate.
Zhang Liang continued to study
his favorite physics major.
On that day,
we talked about the past.
Everyone was happy.
Only she
didn't come because of her work.
That's amazing.
Lin Zhaoxi.
I have something to do in the company.
I have to leave.
This package belongs to my dad.
Please give it to him.
Xi is gone?
Master.
She asked me to give you this.
I'll leave too.
Many years later,
the master told me
what he received
was the letter from your mother to you.
Professor Feng kept it
all these years.
Professor Feng's students
returned the letter to Lin
in accordance with her last wishes.
[Lin Zhaosheng, when you read this letter, I've already passed away]
[I thought about it for a long time and finally decided to write this letter]
When you read this letter,
I've already passed away.
I thought about it for a long time
and finally decided
to write this letter.
In this world,
there are many people who are more talented than you.
Mom.
Let me ask you again.
Are you going back with me?
Mom.
How many times have I told you?
I won't go back to Yongchuan.
I don't want to be a counselor.
If you miss me,
you can come back to see me anytime.
But my house is too small.
I have no place to stay for you.
Mom, I...
Mom!
About you and my daughter,
I will never
forgive you.
But I regret
for the matter of Xi.
Please allow me to apologize.
I give Qiu Yue's last letter
[Lin Zhaosheng, when you read this letter, I've already passed away]
[I thought about it for a long time and finally decided to write this letter]
back to you.
I hope I can make up
my mistakes.
That letter evoked
the master's memories of his wife.
He cherished that letter very much.
One night,
he tried to remove the blood stain on it.
When the first blood stain
was removed,
he travelled to the year of 1995.
This business can be handled
in the first room on the left ahead.
[Reference Desk]
Okay, thank you.
You're welcome.
Hello.
I...
[Tian'an District, Anping City]
[People's Court]
Sir. Sir. Sir.
Sir, what's wrong?
What should we do?
He has woken up.
Sir, are you okay?
Where am I?
Here's the court.
You fainted.
Are you not feeling well?
Let's go to the hospital.
Take care.
What day is it today?
It's February 20th.
What year is it?
It's 1995.
Sorry, sir.
I'll borrow your bike.
Sir. Sir.
Sir.
The master thought
he went back to the past.
But when he returned to the desk,
he realized
nothing had changed
in his world.
What we just arrived
wasn't the past of the Cheese World,
it was the Strawberry World
you mentioned before.
He changed your fate.
[Stick to the policy of rejuvenating the country through science and try to improve the medical technology level]
We stopped the hemorrhage.
[Operating Room]
But the mother suffered great postpartum bleeding
and it was too late to give her a blood transfusion.
[No Smoking]
She left her child a few words before she passed away.
[Anaesthesiology Department]
I wrote it down for you.
[I love you, although I've only seen you once. I want to be with you forever, but I have to leave]
[You have no memory of me. I don't regret that. Don't have any imagination about me]
[Imagination can bring sadness. I'm just an ordinary mother who has gone far away]
I love you,
although I've only seen you once.
I want to be with you forever,
but I have to leave.
You have no memory of me.
I don't regret that.
Don't have any imagination about me.
Imagination can bring sadness.
I'm just an ordinary mother
who has gone far away.
The master didn't
tell me
about the travel immediately.
In the next decade,
I researched the P=NP problem
while looking for a way
to come to the Strawberry World.
I succeeded in the first thing.
But I failed
at the second thing.
Lin and I proved that P=NP.
My career, wealth and fame
had reached the top.
I changed the world.
But I was still unhappy.
I bought your old house
and kept it the way it was twenty years ago.
I lived there.
One day, the master came to see me.
I always thought
you would give up.
I didn't expect you to hold on for so long.
There's one thing I don't understand.
You haven't been together for long.
Why do you love her so much?
I don't know
what unit should be used to measure the love.
But for me,
it can't be the time.
Maybe this can help you.
[I love you, although I've only seen you once. I want to be with you forever, but I have to leave]
[You have no memory of me. I don't regret that. Don't have any imagination about me]
[Imagination can bring sadness. I'm just an ordinary mother who has gone far away]
I couldn't wait to remove
the second blood stain.
But nothing happened.
I realized that I was impulsive
and I wasted a precious opportunity.
I should be careful.
[Strawberry  2018 Cheese 2006]
[Strawberry 2018 Cheese 2012]
[Strawberry 2019 Cheese 1995]
The characters and numbers were uncertain.
The formula and blood stains could start the travel.
[Blood stains] [Letter]
They had similar forms.
They were all removed.
[Strawberry 2018 Cheese 2006]
[Strawberry 2018 Cheese 2012]
[Strawberry 2019 Cheese 1995]
They might be related.
[Time] [People]
What determined
the time points of travels?
[Anchor]
I need other anchors.
[Strawberry 2018 Cheese 2006] [Lin Zhaoxi, Ji Jiang]
[Strawberry 2018 Cheese 2012] [Lin Zhaoxi, Pei Zhi]
[Strawberry 2019 Cheese 1995] [Lin Zhaosheng]
I had nothing
[Anchor]
related to the Strawberry World.
So, I thought of
those two things.
[Zhang Liang, Lin Zhaoxi, Pei Zhi]
[Lin Zhaosheng, Zhang Shuping]
The photo and the recorder
were related to you.
They were my only choice.
I could only take a bet.
There was only one blood stain left.
I had only one chance.
I needed to prepare more.
I started to think
about all kinds of situations
after travelling to the Strawberry World.
Most importantly,
I needed to think about how to deal with Pei Zhi in the Strawberry World.
I started to learn
how to hypnotize myself.
Let me tell you.
Hypnosis
is a process
of self-exploration.
In the whole
hypnosis process,
you need to trust me completely
and relax yourself.
-Okay? -Okay.
Let's start now.
Take a deep breath.
Relax.
You can feel
your eyelids are getting heavier.
Relax yourself greatly.
Imagine there's a beam of light
shining above your head.
You feel warm,
comfortable and relaxed.
Take a deep breath.
Your forehead is relaxing.
Your eyebrows
are relaxing slowly.
[I love you, although I've only seen you once. I want to be with you forever, but I have to leave]
[You have no memory of me. I don't regret that. Don't have any imagination about me]
[Imagination can bring sadness. I'm just an ordinary mother who has gone far away]
Everything was ready.
I started my last attempt.
I erased the last blood stain.
[August 12th, 2018]
I did it.
Wait.
So, you...
When did you
come to the Strawberry World?
August 12th, 2018.
That's impossible.
Back then,
I had never gone to the boxing club.
Was it you
who I found at the beginning?
We're really friends.
We're also alumni.
Don't talk nonsense outside.
Especially don't talk to
people who like to post Moments in your shop.
It will be bad for him.
You care so much about him.
How could you say there was nothing between you two?
Pei Zhi.
Pei Zhi?
You already have Ji Jiang.
Why do you still want Pei Zhi?
[Qu Jingjing Hot and Sour Rice Noodles]
I'm hanging up now.
[Private Boxing Lessons]
I never thought
I would meet you here.
Are you avoiding me on purpose?
The person you met was him.
I was very excited
when I just travelled to this world.
I wanted to see you right away.
So, I rushed to your house
and saw you and the master
arguing from afar.
Has Pei Zhi graduated?
Has he returned to China?
I don't know.
Don't you like him?
He went to Germany
without a word.
I couldn't contact him.
Why would I like him?
You were so eager
to go to Germany to meet him.
But I gave up.
I've grown up.
Nothing is difficult in the world
as long as you give it up.
Is this growth?
Growing up is about learning to compromise.
I immediately realized a problem.
You hadn't
experienced travel at that time.
You and I had never met.
A person's experience
determines who he or she is.
At that time,
you were still not
Lin Zhaoxi that I knew.
Is it more difficult than
solving the P=NP problem after we learned the Pythagoras Theorem?
That's enough, dad.
I've heard enough chicken soup for the soul.
My hiccups smell like the chicken soup.
I really don't want to hear it.
I remembered what you did
in your two travels.
You didn't change
the history of the Cheese World.
And you are a part of
of the Cheese World.
At this moment,
I also became a part of
of the Strawberry World.
I was making up for the past.
Who is it?
According to my plan
based on the temporal logic,
you would find
the photo
I put in the mailbox.
That was the opportunity to interfere with
what was happening in the two worlds.
It was also the key
to get to and from the Cheese World for the first time.
[Group 1: Lin Zhaosheng, Zhang Shuping]
[Group 2: Pei Zhi, Lin Zhaoxi]
I finally found you.
[Pei Zhi, Lin Zhaoxi]
[Lin Zhaosheng, Zhang Shuping]
Why do you have this photo?
This is the photo
of the members of Zhang Shuping's training camp.
I even took part in it.
Where are you going?
Calm down.
Don't do this.
Don't touch me.
Even if I have travelled to the year of 2006,
I shouldn't be
at the welfare home.
I have my home.
I've grown up
with my dad.
Why am I here?
[Certification]
[Lin Zhaoxi, female, born on February 25th, 1995]
[was found abandoned at the Hongxing Children Welfare Home in February, 1995]
What's the reason
caused all this?
The photo?
The formula? Or anything else?
Do you think we can go back?
In order not to affect
your second travel,
and in order to collect more information
and hide my background,
I decided to carry out
one of my plans.
That was to hypnotize myself
and hide inside the body of Pei Zhi in the Strawberry World.
[Choose the target date]
I know you didn't take the postgraduate entrance exam
when you travelled to that world.
[Finished]
[The countdown is 246 days]
I set a countdown
with the postgraduate entrance exam as the time point.
I hid the timing application
and waited for you to finish your two travels.
On the next evening,
Pei Zhi in the Strawberry World woke up.
Because
I controlled my body for a short time
and I did it after he fell asleep,
he didn't realize the problem.
He just found
there was a Newton's cradle
and a recording pen on the table.
Pei Zhi.
Pei Zhi, are you still there?
Wait for me.
What's wrong?
Lin is missing.
I'll accompany you to find your master.
Wait.
Pei Zhi! Pei Zhi!
Pei Zhi! Pei Zhi! Pei Zhi!
Are you okay?
What year is it?
It's 2012.
What day is it today?
It's September 25th.
Once upon a time,
there was a little fox.
She lived with her dad.
One day,
Mr. Fox was sick.
It was very serious.
At this moment,
the little fox suddenly travelled
to a parallel world.
In the parallel world,
she met
a healthy Mr. Fox.
After that,
the little fox found
she could choose
to travel back to her own world
and take care of her dad.
But she could also stay here
to live a easy life.
You...
What do you think the little fox would choose?
People have to face their difficulties.
[Girl, don't cry]
Do you think that parallel world
is somewhat let us escape from reality?
It doesn't matter if you succeed or not.
You just need to be healthy
and keep fighting.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
Don't worry.
There's no pressure.
Can you describe
what happened just now.
I'm recording it.
Keep a file.
My daughter and I were on our way.
I heard...
He heard my dad's voice
from the recording pen.
So he put his attention
on the recording pen
and started the investigation.
Your father
died in 2009.
But the time of this recording
was February 22th, 2013.
So, the sound in the recording
is definitely not your father's.
But this is my father's voice.
You mean you know
who the other person was?
The master?
The car was too fast.
It rushed towards us.
My daughter and I were walking.
Thank you, dad.
I wondered why the voices of the two people
sounded so familiar.
But when I was
in the Strawberry World,
I never thought it was my master
because they didn't know each other.
But now in the Cheese World,
they have known each other for a long time.
In 2013 of the Strawberry World,
my dad did have a car accident.
I don't remember the exact date.
But it should be
a few days after my birthday.
after my birthday.
The driver ran away.
Lin was fine,
so he didn't call the police.
But then he suffered the sequela.
So, I didn't remember
to connect the recording to this.
But now it seems
Lin in the Cheese World will suffer a car accident.
The recording shows that I can save him.
If I can save him,
he won't have
Alzheimer's disease.
Stop. Stop.
Eight months later,
the awakening condition I set triggered.
Stop.
Pei Zhi.
Pei Zhi in the Strawberry World.
Can you hear me?
Now I officially
introduce myself to you.
I'm Pei Zhi in the Cheese World.
Don't you want to
live with your dad?
I have a way
to get you to the Cheese World.
[All alarms are closed]
[The bell will ring in 9 minutes]
Pei Zhi in the Strawberry World.
Let's exchange our lives.
So,
you've been here
after the modeling competition.
Yes.
Although I stayed in his body
for half a year and knew everything,
I've never been to Germany.
After all,
we're two people from different worlds.
We have many differences.
Then why did you hide it from me?
Because he didn't agree.
Only if he voluntarily
wanted to,
he would be able to go to that world.
The reason why I didn't tell you
my real identity
was that I wanted to tell you it
after he left.
So, you wanted
to tell me it
after everything was settled.
Sorry, I...
I had to hide it.
You shouldn't be here. Do you know?
Since you were there
when I came to the Cheese World with him,
you should know
my choice.
I won't let you
stay here.
Of course I know.
Thus, I also come up with a way
to get you all to agree.
As long as you choose to let me stay here,
I'll complete
the proof that P=NP right away.
In the world of P=NP,
the medicine for Alzheimer's disease
will appear in advance.
This is the history
the Cheese World has been verified.
When I in this world
understand this,
he will agree to leave.
He hasn't appeared
to affect me during this period.
That's the best proof.
Don't you want to cure Lin?
If you miss
this opportunity,
Lin may not
be able to last long.
I...
I need you to tell me
your choice now.
If you choose him,
I won't leave
the arguments of P=NP for you.
I...
I don't know.
If you choose me,
I will always be with you.
I will be with you forever.
No. No. No.
I'm also Pei Zhi.
You don't understand. You're not the one
who grew up
and experienced
so many things with me.
What about Lin?
He only experienced half of his life.
He's still so young.
If he's not sick,
he must be passionate
about the life
and the math he loves.
Do you let him go?
I...
Can you accept his leaving?
I can't.
But I...
Xi.
He and I
are watching you.
We're waiting for you to make a choice.
I want to save Lin.
But I... I have no choice.
I...
Sister.
Little Lin.
Dad said
he would row a boat one day
to a place very far away.
By then,
he can't take care of you anymore.
So, he created me.
Sing.
The bitter sand
blew on my face. It is painful.
It is like my father's scolding
and my mother's cry.
I can't forget it forever.
When I was young,
I liked to stay by the sea alone.
I rolled up my pants and my feet were bare.
I stepped on the beach.
Let me accompany my sister.
It's like our dad hasn't left.
I can talk with you,
tell jokes to you,
and sing for you.
Dad left a lot of words
and let me tell you.
In our lives,
we have a few opportunities to struggle.
[Starlight Sports Park]
What a pity to miss them.
The passion itself
is the most touching thing.
There is no contradiction
between simplicity and beauty.
As long as I want,
I can live in whatever way I like.
The study itself
is a happy process.
Plant a seed in your heart.
Maybe one day,
it will grow into a big tree.
Compared to the beauty of exploring the unknown,
most of the bad luck
is not important.
One day,
you will ride the same boat
and go to the same place
as the song goes.
The person you love will always leave.
The robot will be broken sooner or later.
I'm not afraid.
I want to be your support.
Go back.
Go back to the Cheese World.
This is the last lesson
Lin taught me.
I can't let Pei Zhi in the Strawberry World leave
because I want to save Lin.
I want to face my life directly.
[Change shoes and put on socks when you go out]
[Remember to turn off the lights]
[Have fun today]
[Change shoes and put on socks when you go out]
[Remember to turn off the lights]
[The Heart of Genius]
Okay.
I've finished
my new story.
What do you think about it?
Very good.
Do you understand
the latter part?
No.
After listening to the story,
tell me
if you want to study math hard.
Yes. Yes.
You want to study math.
Zheng Tianming.
Do you have any questions?
Teacher.
Is the P=NP problem
really so powerful?
Can the cancer be cured by it?
Actually, I don't know.
Because in our world,
P=NP has not been confirmed yet.
That's why you should
study hard, right?
Yes.
Qi.
Do you have any questions?
Teacher, you used
the name of Zheng Tianming and me,
Will you pay us?
No.
I'll change the names.
I'll change you to Zheng Wenqi
and change you to Sun Tianming, okay?
Xi.
Hello, Mr. Pei.
Hello, principal. Hello, principal.
Hello.
Is Ms. Lin
telling you stories again?
Yes.
You dad doesn't know that yet.
You'll know it soon.
We know.
We all know.
Am I not a villain this time?
Yes.
Good girl, you've made progress.
You don't write your dad as a bad guy anymore.
But...
But what?
What are you laughing at?
Dad.
She wrote that you had the Alzheimer's disease.
Is she bad?
Ms. Lin, what happened next?
Where is Pei Zhi in the Strawberry World?
At the end of the novel,
Pei Zhi in the Strawberry World
chose his own world.
Pei Zhi.
I have something to say.
I understand your feelings for me.
But you can't
replace my Pei Zhi.
You have your parents,
the math,
the fame, the wealth and friends in the Cheese World.
But you don't have me
who doesn't belong to the Cheese World.
And you shouldn't leave
those who love you for me.
Do you know?
At the same time,
you're taking other person's lives.
You're right about one thing.
A person's experience
determines who he or she is.
You're right.
As for the Pei Zhi I love,
his father died in an accident
and his mother stifled his hobbies
since he was a child.
He had been fighting
with mental diseases all the time.
But he never gave up.
Do you know
how much he wanted to replace you
when he was in the Cheese World?
Do you know how envious he was?
There is such a...
Xi.
But he still chose
to come back with me.
So, what I want to say today
is that we
should face
our lives bravely.
I hope you can leave.
I've been waiting for him for so long.
Now I finally get him.
But if you must
stay here,
I can only
accompany Lin till the end
and spend my whole life
to find him in the Cheese World.
Do you remember
when we competed to guess the steps,
the stake was
your childhood photo?
3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
Oh no.
10, 11, 12.
13, 14,15.
16, 17, 18.
25, 26, 27.
28, 29, 30.
31, 32, 33.
It's me.
He's gone.
[I love you, although I've only seen you once. I want to be with you forever, but I have to leave]
[You have no memory of me. I don't regret that. Don't have any imagination about me]
[Imagination can bring sadness. I'm just an ordinary mother who has gone far away]
He asked me to tell you
he loved you.
He just forgot
the Lin Zhaoxi he knew
was a person
who never gave up easily.
As long as she thinks it clearly,
she'll go in one direction.
No matter how hard the road will be,
she'll always go ahead.
This is the person he loves.
This may be
the only hope to cure Lin.
Don't you regret it?
♫Every day, every night, everything♫
Maybe...
Maybe we
♫It belongs to me♫
♫And it is anyone something just like me♫
can prove P=NP
together.
♫Just leave it together♫
♫Most thing will be ok♫
P=NP.
♫Something new, something hates, something change♫
Can we really make it?
Can't we?
♫It connected with me♫
♫And it is nothing makes me♫
There are two of us.
♫However nothing's gonna change♫
What you can do in the Cheese World,
we can do it too.
♫Yes, I will be ok♫
♫Take me back I used to be♫
Consistent Efforts.
♫I don't wanna be no one♫
A life that cannot be slackened.
♫Slowly sinking on my dream♫
The destination is right there.
♫There's one thing on my mind♫
♫Together♫
Let's walk over there.
♫Take me back I used to be♫
♫I wanna be the one♫
♫Take me in your mind with my time♫
♫I've done with my life better♫
♫Take me back to me♫
[The End]