[English subtitles are available]
[The Heart of Genius]
[Episode 10]
So I'm an accountant.
Say something.
Yes?
Have you solved the P/ NP problem?
Not yet.
What about my research?
Is it a success?
You've been studying math.
But I don't know
the details.
Then it's a failure.
In the first half of my life,
I thought I was a genius.
But then...
No, dad.
Don't think about it.
I'm out of my mind.
How could this happen?
Dad. Dad.
Let's not think about this, okay?
You'll get better.
Dad.
You know what?
When I first went to that world,
I was really scared and panicked.
But you gave me a lot of support.
Every time I do something,
I always think of
what you said to me.
Here are some examples.
It's not a big deal.
There will be a solution.
It's not the time to be hopeless yet.
No matter what the result is,
the experience of being hardworking and dedicated
will always bring me something.
As long as you are not changed by the world,
you'll change the world.
What are you doing?
Why haven't you went to bed?
I'm going to bed now.
Something is playing in your mind.
Why do you say so?
You've been acting weird lately.
The last time you behaved in such a serious manner,
it was
when I filled out my application for the college entrance exam.
Your menopause has come?
What menopause?
See,
other parents
are always
urging their children to get jobs and married,
and give birth to their grandchildren.
But you didn't urge me for those stuff.
You urged me to be a moth flying to the fire.
I also want you
to live a normal life.
I know it's a kind of happiness.
But I'm your dad.
I know you well.
I'm afraid you'll regret it later.
In the future,
one day when I'll be dying
on the bed.
and you'll just stare at me
like what you are doing now.
With the chat today running in your mind,
what will you say?
What's the password to our saving account?
Why do you...
Can you stop killing this chat?
Let me say it another way.
I like Michael Fassbender.
Can I go after him?
Your classmate?
No.
The young Magneto.
I like him too.
But even so I don't have to go after him.
I don't care neither if I fail.
Can you guarantee
from now on, you won't think about maths
and Pei Zhi?
You are better at killing this chat.
Forget it. I'm going to sleep.
Lin Zhaoxi,
in this long yet beautiful
life,
as long as you truly
want to do something,
no matter when you start it,
it's not too late.
When I was in primary school,
to finish the writing practice,
I always quoted your words
as sayings said by
Golkie,
Edison and Franklyn.
I was praised by the teacher.
She said I'm knowledgeable.
My classmates also said
I was chef Lin good at cooking chicken soup for the soul.
I told them
I didn't make the chicken soup.
I just passed it on from someone else.
You're right.
I shouldn't be
submissive
and worried about gains and losses.
It shouldn't be like this.
I'm going to resign.
I'm going to study maths.
I'll find Pei Zhi
and tell him I like him
even if he may reject me.
I will take good care of you
and myself.
Everything will be fine.
Dad,
is this place familiar?
Take care.
Move.
It doesn't work.
My dad has no response.
Does it has something to do with the doctor?
My dad is close to
a leader in Sanwei Medical School.
How about ask him for
introducing us to a good one?
It's okay.
Have some water.
Thank you.
Director Ma is
an expert in this field.
He made it clear last time.
There's little hope for my dad to recover.
I just want to take good care of him.
I'll cook for you.
Don't bother.
Just order a takeout later.
It's okay. I can cook fast.
How about I hiring someone for you?
I can do it myself.
You're a girl.
If anything happens to your dad,
you can't move him.
Not to mention, you can't
watch him 24 hours a day.
Let me think about it.
You've bothered a lot to help
me and my dad.
I'm really grateful.
We have brought you so much trouble.
Thank you.
After coming back,
you've been so polite to me.
I'm really not used to it.
I...
I'm actually not used to it either.
When we were in the Cheese World,
I didn't feel it.
After I came back,
your superstar's face shows up before me every day.
I need to take this call.
Okay.
I want to quit.
You heard me right. I want to quit.
Okay, I'll be right there.
I might need you
to take care of my dad for me.
I need to go out.
Sure.
Thank you.
Is anything
in trouble?
I'll go through a resignation procedure.
What's being a regular worker?
Go away.
I want to be a postgraduate
for mathematic study in Sanwei University.
You have made up your mind?
In the Cheese World,
before so many people,
I announced that I want to study maths.
I can't break my words.
And I've thought it through.
One percent possibility is better
than doing nothing.
If my dad continues to be like this,
I'll carry on his research.
You should have done that earlier.
You don't have to sacrifice yourself.
I... I'll go pack up.
Well,
let me order a takeout for you.
No need.
I can order it myself later.
Sure.
Wait for me.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you
for your recent help.
I've learned a lot.
Thank you.
There are so many scenes.
Who are you acting for?
We won't see each other again.
My aunt told me
you were a hardworking person.
I admire people like you the most.
What's the use of
these tricks?
You're acting one way before us
and another behind our back.
Can someone like you be a genius?
Luckily, I didn't let you be a member of my family.
If prestigious universities accept
students like you
they all will be closed sooner or later.
Human beings
should respect each other,
director.
Yes.
To graduate from a prestigious university
maybe
not a big deal.
But do you know,
why many girls like me
study hard?
Because only studying hard
can make them independent
spiritually and economically;
and give them the courage
to refuse boys and work
they don't like.
Lin Zhaoxi,
in this long yet beautiful
life,
as long as you truly
want to do something,
no matter when you start it,
it's not too late.
Mom, I'm going out.
Come back early.
Okay.
Look,
you get dressed up.
Where are you going?
None of your business.
Come back.
Come here.
What's wrong?
Well.
How is Xi's father?
The sun is rising from the west.
I don't know you can care about others.
I thought you only cared about
playing mahjong and counting money.
Don't be sarcastic.
I'm serious.
Uncle Lin has waken up.
Wait, wait, wait.
He has waken up?
Yes.
He has left the hospital.
But his condition seems to be worse.
He can't even speak clearly.
I see.
Find a free time,
buy some fruits and pay a visit to Uncle Lin.
Just say it's a gift from me.
Sure.
Dad?
What?
Money.
Kid, you even wouldn't pay such a little money
for your dad?
No.
You said it was a gift from you.
Why should I pay?
Why didn't I have another kid!
Fine.
Here, take it.
That's it?
Tell me the cost when back and I'll reimburse your payment.
Is it enough to buy anything?
Forget it.
I'll cover the spend for you.
Only spend but don't earn money. You black sheep.
Uncle Lin, do you want some fruit?
Lu.
Where are you?
At home.
At home, right?
Open the door.
I'm in front of your apartment.
I say I'm at my friend's home.
A girl, right?
A boy.
Okay, come on.
Take a photo for me.
I don't think it's a good idea.
Take a photo and prove yourself.
Or tell me
your address.
I'll be right there.
Lu,
why are you acting like a grumpy woman now?
You're in an emergency.
You can't have any more scandals.
I'm afraid you'll lose your mind
and forget your identity.
Remember,
You can hide anything from anyone
except the company.
I know.
Lu,
how can you not trust me?
Wait for me.
I'll take a photo for you.
Did you receive it?
Yes.
Who is this?
A friend of my dad.
I came to visit him.
We haven't finished yet.
I'll hang up if there's nothing else.
Bye bye.
Who is your dad?
Xiaomeng, don't rush over.
I'm still outside.
Is Uncle Lin alone at home?
No.
Ji Jiang is taking care of him for me.
What? Ji Jiang is at your home?
What’s going on between you and Ji Jiang?
We are just friends.
He accompanied you to the hospital,
handled things here for you,
and almost brought about a chaos in the hospital.
He also helped you take care of your dad.
He's not just a friend.
We're truly just friends,
and alumni.
Don't talk nonsense outside.
Especially in your shop.
People in your shop like to post Moments.
It'll be bad for him.
You care so much about him?
How could you say there's nothing between you two?
I remember now.
He talked about the common jet lag
that day.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Am I right?
Pei Zhi.
Pei Zhi?
You already have Ji Jiang.
Why do you still want Pei Zhi?
I am hanging up now.
Thank you.
Excuse me,
where did the person you just carried go?
Over there.
Thank you.
Hello.
It's your first time here, right?
Do you want a card?
We teach boxing,
martial arts, taekwondo,
and any lessons you want to take.
50% off during the promotion.
You can't find a second place like us
in the whole city.
Long time no see.
Aren't you hot?
I've never seen you so nervous.
Actually, I was also nervous before.
I was nervous every time I went to your home.
But I did some preparations
so I hid it very well.
After you went to Germany,
I sent you
many emails.
Did you receive them?
Why didn't you reply?
When did you come back?
I've been back for 8 months and 27 days.
I saw the poster of you
outside.
I'm now
the boxing coach here.
I heard
that your dad taught you boxing when you were young.
I didn't expect
you're working in this field now.
I haven't thought...
I haven't thought
that I would meet you here.
Are you avoiding me on purpose?
I didn't study maths in Germany.
I let you and Mr.Lin down.
Do you think I meet you here
because of maths?
Zhaoxi.
Memories are beautiful, but...
That's the reality.
So I'm just a memory.
You know what?
According to
my original personality,
I would stand up now
and tell you
I'm sorry for bothering you.
Then I would leave with tears.
But today,
I have to react in another a way.
Guys,
give me some time please,
I have something to say.
Pei Zhi.
I've always liked him.
I have a crush on him for a long time.
Wow.
But we're not in a relationship.
Because after the high school,
he went to Germany.
and disappeared without a word.
Today, God makes me
meet him again.
So I won't let him
run away again.
Please keep an eye on him.
I'll come here to see him from now on.
If one day I can't find him
and he disappears,
I'll get even with you one by one.
OK.
Don't worry, Mrs. Pei. We will keep an eye on him
and follow him wherever he goes,
even to the toilet.
I have to go home now.
But I'll come here again.
Welcome whenever you come, Mrs. Pei.
Not bad, bro.
This girl is interesting.
Watch your opponent.
Lower your gravity.
Like this.
Focus on using your waist's strength to move your hands.
Come on.
Go on.
Lower your elbow.
Go on. Left, right, left.
OK. Watch your steps.
Left, right, left, head down.
Too late.
Left, right, left. Head down and punch.
Come on. Left, right, left. Head down.
Turn around.
If you by then
stuck on this,
we would have had
ten, or at least eight,
golden belts.
Mr.Yu, you flatter me.
Many people are better than me.
Don't pretend to be modest.
Tell me.
When we were on training before,
who was better than you?
Don't you think
you shouldn't
follow the instruction of your father-in-law
and become a traffic police officer?
Look.
Look how good the boxing market is now.
You are elder than 40 years old?
Enjoy your meal.
Mr.Yu.
Was my dad awesome
when he was young?
What do you mean?
He was quite impressive.
With a pair of iron fists, he was so ambitious.
He was the one we adore all the time.
He was said
to be invincible in the south of the Yangtze River.
His wish was
to conquer the boxing world in northern China,
and to go as far as Harbin.
Unexpectedly,
just entered northeast China,
he ran into your mother.
He was captivated by your mother.
Dad, watch your mouth.
Okay.
Use the phrase popular in your school.
What is it?
A perfect match.
You,
you are the result of
the perfect match.
Come on.
Dad, I want to play boxing too.
Study hard.
Boxing can be a hobby.
Come back soon.
Sir,
can you drive faster for me?
Okay.
Okay, thank you.
You're welcome.
Ji Jiang.
Where is my dad?
You are back.
Here, have a look.
What happened?
Let me tell you.
After your leaving,
your dad suddenly woke up.
Just like what Xiaomeng said,
he thought he was in his 20s
and in his youth.
He even asked me who I was.
Why was I at his home?
I could only tell the truth.
I said I was your daughter's friend.
How could you tell him that?
What if he realizes
he is old,
and can't accept it?
Your dad saw my phone.
He was so smart.
Within several scrolls,
he realized something was wrong
and asked me which year it was now.
I was terrified.
I was wondering if I should tell the truth.
Suddenly, I thought something.
I thought the day we arrived at the hospital.
Didn't I tell you
your dad looked like he did a time travel too?
So I lied to Uncle Lin and said,
"Uncle Lin,
you've traveled from the past to the future.
It's 2018 now."
I then showed your dad
all kinds of home appliances
such as TV, computers,
and the phone.
Your dad did believe it.
He really thought
he traveled from the past.
How could you lie to him?
I had no choice.
It was an emergency.
But think about it.
Your dad has accepted it.
He won't be destroyed
by it anymore.
He won't be in a slump.
It will be much easier for you to take care of him.
No.
Lies
will be exposed one day.
When he finds out
his life in his 40s
is a mess,
he wants to go back but he can't,
and he can only waste
more than 20 years.
He would be devastated.
So you have to let him know
he can go back.
We've been through this.
Give him some hope.
Set a difficult goal.
Tell him
that he can go back after achieving it.
Let him live in peace first.
You can
gradually impart views to him
and let him accept the reality.
Then everything is fine.
What did he read?
Uncle Lin heard from me
that the Internet was very advanced now
and any program could be watched online.
He told me
he wanted to watch the 1994 World Cup.
I taught him how to surf the Internet by computer.
He searched the program himself.
Last time he used the computer,
he was freaked out.
This time
he was sitting there and watching the program.
Maybe your idea works.
Right?
I told you my idea was not bad.
If it were me,
I wouldn't dare to use it.
I'm afraid my dad will go into pieces.
Let's give it a try.
Nice shot!
Are you avoiding me on purpose?
I thought the decision that I didn't learn maths
let you and Mr.Lin down.
Do you think
I come to meet you here because of math?
Memories are beautiful, but...
that's the reality.
The harsher you treat yourself, the more you get.
What do you think?
No.
You...
Why are you throwing this book?
This book...
He's just a middle school student in Grade 9.
Why did you let him study
in the maths class of the Juvenile University?
My son is
a math genius.
What kind of maths genius is he?
Can you describe
what happened just now.
I'm recording it.
Leave a file.
My daughter and I were on our way.
I heard
the car behind me was noisy.
When I looked back,
the car rushed over.
Luckily, my daughter reacted quickly
and dragged me.
Then the car
crashed into it.
You are back.
Dad, you remember me?
No.
But I know you're my daughter.
There is your photo on the table.
Your file is on the computer.
And the things in this room are
for girls.
This is my home.
I can infer that
you are either my wife
or my daughter.
But you're young.
You are my daughter.
You head was hurt,
but it works well now.
I'm a genius.
The computer system
and the Internet
are much more advanced
than what I used in America.
Judging from this point of view,
what he said is true.
I did come from the past.
I just searched online
for the four words: transcending time and space.
I found massive information.
Our society has moved forward.
In this era,
transcending time and space
is not something surprising.
He probably found a bunch of novels.
It is still something surprising.
So this is a secret.
We'll keep this secret for you.
OK. I was afraid you wouldn't believe me.
Yes.
Ji Jiang told me everything.
She didn't believe it until I explained.
Well,
can you two
take me out?
I really want to see
what the world have become
after 20 years.
Sure.
Okay.
Wait for me in the living room.
I'll pack up and leave.
Don't be so polite.
It's awkward.
Although
we are father and daughter,
we're peers.
We are about the same age.
You can call me Lin.
I'll call you Little Lin.
Okay, Lin.
Then, when you go out,
don't call me dad. Don't call me dad.
Let me dress myself up.
Now I'm not sure.
Is your dad
too excited?
Help me calm him down.
Well,
I'll call Director Ma.
Okay.
Hurry up.
The car is here.
♫When you need your space♫
♫Find your home in this way♫
♫You know the time is right♫
♫When there's light in your eyes♫
♫That is when stars shining♫
♫Hope hope keep strength ♫
♫Hope hope be strong♫
♫Hope hope keep strength♫
♫Hope hope hope♫
♫Hope hope be strong♫
♫Hope hope keep strength♫
♫Hope hope hope♫
Lin.
Take back your hand.
It's okay. I'm watching.
Okay.
♫Hold on moments in days♫
♫We are happy our hearts in wait♫
Dad, wait for me.
♫You know the time is right♫
I'll leave after I pay.
♫When the light in your eyes♫
I'll scan your QR code.
Show me your payment code.
♫That is when stars shinning♫
OK.
♫Hope hope keep strength♫
It's 768 yuan.
♫Hope hope be strong♫
Keep your receipt.
Okay, thank you.
♫Hope hope keep strength♫
♫Hope hope hope♫
♫Hope hope keep♫
♫Hope hope be strong♫
♫Hope hope hope♫
♫Come on the scary sun♫
♫Hope leave some stamp♫
♫Dreams are always in your hands♫
♫Chances are breathes♫
♫Hope hope keep strength♫
♫Hope hope be strong♫
♫Hope hope hope♫
♫Hope hope keep strength♫
♫Hope hope be strong♫
♫Hope hope hope♫
♫You gotta keep faith♫
♫You gotta keep the faith♫
Your society in this era
has developed so fast.
I'm so happy today.
I don't want to go back.
Of course.
As for the rapid development of China,
people living 20 years ago
couldn't think about it.
No way, no way.
Come on, calm down.
Lin.
It's such a nice place.
Why don't you stay here?
No, I have to go back.
I have to contribute
to the social development.
Think about it.
If everyone rushes to the future like me
and only enjoys his life,
who work to develop our society?
Look at Lin. He's so noble.
Besides,
I'm 20 now.
Look at my body, it is in my 40s.
I have a great youth
which I haven't experienced yet.
If I stay here,
I'll lose more than 20 years.
As for your guys,
one thing you said is right.
Yes.
I shouldn't have
come here for no reason.
I have my mission.
I have a task.
Yes.
I can only go back
after finish the task.
Otherwise, I can't go back.
But the problem is I don't know
what my mission is.
Do you know?
That's tricky.
Don't worry.
You have so much time.
Right?
Take your time.
Steady steady.
Let's have fun first.
Yes, fun first.
I'll watch the 1994 World Cup
when I go back home.
I just watched the qualifiers.
I have to see who the king was.
I remember it was...
I forgot.
Here, Lin.
Here's to you.
Here.
Me too.
There are many things on the Internet.
You can watch anything you want.
Great!
Great.
He's asleep.
Thank you for today.
Don't mention it.
Now we're back to the reality.
Why do you think the Cheese World
is fake?
You know
that's not what I meant.
By the way, I found Pei Zhi.
He came back.
I met him today.
You wouldn't have thought
he's now a coach at the boxing club.
Did you mistake him for someone else?
No.
I'm glad you found him.
How is he now?
I want to see him.
Pei Zhi.
He has changed a lot.
What are your plans?
What plans?
More than 4 years have passed
and he's quite unfamiliar to me now.
I just don't know
what happened to him in Germany.
He didn't even reply my emails.
We need to figure it out.
Four years is not long,
but it's not short neither.
People are changing.
Ji Jiang! Ji Jiang! Ji Jiang!
The old way.
Ji Jiang is here.
Ji Jiang! Ji Jiang! Ji Jiang!
Thank you for your support.
Be careful.
Don't stay here.
Okay, thank you.