[English subtitles are available]
[The Heart of Genius]
[Episode 22]
Before I leave,
can you consider me as him?
Even if it's only for a little while.
I promise you.
Pei Zhi.
What kind of person
am I in that world?
In my heart,
he is like a mountain.
Good morning.
Why are you here?
I came here in the morning.
I waited until you woke up.
You... Wait for me.
Where's Lin?
He went out an hour ago.
Did you have a pleasant conversation
with your dad last night?
Anyway,
we reached a consensus.
I promised him
I would leave the Cheese World.
Of course, he promised me
before I left,
he would treat me as his own son.
I think
it was good.
Actually, I'm quite lucky
to come to this world
to meet him
and spend a few months with him.
Many people who lost their loved ones
couldn't have the chance like me.
I was too greedy.
And I used to...
Do you remember
what I said last night?
Now we're
even.
How's the program
for measuring car accidents going?
I'm still trying.
Now I realize
that I do take advantage of
my age
to experience the feeling
of being a high school genius.
But when I learn new things,
I still feel that I'm an ordinary people.
I...
I can help you with programming.
Will you help me?
If you mind...
Of course not.
If you help me,
I definitely have a greater chance of winning.
Aren't you afraid
I'll go back on my word
and ruin your program?
You won't.
Wait. What day is it today?
Monday.
Oh no.
You...
I'll put on my school uniform.
Don't worry.
We can catch up
the first class in the afternoon.
I can do it. Wait for me.
I don't like criticizing students,
[Go for the college entrance examination]
especially criticizing students by their names.
That's because I want to give you face.
[Details determine success or failure]
[Attitude determines everything]
But this time, there are a few students
who have gone too far.
Zheng Tianming.
Tell everyone
your English score this time.
Sir.
It's 44 points.
[Details determine success or failure]
[Attitude determines everything]
Are you proud of it?
You think this number is very auspicious,
right?
It doesn't reach half of the passing score.
[Details determine success or failure]
[Attitude determines everything]
Bao Xiaomeng, stand up.
Did I ask you to sit down?
Tell me, what's your math score?
23.
Louder.
[Details determine success or failure]
[Attitude determines everything]
You guessed four multiple choice questions correctly.
You didn't get any of the fill-in-the-blank questions right.
As for the seven major questions,
you only answered the first subquestion
of the first major question correctly.
You ranked last
in the whole grade for this course.
How did you do that?
The last student
was always...
was always Lin Zhaoxi.
Now Lin Zhaoxi's grades
have risen,
which makes you become the last one.
You two are so close.
Why don't you learn from her?
Are you crying?
The boys in our class
are brazen.
Girls cry when they talk.
Are these traditional features
of our class?
[Details determine success or failure]
[Attitude determines everything]
Why are you laughing?
Class, you're in the 12th grade now.
It's time to hurry up.
Ask yourselves.
Do you study hard
for me?
It's for yourselves.
Be responsible for yourself.
Sir.
You two still know to come to the class.
Sorry, sir.
Sorry.
We got up late.
Be quiet.
[Go for the college entrance examination]
Go back to your seat.
Sorry, sir.
Zheng Tianming and Bao Xiaomeng.
Sit down.
Take out your paper.
Let's review the test questions today.
Goodbye, students.
Goodbye, teacher.
Mr. Xie. Mr. Xie.
I have something to discuss with you.
Can I sit
next to Pei Zhi?
[Details determine success or failure]
[Attitude determines everything]
Thank you.
Pei Zhi.
What's wrong with you two?
Are you back together?
Don't use random words.
We had some conflicts before.
Now we're reconciled.
Bad excuses.
I've discussed with Mr. Xie.
I'll sit here from now on.
Great.
Let me help you.
Okay.
Zheng Tianming.
What happened to Xiaomeng?
Nothing.
She was criticized by Mr. Xie.
She was used to it.
She is sleepy now.
What are you talking about?
This is my home.
This is Sanwei University
in the suburban university town.
The straight-line distance of the two places is 20 kilometers away.
There are many different routes
to reach there.
But if we don't take a taxi,
we need to change buses and the subway
for several times.
Moreover, if we change the public transport,
we should walk for a long distance.
So what I'm thinking now is
to divide the map
into equal-sized grids.
Use N and E as the place's longitude and latitude respectively.
T is the time.
P is the probability of a car accident
occurring at a given moment
in a given time period.
Then, based on
Lin's experience on that day, his actual location,
and the route to the venue,
including the traffic condition,
the historical data,
the running time of the traffic lights at each intersection,
we can continue to give each grid
new values.
Using the historical data
and designated routes,
we can firstly give each grid
different prior probabilities.
Then, based on emergencies
and the time order,
we can use the real-time data
to update the posterior probability p
of every grid.
Bayesian Network.
You're right.
If we repeat
Bayes' theorem,
as the remaining distance
becomes shorter and shorter,
we'll get the grid
of the highest probability
after continuously updating and verifying the probabilities.
We'll be alert
to make up for the bias
caused by subjective judgment.
What tool will you use
to make a model?
Python.
Why not use
MATLAB?
It has many toolboxes.
and many
mature modules.
I think there are also
many third-party modules
in Python.
Just like NumPy. It can make Python
deal with large matrices
like MATLAB.
SciPy
also contains a lot of algorithms.
And
Matplotlib Module
can also let Python
draw a lot of function graphs.
So, in fact,
Python can replace a lot of tools
in MATLAB.
It also has some advantages
that can't be replaced.
I'm not talented.
You are a genius.
If I'm wrong,
or if you have
any better ideas,
just tell me.
I'll listen to you.
No.
I think you're right.
Really?
You've only been studying it for two months, right?
You're so smart.
No.
How can I compare with you?
Besides programming,
we also need
a lot of traffic data.
I can
ask my dad to help us.
You'll be in charge of programming.
Your dad will be in charge of the data.
I'll beat the drum for you.
Will it be too easy for me?
No matter how good the program can be,
you'll be the one
who takes the final risk.
You are the most important person.
So is the master.
By the way,
if I destroy the IOU,
will he continue to run the tutoring class?
My dad
is thinking about
to improve the family condition.
The class will start soon.
But he won't give up his math research.
Does he know
about our jump?
I have told him.
The safest way now
is to tell him
all the rules
and let him set off to the meeting hall
in the scheduled time
and then come back
after the meeting.
In this way,
whether he will attend the meeting or not,
the result will be the same.
How about going to my house this weekend?
We can do the programming together.
This weekend...
Will your mother be home?
Yes.
What's wrong?
It was my idea
to go to the police office to report. She didn't...
No.
It has nothing to do with that.
Really.
I...
I'm just a little embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little scared of your mother.
Are you scared?
I'm a girl after all.
I can be shy,
embarrassed,
and weak.
Xi.
[Education is an important cornerstone]
[of national revitalization and social progress]
Let's go.
Let's play basketball.
Do you want to die?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Weak.
This might be Lin Zhaoxi in the Cheese World.
Why are you laughing?
Let's continue.
Dad.
I may need
some traffic data of our city.
Do you have any idea?
What data?
The car accident record of a year
and the data of traffic and pedestrian flow
of some roads.
It would be better if we can set a date
to check traffic monitors of the city.
We can't check traffic monitors.
The car accident information
is about the parties involved
and what happened to them.
This is personal privacy.
So we don't need details.
I only want the data.
There must be some data
that our city needs to submit to the higher authority every year.
For example, the number of car accidents,
the number of
casualties,
locations of accidents,
and so on.
Yes, it's available.
Why do you need it?
We need to go back
and get ready for it.
Well.
Go back there.
If we want to go back,
we have to suffer a car accident.
So we want to write a program
to predict the location of the accident.
Will the accident be dangerous?
I won't be in danger.
But Lin Zhaoxi and the master
may be in danger.
So we need to lower the risk
by predictions.
How do you predict the accident?
Can you do it?
It's actually very simple.
In our daily life,
for example, we often say
at a place
that the front is an accident-prone area.
Yes.
It's a warning.
This is the simplest use
of statistical mathematics
in transportation.
Now we know
there must be a car accident
and it must
happen to my master.
All we need to do
is to bring in a large amount of data
and to use
a more sophisticated way
of processing the data.
Then, we may be able to calculate
where the accident will happen.
How do you calculate this?
By math models.
I don't understand.
But don't worry.
I'll take care of this.
I've been a traffic police officer for many years.
They should
give me a face.
Thank you, dad.
Thank you.
Don't say that.
You're like a stranger.
Well.
how long
do you plan to stay?
Till next February, okay?
We can only leave at that time.
Don't worry, dad.
I promised you
to leave.
So, I'm a man of my word.
No.
Don't think too much.
I'm just checking.
Why are your hands so cold?
It's not good for a young man to have cold hands.
Dad, this is your son's body.
I'm very healthy in that world.
Look at me.
Well.
How old are you there?
23.
You've graduated. Do you have a job?
A university teacher?
A boxer.
A boxer?
Just like me.
Yes.
How can you
become a boxer?
It's to
commemorate you.
Pei Zhi, stand up!
Pei Zhi.
Stand up.
Dad.
No wonder
you've improved a lot recently.
It's okay.
You're more like me in the past.
Before I came here,
I participated in a competition.
I met a Thai boxer before.
He was short and strong.
He had great resisting ability.
He called Pilavakhun.
I know Pilavakhun.
He's a famous Thai boxing champion
in the past two years.
Yes.
He's quite famous in my world.
Have you fought with him?
Yes.
But at that time,
when he competed with me,
he was a veteran.
He was actually powerful
in all aspects.
He was just old
and not strong enough as before.
So I calculated how to win
and beat him.
You can use your mind to fight.
You're much better than me in the past.
Thank you, dad.
Where are you going?
I'll find Pei Zhi.
Why do you still go to him?
Have you forgotten what he did to you?
He also let our father take so much debt.
Okay. Okay. Calm down.
The debt has been canceled.
That was a misunderstanding.
How could these troubles be explained
to be caused by a misunderstanding?
Anyway, the relationship between Pei Zhi and I
can't be described simply.
You don't understand it.
Are you two back together again?
No.
Just focus on your study.
Sister. Lust can make people vulnerable.
Who's that?
Hello, auntie.
I'm here to see Pei Zhi.
Pei Zhi.
Auntie.
I bought you some fruit.
No, no, no.
Take it. Take it.
That's inappropriate.
Just eat it.
Let's talk in my room.
We'll go in first.
Will you have lunch here?
No, thanks.
We'll just talk for a while.
Hello?
Hello, Pei.
Come back quickly.
Something happened.
No.
Something really happened.
Lin Zhaoxi is here.
Why isn't it a serious thing?
The two kids
were at loggerheads.
Now they
seem to be close.
I don't know if it's true.
Come back quickly.
I was so embarrassed just now.
We need to use a computer to monitor in real time.
I'll ask my dad
to rent a car
so that I can follow you
with my computer.
But will it trigger
a new factor
and then change the result of the accident?
I'll let the car
stay across the road at all times
or slightly exceed
your position.
Hello, dad.
Okay.
We'll be right downstairs.
Dad.
Have you got the data?
I overestimated myself.
I didn't get anything.
I've worked many years,
and it made me feel ashamed.
Your mom was right.
Dad.
It's okay.
We can think of
other ways.
Actually, we can try
to collect data ourselves.
But it will take a lot of effort
and a lot of time.
Let's drop out of school.
Drop out of school?
Now our priority
is to get the program done.
What we do usually
has affected other students in class.
Why don't we drop out of school
and finish the program first?
It'll be more reliable.
What do you think, dad?
Of course I'm fine with it.
But your mom won't agree.
I think we should
keep it from my mom.
I'll pretend to go to school every morning.
Actually, I'll go to make the program.
I just need a place.
Is my master's house available?
Lin has known
our things.
But
Hua Juan is hostile to you.
We can only
find another place
that allows us to sit down and use computers.
I have a place to go.
Back then,
your mom and I
invested in a shop.
But after we bought it,
we couldn't rent it out
or sell it.
So I left it there.
I usually
had a rest
with my friends
after night duties.
We played boxing or cards.
Water and electricity are all available.
It also has a bathroom.
What do you think?
It's great.
This is our secret base.
Let me confirm for the last time.
This is the last sprint stage
for students in the 12th grade.
Are you sure
they'll drop out of school?
Mr. Xie.
I have a liver problem recently.
I need someone to take care of me.
I have a kidney problem.
What are you two thinking?
Mr. Xie.
Every family has their own problems.
But what about your grades?
I can help them.
Mr. Xie.
I don't think
Pei Zhi's grades
can improve any higher.
Okay.
Since you've made up your mind
and you've talked to Principle Zhang,
I can only agree.
Thank you for your support.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Come back early.
Goodbye, Mr. Xie.
[Countdown to the College Entrance Examination]
Mr. Xie.
I have a question.
Where did you buy this?
[Countdown to the College Entrance Examination]
[Countdown to Home]
Let's go.
This sofa is nice.
I like its color.
But we don't need the sofa.
You said you always go straight to the point
when buying things
and didn't show around.
Well.
I come with you today.
We're shopping for home furniture.
Mr. Pei.
Would you like some coffee
or tea?
You're so happy.
Of course.
That one seems good too.
Let's go.
But seriously,
should we buy
[Solid Wood Series]
one table, two lamps,
and two chairs?
[IKEA Whole House Design]
[Design you ideal home]
That's what we need.
I just checked the map.
We're close to tables.
We can look at tables first.
This bed is good.
Come here.
Try it.
It's soft and bouncy.
I feel very warm.
It makes me feel at home.
Come on. Lie down.
Lie down.
Close your eyes and feel it.
What?
Didn't you say to close your eyes?
Just kidding.
One, two, three. Close your eyes.
One, two, three.
A liar.
Xiaomeng.
Do you know?
Zhaoxi and Pei Zhi dropped out of school.
How could they?
And they are together.
Guess what the reason is.
I don't guess.
It has nothing to do with me.
Aren't you curious?
I'm not.
Anyway,
we are not
from the same world.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Let's go.
[Key Making]
How much are these, sir?
Ten yuan.
Okay.
Thank you.
[Key Making]
Do you have a key chain?
Do I have?
See?
[Countdown to Home]
[111 Days]
Three, two, one.
Do you like them?
Did you arrange all these?
I did these last night.
Do you like them?
[112 Days Countdown to Home]
Yes.
I cooked some frozen dumplings.
Do you want some?
Sure.
Here.
Do you want some vinegar?
There seems to be something missing.
Thank you.
Come on.
Cheers.
Let's celebrate
the completion of our secret base.
For the celebration,
I have a gift for you.
I have a gift too.
How is it?
Are you ready?
Where is the other half?
The other half...
Let's eat.
Try the dumplings.
The dumplings are stuffed with pork and corns.
Great.
We're like a family.
[Countdown to Home]
[100 Days]
Excuse me. I would like to know
♫Every day, every night, everything♫
if you can lend me
your monitor to have a look.
♫It belongs to me♫
What do you want to see?
I've lost something.
♫And it is anyone something just like me♫
I'm finding it.
I've found 4 monitor videos
that can record the intersection's condition.
♫Just leave it together♫
They can record for at least five days.
I've only found one.
♫Most thing will be ok♫
It's okay.
Let me analyze the videos first.
[Countdown to Home]
[100 Days]
I'll analyze the traffic flow
in every period of time at least.
♫Something new, something hates, something change♫
As for the rest,
after I finish analyzing these five monitors,
let's find another way.
Okay.
I'll continue to write the predicting program.
♫It connected with me♫
Okay.
♫And it is nothing makes me♫
[Countdown to Home]
[100 Days]
♫However nothing's gonna change♫
♫Yes, I will be OK♫
[Countdown to Home]
[95 Days]
♫Take me back I used to be♫
Here.
A S is missing behind the G.
♫I don't wanna be no one♫
My eyes are blurred.
♫Slowly sinking on my dream♫
Do you want to take a rest?
It's okay.
♫There's one thing on my mind♫
You can take a rest.
You've been busy all day.
It's okay. I'm not tired.
♫Together♫
♫Take me back I used to be♫
[Countdown to Home]
[95 Days]
♫I wanna be the one♫
♫Take me in your mind with my time♫
♫I've done with my life better♫
♫Take me back to me♫
♫Another day, another place, another way♫
[Countdown to Home]
[93 Days]
♫You come around to me♫
♫It should be it will be so much luck for me♫
♫We will be together♫
♫Most thing will be OK♫
♫Something good, something great♫
♫Something real♫
♫I found a love for you♫
♫And it is it will makes me joyful♫
♫Let me share my love for you♫
♫Take me back I used to be♫
♫I don't wanna be no one♫
Hello, this place is closed.
♫Slowly sinking on my dream♫
♫There's one thing on my mind♫
Pei Zhi?
Yes. Who are you?
Hello.
I'm a friend of your dad.
Recently,
around your place,
some electric bikes were stolen.
He'll just wait
at the door of our shop.
He'll also use the bathroom occasionally.
It won't last more than a few days.
It won't affect you.
Got it, dad.
[Push]
I'm still worried
the accuracy
of this program.
Is there any way
to verify it?
The success rate is based on the fact that
we limit the scope of
the master's actions
and behavior patterns.
But if we want to predict
the random traffic situation
of the whole city,
we still can't achieve it.
Do you have some water?
Yes. Let me help you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You've been here for three days.
Are the thieves not coming?
This is an old neighborhood.
It's not well managed.
Those thieves work in groups.
They will definitely come back.
It must be hard.
Be careful. It's hot.
Serve the people.
What are you doing
with the computers every day?
Programming.
You're still young. You're great.
No, no.
What are you making?
A game?
A program to predict
traffic accidents.
Can traffic accidents be predicted?
It's awesome.
If you can make a program
to catch thieves,
we won't have to work so hard.
Stop!
You just talked about
the verification of success rate.
I have an idea.
I also have one.
But what about the data?
If it's only
about nearby streets,
it's easier to collect the data.
And as for electric bikes,
we don't need to consider traffic conditions.
It's a good opportunity
to verify our ideas.
We can also get rid of the evil for the people.
Kill two birds with one stone. Let's go.
Let's go.
[Countdown to Home]
[85 Days]
Next, we need to record
parameters of electric bikes of mainstream brands.
I've done.
Okay.
I got it.
[Removable Disk]
[Rear Wheel Center][Motor Type]
[Countdown to Home]
[85 Days]
Time flies.
We're going back in less than three months.
Do you have any wishes
to fulfill?
To be honest,
I can meet my father
and experience the family reunion again,
which makes me feel very satisfied.
Thank you.
Xi.
[Countdown to Home]
[85 Days]
What are you going to do
when you go back?
When I go back,
I want my mom
can live comfortably
like she does in the Cheese World.
It's good.
Then...
Anything else?
Play more boxing matches
for my dad.
What's your plan?
Just like you.
I just want to take care of my dad
and take the postgraduate entrance exam.
I'll study math
for him and especially for myself.
[Countdown to Home]
[85 Days]
Actually, I've found
your talent in math
and your effort this time.
I don't think it's hard for you
to pass the postgraduate entrance exam.
Pei Zhi.
Have you ever considered
our relationship?
This is
the reason why I decided to go back.
Let's eat.
[Countdown to Home]
[85 Days]
What has Pei Zhi been doing recently?
How could I know?
Why are you looking at me?
You're staring at me when I'm eating.
My back is feeling cold. You...
You have something to hide from me.
No, absolutely not.
Why were you so happy
when I asked you just now?
Do you think
our child has been closer to you
if he told you something
and didn't tell me?
Are you very proud of it?
No.
When have I been proud of it?
Nothing happened.
Pei Donglai.
We've been married for more than 20 years.
I clearly know
when you feel proud
and what you want to do.
Tell me the truth.
No, I swear to God.
I remember
that my son told me
he would make a program
to predict the traffic situation.
It was like an extracurricular activity.
I went to the traffic police
to help him find some traffic data.
That's all?
That's it. Nothing else.
Did you get the data
for our son?
No.
You've been working for so many years.
You can't even do this?
I knew it.
You'll say that again.
Why don't you quit?
Pei Zhi is going to the college soon.
Let's think about
doing something else.
It's better than
working outside every day.
Okay.
As for this thing,
let me think about it.
Pei Donglai.
Yes.
Director Wang wants you
to his office.
What happened?
Don't you know what happened?
[Police]
Your son did a great job.
Pei Zhi?
What did he do?
Pei Zhi wrote a program
to catch thieves.
He helped to catch
a gang of electric bike thieves.
The media has reported it.
The leader
wants to make it
as a typical case of using high technology to solve cases.
I don't know the details.
It's a good thing anyway. Go now.
Okay.
Did I scare him just now?
[Countdown to Home]
[78 Days]
I didn't think we could make it.
But the time error
was a little big, right?
Maybe we neglected
psychological changes of thieves.
After he succeeded,
he was nervous
when he passed by places near the crime scene.
So, he would ride faster.
But after riding a certain distance,
he felt relaxed
and slowed down.
We didn't think about that.