[English subtitles are available]
[The Heart of Genius]
[Episode 7]
I used to change jobs a lot.
Let me help you move your stuff.
What stuff?
I moved them all last night.
I was just kidding.
Men's words can not be trusted.
You've improved.
The colleagues of the Education Bureau
has arranged some activities
to improve the comprehensive ability of students.
It includes experience farming, physical games,
camping and so on.
Yesterday, the staff in the park
asked us
when we are going to start.
We have less than a month
to prepare for the competition.
We don't have time for this.
Cancel it.
But the Bureau has arranged
newspaper reports.
We also need some pictures of
extracurricular activities.
And this project
is part of
of our city's quality education project.
Come in.
Sir, I...
Chen Chengcheng?
Where did you go?
Take a guess.
Don't smile like that.
My back is cold.
Lin is here.
Really?
Master is here to see us?
Not only that,
he also sneaked into
the staff team here.
Then he can
teach us
like what we did in the Youth Palace.
I think so too.
After class,
I'll take you guys to meet him.
Mr. Zhang is here.
Just now,
a violent incident happened
in our training camp.
I've been encouraging you
to compete with each other,
but you are not allowed to fight each other.
Lin Zhaoxi, stand up.
I...
Stand up.
Come here.
What did I do?
Apologize to Chen Chengcheng.
Why should I apologize to him?
So you just
don't feel guilty
after hitting him, huh?
I hit him?
Why should I hit him?
Leave aside the fact that I'm only a girl,
where did this happen?
And when?
Chen Chengcheng.
Repeat what you said
in the meeting room.
I...
No matter what happens,
just tell me the truth.
I'll handle it.
I...
Sir, I remember now.
Maybe I bumped into him
when I was running.
Why didn't you help him get up
when you bumped into someone?
I'll be more careful next time.
Your behavior
has violated
the discipline of the camp.
Do you think there will be a next time?
Sir,
I got it wrong.
Lin Zhaoxi didn't hit me.
I accidentally fell down.
Don't be afraid.
Just tell us the truth.
I did it myself.
So you lied
in the meeting room?
I'm sorry.
I got it wrong.
Sir, this is obviously a misunderstanding.
There's no need to blame her.
Lin Zhaoxi won't
bully her classmates.
Since Chen Chengcheng didn't lie,
then it's Lin Zhaoxi.
I don't care what is the purpose of your lies,
you should be punished.
Pei Zhi,
now you just stand up
and speak?
You're at fault too.
Your team members
will be punished for being implicated by you.
This afternoon,
all team members in these two teams
are not allowed
to study in the library.
You will follow Mr. Xie
to dig sweet potatoes.
Dig the sweet potatoes?
Lin Zhaoxi, raise the hoe higher.
Higher.
Smile happily.
One, two, three.
Great.
Guys, let's dig sweet potatoes.
Let's dig sweet potatoes!
Hurry up!
Here.
Be careful.
Here it is.
Look, this one is really big.
Here, Lu Zhihao, Lu Zhihao.
Take this and look at me.
- There are so may sweet potatoes here. - One, two, three.
Look. There must be some here.
When are we going to find Lin?
I wanted to go now,
but I guess I don't have a chance now.
Is this called reforming us through labor?
Reforming us through labor?
Look at them.
They are all having fun.
I guess
it's a teaching mission.
Snape found an excuse
to drag us here.
But I already told Lin
and I didn't go.
I didn't want him to worry.
I have no choice.
Do you think I should pretend to be sick
and distract Mr. Xie?
You guys can go and find master.
That's a good idea.
But it's a bit...
Wait.
We don't have to do this.
Here.
Look at this.
Take a photo.
Hurry up, Yu Tianjiao.
Look at our results.
OK. OK.
It's great.
There's another one here.
Let's dig here.
Here?
This place!
Hello.
You are...?
I'm...
Are you
Xie Ran from Sanxiang University?
Yes, my name is Xie Ran.
You are a journalist from City Times,
right?
Hello, hello
Hello.
Welcome.
Hello, hello.
I didn't bring my business card.
It's okay.
Didn't we agree
that I'll send you the photos online?
Why did you
come all the way here?
Didn't the leader take it seriously?
He asked me
to take a look.
Only in this way can I write
a good story...
the truth about this activity.
You're right.
Take a look.
Follow me.
When did master become a reporter?
How could you believe Lin?
Everyone,
the reporter of City Times
is here to interview us.
Let's extend our welcome to him.
Guys,
aren't you here to learn Olympic mathematics?
Why are you digging sweet potatoes?
We made a mistake
and we were punished to work.
It's not like that, sir.
It's a project that aims at
expanding their capabilities,
they will experience farming and build their willpower in this process.
Of course. The most glorious thing is working.
That's right.
Class,
are you tired now after digging sweet potatoes?
No.
Are you happy?
Yes.
After digging the sweet potatoes,
I'll bake these sweet potatoes with you.
OK?
No, we...
Okay?
OK!
We don't have this in the project.
I understand.
They've been working all day.
Why don't you let them experience
the fruit of their hard work?
Otherwise they will feel uncomfortable.
In this way, they can feel
the joy of the farmers in the harvest season,
right?
The joy of harvest.
There are three here,
and they are linked together.
This is rotten.
It's so big.
Let me do this.
I'm a professional. Come on.
Come on, guys.
Here.
Look at the camera.
This little girl.
Hurry up.
Look at the camera.
Smile.
Here.
One, two, three.
Cheese.
1/6 minus
7/12,
plus 9/20,
minus 11/30,
plus...
What do you want?
Give me the pen. I need to do the exercise.
Give it to me.
Give it to me. I need to do the exercise.
Give me the pen. I want to do the exercise.
I want to do exercises.
Give it to me.
Give it to me. I want to do it.
We'll find someone
to lure her out.
Then you can
say something to her.
When she leaves,
get yourself dirty
and go to Zhang Shuping.
Sir.
Do you understand?
Chen Chengcheng.
He said he didn't lie.
That means you lied.
I don't care
the purpose of your lies,
you need to be punished.
Can Mr. Zhang believe it?
We are the witnesses.
The five of us saw it.
We saw it clearly.
Don't worry.
Lin Zhaoxi.
It's her.
Great.
Now we don't even need to lure her out.
Over there. Hurry.
Go in.
Hurry up.
Someone is coming. Hurry up.
Mr. Xie.
Would you like to have a seat?
Coming.
Mr. Reporter,
when will the sweet potatoes be cooked?
Did you see the fire?
The sweet potatoes will be cooked after the fire goes out.
You really know it.
Just some experience.
Mr. Xie,
what are they studying?
Olympic mathematics.
Don't you know that?
Let me ask you.
What do you want to learn?
I want to learn math.
Do you want to study math
or Olympic mathematics?
What's the difference?
At least, their spellings
are different.
Mr. Reporter,
I can tell that
you have your opinion on Olympic mathematics.
No.
Let me ask you.
In your
understanding,
what is the difference
between math and Olympic mathematics?
Handsome boy, you go first.
Math is a subject.
Olympic mathematics?
I'm not sure.
I know.
Math is simple and Olympic mathematics is difficult.
What about you?
If math is a car,
Olympic mathematics will
enable you to drive in a faster and more flexible way.
What about you, Mr. Xie?
I think
Pei Zhi was only half right.
Math is a subject.
Olympic mathematics is a competition project
in this subject.
What do you think?
I think Lu Zhihao is right.
Certainly
Mr. Xie is right.
Let me ask you a question.
Raise your hand if you know.
Who knows
how many sweet potatoes we dug today?
Then raise your hand
if you know how many you got for yourself.
Good.
You're quite sensitive to numbers.
Put your hands down.
But I still want to know
how many sweet potatoes
we got today.
What should we do?
We can add the number of sweet potatoes
of each person.
Smart.
But the problem is
what if we don't know how to add?
If we are primitives,
and addition
hasn't been invented yet.
What should we do?
Actually, in the beginning
in human society.
At that time,
we all wore
tiger skin skirts.
And we will gather around the fire,
just like now.
At that time,
there were no addition, subtraction, multiplication or division,
and there were no numbers.
We live on hunting.
We hunted a lot every day.
When we get home,
we don't know
how many animals we hunted.
But one day,
I think I should write it down.
Otherwise, what should we do
if Mr. Xie comes to our house
and take them?
When I got home,
I'll draw some lines on the wall,
to record
how many animals I've hunted today.
I got three chickens this day, and four ducks the other day.
But there's another problem after a long time.
Because when I got home,
I found the wall was full of lines.
The wall was going to collapse,
so did I.
I need this house to get myself married.
How can I live in it now?
This problem
happened in every family
of my tribe.
Everyone
need to start counting.
So,
someone started
to solve this problem creatively.
This
is basically
the process of how numbers are born.
If you're lucky to see
the stone board carved by the ancient Babylon,
these Babylons
will use a pen that looks like a triangular prism
to carve the words.
It is known as the cuneiform
today.
When they
draw one line on the wall, it represents one.
Two lines means two.
And other numbers are similar.
When you draw to ten,
a new math symbol
is born.
Like this.
This is a great leap of human civilization.
Calculating with symbols
represents the birth of the great algorithm.
[The birth of the great algorithm]
OK.
Olympic mathematics, in my opinion,
is a method that enables you
to put aside
the advanced tools
when facing a difficult problem,
instead you should solve it
with innovative thought,
just like previous scholars.
It's like a person
is trying to fight the evil dragon
with a small wood stick.
Each time you solve a problem with it,
it's a marvelous achievement.
Maybe one day,
when you made some accomplishment
in math,
you'll meet your river.
At that time,
you need to pick up the axe
and build a bridge
of your own,
so that you can cross your own river.
Olympic mathematics
is like cleaning the rust of this axe you need.
Even if you make your axe pretty sharp,
the bridge may not be built well.
But a sharp axe
is helpful anyway.
But please remember,
sharpening this axe and building your bridge
are not all about math.
If you focus on it too much, you will lose
the happiness of learning math.
After all, most people
who study math...
Is the sweet potato ready?
Okay.
I'll go take a look.
Here, have some sweet potatoes.
Have some sweet potatoes.
Be careful.
Here you are.
- Thanks a lot, thanks a lot. - My pleasure.
Let's share them.
This half is for you.
Thank you.
Here, more for you.
That will do.
Thanks, that will do.
That will do?
Here.
You're welcome.
Xiaotian, I'll give you some more.
Smells good.
Have some of this.
Thank you.
It's hot.
Is it well cooked?
Yes.
Is it because you're bored?
You didn't finish what you just said.
Mathematicians study math
because they're bored.
Right?
You're not a reporter.
Who are you?
I'm a parent.
Parent?
Which student's parent?
My surname is Lin.
You're Lin Zhaoxi's father?
I'm her master,
at least for now.
It smells so good.
So sweet.
This sweet potato is so...
Guys, I'm leaving.
Everyone,
say goodbye to Mr. Journalist.
Goodbye, sir.
Goodbye, Mr. journalist.
Bye.
He said
this pain is nothing.
Wipe your tears. Don't be afraid.
At least we still have dreams.
He said...
Guys, let's sing a song
and go back while singing?
OK. OK.
Let's sing...
Lin Zhaoxi, can you think of a song and lead us singing?
I know a song.
I'll sing.
Please sing along.
OK.
One, two, three.
I'm riding my little motorbike, and I really love it.
It never gets stuck in traffic.
What are you doing?
Why did you kick Chen Chengcheng out?
He wants to leave.
It's none of my business.
You asked Chen Chengcheng to frame me.
He changed his mind,
so you kicked him out,
right?
Why are you asking me?
Are you a teacher
or a police officer?
I'm going to tell Mr. Zhang.
Go ahead.
Who can prove what you said?
Wait and see.
The society will teach you how to be a human.
I'll wait.
But you will leave
after the next exam.
I'm afraid you won't see me in the future,
and you won't see that day either.
Brat.
What?
He didn't admit it and provoked me.
He said we were going to leave here.
Brat.
Don't mind them.
We'll try our best.
The result is not that important.
Come with me
to meet someone.
He will definitely help us
pass the exam.
Who is that? Sounds amazing.
You all know him.
This is the book list.
And this is
the outline I made for everyone.
But the books are in the library.
You have chosen good books.
But I still have to
go to the library and take a look.
Let's discuss
when the class begins.
Don't let Mr. Zhang know
that we have master.
We will be noticed
since there are 12 of us.
It's better to have classes at night.
But we don't have sufficient time at night.
And we have to return to the dormitory before ten o'clock.
We'll sneak out
after the teacher left,
and gather outside
and then go to the mailroom.
The class will end at
two o'clock.
Then go back to sleep.
Two o'clock? How can I sleep?
We won't get enough sleep in this case.
Guys,
the training camp will be
our memory.
Do you want to end it with failure
or do you want to win
with sweat?
Lin, don't laugh.
I'm serious.
Usually, we won't find the meaning
of something
until we really devote ourselves to it.
If we keep that "I don't care" attitude,
and tell ourselves that nothing is going to
make a difference, no matter what we do,
maybe we will regret
when we grow up.
I have experience regret,
I don't want to feel it again.
Auntie,
can you get me a takeaway?
Please give me the fried pork with garlic,
fried eggs with tomatoes,
and braised chicken wings.
The food here is good.
It's not as good as mine.
You can cook meals?
Of course.
Great.
Your hands can earn you a large amount of betrothal gifts.
How can you calculate like that?
Don't be that snobbish.
You're not my dad.
My betrothal gift is not your business.
Just kidding.
Have a chicken wing.
You eat it.
I don't like this part of the chicken wing,
I like the tip of the wings, it's delicious.
No way.
Back in the Youth's Palace,
I said you liked the tip of wings,
you said who will eat the tip of the wings if you can have the middle part of the chicken wings.
So you lied to me.
Hurry up and eat your meal.
Look at you, how skinny you are.
Let me tell you.
you will feel regretful
when you find yourself short in the future.
Dad.
What are you laughing at?
Thinking about your prank?
No.
I think Pei Zhi is right.
You didn't change.
You've evolved!
MANMON Evolution!
I wonder what are you thinking
all day long?
Just eat your meals!
MANMON Evolution...
[The Chicken-and rabbits Problem]
This question.
Some chickens and rabbits share a cage.
There are
have 12 heads.
34 legs.
Please find out
how many chickens and rabbits are there.
It's simple, right?
It's just a linear equation with two unknowns, right?
But now,
I want you not to use
linear equation in two unknowns.
How to solve it?
Look.
Let's assume
we removed
half of all the animals' legs.
Therefore, half of 34 equals to 17.
Now,
the amount of the head of chickens
equals to the amount of their legs.
If we subtract the amount of all their legs, 17,
from the amount of all their heads,12,
it means
we removed
another leg of them.
Now the chicken has no legs,
right?
The rabbit has one leg left.
17 minus 12 equals 5.
So there are five rabbits.
Seven chickens.
It can be solved like this?
It's quite interesting.
Come on, let's make a contrast.
I'll write down the questions.
Now, let's
suppose there is a turtle who has
with three legs and two eyes.
♫Dappled light and shadow♫
So in the future,
when it comes to
usually we can solve it with
these three methods.
the lift feet method, the packing method,
♫Flowing time♫
and hypothesis.
Understand?
Yes.
Next question.
Two places in the east and west,
♫Don't hesitate, or it will slip through your finger♫
they are 5,400 meters away from each other.
Now two person depart from
these two places at the same time...
♫Just live in the moment♫
♫Fill your heart♫
♫Fill everything with joy♫
♫Take your time to let those things grow♫
♫You will be accompanied by light even if you are in darkness♫
♫When you look at the two sides of the world♫
Boss, have you printed it?
Coming.
One copy is ready.
♫You will make everything come true with your hand when you reach for you dream♫
Okay, thank you.
We still need one more.
You asked me
why should we study prime number,
♫Dappled light and shadow♫
right?
♫We should find the real incentive in our heart♫
The mathematicians have studied them
for over 2,000 years.
They studied the distribution pattern of prime numbers,
♫Time flowing♫
and calculated the amount of prime numbers
♫We should take back the light that were taken away from us♫
in a certain range.
They worked with great diligence, and spent their lifetime on it.
♫Don't feel confused♫
Does it work?
♫Do not repeat the mistakes of failure♫
It looks meaningless,
But it's not.
Because today...
Hold on. Take it.
Sit straight.
Look at this question.
Is it familiar?
How long will it take?
I'm sure it'll be soon.
What about you?
Up to today,
three of you quitted voluntarily.
One team was cancelled.
Therefore,
the ten teams here,
half of you will leave after the exam.
Everyone,
our daily accumulation
is to show our current performance.
Don't be nervous
during the exam.
Relax.
That's how you can show your real level.
The seat of this exam will be mixed.
Please come to Mr. Xie
to get your seat number
and sit in your corresponding position.
Come on. Come on.
Among the four-sided ABCD,
AB=BC=CD
∠C=70°.
∠BCD=170°.
Please find out the size
of ∠BAD?
I should know this question.
What's going on?
There are two person Xand Y,
they set off at the same time
from two places, A and B,
and head towards each other.
They meet each other somewhere in 20 minutes.
If X can walk 15 additional meters
per minute,
how many
positive integer are there
that satisfy
15 (x-2)<7x+ 4/5?
Easy.
First of all,
solve the ninety-nine point formation.
The amount of points in the 99th floor is
6*99=594.
Then, with the formula,
we can come up with
the total amount of points in this ninety-ninety-nine point formation,
which is...
If Lin Zhaoxi returns to Strawberry World,
can I meet her in the future?
What are you doing?
Do you have fried peanuts?
No.
Can you cook something for me?
Do you think this is a restaurant?
I'll prepare the materials.
Please help me.
Come and pick up them in this afternoon.
Okay.
Over there.
How is it?
Are you okay?
I can't throw up.
I feel disgusting.
In order to get your dad
buy you a computer,
you worked so hard.
It's not about the computer.
Then what is it?
I want to do my best.
I don't want to regret in the future.
Didn't you say that?
Now I'll announce
the final average score
of this exam
The top five teams
are as follows,
the first place, Group of Zhang Liang.
Great!
Zhang Liang, 97.
Liu Xu, 88.
Wang Feng, 78.
Li Ming, 82.
Shi Zhe, 80.
The average score is 85.
The second place is group of Zhao Hongliang.
Zhao Hongliang, 84.
Yan Su, 75.
Qian Zheng Yi, 82.
Du Feng, 82.
Lu Ang 79.
The average score is 80.4.
No.3.
Nie Shuai's Group.
Nie Shuai, 82.
Zhang Chen is 78.
Yang Youcai is 77.
Lu Dazhi, 75.
Luo Yi is 80.
The average is 78.4.
Lin Zhaoxi, Pei Zhi.
The fourth place is group of Pei Zhi.
Great.
Yeah!
Pei Zhi, 100.
Dang Aimin, 80.
Liao Tianhua 76.
Zheng Bingqing is 70.
Zou Wenchao, 65.
78 for the song.
The average score is 78.2.
Lin Zhaoxi! Lin Zhaoxi! Lin Zhaoxi!
Lin Zhaoxi! Lin Zhaoxi!
The last group left is,
the fifth place,
team of Lin Zhaoxi.
Lin Zhaoxi, 98.
Lu Zhihao, 82.
Shao Mingchen 67.
Yao Xiaotian 70.
Yu Tianjiao is 72.
Wang Lu 76.
The average is 77.5.
The rest of you,
whose names are not mentioned,
please leave here
this afternoon.
See you.
Half a month ago,
80 people entered this camp.
After selection,
only
27 people are standing here.
You are the elites.
You should applaud for yourselves.
Don't let yourself slack off..
Hang on there.
You go first.
I'll talk to Hua Juan alone.
OK.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
Snape said
only three groups can get in the competition.
But in the photo,
There are four groups.
It's OK.
We've tried our best
to come here.
We worked together
and chased the same target.
Let's leave the rest to God.
After all, the things about that photo
is just our guessing.
We still have time.
Maybe he changed his mind.
Maybe there are other changes.
Stop worrying.
You almost got crushed before.
Just relax.
As a star,
I spend my time wandering around the parallel universe with you.
That is great enough.
I haven't heard you say
you're a star for a long while.
So I should remind you,
as a fan,
you have to know your place.
It is your fans that gave you all you have,
okay?
Let's go, mom.
Go to hell!
I don't have a naughty son like you.
How am I naughty?
Aren't you naughty?
No.
Hurry up.
Stop running.
I got the lowest score this time.
I dragged you down.
Don't think like that.
We are all human.
We only have two legs.
Left leg and right leg.
They are all here, so you are not dragging us behind.
You can only drag the legs of pigs.
Everyone has made progress.
Don't be discouraged.
Besides, Master is here.
We're not afraid of the exam.
You're right.
I'm sure Snape didn't expect that
we already have
a teacher of our own.
Long live, Lin!
We haven't thanked Master yet.
It's not convenient during the day.
How about we prepare a surprise
for Master tonight?
Sure.
What surprise?
How about prepare the breakdancing
for Master?
What are you dancing?
So ugly.
I'm the best dancer.
Pei Zhi's group is here, that's awful enough.
Now the team of
also stayed.
This is so annoying.
This time, Lu Zhihao
got 82 points.
Look at him.
It seems he got full marks.
Wang Feng, what's wrong with you?
Your score is not as high as Lu Zhihao's.
Sorry, Liang.
I failed this exam.
But I have an important information
to report to you.
I woke up in the middle of the night before yesterday
I saw Zou Benchao
from Lin Zhaoxi's group
came out of the toilet.
I didn't think much at first.
When I went back to my room and looked at the watch,
I realized it's already two o'clock in the morning.
The more I think about it, the weirder it is.
What's wrong with going to the toilet?
He was wearing clothes, pants,
and sneakers.
He must have just come back from outside.
Then tell me,
where did he go at 2 a.m.
No matter where he went,
it has nothing to do with your failure in the exam.
Don't change the topic.
Let's talk about scores.
Liang,
I just heard something.
It seems that Lin Zhaoxi and Pei Zhi
have a master.
Master?
Interesting.
The performance of
Lin Zhaoxi's and Pei Zhi's group
is beyond my expectation.
Not mention
Pei Zhi and Lin Zhaoxi.
It's rare that
everyone is improving.
Mr. Zhang, you even praised them.
I thought
you don't like them.
Every teacher likes
smart students.
But if I didn't
give them some pressure,
they can't achieve
their current results.
Yes.
Sister, where are those peanuts?
Here.
This
is against our company's rules.
Understand?
Good craftsmanship. You really know how to do it.
Hurry up.
I'll come again next time.
Don't come. Just go.
We're colleagues. I'll come.
Zhaosheng.
Shuping.
I thought it was you.
Look.
Why are you...
Your child is here?
What? I don't have a child.
I'm the guard at the gate.
You have got a stable job.
Yes.
Because of that thing in college,
I didn't get my certificate.
It's hard to find a job.
Just deal with it.
Are you a cook here?
Well, the Education Bureau
asked me to come back
to teach the Olympic mathematics class.
I can use this base
to prepare
for training.
It's actually good.
So you are a leader?
Can you arrange it for me?
I'll be a cook.
I'm just
a teacher here.
And I'm not
in the same system
with the management department.
Good.
Let me see
if I can find a chance
to talk about this.
OK.
Thank you. That's good.
I'll get some food.
I'm going to my room.
Okay.
This is...
This is a surprise
we prepared for you.
Hua Juan painted the outline.
Pei Zhi painted the hair.
Lu Zhihao drew the beard.
I put the eyes on.
I'm not blind.
Why am I wearing sunglasses?
I have another surprise for you.
Twist it.
What's that look?
Doesn't that look like you?
Not like me. I'm so cool.
Try your sunglasses cookies.
By the way,
Mimi, it's time to eat.
What are you doing?
A stray cat.
You really decided to adopt it?
It won't leave.
What can I do?