I like you, teacher.
You did well on this.
Please grant me one wish.
A wish?
Did we ever make that kind of promise?
Am I not pretty?
What should I do...
I like smart people.
With these grades, you wouldn’t even get near our school.
Ah.
I really like you, teacher.
You even show up
in my dreams.
Geez.
You’re such a kid.
Why isn’t Jeong-yeon here?
Is he sick or something?
Sorry I’m late.
Whoa—did you get into a fight?
Do you need a lawyer? I know someone.
No, it’s nothing. I’m fine.
If it’s nothing serious,
let’s start the experiment for HQ first.
Wow, that’s cold.
Are you insane about work?
Hey.
Do you get paid more than me?
What are you talking about?
Jeong-yeon.
Come over here.
I’ll skip the explanation.
This is Case Delphi, trial six.
What’s the most precious memory of your life?
Um...
I used to spend a lot of time with my first love.
Every single day back then was precious to me.
And the worst memory?
I confessed, we even kissed.
And then he patted my head
and said it was “just a momentary feeling.”
Wow. What a jerk.
Right? Pretty awful.
Jeong-yeon.
Shall we step outside and talk?
Are you rebelling again, now of all times?
Oh, this?
I thought you might care if I looked beaten up.
Like before.
Then what about your hand?
You’re still a kid.
I’m grown up now, you know?
You don’t need to feel guilty anymore.
If you want to sleep with me, you can.
You’ve got some nerve for someone so small.
Ha.
You’re not my type.
Yeah, right.
Why do you think that?
You like pretty types like me.
I saw everything.
Saw what?
My observation notes from high school.
[Emotional Attachment Formation
and Correction Experiment
in At-Risk Adolescents]
(It was all written there. About me.)
(He shows a strong interest in appearance.)
(Especially when called “pretty,”
he blushes.)
(Jeong-yeon is pretty.)
Back then, you were young.
You were perfect as an experiment subject.
Was that really all it was?
And...
Just...
a cute student.