Yes.
(It's coming. Daydream.)
It must be General.
When the door is closed, it must be like this.
The gesture of knocking...
He's familiar with us.
They even made trouble
you two
what a surprise!
My goodness.
I was just here bragging about them.
I didn't knock on Park Wen's door today.
But Jia Rong's.
I still have my original thoughts.
I think everyone is outstanding.
I want to know more people.
At the same time, I want to see Kvi's attitude towards me
kvi's attitude towards me.
To date with me.
Why are you talking so quietly?
That's fine.
What do you want to do?
I'll think about it.
We'll discuss it tomorrow.
How Jia Rong sneaks her
she just got here.
She wants to contact other interested parties to make a judgment.
Actually, I'm surprised.
Not that surprised.
I figured it out.
If there's anyone knocking at my door,
It might be him.
I'm looking forward to it.
But I still don't know what I'm going to do tomorrow.
Why?
But I knocked on two people's doors today.
After I asked Jiarong out,
I knocked on Kevin's door.
I wanted to give him the medicine.
He did catch a cold.
I was worried that he might get sick.
But he may want to tell him
what's this?
Look at that.
Zhang is smiling happily.
In the end,
and specially invited him.
I'm not here to ask you out.
I'm here to bring you the medicine.
Help
I'm not here to ask you out.
Sister Meng,
I need to call Sister Meng.
Help
I didn't regret after knocking on Jia Rong's door.
But when I gave Kevin the medicine,
I saw his smiling face when he opened the door.
I felt like I had betrayed someone.
I feel like that. How come?
What on earth did I do?
How can you smile so much
you didn't ask him out,
how could you?
To experience this kind of feeling?
Do you think it'll be hard tonight?
If I were you,
I'd feel a little disappointed.
But I believe he's 41 years old.
He is a mature man.
He will adjust himself.
He can adjust
confused.
Is this OK?
Da Meng just gave me the medicine.
She said it wasn't medicine.
I...
This is the way to play it.
We can't play it either.
What kind of game is this?
And...
The door is knocking again.
Isn't Shirley Wang Zhen?
Right.
Is Shirley Wang or Da Meng?
What's going on?
Why?
Right.
I also want to know why.
Alright.
Yangyang and I have dated twice.
As the last male guest to enter the hut,
I think we should give him a chance to date someone.
To start with,
the first person I want to know is Lao Wang,
to know
to know each other better.
The t dress is what makes you.
But I'm not sure how to carry it out right now.
Maybe I'll continue to
when I've thought it out.
General Lin is the first in my mind.
However,
after much hesitation,
for a long time.
The problem is that I'm afraid that
when we have nothing to talk about,
this is too hard.
Too hard.
♫ Beat the air ♫
You asked me out for dinner.
General Lin's smile is so cute.
General is confused again.
Has anyone asked you out tomorrow?
No.
Is it okay if I ask you out?
Alright.
Really
really.
You didn't reject me.
I won't.
Be good.
I won't do it. Alright, be a good boy.
See you later.
I'm off.
Stop it!
Help
help
I didn't expect that uncle would invite me to a party.
Because I didn't really talk that much to him.
He's the one who doesn't talk to me that much.
He won't...
It's true.
I'm leaving now.
He's the king.
I want to confirm my heart
today, all the boys in my Moments are flashing
mouth wash dishes
old Wang.
He's very interesting.
Besides funny,
I also think he has some aspects that I haven't seen before.
I could never fathom his feelings.
How come you didn't say a word to him today
master and Kevin are out.
That's right.
How is your feeling now?
I...
It's
but why is this door so much like CVI's?
The footsteps and breath
It's Wang Zhen.
Not really.
I also told Mr. Wang
that girls are mine.
I didn't hang out with you before.
I think I've talked to all the other guys
but I know Wang the least.
There's always another side to him when we meet alone, right?
So I'm curious
to know more about
because I think
I've told him
we need to know more about other people
I think that just because we're in contact with someone,
but I have no other choice.
A crush on that person is not a crush.
Maybe it's just that I have a good feeling after knowing more
that's when it's real.
So I think it's a good thing to meet people.
Did anyone ask you out?
She has.
What?
Wei,
should she confirm it?
Hello there.
Ah
wei!
What?
Eat.
Right now?
Tomorrow.
Your room is also big.
Show around?
No need for a tour.
It's so neat.
Temporary accommodation? No. I live here every day.
You can't stay over there.
To keep the quilt clean,
It's over.
See you off.
No need to see you off.
You don't have to.
I also know
that I meet with those I'm interested in.
Then I started to learn
ka Jun and Wang Zhen strike me as different.
Jia Jun shared many things he had seen with me.
He's really knowledgeable
I feel a little small in front of him
I feel like a burden, yes.
From here on,
when I get along with Wang,
with Wang.
So,
to take this opportunity
to see if he is the right man.
This is quite normal.
He is doing this logically.
That's right.
There is logic.
Hey.
Thank you, Qiao Wei.
Are you afraid of the moon?
Right.
So the post you posted today was sent to him?
I don't know whose Moments I use gold.
You have to find him
to re-establish...
What's the schedule?
All right.
We'll arrange it then.
I won't see you off.
I love when the punch lights and
you were in your yellow coat the.
Of course there were accidents.
I was not expecting that.
I didn't expect the second one to be more awkward than this.
But that's fine.
We're both unafraid of embarrassment.
They won't have any problem getting along.
I think
who is so happy?
Are you watching a pony?
Pony, right?
I'm sure I'll choose a pony.
That's right.
I chose Ma as my second date today.
The reason?
We agreed.
I invited him for dinner,
but he secretly paid the bill
and
the first time
I think it was a good time.
It's fine if you want to know more about me.
May I come in?
I went right in.
I was afraid that others might find out
and work stealthily.
You're very low-key.
To be honest,
I really want to play games.
I don't know if the other guys play games.
So this game is really...
How come I'm even making myself nervous?
He's so nervous.
I think he can.
You want to meet Xiao Ma?
Guys,
he took something out.
He didn't leave empty-handed.
What did you give to Xiao Ma?
I want to communicate more with Lao Ma at this moment.
What a coincidence.
Can I come in?
Alright.
I'll come in then.
It's a bit messy here.
What?
I might be a little messy myself.
What do you need?
I prepared honey water for you.
And I have no other medicines.
I can only get you some vitamin C.
He has diarrhea.
Is it because Lin Yi is sick
Isn't Xiao Ma the one who gave him the medicine?
You're too humble.
Take it first.
Would you like to have a sip?
Xiao Ma is into this.
It's...
The moment
when I said I had diarrhea,
he didn't seem to be that concerned in front of everyone.
But after everyone had left,
he gave me something secretly.
I think he cares about me as well.
Then can I ask if any girls invited you?
Honestly, there are good ones.
That way, will you
think a lot?
About today's matter?
I also wanted to tell you.
Humph!
Is Lily here to talk to you?
Right.
Actually,
I told Lily before.
I said...
Would you like to ask Lao Ma about your time today?
Right.
He's got a lot of secrets.
That's why he came to ask you.
So you asked him to do it.
I don't really care about this.
Humph!
But I was hoping to see if you'd show your concern.
Then I'm concerned about you.
Right.
So I'm very satisfied with the result.
So I'll tell you the truth now.
Someone posted on Moments
about the report.
I'm thinking why I should report it.
You didn't report yourself.
But I...
I threw a fit or something.
You said that
I might hear it in nine days.
What am I looking at?
Isn't it what you want to see the most?
Alright.
-Bye bye. -Bye.
Have a good rest.
I didn't rest well at noon,
I'll eat this then.
What about this?
It has natural vitamins. You can also protect yourself from the sun. It's good.
See you
aren't enough for both of them.
It's sweet.
Lao Ma was chosen by two girls.
I expected that.
He's always popular.
It's normal for multiple people to choose.
That's right.
If there are two girls,
I knew that.
The other girl
the other girl should be Yi Ying.
That is Jingyang and Jia Jun.
There are two new boys left.
They are real.
I didn't know how to do it.
This...
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it either?
Go talk to Jiang Junlin.
He won't.
When they all come to me,
I'll think they're interested in me.
To me,
I wasn't actually very happy.
Instead, I feel stressed out.
And burdened.
I hope that every date
every date is an important experience.
Whether it's as a friend with Shen Zhen
or as a friend
we all start with good feelings
I think these two have their own needs to be very important to be treated
Instead, they're arranged in a day.
I don't know how to handle this.
So you're doing two, too.
You got two performances.
I have two.
There must be Yin and Lin Yi.
So it's hard for me to deal with now.
How do you arrange your schedules?
What's your arrangement? You can discuss it with them?
That's right.
Really?
You can't.
Because you don't understand me.
You don't understand, adults.
Yeah, it's good that you don't understand them.
I think it's good.
I feel relieved knowing that you're there.
No need to face it alone.
It's good.
Let me tell you something. Honesty is your only choice.
It's my
wang Zheng is right.
Young people are funny.
They may have a heavy psychological burden.
And he feels that his actions affect other people.
And then other people's opinions of him affect him.
He cares a lot about these.
What about you?
I'll care more about myself and those I think are important.
What more do you want?
I know a good food stall in three locations.
Let me contact them.
I want to eat at a food stall.
Let me take you there.
I ate at a food stall for days.
That's right.
Without taking me,
tactical retreat.
We'll leave now.
Very sensible.
With Li tomorrow.
Really
that's right.
Can't more people have the big platoon?
Yes, you can ask them.
What he will do.
If he comes back early,
I'll see if I can go there early.
Go there early?
I asked for it.
I'll check it out later.
OK. Let's see.
To me,
I take this very positively.
A lot of things
they need a process of comparison.
That's the saying.
The bullet will fly away and leave a blank.
I've only been here for three or four days.
I've already been out with Susu twice.
I know. I've known a lot of people usually.
If it were me,
I'd make the same choice.
So I wasn't upset.
The
It's
susu, this is baseless.
Without a trace. Yes.
That's the charm of reality shows.
Why didn't you ask Wang Zhen out?
They haven't dated him before.
After that first date,
we two couldn't get along much longer.
To choose Wang Zhen.
He's very curious about him.
He's curious about his
so curious.
Why not seize the chance?
He said he wasn't sure what to ask him out for.
He wants to make it perfect and more thoughtful
to get to know him more.
If we let it go...
I can just look at a random person.
I think this is what he thinks.
He also feels the same way.
It's strange though.
I think he's just full of ideas.
This girl is complicated.
It means internal friction.
Please help us at this time
help us taste it.
Miss Mo.
I think everyone is fine
there's nothing wrong with that.
I need to see more, right?
Yeah, that's all right.
So you think
da Meng said it's his
I think Da Meng can understand
because after all, he's new to the cabin
he said he wanted to see Junlin.
After choosing someone else,
his own reaction is reasonable.
What I did to win him is like him.
Why would he look brave and cowardly?
Was he playing in the water
or something.
He was very, very aggressive,
he is very independent and powerful.
But sometimes when he has something to say,
he's afraid of that
he's two-faced.
He knocks on the door and brings medicine to people.
It's actually brave.
But the door opened,
and you're a coward when you see her.
It's hard for others to judge.
And mysterious to us.
It's interesting.
Right.
There's flavor.
What do you think of Sun Wumi's pair?
Very interesting.
That's a totally different smell.
The current state of
seem to be in such a state,
so far we've reached a consensus in the house.
And they're a little bit small.
I think he almost feels that way.
But I am very curious.
If no one helped him,
will Lin Yi still be this steadfast?
Indeed, it's hard to say for sure.
It's hard to tell.
Love is very complicated.
So Xiao Ma is childish.
Oh, right.
But I think Lin Yi is good at one thing.
In a relationship, she has a long mouth.
Right.
He can communicate.
He speaks it.
Yes, he is very smart.
I think he is a good communicator.
He is also very important.
He has a long mouth.
Some people have long mouths, too.
They have smelly mouths.
It's better that you don't tell me.
I'm really...
Fatty and smelly.
The moment he starts to speak,
the most obvious contrast between Lin Yi and Xu Li.
Why?
Because Xu Li is like this.
There is a detail
she read Moments.
She took a photo of Wang Zhen.
But he said I wanted Jiang Junlin to see it.
I'm going to see Wang Zhen.
But he didn't open his mouth.
I want you to see that I'm looking for someone else. He can't admit it.
He thinks Jiang Junlin is a good guy.
Yeah, I can do that.
He and Zhang Jun Lin only stayed on the beach walk so far.
He said we should go and get to know other people.
He didn't tell us
that he might have later.
For example, after I saw you dating with Mother Pornpan,
I was having feelings.
To express this kind of thing.
They had a deal to contact other guests.
He might be too shy to meet Jiang Jun.
You're anxious?
Yes. What is Mr. Du's view on love?
Because I think Jin Jing is right.
Not just the slap.
I want what's fragrant. Yeah.
Is the taboo in love. Let him guess.
It adds to the uncertainty.
In fact, there are many, many uncertainties in a relationship.
If I don't talk about many things, I'll let him guess
and he can't guess.
So, the truth you must always remember in a relationship is
no doubt about it.
Right.
Don't have any doubts.
Kill any doubt right away.
Keep guessing
even though you couldn't.
How to arrange it
how to adjust yourself.
Let's take a look at the upcoming date.
You go ahead
that I can't refuse.
I love handsome guys.
Handsome guys love me.
We've changed a lot today.
Super cool!
Don't forget your original aspiration after you cut it.
I came to watch handsome guys.
They've earned it!
We got it.
Is he going on a date after shaving for real?
He's so handsome today because he wants to see you.
Because I shaved this.
I was wondering what's different today.
You change.
It's always the same.
What do you think
five years younger.
You shaved your beard.
Can I see that you don't have a beard?
That's fine.
That's right.
Please remember this.
Li Mengdie told me in the simplest way that she wanted me to look without beard.
I think Li Mengdie likes young girls.
Right.
Is to create a young and vigorous look especially on the appearance.
I feel like a boy will be at home today.
I knew who it was.
Because I asked this guy.
I think maybe Jie
I don't know.
Why are you laughing?
We're guessing.
I said boys would stay in the hut today.
Why?
Because two girls are dating the same guy.
That's right.
This may happen to more than one person.
It seems Wang was asked out by Lily and Pan.
Actually, Lin Yi was talking about himself.
And he extracted other information.
My headphones. Sometimes my cellphone is the voice of my voice.
The two of them
he broke up.
Why should I?
We talked the other day.
That might not have happened.
What's the matter?
That's right.
Lao Ma taught me
I should forget all about it.
Got it.
Congratulations.
They've got back together.
Boss.
I have music.
You mean it.
I'll order that.
OK. It depends on your time.
I know you'll be busy in the afternoon.
I really invite you to dinner.
Really
I'll wait for you, okay? Your food is real.
See you later.
Alright.
He's meeting Lin Yi
looking forward to it.
Where are you going with Susu and kvi?
So, you and Susu today?
I will.
I didn't expect it either.
How could that be?
Because he and I are the youngest.
Right?
Except the accident,
the dream.
I'm going to tell you a little expression I observed.
Maybe it's what I feel when I met Jia Rong
I think
did he hear it?
He heard it.
A lone wolf...
He ran to the highway to be fed by humans.
And then his eyes started to look like this.
And husky.
He's so funny.
I...
Is he cool every day? He's so cool.
Every day he comes in like the gust of wind
have you eaten that Mengdie?
I've got some noodles. Do you want some?
I have eaten.
You have eaten.
Thanks.
I just wanted to tell you to share the food.
We didn't see many people there.
So I bought some
I gave him half of it.
Today...
And two dates.
You gave my words out loud.
I don't want to
Is this
Is this one.
But I'm different from him.
Why not?
I'm in a more relaxed mood.
He's already sweating.
(It's serious.)
I'm revealing a little message to you.
Today, I saw something
and I was like,
who bought this
If it's edible.
Then Wang came in and said Lao Ma bought it.
And Lin Yi said,
I'm also one of them. "
Who bought this?
Of course it has mine.
No wonder they wouldn't have mine.
I have research license.
No. There's no.
No, Yin. I didn't expect them to get up so early.
So I didn't buy her any.
No.
I'm looking forward to your return tonight.
And you.
You're alright.
I like him better. He carries a bag for you.
Is there another secret?
There is.
Do you know how exhausting it is to switch between two scenes?
I even wondered what I was doing.
I think Xiao Ma is not a bad guy
he thought I need to be new for every girl.
It's a form of respect.
Face the same situation.
The state of Xiao Ma
It's me.
The
the
to the stage.
In fact, I've been
I want to see this.
It's here.
So when I asked you out yesterday,
did you get any idea?
He didn't stay straight.
Why didn't you think of that?
I already told you
you think I was joking?
I didn't expect that you are so trustworthy?
No one is this trustworthy.
I'm the only one so honest.
That's funny.
Who do you think I asked out yesterday?
If I hadn't asked you out,
take a guess.
You don't understand. I see if you've seen everything.
Jing Yang is better for you than JA.
Because I haven't said anything to him.
But you're wrong.
Why?
I think I didn't ask you out, maybe you did.
Because I think I haven't really talked to him lately.
It's right that I neglected him.
Something was wrong.
But then I felt like we had dated twice.
It's better to ask someone else out.
Why is my brother so quiet?
What's the answer?
That's right.
What kind of co-pilot do you like?
I like to drive on my own.
This conversation.
If I'm out with my family or friends,
I don't need them to talk to me.
A lot of people prefer to sleep in the car.
They told me
you can sleep if you want to.
No, I won't be sleepy.
We chat for hours.
What kind of co-pilot do you like?
I like to drive alone on the highway.
I like the co-pilot who sleeps.
He said you can go to bed if you want.
Think about how he sang with Chocolate in the car.
I will.
But...
Who did you date with before?
The first time Cupid ordered us. The second time Kevin called me.
And the third time is now.
And I'm happy to meet Kevin.
Why are you happy to meet Vin?
I like him very much.
Really?
What do you like about him?
I feel that he's very loving
and warm.
Right.
At the New Year fireworks,
he hugged everyone.
I think
a very warm feeling
actually, the first day he came
he didn't even say a word
without saying a word, right?
That's right.
I'm not.
It was me.
He got to talk.
He's cute.
By this,
I may be anti-logic.
I felt like this person didn't say a word
and then I sat there.
He must be very talented.
He must be an amazing person.
Right.
He might not be able to
he might not be able to say it in person.
Yes, he should tell Kai at that time
they're all in this state right now.
They dare not say it in front of them.
They don't care when they're not.
But he wants to get in touch with Wang Zhen. Let's talk about him, right?
I'll divide the fish.
I didn't move these.
It doesn't matter.
So,
do your employees think you are a good boss?
Are you okay with your temper
do I think that's OK?
Do your parents think you are a good son?
This is a difficult question.
It's true.
Don't say that you know nothing.
Actually,
I hardly listen to my parents.
Mine is...
What life?
That day, I remember we chatted together.
I was also talking about
I said I read a book about that junior high school.
Do you know how to become a CEO?
I was in junior high school.
Old Wang.
It depends on how the CEO becomes in junior high.
You're really weird.
I don't know why. See?
We are watching Meteor Garden.
How many flowers have come out in my dream just now?
I don't know why I read this book.
When I was already talking about HP.
I was talking about Jack Welch,
they're talking about GM.
You're glowing now.
I suddenly see that
I think you look a bit like Bill Gates.
His head was laughing, you know?
Boss planted the seed in junior high school
he's like a brilliant old king.
We don't have much chemistry.
Right.
This.
Are we ready?
Is it fat or not?
Do you want to fly?
Are you taking me to fly?
Old Wang.
Tiramisu.
Tiramisu?
It's taking me with you.
That's why you matched.
Wang didn't reply.
This is a non-singing, happy and bland date.
But I don't think it is a date.
It's just
casual dating is light.
It's very...
If it's really 1
Wang is really driving on the highway.
For me,
he's willing to talk to others.
And he's willing to talk.
I had fun talking to him.
Right.
But maybe it's someone I think can be close friends with.
Come on.
This date is so unexpected.
So what's the surprise?
It seems that they don't have links in the game.
For example, many people who did exercise
or climbing a mountain
and did they not do hot air balloon later?
No.
Because Wang didn't do anything.
He asked me to fly with him.
Old Wang.
He took me away. He didn't pick up.
He didn't respond!
He has totally different reactions when he is with Qiao Wei.
It's totally different
they are so different.
They are all good at singing and listening to music.
Also,
wang Zhen was really evasive.
It's the first time I saw the copilot you like.
He said I like to drive alone.
Yes. They are usually sleeping.
He was clear
like the one who told Xu Li,
but he can clearly see that Wang Zhen has his sense of border.
Right.
So he pushed back.
Is not the type to hit the wall.
I also think
It's like a team building in the company. Two of our colleagues who are in a good relationship happened to meet a car.
But there was no spark.
There was no spark
that's really annoying.
Ah
let him give it a try.
Jia Jun won't be here anymore.
I think he's made a plan to get along.
What?
It's called writing.
How come he started a class himself?
I wrote these before.
Did you check my Moments yesterday?
Yes, I did.
I couldn't understand
Is an authentic work.
Whose genuine?
Only his own handwriting.
He called it an authentic work?
You scared me.
I only understand this.
These are all I can read.
I don't know.
I can't really read it.
Because it's cursive.
Right.
Cursive script. You can try it.
The characters are ugly.
You can write it to your brother with a hard pen
how about this?
It'll be uncomfortable at first.
And generally,
we can only move our wrists.
Right?
You can only move your wrist.
When you move your wrist,
you need to use your muscles to keep them down.
For normal people, there is a pulse here.
It beats.
So I usually hold my breath when I write.
Without breathing.
To breathe.
That way,
your hands won't shake.
So, you know?
I can hold my breath for a long time?
Is obtained by writing
not swimming.
Pilates is all about breathing.
Alright?
Actually,
with calligraphy, you can read a lot of people's emotions.
And his personality.
There is no need for this kind of study.
When we're practicing calligraphy,
you can have an idea of where it was in the past.
You have emotional pause. You can stretch it out.
Especially when you're writing this flute.
When I wrote this sentence,
I have almost finished.
Before I made a bold statement,
brought out a big breath.
It's getting angry again.
You heard that the rhythm of my breathing inspires everyone.
Almost there.
I'm sitting up straight.
I...
Has this novel
don't you think I'm a bit strict as a teacher?
Your tutor missed you a lot when you were a kid.
The picture is so oppressive. The dead memories attack me, right?
Alright.
That's it for calligraphy class.
It's finally over.
The class is over.
This is for you.
OK.
Thanks.
You can give that to me, right?
Guess if there's anyone in the living room?
No.
I think there should be.
You're back.
Hi.
We're back.
Where are you going?
These boots look so nice.
They are...
It's...
It's mine.
- It's mine! - My...
Not this? Which one?
This is version 1.
Version 2. I've hidden it.
Whose writing is so nice.
It's his.
His is so pretty.
Wow!
I wrote it before.
Chen Qiao Wei, let me see your handwriting.
I wrote this.
This is for him.
I wrote it for him.
Not for me.
We practiced calligraphy together.
Xu Li has had melons again.
Yes.
Alright, class is over.
Thank you. Class can begin.
Miss Mo.
For the next class,
thank you very much.
Old Wang.
See you later.
Qiao Wei. Bye.
Have a good time tonight.
Stand up.
Have a meal together.
No need.
I ate too much.
It's too much.
Say it here.
Do you want to go on the hot air balloon?
When shall we depart?
We're leaving?
- No. - 6: 00 p.m. That's right.
Come on.
Do you want to take a rest?
I will be fine soon.
Then you can go.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I've been reading lately.
This one.
I read this just now.
Yeah. Have you read it?
No, I haven't.
But aren't they famous?
You two
we talked about it yesterday.
It's a little hard
like that girl.
I really can't remember the name.
Names are. As long as they are related to names,
I can't help it.
Like Wang, that's easy to remember.
I know right away.
Were you supposed to be Wang and Li today?
They're all the workers' version.
This
what should Jia Jun do?
Read the books.
Got it?
That's great.
Jia Jun and the sofa are perfectly integrated.
Which position does it depend on?
Please.
They always happen to
you tied a knot by yourself.
So it's not good.
Maybe you can read it for me.
Don't move.
Don't force yourself.
Alright.
Thanks.
Come on.
I'll open the door for you.
You don't have to.
My boss, please get in the car.
You're welcome.
Don't mention it.
OK. OK.
Thank you.
I think it's a good timing.
Because I was calligraphy with him this afternoon.
He had dinner with another guy.
It's a perfect contrast process.
Because I'm not the same kind of person as his male guest.
It depends on who he likes.
To worry about him.
What do I worry about?
I'm worried that he won't choose me.
Jia has tried my best.
They've tried their best.
I'll treat Mr. Wang to a meal.
Don't.
I'll treat President Chen to a meal.
Let me do it.
Leave it to me.
Why won't you invite other bosses?
What?
I'll buy you a drink.
Alright.
Come here.
Do you want anything else?
That's enough.
You eat so little.
Delicious.
We can come again next time.
We can eat here secretly.
That's OK.
But you didn't do too many things.
- Return it. - I didn't do any of it.
I'm a well-behaved student, right?
That's too cute.
Such a good boy.
I see him smiling.
Strange laugh.
You're really cute too.
He was asking why
she smiled.
I'm used to that.
Is this the Lao Wang I know?
It's finally served.
Alright.
- Thank you. - This one is nice.
It's good to eat.
Come on.
Do you want a fork?
Not a knife, right?
Nothing.
I have teeth.
Really?
Great.
Is Fang Ye that amazing?
That's great!
Don't worry.
I'm stressed.
Back to you.
After the meal.
That's right.
How to eat this then?
No.
I don't see that high.
You don't have it, right?
It's alright.
I already have it.
Don't touch it.
I touched it.
Then you have to have another one of these.
It's OK if you don't want it.
It doesn't matter to me.
Really?
Or we can have half more.
I have. Do you want more?
I can.
Just wash your hands.
You're both stubborn.
Do you want to insist like this?
Yes, stubborn. He has some character flaw.
No choice.
Just a little please.
The food is magnificent.
How else to eat it?
There is no other way
I also eat bravely.
You don't seem that heroic anymore.
Alright.
Then I'm going to give it to you.
What's up?
I'll pass. No need.
That stubborn girl
half?
I've finished two-thirds of it.
I want the best for each other.
That's right.
Do you think I ate much?
Nothing.
Wasn't it just a shrimp?
I have no balance left for my jeans.
I'll buy them.
Really?
It's kind of romantic to joke about it with someone else
It's fun
try it.
Great.
This joke...
Yes.
What?
This is interesting.
They look mature.
And childish when they meet each other.
But I love it.
Me too. I'm so happy to watch it.
It's mine.
It's me.
The first one is
bring me the toilet paper.
And get Wei Zhenqi back.
Give it to me!
Give it to me.
And throw you away too.
Here you go.
Put it here.
You think I'm stupid?
Alright.
I'm just a fool.
Then I...
I laughed.
It was just a reaction.
Do you think I smiled too much?
That's not true.
That's all.
Because of you.
Because of you?
Right.
I don't think so.
Really?
My friends said that my face looks stinky.
I want to ask
It's mine.
It's...
It's me.
It's
I think it's good.
Then your boss
who's very old.
Students who are older than me
did you pay any tuition?
That's too many.
All the time.
If you don't have to pay the tuition,
what would you do with it?
To...
Our...
No fun at all.
I'm good at studying.
It's the easiest to do so.
Yes.
That's right.
When you can't do it, you ask the side and tell me what to do.
Can you take care of it for me?
Tell who?
Who is this?
A friend by my side.
I will
I'll ask a friend first.
If not,
find a way.
You can let your friend learn.
Right.
I also think that if you learn it, you won't be able to master it.
I'll let you learn next time.
It's mine.
It's mine!
I told you we were going to the amusement park.
Did I?
I passed, right?
I can't make it.
Why not?
I'll go back and post it on Moments.
We can go back after posting.
Who should read them for us?
Each other?
Let me show you.
Before this,
that close?
Wasn't it put into storage just now?
You brought me back to the courtyard and waited for more than 1,000 people.
No.
It was just now.
I'm going to adjust it back.
Sorry
what did I say just now?
No, it's not.
The situation now?
It's different.
We must make it in Beijing.
We can't lift it up.
Why? Linyuan...
This is it.
I guess the entrance to the playground is free.
Are you taking me to the park?
Are they free?
Maybe they won't let us go.
And run.
Just get in the car and drive.
Do you dare to do that?
It's
two three.
I'm going to play.
Hey...
How short you are.
When I was
that made you happy.
I'm so happy.
On a date when I saw
they were holding that kid in their arms.
You want to hit that?
You don't believe that?
When I was clipped by 9 legs,
his right elbow was straight.
It's amazing!
They have something down there to dig sand.
Come on.
Are you going to dig sand on the beach?
I don't know how to use
I...
- I will use sand. - Okay.
Then choose whatever you like.
Here, your pig.
My rake is so cool.
Pig rake?
This is the nine-tooth harrow.
Really?
That's right.
I'll give the weapon to you.
Tie it on your hand
you think Lao Wang has become childish?
They are really 3 years old.
A real date.
Be confident.
Speak louder.
A real date.
The last time I saw such a childish but also such an emotional story
was in Dao Ming Temple, you pig!
Which one gets you the most?
It's like the necklace part.
And then they throw fingers
eat each other's shrimp.
We have to let each other have the best.
And I have teeth.
You are really something
my face stinks.
Let me smell it.
Goodness.
Wow.
Various economic output frequently.
When I see these people
they don't even know what they're doing.
They must be so shy.
Right.
I think the two of them are completely in tune with each other.
They didn't realize it themselves.
Right.
You can become childish when you're with the one you love
but I think this kind of naivety is really expensive.
Very, very hard.
You created a new genre
It's called Flow.
A flow of emotions.
It suddenly occurred to me that the childish things you did with the one you loved in the play
about flow...
Which one?
Your Majesty, listen to me. I'm not at ease.
Your Majesty, listen to me.
My heart is still beating.
Then I will fall.
I'll take it.
This is how Erjia plays flow.
Wow.
Flow laid the foundation at that moment.
That school
tang Yixin's flow is good
so,
are you guys in a relationship like this?
Or just do some cute and brainless childish things with someone close to you?
Will it be
I don't think there's room for naivety.
He's too childish.
He used up his share, didn't he?
That's right.
For example, if our office keeps editing videos,
and I'm recording something.
He'll suddenly come here at 4: 00 or 5: 00...
He'll come with two kids and shoot you.
And then when you get off work
I can't do this.
I can do the most
you can do this.
That's right.
It's already promising.
Good love makes people smaller
and become a child.
That's right.
Mr. Du, what do you think of this round of dates?
I think I'm excited, too.
That's such a blessing.
It's a blessing to be childish
that would be a blessing.
We saw them talking nonsense during the date.
And doing all meaningless things.
But this is love.
When childish happens,
first of all, it's hard to
you will find that you have to be in the mood to be childish.
You're with many people.
You are not in the mood to be childish.
You also need to trust.
Do you believe that in front of this person
that's enough of your foolishness
remember your public embarrassment
he will surely catch your naivety.
And be childish with you.
If you meet someone who can be childish with you
to inspire your naivety.
Hold him tight.
It's so warm.
Mr. Du can at least have a moment like that
you can have a moment like that
become that childish
an unpolished version of yourself is valuable.
Right.
I...
And I was watching the playground.
I just feel like I really want to say one thing to a man who wants to be in a relationship
to take a girl to the playground.
Don't teach him calligraphy.
It's the contrast.
You just told me your ID number.
What you said to all men?
Mr. Lu is still preparing lessons at home.
Do you respect him?
By contrast,
the effect is so different.
But in fact,
If he likes Lu,
the calligraphy is different.
With new styles.
I think it's because they don't have chemistry.
We always say whatever you do with the right person may be right.
That's right.
Yes, that's right.
Yang. Yang?
There's no response.
He ignored me.
He took one look at me and left.
Who ignored you?
Yu Zhengyang!
I saw him
I shook my head back.
He probably didn't see me.
I'll check it out.
Gossiping about it for a bit.
You... I just told you to shake the shake.
Why did you just turn around and leave?
I didn't see anyone.
I heard someone telling me to have fun.
Today is an interesting day.
I have drawn two in my diary book
really, like those kids.
Can you show it to me sometime?
Alright.
You probably wouldn't be able to read it.
No, I won't.
That won't happen.
You can draw whatever you want.
Very unhappy.
What are you doing there?
I'm going to look after the house.
Really
really, why?
Because no chosen one looks after the house.
Really
It's true.
I fell asleep waiting for you yesterday.
Really?
Don't you see
you exercise like this?
Is there anyone who guards the house with you?
I don't know.
I didn't ask about Susu.
I did notice his state after he wasn't chosen.
I'll wait for your return.
But don't expect me to cook for you anymore.
Forget about my cooking.
You should be full.
Your words are so poignant.
I thought that's too much to ask.
I saw it on his face and I felt guilty.
In fact
I don't have any blame or anything.
Because everyone will have this opportunity to meet different people
I think he is kind and considerate.
An unspoken promise.
No worries.
His singing is different
It feels like the style is a little bit of the voice changer in your mouth.
She's my daughter.
We're off.
When there's a chance,
when you're in Hong Kong.
Come here.
I'll do it.
Make sure to
to this day,
you dated
old Wang, right?
Go beyond Wang,
and Jingyang, Jinyang,
there will be no pair.
And then
you're the third guy on a single date.
Is there a girl you want to know?
Maybe I am.
I think
however
It's not that easy for me
I'm not sure how to understand it, right?
Please one. You don't talk much.
The other didn't talk quickly at all.
Maybe I don't talk too much.
Many guys would think I was hard to get along with.
Mr. Xu,
that I...
Even when I said that.
You don't seem difficult to deal with.
Do you have any other appointments today?
No.
I...
I also think it's complicated.
Can anything be
there might be some things we didn't handle too well.
Racia,
If you don't want to answer,
no, it's not.
Lily and I are easy. He took good care of me on the first day.
So I was able to talk to him more.
But I don't know
I don't know if I said too much about my past.
I don't know if I gave him a little pressure.
Maybe everyone
when they get along with others.
Right.
Yes.
However,
I think it's okay.
You told him your own pace.
I'm a steady driver, right?
You're a great driver.
You're such a great driver.
I don't have
It's...
This is so scary.
Are you here to take the courage test?
I'm...
I...
Right.
Don't be afraid.
I'm ready to
why are you doing this?
It's so scary.
It can be done upside down?
It's a pure swing.
But it's always hanging when it swings.
I don't think I've seen it before.
But I only saw it.
My tears are ready.
I really regret it.
Let's go back.
I don't want to.
Come on.
It's alright.
It will pass very soon.
It will be over very soon.
They went up.
I'm scared.
Help
It's funny, my decorative painting.
Nothing.
It's alright.
Three seconds will pass very quickly.
That's so scary.
Did I really only have 3 seconds?
Just 3 seconds of the moment you fell,
I feel weightless for 3 seconds. That's quite a long time.
I think my legs can't move.
Kevin.
Fighting!
I'll leave now.
Hold on.
Come on.
Got to go.
I'll leave when he does.
This is scary.
Will it be ejected?
Oh.
But it turns on all of a sudden
and boom all of a sudden, right?
A rope goes down.
212.
What's the difference between a child and a bungee jump?
We can call at the designated area
this is for the
It should be the first one down. Instead, it will be better
because there's no feeling of weightlessness.
It's probably
It's kind of scary to go back halfway to the top
actually,
or want to give up.
I'm just afraid that
I don't do it now.
When I get old.
♪ Oh ♪
I could stand up. Fighting.
Alright.
Then we'll set out.
Great!
Alright.
Come on
you have to do it too
I'm trying so hard to open myself.
Not something I normally would do.
I hope I can keep this attitude.
To grow in this way.
And then
I think our date today meant a lot to both of us.
We both challenged ourselves
must be another memorable date in the hut for me.
Actually,
we were both a little afraid.
But we encouraged
after they finished,
we'll think we can be very good friends
because we had such an unforgettable experience
I think I'm the best.
Come on.
This is a friendship group.
This is an obvious friendship board.
Is there anyone out there that you've been dating and have a crush on?
Can I make a guess?
Yes, let me guess.
I think it's him.
I think it's Wang.
Very accurate.
Why?
That's because
that you don't talk a lot.
And then he could
to
to be embarrassed,
or
maybe I've guessed it right.
Got it right?
But I really got it right!
Then why didn't you ask her out today?
Because we...
First day of our date.
I have a date with him.
But I wasn't planning to have a date with him so soon.
Because I would...
I don't know what to say.
I think I've only seen the E side of him.
And I don't know how to unlock the love side of him.
So I don't want to date him alone right now.
That's right.
I'm the only one in the cabin who doesn't have any secrets.
Why do I write everything on my face?
I can guess right every time.
It's not that hard.
I know Wang a lot.
He is very interesting.
I also like him a lot.
Guys can say that,
but girls, you can't say you like him.
Why not?
So, do you really like him?
You disclosed other information,
you think he is feeling this?
You can see that?
Everyone should know.
You can see that.
Luckily, his Chinese is not that good.
I can't recognize these
Is it that other than the date with Lily,
you went surfing with Da Meng yesterday
how is the feeling
so happy.
It was really fun.
I just want to know what Lily thinks.
My feelings for Lily are probably...
She takes care of me.
I want to be good to her.
But I don't think I should say too much
I even put a little pressure on her.
Pressure?
Right now,
right now.
Maybe I had feelings for Da Meng as well.
Don't tell anyone.
I had a crush on you when I saw that curtain.
I said no.
I can't tell.
I didn't know.
I saw his eyes,
I thought
It seems that I do not feel the same as other girls.
Well, I... I don't know if I'm feeling something.
But this shouldn't be too funny.
They have become besties.
That's right.
Mr. Du is so similar.
Is there anything you want to know about Jia Rong?
I know whom she's good to.
Take the microphone.
Actually, we talked about that the other day.
This is the picture he showed us without beard.
Can I see you without beard?
OK.
Then I shaved it.
It was so obvious.
I want to ask you about
lili and Da Meng would be two different people if
as you want to know?
It's a good question indeed.
That's a good question.
I think it's better to watch more
really?
This is the Secret.
Others
my secret is that we are really good.
Then I can also tell you that
you know.
I don't...
Right.
It's mine.
The...
I didn't know who you went out with...
If no one invites you,
why would I think that's so lame?
That lame?
We're going to change the dating rules next.
We'll announce three different spots.
The quota is 4 people.
They can choose to date.
It's so unclear.
It's so confusing.
Wei will definitely choose sports.
Why should I choose?
Come on.
I thought it through.
Girls will choose the project,
and boys choose the players.
It's possible.
He may want to guess
the guy I want to meet
does the person prefer?
It's not that important
Is not that important to me.
Just be active for him.
Wow!
This Shura Field.
One described himself as a wolf.
When you're alone.
And then you talk to me
I'll revert to the dialect.
So you led me astray?
Have you had breakfast?
There is a kind of smile that you can't understand
I think there's a big smile on their faces.
I think the four of them get along so well.
Be special. We don't have to get love to lose it.
Join the discussion about half-close love on Weibo
share your views on love on Weibo.
(More exciting content)
On variety show on Sina Entertainment's Weibo.
Thanks to Weibo, the exclusive social media platform, for your great support.
Thanks to our chief partner media, Sina Entertainment Weibo Variety Show,
content cooperation platform Sina News, Netease News Zahniun
hold ac ousting.
We don't have to get light of losing
All it needs is just me and you
We don't have to scream out to proven we could keep it all whole up
Gsed I
keep it all throughout.
VIP users can update at 39PM on Tuesday and members can watch the show for a week first.
VIP users can watch the live show for an additional 7 hours in advance
I'll return to the club in a week for free, and exclusive to members of the reality show on Thursdays.
I'll watch half of the show with you on Friday
♪ Sweet without stop ♪