Ill justo say that I'LL
cause you know
you know
It's all right
how long did they have the longest relationship?
Ten years.
There're many reasons
there are many reasons
the most important thing is that we don't have the same goals.
I've been working long hours.
I don't have the time to accompany you.
Yes, I'm qualified.
So you still have a priority.
Rather than feeling,
maybe even now,
but I also changed a lot.
But if someone says that
he wants to spend his life with you,
you have to move to the United States
and become a wet nurse.
What would you be willing to do?
And then I will...
I will climb.
Just... Just didn't leave all of a sudden.
Leave Hong Kong for America or something.
Or I'll tell him
please
give me one year
If you give me one year.
I'll settle everything in Hong Kong.
And take the train to America.
So for my future family and the people I love,
Is either giving up my job
decreased the number of
In that case,
I want to ask
what if you find someone
what can we do
It's different timing
that's why I made a different decision.
Now I'm finding that
geography isn't a big problem for me.
So, what do you want to achieve in your career?
To be the hottest architect in Hong Kong.
I don't think it's a big goal. That's to be in Hong Kong,
not in the international,
the most famous
what about you?
What's your goal?
Me too.
I want all girls in the world to learn how to invest.
If I had a daughter,
If I had a daughter.
What about the boy?
Would you want him to learn that?
I, he is the most popular.
The hottest part is to be the most popular.
I think he's very direct
he's got his own ideas.
He's got dreams.
I don't know what's going to happen next,
but I felt comfortable being with him.
Right.
When I was talking to him yesterday,
I thought he really likes to joke around.
But when I saw him today,
I found that he was very serious
and polite.
And
she kept feeding me vegetables,
and crabs.
Or prawns.
I think he's
responsible.
A very nice man.
What's going on?
Put the takeout in this
I think we are the only ones
why did you pack up?
It seems not before you open the fridge.
It's full.
It's mine.
Is probably mine.
I forgot to bring it on.
I said that...
They should be mine.
They are mine!
Haha!
You're back.
Why is her hair so pretty?
Her hair was braided.
Your Highness.
Where were you?
We went riding.
Cool.
It's mine.
Such a move up
I'm not the one
of the app.
Of this app
It's too hard.
Do we think I'm older than you?
Me, me.
Me?
Right.
So you didn't miss any key information.
They'll bring us Guess.
♫ Still guessing ♫
Still guessing?
The order of the ages of the four boys.
Let me guess.
I'm very direct.
I'll be straightforward.
Eldest Brother.
Second brother.
Third and fourth brother.
Who will announce the correct answers?
I'm really born in the 1990s.
That's right.
Mine is 96.
It's true.
♫ The next life, come on ♫
Guess the girl.
That would be fair.
We can announce it.
Are you free now?
And make a wild guess.
We'll go home after that.
(House of Calligraphy) Eighteen.
Twenty-two.
Twenty-three.
Alright.
Who's the 23rd?
OK.
Hurry.
I can see that
you
you have a wicked
harbor evil intentions
you're always...
Throwing traps.
The
the...
We don't know the answer.
Enough.
I don't want to be hurt.
I think his eyes were filled with fear.
Fear.
I am afraid of being stabbed.
This is very dangerous.
It's not that big.
Of course, girls don't like it when guys talk about them.
Especially about their eyes.
One of them is rather bad.
Let me do this then.
You want to guess the youngest?
Second grade.
The second youngest.
The second youngest should be
the
It's...
Yes.
It's mine.
The...
I'm out of your order.
You can talk about your own ideas.
I agree with them. They said one two three in order.
I can
the answer can be known.
One is
to be my partner.
I asked mine to be 92.
About the same.
Around the same.
Nine three.
The biggest surprise was Lin Yi.
He may look young,
but his way of dealing with people makes you think that he must have
experienced?
I'm 89.
So,
I'm the oldest.
Not really.
The oldest.
How could you not...
I'm the 3rd.
You're older than me too.
Right.
I don't think I care that much.
Because I don't think 34 is that old.
But Kelvin immediately said I'm the oldest.
And Wang Zhen said I was the second oldest.
I was like, wow.
The two of them are so nice.
I was quite moved then.
Tomorrow night -- tomorrow, not the shopping first, right?
Four of us are going grocery shopping.
Right.
Who's going to cook and do the dishes tomorrow?
I can...
I can cook.
I can heat it up.
Coco.
We can be Kay.
Can we do that?
OK.
I think we can do it.
And then
they brought us here.
You brought them back?
Lobsters and crabs.
You guys brought so many things with you.
Make a guess.
Listen to him! Yes! Guess!
Do you think this is true?
Its name is lobster.
This dish is
It's a plate.
In the plate.
The
the...
It's
great.
So four of us went to watch it.
Tired?
It's fine.
It must be tiring to ride a horse
no, it's okay. It's supposed to be tiring
the more the SUV on the mountain road
Is one way up the mountain
this is very dangerous.
That's right.
It's dangerous.
There are mountains and cliffs.
Really.
Next to it is...
So...
I have
have gone to great lengths.
Beat it.
It's you.
With me.
It's a pity that I didn't take photos on the mountain top.
I forgot that I could take photos.
That move would be cool.
I should have a winning move.
They
the group's
team Human.
Moves.
For example, I do a move in the sky.
It is...
The...
My...
I will...
It's...
I...
0sep0 is fried rice
is fried rice
yellow eel
but it's not enough for eight people.
Buy some more if it's not enough for eight people.
Right.
I'll go to the supermarket tomorrow.
Let me ask you something.
What kind of food would you like?
Cuisine is...
Actually, I can just eat eggs.
Eggs do the right thing.
I'll buy 20 eggs.
Hard-boiled eggs.
Let's write down the dishes you can make.
Please tell us.
I can make paste.
For shrimp, shrimp, and egg,
then I'll make shrimp soup.
I think it's light.
Because we all eat.
I can make fish.
You know, steamed fish.
OK.
I can have the broccoli salad.
What else do you want to eat?
Then I will install another app.
I will come to see the dishes.
I can do it.
I think we are in charge of cooking today,
they will make the arrangement.
Because I think after today's arrangement,
we might have to think about the next few days.
It's very troublesome to think about it every day.
It would take a lot of time.
But we may not eat it every day.
Is there anything you want to eat?
Susu.
I want to eat shrimps with salt and pepper.
This is good.
We can make shrimps with salt and pepper.
Really
you can buy Pipi Shrimp.
Then I went to Xiaohongshu to search for salt and pepper
It's not that easy on the Internet
right.
It's kind of hard, isn't it?
It's the same.
It's great if we have the chance to go to a food stall together.
Can we fry it?
We can.
I...
Yes.
I want to have a try.
Let me have a try.
Alright?
I want to challenge you.
With your words,
I'll be the one
It's mine.
You are also little mice. Still having breakfast, aren't you?
You're hungry, too.
Give me bread and sausage if I order.
I have to skip the choice questions.
You really eat a lot every day.
I'm curious.
I'm going to play that beach game with you today.
Me.
♫ Break. Being abnormal ♫
You did it as abnormal and you imitated it.
That's right.
Why not be normal?
You played with each other in the first round.
But she stopped playing after that.
That's abnormal, right?
Right.
I already dated him once.
I can't choose others later.
Do you have to play with him until it's dark?
No, I'm just curious.
Don't you want to spend more time with your match partners?
Since you're not around,
you'll go on a date again.
I think we all have different ideas.
Some of us want to know more about the same person.
For some, I'd like to know more about them
before making a choice.
Or to feel
so,
do you chat with someone after playing the game?
They always play with the same person.
Do they chat or not?
Talk about how much
what else can we talk about?
I'm really squirting water.
Is it obvious that I choose one person every day?
Obviously.
I think you can be happy and know more about everyone.
On day 3,
If I had intended to do it,
I would still choose the same person.
Do you think Hong Yan is the one you know for sure?
But I'm the kind of guy who
that
you won't have any ideas
you won't have any ideas later.
I think the male guests in the hut were all excellent.
Because they were well-intentioned.
They are those who are willing to make you happy.
Not all of his intentions are right, okay?
I know that
there will be an experiment for Kendo, right?
You have to get in touch with them
you will know if he is suitable or not.
Here's what I think.
I think everyone has different ideas.
I just want to give them a chance
Is to make each other think there is a more suitable one.
So,
you are the passive one being chosen.
I don't think that's a good idea.
I don't think I was chosen.
I will give my signal.
But if he receives it,
or it's too
the feedback,
because they give you the feedback,
then you'll be willing to try it out.
Right.
But if I give the signal,
and she's not thinking it through.
I hope you can try it
give it a try
and then...
Right?
Got it.
I'm who I am.
I choose the one I want to know
that I want to get to know
then I won't change much.
I'll check out the fitness equipment.
I haven't checked them carefully.
That way.
This is the ball.
And some dumbbells from Jane.
The
the...
one leg bends.
Then straighten one leg.
Do you need this blanket?
It's not necessary.
No need.
Are you sure about this? Or do you teach me to use it?
There's no stretching at all.
To relax your spine, right?
You want to do that?
You don't need to do that.
You just need to know that you can do it.
I don't need to show you.
Alright.
Just the long skirt.
Keep your feet apart.
The same width as yours.
Put your hands behind your head.
Do a triangle.
And hold yourself.
Crossed your fingers.
Intersect.
Then place your thumb at this position.
And then slowly move your spine along this arc
and then close to
the lower legs.
Your thighs.
That's not the place to open your legs.
Stretch them out in this position.
What's the brake?
Then
lie down slowly.
Right.
And then breathe out.
And then get up.
Then,
against the edge of the bucket.
There's the power to push.
And then the hand and the eye look here
every push and pull.
It seems the power here
I'll take you here.
And then
hold your hand to your head.
Look at your eyes and stretch your fingers.
Breathe in.
And exhale and pass the middle.
And...
Your right hand is going to move.
Pass the bronze crown.
Copper?
These are barrels.
The copper top.
Then draw a fan to the opposite side.
And draw a circle.
Pass it through your armpit.
Same on the bed. Yes. Again.
Inhale through the top of your head
and then to the side.
The power to push it
stretch it out.
And then this rustic
oK.
After the middle
open your hands.
And fall gracefully.
End.
Am I elegant?
Is it OK?
Feels so good.
I think I can dance better now.
Your hands.
What do you mean by this?
Are you picking on me like this? Now?
What does that mean?
Don't come near me.
Did you learn this?
You want to know?
You're so hard to understand.
I just don't know where to put my hands.
Naturally moving is heavy.
Put your hands behind your back.
Got long hands.
It should be better in the back.
We could take it back to basics
baby
we control the sun
we could make it with the neighbors
but baby
let's be quiet now reach out
pulled out on the FA
We don't have to get so theatrical
you know
even simple can be special
We don't have to get love to lose it
All we need is just me and you
We don't have to scream out to prove we could keep it all acoustic
Keep all
let me seethe real you
takeoff your
I me to the naked truth
Until we're both unp complicated cause all the things we want IDO so much better when we're like
deep it