Take off your hair.
To control oil and prevent hair loss, use Yang Yuanqing.
This program is sponsored by Yang Yuanqing.
I've been dreaming of the television
I think everyone is sincere
very sincere
nothing like some baggage that you have at a certain age or something.
I think this
and the festival
to spend more time with her.
I really enjoy this atmosphere.
The rule of a second date.
Every guy has one chance to knock on the door and ask a girl.
Do you want to come with me tomorrow?
Very good. Accepted.
Am I late?
Hello.
The weather will be fine tomorrow.
We're going out again.
She is doomed.
Susu heard it?
My goodness.
I become a waiting
I feel like a child who has made mistakes.
Who doesn't know what to do at the moment.
Who didn't know how to refuse.
He's crying.
Qiao Wei is crying?
I just to that
I'm you know.
Welcome to the third season of Half Mature Love Show made by WeTV.
I'm Xie Nan, an islander on the half-cooked island.
Half of the island's residents.
Miss Su Juan. Welcome.
Thank you all.
Our Lip Leaf, Tang Yixin
hello.
And lovely Jingjing.
Today, we have a new comer on the island.
We're going to welcome to the handsome and full of talent.
You must be sweating.
Pang Bo was like this in the last season.
I was often bullied by other girls.
He felt so nervous
thank you to the program.
Thank you all.
Hi, everyone.
I'm Pang Bo.
This is so painful.
I'm so happy.
Alright.
We also want to welcome another lovely new islander, Cai Wenjing from Quan Tang.
You got off to a good start.
Because the roles are basically sweet.
That's right.
In character, I can experience
the pleasure of falling in love.
But the main reason is I love watching Mr. Romance.
And I love watching them when they're getting massages.
And when you're bored,
they all have a screen nowadays.
You're so sensitive.
Is this
and the technician said
I also think he's such a good guy.
And then it's so happy, so happy.
I'm very healing.
In that case,
I have to ask
you watched our previous two episodes?
Yes, we watched.
Do you have an impression with anyone or couples?
This line I like Zhang Junning.
I'm kvi.
That makes people feel comfortable.
And then he's clear.
And the girl who chose her in the previous episode
this Xu Li...
I think she's a good person.
I also like her.
It's very generous.
Are the rest of our friends impressed by the first two episodes?
I felt sorry for Qiao Wei's tear
she couldn't bear to say no to others
I was very curious and said
he'll be dating Wang Zhen now.
The ending will be?
I think this is a mystery
there's another suspense is Susu Yes
we were worried about the girl
that girl felt like she was very broken.
We just hope she can find a nice boy to treat her well.
I think this is also this season I want to see if there is any progress
because we have a new guest coming.
Right away. She's going on a date with Susu.
So we don't know who the guy is.
Let's hurry up then.
Because a new day begins on the island.
They will start different styles of dating.
Let's get close to them.
Let's watch together.
It starts.
My... my...
The food for him
I'll make it for you tomorrow.
Don't worry.
If I had asked you to cook
to cook?
It's good to cook.
Hello.
Are you going with Wang today?
Not Jiarong.
Mother.
Who are you?
I don't have anyone.
Oh...
Really?
Just teasing you.
Was teasing you.
But it's really not.
But that's not what you said.
I want to invite you
I wanna tell you a secret.
No one knows yet.
Lily knows about it.
Then tell me.
A male guest
who came to the hut said
you are really surprised?
I don't believe you.
Now I really don't believe you.
Are you not sincere?
Because you just lied to me?
You lied to me?
I'll listen to your opinions.
This is the plot of an idol drama.
What I said just now is that the new male guest is very real, very real.
I don't know who it is.
I am the new guest that will move in.
To date each other first.
I want to ask you out.
Well, if you have a new male guest,
so happy.
Anyway, you just don't know
I think
he's a man.
He must be very handsome.
The kind
look forward to it.
He should come back to meet you guys tonight.
Alright.
I'm really looking forward to your coming back tonight.
I'm a little...
Come on.
You're happy now.
I really think Susu's condition has changed.
After this invitation,
she's getting closer now.
It's almost time. I'll make you breakfast.
Thanks. Thanks.
None of us are worried about Li.
If Xiao Ma and Lin Yu are going...
Conversation One, where's Wang?
Good question.
Were you alone at home?
Then you didn't knock at my door yesterday.
Hey.
Ladies, welcome to join our group. What are you talking about?
Did Wang hurt you?
No.
No, really.
Right.
No.
Really didn't kill me?
Is there a new female guest?
Airport?
Break up affectionate couples
It's because
wang wanted to knock at your door.
Trying to break my door.
Why did you think so fast?
None of them are. Wang asked Wei out.
But they've never guessed
what is the mystery?
To find out the mystery.
What are you going to do today?
I want to be myself today.
Wang suddenly gets a lot of confused eyes
but I feel that
he is searching me today.
I think Wang is...
There's a possibility.
First of all,
lao Wang didn't knock at my door yesterday.
He might want to knock at your door first.
There's no time
he didn't ask anyone to
maybe he didn't have anyone.
Because Wang Heping and others didn't play any role for you.
The role was...
Think too much.
Did she make the appointment?
They are happy about it.
They would rather believe that they didn't knock at anyone's door,
than that they knocked on Wei's door.
Stop guessing.
It's so straightforward to ask.
Very straightforward.
You've really changed.
Obviously, he expected more interaction with Wang Zhen.
Now he bravely goes to ask
with whom?
I think it's good.
It's good.
I like this, too.
I can adjust myself quickly.
Where will you go today?
I don't know.
You don't know
you said you would be yourself.
You don't know.
You're right.
Where to be yourself?
What do you want to ask?
I can tell you
now you're a difficult problem for us.
Difficult problem
you're a point in our regiment
what difficulty?
What?
I had an appointment with
all of them
very surprised.
I always thought Wang Zhen knocked on Lingyi's door yesterday.
But I didn't think so this morning.
Which really surprised me.
Our calculation was wrong?
We got the word wrong.
So many unknown things?
I can tell him without telling me.
Tell him?
I wanted to tell you
but Susu told me not to tell you.
Go ahead then.
Susu is dating a new boy.
Is it a newcomer?
I don't see any new arrivals.
So I brought you some tonight.
I'll check it for you.
Alright.
OK.
I'll go to my room.
And the sunscreen.
Right.
Sun protection.
There you go.
What are you doing?
I'm washing the quilt.
The quilt, the sheets?
The sheets.
What are you doing?
Let me see if I have anything to eat. I think I'll leave right away.
Right.
Maybe you can make something simple, eat more fruit.
Do you know what you're doing today?
Do you have any plans this afternoon?
Nothing special.
Come with me.
I can't finish them all.
You suddenly look like me.
One forgets his name
an Yixuan.
An Yixuan like you?
A little bit.
Your hairstyle...
My hairstyle is alike?
That's not it.
You can be like anyone.
You can say that I'm like Shu Qi.
My...
It's mine.
It's...
Sorry
sorry
he said
his hair covers his face.
He can look like anyone.
You have his hair.
You said your hair looks like her.
What's with her hair?
That's
she said I was like a Taiwanese actress.
Right.
That's spraying.
Spraying mosquitoes.
Right.
I'll take mosquito repellent.
It
It is easy to be bitten.
It's easy to be bitten
you only know me.
I wear pants
eat.
I've eaten the Lian and the orange.
Two fruits.
She
I'm off now.
-Bye bye! -Bye now!
It's
our...
Disappointed.
He's not here today.
Right.
She is alone.
She's dating the rest.
Get in the car
thank you.
He has a great personality.
I'd like to know
he did tell me that he's a little stressed.
I hope today is not so stressful
no pressure.
Just make us happy.
I want to know more about you.
More chat
and more feelings for each other.
I think I'll be happy to talk about it.
Such a huge
this huge and beautiful place is mine.
Right.
It's beautiful.
Come on
when I was waiting to knock on the door at night,
when I was waiting for the door.
I received a male guest who just entered the hut
who just entered the hut.
I was really panicked.
I don't know what criteria he used to make this person.
Is this my Moments?
But I obviously post the same person every day.
I think you won't think about asking me out.
My name is Yu Jingyang.
I'm from Beijing.
I'm 29 years old.
I'm a fitness instructor.
I like music.
I play the zither in my spare time.
I can make handmade leather goods.
They know about music
I can keep fit.
I'm free to control my life and work.
I'm very happy.
Love is different from other emotions.
It's very intense
you can't control your emotions.
Life will be better
your life will be better.
I think she's a must.
What kind of boy is she?
Hahaha.
She's so cute.
Susu!
It's me.
This is Yu Yang.
Just call me.
Hello.
My name is Susu.
You can also call me Su Hua.
Alright.
-Here you are. -Thank you.
Thanks.
Have you arrived for long?
No.
I just arrived for a while.
Sunglasses are good on him.
You don't look the same as you look in the photos.
But in fact, Yu Jingyang has watched Susu in there for a while
remember that?
He has his reason to choose Susu.
Must be something.
Will meet in reality.
Really?
Just the photo. P trace. Not really.
This is the original.
Probably the original.
Would look better.
I'm very curious about
what you did yesterday.
How did you choose today's date?
The photo.
And to me,
the feeling you give me
that's why I'm attracted to you
and then...
We ate.
A girl in white sitting in the corner
with long hair
he kept eating in the corner
she was very quiet.
And then she was a very beautiful girl.
I want to know more about her.
To communicate with her,
or one-on-one.
Like a one-on-one meeting.
They said there's a nice prize board game that's fun.
We can try it later. Great.
Come on.
Let's do something while we're there.
It's beautiful.
It's mine.
It's...
It's safe.
So put on the life jackets first, okay?
Put it on and zip it up.
Alright.
I have no strength. Come on. Help me move a little forward.
The belt down there should be
I'll pull forward
okay then
so they can
you can hold the cabinet in this kneeling position.
We can stand up.
It's a little hard.
Alright.
We can set out now.
Here we go!
This feels so hard.
I'm so panicking.
It's...
Very stable.
It should be fine.
Watch them.
Look how steady they are just now.
And no one fell off.
The goal today is that I fall.
We're fighting.
Come on, we can go!
We won't be the first fish.
Right.
Let's go that way.
You need to roll up your pants a little more.
Come on, give me your feet.
They're right in your position, right?
Right.
The female guest to sign.
Hold on.
Let me help him up.
It's fine.
Kneel down.
Kneel down and sit.
Yeah, you can sit.
It's up to me.
From this side
I have drifted far away.
Keep it steady.
Sure, please.
In the middle.
Which part do you use harder?
I...
It's so hard to walk on my side
should we follow the same frequency?
Alright.
We can wait.
Be slow.
Like this. Slowly.
Just a little slower. It's okay.
Alright.
Lie on your back.
That way, it'll be more comfortable
they match ours.
You skated well.
I think we're on the same frequency now.
Almost the same.
So, your direction is right. Take a break.
I think he went to the left.
I can't think of anything, right?
Alright.
Introduce the scenery.
Have you seen the rainbow?
It's very nice.
This is the rainbow.
What are these?
The seven auspicious clouds?
We see such auspicious clouds.
Do you see the heart in the middle?
That seems to be real.
It's true.
Is the bottom one like those colorful clouds?
It's really one.
This isn't the end.
Is it such an obvious sign?
That the right person is coming.
Under your feet is the colorful light rain
you can't see it when you just slide here.
The successful completion of
come on
be careful
It's not easy to trip.
Will you feel the sun?
Not really.
We are trying to guess what the new male guest is like.
You know that there will be new male guests, right?
I told them that
the way we chose our date yesterday was that the male guest could knock on the girl's door
alright.
But I contacted you last night.
What's your reaction
what were your feelings and reactions?
My first reaction was ha...
Why me?
I don't want to date alone.
Because I'm the one
love the most right now.
Are you your lover too?
Right.
What... What do you love?
Infg then.
That's exactly the same.
Exactly the same. Right.
That's why I don't want to say
on a date.
We haven't met yet.
But in fact, it feels like it's okay to see each other.
No, not so... We are both infg
how are you going to describe me to them after we go back?
The tall and handsome Xing Da.
I'll be stressed.
Normal people.
Ordinary people?
Through understanding
through communication,
I found that her thoughts and character expression
I think she is a little like me
she felt like a real girl
should we go back?
Should we walk backwards? It's too hot.
Isn't it fun to walk backwards?
I miss the old people who exercise in the morning, right?
Why don't you
you walk in reverse.
I'll do this.
They're on the same page.
Very comfortable.
Yu Jingyang has a great balance to their sync.
A little more to your side.
Right.
More of it.
He doesn't know.
No. It's so romantic.
That small detail is quite moving.
She can take care of people.
I think watching the sea
you can feel healing.
She's very quiet.
Wow!
I can't.
I'm tired.
I can't walk anymore.
I happen to have
there's a stall.
Alright,
I'll take your seat.
What's your type of guy?
No questions.
I've already answered them.
What? I didn't hear you once.
Alright.
I like that.
Humorous,
smart,
and a sense of borders.
Pretty much.
Nice to meet you.
The concrete...
Get over it. Come on.
Is it cold?
No, it's not.
The weather is perfect.
Later. Let's go.
Come on.
This feels good.
You can sit anywhere you want.
Then you can sit here.
Wang Yi,
I'll sit here.
Then please.
This is the dinner he arranged.
Let's have the barbecue first.
Let me do it.
Place all the dishes you want.
OK, I'll listen to you.
He always asks Susu to choose first.
He's very good.
I know nothing about cooking.
If you have any brilliant ideas,
let me know.
The squid is ready.
And the shrimp is delicious.
I'll roast them. Eat first.
The meat will get bigger.
The shrimps will be fine.
Alright.
Do you like shrimp?
You can have another one.
My... my prawns are relatively normal.
Have another one.
It suits Susu well.
I have a curious question.
If you get to the cabin,
and then
you're gonna be like, every girl needs some space
to get to know each other.
And get along with each other.
Then we can find ourselves.
I roughly understand what you mean.
Yes, you do.
You miss your friend.
Alright.
I'm a person who is actually
and then
In the beginning,
I might be a little scared.
Take a rest.
Have some drinks.
(We're showing the attributes of lovers.)
But will it embarrass you?
I don't...
It's comfortable.
Me too.
Did the eight of you enter the hut together?
There's another exam session ahead.
Let me recall the questions in the test.
Let me ask you something.
Alright.
Can you be friends with your ex?
This is also very important to Susu.
Former.
Former?
It's a multiple choice question.
I can or can't.
I think I can't.
Why should it be like the good ex has disappeared
the right ex
the former you mentioned before.
We said we wouldn't bother each other.
We will start a new life together.
What about you?
What was your response?
Take a guess.
I can't.
It can.
Are wrong.
There is a third option.
Why don't you tell me?
I didn't choose the third option originally.
But I chose both.
It depends on the circumstances.
I'll think about what else...
Stop thinking about it.
This can't take you.
They didn't want to go through the exam again.
We are all afraid of the exam.
Hold on.
For my exam paper,
I took pictures of you in my phone. No, no, don't let you stop working.
Then I came to the cabin
nothing more.
You are right then.
I think you want to repeat what you have suffered.
Do you mean that
look, look. You've got her.
Pick a simple one.
I'll take it from you.
Tell me first. Are you older or younger than me?
I don't know.
She's younger than me.
I followed your advice.
I'll choose some simple questions.
Since you're older than me,
then I'll...
I don't think it's polite to ask this.
How old you are.
I don't know your age.
I was impolite, you know.
Separate?
Let's have a drink first.
You said I was impolite.
No. Let me choose one more.
It's not that I'm talking about me.
Because I didn't know
you
I want to ask you.
I was being impolite.
Or do you want to know? Are you implying that I was impolite?
No, that's not what I meant.
No...
We just flipped it upside down.
We can't hold up our fork.
Is hard to do.
She is here.
Do you think that loving someone means you will give her all without reservation?
Yes or no?
No, it's not.
Let's see what I chose.
Your choice is...
No, I mean...
Tell me why you chose No.
Because I think
love is not an open thing.
Well
also, healthy love must first love oneself before having the ability to love others.
You know how to love yourself,
so you can love others in a better way.
That's the way.
It must be a way that they want,
and willing to accept it.
If you love each other too much,
first, we can give each other pressure.
And on the other hand, you might lose yourself sometimes.
So I think love is when I love someone
and then I'm willing to give something back.
You don't expect anything in return for this.
That's, I love you.
That's why I'm doing this.
I don't want you to love me.
But because I wanted you to.
Right.
So, when you put in a lot of effort into it
there's already some emotion in your effort.
Once it's accumulated,
when you're not realizing his feedback,
I think it can create conflicts.
I like that.
Cai Wenjing.
She loved another girl.
Let Cai Wenjing come in.
That's right.
Do you still want to answer the questions?
Go on.
I think it's fun.
You were reluctant just now.
And now I'm having fun.
I think you're enjoying my reaction.
Well
he asks some interesting questions.
And then
and when he remembered the answer,
he was looking for the exam on his phone.
He looked for the exam papers
and then
he suddenly wanted to ask some questions
he starts laughing and laughing.
He's very dramatic inside.
I think so.
These?
I think they're all cute.
I think Susu is so charming in front of him
right.
He feels so relaxed even when I'm filming him.
Let's go then.
I'm going to drink it up.
You even turned it off, I didn't come here.
Nice to meet you.
I've met Wu.
If Wu finds out, we'll go back together.
I won't go back today.
I can't take you back to the cabin with me today.
Do you want to take me to the cabin with you?
No. Alright.
See you at the cabin.
Yao.
Is falling in love.
In terms of meeting him,
I think I'd feel more comfortable with Susu today
more willing to go on and get to know her?
After dealing with him one day,
I think Yang Yang
very thin boy.
Yang Yang was very proud.
Why did you bring tissue with you?
That I don't bring
I wouldn't even bring that with me.
I eat shrimps.
I'm not that particular about it.
I would peel prawns with my hands when I was hungry.
He also took a glove
let me put on gloves before eating shrimp.
Very meticulous.
With all the details.
I think today's date was more relaxing and natural than I expected.
The date?
Think about it.
In a proper relationship,
the other person will see the uniqueness of Susu.
And then
susu is in such a relationship.
She also brings out the best in her lover.
The details that this boy Yu Jingyang took care of.
When they were taken care of.
He saw it all.
And feel it.
That's right.
Right.
And he has a thing
Is very special.
You grilled prawns for him.
And when he gives it to him,
he said this.
He said this is for you
I might be a prawn.
You know, it's just like the one where parents gave their children dinner together
mom and dad are not hungry when you eat
yeah, I won't make it hard for others to accept.
That's natural.
It made me feel very comfortable as a whole.
And then it's very thin.
Yu Jingyang, who we all think is meticulous,
when he joined us,
what do you think of the little girl
the change in our relationship
he may create some competition,
and a sense of crisis.
Because the number of people will be different.
Right?
Right now, right?
You have five boys
there are four girls.
I think boys will naturally have a sense of competition.
Right.
Especially Wang Zhen.
Because Wang Zhen has the most complicated emotions.
He knew that Susu had feelings for him.
But he didn't respond.
But Susu is getting along well with her friend today.
It might inspire him
have I missed out on a wedding or something?
And I really appreciate
I really admire his answer.
About giving.
I think his view on love is very good.
Right.
Love yourself before being able to love others.
There is no such thing as giving or not giving. This is a very mature expression.
And you look pretty
and got your certification from Cai Wen Ji.
I think she has a good overall score.
I love him.
It's you or not.
Sorry
sorry. It's the first time I didn't do this.
Since everyone has such a good impression of Jinyang,
his emotional output earlier.
He promised.
Your ex...
Should have disappeared.
That's right.
Yes. Do you agree or disagree?
I don't agree with you.
But lately, I always think
no matter it's the ex
that you don't like,
life is fluid.
A person you used to hate
that you hated many things.
But after 10 years,
may have changed him
he became a gentle person.
Maybe everyone can just re-accept
and meet again in the underworld.
For example,
If my other half
that I'm not interested
I won't insist on asking for her.
You will disappear from your life.
You could classify it as an ordinary person.
But after many years,
we can get to know him together.
I think a lot of things can fade away after a long enough time.
Staying here is a good experience for you.
What I feel is that
Is this a demand on yourself
or a demand you have on each other?
I think if we're mature to deal with relationships,
this is more about our own requirements.
Since we've already made a decision
to split up,
as long as there's no other connection?
You... You have so many troubles in your life.
Do you have to trouble this man?
Is it that lacking of friends?
You should be friends with your ex.
Don't put yourself and each other in trouble.
That's right.
There's a very important point about this.
In fact, what Pang Bo said is right.
It's not that our ex should disappear,
but whether we have the ability to make them disappear.
Even if her ex disappears,
we often see things in life.
You still hate her?
Feel regret.
You even compared him with your current boyfriend.
That's right.
Then
even if your ex is gone,
he's still there, mentally and emotionally.
So,
If you have the ability to make him disappear,
It's not the same thing
those are two different things.
Right.
There are many times
what we lack is this ability.
Right.
Would be the best thing to do
If you end up in a relationship.
A feeling when your ex isn't gone
what is it?
That after an unpleasant experience with his ex,
he came to a conclusion.
He would graft it into our relationship.
From my point of view,
It's also a sign that the ex hasn't disappeared,
because I'm in a new relationship.
To see the new me from a new perspective.
But then because I was different from his predecessor,
I hope that he
who was fair to me before.
With their new eyes. The date between Susu and Jinyang.
Besides the fact that
he's very good at creating a relaxed atmosphere
and considerate.
Susu also showed a very different side.
He may be more lively than in the hut.
I'm also looking forward to the changes
to change our relationship with the guests.
What about today?
Two more couples have dates today.
Let's continue watching it together.
Come on.
The potato.
The horse or...
Come on.
This is for you.
Maha!
Is so silly that it's too hard to write.
You can open and have a look.
But I see that you've already bought the glasses.
Right?
I asked Tao to go with me.
That's for you.
I saw him go out to buy something this morning.
And then he opened a glass when he brought it in.
And I nudged him
because I got him a cup too.
I think he went out and bought them himself.
It seemed to repeat what I gave her.
But I didn't expect that she bought it for me.
This is fruit tea.
Use green tea as the base
then add honey and orange.
He said he liked green tea.
Using green tea as a base
then add some fruits,
and honey water,
to make it healthier.
Wow.
They didn't seem to be dating.
Like they had a fight.
I'll help you.
Lower your head.
It's too sweet of a joke.
I think it's OK.
That's OK.
Suddenly want to buy me a cup.
You might like to work out.
I heard you brought some protein powder.
The protein powder
It needs to be water soluble.
Stir.
I've really thought a lot about you.
It's been very detailed.
I've tried my best.
But I don't think I'm as good
the
we went there.
I think it's yours.
But this is...
He gave me a surprise today.
He knows that I like chocolate.
But I didn't expect that this cocoa orchard can have chocolate here.
It never occurred to me that many of them...
What others say is meaningful to him.
Have a seat.
These are
Is a material for making chocolate.
The cocoa fruit and beans.
Carrying it with one hand.
You can hit it from the middle with a wooden stick.
Crack it
open with your bare hands.
Be careful with it.
Watch out.
I hit your hand.
It's
you are really something
I'll catch him
he said
look there.
I think what Pang Bo said would be very helpful
will be a plus to me.
Right?
It's like a guy's humor.
But I can't.
Who's more funny?
All we are doing is peeling the beans.
How many beans does it take to peel a whole cup?
Thank you in advance.
After all, this is
this is just a dilemma.
I'm not good at things.
I'll always look for automated
or ready-made
you know, the kind
he's mine.
Beautiful.
I'll broadcast it.
It won't take long.
Please don't.
I don't want you to be the only one doing it.
You mean you're in charge of beauty?
I'll broadcast it.
It's mine.
If I don't have
you're impatient.
I'll surely find something fast.
Sorry, I have no patience.
Yes.
I'm happy to be praised by you.
From the smartest person in the world.
I didn't expect this...
I didn't expect this much.
You're more honest
you're honest.
I'm really
pretty good.
Skin care.
You're so smart.
Very clever.
I've added sugar with it.
I only added a little.
I don't think you like to eat a lot of sugar.
So you don't like sweet food?
You like sweet food
but considering that you don't like sweet,
they have good memories.
Because he doesn't like sweet
actually,
If it were me,
I'll put in at least half of the candy.
I was afraid he wouldn't put any sugar in it.
So I almost didn't add any sugar
start the power
It's like an experiment, you know.
For our previous experiments, we needed to grind the particles into powder.
Then...
Do you want to grind it by hand?
Yes, it is.
Hand grinding?
Because of some chemicals
It's very thick
It has very large particles.
It cannot be dissolved directly.
It dissolves very slowly.
We have to grind it to a powder. The surface area of the contact surface
and grind it in the same way.
Right.
Sharpen it like this.
Just use this.
This is actually the one that sharpens medicines.
They're really professional in scientific research.
I'm tired. Rest.
It's indeed heavy to begin with.
Let's see how fine you can grind it.
The biceps muscles work like crazy.
They are usually mashed before grinding.
Yours is more interesting
the...
It is a test
so you're going to the gym?
Right?
It's...
It's weird.
It's weird?
You know?
Hurry up.
I'm so weak.
I crossed the line.
So ruthless.
It's me.
It's...
My melons are precious.
It's comfortable.
Use a little bit.
With a little bit. Harder.
Don't.
Don't force too hard.
Yes, of course. Can I?
Look at my shoulders.
Really.
You're starting to want to speed up.
It's mine.
I'll put this in the fridge now.
What about
It's too much work.
It's fine.
Actually, I think it's okay.
When I did the experiment,
how much longer is it?
Usually when I did the experiments before,
I would do sludge digestion.
It takes one or several days
a day or several days.
To stay in one place?
I'll stay in the lab during the day
and then go back at night.
And I have to be there the next day.
For a long time.
I need to pay close attention to his
you should always look at it. It's like the stone is melted into water.
Think about this.
And see what's in it.
That's right.
We need to see how it melts.
That's a plus.
Because I'm not a doctor.
I want to communicate more with him and top students.
I don't understand anything about his major.
So I'm curious about his learning journey.
At the end of the day.
We're going home.
We...
I'm not feeling well.
What?
What's the problem now?
I'm dizzy.
A bit dizzy.
Then I...
Just give me a break.
What's up
are you hurt?
I don't feel well.
I might also have motion sickness or hypoglycemia all combined.
Take a rest then.
I'll take a rest first.
Hey!
It's...
He's lively.
I'm partly responsible for his condition.
It's not only because of hypoglycemia,
but also because he drove too fast
he got motion sickness.
This is the reason
I'm kind of...
It's mine.
I'll get you some warm honey water.
Taste it for me.
Just a little.
Let's cook something
to grab a bite.
For the food you made.
I want to eat ramen when I get back.
Here comes the food.
I'm coming in.
I brought you something to eat.
Would you like to eat something?
First.
Thinking about dad's noodles.
Having a bite of noodles
just a bite.
First, the food will adjust
the taste.
Just put it here.
-I will. -Okay.
Come on, you need to go alone.
I'll stay with you for a while. It's okay.
You can leave now.
Can you really do it?
I still want to thank him.
He kept asking if he needed me to stay with you.
And I didn't want to be so miserable.
You could see me and say no.
But I'm happy.
His Majesty.
Lao Ma is also very real.
For the third consecutive year
never love it
such as
I'm coming in.
I'll buy you some medicine.
I'll get motion sickness
and motion sickness.
After that,
drink this.
Is a little disgusting.
But a little bitter.
Drink more water.
You've eaten your food
and medicine.
Everything will be fine.
Yi Han. You will be fine soon.
You can just...
Have a good rest.
Then I won't bother you.
Take a rest first.
Is he too bored?
Take it down.
Take a rest then.
Then, I want to ask you,
what you told me last night,
actually,
can you feel...
You feel that
did I put a little pressure on you?
It was Jiang who asked him directly.
And other people.
They all miss us.
With each other.
Right.
Or an event,
we do it together.
You think it's not good?
Right.
Yesterday it was because...
Because I, I thought about this too.
Today is the fourth day.
We are together.
And then
maybe every activity is just the two of us together
It's about the experience.
It's very...
I...
I want to be in a team with K.
I'll go with him.
It's unnecessary for others to think like me.
I think so too.
I don't want you to blame him for thinking about it
and you blame me on him?
Because I noticed that you didn't talk much.
And people think that we
we really love someone
but... But we just
It doesn't take long to know each other.
That's right.
No need.
No pressure.
Right.
I'm a slow person.
I wanted to keep a distance.
He must take care of me so much that
that's good.
They think the same.
There's no misunderstanding.
And,
I think it's best that they both just talked about this.
Great.
So today we are building a ceramic company.
You and I like that.
I told you, didn't I?
To me...
You love me.
What kind of?
Is it like "haunted"?
Like a haunted house.
The one that turned?
I want to make a vase like this.
And cups.
I want to make something I can paint. Yeah.
I thought of ghosts when I saw the pottery.
It's so much fun
because it's one of my favorite movies.
So, when I watched it, it reminded me
to be in the same industry.
He was not happy yesterday.
So I thought I could do some
that we like together,
I think that will make him happier.
Can you help me sort it out?
Please.
He's handsome.
Is it strange to look like this?
Not really.
I think...
Here is the thing.
Very beautiful.
You want to do it?
It doesn't matter.
Which one do you want to do?
Then I'll do this...
You can call me
If you need anything.
He can guide you there.
Alright.
I want both hands.
Right.
Your hands should be wet.
I am the kind of student who copies homework.
You go first.
Don't tell us what you're doing before doing that.
And then decide what it is.
It's hard.
It's very good!
I only know
what's the use of going to Harvard?
Are you kidding?
Architects don't normally make bricks themselves.
From today on,
I'll be able to beat my graduates.
I...
Can 'reflection try to make a funny face a second.
The shape.
Wow.
Decide what this is
what do you think the flaw is?
Let me help you out.
I'll try.
Let's see how I can help you.
You can help me?
Make a vase then.
It's
the...
The...
You'll need to pay
with this house like this, right?
I won't have a job?
I just like a less stressful environment
and don't do anything too formal.
I think it's relaxing.
Thank you mentor.
Alright.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
I'll bake your pencil tape. Can you send it to me after the bake?
That's right.
It's good.
Come and get it.
If there's enough time,
he can come to get it.
- Yes, Miss. - Thank you.
-Bye bye. -Bye.
Thank you
this is a beach by the sea.
Hang in there.
Come on.
Then let's go.
Should we find a place to drink coconut?
I'm going to buy a good one.
Can say.
It's the first time I'm so...
I couldn't relax at the beginning.
It's...
I feel embarrassed in a lot of things.
So you think today is better?
Slightly better than before.
I think they are
then I talked more.
Communicate with others more?
That's why
do you think
what made you realize the most difference yesterday?
Probably.
Because in the beginning,
when I made
when I was...
His answer is really cold.
But he's actually a warm man.
To Susu.
I... I'm not...
My uncle is an interesting man.
I think I could have said more to them.
Because we love each other.
Actually,
I didn't talk to them that much
or
I want to know more about them.
Actually,
xiao Wang wanted to talk to me last night
but I never got the chance.
I think Wang should be a very interesting person.
I'm sure it's fun to talk to him.
He's a happy boy.
You can learn more about Wang.
Your name is Wang,
you should call me Wang.
Wang.
But Wang is mine.
So,
what do you talk about with your friends?
Are very boring.
Is there anything special?
Because I was in Hong Kong.
I rarely hang out with my friends.
I worked overtime when I had no time.
Maybe I'm really a workaholic.
I think my career is the most important right now.
I really want to have a family of my own.
But I don't want to give up on this.
If that's not the case,
I will put all my energy into my work.
When you decided to come here,
have you thought about how could you find a
very simple and childish.
That's not the case.
I think
I may not be as optimistic as you are.
You're not optimistic,
why are you here?
Want to give it a try.
Your logic might not be the same
maybe I can find it.
I'm just not as optimistic as you are.
So you think
out of the four girls in our hut,
of the four girls in this room?
I think it's really yours.
I think you are
that's why
we had no choice.
It's impossible.
Sherry.
I'll say it in English.
They hard to make a connection with
people are
similar to my background
I
It's like this.
The most similar.
This is really important.
Similar topics in the future.
I also want to say
It's normal if you want to know more about
to know more about other male guests.
I want to make friends with everyone.
Me too.
And I didn't mean to say that
I wouldn't fall in love at first sight.
I'm just slowly making friends
when I'm with you.
To be with you.
Inspired by you.
Was I inspired by you?
You fell in love
fell in love at first sight?
No, I used to.
But now I think I can try to
to talk to other girls.
As a friend.
There's no pressure either.
I think I know him better.
Some of the doubts in the past may be resolved.
We didn't think about anything else.
It's just like getting to know a new friend
like a friend.
Do you want to take a walk in the sea?
OK.
And...
Have you seen the post of other girls?
No.
Why don't you check my Moments?
If you are not allowed to check my moments today,
whose Moments would you check?
That's good.
I think it's me, I...
Me too.
Then I...
Moments.
I think it's a great way to get along.
We were both relaxed.
We should just give each other some space
some time.
As a potential friend
and then
we'll see if we can continue.
Yes. This is great.
That's right.
I'll leave then.
What happened?
They must be with me.
What's up
jingjing,
although it is very rational for an adult to act,
but as the audience,
I wanted to say that
they are in a relationship.
But I really appreciate that kind of rationality.
I think it's very good.
When we get to that age,
they won't easily get excited about someone.
And they talk about each other.
I think that's a wonderful feeling.
That doesn't mean they won't be together in the future.
But maybe I like this development.
They were very happy with the last BGM.
But I have a feeling
subtle sadness.
Not subtle but deep sadness.
Maybe the feeling of sadness is like the young people
the way they said goodbye could be clear
to the public.
The temptation between adults.
For them to leave with dignity.
I know what you mean.
A comma on it,
might be a full stop.
In my heart, I've already turned off
are you that pessimistic?
I don't think so.
But I think one good thing about the two of them
that they don't increase their internal friction or burden
due to the reaction from the other party or others.
Looked at each other's social circle
not checking each other's Moments.
Or whose Moments I really want to check?
I'm also very generous to say it
I think that's especially in line with the feeling of half-cooked
I've received
that you treated me well.
But this thing
I won't change my mind just because it's good or bad.
This really got to me.
I think this is a conversation between two very, very mature people.
Real adults should try to understand more about love
to know more about it and find the right one for me.
What is maturity in love?
In fact, it's about overcoming blindness.
Do you think Lin Yi and Ma Jing Long are blind?
I think an uncertain relationship like this deserves an advanced development.
The first step,
for now, we are just what we usually call a partner.
And then we're more like
friends.
We are intimate.
However,
xiao Ma treats Lin Yi in the way of intimacy.
But there's one detail that I think Lin Yi likes.
He thought his hypoglycemia was awkward.
He didn't want Xiao Ma to see it.
At that time,
I see that
this small detail shows that you have paid a little attention to it.
Of course it is.
Will you also feel guilty
your own uncomfortable beauty.
You were afraid of being exposed.
I'm very scared.
I'm not scared.
Not scared.
I said it was better early.
You are so pretty.
You're not scared.
You don't see that
you wouldn't be able to recognize them
you wouldn't be able to recognize her.
Right?
You don't know how to dress up?
To look the worst
In the worst form.
Aren't you afraid of him? Of course, of course.
Not that you want to expose yourself on purpose.
I don't think it's natural to tell you
yeah. It's better to expose yourself early than late.
You can't pretend all your life.
I have to do it every morning.
It's so hard.
There is actually a lot to show.
You can't hide must be showing your nature
and
as Wenjing said, the earlier the better.
Alright.
Now we'll continue to check out their dates.
One of them surprised us in the last episode. I'm looking forward to their dating.
And Shao Jiarong is here alone.
What will happen between them?
Let's watch them together.
This is the first time I have the right to ask a girl out on my own.
It's not that stressful.
And then I hope that I can try to get in touch with
did you come here much before?
No.
The vibe of Sanya is good.
The tropical climate and vegetation.
Be absent-minded
I felt like someone has introduced me on a blind date.
Do you really like him?
Don't mention it.
An imitation game?
The imitation game?
What an imitation game is about?
You know Doctor Strange?
Doctor, the lead actor plays a scientist.
The father of computers, Turing.
And he saved a lot of people's lives.
The machine he developed
since the beginning of this period.
His acting was good.
That's him.
I have never seen this before.
Now you're giving me goose bumps
It gives me goose bumps.
Would it be the cold?
No, it's not.
I like stories like this.
Search for it.
There may be a real
I think this is funny.
Avatar.
It's not his name.
It seems to have an accent.
Where is it?
Can you hear me?
Who knows?
It's me.
It's...
Who knows?
How you got this name?
I was all mixed up the night before.
Yeah, I just want to relax and walk out today
and try to relax
so nervous.
You only had a little food just now, right?
You can see if there's anything you like on the way.
Come on.
It's a relaxing atmosphere.
It's great for going to a food street.
That's right.
This is lively.
It's actually...
The cat soup now.
Eat the salty ones first.
There's a process
a harmonious union lasting a hundred years
I wish you a long-lasting and harmonious union.
Wang Zhen is very funny when he comes out.
Wang Zhen's style of painting
Is very funny.
Chili pepper. No chili.
I'll eat first.
You can have it first.
To
going to the night market.
Maybe young people like it.
If he really likes this kind of local snacks,
I can shop with him.
However,
I don't eat junk food
and I don't eat junk food.
All the time.
Have you had dinner
one.
You first.
He won't eat junk food.
And then
but isn't crispy food better?
Because it has certain requirements on the food.
This is the F & B specialty.
Let's walk around.
And eat here,
and back through there.
Did I see stinky tofu just now?
Yes, there is.
A little bit.
Just a little.
That
the...
The...
You're these
what do you think
why you don't try it?
Because I'm old.
You eat occasionally.
Me, too.
That's right.
I think it's good.
He said this.
He doesn't eat much.
He wants to cooperate.
Then we'll have a bite together.
I think I forced myself on him.
I don't know if it's true.
It's internal.
I sleep until it's dark. I...
You can try them
from dawn to dusk.
You made them yourselves.
You want that kelp?
This one?
Yes, boss.
Thanks.
It's very windy on his side
I'm facing the side
It's fixed.
The view is so great.
Everyone wants to eat two pieces of stinky tofu
and crispy pork belly.
If you don't like this
don't affect
I like the breadth of what I accept is pretty wide.
I feel like it's awkward when you talk to me.
I was shocked.
Am I the one who feels awkward?
I'm not.
I thought it would be weird for you.
So is it?
No, I don't.
I don't have any.
It's
the...
The...
The
If they talk,
I wouldn't be able to speak either.
But I won't feel uncomfortable.
If he's not embarrassed,
It'll be embarrassing for others.
I think I'm the same.
Embarrassing?
Embarrassing is when someone else
huang Zhen,
how can you believe anything he says?
He used to say something
he doesn't even say any now,
just one opening.
You're chuckling.
You
don't you think it's funny?
Not at all.
Do you have any blankets? It's cold.
Take my shirt.
It's not good.
I'll go there myself.
Thanks.
Don't...
The cold is not my fault.
That's not the case.
I forgot how old you are.
I was in 1988. Two years older than you.
Two years older than you?
(Four months older than you!)
Four months?
I was born in May.
But I can't see that.
You seem to be a little younger.
Right?
Maybe it's just like Xiao Ma.
Shocked again.
Brother Wang.
I need a set of memes.
I'm really surprised.
And it's 3 consecutive songs.
3 different ones.
You look the younger, don't you?
About as young as Xiao Ma.
Xiao Ma, do you know how many years it's been?
Nine-six.
Right.
I'm eight years older than him.
I think it's almost the same.
I have no concept of age.
What's the difference?
So when I asked you out,
to ask you out?
I asked her.
What do you think?
I'm a little surprised.
Right.
I just asked you,
there's actually a performance
during the ring.
You know?
The
and I thought,
finished
you know?
I can rest at home tomorrow.
With...
And you know what?
I remember you said "Yes," in the end.
Like this.
In the first one,
I thought you were going to reject me.
You know?
Then you tell me, okay, okay.
I realized there's no subsequent.
I said, is that a yes?
And then
there are quite a lot of turns
and then...
That's the quiz today, isn't it?
I thought it would be the first day of their date.
According to the quiz ranking,
right.
The ceilings.
They correspond to each other.
They were in the basement.
Love in the basement.
And then...
I want to finish my date with you.
I want to know something about you.
I watched the test.
One of the questions says
If someone doesn't like what you're wearing,
will you change for him?
Then you said you would.
So I thought you might be a little
a little optimistic and outgoing,
maybe he got hurt in love.
I had a little low self-esteem.
But the thing is
that's what I wrote
I'll change for each other.
It'll probably be within my comfort zone.
A certain percentage
like this.
If I don't like it,
I might not change.
Right.
However,
don't mention it.
I think
In my opinion?
Right.
Yes, that's right.
You said we are similar yesterday.
So you think I'm the same?
I don't have
we're not talking about personalities.
Which one do you think is like...
I was talking about my eating habits.
I like to be calm.
To be
emotionally stable.
Like this.
I'm not stable.
This is what I seem to be.
Their emotions seem to be stable.
Inflammable and explosive.
Maybe when it's ripe,
his trick was exposed
they told it
don't show it.
Cheers.
Nice to meet you.
Flower.
No, I'm serious.
I said it's nice to meet you.
No, I mean it.
I think this is our first formal acquaintance.
Today is the time
I just want to adjust myself
and then the overall performance
It's really good.
I was very relaxed
I don't have too much pressure or psychological burden.
Are you saving your stomach for that
for the seafood?
Let's go for a run later.
Shall we run?
Run a little.
Try to digest it.
Let's see who can run to the lighthouse first.
That's great.
Really
I am wearing sneakers today.
It shouldn't be.
The key is
are you fast?
I can't.
Not very fast,
but I think it might be a little faster.
No, I can't.
- Go. - No.
No, we won't.
I just don't like the feeling of losing.
Just kidding.
Wait, how can you run after eating?
I run with weight.
I like that.
I even ate more than you.
Even if I have to eat more than you.
It's fine too.
And get rid of them.
It's really starting.
Eight.
Come on.
It's too early
to start.
He asked you to take 10 steps. Is that four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten?
Why did you run away with the talking?
The camera is off.
It's so romantic.
Like this one.
You're on site.
Be careful
you win.
After a while,
run away with me.
They started panting.
Really panting.
That's a long way.
Really.
I thought we were joking and chatting.
And then he got up and ran outside.
Just face what you want to do.
I just want to
and run as if no one is around
that's right.
Then I can do it.
This is itself a very romantic and cool thing
and ran as you like.
They both want to win.
Right.
It makes her relaxed.
They are free.
Because we do whatever we want.
The things we wanted to do.
I'm old.
Very old.
I'm tired.
Sister.
You win.
The rose.
A dazzling my
running shoes really works.
Twenty.
I can't.
I have really aged.
You can just run like that.
You can't leave the old man in the lighthouse.
You seem to be panting.
You make me look weak.
What's up
wait for me.
I can't.
Xing, this is a mountain
luckily,
we can let go of our worries about him.
I think
the teacher said to release, then the certificate can be released.
They are all kind of good.
I respect my feelings.
I didn't cater to anyone.
Girls like her are really shining.
She's totally at ease.
I like being at ease.
Now Daoxi needs to do some shopping at the supermarket.
Let's go to a supermarket.
Yes. Let's go to the supermarket to buy something.
On the way back,
I want to go to the supermarket to buy some earplugs.
The muted type.
And I like going to the supermarket.
I like going to the supermarket.
I told them
I said I thought
the most romantic thing is going to the supermarket.
Really?
I said the same thing.
Really
right.
Checked it out.
I think the most romantic thing is just two people doing trivial things in life together.
We can go to the supermarket,
go to the supermarket, do some shopping together.
To experience common things
every little thing
they will eventually have common interests.
What's your hobby?
Next time when we go to the supermarket,
like this.
You make me laugh, huh?
We're in the city!
Calm down now?
And bustling.
I did come to buy the refrigerators.
That's all.
The first time in my life...
We're at the supermarket.
Entrance
what should we buy? Western food and milk. Ear plugs. Yes.
Hello.
Do you have some earplugs?
Sponge earplugs for sleeping.
Not headphones. Do you have them?
In the daily necessities area?
Hello.
Are there some earplugs?
Are these the only ones?
Is this the only one?
You have no choice.
The chef, say hello to everyone.
The chef says hi.
I am the chef.
I'm from supermarket.
What? Face to face?
What are you filming?
They've done a lot of things.
And they've all been effective.
Right?
The vibe is totally different from when they were first out. It's not awkward at all.
It's very live-streaming.
I thought it was fun when I was holding this.
Now my hands are sore.
You don't have to hold it all the time.
You can put it down when you're tired.
And hold it up when you want to shoot.
Turn off
bye-bye.
He doesn't know simple love?
Right?
Nothing. What's wrong?
What are you doing?
It's here.
Right.
I can't help it.
I...
Watching the sunset so happy
till we all fell asleep
are you Jay Chou?
This is the song.
♪ Forever pure, no sadness and love, dream of becoming your ♪
Sleep on my chest.
What kind of life.
I love you.
You love me?
He wanted to see her.
He's totally different now.
Then
huang Bo suddenly appeared
he seemed to send a blessing.
The other day,
I thought of him as myself...
Or in my opinion.
And today is
I think it's important to make one side more solid.
I think he's very interesting.
Back in the cabin,
he's still a little distant.
It's not that
It's just that they meet in private
they might be closer.
In the end, he still said goodbye.