I just to say that I'LL
cause
you know
It.
Tik Tok.
Here we are.
I think it's huge.
Let me walk this way
I'll take a look around.
Wow.
There's also a pool. Wow.
Great.
Should we face a problem?
What should I eat?
Can you cook?
Not really.
I'm going to show you all your skills.
Can we have a good cook here?
I can do something simple.
Just fried broccoli, scrambled eggs with tomatoes. These are simple dishes with rice.
I think I can't do it.
But if you don't mind me asking,
you're not good at cooking, are you?
He can.
I'm not really good at cooking.
I'm worried about eating.
My head hurts.
I...
It's very
they worry about everything.
It's so good that we have 3 coconuts
3 coconuts.
1 pot.
That's why we're making coconut chicken.
Three coconuts are just enough to make one coconut chicken.
He's got the pan ready.
Isn't this the stove?
The hints are obvious.
It's already
shall we have to do it now?
Come on.
Is the box full of muscles?
Yeah, I think it's been prepared for us.
Open them.
This one.
What's this?
This is my fate.
Seasoning.
Then let's take it over.
They should be the same thing.
Just put them on both sides.
I will do it.
Let me take it.
Can you hold it?
This is the roll
put this in.
Then the chicken.
Do it together.
Right. I'll pour this in.
Wow.
So sumptuous.
Should we toast first?
We can have a coconut toast.
Let's do the coconut.
Cheers!
Nice to meet you, everyone.
Nice to meet you all.
Now let's start eating.
Let me serve them.
I'm the waitress of this week.
Thank you, honey.
Thank you.
Wang is a very meticulous man.
He always serves us food.
I think it's warm.
Lao Wang cares a lot about details.
And he takes care of everyone.
I'm curious,
the car in front of you
have you chatted for the whole journey?
No.
He said nothing?
I don't believe that.
Really
how dare you believe him?
There's a silence.
I think Jialong is going to be
very...
What's wrong with you?
I one.
What's your problem?
You may not have passed all of them.
Think twice.
Every time
when I see the eyes of their families,
the eyes of the family should show excitement in their eyes.
I see the light
the light.
Maybe he's already
the start to shine.
He's mine.
Wang and I are
yes, Mr. Yin was about to tell us
how you answered the question of hitting on someone.
He said he didn't know how to hit on someone.
Why?
You love me.
Come and find me.
You probably get hit on a lot.
Occasionally.
It's the question.
They're after them.
It's yours?
You
with the sound of the door,
they won't eat,
no talking.
Focus on eating.
Don't cook it for too long.
Will it become old?
You'll have no nutrition.
Would have no nutrition.
Let me give it a try.
I think it's ready now.
It's good.
Alright.
I will destroy them.
You want more meat?
I will.
Enough.
That's enough.
You can eat downstairs.
Sit next to me.
I will definitely sit next to you.
I can sit next to you.
You sit next to you, too.
You won't have to worry about eating.
But you are a man.
What do you think
what do you think I look like?
Let me guess.
I really want to guess.
Let's start from this side.
I'm originally from a mountain.
My origin is Shanxi.
So I let you tell me who you are when you're here.
Guess that these few
these few of them?
My energy didn't support me to finish this job.
Have another bite.
And then I'm so easy to guess
hangzhou. = Tropical Depression rehearsal =
Northeast, northeast, it's not like Northeast.
It's not like Northeast.
It's like Jiangsu, Zhejiang and Shanghai.
It's northeastern.
Yes.
In black every day.
I think one year will help me
I think you must be from the south.
I think you're like someone from Jiangsu.
(Shanghai) Shanghai.
(Shanghai) Shanghai?
Yeah, Shanghai.
You're Shanghai.
Have you been in Shanghai the whole time?
But your accent sounds like a northern accent
I'm easy to be influenced by your accent.
Then spend more time with Kayin.
We'll listen to you.
And...
I didn't know.
You don't understand?
He does copy you.
- He's copying me. - That's a good speech. - Is that a good mouth?
That's good.
I think it's fun.
Right.
I...
It's not.
She left Shanghai for a long time.
Right.
She must have left Shanghai for a long time.
So I can't see
chinese
lives in Shanghai.
Right.
I think you are Taiwanese.
I agree with Chen...
One
It's mine.
Where are you?
Shanghai?
You are in Shanghai too.
Because I'm also in Shanghai.
And also in Shanghai.
We're both in Shanghai.
She is also in Shanghai.
A lot of Shanghai's.
Do you want more kelp?
I think you like this.
What's this?
Self-discipline means having little time to sleep
she can sleep late and get up early.
Working out.
He kept a diet.
He doesn't eat sweets, either.
Do you like to exercise?
It works out.
Working out?
How long have you been working out?
1.
It's been 0 years.
It's been 10 years.
Right.
No matter boys like dessert,
he will cut down on carbs.
Did you strictly control the intake
are a very disciplined person.
No, I mean...
I've read them all.
Mother.
Do you want some chicken?
There's chicken here.
We also
really?
Hurry up and eat.
Otherwise, he'll come and eat.
Our atmosphere
we were having a great time.
After the whole day,
we all have our own stories and characteristics.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow's arrangement.
I'll go back to my room.
See you
lily
we have come to see your room.
Come here.
You picked the biggest one, right?
I didn't know
I... We walked all the way here...
With that balcony.
Whose balcony is so beautiful.
Welcome to be our guest.
Come here.
Alright.
I'll come here.
Come.
I'm coming.
It's mine.
The...
The
so,
at first, you and Jia Rong exchanged the answer sheets,
yes, you said he is an uncle.
Yes. Mengmeng's uncle.
I think
I didn't even tell him.
I think you're...
Really
he's very thoughtful.
He has been serving me food.
And Jia Rong got food for him too.
I saw that.
Did you send me the photos?
I send dishes to anyone.
Right?
Alright.
It's done.
Here. Velveteen.
Do you want some?
I'll take some for you.
Thanks. Thanks.
Eat more.
Give him all the good
my watch is too afraid to run out.
Without him,
I wouldn't have enough to eat tonight.
Luckily...
So something new in this is yours?
I...
Don't know, to be honest.
They don't know.
Because some people might be nice,
they can be meticulous.
She's not angry.
Do you guys have any
me, too. I
but I didn't even know what type of guy you'd like.
I think I knew.
When I saw them,
we don't know
I want to see
after getting to know each of them,
and find out who I like
who I'm more interested in.
I think this place is nice.
It has its own yard
and a swimming pool.
And three beaches.
Whose dog?
That's...
Alright.
Please assemble in the living room.
To view today's love test papers together.
In the living room?
Right.
This way.
Hey.
Get out.
We watched you all the time and passed by.
Already?
Be careful of the pool.
The two of us may want to take a shower.
Do you want to stop me?
The
the...
The...
Ha ha.
I've brought you some local products from England.
They are biscuits.
What a coincidence.
I also bring something.
Everyone has brought things.
The
hey!
These four are for the beauties.
And then
(Label producer MaSiWei) These four are different things.
Put it here. Everyone can choose.
You first.
Alright.
I'll take this one.
You come.
The second.
Susu!
Thank you for the gift.
Thank you, Lao Ma. You're always happy to receive gifts.
This is mine.
Did everyone in the kitchen pick the dinner?
I chose the knife.
I also chose a knife.
You must have used a kitchen knife when you got into a fight.
It's scary.
It's better to sit there.
When you're flirting with someone, you find other people's problems.
I won't tell them.
So you tell me later?
It's not a problem.
It's just not used to it.
Find
then when you find others' faults,
and don't mention
during the flirting,
they won't.
But when we're in a relationship,
I'll tell him I don't like that.
I'm curious,
why you can tolerate these problems during the flirting period
when they become the real one.
Maybe that's because
sometimes I ignore some of my shortcomings when I like him.
It's...
That's me.
It's yours.
You can think about your problem again.
Let's pass them.
Let's go first.
This is a tough one.
There's a "I don't you"
Yeah, really.
He doesn't eat?
To eat outside is the same as going out.
Like going out for a meal.
If we have to have one meal,
so he'll eat mine.
And wait for him to see it and be patient.
Actually, I thought to write that as a kick for him.
And then I thought
like the first day.
Not so good.
You're really strong.
Right.
Very impressive.
I'm like that uncle.
The first time I answered this question, I was like,
or when he's finished,
my star might turn off the television.
He is polite, right?
Yes, he is.
Turn off the TV.
Right.
And then it's on his face.
This is more interesting.
You don't always say "I love you" to Dan
I might not be able to express
how would you express it?
It's probably just a routine concern.
And to express my love to you.
Do you share sadness?
Me too.
What did you tell your girlfriend then?
You didn't share the sadness.
♫ You won't share my love ♫
I'm the only one
I was slow to open up my heart
this kind of
It's not me. I am a cancer with a shell.
That's right.
Then maybe he wouldn't say so much
he might not say so much
express yourself.
Is a slow process.
In the beginning,
It might not be that many.
But it needs to be gradually.
But I think mine will be the top.
When two people
we can do this
they are very much in love.
That kind of
I might
for each other.
Yes, I'm careful about
about entering a relationship.
Because I want our relationship to last long?
Alright.
It's almost over.
Come on.
He's hungry.
Take my gift
just go.
Come.
Come on.
Sorry for all the trouble.
I'm curious.
Do you buy every girl the same gift?
No, they belong to the same type.
But they are different in different bottles.
I like them.
That's good.
I quite like Na.
Also,
(That doll's clothing is the same color as mine.)
A little bit.
The gear might be stuck.
It smells so good.
You're just the old man, aren't you?
No.
I cooked fried food.
Yeah, I made some bread.
That's good, Boss.
Would you like to have
I know you have it for others.
I won't...
I won't take it.
No.
The
the...
If it's just the milk, it'll be warm.
Yes. Try it.
I don't know what to do.
Well
delicious.
I warmed the electric bread.
The bacon and...
Did you take a good rest yesterday?
Is it OK?
What's wrong?
I did some cooking just now
but it got robbed by me.
The two of us
they took it.
I'll make some bread too.
Can I make a small request?
Great.
I can learn from you.
How you cook?
That's good.
But I just eat toast and egg.
Let's see how you'll make it.
First,
wash the eggs first
there's some salmonella on it.
But didn't you break the shell?
Your hands are stuck to their shells.
Your hand is stuck to its shell, too.
Look at this. It's hairy. So fishy.
Salmonella is bacteria.
So you wait for the heat
you just say no to it
because it's not a hot spot.
I need two plates.
I think they can make me look more vivid.
Like a couple.
Bring it to the table.
Wow.
That smells so good.
Shall I make room for you?
No need.
I put the spoon in
you finally have the look of a restaurant owner.
You are right.
Very reasonable.
You are finally
you finally become a restaurant owner.
The
the...
The...
So it's not cliche?
They were eating
to lower their guard,
what are your criteria for evaluation?
Right.
It's me.
It's...
This...
This is the one.
I don't have
I remember there is a very interesting story.
But I don't remember the idiom.
It means "avoid horse racing from the field."
You said Tian Ji's racing last year?
It's not good for them to compete like this.
We still need to mess up the order.
So I know what their principle of pairing is.
The sun panel in the basement
the silence.
Our logic is very confusing.
Take it back to basics baby.
We control the sun
We could make it we
Davis but baby, let's be quiet now. Reach out, pull out on the
we don't have to get sophie.
Join the discussion about half-baked lovers on Weibo.
Share your views on love on Weibo.
More exciting content
on Sina Entertainment's Weibo.
Thank you, exclusive social media platform Weibo for your great support.
Thanks to our chief partner media, Sina Entertainment, Weibo.
Content Collaboration Platform Sina News, NetEase News Talknews Xiaohongshu keep.
Let me the real
takeo all your
I dress me the naked truth
until both I complicated all the things we wannado
much better when
it