Take off your hair.
To control oil and prevent hair loss, use Yang Yuanqing.
This program is sponsored by Yang Yuanqing.
Let me show you the morning tea life of Guangzhou people.
Would you like to come back to Shanghai for a while?
I will.
It's me.
Go to Hunan province.
Just eat.
Really?
I will definitely eat it up.
My mouth is swollen.
This is the park where I used to play when I was a kid.
I used to do this.
Enjoy the fun of childhood with him.
I feel like two people are getting closer.
Guangzhou is having a nice day.
It's always cloudy in Guangzhou.
It seems Guangzhou likes you a lot.
Everyone loves you.
Seriously?
It's me.
Enough.
Your wish must come true.
May your wish come true in a sweet way.
Just gotta say that I feel
cause you know
you know
you know it
have a seat.
It's fine.
So open.
How was your sleep?
It felt good to sleep in my own bed.
But I usually sleep one o'clock.
How soon? Go to bed at two.
Didn't you see me tonight? Miss me?
A real one?
They have begun.
Oh my goodness!
You can't sleep?
Right.
I can't fall asleep.
After falling asleep,
I might be wondering how late I can't sleep.
It's past two.
It's still too late.
Tell the old
I almost think of something to make you lose sleep.
Think about
If you like to eat food in Guangzhou.
You like that, right?
Can you stay with the Guangzhou food?
Food can't.
People can.
Great.
I...
They said to cancel the tickets.
Are you jealous?
You're being jealous.
Can you accept jealous people, then?
You mean being jealous or being jealous?
It's a pun.
Can I accept that?
Because I'm also a jealous person.
What a coincidence.
What is your love view then?
I think
If you think about how long our close relationship lasted,
you need to invest in it.
Even if they're compatible,
If you don't have one thing on,
It would go in a different direction.
So when I was in that igloo
I said you were braver than me.
I think I'm in a state of being slow
other people gradually.
Have you always been like this?
Or did it become
It should always be that way.
But it wasn't that long before.
You said you could speed up in that igloo,
do I have one?
Yes, I have.
I forgot about it.
How long is the deadline?
Inspect someone
1 to 3 months?
1 to 3 months
that's one to three months.
You can't be together
when you can be together
Is it very intensive for you to get together during these 1 to 3 months?
You'll see things in the middle.
To live with each other.
You can't just listen to him.
You have to see what he has done.
It's useless for you to say it.
Everyone can make it beautiful.
There's a piano shop downstairs where I live.
After I finish the house,
I will go back to learning guitar and violin.
Have you learned?
I learned a few lessons.
It took me a lot of courage to walk in there.
Because we are all young.
You are such a brave.
From Liang Jing Ru's side.
Is that it?
I'll wait for you to repay it for me.
Use your courage first.
Can I lend you some money?
Coco.
To pick you up for an hour.
That's great!
It's like being finished school.
I'm already a grown-up.
You're still a child.
You're not childish,
you've grown up.
You've grown up.
You've grown up so soon.
You can grow up as you wish.
I have eaten too much these days.
That they were talking nonsense in a serious manner.
They chatted on the same channel.
Because someone said that.
You answered like that.
That's rare.
Fixed.
The two of them.
Here we go again.
Why is that look again?
It's mine.
Let me take a picture.
Don't move.
It's true.
Just squat down
that's it.
No...
You look down there
and you'll think,
all the time.
Why would you?
I've been in Guangzhou for over a decade.
I've never been to Gore Tower actually.
Pan's here.
I just want to say that you and I can feel
this is what it is?
And then
for the director, write the one outside the tower.
We can't write each other.
Can you help me open the necklace?
My first impression is
that Iron Man.
Is this the Iron Man?
He has something on his hand
and then it's released.
Nice hands.
Then you have to hand out these things
my hands are sore.
So I want to borrow your answer.
You are really a zombie!
Many of them are businessmen.
Avatar.
Because there's no Avatar for him.
This is so much fun.
Avatar.
(Avatar: The Last Airbender) Should we go this way?
Let's walk on it.
I can't feel my legs now.
You can hold your hand here.
Look down.
It's scary.
OMG.
Wow!
Really scary.
Can you handle it?
I'm a little afraid of heights.
It has
It's the first time to stand on such a high place
he was out.
And scared.
I would date in a place I'm not good at.
You will have the feeling
to overcome difficulties.
I want to hold it with two hands,
can I walk with my eyes closed?
Today, I realized my fear of heights is so serious.
So high.
So scared.
I can't hold on for long.
My goodness.
Help
you can take a deep breath and try.
Come on.
Wait a second. OK.
Are you ready?
Hold on.
I'm...
Surrender to the fear in my heart.
Overcome represents anything.
Then I took my hands up
took a picture of myself first,
and then I took pictures of the scenery outside.
And the moment I looked down,
enough. Enough.
I can't see that.
I closed my eyes.
I'm afraid of heights.
It's mine!
I can't.
I can't do it.
Did I give you courage?
I don't...
What a
what a great view!
I'm not afraid at all.
And pretend to be me now?
You're really stubborn.
Just look at them for a while.
Open your eyes.
I was closed all the time.
Crying.
That place is where my home is.
Can you open your eyes?
Yes, I can.
I saw the bottom.
I did look down there.
I've checked the hotel,
our...
Welcome back to the man's world.
I think Mr. Wang arranged it well.
During his trip to Guangzhou,
to
I think I'm more active after that. = What do you think about the future =
I'm more active in talking
and start talking.
I opened my first store in 2014.
But I went to Shanghai last year to learn how to do it.
Taking photos.
This is so beautiful!
In terms of body language.
They're closer physically.
I saw them
they were laughing all the time.
They were laughing for no reason.
I came here once.
It is for midnight snacks.
Night snacks?
Han clothing.
Have you ever worn Hanfu?
You know, I didn't either.
I kind of want to wear it.
Why don't you open the door?
Why aren't you working yet?
Too cute.
Changsha dialect.
Can you guess what that means?
I know that.
I know.
That's smart, isn't it?
It's not.
I know that too.
This is also good.
I can't.
Alright?
It's beautiful.
Thanks.
Take a seat.
Sit down.
Why are there so many things here?
We changed it.
Although I don't really like taking photos,
I've never taken photos with boys.
These are my photos.
But I want to record this moment.
He wanted to do this
just with a little sweetness
with swag.
Because the photos I choose are cool.
We might have some hand holding
so I just want to say,
holding hands should be fine.
I'll put on makeup first.
I...
It's me.
Your
wasn't you.
His hands are released.
Catch them.
I'm embarrassed too.
I want to scrub the floor.
No. Don't look so helpless.
Right. Don't look at me.
Look at him.
- Are you looking at me? - Huh?
Don't laugh.
Be happy.
Alright.
Give me a break.
My goodness!
I can't do it!
Please allow me
no.
Keep your eyes down.
With your big eyes
open your mouth.
Alright.
Hello.
It's cold.
Go on.
We held hands and hugged when we took photos.
At the beginning, I felt like
at first.
But we were familiar once and second time together.
And you hold the rope.
Like I'm supposed to be holding a hand.
Hey.
These photos will look nice.
I feel like I've taken him to a new level
and I took our relationship to a new level.
Anger?
You can go down the slide.
Do you want to put it in there?
OK?
It's me and wow
this is amazing.
Draw the radish.
The turnips?
Here's your order.
This is the order.
I think our trip to Changsha was great.
We managed to get along with our worries.
Back to reality,
we're still very comfortable with each other.
Very comfortable.
I really enjoy spending time with him.
When we have time,
I'll take the opportunity
and then I'd like to say under the time
let me teach you long words.
Did you hear the word "treasure" in it?
It means I'm going to treasure you.
It means I...
Are you alright?
Sir, I'm fine.
But he lied to you.
Lie to him?
Right.
You're having a baby.
You're a bit silly, right?
Treasure spirit. Within treasure spirit.
That's right.
A little.
He even communicated with the shopkeeper about me.
They said you must eat meat pie and steamed egg.
We have no problem now.
We may have some problems in the future.
We should solve them together.
If there are problems in the past,
I hope the past can stay in the past.
We need to move forward.
What do you think of our trip to Changsha?
We have
progress faster?
I think so.
I feel like everything is perfect,
and I don't want this to end.
Will it make you stressed?
No, I don't.
Why would I feel that?
It's not true.
Don't...
I still think it's fast
happy.
I'm scared.
But I don't think there's anything to be afraid of.
If I'm scared,
why would I do this?
I didn't start until I finished.
I know
has ended.
Was the real beginning.
However,
just let nature take its course.
That's when I don't want to live.
Or escape.
Me too.
You trust me on your own.
I really like it when you're like this.
Because I'm the one
thank you, Niu.
The weather is good
for our date.
He helped me all day.
So what does this prove?
We're a good match.
You're shining the sun on our behalf.
Our trip to Changsha is over.
I was very happy these two days.
The sky is pink.
Really?
Oh, my goodness.
That's amazing.
I love this feeling so much.
Just kill me.
To cheer you up.
That's awesome.
This is awesome.
How can this group be photographed with this photo?
That "wow" feeling.
Right.
Exactly.
With my feet on the ground, yeah.
But on the other hand, their relationship develops very quickly
dream is very brave
I'm going to push it
the point is that the other party likes and accepts him and Junlin gave him confidence.
Perfect cooperation.
Which way is the main entrance?
The front door is over there.
When you came here in November,
It's super beautiful.
It's covered with ginkgo biloba on the road there.
He said this place is huge.
To school?
School.
Finally.
I've been in school most of the time.
I remember the place in Shanghai the most.
So I want to show her the environment I live in.
So I hope he can know...
There's a lake.
Across the library.
It's...
Because Fudan University
Its name comes from Minister,
It's called Moonlight Brilliance.
Dandan and fudan dan.
There's the sun and the moon.
Like this.
Do you guys have that kind of collection
as an undergraduate,
he has so many clubs
he might form one.
Running in the morning and at night.
And camping.
Really?
But masters and doctors may have more time by themselves.
This view is quite pleasant.
Breathe in the natural oxygen bar. '
You can go now.
- Let's find another place. - Wow.
Let me go this way.
It's beautiful here.
You have to punch in at Fudan.
Would you like to punch in?
You can profile me.
That's fine.
I'm the one
It resembles ours.
Great.
Wow.
That's impressive.
Right.
Wow!
It's mine.
It's so cute.
Sweet girl carrying a basketball bag is a statement of sovereignty
my life used to be so boring.
It's very simple.
From the dorm, canteen to our lab,
but now someone followed me to the university.
He brightens a part of my life.
The memories I made
I must be very happy.
What's your activity this afternoon?
I'll attend a meeting.
A meeting?
The camp?
When will this camp end?
Maybe around 4 p.m.
I should have finished my work by then.
I'll go and find you then.
I'll pick you up after work.
I'll come home today.
Wait for me after school.
But he rubbed his hands.
He didn't touch his face?
Pinch your head.
Go on.
Go up to the sky.
You're leaving?
To leave?
You can't.
It's over.
I've forgotten all of them.
Also,
your ring is in your left pocket.
Thank you. See you later.
I knew Lin Yi was in Linjiang.
And I wanted to surprise him.
Wow!
Got changed.
She's a professional woman now.
My goodness.
Well
It's so different.
The female lead in Shuang Wen
the new achievements and goals of the exploration and practice in the construction of Leisure Section Shanghai.
The total amount is around 30g,
right?
Thanks.
Hello.
Did you plant these flowers when they were down?
Imported.
An old one from New Zealand.
And then the starry sky.
This one and this one.
What kind of TV series is this? Idol drama?
Hey.
For a long time.
And Huahua?
For you. Huahua.
These flowers match you well.
The outfit today
you have...
Is there anything in your house?
I'll buy some flowers.
Flowers. I might keep an hydrangea in summer.
Hydrangea?
Right.
There is a species of hydrangea called Infinity.
Summer has always ended.
Good name.
I will do that.
There's no...
But unfortunately, there was no sign of Wu.
But find someone who's close to Wu.
I need to take a picture
are you going to prepare a gift?
I'll get you a perfume this afternoon.
You are so insightful!
Smell the perfume.
Interesting.
I like the subtle fragrance of flowers.
I also like to prepare small snacks.
How do you know I like strawberries?
You said that.
I'll keep that in mind.
Did I tell you that?
You told me that, right?
That you did?
I feel ashamed when there are so many surprises.
I'm really touched.
He prepared a perfume just for me.
It's my...
Really?
To see you.
I was a little tired this afternoon.
The strawberry I ate
I feel that I am totally alive.
I'll eat something else.
You have to stop eating.
Hey!
To spoil your look.
I knew more about his childhood and his daily life from him.
To introduce my daily life
and let him know me better.
Our relationship better.
In the future,
In the future.
After going back to our cities,
It's more about the two of us
to walk into each other's life
and get to know each other's lives.
I think it's closer to the feeling of love
this is better than a TV series.
I really think
as for his hand.
He was in the car.
The boy-crazy
little nympho.
So in fact, we will find that
we'll find that
we can see the details
let's go to
the candy of love.
But when we get into this real intimate relationship,
It actually takes a great deal of wisdom to get along
to manage it
and not when love comes.
It will always be there.
I think a relationship must be managed.
We can't let it stand on its own.
Certainly.
Of course it is.
You have to let your relationship perish on its own.
It will.
Oh!
You need to be independent.
Don't say that.
Come on.
I can't live without you.
Sometimes
we use a word called breakup power.
The more powerful you are,
In fact, the steadier your relationship will be.
The more they will cherish you.
If you want to say such a thing,
I can hang myself on this tree.
I often said that the tree felt terrible.
Well
for the second aspect,
we have to work hard
we need to express love.
We should express it in some way.
Do it.
The food
all you want is this.
We can't be lazy.
Keep showing love to each other.
This...
Unlike what we say sometimes,
come on.
We're already married.
Please don't.
This is the hidden danger.
I can't imagine how happy Mr. Du's marriage is.
It's true.
On Mr. Du's WeChat.
Next time, just send me
just give it to me.
To me?
And
what's my greatest strength?
There are so many excellent examples around.
All of you are outstanding
are all this
the shining.
That's what Mr. Du talked about earlier.
And stay attractive to others.
You too, what am I?
I don't blossom like me
It's a pity that you blossom in Heng Dian.
Thank you.
Where are you going?
I'm going out to buy something.
What's your plan today?
I wanted to cook for you.
Really?
Do you want to play badminton?
I won't go to play badminton.
Yeah, you can go then.
But I cooked for you.
Hey...
Just woke up. Just finished.
I'm off.
See you later
I heard you're going to play badminton.
No, I may find a friend later.
I have a friend in Sanya.
It's out there.
Well
come on.
Let's wait for your feast.
He is my senior.
We knew each other when we were in college.
When they get married later, they come here.
I remember that when my friend got married,
am I the bridesmaid?
We were there at the wedding anyway.
At that time, my brother-in-law said he would introduce a boyfriend to me.
Over 10 years has passed.
We knew each other since childhood.
Whenever we meet, I feel that I have a lot of things to talk about what's going on.
And talk about my house.
Why did you come to see your friend today?
There's something the way
It hurts.
There's a surprise attack.
Drop us in.
How long has it been since last time?
Over a year.
A year or so ago.
That's right.
What were you busy with?
I'm busy looking for true love.
Then you haven't found her.
Not yet, I think.
You have such high standards.
Really
do you think I have high standards?
Really?
I am not so demanding now.
I'm really not that high.
Do you have a favourite?
Let me show you.
Let me see if we have any photos taken.
Which one do you think I like?
He and another boy named
It's me.
It's...
Because you know
I've never had
with a boy younger than me in many years.
You weren't in a relationship either.
The point is,
that's a lot.
There's no problem with that.
Age is not a problem.
As long as he's mature enough at heart.
I think I can live with being 3 years younger than me.
Yang Yang is in there.
He's over 3 years old.
I can't.
People grow up in a different world.
How to do this?
Maybe I'm a little stuck in this.
You haven't met one who's young
who is actually very mature and mature.
That he hasn't met
so you're just a little too sure of him.
Actually,
this is not
he's childish for a young age
he's obsessed with playing.
Maybe I haven't encountered
your brother-in-law is a good example.
He's over 40 years old.
They still love to have fun.
So brother-in-law is so pitiful
right?
Right?
So, you can't
you can't set this age, he's not set so dead
I think the character
but you must have the same interests.
You can still talk when you have common topics.
You can hang out together.
You both like the sports
and the other sports you like.
This is really important.
And I went paddleboarding with that boy once.
Were you happy that day?
Yes, we were.
Have you seen the rainbow?
Wow.
Colorful clouds?
Do you see the heart in the middle?
That's right.
Right? Yeah.
Have a lot in common like what you said.
Right.
Then why not?
We should talk about it later.
Maybe I'm working too fast now
that's why when I'm in a relationship,
roughly.
And then I felt like I didn't have any special feelings in the early stage
and I feel that there is no other feeling after it.
No, that's not true.
You too. So you said it's slow development.
How can you let others take it?
Right?
Gradually.
I mean that
If there's someone who's good to you,
to contact
If he treats you well,
that means he loves you.
Right?
Maybe which point you are right
If you talk about what's good about him again,
or something, you didn't know at the time.
Actually, we got married in a flash.
That's right.
I know you got married in a flash.
It was fast.
And they said,
then why is it only
Is good to me?
I thought that was enough back then.
Then...
No matter what you do,
I'm the first person you thought of.
And leave everything else behind.
Laugh.
I can sit by your side.
Here you go.
- Here you go. - Don't...
Don't come out.
Does it hurt here?
Just a little bit.
It doesn't hurt that much.
But your hand won't hurt.
Give him a chance
and yourself a chance.
Got it?
His every figure is still good.
Really?
I'll go back and talk.
You can let me know.
How should I talk?
What should I talk about?
Help
we can talk about it
we can talk as long as you don't hate me.
Well
that makes sense.
Maybe a little bit of
or before the hut,
I felt that I already knew the relationship very well.
But after talking, I feel that
there are some
well
the standards are probably too slow.
We might lose some chances later on.
After that,
I might try to stretch the line a little bit.
Don't be so stubborn
remember to go back.
-Bye bye. -Bye.
Or I will leave?
Just go.
See you later!
Fight hard.
But in the end, Susu should judge by herself.
Of course,
at least you gave me a possibility.
Let Susu not be so quick to deny
I think that's
It's important to give yourself a chance
right.
You are back
yes, I am.
Have a seat.
We can wait for our meal.
So sumptuous.
Carrot slices.
Why do you guys need my help?
No.
There's no need to wait.
I'll let you do the dishes, okay?
Alright.
To get you involved.
OK.
Alright.
Soon I bet you int back to bed my pill beneath your head repeat the last words I said.
Miss.
Let's see who is this
come on.
Got something?
I was wondering where they were. Where were you?
You were busy today?
You can't guess that?
I shouldn't have guessed.
The makeup is actually quite nice.
I heard cooking.
Have you eaten?
What are you doing?
You two went out together?
Did you fight? I'll ask them to play later.
You went to play badminton?
When we left,
we need to call you.
You're not here.
Did you secretly play?
That's right.
Where have you been?
I went to find my friend.
I think it's very delicious.
I can't.
I can feel the color, smell and taste.
J becomes handsome.
Right.
The one who cooked with his head bent
hello.
We also bought eggs.
Where were you today?
I went to the supermarket to do some shopping for you.
Wow!
This chicken drumstick fits the six people.
There's rice in the rice cooker.
You can have rice to yourselves, right?
First, you can eat.
Let me do it.
Su.
I'll come.
Let me do what I can only do for you.
Look at this,
what are you doing?
Just play more basketball.
You're also wounded.
Are you broken as well?
This one is broken too.
I want to taste it.
Two of you who have the feeling of staying here. Try the meat.
And see how it tastes.
Mr. Ou, it's time to cook.
Get out.
I came for a feast today.
It smells good.
It smells like a pot.
Look. Bring it to the table.
It's beautiful.
The dishes are colorful, fragrant and delicious.
Be riotous with colour
we can only try to make them mature.
Yes, we are being conservative.
The smell alone can't help me. It's too good.
Don't eat it then.
Is all ours.
That's OK.
We can.
After all, they have nothing in common.
This is disrespectful to us.
Try the drumstick.
There's cod fish for six.
This is the first time I cooked this.
I don't know how to do this.
So I think it's good
heat it up a little. It's good.
Is it good?
It's OK.
This is my first time.
Do you want more?
Yes. Do you also want some?
Let me finish it first.
I'll do it myself later.
Not right.
Come on.
Alright.
This is it.
No food.
Nothing.
We prepared noodles
and mung bean porridge.
There are many dishes.
The spoons are all yours
just show your skills.
Alright.
My food didn't move.
Anyone who wants more
take it from my bowl.
It feels a little too small.
If you want noodles,
I'll cook the noodles for you.
It'll be quick.
Let me cook you some.
Just eat something.
Have you washed the pots?
Check it.
Hurry. I'll wash the pot.
You haven't washed it, have you?
I'm doing a kind of contribution.
Otherwise, I'll feel guilty all day.
Nothing.
It's alright.
You don't have to come.
I have to do it even if you come.
But you stay here.
And you have no idea what to do.
Go and eat.
I value justice and fairness.
Alright.
Wash yourself.
Jia Rong is still carrying on
and create a chance.
Jia Jun's smile means a lot.
Do this.
Which angle?
This is fine.
That's actually a little realistic.
This is as good as it gets.
Hold on.
Wait for me. Get down.
Belongs to me?
There is no other choice
there's no other choice.
Do you know
In my whole life,
I've only been waiting for you.
Is your song choice so good?
Sometimes, the song someone hums inadvertently means to calm her down.
Really.
I find...
You have no other choice but me.
That's hilarious.
Come on.
How many towels is your room?
This should be the last one.
I don't need it either.
I haven't used them.
What do you use for shower?
My own towel.
I'm not the same as a clean person.
I remember that once you said your shoulder was uncomfortable
I'll rub your shoulders.
I didn't see you with that cushion.
I...
I need
you
your feet are cold.
OK.
Why don't you put a little...
Give me a second.
Smell it?
Secretly perfume.
How about wearing a mirror?
Thanks.
It's new.
Here you go.
Why does your dress smell so good?
You applied perfume on purpose.
You must have it.
I've never worn this before.
Do you smell perfume if you haven't worn it before?
That's new.
Give this one.
This must be new.
I wasn't sure just now.
I didn't open the nut.
This one.
Got it.
May I
from
knock it off
what are we going to do tomorrow?
We don't know tomorrow.
Tell us what you want to do.
You guys make the call.
What do you want to eat?
Tomorrow, why aren't they back yet?
Didn't they say they'd come today?
I guess they'll be back late.
That's right.
It's midnight, right?
They're at the swimming pool.
Hello.
You're really back.
It's really back.
Who is this?
Where the hell is she?
Hurry up.
Did you go to Changbai Mountain again?
I'll go back to my hometown later,
I'll meet your parents when I'm back.
That's right.
Without my door,
I'll let Kevin speak then.
Where's Kevin?
He's back to Changsha.
Really went to Changsha?
Have you really met Kevin?
Maybe somewhere he used to live.
Wow.
Is Changsha delicious?
Yeah, enough
have you had that stinky tofu?
Yes, can I?
It's good.
Yeah, it's delicious.
People ring more bells nowadays.
No matter how good it is, it's delicious.
What happened?
Like a couple when you grow up.
Really?
Alright.
Sit down.
I... You should be exhausted.
We went to the massage.
The foot massage.
And then we went to shoot a photo.
A couple's photo shoot?
Come on.
My head hurts.
What should I do?
If this goes on,
people say it's "seven years' itch,"
Next year will be seven years.
Myself and I
I'm sick of it. I remember how many years you've been single.
Next year is seven years.
In 2025,
seven years will be mine.
Seven years? You don't want to be in a relationship anymore?
That's true.
We can chat, right?
No, I'm sorry.
I may be lost in the topic.
That's true.
You need to be in a relationship the way I am.
I don't want a relationship.
If you want it,
the energy.
I didn't tell myself to be single this year.
I really like him.
He's cute.
It's like you get on a car
to the highway.
We... We're going to the 36th car on the national road.
We're your glory
he's the happy you?
I can't see it. No. No.
Aren't you cold?
You're so hot!
As expected,
the power of love can ignite your heart.
Look at us.
We're all dressed so cold.
Sitting here got colder and colder.
In here,
she's wearing a sweater.
I see more and more expressions on Jiayu's face recently.
Well, that kvi...
Isn't it always like this?
These days.
Very interesting.
When Kvi first dined with us,
It's
which is cute
and polite.
He can see
he can see
there's love,
and focus.
You know?
It's not that serious.
That's disgusting.
We bystanders see all too clearly.
Is anyone missing us?
No.
They didn't think about it.
We
they look good in everything.
You can feel it right now.
You're already back.
Just arrived.
Just now.
Where have you been, Lao Wang?
Where have you been, Wang?
Why are you wearing a suit?
Is there a major milestone we missed by going to Guangzhou?
Right.
1. What did you say?
The love
they
where did you come from?
Guangzhou.
It's so cold in Guangzhou.
It's a little winter.
Don't be sorry.
That's fair to everyone.
It's not me, Wang.
It's mine.
I want to hug you.
I only want your love.
Give me a hug.
I kind of missed you.
I missed you, too.
They came back from that way.
No romance yet?
You brought this flower back.
It's like a girl in a boy's coat.
Are they wearing school uniforms?
These are...
To stay young.
Are you from Shanghai?
Right.
We just arrived.
You must be tired.
Yes. I haven't put down my luggage. I'll see you later.
You can give her a hug.
Down the well and have a hug.
Give me a hug. Long time no see.
What's wrong?
It feels like I just woke up.
My eyes hurt a little today.
What's wrong with your eyes?
I haven't worn contact lenses for a long time.
Old Shanghai photos?
No.
I'm getting an award this afternoon
that's why I took off his coat.
Did you accept the award with him?
He picked me up after work
and gave you flowers?
Right.
What have you done these days?
What we have done these days?
Why don't you tell me first?
You
that's all for the pics.
Would you like to put them on?
Let me put them down first.
I'll come to you again, okay?
Come on.
My luggage is still there.
Did you still put them away?
No, we haven't.
We'll leave it here.
Come on.
There's news.
It's good, right?
Why?
From the first day you came to Half-cooked Hut,
you've spent the most special time of your lives here.
48 hours.
This time of life is coming to an end.
The day after tomorrow is the final time for everyone.
I hope you can cherish your time.
I don't want to leave after 48 hours.
Surprised, right?
And I think we've built quite a few connections
I've built lots of connections with everyone.
With boys and girls.
Suddenly said we were going to break up.
And there are 12 of us.
It might be hard to have this opportunity to be together at the same time in the future.
It's kind of sad.
So sudden.
It's going to be over.
Will leave this place.
I still hate to leave.
Suddenly I feel like there are so many things to do.
And it's hard to leave.
I just didn't expect it to end so soon.
There isn't much time here.
I feel disappointed mostly because of everyone in the cabin.
Because I think that our trip through Changsha
we both talked about our plans
for the future.
So I think we will remain the same
we will still be the same.
When we received this news,
we thought every minute counts.
I'd like to spend every minute with her.
A little bit.
I feel like it's not easy for me
I opened a little bit
opened a little.
Then everyone parted ways.
It's...
The...
The
all over the world.
To make dumplings
I made dumplings for you.
She may be reluctant to leave,
and excited.
Because it's the last part
to be in a good mood.
I think time flies.
A little
that's emotional
It's just that I'm leaving soon
have you seen the message?
He didn't read it.
They didn't check it.
We only have two days left.
When I knew there were 48 hours left,
so I thought
we need to find time to talk to Pam.
Let's find out your thoughts about the future.
This is how you like it.
I think time really flies
a little
be at a loss
the world is falling apart
what decision Mr. Wang will make
here you are.
And write this.
Where should I go?
Go write on the balcony.
Come on.
Write here.
Have you received the message?
Two days after receiving the message,
maybe your guess is right.
Hurry up.
This is yours.
Did you cut your stitches?
Scissors?
Got a nail clipper.
How long do you want to cut this fringe?
To the same size as the one next to you.
Cut it like this.
The bangs are not aligned.
No?
Is that long?
This way
this way.
Is this long?
Did you cut my hair without my nails
what's with the princess signature?
It's too short.
Just one more year.
OK. Alright.
Alright. First one.
First one.
Wow!
This is a huge responsibility.
Let me try it on first.
What if you don't look good?
What more do I need to try?
Writing. I need to try.
Do you want to try it?
What should I write?
No need.
It's
and sign my name?
No need.
You don't want to write your name on it?
That's not necessary.
Can you find a postcard in Taiwan?
He didn't write or write.
They don't write
and then I don't write
write nothing
are you wise to write in the blank spaces
I should know it's me when I write there's a space.
How would I know what you wrote without traditional Chinese characters?
You can only use this
who should be here?
It's me.
Hui's little princess.
Me, you...
Illuminating everyone.
You can do this yourself.
Alright.
Go on.
Let me write it myself.
Let's go, go.
Slide, slide, swing.
Are we planning to meet?
What a coincidence!
When did you go to bed every day?
I'm always at 2 a.m.
It's almost three.
When did you wake up?
I've been doing this for the past two days.
You
do you want to...
I'll make a choice.
What about 6: 30 tomorrow?
Watch the sunrise at 6: 00.
How did you know?
How did you know that?
How do you know why I want it?
I feel happy.
Your behavior.
You can feel that.
You can look at anything.
And Yao told me that
he is so happy to look at him
and he's a little impulsive.
Yeah, he made an invitation.
Really, Susu is such a good date.
We just said we saw each other.
She should watch the sunrise together.
Right.
Yeah, it changes so much.
I didn't expect it,
I thought it was over.
Right? This sister is quite suitable.
That friend of hers
from his friend.
Right.
And he said something.
If it were me,
I think he got to me.
He said you were taking your time.
Why can't you make it start slowly?
Miss Fairy.
Mr. Du has been waiting for such a long time.
For so long.
Waiting for me
If he comes out,
It's time for you to solve this problem.
-You showed up earlier? -Yeah.
That's great.
For the past season,
don't you think this is sudden?
How come we only have 48 hours left?
The next 48 hours
the next 48 hours
I can confirm my feelings
and the future
will happen faster in the past 48 hours.
Faster?
But I'm really looking forward to a miracle in the next 48 hours if there's no results
today won't be without a sunrise, yes
It's coming out
finally
never seen the sunrise on such a big sun before.
Love is with him every minute
♪ To be with him every minute ♪
That's good.
I can do that.
I...
It's...
I want to
It's too late.
Carry me up.
I think his appearance has made up for many of the regrets in my memory.
Hey!
I can't.
I think they're gonna kiss.
What do we want?
You didn't want me on this show, why did you return to your real job?
I can't do that every day.
Let go of me.
It's...
I really want to spend the rest of my life
Is the first meal you had in the morning?
Because Wang needs to play this too.
We don't have to watch it.
This is much better than idol drama.
Join the discussion about half-cooked lovers on Weibo
share your views on love on Weibo.
More exciting content
on Sina Entertainment's Weibo.
Thank you, exclusive social media platform Weibo.
Thanks to our chief partner media, Sina Entertainment.
Content cooperation platform Sina News, Netease News and News keep
cousty we don't have to get back to losing.
All it needs is just me and you
We don't have to scream out to proven we could keep it all wholecsted
I
keep it all who lecsted.
VIP users can update at 39PM on Tuesday and members can watch the show for a week first
vIP users can watch the live show for an additional 7 hours in advance
I'll return to the club in a week for free, and exclusive to members of the reality show on Thursdays.
I'll watch half of the show with you on Friday
♪ Sweet without stop ♪