My deep impression comes from Meiying-chan
Then my deep impression comes from Zeng Qiao
I don't know why they're being so strict
Because you're acting like this
Just like this
What are you afraid of?
You're blushing again
Is it really red now?
I probably wouldn't have said it like that at the time
If I said it like that, you'd just deny it
Hello, everyone
I'm Lao Ma
I'm Lin Yi
Am I not Lao Ma?
The first time I streamed, I watched with friends
But then work got too busy
so we stopped watching together
I just watch alone at home
I usually watch in the car
Mm-hmm
I watch during spare moments
I...
I also watch with friends
but mostly watch alone
When watching with friends
there's live commentary
They'll tease me
saying "Is this really you?"
How would you respond?
I just freeze up
I-I'm like this...
You're blushing again
And...
Your ears are...
When your friends watch you
they react the same as Xiao Ma
First they laugh at you
Then I start losing friends
No...
It's my friends who lose friends
When we first started getting to know each other,
dates were more about the getting-to-know-you phase.
Things weren't so certain back then.
This feeling between two people,
or this kind of relationship.
But in the end,
I can say I've come to understand my feelings clearly.
The last time,
we were in quite a romantic place.
It left a deep impression on me.
It was truly romantic.
I'm so envious!
The two of you in the snow,
that looked wonderful too.
The whole scene,
just the two of you.
Yes,
I...
could just relax and fully enjoy it.
Now the boat is rocking a bit, making me slightly seasick.
A little dizzy.
But the atmosphere was actually...
Because it was a sunset at sea,
and after experiencing that frozen tale at Changbai Mountain,
plus some deep conversations,
I felt I could relax more.
I just wanted to properly enjoy our last date.
Then welcome the final conclusion.
Do you have any particularly memorable moments?
I...
I knew what was happening
then it aired
Only later did I realize what you were afraid of
I don't remember
Did you two watch that part?
We did, and it did give us a slightly nervous feeling
Right
Yeah
Because actually at the beginning
it was only mentioned that the guy visited the girl's dorm when he asked her out
Yes
It felt like a boundary to me
Breaking through this boundary required some ceremony
You had to dance the "Subject Three"
Exactly
What about you?
What left a deep impression on you?
The hair
I really liked the hair
And the New Year greetings with Dameng
Watch out
Hurry up and go down
Walk faster
The beauty walks so fast
I did fall once
What left an impression on me was the beautiful craftsmanship
For me, it was the amazing coincidences
I think their elopement scene
Because we didn't get to see it
and didn't even know about this part
Only when the show aired did we see it, which gave me a very different feeling
Very cinematic
And it gave me that passionate feeling
Because in our daily lives we're used to certain restrictions
that limit what we can do
so we rarely do anything outrageous
But
your running scene really touched me
That's why later many camera operators kept a close eye on us two
Like when we were walking in Guangzhou
we ended up running again
ran once more
but got caught again
In one episode, old netizens returned to their own cities
Right
How was it in Guangzhou?
Just had dinner
This is also our...
Yes
Had I known, I should have gone myself
Had I known, we should have been together
Is that why you added so much salt back then?
I don't know why I added that much salt either
Because you didn't have a reference
You didn't test it by touching some to your own elbow first
Just like this
That was an electric grinder
So that's why so much salt came out
This is probably what I normally use
I usually only...
Uh...
Um...
I'd give it 100 points
What about the flavor?
Flavor
Give me five bowls of white rice
Thank you
Next time bring a bowl of white rice
If I can eat it, I will
Done
I have some words here
They want me to share more of those Zhenqiao candies
Right
Then I came up with an idea that...
Old Wang
I have some unaired footage here
Do you want to buy it at a premium?
He probably doesn't want it
Old Wang is good at business
He'll bargain hard
I said
Send it to me first
Let me take a look
We're your online influencers
Because I posted a lot of their content
You have it here too
But you've already posted it for free
Because I'm an exposé blogger
A gossip hound
Something like that
Then today, let's watch Episode 9 of *Half Love Season 3* together
My
's
Is that the coconut we picked up that day?
These little short legs
Looks pretty good
Because it has that cinematic feel
Like your social media background
This is also the sea
Because I feel I'm already very heated
And quite passive
Then you're even more intense than me
[untranslatable fragment]
We're both very competitive people
What should I do if I meet someone who's slow to warm up?
I... I...
I...
So I wanted to get hurt
I'm fine now
[Particle indicating emphasis]
My condition is a bit different
Can I be the cameraman next time?
He's got so many jokes
I think it's possible
Are you going to hire this photographer?
So sweet
Capturing your beautiful moments
I believe this courage can bring us together
So I think
I've always
Going down this path of mine
I'm kind of thinking
I probably didn't say it like that at the time
Too sweet
The two of them with auntie smiles
This is a bit
I probably didn't say it like that
I definitely said it like that
You refuse to admit it
This
You pay great attention to details
The men's basketball team
Men's basketball
Lian Lian
Connect the whole sentence together
The reserved Lan Lan
Durian
Milk
The introverted Lan Lan
Durian milk
Durian milk won't work
Always watching
You try it
Try it over there
Reserved men's basketball with durian milk
Durian milk is acceptable
We'll talk when everyone looks good
(particle indicating change of state)
Durian
Too amazing
Been stealing faces at your home all along
Then what you have now
Let's experience it
Wow
Your scream
I fell forward
I'm sorry
I get goosebumps
What does it mean
I can't walk anymore
Can't we walk slowly
Do you want me to carry you
You carry me
Really don't have any
Probably not
Missing a few steps counts as nothing
You still say there isn't any
It's different
It's like how things used to be slow before the holidays
then suddenly sped up
Right
Just like a rollercoaster
Well
All these are new words to you
Right
Because during our previous dates
We always tended to
Have a really good time together
I think we probably had the most fun
Everyone was happy
Can you even speak properly?
Yeah
You could put it that way
It's not that we were solely focused on having fun
We talked
Maybe it was the progression of our conversations
We gradually enjoyed the happy process
During our previous dates
My thought process was probably
To confirm your thoughts step by step
I think we were both trying to understand each other's perspectives
We needed to confirm if we shared the same view on this
Uh
Um
I
Was genuinely sweetened by this
Especially, you know what?
It was when we were eating at the restaurant
There were so many little details
It was super exciting
Like when we switched seats
And the band-aid moment
Right?
And the clothes thing
The most playful was joking about the durian milk
That
That was it
We bumped into each other earlier
We actually talked about quite a lot
But nothing really came out of it
So we just talked
Not sure if those feelings in the moment were real
Didn't want to be influenced by the atmosphere in the cabin
That artificially catalyzed kind of emotion
But the moment you held hands
Everything just froze
That actually represented just being in the moment
I think it might have been
When we crossed a boundary
That feeling
Sometimes physical contact is needed to confirm your true feelings
Don't let them start again
Without telling you
When I first met Yingying,
I thought she was really special.
She was the first girl I wanted to approach upon meeting.
You can all just call me.
I feel like you've always been in a kind of...
...state like this.
I think when people go through certain experiences,
they will...
...develop a kind of protective shell.
Me too.
Then gradually, you'll find a feeling that lets you relax.
That's me.
After watching it, I felt quite emotional.
It's them.
Because I only saw everyone's colorful stories later.
I think...
Moreover...
They're really similar.
They have similar experiences.
They could say exactly the same things.
They just have similar experiences.
So they resonate with each other in many ways.
Actually, Yiyi once said to Jiarong:
"Your metronome has started ticking now."
Right.
That exact phrase.
It might be that segment from the Frozen story.
And then...
Yinyin remembered this sentence.
They're truly in a mutual healing process.
I feel Jialong was really well-prepared.
From preparing the location...
First testing the piano...
Trying out the piano spot first.
Then thoughtfully placing that coat in position.
Guess what this is?
Are you making him guess which meal this is the last of?
Let's go on a date.
We're going on a date.
They're at home.
Boiling coconut.
It's okay, I ordered plain rice for you.
You don't eat sweet things.
Jinyang remembered his preferences.
Jinyang is very considerate.
That's rare.
Class monitor of the senior class.
I remember us waiting for sunrise at the beach and seeing that floating...
That thing that looked like a person.
Then I saw it.
I thought there was something floating in the sea.
I said someone was swimming.
LOL
You
are still eating?
Snack time snack time snack time
I'm eating again
Why am I still eating? Yeah...
's
I think I guessed what you were doing that day
Do you remember me passing by your door?
I think I asked if you were making a PPT
or something like that
Yes, at that time I...
But you... I wasn't working
On the confession day, I thought you came to confess while I was at the computer
You were at the computer
You were too nervous
It was very serious at that time
I said it was too...
I made you a lunch
Would you like to try it?
I'm coming
Actually, I feel your two styles match well
Always
Male
Motorcycle
No
Start posting short videos
Learn on the spot?
Right now
Everyone's learning ability is strong enough
Do we have garlic chives?
What are you making?
Dumplings with garlic chives and eggs
Garlic chives and eggs
Do you have minced meat?
Seems like Lao Ma always makes breakfast for me
I think I won't move on the last day of returning to work
Yes, yes, yes
There are many profound things inside
Memorable
Stir-fried vegetables with eggs is his loving lunch
Chef
Culinary skills
The thought counts most
The intention is what matters most
Plating
The sense of ceremony is important
Everything looks good
With my help, you'll definitely eat until you're stuffed
Because I ate several bowls
And the dishes were plentiful
There were three dishes
I feel this was the most memorable meal
Because Lin Yi made it personally
Made this dish especially for me
Praise
And he made my favorite dish
Stir-fried leeks with eggs
I was deeply moved
You left a deep impression on me
The most memorable meal was our first one
You kept eating
The most enjoyable part was eating continuously
From start to finish
The first meal helped me get to know everyone
Then every meal and date we had together
Helped me understand him better
So every meal left a deep impression
But the most memorable was still the first one
Don't be so desperate to survive
There's an international wall ring
Aside from this meal Ling made for you
Aside from this meal Lingling made for you
Which of the other two meals left a deeper impression on you?
I'd like to know too
I think it was the first meal
When we first met everyone at Xiaowu
And began this wonderful journey together
I actually miss that meal quite a bit
It was the beginning
What I miss more is...
There was this one dinner
I think we all cooked it together
That day, each of us...
It was probably on our third day knowing each other
Yes, I thought the atmosphere was great
The atmosphere when we cooked and chatted together that night was really good
What about you?
Anything you'd like to say about the meals?
The most memorable for me was also that dinner we shared together, same as Lin
That very night
Everyone shared their heartfelt thoughts
Which brought us even closer - we've had many group meals
And some one-on-one meals too
That street food stall
Should we pack that up too?
We went to eat there once
Yes
Scouting first
That's me
To me, meals represent a very down-to-earth life scene
And then
Whether it's friends eating together
Or
Couples on a date sharing a meal
Or family members dining together
I always feel
That dining is a rather special occasion
During the meal
You can experience so many things
Look
We went from strangers to becoming close
Through sharing meals
From dining together in Sanya
To meals in Changbai Mountain
Then having Northeastern cuisine
And later gathering for hot pot
I think these are all wonderful moments
Moreover
We take care of each other
And chat freely in a relaxed atmosphere
Every time I see scenes of them together,
I can't help but laugh.
It's so incredibly amusing.
My boy can't cook,
but being able to buy food is fine too.
That's fine too.
Ha
Who cooked this?
Kevin bought it for me
I think he's trying to kill me with spiciness
What's wrong?
Spicy and fragrant
Material
What do you mean?
Jinyang, are you going all out tonight?
You think I'm the type to go all out, huh?
I know you're not the type to go all out,
that's exactly why I want you to try it.
Seriously.
Why don't you give it a try?
On the last day, that morning,
do something different from usual.
You might be pleasantly surprised.
Well said.
Actually, he's encouraging him, right?
Right?
Yes.
Give him some encouragement.
Yes, yes, sometimes people get stuck in their own way of thinking,
and can't take that first step.
You know,
when a true friend helps you with this,
I think it's a great team.
I, I...
I...
Do you have any?
I do, I do!
Create some scenarios
Like gathering everyone together
So they can have more opportunities for group interactions
I had a close friend once
She liked a guy
But didn't know how to approach him
At that moment
I just took over her phone
I'll text him
I said "Why haven't you texted him yet?"
I'm naturally impatient
Right
So I typed for her
I said
"Then just hit send"
Why not let the other person press send?
That way it shows he made the first move
The initiative should remain with him
You can give a little push
"So how have you been lately?"
Nothing much
Today's my last day
Everyone thinks he's mature and steady
I don't know why
But I'm the only one who thinks he's childish
So could you tell me more about this guy?
He's 2 years older than me
He's 20 years older than me
Tears of the Heart
Have you told him about your past?
Yes, I have.
That story is exactly like mine.
About marriage?
Yes.
That's actually good.
How is that good?
And what I want to say is...
When people share similar experiences, they understand each other. Are you the more proactive one?
Don't you think men should be more proactive?
The same theory applies to men now, okay?
If you like someone, you should take the initiative.
That's so true! I told my best friend I'd give you another chance.
Please take back what you just said.
Okay.
Waiting for your reply.
Bye bye.
Let the person involved speak.
You're the one involved.
You too.
I feel like I've always maintained a pretty relaxed mindset.
And then...
At the beginning...
It was truly an immersive experience.
This whole cabin experience.
And then...
For example, when having fun, I really enjoyed myself.
Just enjoying the present moment and atmosphere.
But...
Actually, as we got to know each other better...
Then there were more things...
I wanted to talk about.
But I think my state remained relaxed throughout.
A relatively relaxed state.
Like this.
So my state probably didn't change much.
But with more interaction...
Our conversations might have gone deeper.
Adding one plus one.
I, I...
Um, I...
Before watching the show, people probably didn't know this was our dynamic.
Right?
No idea, no idea - exactly.
Just before watching the program,
I always thought both of them gave off this vibe
that was somewhat...
hard to approach.
And they probably wouldn't...
be the type to directly express their feelings.
But after watching the show,
especially today's final date,
I realized they actually had so many passionate moments during their dates.
It was really touching.
And full of chemistry.
Yeah.
I think their relationship developed because earlier, we all...
were focusing more on our own romantic interests,
and went on separate dates,
so they didn't interact much.
But I feel they've been gradually getting closer.
Like Lao Wang just said,
it's like they're on a rollercoaster together -
slowly climbing at first,
then reaching the peak,
before rapidly descending together,
and suddenly their connection intensifies.
Didn't he just let me work?
But am I actually working now?
I'm working on something
Everyone can try to guess
I did something completely unexpected
's
show
just
Do you have any spoilers
to share with everyone?
Later, Lao Wang did something really outrageous
that made me extremely angry
We almost got into a fight
Okay
Let's watch it together
Everyone guess
No one can say who won the fight
Isn't it obvious?
It must be you
On the final confession night, we could hear singing
Thank you for watching this episode of "Half Love 3" commentary
Let's look forward to the next episode together
We hope everyone will keep following "Half Love Season 3"
Bye bye bye bye bye
"Half-Ripe Lovers 3" has aired its finale directly.
Episode 10 (Parts 1 & 2) updated at 12:00 on April 23
Witness the romantic confession night
Plus sweet couple stills
Takada Behind-the-Scenes
Post-release vlogs to be released successively
Starting April 30th
4-episode special content update
Watch the sweet couple's adorable moments