There is a feeling that you can't understand what they are saying
I think there's a big smile on their faces.
But I think the four of them get along so well.
I don't...
What?
Hello, everybody.
We are
a couple who love each other.
What's up?
Hello, everybody.
I'm Zhou Jing from Season 1, Shun Shun.
I'm Sun Muyu from Halfway Couple Season 2.
It's nice to meet you again here.
What?
Hi, everyone.
I'm Zhou Nan, a semi-skilled worker.
I'm Zhongzhong Zhong Pei Yan from Signal Season 3.
I'm Yang, the scholar in Signal Season 5.
There are candid photos of your couple on the Internet.
Kiss.
So I'd like to know
how you two ended up together.
Who? Right, who knows? Because we have many mutual friends.
The one time we attended a wedding
just the two of us went together.
And then my friend's wedding.
And then I sat down and found his friend across the hall.
And they recognized each other.
And I realized we had a lot of mutual friends.
And we first knew each other because we had mutual friends.
The one who started it first
I went to Chongqing first.
And went to Chongqing for love.
Then
Is there a nickname between you two?
That is a pig head.
Baby.
I think I'm sitting in the wrong place.
Hurry. Let's three leave now.
Oh!
I think the funny thing is
he was cooking glutinous rice balls yesterday,
In the toilet,
then suddenly he asked me
do you want to see handsome guys?
Yes, I mean...
Look at this.
Watch here.
What handsome guy?
And he walks over
he said,
I heard that men who do housework are the most handsome.
Are you here to see me?
You're here to see me?
I don't have any news.
Nothing. It's been two years since Fan Shu's arrival.
The third season has already arrived.
You see,
we are...
What? Why are you pointing at her?
You haven't made any progress now.
You're the same.
The other day, I told everyone in the group
that I was looking forward to it.
And then...
It's cooked half-cooked.
Still no progress.
You're still where you are. It's okay.
It's all right.
That's right. Good dinner is always ready.
When fate brings us, let's ask Miss Sun.
I... I'm just a little bit away from Medium 4.
Let's see if there's something different in the following.
The third one doesn't suit your taste?
Hold on.
Is to follow the rules.
You need to be one step faster
or to be in love again?
Into the river of love?
We'll catch up on the TV series first.
Let's go catch up.
See who's left. We'll...
Back to very
but he wouldn't open the door.
Give him the door.
Did anyone open the door for me?
Jealous? Are you going on a date?
I don't care about you.
When I was here,
Instead, I pretend to be calm.
That's right.
And keep watching.
My ears are already red.
Malone.
You're cool.
Oh, right.
Where are you going to play?
Just eating.
What delicious food have you had?
Seafood and Cantonese food are delicious.
Then why didn't I get invited?
How can I call you
when you are gone?
How did you know I wasn't there?
I know. It's so sour.
What are you talking about?
She's so cute.
I don't have the title.
What can I say?
That's cute.
But girls, do you think that's a minus?
Or is this stressful?
If you're in the contact phase,
this kind of behavior makes you feel a little childish.
Right.
I think so.
A little bit.
Well
I think it depends on my feelings for that boy.
If I really like him too,
but with him being like this,
I think
It's sweet.
Yeah, confusion.
You two have a point for familiarity with the feeling
yes, I can understand his feelings.
But maybe there is a better way to handle it.
Or you can just talk about it.
We haven't got the time to be angry.
Right.
But when we were in the hut,
I felt all the emotions would be magnified.
Hold it up.
Lonely gym with someone working out?
I've never seen one before.
That you've never seen them before.
They work out.
This pose is very standard.
He said that
I wanted to relax myself.
In the arena.
Oh!
He's good.
Very standard.
Is this one of these moves?
What butterfly?
Or flying birds,
or Snow White.
That's pretty cool.
The back of the forearm will be the same
numerous ingredients in milk and food.
He's standing on a death ray.
He thought the light shone on my muscles. He felt cool.
The result might be more obvious.
Like this.
Let him be the main character now!
Wow!
Why is it still here?
Look at that.
He came out,
he continued to practice.
It's mine.
Even if I come to the hut,
we are actually quite good with each other
she felt it already.
He was always by the person I wanted to know.
I want to say that
so she also likes
so he is very specific.
She and Lili are a bit alike, both of them are pretty cool.
You know, if your friend likes the same guy as you,
you two...
What would you do?
I think everyone can like it.
It depends on whether this boy is firm in his will.
When we were on the show,
qin Qing and I were having a good relationship back then.
We were going to invite a boy at the same time,
and it's the same day.
The same time.
After the invitation,
we talked about
hey,
do you mind if I invite him
then he said
he doesn't mind.
I won't mind either.
From then on,
we got closer.
This is good.
Sometimes it's good to make things clear.
Right.
I think so. Just be honest and tell us
generally, girls won't mind that much.
To be honest,
there might be more of that between guys.
Girls won't mind this much
that much.
Can you guess it?
With that smile, you went out.
Guess who he went out with?
I guess he went out
with Daydream or Yiyi.
How is your mood?
Let's go then.
Interview on the spot.
You are so sharp. Go and have a look.
Go out and have some fun.
Then come back and share with us
about your trip
what you did,
what she ate.
Who was she out with?
(She's out with Kevin.)
She went out with Kevin.
That's right.
How is your mood?
And interview her.
And interview them.
I was also surprised by them.
They got along well.
The...
It's mine.
It's me!
There's a spark
but to be honest,
before you came,
you just have very high expectations.
Really effective.
His question
It's time.
I think he's confident.
Yes. I was motivated to get a positive answer.
That's why he asked me
maybe, really maybe.
This one.
Told him I like you
are hitting on each other.
Have feelings about these things.
Is really nice.
You feel young.
And he got close to her.
He knows the details
and take the initiative to take photos.
Yes. You should pay attention to
you're not listening.
Right.
I wasn't listening.
In his
I have been watching him,
there is a feeling that I don't understand each other.
I think he's a little crazy and silly
It's just no brainer.
You have to squat all the time.
Then
the person is here.
Listen carefully now.
I'm in the water after all.
Right.
So this is a double-edged sword.
But if the guy never gets along well,
the date won't be happy.
You can watch the girls play
and then the girls are cool
yes, that's awesome!
He never learned how to surf
so I'll think of him when I surf in the future.
You're right.
The girl is awesome.
She even pulls him along.
Watch me?
Watch this.
I have...
Had a goal.
We'll be stable.
He's
he's pretty good even if he stands up the second time.
My goodness!
Wow!
He's good.
They got along well. One was encouraging them.
And the other one learns patiently.
The girls are super charming
and enthusiastic.
They look much younger now.
I think
I...
It's
all right. This one.
It should do.
That's awesome.
Wow.
He's so fierce.
So cool!
I can't.
I need him to speed up.
Hurry up and hold my hand.
I didn't expect this.
Good. I'll go.
I'll go, okay?
Drop this man.
I thought you were going to touch this woman.
I want to hold her hand too.
I want to know her.
I'll learn it.
I'll try to
she's so straight.
This girl,
my goodness.
That's awesome.
You've learned it.
One by one.
It's not uncommon for girls to mention
he's not.
After he came up here,
he said you were great.
Yes. He will encourage you
here you come. I want to see you.
It's time to show your charm.
Come on.
I think this is a good one.
There's sugar.
This 1 / 8 has sugar.
It's mine.
My eyes 1
Right.
I think they almost hugged.
They, look.
He only needs a brake.
I think there's already a romance in their conversation.
Really?
Look, I can take care of you.
The key is that you can relax when you're flirting
this one is one of the most successful fish. Go!
Wow!
One date changes a lot.
Wonderful.
We have learned it.
I don't know if I can learn it.
But you can teach her.
Wow.
Come to the dance studio on your next blind date
and ask him to do the splits?
No shoulder.
And open his shoulders.
This is something physically challenging.
But
every time I take the fitness class I gave Shun,
I will totally focus on my major.
But when I saw their date, I felt that they were not only showing themselves
It's more than an effective date.
Still talking to each other?
So,
It's true.
I have been thinking about this recently.
I think it's important to respond,
no matter which team it is,
If I vote for a player,
I want to know if you feel it,
or what.
The response is very important.
If I shoot a tree today,
and send it to you.
No, I can send it to many people.
But I sent it to you.
But you didn't respond at all.
They might not send it next time.
Great!
This tree...
This is a tree.
You're so great.
So impressive.
It's a cloud!
This must be the camera, right?
But the date...
You see,
obviously, boys and girls are not the one who takes the initiative.
It's a little short.
The girl is more detailed.
And the
the girls are more dominant.
But the good thing about guys is that they'll pick up
everything a girl says.
Yes, he will respond.
That's important.
So,
this candy tastes better.
This sweet is so sweet that
the four of you are so good.
That's right.
We only have friends.
I need to eat more today.
To have more strength?
She might make a scene at night.
Today is the day to be jealous.
Jealous?
And I think the four of them get along very well.
Because he's not hiding anything now.
In fact, he's told all his friends
that he likes chips.
Take it back to the room.
Come on.
Alas!
Someone's back.
Come on.
That usually happens around this time.
Someone came home first.
There's laughter inside.
I bought some bread.
Who are you buying bread for?
For everyone.
Wang Zhen, how do you feel?
Are you okay with them?
Are you preparing for interview?
Sure enough
there is a spark between two boys.
Sharp eyes.
Generally, if you give a relaxed answer, just say
It's not bad.
It's fine.
That you're being stepped on.
I'm so defensive.
Did Dream and Kevin go surfing?
You're back?
Yiyi.
It's my good.
Inside my heart.
Put down your bag.
Get ready for war!
When I'm so thick
maybe they think it's okay.
Has anyone returned?
No.
Look, they were waiting here when they entered the house.
Judicial Bureau.
My...
I...
Face the why?
That your mental state is not right.
They are all right.
Having sisters
you
not very...
The same dish.
Return your attention
xiao Ma has achieved her goal.
Li Yi is here.
Where did he go?
He ignored him.
I'm serious.
I'm an honest person, right?
I have no mission today.
And dishonest, right?
I have a lot of work to do today.
This is good.
So dramatic?
We actually...
Match well.
It's funny.
It's kind of funny.
She's so cute.
Xiao Ma, what's up with the chat?
Let's talk about my assist. Here comes the assist.
Yadi is here to find out.
We didn't say too much.
Just some jokes.
But I think they sound quite sincere.
Right.
Wow.
That's great.
I think it's very challenging to talk.
Right.
Many of them might be pushed.
Or they might actually pull it off.
But I think this has an advantage.
You don't have to guess.
That's right.
Come on.
No need.
I think after going on a date with the second guy
after a date with another guy
look at his condition.
You'll obviously know if it's possible.
It's me.
I want to know how Sun is jealous.
When Sun is jealous, it's the same.
Really
when we were watching Lao Ma,
we thought,
how could he do that?
He came in
and lose your temper.
Well
when the girls are around,
they are very empathetic.
Yes, they are.
But if you think you can do better,
If I take the initiative to ask
and be honest with me.
I can accept that.
Right.
This scene
he is there
he just came back.
He has no chance to tell you about it.
And in front of so many people.
Mainly because he tried his best to
the client is using the most appropriate way
to make it seem that I don't care that much.
Right.
And I think it was so emotional
It's hard for you to suppress that.
That's right.
Old Xue.
He also thinks they are having double standards.
When you were talking about Xiao Ma,
what were they talking about? So childish.
What's going on?
This guy is really...
This kind of behavior makes you feel a little childish.
Yes, I think so.
A little bit.
Really?
Now you talk about empathy?
Female.
What's your opinion?
Mr. Zhou,
Is just very good at empathizing with girls.
Right.
Do you think it should be done in this environment
In this environment.
You might have to do it differently for everyone.
Just like to Xiao Ma.
Tell him
he may find it hard
hard to accept or not.
But if you're talking directly to a guy
and you directly said it,
the reaction might be different.
You need a lot of EQ to do this.
So, I don't think
I don't think it's proper to be or not to be.
This is the most important.
This.
Today I am the nice guy. I will explain it.
I think it's better if your client says so.
Really?
Thank you for talking.
This is important.
If the person involved isn't talking about it,
that will be another feeling.
Right.
They're like the sisterhood.
This...
You
one banana.
Two people eating.
She sent them to knock on the room.
And the staff.
I want to know more people.
At the same time, I want to see
when I choose others,
kevin has learned that
Is he going to explain to him
I didn't ask you out, I'm just taking you the medicine.
And you left without saying anything.
To him,
to him.
I... I didn't come to ask you out.
It's important.
He must be confused.
He was so happy when he opened the door.
So I think he's really leaning towards Kevin at this point.
Forty-one.
He is a mature man.
He can adjust himself.
He thinks about it.
He should be able to calm down.
Instead, he had the chance to think about whether he likes him or not.
He sends him messages.
He's a little cute.
He's so tall.
Forty-one.
(This is the first time) Through the ages,
I'll adjust my attitude.
I...
Me?
That's the right thing
that's the right thing to do.
(Dream on.)
I met Jia Rong last night,
I'm very happy.
I found out who he hung out with today.
I think they're
It's a little different from ours.
They always talk to each other.
Lots of chances to communicate.
Back then, we were working on our own.
I brought a copier for you.
Okay. The color is so cute.
It's that cute, isn't it?
Yes. You don't tell everyone that.
How could it be?
How can I give you the answer?
Actually,
the signal is clear.
I think they're at another stage.
That's why they said
she needs to think about how to talk to Yinyin.
Right. Come on.
This is so tense.
The
the...
The...
It's...
Alright.
You two
something is wrong.
Your appointment is at 6: 30 a.m.
Then I can manage it just right now?
Looks a little like Yin and Yang
does it sound weird at once?
Let me send you there.
A working dinner.
I'll send you to the dinner.
What do I want to eat?
Let me order one.
I'm a teacher. That's important.
You know what he said?
Tonight, another friend of mine is the male guest in the cabin,
he was also invited by two girls.
And then
and the charming Wang
he's actually a very interesting person.
Oh,
you are showing me other boys in Amway, right?
No, it's not that.
I'm just trying
and trying to give a signal.
At least find a decent way to
Is to meet people,
with the progress,
that's your effect.
That's right.
You can't hang them up so high.
As long as there is kind feeling
you can feel the suspension bridge effect.
The
the...
The...
The
the battle is so funny.
♫ Like I'm the grass ♫
I might have a little crush
about Da Meng.
Do not tell them.
Don't tell anyone.
When I have a dream,
there's a little crush on him.
He's so cute.
All right.
We finished episode 4 today.
What do you think is the most impressive?
I like the dating of Mengdie the best.
We should be exactly the same.
Yes, he's so brave.
And special
It fits the essence of our show.
It's...
Some people
chase love
that's love.
I think the two parties are very impressive
the first is the date to save the butterfly.
I think he's really brave.
And this date works.
We'll get the answer to every question
to get the answer he wanted.
Is very important to our relationship.
I was impressed by Lao Ma in Part 2.
Old Ma and Yin Yin.
Because we might have had a similar situation before.
So this I think is very different from our period
they?
It's like
It seems that friends would tell each other what they saw.
Then maybe they'll understand the whole situation better.
And fewer misunderstandings.
Moreover, I think the catfish of this season are effective.
I think the catfish has another function.
You can try to confirm if your own feelings are that or not
or you're just someone you want to get in touch with.
I can try to contact him again.
To help you figure out what you're feeling right now.
That's right.
This is the one
Is also a feature of your half-acquaintance.
That adults are more accepting
I can have more choices,
rather than follow a path.
That's right.
I think it's possible to check on them.
He might have some time for himself
for others.
They can see things clearly.
Right.
Think about it.
Well
I think another thing in this season is that it's very different from us
this time we're in a relationship full production.
Love.
I was completely free back then,
about it?
You're on your head very fast.
Because you don't have
I have nothing else to do.
Your thoughts.
So we went in different directions.
I was just too busy.
We were all dating at about the same time.
I came back
and you haven't had anything.
You'll see the pair
this pair are talking here
then they talk here.
Where to go, yeah.
So this is all for it.
There's no other difference.
Anyway, I think just four words this season
It's good to open your mouth.
Right.
I also like how they were able to talk about it.
It's like watching a good drama.
We'll clear up any misunderstandings right away.
You know what?
What are you doing
you're probably seniors
there aren't so many scenes back then.
Have you seen others analyze it?
If we record it a second time,
I might get better.
Alright.
Thank you for joining half of Hunters 3.
This episode ends here.
We're looking forward to the next episode.
Hope you can continue to focus on Half Lovers Season 3.
Thank you all.
Bye-bye.
VIP users can update at 39PM on Tuesday and watch the show for a week first.
VIP users can watch the live show for an additional 7 hours in advance
I'll return to the club in a week for free, and exclusive to members of the reality show on Thursdays.
I'll watch half of the show with you on Friday
♪ Sweet without stop ♪