Come on.
How is it?
It's not over yet.
Look over there.
The old men are all here.
Pick me. Pick me.
Don't go.
Pick me.
Look carefully.
This cutting skill
It's transparent.
Awesome.
Let me tell you, my cutting skills
It's called "open open the stomach".
to kill the Japanese.
How is it?
I trained with you.
Let me tell you.
Join your team
not only can we protect our country,
but also improve cutting skills.
Wait.
You can't do this.
You're too tough.
I want to see soft ones.
I have one.
It's called using softness to counter strength.
Four or two, two.
Anyone who joins us
Today's dish is to overcome hardships with softness.
I'll give you one for free.
Come and sign up.
You even care about food.
Come on.
I want to sign up too.
Guys, let's go.
You're good at fighting with tenderness.
Calm down.
Everyone has a share.
What's going on ahead?
My lord,
The market ahead
He might be performing acrobatics.
Let's take a look.
Forget it.
I just took office.
The government has a lot to deal with.
Go back to the government now.
Yes, my lord.
Slow down.
What's the rush?
We need to start with basic skills.
All of you.
Now I'm going to teach you a set of swordsmanship.
The training is so hard.
Just give you some food.
It's not enough.
That's right.
Sanniang, you did play pretty.
But who can stand such a hot day?
Look at a knife.
It's so hot that I vomited my tongue.
My legs are going to break.
Madam.
Are you okay?
Get some water.
Hurry.
Stop practicing.
I'm not here to practise martial arts
but to make a living.
I thought I could make a living
I might as well go home and teach my husband.
No more practice. Let's go.
Uncle Wang, Magistrate Lou is in heaven.
Girl, the living must eat too.
Please wait.
This scar was left on my shoulder
a few days ago.
If the knife was one inch more,
it could have killed me.
Do you know who killed the first person
when the Japanese massacred the village?
The elderly and children.
Because they have the least resistance.
The pregnant woman was stabbed to death.
The scholars were buried alive.
And the survivors are regretting
I regret that I didn't pick up my weapon.
You always said that you love Xiaobao the most.
If the Japanese invade the academy,
how can you protect your child?
I...
Uncle Wang, you always praise your son for being smart.
Brother Zhao,
You just got a new wife.
Do you really think the Japanese are here?
I can live if I bow my head and obey him?
When I saw Magistrate Lou die in front of me,
I realized
how weak a person is.
But now we're all together
our power
and build a sea.
I don't want you to be heroes today.
but to teach you how to protect yourselves.
When the Japanese come,
we can protect our loved ones.
We won't regret it.
Ten years ago, the Japanese invaded us.
In order to protect his grandson,
to protect his grandson.
From today onwards,
practice hard every day
and never slack off.
Although I'm old,
I want to learn some moves too.
I want to learn too.
I want to protect Mother too.
Okay. I'll wait for you here
I'll wait for you here.
Okay.
Tie it up for me.
You can't even do the horse stance well.
how can we go to war?
If you want to practice well,
you should at least start with basic skills.
Four.
One, two, three, four.
Two, three, four.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Everyone, disperse.
You stinky tofu!
Are you playing dirty?
I didn't mean it.
I'll kill you!
Stop!
Can they go to the battlefield?
At least they're willing to learn.
You're right.
You're the best.
Why is there no one on the street?
You just took office.
You don't know.
our daily schedule is actually upside down.
Tell me the truth.
Please forgive me.
Most people in the county went to the training ground in the west of the city.
It was Xu Sanniang who brought the people to strengthen her body.
to gather the people to practice martial arts.
so I didn't come to greet you.
Private army.
How dare you!
Attention, officials.
Yes.
Follow me to capture Xu Sanniang.
My lord.
How dare you! I'm Governor Gusu.
If anyone disobeys,
will be punished for harboring.
What are you waiting for?
Lead the way.
Yes, my lord.
The new magistrate has arrived.
You scoundrels, kneel and greet him now!
Where is Xu Sanniang?
My lord.
Are you looking for me?
Go, go, go.
Criminal Xu Sanniang
and attempted to rebel.
Arrest him and put him in jail.
My lord, I am loyal to the court.
But in recent years,
there are often Japanese invaders in Gusu County.
The people are not living in peace.
I trained the villagers to fight against the Japanese.
I'm loyal.
How dare you!
How dare you deny it?
There's an army against the Japanese. It's none of your business.
Guards, take him away.
I'm sorry.
My lord, please wait.
Ma'am.
My lord, we didn't rebel.
My lord. My lord.
Xiao Bai, do something!
Stop him!
He caught your wife.
The law is the law.
The law is ruthless.
I will save her.
Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li.
Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhang, and Zhang, the late King of Jia, Wu, Wu Tan, Niu Su, Zheng Tian.
Li, Li, Li, Li, Kong, Zhu, Zhang, Wang of Jia, Wu Tan Niu.
Liu, Li, Liu, Liu.
Li Wang Li Diao
Zeng Chen.
Cao, Zhang, Zhang, Wu, Song, Zhang.
Cao, Cao, Cao, Zhou, Cao, Zhang, Zhang, Wu, Song, Zhang.
Lord Lian.
Cao Xu Chang, Huang Peng, Zhang Yanyan, Cai.
Wen.
Ma Yang, thank Liu, Xue, Bai Quan.
Lü, Lü, Li, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Huo, Wei, Xuan, Du, Wei.
Liu Yu, Zhang, Zhu, Zhu, Zhu, Zhu, Liu, Wu, Zhou, Wu, Wu.
Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Li Meng.
Yunshui Glasses (Beijing) Culture Media Co., Ltd.