Xiao Bai.
How dare you!
How dare you kidnap the execution ground!
Guards, arrest him.
and punish him.
I am the Crown Prince. Here is the imperial edict.
Are you okay?
You are the Crown Prince.
I've found out your identity.
She is General Wu Yi, commander of Taizhou.
This is her military badge.
My benefactor is such a great character.
Lord Yan, look carefully.
General recruited soldiers.
What's wrong with that?
Just now,
I didn't see it clearly.
The Crown Prince is here.
He is right.
General Xu is innocent.
Not guilty.
I'm innocent.
Great, she's fine.
Sanniang is wronged.
Let's go.
Great!
Great.
So...
So I hid my identity as the crown prince.
But I will help you find your memories.
I will.
Can I not call you Xiao Bai now?
I should call you Young Master Ban.
No, no, no.
I'm not your son.
You're just my aunt.
Here comes the imperial edict.
I accept the decree.
By God's will,
According to the imperial edict,
the Commander of Taizhou Guards to suppress General Wu Yi.
Xu Qianzhen.
Since you've lost your memory,
I feel sorry for him.
So I'll lead the Commander of Gusu
to assist the governor of Yan Wei to fight against the war.
We'll call him back when he regains his memory.
and send another Taizhou guards
and reinforcements.
Respect this.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I shall take my leave.
I misunderstood you before.
and offended you.
I’m counting on you to fight against the Japanese.
It’s my pleasure.
I will do my best.
1,900 pence.
2,100 pence.
Done.
Gosh.
It's such a tough time.
It's not easy for you and Xiao Bai.
I can finally relax.
After going through so much,
I'm sure I like him too.
He likes me too.
That's great.
When can I meet my Mr. Right?
You are so nice.
God will definitely give you
a tall and handsome man.
I don't like toy boys.
How have you been?
You know me?
Look at my cutting skills.
you'll know who I am.
How arrogant.
Do you remember when you were 15,
when we were 15?
[The fact that we met.]
Who are you?
Don't try to get close to me.
General Xu.
We'll meet again soon.
What? I haven't had enough.
The Crown Prince's calligraphy.
The Crown Prince's calligraphy?
His Highness's calligraphy.
Your favorite tofu.
The tofu is so fresh
Try it.
It's free.
The Crown Prince's calligraphy.
Your Highness.
When are you going to have a baby with him?
Today is a good day.
I'll give you a piece of meat.
Take a piece of meat.
Ma'am.
General and the Crown Prince are a perfect match.
Especially the Crown Prince.
Look at my shop.
Get out of the way!
I told you we would meet again.
Officer.
We are just a couple in Gusu County.
Please behave yourself.
Who are you?
I'm Xiao Bai, your husband.
May I know your name?
Vice Commander of Taizhou, Wei Dabao.
Under His Majesty's order, I'm stationed in Gusu County.
Do you know your name now?
Sanniang, see you at the county office.
Sanniang, you know him?
He was the one who practised martial arts with me last night.
But he seemed to be better than me.
The Japanese have gathered here yesterday.
Magistrate Yan.
Your spy didn’t even find this.
My lord.
My subordinates are all officers.
I really don't understand military affairs.
In the battle yesterday,
you used the sword technique I taught you.
Don't pretend to be strangers.
Mind your manners, my lord.
I only know the sword to kill the Japanese.
If you don't know the wind and moon,
It's awkward to say that from your mouth.
You must have learned it from that poor scholar.
But it's okay.
There's still a long way to go.
You will remember me.
He taught you swordsmanship.
Then you must know each other before.
Did we
know each other?
Are you jealous?
I only recognize you as my husband.
Since you admit that I'm your husband,
can I be promoted?
What do you want?
Over there.
What are you doing?
Go down.
I'm leaving.
Behave yourself.
No.
Officer
You made my chicken like this.
You have to pay for it.
How dare you!
Mind your chicken.
It's my lord's fault.
You...
Jiabao
You'll lose your integrity.
Who is calling me?
Who wants to harm me?
Come out!
No one can ruin their plan.
Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li.
Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhang, and Zhang, the late King of Jia, Wu, Wu Tan, Niu Su, Zheng Tian.
Liu, Li, Liu, Liu.
Li Wang Li Diao
Zeng Chen.
Cao, Sun, Zhou, Cao, Zhang, Zhang, Wu, Song, Zhang.
Lord Lian.
Royal Descendant, Royal Descendant, Royal Descendant,
Cao, Xu, Chang, Huang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Zhang, and Zhang Yanyan, Cai.
Wen.
Dragon, Qin, Liu, Song, Lü Momo, Wu Zeng.
Ma Yang, thank Liu, Xue, Bai Quan.
Ma Yang, thank you, Liu Xuebai.
Lü, Li, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Huo Jinwei.
Liu Yu, Zhang, Zhu, Zhu, Zhu, Liu, Wu, Zhou, Wu, Wu.
Yunshui Mirror (Beijing) Culture Media Co., Ltd.