The saliva is spraying on the beans.
I think
cut a piece of meat for Bai.
Xiao Bai is so skinny now.
Come on.
Look.
Pick a piece of good meat.
Okay.
Look at this piece of meat.
This is great.
I think you've changed your way.
She's considerate and gentle.
She's always gentle and considerate.
She was...
gentle.
How gentle.
Oh my god.
Dayao has a saying.
"A wise man submits to fate."
Now we are on the same boat.
I want to see your sincerity.
It's her.
You know him?
Not only that.
We're sworn enemies.
If you help me kill her,
I'll be very sincere.
You made it yourself?
It's my first time.
I don't know if it's good.
Try it first.
It must be delicious.
How is it?
It's so delicious.
I'll open the cook tomorrow
Really? Let me try.
No.
Do you have something to tell me?
Shut up. Tell me. Why are you so down-to-earth?
I just...
Let me try some vegetables first.
Wait.
It's so salty.
How did you eat it?
It's okay. I have a heavy mouth.
I like it.
Stop eating.
How did you do this?
Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
You're so careless.
Xiao Bai.
will you always be good to me?
Of course.
Whether you like me or not,
I will always...
I like it.
What did you say?
You...
Say that again.
The dishes are cold. I'll heat them up.
Sanniang.
So you mean
I like him.
Then why didn't you tell him how you feel?
I will. Thank you.
But why are you so nice to me?
I don't want my brother to have one-sided love.
Why are you here?
Go back to your mansion.
Are you punished by your uncle again?
Don't take the responsibility yourself.
The Japanese.
Back then, it was Xu Qianjing
stabbed my left eye.
I managed to escape.
I must take revenge.
This Xu Qian Tian is a skilled fighter.
and decisive.
Qingfeng Camp has fought her many times.
and failed many times.
Don't worry.
Since I dare to go to Gusu County,
I'm already prepared.
What's your plan?
Since we can't fight head-on,
we have to avoid it.
and be upright.
What do you think of this plan?
As long as 14th Prince can help me get rid of Xu Sanniang,
Qingfeng Camp will be at your disposal.
Okay.
Cheers.
I'm here to take revenge for what happened back then.
How dare you disturb me!
Fire! Fire!
Fire!
Japanese!
The Japanese are here.
My lord! My lord!
Bad news!
The Japanese are here.
What?
Do you see me?
There's a one-eyed ghost who stabbed in the heart.
Gather the brothers.
Pack up and rush over!
Yes, sir.
I won't let you escape alive.
Stop!
Sanniang.
Shoot!
Brothers, kill the Japanese with me.
Kill the Japanese together!
Hurry up.
Hurry!
Shishirou.
Where are we going?
You have to take me with you.
Why are you here?
Don't go.
You one-eyed bastard!
I can't let them go alone.
I want to fight the Japanese!
I want to be
Chen Dingshan.
You can't leave.
You can't go.
Let go!
No.
No, I won't.
Let go!
No.
Uncle.
He's still alive.
Uncle, get up.
Uncle, look at me.
I'm Suqin.
Uncle, you promised me
you will watch me get married.
You can't leave me.
Soo Geum.
Uncle.
Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li.
Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhang, and Zhang, the late King of Jia, Wu, Wu Tan, Niu Su, Zheng Tian.
Liu, Li, Liu, Liu.
Li Wang Li Diao
Zeng Chen.
Cao, Sun, Zhou, Cao, Zhang, Zhang, Wu, Song, Zhang.
Lord Lian.
Lian Wang.
Royal Descendant, Royal Descendant, Royal Descendant, Royal Descendant, Royal Descendant.
Cao Xu Chang, Huang Peng, He, Zhang Yanyan, Cai.
Cao Xu Chang, Huang Peng, Zhang Yanyan, Cai.
Wen.
Dragon, Qin, Liu, Song, Lü Momo, Wu Zeng.
Ma Yang, thank you, Liu, Xue, Bai Quan.
Lü, Li, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Huo, Wei, Xuan, Du Wei.
White Dynasty, Zhao, Zhang, Li Meng.
[Beijing] Cultural Media Co., Ltd.