What are you talking about?
Just tell me if you need anything.
I'll do anything.
All right.
Don't be so polite.
I
think a lot recently.
Fighting and killing
is not a long-term solution.
Right?
This bully
is even worse.
I'm going to
negotiate peace with Gusu County.
What's wrong?
You don't want to
with me?
No big brother.
No, no, no.
I'll give these letters
to the county magistrate of Gusu County
to the county magistrate of Gusu County.
Long Yue.
Did you drink?
I was drinking with Madam.
What are you doing?
Don’t you know?
Leader asked us to move half of the warehouse
into the car.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
He said he would send it to Gusu County.
Oh no.
This is crazy.
Everything in the warehouse was poisoned.
He just told me
he promised Governor Gusu
to surrender.
Those things
were sent to Gusu County for a banquet.
He wants to poison everyone in Gusu County.
No, help me stall Chen Dingshan.
I'm going to inform Xu Sanniang to stop this slaughter.
It's too dangerous.
If they find out,
I can't watch
hundreds of villagers being slaughtered.
I think three of our men are not here.
I guess they're in the back mountain.
You must be careful.
It's Li Renyi from Qingfeng Camp.
What?
I have something important to tell you.
What brings you here
What's the matter?
It's Mount Chen.
Chen Yashan plans to pretend to negotiate peace tomorrow
to trick the whole village into drinking poisoned wine
and eat poisoned rice.
Magistrate Lou said
they want to negotiate peace.
Chen Dingshan, you bastard!
Why should we trust you?
This...
This is the defense map of Qingfeng Camp.
Chen Dingshan will take more than 30 people down the mountain tomorrow.
I guess there will be only a few guards in the Fortress.
There are also some villagers here.
Why did you help us?
Sanniang.
What are you doing?
Why are you taking off your clothes?
Well...
I want to show you my face.
No.
Show this to me.
Isn't it normal for martial artists to have scars?
Ma'am, take a closer look.
You really don't know him?
You know me?
Oh, no.
I've never seen anyone who lost their memories.
Well, I have to go.
Are you crazy?
Sanniang.
Where are you going?
To see Magistrate Lou.
Didn't you hear what he said?
Calm down.
I don't think it's that simple.
What do you think?
I always feel something is wrong.
When Qingfeng Camp came,
when Qingfeng Camp came.
If Chen Dingshan lies to us,
we’ll catch them all.
But if Li Renyi said some villagers were kidnapped,
when Magistrate Lou brought the soldiers to save them,
they can take advantage of the opportunity
and catch us off guard?
But I think
Lee In-yi is not like that.
After all, even the ransom will be returned.
I'm worried that
he is also kept in the dark.
What do you think?
Let's not tell Magistrate Lou about this.
Suzhen, stay at home.
I'll go to Qingfeng Camp to find out the truth.
You?
Can you ride a horse?
I have my own plan.
Just wait and see.
What are you up to?
Man-yue.
What are you looking at?
Madam.
Why didn’t Long Yue come down?
He has to guard the fortress.
Why?
Aren't we going to negotiate peace?
Peace?
If you dare to ruin my plan,
Li Renyi will die.
Brothers, let's destroy Gusu County together
and let them die without a burial place.
Didn't you say you want to negotiate peace?
Why are you still fighting?
Shut up!
If anyone leaks,
I'll kill him first.
Sorry for offending you.
How dare you talk to me like that?
Let go of me!
We’re negotiating peace today.
Don’t ruin her plan.
She said
today,
to make dried meat.
He really went to Poison Gusu County?
I knew it.
Qingfeng Camp is so stubborn.
How can we not know
how could we not know?
There's a way for thieves to act like this.
A bunch of scoundrels.
A villain?
You’re so kind.
The wine is not poisonous.
Those officers should be on their way
to save the villagers.
You used me as your weapon.
You always ruined our plan.
Today, I will let you
watch those officials
die in a trap.
God is merciless.
Sanniang.
Everyone.
Don’t panic.
Master Chen is here
to apologize to you.
Folks,
I didn't recognize you before.
I'm here to apologize.
Serve the good wine.
Be smart.
We’ll attack
we’ll go in.
Understood.
Okay.
Lower your voice.
Here's your good wine.
This wine
is my precious wine.
There’s a carriage outside.
Thank you, Master Chen.
OK. Come on.
Cheers.
Wait.
Madam Xu, don't you trust me?
It doesn't matter.
What's going on?
Look at me.
You worry too much.
Sanniang, you...
Why are you doing this?
You must be tired.
Drink some water to quench your thirst.
I'm not thirsty.
Are you not thirsty or dare not drink?
Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li.
Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhang, and Zhang, the late King of Jia, Wu, Wu Tan, Niu Su, Zheng Tian.
Li, Li, Li, Li, Kong, Zhu, Zhang, the late King of Jia, Wu Tan, Niu Su.
Liu, Li, Liu.
Li Wang Li Diao
Zeng Chen.
Cao, Sun, Ma, Zhou, Cao, Zhang, Zhang, Wu, Song, Zhang.
[King Lian]
Royal Descendant, Royal Descendant, Royal Descendant,
Cao, Xu, Chang, Huang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Zhang, and Zhang Yanyan, Cai.
Wen.
Dragon, Qin, Liu, Song, Lü Momo, Wu Zeng.
Ma Yang, thank Liu, Xue, Bai Quan.
Lü, Li, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Huo Jinwei.
Liu Yu, Zhang, Zhu, Zhu, Zhu, Liu, Wu, Zhou, Wu, Wu.
Yunshui Mirror (Beijing) Culture Media Co., Ltd.