Hello!
Welcome.
What can I help with?
Hello.
(Tell me more about YUHA.)
(YUHA, an H2H member,
born on April 12, 2007.)
(Do you want more details?)
Listen up.
Hello!
I'm YUHA.
I was born on April 12, 2007.
My MBTI type is INTJ.
I'm like a strawberry in a cream cake,
meaning everyone needs me.
(So sweet)
I love playing the piano.
I started playing it when I was six,
so I've been playing it
for a very long time.
I participated in piano competitions
every year...
from the first grade until middle school.
And I won first place every time.
I'll play it for you someday.
I love hanging out with my teammates.
I laugh nonstop...
when I'm with my friends.
I laugh really easily.
(Laughing every day around her teammates)
Dumplings?
- Galbi dumplings?
- Kimchi dumplings?
(Giggling at every little joke)
(How will Ms. Giggles be like
on a reality show?)
You're so good!
How did you know?
(Laughing uncontrollably)
(Stay tuned for happy YUHA
with the most dramatic reactions!)
I think...
A-NA is the funniest teammate.
She makes me laugh without even trying.
I laugh at her jokes the most.
We have amazing teamwork.
- Who picked me?
- Me, of course.
I'm so touched!
(Endless flirting)
(They're always in their own world.)
(Sharing love,
even through tangerine slices)
(Your love makes me dizzy!)
- We're meant to be!
(May A-NA and YUHA's friendship
last forever.)
I know I don't show it often,
but I really love you.
You're totally my type.
(YUHA)
(Where it all began)
I was always very energetic,
so I loved to watch people perform,
dance, and sing.
That was what made me
want to become a singer.
(How did you join SM Entertainment?)
On my way home from school,
someone asked me,
"Do you know Red Velvet?"
Then, they explained
that they worked for SM...
and wanted to offer me an audition.
I took their name card
and gave them my number.
My mom scolded me for this.
At first, my mom was a bit against it,
but I wanted to see what it'd be like...
and what I could learn there.
So, I kept convincing my mom,
and she eventually started
supporting my dream.
(The trainee life)
I had fun dancing and singing...
since I started training.
Everything was fun to me.
When I first started learning things,
I struggled with some things, of course,
but I still have fun practicing,
even to this day.
I like to practice alone,
thinking about how I can be better.
I guess I'm the type
that tries hard in silence.
(What was the most memorable moment?)
I was in several showcases as a trainee,
and I felt so happy and proud...
when I won first place.
That was a huge motivation for me.
It pushed me to be better.
(Full of laughter)
(Great teamwork)
(Lovely)
(Tell me about A-NA.)
(A-NA, an H2H member,
born on December 20, 2008.)
(Do you want more details?)
Hello, I'm A-NA.
Hello!
"A-NA" stands...
for "I'll ace everything."
My MBTI type is INFJ...
with a strong feeler tendency.
My best trait is...
that I have so many layers of charms,
like an onion.
I'd say that I have about 82 layers now.
"Ay! Don't do that!"
"No, you can't look at anyone else."
"A-NA is the only one you can look at!"
Thank you.
(What's your favorite thing?)
I love watching horror or mystery movies.
The suspect is you,
tangerine!
(Horror?)
No, I'm not scared.
(Never mind. I'm scared.)
I don't know how I'm going to change.
(But she's still okay.)
(No, I'm not!)
I get it! Sorry!
(Stay tuned for the scared onion
who loves anything horror.)
My special talent is making people laugh.
I'm pretty funny.
(Giving a shoutout to herself)
(Wherever A-NA is,)
(the laughter spirit comes.)
She's hilarious.
I laugh a lot, thanks to her.
A-NA must've been born funny.
Are you guys going to have any?
No.
- Are we getting mangoes?
- Wait!
Wait!
(A comedy treasure is born in 2025.)
I feel loved...
when people tell me that I'm funny.
(Where it all began)
I used to dance and sing...
all the time at home ever since a kid,
so my parents signed me up
for proper lessons.
And I naturally started thinking...
that this had to be my career path.
(How did you join SM Entertainment?)
There was an audition
for SM Entertainment at my dance school,
so I was determined to give my best.
I thought I'd been rejected,
but on the next day,
(She got a call
the day after the audition.)
I was told I was accepted.
It the happy moment I can never forget.
(The trainee life)
I debuted after three years of training.
I'm a hard worker.
I've been practicing...
with a focus on showcasing my best traits.
I was complimented
at my first monthly evaluation.
I felt incredibly proud.
Until then, I wasn't sure
if I could do well there,
but that moment gave me faith
that I'd do well.
It got me more focused on my goal...
until this point.
(A reality show gem)
(A sensitive onion)
(A mystery enthusiast)
(Tell me about JIWOO.)
Hello!
I'm JIWOO.
I was born in Seoul on September 7, 2006.
My personality type is ISTJ.
I love...
traveling more than anything.
I also love watching animations.
"Just you watching this right now!"
"Would you be my friend?"
(Looking for friends to travel with)
(JIWOO's character)
I'm a natural leader,
like a class president.
Even when I'm with my teammates,
I'm the one to lead the group
through situations...
where we must make decisions.
I have good leadership skills.
Let's all start with the crop move.
- Can we start the music sooner?
- Sooner?
(The leader of H2H
to orchestrate the teammates)
(So charismatic)
Stay safe.
(Leader Duty One:
Caring for troublemakers)
Let's go!
(Leader Duty Two:
Encouraging her teammates)
(Through the challenges and hardships)
The wind may be strong,
but we're fine!
This is what dreams are made of.
(Leader Duty Three: Mental conditioning)
(The perfect leader we can trust)
She's always so attentive
and taking good care of us.
She always watches out for me.
She's so reliable.
Thank you, and I love you.
Thank you for trusting and following me.
Remember that I always love you!
Let's give it our all!
(Where it all began)
An SM Entertainment employee invited me
to an audition on the streets.
Isn't that impressive?
It was 2018,
and I was at a convenience store
with my friends.
The employee at the checkout...
couldn't stop looking at me.
Then, they asked me for my school,
division, and name.
I was young and naive,
so I told her everything.
She turned out to be
my current manager's friend.
That was how I got invited
to join the agency.
(The trainee life)
I debuted
after about six years of training.
I started training in sixth grade
at the age of 13.
I grew up doing ballet from a young age,
so I was always into dancing,
but I knew nothing
about dancing to pop music.
I still remember getting so fascinated...
on my first day as a trainee.
It felt awkward,
but I had fun from day one.
Doing things for the first time...
kept me happy throughout the years.
I had a long way to go,
but I became more interested
in this line of work...
as I started learning things one by one.
I can confidently tell you
that my hard work has gotten me here.
(Born a leader)
(An attentive planner)
(Go-getter)
(Tell me about CARMEN.)
(CARMEN, an H2H member,
born on March 28, 2006.)
(Do you want more details?)
Hello, everyone!
I'm CARMEN.
I'm from Bali, Indonesia.
Hello, everyone!
I love to sing,
play the piano, and bake.
My MBTI type is INFP.
I'm very dramatic with my reactions.
I'm happy 24 hours a day,
and I smile nonstop.
(A sunny girl filled
with optimistic energy)
So sweet!
(Even her reactions are overly happy.)
(It's okay,
even if something sad happens.)
(Always doing her best)
I can do it!
(The sunniest girl ever)
She's like a ray of sun.
She always shares positive energy with us.
She gives me bright energy.
(Every day is a sunny day
for the sunny girl.)
Be as happy as me!
(Optimistic energy shooting
through the screen)
"Hey, you, watching the camera!"
"Do you know who I am?"
"I'm CARMEN."
"Please give me lots of love!"
(Where it all began)
I always wanted to become a singer...
because my parents were musicians.
Then, watched
the K-pop singers' performances,
and I found them so fascinating...
as they sang and danced at the same time.
I knew that I had to become one.
I auditioned without much expectation,
but got accepted.
I'm so thankful.
I think I was meant to join the agency.
(What song did you sing at the audition?)
I sang several songs...
like "When This Rain Stops"
and "Like Water."
I also sang "Fine" by Taeyeon,
"Reflection," "I Have Nothing," "Listen,"
and "Into the New World."
(The songs that got her accepted)
(The trainee life)
It was tough...
when I first joined as a trainee.
Everyone else was at this level...
while I was down here.
It was hard to catch up with them.
I wasn't from Korea...
and couldn't speak any Korean,
so I couldn't talk to anyone,
even when I wanted to make friends.
I felt so lonely.
I just focused on giving it my all.
I always practice alone...
and do my best.
I'm a hard worker.
(How did you study Korean?)
My agency gave me Korean lessons...
about three times a week.
Those have been so helpful.
I worked hard, and look where I am now!
I'm always grateful for my teammates.
(Whenever she doesn't recognize a word,)
(the girls quickly help her out.)
(Whenever she looks for help,)
- Motto.
- Motto!
(the girls are there to help her
with difficult words.)
- Hometown.
I'm so thankful for them.
I love you!
I hope I can keep improving.
I am...
going to try harder.
(A girl from Bali)
(A ray of sunshine)
(A tireless hard worker)
(Tell me about STELLA.)
(STELLA, an H2H member,
born on June 18, 2007)
(Do you want more details?)
Hi, I'm STELLA.
Hi, everyone. I'm STELLA.
I'm from Vancouver, Canada.
My MBTI personality type is ENTP.
I enjoy playing the guitar and the drums.
I also love skiing and eating dessert.
I enjoy all kinds of desserts,
but if I had to pick just one,
it would be cake.
I'm obsessed with cheesecake.
I'm always smiley and chatty.
(She has fun even while waiting her turn)
IAN and I are the extroverts on the team,
and we love bringing energy
and lifting everyone's spirits.
Everyone, welcome back
to Hot Girl News today.
We have IAN.
Can you tell us why you are here today?
Because...
of filming.
This ASMR is just for you.
(The ASMR object: IAN's skin)
Can you hear the sound?
Whenever I'm with her,
I have so much fun. She's hilarious.
She was like a hot Canadian girl.
(STELLA is a hot girl
with a cheerful personality.)
(Being cute is just a bonus.)
(She's naturally gorgeous too.)
- My English has gotten rusty.
- Are you serious?
I'm going for the sheep fashion today.
(Her quirky charm can
even attract a horse.)
If I had to describe myself
in one sentence,
I'd say I'm like a cat with many charms.
"Stop!"
"Who is that girl on TV,
glowing so brightly?"
"That's me!"
(Where it all began)
When I was in kindergarten,
I went on stage for a talent show
before our parents.
I felt such joy being on stage...
that I started dreaming
of becoming a performer.
(How did you join SM Entertainment?)
After the COVID pandemic,
I moved back to Korea.
Soon, I began taking dance classes.
That's where I first heard
about the SM audition.
I wasn't sure if I could become a singer,
but I decided to give it a shot.
I remember crying...
when I got the acceptance call.
(The trainee life)
I trained for about a year and a half.
As a trainee,
I struggled
with frustration and disappointment...
whenever I had trouble
with dancing or singing.
But each time, I worked hard to improve.
While doing various group tasks,
I became more and more ambitious.
Since then,
I've regained my self-confidence,
and I still try hard to think positively.
(I can do it with a professional mindset.)
I'm really proud
that I've become a lot more confident...
and mature.
(Cute and hot girl)
(A kitty with various charms)
(I can do it.)
(Tell me about JUUN.)
(JUUN, an H2H member,
born on December 3, 2008)
(Do you want more details?)
Hi.
I'm JUUN.
My MBTI type is ISTJ...
with a bit of an emotional side.
My hobby is unwinding with a half-bath...
after working.
I love rapping and dancing.
I feel the happiest when I'm dancing.
The first genre I learned was popping.
So, it's still the genre I'm best at.
It's also my favorite genre of dance.
Let me show you a little bit.
(Upper body popping)
Something like this.
I feel so shy.
I may look cool and charismatic on stage,
but offstage,
I'm as soft as tofu.
I guess I feel the most comfortable
around the members,
which is why they say I'm really gentle.
(JUUN's two sides)
(On stage)
When she dances, she literally soars.
And I could fall in love with her.
(Offstage, she becomes softy.)
I don't know how she can be so cute...
and kind during practice.
I'm a sweet girl.
(She really is
the embodiment of sweetness.)
This is the hand gesture I do
when I'm happy.
(Her soft, tofu-like charms)
(Addictive)
(The softy's dancing on the show
is irresistibly attractive.)
(Even her dance showcase is delightful.)
(She finishes it with a witty homage.)
Keep going!
(Her passion for dance shines
even without music.)
That's it! Don't stop!
(Final footwork)
(Warning! The softy cutie JUUN is coming.)
(Where it all began)
I think I was in third grade...
when I first watched a video.
It was "ID: Peace B" by BoA.
The way she owned the stage...
left such a strong impression on me.
And I wanted
to become a singer like her too.
(BoA inspired JUUN to be a singer.)
Then, I started learning dance.
I won several awards,
and it felt incredibly rewarding
to see my own progress.
I love dancing.
(How did you join SM Entertainment?)
I wanted to express myself
through dancing,
so I uploaded...
many of my dance videos to social media.
One day, the agent sent a direct message,
and I ended up joining the company.
(The trainee life)
As a trainee,
I was determined to give my all,
and I really did my best.
There was a trainee showcase
open to the public,
and after it was over,
many people mentioned my name online.
I felt so proud to finally have my name...
known to the world.
Yes, I got first place.
I won.
(Is there something
you want to try after your debut?)
There's a song called "Only One" by BoA,
and many people associate it
with its partner dance.
I'd love to try that partner dance
with BoA.
I want to perform "Only One" with her,
no matter what.
I really want to do it.
"Attention!"
"I'm JUUN, ready to steal your heart
anytime, anywhere!"
Bye!
(A born-to-be dancer)
(Soft tofu)
(Different on and off the stage)
(Tell me about IAN.)
(IAN, an H2H member,
born on October 9, 2009)
(Do you want more details?)
It's time for an interview.
Hello.
I'm IAN, your dopamine generator!
I love hanging out with people.
My MBTI type is ENFP,
and I'd say I'm a fun-seeker.
(Extrovert IAN gets excited...)
(whenever she finds
something interesting...)
(or touching.)
I want to be an artist...
who's cool on stage
and makes everyone happy.
I tend to get really excited...
when I'm around the members,
and I think they feel the same way.
(Get ready for a dopamine rush? Let's go!)
IAN!
(A quick dopamine rush)
I'm flying!
Here I go!
(Dopamine Rush Stage One)
(Dopamine Rush Stage Two)
(Dopamine Rush Stage Max)
(With my members,
I always become so excited.)
(Simple greeting makes her happy.)
She's like an undying battery.
She always cheers me up.
I'm always grateful
for how bubbly she is with us.
(I'm so happy to have...)
(all the members' attention.)
(A shot to boost dopamine)
I need lots of your love!
"Is IAN the cutest in the world?"
"No. You're the cutest."
(Proud)
(Where it all began)
Since elementary school,
I've loved getting people's attention.
I thought it was such a wonderful thing...
to be loved by many people,
so it made me want to be a singer.
(IAN dreamed
of becoming a beloved artist.)
My parents are fans of many SM artists,
so they showed me
a lot of Girls' Generation videos.
I found them so cool
that I wanted to be one of them.
As a kid,
I was obsessed with social media.
One day, when I uploaded a short video,
a casting staff member saw it...
and sent me a direct message.
At first, I thought it was a scam...
because she didn't mention
which agency she was from.
But my mom had a good feeling,
so she told me to ask
where the agency was located.
It was in Seongdong-gu,
so I thought it could be SM Entertainment.
I thought it could be a chance
to realize my dream,
so I felt delighted.
(The trainee life)
It's been three whole years.
When I joined the company as a trainee,
everyone told me how tough it would be,
so I was a little scared.
It was so different from school,
and I realized there was so much to learn.
But when I accomplished my goals,
it felt really rewarding.
I think I'm most motivated...
when I receive compliments from others.
During my first evaluation,
they encouraged me with lots of praise,
saying, "You're a very talented girl."
"We believe you have big potential
to become an amazing artist,"
"so keep up the good work."
With the belief in myself,
I gave it my all.
(The journey toward her dream)
I practiced hard to master the basics,
and thanks to that foundation,
I've become who I am today.
(A genius idol)
(A human dopamine generator)
(A passionate extrovert)
(Tell me about YE-ON.)
(YE-ON, an H2H member,
born on April 19, 2010)
(Do you want more details?)
Hi, I'm YE-ON.
(YE-ON)
My name's "YE" means talent,
and "ON" means to build.
I'm YE-ON, and I want to achieve
many things with my talents.
I'm from Yangsan, Gyeongsangnam-do,
and I'm the youngest on the team.
I'd say she's the diamond-like youngest.
All members adore me.
(Coddling the gem-like youngest)
So cute.
- You did a good job.
- That's so cute!
(They give the youngest
unlimited applause.)
It's all right.
- It's okay.
- Don't worry.
Let's go.
Hello, cutie.
You're just so cute.
I just want to smoosh her little cheeks.
I wish I could shrink you...
and keep you in my pocket everywhere.
You're just so adorable.
(The synonym for YE-ON is cute.)
I love it.
My MBTI personality type is ISTJ.
I'm extremely rational and organized.
I'm a very disciplined individual.
I'm good at waking up early.
Sometimes, when some members have
trouble getting up,
I knock on their doors and wake them up.
We'll try harder to get up on time
so you don't have to wake us up.
(YE-ON's character)
I'm a quiet chatterbox.
(Whispering)
(Endlessly talking to herself)
What is it?
(She talks to the camera too.)
Should I make it smaller?
(Quite serious)
(It's the morning fairy's bedtime.)
(Unwavering peace)
(Shaky hands)
What are you making?
I'm making a dragon.
I'm not sure if I'm doing it right.
It's not because I want to taste it.
(She takes a bite of the tangerine.)
(Everything feels like a miracle
for this diamond-like YE-ON).
"Let YE-ON be the light of your life."
"Switch it on."
(Where it all began)
I was a kid singer and a musical actor
when I was young.
Every time I was on stage,
I felt thrilled and renewed.
(How did you join SM Entertainment?)
My parents uploaded a video
of me singing and musical performance.
The company saw them...
and messaged me to offer an audition.
I was really surprised...
and thought I had to do it.
(The trainee life)
It was last year,
when I was 13.
I had the shortest training period,
so I was eager to be
as good as the other members.
Whenever I face challenges,
I rely on them.
I want to be an artist
who always shows growth.
(The hours devoted to chasing the future)
Although I was scared about my future,
the excitement was even bigger.
I'm so excited to see...
what the future holds for me.
Let's go!
(The diamond youngest)
(Calmness)
(The morning fairy)