We feel very honored
to publish your book this time.
But, it's a pity that
Kido can't be your editor in the future.
Kido is going to...
Excuse me.
What do you mean by saying that?
What?
He didn't tell you?
We promised to transfer
Kido to our sister company
if he could get the publication right
of Mr. Gamoda's posthumous book.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Kijima.
You are a scum.
Hey, Kijima.
Let me explain myself, all right?
No need.
Actually, I have wanted to
tell all this to you.
But I haven't got a chance.
I am angry about two things you did.
The first thing is that
you made up with your
girlfriend without telling me.
When did you two make up?
When did that happen? Tell me.
This couldn't be worse.
You did that kind of thing with me.
I am so ashamed that I want to die now.
Kijima.
- I...
- Don't touch me!
Then,
what is the other thing?
The second thing is that
you were ashamed of your job,
but you still persuaded me
to write erotica.
How could you marry someone
who disdains your job?
Moreover,
to change your job, you used Mr. Gamoda.
To get Mr. Gamoda's
contract, you used me.
Did you do all these
for getting married?
Your behavior is really base.
But,
you are always such kind of person.
You always do things to please others.
You just can't do things you like.
You are unable to stick
to your own convictions.
Putting it accurately,
you don't have any conviction.
You are a person
with spiritual emptiness.
What?
You don't approve of my opinion?
You obviously had no convictions,
but you certainly have pride.
I can't be like you.
What?
Don't think that everyone
can live as you do.
You do things as you please
disregarding what others
think of you and your future.
You need not watch people's moods.
Darn!
(You have the talent allowing
you to get your own way.)
Darn!
(You have enthusiasm.)
(You are strong enough
to endure loneliness.)
(I want to be like you.)
When I was with you,
I found myself especially unlikable.
Really?
Then we finally agree on something.
You make me feel sick.
Hurry to pack up and get out of my home.
=Pornographer: Indigo=
=Episode 5
The Chain of Betrayal and Sadness=
(Throughout March,)
(Mr. Gamoda has been
suffering from rain and cancer.)
(The cold days of the
early spring are unpleasant.)
(Though warm weather
is coming with the spring rain,)
(Mr. Gamoda's health is
becoming worse and worse.)
Mr. Gamoda.
Sorry to disturb you
while you are resting.
- It's all right.
- Just keep lying down.
I am sorry that I can't
give you the manuscript.
It doesn't matter.
There are only a few
pages to be finished.
But I can't concentrate on writing.
Just revise it till you are satisfied.
We can release the unfinished version.
That is indicated in the contract.
You are really good at your work.
I am flattered.
I heard that
you would resign
after finishing this work.
Rio told me this.
In fact...
I am sorry.
This is normal when it comes to work.
It is understandable that
you want to find a better job.
Don't mind it.
OK.
But,
you are Rio's schoolmate, right?
Besides work,
could you also help him
with other things?
Mr. Gamoda.
I,
I am worried about him.
It is true that
he is good at writing.
But if he doesn't know how to relax,
he will break down
under too much pressure.
Yes.
So,
I will entrust you with him.
Please watch over him.
OK.
I'll do things for him within my power.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
I thought I could die without regrets.
Mr. Gamoda.
It's your fault, Kido.
Your rash doing
made me...
You must be responsible for your doing.
Don't worry.
I will,
I will take care of him.
I will entrust you with him.
Look out for him, please.
(It is so painful.)
(But,)
(he must be more...)
Such a good chance is rare.
I know.
But I still want to stay.
- Even so...
- Sir.
I like the books published by us.
Please let me stay.
I see.
It is true.
Our publishing house is wonderful.
The reason why we can publish such books
is that we live in the age of peace.
You big fool.
I will fulfill your foolish wish.
I will go tell the publishing house
offering you the job.
Your refusal won't cause it any harm.
Sir.
I will be off.
This can't happen again.
Just work hard in our publishing house.
Thank you very much.
(This is fine.)
Kijima.
Is Mr. Gamoda fine?
Has he been in a coma for two days?
Why haven't you contacted
me immediately?
You are noisy.
You look pale. Have you got any sleep?
It's none of your business.
Don't push yourself
too hard. Have a rest.
OK?
No, I won't.
All right. Go to have a rest, OK?
What if something bad
happens during my sleep?
Don't worry.
I will wake you up
once something happens.
Let me take your place, will you?
If anything happens,
you can ring the bell.
Got it.
You are awake?
Have you fallen asleep?
Yes. For a while.
I want to apologize to you.
I am sorry for many things.
I wasn't honest with you.
You need not apologize.
I was wrong to have
expectations for you.
You had your reasons.
I understand.
Kijima.
Kido.
Thank you for coming here.
To be honest,
I feel I might not be able to hold on.
I still have many things
to tell Mr. Gamoda.
I ever imagined
what an ideal father should be like.
Now I know it is
a person like Mr. Gamoda.
He loves the world that I love dearly.
He is willing to understand me.
After I told him this,
he burst into laughter.
He said if I have had a father like him,
I would not have become a writer.
Right.
I don't know what I should do.
Five days ago,
Mr. Gamoda began to
have difficulty in speaking fluently.
That made me realize that
words are slipping away
from his mind
and...
they will never come back again.
I feel so painful.
But,
I guess Mr.Gamoda no longer needs them.
Mr. Gamoda has finished his manuscript.
I am keeping it for him.
But I might be busy
for some time to come.
After I settle all matters,
you can come to fetch it. All right?
OK. I got it.
(When dawn broke,)
(Mr. Gamoda passed away
silently in deep sleep.)
♪In the pouring rain of that day♪
♪I forgot to open the umbrella
possessed by surging emotions♪
♪I could not help
thinking of my mistakes♪
♪And wandered in some unknown place♪
♪Language is powerless♪
♪Tenderness is invisible to eyes♪
♪You said you would
love me even if it is a sin♪
♪Even if the sight
of my back is tainted♪
♪You keep telling me
you will help me go forward♪
♪Luckily, you are living here♪
♪At this moment, I only feel joy♪
(This is a work of fiction.)
(The Final Episode)
(There is also the)
(mourning apparel genre, right?)
We can't do this.
For me, you are someone special.
(I also want to give him support.)
Darn!
Take care.