[Life and Desires in Joseon]
[Erotic Paintings]
Why does my heart ache?
[Baek Na-gyeom] It's clearly
the first time I've seen this painting
Why does it feel so familiar?
Why does my heart ache?
[Servant 1] Master Seung-ho
The erotic painting artist you asked about
I found out
His name is Baek Na-gyeom
He was picked up by a brothel madam
and adopted as her son
Although he painted the erotic painting collection under a pen name
For some reason
he said he would no longer paint
[Seung-ho] No longer paint?
It seems I must go myself
and make him paint erotic paintings again
[Yoon Seung-ho]
[Baek Na-gyeom]
Who are you?
Are you Baek Na-gyeom?
Yes, and you are?
I really like
your paintings
Paintings?
I don't know what you're talking about
Paint erotic paintings for me
How about it?
I am not a erotic painting artist
This... person
is the erotic painting artist!
I'll provide you with food and lodging
and you paint erotic paintings for me
Yoon Seung-ho, the eldest son of the Yoon family,
at any time, day or night,
prefers men.
I heard his wrist was broken by my father.
He is truly the most unruly scion in history!
What should I do?
No...
I can no longer paint.
Why is it a blank sheet?
I...
I will no longer paint erotic art.
Why?
I cannot say.
Your eyes are intact,
your ten fingers are complete.
Why can't you paint?
Do you want me to gouge out your eyes
and break your ten fingers,
so you have no reason to paint again?
I don't have that kind of patience.
You remember this.
Open the door, sir!
Let me out!
Sir!
Sir...
He actually wants me to paint erotic art for him.
I have clearly sworn
never to paint such filthy pictures again.
I heard that this kind of paper
is only used by the painting academy.
Using such expensive paper
to paint such vulgar erotic scenes.
I have sworn to stop painting.
Why... did I pick up the brush again...
How ridiculous.
Clearly trembling with fear,
insisting on never painting,
yet now you paint so lewdly.
Are you trying to run away?
"A long journey of ninety thousand miles,
bidding farewell to a beloved one."
- Please give it back
- Jeong In-heon?
Such a poor piece
I'd be ashamed to even call it plagiarism
That's not true!
The poet is extraordinary
Someone like you, indulging in male beauty,
has no right to judge
It's precious to me
Please give it back
That precious?
- Thank you
- No
- Thank you...
Wait until you finish your painting
Then I'll return it
Go and find out
The person who wrote this poem
is named Jeong In-heon
The poet is extraordinary
Someone like you, indulging in male beauty,
has no right to judge
What kind of extraordinary person is he?
I'm so curious I can't sleep
[Boy] Sir!
The flowers are beautiful
So I picked them for you!
[In-heon] What beautiful flowers
Thank you
You're welcome
Are you by any chance Mr. Jeong In-heon?
The young master of the Yoon family
Why would you condescend
to visit my humble home?
Do you know Ja Ro-gyeom?
He studied under me
I saw he always drew vulgar pictures
So I reprimanded him
He had your poem with him
I was honored to read it
Truly a masterful work
Are you teaching children to read?
They were born ignorant and lowly
Teaching them is futile
A man of your talent
Teaching in a remote village is a waste
To be honest
I am waiting for the right opportunity
I will make you successful
Where is it?
My lord, forgive me.
What is it?
I was flustered and spoke without thinking.
"Someone like you, indulging in male beauty,"
Didn't you say that?
Those words were not from my heart.
I hope you will be lenient.
Why did you return it to me so easily?
[Xiaojin] Young master.
Mr. Jeong In-heon is here.
Sir!
Sir, why are you here?
I heard from Young Master Yoon.
You spoke of me
with much praise.
What?
With your help, I got this opportunity.
I'll take you to your room.
You're all smiles, aren't you?
Do you like this scholar?
Why did you call for the sir?
If you agree to paint erotic pictures,
I will grant him an official post.
Even without your help, the sir will surely...
Come to my bedchamber tonight.
I'll be waiting.
The sir will understand me too.
What... what are you doing?
Young Master Min, although I'm not interested in commoners,
with your looks, it wouldn't hurt to have some fun.
Please don't.
Do you want to join in too?
[Jihwa] Seungho!
That's going too far!
A commoner might find it hard to fit in.
Why is he always looking at me?
That's not it.
Don't misunderstand.
He's not looking at me.
He just wants to see the painting.
Mr. Inheon?
Why are you so impatient?
Lord Seungho?
Why am I dreaming of Lord Seungho?
Is Nakwon here?
Yes!
I was really startled yesterday.
I'm actually worried about you.
Why worried?
I heard that Yoon Seungho
frequently mingles with men and indulges in male pleasures.
You're not going to
paint such lewd pictures here, are you?
Of course not.
You
wouldn't do what I despise, would you?
My lord, I don't know why.
I went out for a walk and came back to find it like this.
Did anyone enter this room today?
I saw Lord Jeong Inheon walking in the courtyard.
It wasn't him!
He was with me the whole time.
With you?
Yes!
He was walking with me all morning...
I remember you
never wanted to paint.
What?
Would you go to such lengths to refuse to paint?
It's not that...
I believe you.
Perhaps it's a blessing in disguise.
I don't want to paint.
But
I'll do anything else...
Have you never thought
I have the ability to make Jung In-hyun successful and famous.
And I have ways to destroy him.
Even if you are thrown into a well and die,
no one would dare suspect me.
Seung-ho, did you beat that guy to death?
Yes.
Oh my, those slaps were loud.
Right, that's the Yoon Seung-ho I know.
Ji-hwa, you,
are truly scary.
Don't move.
It's fine without medicine.
Oh no, that won't do.
Young Master Seung-ho instructed me
to apply it until the scab falls off.
The master ordered that?
Are you very afraid of Young Master Seung-ho?
Because he suffered great trauma,
his emotions fluctuate.
However,
he seems to care for you.
If he truly cared for me,
why would he hit me?
I have said it many times.
Don't use these people of unknown origin.
Secretly hire painters from the painting academy.
No matter how well you treat these lowlifes,
they only become more demanding.
What's going on? How is he unharmed?
Where are you going?
You may go home for today.
Honestly, as a noble, indulging only in male beauty,
how could he know how to care for others?
Eat.
It's fine, my lord.
Eat when I tell you to.
Yes...
Come to my room today to paint.
Why don't you paint my face?
This face.
Lingering
Why are you so impatient?
Why are you coming closer to me...
Too close...
Tomorrow
I will definitely finish the painting, my lord.
Then you should rest...
Why should I believe you and let you go?
When did it start?
Please let me go, my lord!
Since when have you been so impatient?
Tell me quickly.
Someone is outside!
What if that voice is Lord Inheon?
What if he saw everything?
I need to go find the teacher.
Lord Jihwa?
My lord, what do you need from me?
It's nothing.
Seeing you so absorbed in painting is very gratifying.
So I came to praise you.
But why
is the painting still not finished?
I heard from the servants
that you stayed in Seungho's room all night before returning.
Someone saw it?
You really can't hide anything.
What?
How did it feel?
I'm asking you, how dare you be so audacious?
How did it feel to spend your first night with a noble!
[Maid 1] Oh dear, oh dear! What shall we do!
Oh dear, what shall we do!
Do you think I would believe such words?
Should we wake up Master Seungho?
Tell me the truth!
Don't lie!
I am not lying, my lord!
It's true!
What exactly
How could I, with this humble body, seduce Yoon Seung-ho!
My lord... I beg you...
The day I poured water on that damned erotic painting,
you should have been half-dead already!
Oh my,
Ji-hwa, you're in quite a good mood.
Seung... Seung-ho.
A spacious mansion,
countless servants,
abundant wealth,
and even a powerful family.
He has everything I don't.
A vulgar wretch like him doesn't deserve these.
If I can just find his weakness and manipulate him,
all of this will be mine.
Ouch!
Have you lost your mind!
You humiliate me for the sake of such a lowborn?
Out of past affection, I'll let it go.
Get out now.
Yoon Seung-ho,
you can't do this to me.
I was the one by your side when you were sad!
I know you've planted spies.
Anyway, there's no one in this house I can trust.
Ji-hwa, aren't you well aware of that?
My lord...
Have you heard the rumor that Yoon Seung-ho is addicted to male beauty
and even seeks out lowly people?
This is the first I've heard of it.
Just thinking that you had an affair with Min and I still shared your bed
makes me shudder!
So such rumors exist.
It seems I must live up to everyone's expectations.
The young master is leaving.
Escort him to the gate.
Yes, my lord.
Thanks to you lately,
I've been having quite an interesting time every day.
S-Sir!
Sir!
I did all this for you, sir.
Drawing those obscene works.
All for me?
- That's because you're naturally lustful.
Going in and out of Yoon Seung-ho's room every night.
Was that also for me?
He said if I drew erotic paintings,
he would make you successful.
Enough!
Without that vulgar man's help,
do you think I couldn't have made it in officialdom?
That's not true.
That's not true, sir!
I don't want to hear anymore.
[Young Master 1] My father brought back a fine wine from Qing.
Young Master 2] Ah, then I'll prepare some good side dishes.
Come, have a drink.
S-Sir!
I heard you're at odds with that erotic painter Ji-hwa?
What about that man named Na Gyeom?
Is he that enticing?
Where did that precious strong liquor from Qing go?
If you drink that strong liquor,
you'll be dead drunk.
[Young Na Gyeom] Sir,
why don't I have parents?
They abandoned me because they hated me, right?
Na Gyeom,
look at the moon.
The moon is following us.
The moon always follows people.
Sir, you don't even know that?
Instead of studying, you only focus on painting.
When did you become so clever?
I thought the moon followed us because it likes Na Gyeom.
Because
You're a particularly lovable child.
Sir?
Sir...
Why don't you understand my heart?
I like you...
Sir
-It feels strange.
-Why?
-It feels strange...
-It feels strange.
-Why?
-It feels strange...
It's itchy.
I don't know either.
What do you want me to do?
Okay.
I'll help you.
Mr. Inheon.
I like you...
I love you...
Get up.
Ah...
Come.
Why does my body hurt so much?
Come, drink this.
What is this?
Master Seungho had me prepare it for you.
Why would the young master...
He also told you not to forget the new painting you need to do.
New painting?
Drink it while it's hot.
Will it make my body feel better?
I like you...
Mr. Inheon...
Amazing!
You hit it, Seungho!
So the young master is also skilled in martial arts.
Let's go check the front, let's go.
I know you're not
You came to me after reading my poem.
Of course, who would visit you for such crude imitation?
Giving such shoddy poems as gifts,
Your face is truly as thick as a city wall.
What's the point of writing well
for an illiterate brat?
I heard you promised Luo Qian
to help me get an official position.
It seems the rumors about you meddling with lowlifes are true.
A poor scholar
with neither wealth nor status,
how can he be swayed by gossip?
So reckless and willful,
you'll never amount to anything, sir!
This time, you must pass the imperial exam.
Damn it...
The wild boar Seong-ho killed is really big.
Soon, he'll probably be able to shoot a tiger too.
Damn it.
- What? - I said Yoon Seong-ho.
When it comes down to it, he's good for nothing.
If you need help, come to me.
Wait for me!
It must be a dream.
Sir!
What if Lord Seong-ho
tells everything to Sir In-heon?
Lord Seong-ho.
Come in.
Is the erotic painting finished?
Don't you have an unfinished erotic painting?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't you remember?
Yesterday you were crying and saying you liked me,
but today you push me away?
I said I love Sir In-heon,
not you!
Yes, that's right.
It seems you only just remembered.
Could it be...
Did you tell the master everything?
If you hadn't pretended to be the master,
this would never have happened!
No!
I loathe you!
Loathe me
That makes me a bit aggrieved.
Since I'm loathed,
I might as well go all the way.
I'm going to kill Jeong In-heon.
You can't!
Move aside.
Please, you can't.
Whenever Jeong In-heon is mentioned,
you act like a senseless, rabid dog
and make a scene!
I always thought you were a good person.
Because I knew you were in pain,
I tried to understand your recklessness.
But... it was all an excuse!
You're insane!
I knew you would come.
Please tell me
about the Yoon Seung-ho household.
The families that were close to the Yoons
were all implicated in the rebellion and lost their heads.
Do you think you can remain safe?
Except for Yoon Seung-ho's father,
Yi Chang-hyeon,
Lord Yoon Chang-hyeon.
He was a first-class contributor
in purging the rebellion.
That's how Lord Yoon
rose to high office and advanced rapidly.
Isn't that so?
I already know all this.
Listen, the interesting part is
since that incident,
Lord Yoon doesn't even dare to breathe loudly in front of Yoon Seung-ho.
Could it be that Lord Yoon
has some leverage held by Yoon Seung-ho?
If not,
why would he let that
eldest son run wild like this?
Bringing such shame to our family?
As long as you can
hold that leverage in your hands,
success and prominence
will be within reach, won't they?
What on earth is it!
Sir,
run away now!
Lord Seungho might kill you!
Na-kyum,
I want to stay here.
do something for me.
What?
Keep drawing erotic paintings.
Stay by the young master's side.
Tell me everything he does.
That will be helping me.
Is Na-kyum not in his room?
Shall I go look for him?
Never mind.
Why does it seem like
he's the one who got hurt...
You're insane!
I loathe you!
Did I go too far?
Na-kyum, you'll help me, right?
Yes...
Baek Na-kyum,
pull yourself together.
You're staying here for the teacher.
Why?
Oh my,
Seungho, isn't this you?
No wonder I haven't seen you around lately.
Why are you hiding that commoner
like a treasure?
What?
Is that guy
someone special to you?
What nonsense are you talking?
Just because I said a word to him,
you kissed me.
Isn't it?
I see.
He's so strange.
Forget it, he's always been like this.
Don't take it to heart.
What's the matter?
Let go!
What are you doing?
What are you going to do!
Please don't do this!
Ah!
If we keep fighting, someone will die!
Stop it!
The lofty Yoon Seung-ho
Actually likes this commoner!
What does this mean?
Master Seung-ho likes me?
Ah, how interesting.
Oh, by the way,
Master Seung-ho
really values Ra-kyum's paintings.
[Maid] Master Jihwa
has come several times since then,
but I heard he was turned away each time.
Oh, show us the painting too.
Let's see how good it really is.
Ah... you flatter me.
What kind of herbal medicine is this?
It's the medicine Master Seung-ho drinks every day.
Is the master unwell?
Hey, young master!
Come with me.
The lofty Yoon Seung-ho
Actually likes this commoner!
This fabric is too thin.
Bring better ones.
[Cloth shop owner] Oh my,
it's too expensive for a servant.
He's not a servant. Bring the best.
Oh my, yes sir.
Why is your face so red?
Ah... it's... nothing!
Ah... n-nothing!
My lord, this robe is too expensive...
Are you worried I'm spending too much?
Instead of fretting over my silver,
focus your mind on me.
My lord, Inspector Yin has returned.
It's not a tomb.
In a shrine full of wooden tablets,
why perform such a grand bow?
[Changxian] Long time no see.
Is this how you greet
your father?
When your name tablet is enshrined here,
I will kneel until my knees are raw.
I heard you pulled strings
for an unknown scholar,
opening a back door for him.
Indulging only in carnal pleasures with men,
why suddenly meddle in politics?
How can you say 'indulging in carnal pleasures with men'?
That's far too harsh.
Only if you fulfill your duty as the eldest son
can you inherit the family's power!
Are you afraid that the plot to rebel
will be exposed?
Silence!
Do you truly wish to die?
Kill me then.
If I die, the whole world will know
that the traitor's document bears father's name.
Do you think if this is exposed,
only I will die?
Don't forget, thanks to whom
you enjoy your current power.
Why must I
revitalize the family and inherit power?
Because of you,
I still live in nightmares.
You were born wild and unruly—who's to blame!
Even a stray dog knows
where it belongs.
You wretched creature who can't tell right from wrong!
How dare you call yourself human?
You actually favor such base things.
You
should never have been born.
My lord!
How is his condition?
[Doctor] It's a case of internal depression.
It's blocking the flow of qi and blood circulation.
causing him to lose consciousness.
I'll prescribe some Jiawei Wendan Decoction
to help calm his mind.
Take it after each meal.
Okay.
Let go! Let go!
Young master, young master!
Young master.
You
should never have been born.
How could you look at your own child
with such a cold gaze?
He must be very lonely.
Can you paint a picture for me?
What flower is this?
It's peach blossom.
Watching the falling peach blossoms
feels like the snow that piled up all winter
is melting.
My heart becomes warm.
Every spring,
I go with the sisters from the brothel
to buy Spring Festival couplets.
When I hold the couplets and look at the peach blossoms,
only then do I feel I truly hold spring in my hands.
I hope you live comfortably.
Please, you can't.
Do you like Jeong In-heon that much?
If he passes the highest exam,
do you think he'll take you away?
That's impossible.
I...
only wish for Mr. In-heon's success in his official career.
Sir,
Luo Qian!
You're about to take the imperial exam, right?
Yes.
Did you find out anything?
No.
No?
Inspector Yoon was here yesterday, I know that.
And you say no?
After colluding with Yoon Seung-ho,
have you developed real feelings?
What?
I thought you'd do anything for me.
Changed your mind so soon?
Sir,
I like you...
Shut up!
Since you've done such a lowly thing,
you should at least have found out something!
Sir will surely
top the exam.
Take care.
Pour me a cup.
This is liquor from the Qing dynasty.
I heard Seung-ho doesn't want to see you?
My bond with Seung-ho is extraordinary!
While you were being turned away,
rumors have been flying around.
I heard that lowborn became Seung-ho's lover.
Just kill him.
Killing a lowborn
is a trivial matter, isn't it?
I know him best.
No matter what he does, I can accept it.
Here!
Why are you lingering by the door?
I want to...
Spit it out.
So frustrating.
I want to, before Sir In-heon leaves for Hanyang...
I'll personally bring him a meal.
Huh?
Mr. Zheng left early this morning.
Didn't he tell you?
He did.
I forgot!
Since the master has left,
I have no reason to stay here anymore.
Luo Qian,
Luo Qian, this painting
was found in Mr. Zheng's room.
It's yours, isn't it?
Yes.
Mr. Zheng Renxian
left early this morning.
Understood. You may go.
Also...
Someone left this letter at the door.
Father!
[Ten years ago]
Father, let me out...
Father!
I am innocent!
I am truly innocent!
I did nothing wrong!
The letter says he saw him.
Young master,
your body hasn't recovered yet...
Do you think I wouldn't recognize your handwriting?
I didn't mean to anger you with the past.
But Seungho,
you are the one who changed.
I only wanted...
to remind you of the past,
so you would know who truly understands you!
I can forgive all the insults you've given me,
but I can no longer endure this pride and wait bitterly.
I like you, Seungho.
Don't make me more miserable.
What do you know?
If you truly like me,
you shouldn't have done this.
Father!
We're just friends!
You misunderstood!
That child and his family
all died because of me.
Because you knew
even though I witnessed
them die before my eyes,
if I received a letter about it,
I would surely come out to meet.
So
you used me.
That's not true.
That's not true...
Don't harbor feelings of love for me,
because it won't be reciprocated.
Watch where you're going!
I left without saying goodbye.
That's not
Milord,
Milord!
Milord, are you alright?
He looks very ill.
I'm afraid he's delirious with fever.
I actually hoped that today,
the one who would say they like me
would be you.
The day you mistook me for Jeong In-heon
and fell into my arms,
the way you confessed you loved me,
why does it keep lingering
in my mind?
Jihwa said I made him miserable.
Now it's my turn.
You've made me restless.
Don't go.
Impossible.
Milord actually likes me?
[Deokjae] Milord, you've arrived.
Is he dead?
Should I kill him?
No one saw it,
no one heard it.
Everyone will think
he ran away.
We can cut off his head
so no one recognizes him.
We can also gouge out his eyes
and cut out his tongue.
Throw him into the mountains.
So he can never be a spring painter again.
The rumors are rampant.
I heard that commoner
became Seungho's lover.
Just kill him directly.
If only he disappears...
Don't harbor feelings of love for me.
Because there will be no return.
If he dies...
Will Yoon Seungho come back to me?
If you truly like me,
you shouldn't do this.
It's all ruined by me...
Even without him,
Yoon Seungho won't come back to me!
Where is the person?
I let him go.
What?
Just kill him to silence him.
Why make things so complicated!
If Yoon Seungho finds out,
do you think he'll let us off?
Young master,
Before abandoning him, I warned him
not to speak of it.
Is there anything else you need?
What are you doing!
He knows it was us.
A family that can betray even its master
must be killed.
Na-gyeom...
Is Luo Qian here?
Yes, young master!
Young master, are you feeling better?
Where is Luo Qian?
Seems like he left...
And I poured out my heart like that...
Go find Luo Qian and bring him back!
If Yoon Seong-ho finds out about today,
you're dead for sure.
Lord Seong-ho...
I miss you so much.
[Sina] Luo Qian!
Luo Qian
I heard Luo Qian is at the brothel.
Luo Qian!
Where is Luo Qian!
What are you doing!
Move aside!
Luo Qian!
Luo Qian, get up!
My lord?
I didn't expect you to leave so quickly.
Scared off by my confession
and fled overnight?
I didn't flee...
If not fleeing, then what? Tell me!
I can't say.
Finally rid of me, happy?
I was wrong.
Seong-ho
Are you in there?
What is it?
Is Luo Qian locked inside?
If nothing, get lost.
This Luo Qian
didn't flee at all.
What?
Looks like Ji-hwa did it.
He said he would kidnap Luo Qian.
I thought he was just talking.
Didn't expect he actually had the guts.
Don't be too angry.
At least he came back with all limbs intact.
You...
Why did you tell me this?
Lord Seungho...
I'm so scared...
My lord...
We can cut off his head
so no one recognizes him.
Or gouge out his eyes
and cut out his tongue.
Throw him into the mountains.
So he can never be a erotic painting artist again.
I was wrong...
It was my fault.
Please spare me.
Lee Jihwa, come out!
If you dare touch Nakyum again...
No.
If you shamelessly
show your face before me again,
I will definitely kill you.
You can still laugh?
Yoon Seungho wants to kill me.
Sorry.
How did Yoon Seungho find out?
I killed that servant with my own hands.
Then
who else could it be?
Nakyum?
That's why
I told you to act more decisively.
Help me.
Yoon Seungho will kill me.
I
have a plan.
Because of you,
my emotions are no longer my own.
Nakyum,
you must get well.
Master Seungho?
Nakyum!
Sina, what are you doing here?
I don't know what kindness Seungho-nim has taken into his head to ask me to look after you.
I don't know why you're here either.
But don't stay here any longer.
Come with me.
I can't.
What did you say?
Because...
I have to stay here.
Why?
Only if I stay here
will Master Seungho help Lord Inheon get his official position.
Lord Inheon can become an official without your help.
So come with...
I'm fine, Sina.
You
have another reason, don't you?
Sina.
Master Seungho said
he likes me.
He dragged me here by force and kept bullying me...
But he said he likes me.
Strange, isn't it?
The people here
also say the master cherishes me.
I didn't believe it at first...
But
seeing him speak so sincerely
about his affection for me...
Even though I don't want to like him,
I can't help but be moved...
I want to stay
by Master Seungho's side.
Don't even think about taking him back to the brothel.
Nakyum
will only be unhappy if he stays with the master.
Milord...
You look better.
Are you so happy to see a woman?
Not a woman, it's Heena.
I'm sorry.
She grew up with me.
She's like a real sister to me.
You're getting angry.
Looks like you're much better.
Thank you.
For letting me see Heena.
I thought you wouldn't make it.
Go back to your room.
Don't
leave me again.
I won't leave you...
I like you.
Lord Seungho.
Nakyum...
Staying by your side brings misfortune.
Let me go! Let go!
Look closely.
If you're a man,
your yang energy
should go where it belongs.
[Ten years later]
Seungho?
What are you doing!
You wouldn't dare kill a noble's son, would you?
Useless thing.
You'll bring misfortune to everyone.
Nakyum.
Let's go get the spring couplets.
[Gisaeng 1] Heena, a guest has arrived.
Are you Heena?
Yes.
What brings you here?
My name is
Lee Ji-hwa
So beautiful
I came to buy spring couplets.
[Writer] A commoner posting spring couplets?
Sir!
Come, have a seat.
[Great luck at the start of spring]
Who told you to write spring couplets in Hangul?
I was afraid this guy wouldn't understand!
With such little skill,
you dare to dream of making a living with a brush?
No wonder you're stuck on the streets.
Seong-ho, what are you doing?
Why buy spring couplets
from such a half-baked person?
Only with spring couplets can we drive away bad luck.
Sir,
maybe we should leave.
Give me the brush.
May disasters vanish like spring snow,
and fortune surge like summer clouds.
This is the first time I've seen
such a famous line.
Does it make you that happy?
Happy!
I really like it.
Sir!
Can I go see Sister Heena?
You want to go to the brothel?
I want to show off the spring couplets.
Sisters!
No-gyeom!
[Gisaeng 2] How have you been lately?
I heard you're staying at that noble's house.
Well, he's not exactly a spoiled brat.
I heard he's a playboy
and a lecher.
Hina worries about you all day long...
No need to worry.
This kid, by my side,
a lecher and playboy,
is doing just fine.
Just kidding.
Maybe because they're your sisters.
The way you read the room
is exactly like them.
I apologize.
- It's fine.
He says that often.
I'm used to it.
When did I ever say that!
Are you trying to deny it?
Didn't you call me a lecher?
No... that's because!
Why are you teasing me?
I'm not teasing you.
You said it yourself, kid.
I don't remember.
Luo Qian...
Sister Hina, what's wrong?
I heard Mr. Jeong In-heon is dead.
How is that possible?
He went to take the civil service exam.
Luo Qian, listen to me.
It was Yoon Seung-ho.
He killed Mr. Jeong.
That can't be.
Lord Jihwa told me.
He said you're already in his grasp,
so Jeong In-heon is useless.
So he simply
killed him...
He said Yoon Seung-ho said it himself.
Lord Jihwa is lying.
No way.
Impossible!
Captain, please come with us.
M-Master...
Constable! What are you doing? Get lost!
It can't be...
Impossible.
[Official] It looks like a servant who escaped from the mansion.
So we called you to confirm.
That's right.
He was found in Jeong In-heon's house.
Strangely, this servant
wore a gat and a robe,
a robe similar to Jeong In-heon's.
He also wore glasses.
Where is Sina!
Sina went out.
Where did she go!
Tell me where she went.
Because the young master who often visits came for her.
Who!
I think...
his name is Master Jihwa.
One...
Rogyeon?
Master Jihwa...
What are you doing?
Sina.
I am not Jihwa.
How could you trust someone so easily?
Master Min!
What is going on?
Jihwa.
And there's something more interesting.
Go inside.
What about the aphrodisiac?
Did you give it to him?
That guy's thing...
Can last three days and nights
Oh dear
This all started because of you
How could you be missing
I never had such a thought...
Really
Didn't you ask me to help you?
This is all because of you
I never intended to
What are you doing?
Do you want me to undress you?
No...
This shouldn't be!
What should I do?
What should I do!
Go find...
Master Shenghao
Has Luo Qian not returned?
What have you done...
Where is Luo Qian!
Do you like him that much?
In your heart
Is there no place for me at all?
Stop talking nonsense
Tell me where Luo Qian is!
It's all because I like you too much
I was wrong
Please save Luo Qian
Where is he
In the abandoned wooden hut outside the south gate
Hey!
Ah, awake!
Give me another aphrodisiac
Here you go
Damn it!
This kid is crazy!
Help him up
How is it?
Are you feeling all hot and bothered, dying to get comfortable right now?
Of course!
I've already taken several aphrodisiacs.
Ah...
Is this the lips that Yoon Seong-ho sucked?
Jihwa is nowhere to be found.
Don't worry.
She's probably holed up in her room, biting her nails in a corner.
Yeah, let's just play among ourselves.
I really can't hold back anymore.
Hold on tight.
Master Min, please finish quickly.
I can't take it much longer either.
Seong... Seong-ho...
You know the consequences of killing a noble, don't you!
The matter of you killing Master Jang...
I'll take care of it for you!
Seong-ho, I didn't do anything...
Ah, really,
I didn't do anything...
Listen to me, these things...
It was all Jihwa's doing.
It was Lee Jihwa!
Jeong In-heon!
Don't you want to know why his glasses are in my hands?
Don't you?
Ah, damn it, listen to me!
Na Gyeom!
My lord...
Na Gyeom, you're awake?
I've been waiting for you...
Why did you come so late...
I'm late, I'm sorry.
I knew you would come.
So I wasn't scared at all.
I'm sorry.
Please save me...
All of this
wasn't it all done at your bidding?
How can you
not even handle such a small matter?
Just break up
Yoon Seong-ho and Ja Ra-gyeon.
Why should I do as you say?
Just spread the word
that I was wronged by Yoon Seong-ho.
Ja Ra-gyeon will surely no longer trust Yoon Seong-ho.
No
That sounds boring.
Ja Ra-gyeon...
Don't you want to toy with him?
Now that sounds interesting.
I still need him, so spare his life.
Quickly
Save me
Young master
This will harm your health.
I'll take care of him; you go rest.
Aren't you cold?
My lord
What's wrong?
I
did not believe
that you killed Mr. In-heon.
You ran out of the brothel immediately.
And you expect me to trust you?
I thought it was impossible...
But what if it's true?
I wanted to ask quickly.
So I've been
waiting for you to come.
Heung
Don't try to recall that day.
Mr. In-heon
was trapped for a few days
on his way back from the civil service exam.
You're just worried about him.
It was just a nightmare.
Please give me another chance.
Can't even handle this small task I assigned.
And you still dream of becoming the top scholar...
The deal between us
Consider it never happened.
Please trust me!
As long as I can appease that Luo Qian guy,
I will definitely find the Tongwen!
Do you know why I asked you to handle this?
Me?
I like people who have nothing.
Because they will stop at nothing
for fame and fortune.
I will definitely
bring the Tongwen.
Don't disappoint me.
A fire?
The authorities
said the young masters were smoking opium,
which caused the fire to spread, and closed the case.
It seems the master
has settled the matter.
What about Zheng Renxian?
I heard he came first in the imperial exam.
I think I need to leave here.
What did you say?
Send a letter to the brothel,
saying Luo Qian will return to the establishment.
Yes, understood.
I want this pair.
Sir,
I don't need new shoes...
Make it with this cloth.
[Merchant] Yes, sir.
I'll take all the pens here.
What?
All of them?
Why am I so uneasy?
My lord!
It suits you perfectly!
How do I look?
Beautiful.
The new top scholar has arrived!
Seeing Jeong In-heon achieve success and fame
makes you that happy?
I have always envisioned
you wearing the scholar's flower
as you go out.
Not only did I imagine it in my mind,
I also drew it on paper.
In that painting,
were you there?
I dared not approach,
so I could only watch from afar.
Do you know the biggest difference between now and that painting?
It's that you are by my side.
My lord,
have you ever eaten grilled rice cakes?
You haven't, have you?
I'll grill some for you!
When I was little,
Whenever I cried, Sister Xina would
Why are you looking at me like that?
I feel so uneasy.
- About two plates.
- Two plates?
- Isn't that too much?
- Too much.
Sir, thank you for saving Luo Qian.
You're right.
What?
Luo Qian staying with me
will only bring him misfortune.
Although he's still in pain from that day,
he tries hard to hide it in front of me.
I only make him sad and hurt.
You treat him like a sister.
I hope you can take care of him.
I entrust Luo Qian to you.
Luo Qian,
really likes you.
No matter what happens in the future,
please come back to find him.
Why hasn't the lord come yet?
Sister Xina!
Where is the lord?
What's wrong?
Luo Qian,
from now on, live with me.
Lord Seongho has left.
Lord...
Lord!
Wait for me!
Your body hasn't recovered yet.
Why aren't you more careful?
Lord!
You forgot to take me with you.
Luo Qian,
let's go home quickly.
I'm already better.
Why did you send me away?
When I wanted to leave you,
you refused to let me go no matter what.
I
Did I do something wrong?
Don't you like me anymore?
Luo Qian,
I will definitely solve everything
and come back for you.
For now,
stay here for now.
Sir...
What did you trade for this top scholar title?
Could it be that you sold yourself?
What?
Do you really want to kill me?
Killing four noble young masters was nothing,
killing one more commoner like you
would be a piece of cake.
It was three.
What did you say?
Young Master Min is not dead yet.
Ah, but don't worry,
I've already taken care of him.
If you kill me with your own hands,
Luo Qian will be very sad.
Tell my father,
if he dares to touch him again,
the entire Yin family will die.
If you don't want to end up dead together,
then behave yourself.
If Yin Shenghao makes the announcement public,
I will end up with nothing.
It must be handed over to Lord Yin by me personally.
Sir?
Luo Qian,
are you feeling okay?
I heard that while I was away,
you almost met with misfortune...
Yes, sir...
When I heard the news,
my heart shattered.
You must have been so scared...
I should stay by your side...
Now I understand
My feelings for you
Have gone beyond that of master and disciple...
Come with me
I know
You're worried that if you leave,
Yoon Seung-ho won't let it go
Yoon Seung-ho almost killed me too
If we're to leave together,
There's something you need to do
Yoon Seung-ho has a document
Only if you bring it
can we leave together...
Master, you don't like me
What?
Now I understand
what the gaze of someone in love
looks like
You make me restless
Master has never looked at me
with such eyes
I said I love you
I want to be with Lord Seung-ho
You would betray me for Yoon Seung-ho?
You say Yoon Seung-ho likes you too?
You're flattering yourself
Do you really believe that shameless man
will stay with you for life?
Once he gets bored,
he'll abandon you immediately
And throw yourself into another man's arms!
Lord Seung-ho is not that kind of person
One—
My lord!
With this kid Baek Na-gyeon,
we can get the document!
Please trust me one more time!
Just threaten Yoon Seung-ho
that you'll kill this kid,
and he will surely hand over the document!
My lord!
My lord,
Is this servant enough?
Yes!
I'll take care of it!
Please trust me one more time!
This kid will help me get the document.
Then you,
what can you get for me?
What did you say?
Kill him.
My lord!
My lord, you can't do this!
-My lord!
-[Eunuch Yi's servant] Go!
Let go of me, you bastard!
My lord! I beg you to spare my life!
Luo Qian, wake up!
Luo Qian!
Luo... Qian...
Luo Qian
Why keep calling me, my lord...
I just really want to say your name.
Lord Shenghao.
It sounds so nice.
Say it again.
Ah, my lord!
You turned my son into a murderer!
What?
He killed four young masters in the cabin outside the South Gate.
It's all because of you!
Because of you,
my son is waiting to die in the government office!
Lord Shenghao is going to be executed?
That's right.
No!
My lord,
please save Lord Shenghao.
It's all because of me; my lord has no fault at all.
Shenghao,
No fault at all?
Yes.
It's all because of me.
It's all because I'm useless, being pushed around like trash...
Yes.
So it was you
who killed the young masters
and set the fire, right?
What?
Because you couldn't bear the nobles' humiliation
you caused this disaster
Is that it?
Yes... yes
I killed them!
As the young master ordered,
I found a house in a secluded place far from Hanyang.
Would you like to see it?
No need.
Prepare and go directly.
I need to pack all the belongings; it will take some time.
Take Luo Qian with you first.
I have matters to attend to.
Lord Seong-ho!
Luo Qian
has confessed to killing the young masters.
What?
Step back!
Move aside!
Luo Qian!
Stop!
Come in.
Lord Yoon orders you to enter.
Luo Qian!
My lord?
Luo Qian,
you cannot stay here.
Leave quickly.
Luo Qian,
If you stay, you'll be suspected too.
I can't let you take the blame for me.
Let's go together.
No.
I killed him.
Luo Qian.
I've lived until now
never once thought
about what kind of life I wanted.
Since meeting you, I've started to look forward to tomorrow,
look forward to the arrival of the next season.
I can't live without you...
I
will definitely save you.
[Establish the 'Great Alliance Pact' to promote learning]
[A document recording the names of those plotting rebellion]
[Yi Changxian]
Please release Luo Qian.
You've already gotten what you wanted. Stop while you're ahead.
Do you think this document alone
can save your lover?
From now on, I will follow your orders.
Why should I trust you?
I will be the upright son you wish me to be,
and do my utmost to cleanse our family's shame.
I beg you, Father, to save his life.
You may exploit my weaknesses,
manipulate me as you please.
I bow my head and plead.
Come out.
What?
Have you heard?
It's about the massacre in the wooden house outside the South Gate!
The culprit is actually the scholar Jeong In-heon!
That's right!
It must be that erotic painting artist who stepped forward to take the blame
to protect this scholar!
I heard that in the mountains over there,
a body gnawed by wild animals was found.
Rumor has it that it's Jeong In-heon. Is that true?
Let me go!
I killed them all.
I killed every single one!
Go now!
Luo Qian
Let's run away together.
Only this way
can we help Lord Shenghao.
[Three years later]
Well drawn.
[Country kid 1] Brother!
I finished drawing!
[Country kid 2] I finished too!
Let me see.
Well drawn.
What is this?
A quilt!
A quilt?
Mom and Dad
are inside.
May disasters vanish like spring snow,
and blessings rise like summer clouds.
Luo Qian!
Sister!
Ouch.
Are all the sisters well?
The brothel has been busy lately,
so I haven't had a chance to see you properly.
Is this it?
No.
It needs to be thinner than this!
Bought the wrong one again?
This is already the thinnest!
Luo Qian.
What's wrong?
Let's change that spring couplet.
I heard that Master Shenghao came first in the imperial exam.
Really?
Mm.
And he's getting married too.
They say because Lord Yun Changxian passed away,
he needs to carry on the family line.
I see...
It's a relief that he's doing well.
May disasters melt away like spring snow, and blessings rise like summer clouds.
It seems our fate ends here, my lord.
Your face appears in my dreams every night, but now it has become blurry.
I miss you so much.
But the harder I try to remember,
the blurrier it becomes.
Just once,
Even if only for a moment,
I wish I could see him again...
[Country Woman] Beautiful, truly beautiful.
Such fine work, yet you charge so little?
I'm already grateful that you let me paint.
I heard you're going to help Eun-sook with farm work again today.
Why have you been working for days on end?
Because there's someone I want to see.
I'm planning to visit him.
[Country Merchant 1] This outfit suits you perfectly.
By the way, where is the magistrate?
Has he already left?
[Country Merchant 2] Not yet.
[Country Merchant 3] I heard the new magistrate
is the top scholar who passed the imperial exam.
Why would a top scholar take a post in a place like this?
Exactly.
Isn't this remote area usually for exiled officials?
No.
I heard he volunteered to come here.
Volunteered?
The new top scholar has arrived!
Luo Qian.
The new magistrate wants to see you.
Me?
He's looking for a portrait painter.
He's very satisfied with your work.
As soon as the magistrate takes office,
he wants a portrait painted?
Need I say more?
But you'll still paint it, right?
Make him pay more silver.
[Country official] Magistrate,
the painter has arrived.
My name is Zi Luoqian.
Are you Zi Luoqian?
You forgot to take me away.
Why did you send me away?
Luoqian,
I will definitely resolve everything
and come back for you.
For now...
Stay here for now.
I really like
your painting.
What are you standing there for?
Come into my arms quickly.
Have you forgotten your husband so soon?