Reply 1988
♫  The party last night  ♫
♫  was so lonely  ♫
♫  even if someone offered me the whole world  ♫
♫  I could not exchange it  ♫
♫  Why don't you know that?  ♫
Ooh! Bam, bam, bam, bam!
Hey, hey, hey!
I said that it's not that.
Why don't you know that? Ooh, bam, bam, bam!
Name: Jang Mi Ok; Nickname Maggie Cheung; Ssangmoon Girls High School; first person to have braces.
Name: Wang Ja Hyeon; Nickname: Joey Wang; Ssangmoon Girls High School; High Teen Romance novels supplier.
Best!
Seong Deok Seon, if you keep doing it wrong, it's going to be a problem.
Hey, there are still two months left. Worry about yourselves.
Even if you get everything wrong, you have to get this right. Watch again.
♫ Why don't you know that? Hoo! Bam, bam, bam!
Aunt, three ramyuns, please.
Brazil Spicy Rice Cakes
Why are you here? You didn't go to the picket girl practice?
- Then why are you guys here?
- Hey.
Our school is closer to here.
- Jeong Pal, I'm going to order spicy rice cakes, too.
- Okay.
Please add four servings of spicy rice cakes!
- Jeong Pal, we're going to order, too.
- Hey!
That means he's fine with it.
Please give us one more serving of spicy rice cake!
- Hey, Deok Seon, pass me that water.
- Okay.
I guess you don't have any picket girl practice. You've been practically living in the Hyochang-dong Stadium.
I have to eat and go. I have late night practice.
Hey, Special Forces.
Be quiet. Who is Special Forces?
Didn't she turn and look behind immediately?
Did you practice a lot for the school trip? I heard that you're doing Sobangcha.
That's right. When are you going to do all that?
Picket girl is probably really hard, too.
- Ramyun is here.
- Yes!
Deok Seon, do you want ramyun? Should I get you one?
Hey!
I'm not going to eat it!
Brazil Spicy Rice Cakes
Deok Seon, we're going first. Jeong Pal paid for everything.
How much did you stuff yourselves?
I'm leaving.
Aren't you going to eat it? It's free.
He's Ssangmoon's class president, right?
Who? Seon Woo? The tall one? Why?
What should you do?
What?
I think he likes you.
He kept looking only at you the moment he came in.
No kidding. I saw it, too.
Why does he ask for water from you? He should ask the server.
And, when you said that you're practicing Sobangcha,
did you see his concerned face?
I saw it, I saw it. I really saw it.
And the last crucial evidence.
'Do you want some ramyun?'
Congratulations, Deok Seon.
You got a boyfriend.
♫  I think I fell in love  ♫
(Lee Sun Hee - I Think I Fell in Love)
Deok Seon! Seong Deok Seon!
What is it?
Can you lend me some white-out? The liquid type.
White-out? I don't have white-out.
You're doing well. What student doesn't have any white-out?
Noona, hello.
Seon Woo, don't play with her. You'll become stupid, too.
- Be quiet!
- Look at you!
Hey, hey. Forget it. I'll just borrow it from Jeong Hwan.
I'm leaving. Noona, I'm leaving.
Okay. Go.
Eat.
Did a second Korean War break out?
Why is there only potato, potato, potato? Is it an emergency food supply?
Are you going to be like this?
You bought a box of potatoes because you pitied the bus station ahjumma.
When did I? I should rip your voice box out.
You're putting on quite a show.
I'm good at acting, right?
Does money spoil?
Do you want to use money because we have leftover money? Please, please!
The kids are watching.
And do you know how good potatoes are for the body?
I bought a lot for my children's health, and you don't even know that?
Your hand is so spicy.
(i.e., it stings when you hit me.)
And, Deok Seon, isn't it time for sports news?
Turn on MBC.
It's MBC right now. It's not time for sports news.
Really?
I really like Anchor Kang Seong Gu.
He looks so gentle, he looks like a movie star. He's so tall, too.
Are you serious? All he does is sit in that chair and talk!
Have you seen if he's tall or not?
There's a wiretap in his ear, everyone.
- What is that?
There's a wiretap in his ear, everyone!
I live in Garibong-dong, 136-35...
Oh my, oh my. Something about wiretaps came and went, right?
Did only my eyes see that?
Weird things happen.
Deok Seon!
Seong Deok Seon!
Our Seon Woo might wear out the doorway.
Seon Woo Hyung, a broadcasting accident happened! Hurry up and come here!
Seon Woo, hurry up and come here and eat some food.
And Deok Seon, hurry up and scoop out some rice for Seon Woo
Oh my, she was here a second ago. Today a bunch of things passed by so quickly.
- Wow, look at how flustered he is.
- He looks so surprised.
This is the first time in my life seeing such an accident during the news.
Weird things happen.
- Hello.
- Seon Woo, you came? Hurry up and eat dinner.
Come here and eat a bowl.
No. I'm going to eat ramyun in Taek's room—
Aish! It's more shocking than the broadcasting accident.
Where are you going dressed like that at this hour?
To go eat ramyun.
Let's go, Seon Woo.
In the summer of 1988,
Seong Deok Seon's very first love in her life.
First love begins now.
Five hundred won
Episode 3: One Law for the Rich, and Another for the Poor
Ji Gang Heon and others, convicts accused of severe crimes have escaped,
so all of Seoul is uneasy and frightened.
October 1988, Seoul Dobong-gu Ssangmoon-dong
Last August, on their way to another jail,
the convicts. including Ji Gang Heon. broke through a police blockade.
They are near the vicinity of Anam-dong and Haengdam-dong in Seoul, and are said to be creating hostage situations.
The police do not yet know where they are
and are revealing weaknesses in their investigations.
Hyungnim, I'm scared.
What if they come to our neighborhood, too?
Worry is also fate. What is there to steal in this neighborhood?
There's a lot of expensive stuff in her house!
She has a record player, microwave, rice cooker, and
and also 500 charcoal briquettes.
A robber will never come inside our house.
Why?
There's already a robber inside.
If a human eats food but doesn't do what he has to, isn't he a thief? Am I not right?
This is good. This is it.
You have a lot of greed. Jeong Bong's father is really faithful and shrewd. I've never seen him waste money.
You can have him.
- Why? You're going to give him to someone else?
- Yes.
If there's someone who'll take Jeong Bong's father, I'll also give them this house.
Me, me! Give him to me. I want to.
I want to marry again at this late age.
Oh my, what is this?
Hyungnim, your ex-husband is already getting off work.
Mi Ran. Mi... Ran.
- Stop it, really.
- Why do you do this to only me?
- I told you to stop!
- Okay, okay. I won't do it.
Darn... Were you having an interesting conversation?
Ah... Hyungnim said that you're a thief.
Thief?
Of course. Am I not this person's bellybutton thief?
Then, this bellybutton thief will take his leave.
Everyone. Long life to you! Sheck-sheck-sheck!
So are you the first person in line?
I'm going to live alone. I have to be loyal to my first husband.
What is this? I only see thieves today.
Look at Bora's father. Looks like he looted a shop.
Are you coming now?
What did you buy again today?
What is it? What did you buy again?
See when you come in.
Eat some sweet potato before you go. What's in that dark home that you're in a hurry?
Hyung-nim, Bo Ra's father is really in a hurry.
He probably wants to hurry up and have it over and done with  before the kids come.
Give it. Why did you buy this again?
Aigoo, it's bracken. Bracken. I heard that it's bad for men's virility.
You don't know what you're talking about. Maybe he's so virile, he needs that to decrease it.
- Let's talk when we get it.
- What is this again?
He's in a real hurry.
Ah, really!
Why do those women prattle for 365 days?
I hate seeing them, so we better move away.
What is all this?
You person, can't you know from seeing? It's all vegetables. I bought a little after getting off work.
Is this a little? Is this a little?!
You know there's a wallpaper shop nearby.
In front, there was a grandma kneeling down selling vegetables. She looked exactly like my mother.
That person was kneeling and selling them. Seeing her,
I thought that she wouldn't be able to go home if she didn't sell it all.
So how can I, a humane person, just pass by?
So I bought a little bit.
To speak bluntly, how much do these root vegetables cost, anyway?
People having a tough time should help each other out.
Are we in a condition to help strangers?
At our age, we live in a half-basement, and we can't even buy brand-name sneakers for our children.
Look at your wife. Can't you see her wearing socks with holes? What do you do with your eyes, Look! Look!
Oh my, since it has holes, it must feel cool with the wind blowing in.
Aigoo, are you serious now? Are you serious?
You are so obsessed with money. Sometimes people have money, and sometimes you don't. That's how money is.
Aigoo, if I ever had any, I would know to miss it when I don't. I don't even know that.
You, really! What bracken bundle should I prepare first?
Two.
Three.
Four.
You thought it was four, right?
Five.
Are you joking? Did you only buy five when there are four in the family?
One per each person. Two for you.
Honey, please. Let's please live now like normal people.
Mister Kim Seong Gyoon, let's spend like other people and let's live like other people.
What about the way we live?
Just think about three years ago. We couldn't dream of oranges like this.
We didn't even have rice, so we had nothing but dough soup.
Whenever I think about how I used to carry that metal delivery food case, I feel like we're living in a dream right now.
Again, again, again! Those past memories!
If you like the delivery food case, then carry the delivery food case!
Oh, you. What is the use of having money, when you can't rise to that occasion?
I'm worried that the kids will take after you. I'm worried!
What are you going to do about Jeong Bong? He resembles you so he's timid and frugal.
Is he going to do well when he goes out into society later on? Aren't you even worried?
He'll change when he goes to college.
He has to study in order to go to college!
Our Jeong Bong is always studying in his room these days.
Do you want to bet?
Look. Is that studying? Are you studying right now?
No.
The  scholastic ability test is not far away. Are you not going to college?
President Roosevelt said, "You learn more things in stamps than in school."
Your mother also said,
has there been such a useless son of a b**ch? You son of b**ch!
This damn bastard. After failing the college exams five times, if he has a brain at all, if only to consider his mom and dad,
he should consider himself dead at his desk and study until he gets sores on his butthole!
You son of a b**ch with no conscience!
That's right. What's so important about studying? Just keep on doing what you're doing.
Yes.
Vegetables are good, so consider the vegetables your main course.
You bastard, why do you keep on pushing the table?
- I didn't push it.
- Then does the table have legs to move toward me?
The table is pressing on my stomach so I can't even move.
Dad. Can't you buy me that Ah-Ha? I'm the only in my class that doesn't have it.
Ah-ha! Your sister has one. Why don't you share it?
- Mine's is broken. Buy me one too.
- Then we must buy it.
Forget it. I didn't even expect anything.
Eat vegetables. I bought it for you.
♫  ...so lonely. Even if someone offered me the whole world, I could not exchange it.  ♫
(Sobangcha - Last Night's Story)
♫  Why don't you know that? Hooh!  ♫
♫  Last night, I began to hate you  ♫
Hey. You messed up again.
- No. Man Ok messed up!
- Crazy girl.
Seong Deok Seon, I really don't think dancing is for you.
- We've been practicing for months. How can you get that wrong?
- I only messed up once.
You always mess up. Tomorrow is the school trip. What are you going to do?
The talent show is the day after tomorrow.
Why don't you just stay out of it. Why do you want to do the talent show so badly when you can't even dance?
Notice for Family
School Trip Information
First Place Prize: MyMy Mini-cassette Player
You guys don't have to worry. I'll master it by tonight.
- How?
- Don't you know that a Park Nam Jung lives in my neighborhood?
There's a guy known as Ssangmoon High School's Park Nam Jung (Korean version of Michael Jackson) who's really good at dancing.
You probably met him at the spicy rice cake restaurant. The one with the glasses.
- Oh, bomb!
- At his high school festival, he danced Park Nam Jung's dance and won first place.
This one.
♫ Little dreams that have broken into little pieces.
♫ They scatter far away, far away  to the sky.
♫  hiding my tears and turning away  ♫
♫  love's emergency landing  ♫
(Park Nam Jung - Love's Emergency Landing)
I said do Sobangcha!
Who dances to Sobangcha these days?
Everyone! Everyone does! Stop messing around and hurry and do "Last Night's Story."
Sobangcha is beginner's level. Who here can't dance to to Sobangcha?
Hey. Do you guys know how to dance?
Us?
♫  Even if someone offered me the whole world, I could not exchange it  ♫
♫  Why didn't you know that? Hoo!  ♫
Jerks.
How many months have you been doing this now?
Our Haeng Gook would dance better than you after three months.  (Haeng Gook = his dog's name)
Hey, we even got first place in school last year with this song. This bastard dances this one better than Dong Ryong.
Stop it. It's not like it's something great.
Try the dance and I'll take a look.
Right. Let's see how much you improved.
I will dance if you get him to keep quiet.
Bastard, keep quiet. Okay?
- I can't even laugh?
- No. Just sleep.
Hey, is that enough? Go and dance. We'll watch.
♫  Last night, I began to hate you  ♫
♫  Last night, I began to dislike you  ♫
♫  in the unending music  ♫
Right. Go. Keep on going.
♫  I cried by myself  ♫
Now, let's go.
One, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
No. You should turn.
Is it that weird? Didn't I get it about right?
Not even one right. Not one. It's all wrong. Everything.
You be quiet!
Seon Woo, is it really weird? Was it bad?
Yeah. I think dancing is really not for you.
Hey, is anything right for her?
Deok Seon. We'll just pool our money and buy you a MyMy (cassette player).
No, let's just ask Taek to buy you one. I'm about to die here.
No thanks. Open the door, it's hot.
That scared me. Since when were you playing baduk over there?
Taek, you should have said earlier that you're here already. I've been wanting to eat ramyun since earlier.
Taek, five ramyuns.
Hey! Hey, I will cook it. You don't even know how to cook it.
Hey, Il Hwa! Dong Il is here, your husband!
What's with the flattery this time?
What did you buy this time? You bought something again.
Seriously. Your husband, Dong Il, is here.
What did you buy this time?
Ta da!
Seriously, as you live life, there are a lot of people who live in hardship.
You know that person who came to us and sold insurance last summer.
Ajusshi's paternal first cousin once removed cousin's daughter's hometown friend.
After sending off her husband to the afterlife, she has a boy about Jin Joo's age and lives a really hard life.
After hearing that, I got tears in my eyes.
So what is that?
What do you mean what? It's prenatal education tape.
What? So we should have another baby when we are struggling?
No. She said that if I bought just this one it would take care of one meal.
After I heard that, how could I just pretend not to care?
And she is paternal first cousin once removed Ajusshi's cousin's daughter's hometown friend. She's not a stranger.
She's a stranger! Stranger. Please get your head together!
I can't live because of you, seriously!
While being transferred to a rural prison, 12 prisoners on trial have escaped, shocking the citizens of Seoul.
The citizens are afraid that they may commit more crimes, and are spending their days full of fear.
Today, the police arrested one of the escapees, Kim Dong Yeon.
Aigoo. What has the world come to?
The police learned that he was planning to meet the other escapees in Hooham-dong...
I'm going to rip that up!
It's still wearable. There aren't even any holes either.
Who wears undershirts until there are holes in them these days? Throw it away right now.
Do you know what's the scariest thing on earth is?
When a person who has nothing helps others. Are we in a position to be helping others right now?
Seriously, you're always talking about money. Are you obsessed with money?
Oh my! I'm the strange one?
Go and ask anyone on the street if someone who lives in a half-basement helping anyone out is normal
or a person who struggles and lives hard to take cares of his kids first?
What's wrong with this half-basement?
What did you say?
It's cool in the summer and warm in winter so it's nice.
Alright then!
If it's so nice to live in a half-basement then live your whole life in here!
I can't live like this anymore!
And also, do you know that Deok Seon is going on a school trip?
Are we going to send the child on a field trip without any money?
We should at least send her with about 20,000 won. But this month, we only have 30,000 won left over from our living expenses this month.
What are you going to do? Say something, huh?
Let's just stick to the first verse, darn it.
(Just say things once)
Where are you going?
I'm going to borrow money from paternal first cousin once removed Ajusshi's cousin's daughter's hometown friend.
Aigoo! Good for you!
Hey.
You're all going for a school trip tomorrow?
What's with you, remembering such a thing?
School Trip Information Sheet
Seon Woo, I got it from your bag because there was nothing else to put the pot on.
It's Gyeongju. Your school, too?
Yeah. We're going to Gyeongju too.
You're jealous, right?
That's why I told you not to quit school. How can you just graduate middle school?
Jeong Pal. Taek earned 100 million won ($125,000) last year.
But still, I think you would want to go to Gyeongju. You haven't been there, right?
Yeah.
Hee Dong, where did you say your competition is tomorrow?
(Hee Dong, a character from Dooly cartoon)
Tokyo.
Hyung-nim! I have steamed some potatoes. You're still not asleep, right?
Yeah. Come in!
Prenatal education tape? Seriously.
Who would know how I feel?
We fought a round because of that.
We don't have money and he's going around doing all those good things by himself.
What would you do about a person being so good? It's just that he can't bear to ignore them.
Doesn't he notice his children? I really am getting allergic to him.
But you're still better off than me.
Our home's enemy is still not able to move out from the time we lived in that single-room house.
He still doesn't know how to spend money.
It's just because he's shrewd.
And Jeong Bong's father is the one who lived in this neighborhood with the most difficulty.
It's not like that habit will disappear after a day.
If he has lived so poor for a long time, then he should learn how to spend by now.
I'm so embarrassed of everyone watching.
He will change slowly. Slowly.
You got hit by the lighting of money overnight, so it's not like a person's mind would change that fast.
But still, I envy you the most in this world.
Aigoo. When will I live without having to worry about money?
But then, what brings you here late at night?
Well, it's nothing, but...
What is it?  Between us, is there anything we can't talk about?
Hyung-nim, I'm always sorry about it.
Hyung-nim, I...
It's about the money you borrowed before, right?
Forget it. Give it to me next time. Repay it slowly.
I'm newly rich. I have a lot of money.
Have a drink.
What are you doing?
No, nothing.
Is that money?
It's student fee. I gathered student fees.
You got a lot of student fee. Your class really has over seventy students, right?
Yeah...
Hey, be careful of that. The student fees were stolen from even Seon Woo's class's  leader.
Oh... That's what happened. I'll be careful.
- Sleep first, Noona. I want to get some fresh air.
- Okay.
Why?
Noona is going on a field trip tomorrow.
♫  Let's go somewhere far   ♫
♫  Let's try to erase our loneliness  ♫
♫  Let's go far away  ♫
Why don't you stop fooling around and sleep?
Go ahead and sleep first.
I'm going to give you five minutes until I turn off the lights.
Are we in the army? What's five minutes about?
I don't know what might happen five minutes later.
Do you know how steel becomes tempered?
Not in Nikolai Ostrovski's novel, but in reality
it gets hit to be tempered.  It has to be hit!
What nonsense are you saying again?!
Hey, I told you to stop fooling around and sleep! I told you to sleep, huh?
Stop messing around!
Mom!
Look at Unni!
Stop being noisy.
Bo Ra's mom. Bo Ra's mom, are you sleeping?
Come out for a moment.
Hyung-nim, what are you doing here at this time of night?
My relatives sent us some corn.
Aigoo, really? It must taste good.
I'm going to go. Sleep.
Yes. Go, Hyung-nim.
Deok Seon is going to the school trip tomorrow, right?
Add this to her allowance, Jeong Bong's mom.
Aish...
Here it is.
And promise.
You promised that you'll never lose the camera.
If you lose it, you are eternally my 'dog daughter' (rebellious daughter - Reply series).
And I may even kill you.
Girl, act carelessly or lose it and I will kill you with my own  hands.
Never. I will never lose it.
Dad, what about the film? Give me the film also.
I feel a little bit uneasy.
Give it.
Anyway, I will specially give you two thirty-six count rolls.
So don't just take any picture and be frugal about every shot.
I understand. Don't worry.
That's right. Use it carefully.
But is there any film left in here? Should I try to see if it works?
Hey!
Do you want to die?
I'm leaving!
Does she like it that much?
Of course. It's her first school trip. How happy she must be.
On a day like this, she'll probably smile even if her sister hits her.
I'm really leaving! Expect presents!
Hey! Deok Seon! The kimbap!
Right.
♫  the voice calling me from the blue ocean  ♫
(Song: When Tomorrow Come)
♫  your image, coming towards me like the waves  ♫
♫  in the new, abundant hope  ♫
♫  my heart flutters  ♫
Jin Joo, Oppa will come back.
I'm leaving.
Go.
♫  Only that feeling is in our hearts.   ♫
♫  Someday I will tell you   ♫
♫  When tomorrow comes   ♫
♫ In your two beautiful hands  ♫
♫ I will pour my dream fully in there  ♫
♫ in your lovely dreams  ♫
♫ I'll run to you any time  ♫
Let's eat.
Yes.
Ssangmoon High School - School Trip Information
Gyeongju Station
Hey, Deok Seon!
Take out the camera. We should take one photo before we ride the bus.
- Okay.
- Wow...
It's nice. It's my first time coming to Jeolla Province.
This is Gyeongsang Province.
Is that important?
What are you looking for?
Are you looking for the camera?
Perhaps...
I want to go backkkkkkkkkkk!
Busan
Go buy a new jacket.
This is still new. I can wear this for ten more years.
Do you want to see each other in court later?
Don't buy a bunch of cheap ones, but buy
just one that is expensive, good, with a brand name. Understand?
Deok Seon, it's okay. You can lose a camera, it happens.
It's our family's treasure. My mom might kill me.
Teacher, can't I just go home now?
I don't think I'll be able to have fun because I'm scared.
Should I call your mom for you?
Really?
This is Seong Deok Seon's home, right?
Hello, Mother. I am Deok Seon's homeroom teacher.
Yes.
Mother, it's nothing much but, Deok Seon left the camera on the train.
What should we do...
Mother. M-mother? Mother.
Yes. The child is crying a lot.
This is a one-in-a-lifetime school trip, isn't it?
I don't want this school trip to be full of fear and terror.
That is so tragic.
Thank you, Mother. I will give the phone to Deok Seon. Yes.
Mom...
Deok Seon, it's okay. Have fun and come back.
Really? Really, Mom?
That's right. Really.
Don't worry about the camera, and have fun with your friends.
Mom!
♬ I'm lost in your charm. You're stealing my heart.
♬ Let's dance to my beat.  Let's dance to my beat.
♬ Do it with a lot of gusto.  Please don't stop.
♬ The dance is in the beat
♫ Dance to the beat.  Dance to the beat.
♬ We have a lot of gusto.
Hey, should we have not done Sobangcha and have done Kim Wan Seon? I think she'll get first place.
You only have to do well. Only you. You didn't forget the choreography, right?
Hey, I can do it right after I wake up.
♫ Why don't you know that? Hooh! Bam, bam bam!
But what do we do if after all this we don't get first place?
I think you'll cry if you don't get the MyMy.
Hey, unless you don't break your legs and arms suddenly, we are first place for sure.
Do you want to bet?
Hello?
Aigoo. Hello, Teacher. Why are you calling our house?
Did No Eul cause some trouble?
It's not something big, but No Eul got caught doing one day cafe by the school.
What? One day cafe? What is that?
It's something popular among students these days. They sell drinks and do meetings. It's something like that.
He probably did that to go somewhere with his girlfriend.
For now, I think one of the  parents needs to come to school.
Aigoo... Yes, Teacher.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Aigoo... Really...
Gyeongju Kim Yoo Shin Youth Hostel
How long are you taking washing up? Hurry up and come so we can practice!
What are you eating again when we're going to sleep?
Hurry up and come. I'm going to dance Sobangcha.
Which school is that? The lights are the best.
Hey, it's Ssangmoon High School. Ssangmoon High School naturally has group sound.
Ssangmoon High School has a talent show today? Why do they do it so early?
Is another high school's talent show important?
Our school has the talent show tomorrow. When are we going to practice?
Hey, where are you going?
To Ssangmoon High School's dormitory.
- Are you crazy?
- We're going!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
- We're leaving.
- Bye!
That MyMy.
That MyMy is what Deok Seon likes most in the whole world.
Honey, go to No Eul's school tomorrow.
What is that about?
No Eul got caught doing one day cafe or whatever.
In order to go somewhere with his girlfriend, he tried to make money like that.
Aigoo, I can't go to school because I'm so embarrassed. You go to school.
Okay. I'll go. I just need to go.
And guys can do that while playing around.
It's not like that he beat someone up or he stole money.
You worry about weird things.
Aigoo, I don't know why you have so many concerns?
Grandma, give me all those vegetables today.
And hurry up and go home.
Hurry up and go home...
Did you really buy that?
Of course I bought it. Do you think I stole it?
How is it? Does it look good on me? They say that this is the most popular color.
That's right. How nice is it? Your face looks much better.
How much did you pay? This must have been really expensive.
150,000 won. (About 150 dollars) It was originally 200,000 won, but he gave me a discount of 50,000 won.
It turns out that he's my friend.
Really? Friend, who?
You'll know if I tell you. Wait, let me first take off my jacket.
Because this is a brand, it's really warm.
As expected, expensive clothes are different—
What's wrong with this?
This.
Originally, this clothing
is supposed to be taken off like this.
Which friend? Give me the name.
He's not my friend. It was my first time meeting him today.
Which friend?! Aren't you going to hurry up and tell me?!
How can a friend scam a friend?
Are you a dummy?  Are you a pushover?
How much did you seem easy that a friend scammed you?
Look at this.
Why does a horse have six legs?
And what is this trident?
Just looking at it, it won't even cost 10,000 won (about 10 dollars).
But you gave 150,000 won? And also for  defective clothing?
That friend is ignoring you because you are nouveau riche.
He's not really my friend. I got confused.
Are you taking his side because he's your friend?
Which friend is it?
I said he's not my friend.
You said that I know that friend! Why can't you tell me?!
The legs are like this!
Deok Seon, we'll earn money and get you a MyMy.
If I tell my dad, he'll buy you one.
Shut up.
They say that you can be released.
Mi Ok, you can walk, right?
Of course.
You two, only stay inside the hotel. You are forbidden to go outside.
What about the talent show? They have to go to the talent show with me.
Talking about talent show nonsense. In this condition?
I heard that you're going to dance to Firefighter. Do you want to ride the ambulance again?
No, Teacher. I have to do the talent show.
So how can you dance in this kind of condition?
Anyway, I won't take you guys off of the sign up sheet. So Deok Seon, try your best alone.
I just have to fill the stage no matter what, right?
Why? Are you going invite a singer?
Now 2nd grade, class 14 will gather!
Hey, let's take a picture. A picture.
- Hurry.
- Here it is.
Now, one, two, three!
♫   Meeting you accidentally, my heart is lost in your image ♫
♫ Meeting you accidentally,  your eyes have captured my heart.  ♫
♫  I have something to say to you but why don't I have the nerve?   ♫
Soondheon High School
♫   I want to say something to you,   ♫
Gwangju Speer Girls' High School
♫  but without any confidence, my heart is going  pit-a-pat  ♫
Baemyeon  High School Field Trip
♫ My stifled heart is flying away in the wind.  ♫
Ssangmoon High School  Juniors Room 1
Ssangmoon High School  Juniors Room 16
Where are you going?
Seon Woo. Come here for a moment.
Yes.
We're here.
Hey, Kim Jeong Pal.
- What?
- Keep this for a moment. Our bags our going to get checked soon.
Are you crazy?
Twelve o'clock. Come to the front of the hotel iron gate.
If you don't come out, you'll die. If you touch it, you'll die. If you lose it, I'll kill you.
Hey! Kim Jeong Pal!
Jeong Pal! Hey!
Why?
Do Ryong Nyong! I only have you.
Kim Kim Soo Ro Snack Bar
Just once. Please save me just once.
Still, how can we go out to a girl school's talent show?
Last year without putting in a formal application I came out to your school's Sound Group.
We won second place.
Still, no.
Dong Ryong, please bring the kids.
Really. MyMy.
No. I have woman allergies.
I have a friend called Wang Jo Hyeon.
Her real name is Wang Ja Hyeon.
but because she looks exactly like Wang Jo Hyeon   (Hong Kong acress Joey Wang) we call her Jo Hyeon.
There's another one and her name is Jang Man Ok.   (Hong Kong Actress Maggie Cheung)
Hurry up and get well
Hury up and get well Beauty Jo Hyeon
How do we bring bastard, Jeong Pal? And even Seon Woo?
- Seon Woo?
- He's also a student president so he doesn't want to get in trouble.
He'll come. Seon Woo will come.
What are you talking about?
Say that I asked him. Sell me.
Sell what?
And to Jeong Pal, say one word.
What?
- Something special.
- Something what?
See you later at nine o'clock in front of Kim Yoo Shin Youth Hostel gate.
And next in order is 'tonight the girl's eyes is scarier'
Ssangmoon Girl High School, Chae Jin Ahn!
Chae Jin Ahn!
♫   Dance to the beat.  Dance to the beat.  ♫
♫  There's a lot of gusto.  ♫
I don't think they're going to come.
Deok Seon, just give up now.  I'd be embarrassed and not come if I were them.
They came. There.
Hey, what is this?
- I don't know.
- We came even without discussing it.
Hey, it's not that. Come here. Hey. It's not that.
Hey.
The news says that it's bad,
but truthfully because one day cafe is so popular nowadays, there's no one that doesn't do it.
We have to prevent them from going astray, so we gather the parents.
Truthfully, you don't have to worry too much about it.
But we're really, really sorry.
I will call No Eul and scold him until he cries.
No, no. Don't do that, Father. No Eul is kind. He also has great relationship with his friends.
Just please guide him into not doing this again.
And
because it's the rule, starting from today and ten days onward we will tell him to clean the bathroom.
Don't feel upset.
Aigoo, what is just bathroom cleaning?
I'll just tell him to clean all the toilets of Ssangmoon-dong.
It's about time No Eul finishes cleaning. Take him and go home, Father.
Teacher, I'm sorry. Thank you.
No, it's okay.
Ssangmoon High School
If he comes, I'll kill him.
Dad!
Dad, I'm sorry. I won't do it again. I promise. Please forgive me once.
Gosh, you punk!
If a guy plays he can do that. Why are you so afraid?
It's okay!
Straighten your back!
Pretty bastard.
This. I caught a few carp   (Bread in the shape of fish)   for my son to eat.
Don't take the bones out, and just eat them.
Dad, too.
It's okay.
But then, those who run the one day cafe,
are you really close with them?
Hey, Seong No Eul!
Yeah. They have been my friends since middle school.
You probably know them.
Tae Joo and Hong Yi.
- No Eul!
- You still meet with those guys and hang out?
We are in different classes but we meet every day.
We eat our lunch box together, play soccer together
and sometimes study.
Oh right. Your mother's neck will probably fall off waiting.
Seong No Eul! Hey! Half basement!
Half basement! Wait!
- Hello.
- Hello
- Come here.
- What's that?
Dad, wait a minute.
So petty, eating all by yourself.
Want to have some? My dad bought it.
Give me.
I will eat the tail first.
Yes. Tonight's last contestant.
I will just read as to what is written here.
Contestant number 10. From Ssangmoon High School, Firetruck's Last Night's Story!
Sobangcha! Sobangcha! Sobangcha! Sobangcha!
♬ Last night, I hated you.
♬  Last night, I didn't like you.
♬  While I look at the lights which are spinning around and around
♬  I all by myself am heart broken.
♬ Every time my friends dance holding your hand
♬  Why can't I see your tormented image
♬  Did you also feel very lonely at last night's party?
♬ I can't change you even for the whole world.
♬  You. Don't you know why you are it?
♬  Last night, I hated you
♬  Last night, I didn't like you.
♬  While waiting for the incessant sound of the music to stop
♬  I was depressed all by myself
Sobangcha! Sobangcha! Sobangcha!
Hey, we're going.
Yeah. Thank you, Seon Woo. You were the best!
You like it that much? You're going to have it taken from you by your sister.
Are you crazy? Just you dare tell my family.
Deok Seon, we have something to talk about, right?
Guys, say hi. They are my friends.
- Hello.
- Hello
She is Jang Mi Ok. Among us we call her Jang Man Ok (Maggie Cheung).
Yes, hello.
She is Wang Ja Hyeon, among us Wang Jo Hyun (Joey Wong).
Hello.
Yes, hello.
Deok Seon, what are you among yourselves?
Me? Lee Mi Yeon (Korean actress, who plays the older version of Deok Seon).
Do you want to get hit?
How dare you say her name with that dirty mouth of yours.
You all saw each other in the ddeokbeokki store, right? Talk casually. We're the same age.
Should we?
Hey. You really danced very well.
The best.
No, no Ma'am. I'm not a good dancer.
What are you talking about? Let's talk casually.
You're Ssangmoon-dong's Park Nam Jung, right?
Hey, you danced better than Park Nam Jung.
Huh?
You are exaggerating.
No. I'm sorry.
That... I think we need to go. Kids, let's go.
Deok Seon, you know that we have something to talk about later right?
Then, we will be going.
- Hey, Deok Seon come here.
- Hey, talk as we go.
Me?
How could she be Joey Wong?
Hey but it's too late so I think we will be caught by the Dean.
How did she become Jang Man Ok?
Never mind.
Hurry and give it to me.
What do you keep on asking?
Liquor.
Oh, right.
Hey!
Right, liquor. I really had it with me earlier in the day.
I was holding on to it until earlier.
Later at 9, in front of the Kim Yoo Shin Youth Hostel gate.
Oh! I think your bus is leaving.
I'm going!
Let's go together!
King Kim So Ro snack bar. (The actor's name is Kim So Ro)
Seriously! Seriously! Leaving it to you!
I'm the crazy one! Seriously!
The Dean! Dean! Run!
Isn't that Ryong Nyong's father?
Teacher! Ryong Nyong's father!
Are you crazy?
You punks, stop over there!
Won't you stop right there? Stop right there! These punks want to die!
These punks! Just look at them!
Hey! Punks! Stop!
Hey! Punks!
Hey! Good! Very good! You are being punished by heaven!
I knew you will be punished! Stop right there!
Dong Ryong, you will die tonight!
Are you alright?
Why?
Why is your father so fast?
Seon Woo. Do you have a big rock near you?
Why?
Make me faint.
Breathe quietly.
Keep quiet!
Sheesh.
Let's go. Hurry. Let's go.
That hurts, right? Let's go, you punk.
This punk!
A lot.
Where did that one punk go?
He should be nearby. Jeong Hwan.
Where did you go?
This punk.
♫   While I am feeling little you   ♫
♫  Who are gently leaning on me  ♫
♫  Your sweet breathing becomes a song   ♫&lt;
♫  It lingers in my ears.    ♫&lt;
♫  With eyes which don't lie  ♫
♫  Looking at me, I love you.  ♫
♫  While two hearts go back and forth  believing without saying a word   ♫
♫  the night we are together...  ♫
♫  While two hearts go back and forth  believing without saying a word    ♫
♫  the night we are together ...   ♫
Dad!
Dad, Mom says to hurry and go home. Let's hurry and go home.
Okay. Just drink that and come home. I will be waiting.
Take this and go first.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
You didn't have this exchanged yet!
You need to have this exchanged tomorrow. Do you understand?
I bought it from a friend so how could I go and have it exchanged? I will just wear it.
Friend? Friend, my a**. How do you call a person like that your friend?
What kind of friend is like that? Why are all of your friends like that?
When they heard the rumors that we hit the jackpot they wanted to have a hand in it.
While there was not even one call when we didn't have a single briquette and had the children sleep in the cold.
But then, what is that friend doing? You know when Jeong Bong was this big
and he caught a cold but we didn't have money to buy him medicine so we borrowed money here and there.
That... Your hometown friend. The one who came to Seoul together with you.
He came suddenly and drank soju with you.
I thought he was such a clueless person. In this poverty how could we have a guest?
I thought so, but then your friend, as he left
he secretly gave 50,000 won saying to buy something delicious for Jeong Hwan and Jeong Bong.
He lives with his pay day by day.
That time, 50,000 won.
That time, that friend seemed like god.
Just find a friend like that and not those who just hurt you.
Huh? Call him.
It's him.
That person is him.
♫  You had a lot of hard times  ♫
♫  You lost all originality  ♫
I won't buy it today.
♫ All the sad stories are yours  ♫
♫  Brush away those for which you blamed yourself  ♫
Elder.
Give me some.
♫ Leave the past as the past  ♫
♫  That's what it means. ♫
Today... is the last.
Now, I can't buy.
♫  Let's sing  ♫
Yes. Yes. Go on.
♫  Say that you dreamed without regret  ♫
♫  Let the past be the past  ♫
♫  That's what it means. ♫
♫  Let's sing to those have left  ♫
♫  Say that you dreamed without regret  ♫
♫  Let the past be the past  ♫
♫  That's what it means.  ♫
♫  Let's  sing to those have left ♫
It was a hectic Sunday morning.
Four of the remaining fugitives and  earlier a fifth in a hostage's house which he entered have been captured.
While the hostage situation was bloody, it was brought to an end.
The drama of this escape leaves us with an infamous saying.
"There is one law for the rich and one law for the poor."
When you have money,  you are innocent.  If you have no money, you are guilty.
This case clearly shows the absurdity in our society.
Aigoo. What a waste.
It ended with a tragedy.
Aigoo. So pitiful.
What's so pitiful? Having no money is a crime.
Did you realize that just now?
Mom! Dad! I'm here! Tada! A gift.
This girl! Do you know how much that costs!
Mom!
Where do you leave your senses at!
I can't live because of you!
- Stop right there!
- Mom!
Mom! You said it was okay! What's wrong with you?
Then do I scold you when your teacher was right there?
Hurry and come here! Jeong Hwan move away.
We can just buy a new one, huh?
Deok Seon's mother, first calm down.
Jeong Hwan, get your head out of the way. I will end this with that girl! Move!
Mom! Mom! I was wrong. I won't do it again. Huh?
Such nonsense! Come here! Come here!
Oh my! I can't live seriously.
Who did that girl take after that she's like that! How much was that camera worth!
Oh my fate. My fate.
This person, then you could kill your child like that. We can just buy a new camera.
Just because she forgot the camera, you beat her up like that?
This is all your fault.
If you just earned a lot of money, would I be chasing that child around?
If you hadn't served as a guarantor for other people's loans, we would be living in luxury like and apartment.
If only I had money I could become a better mother to the children.
It's because we don't have money that I feel it's so unfair. This is all because of you!
Where are you going again?
To earn money.
You said you want to live like them upstairs so I will go and hit the jackpot.
Don't bet. Don't bet, please! It's such a waste of money!
Do you think that luck would just fall on anyone!
Three years ago.
May, 1985
Wow! We have three side dishes.
It looks delicious. There's also tofu. Is today a special day?
Eat while I'm saying it nicely.
Yes.
Our Jeong Bong, what are you collecting these days?
Probably... probably you all remember.
September 30, 1981. We heard very good news from the small town of Baden-Baden in far away Germany.
The winning bid is Seoul. Wow
(This was the time and place of the announcement of the site of the 1988 Olympics.)
Hyung is collecting lottery tickets lately. Olympic lottery.
Ouch!
Mom, I only buy one every month.
Mom, one only costs 500 won--
Is 500 won a small amount? With that you could buy 3 briquettes!
Hyung they're drawing now.
Indeed, the main character
somewhere is the one who unknowingly purchased the winning ticket.
I will just watch until today.
We'll begin with the first number. Roll it.
We'll go from Group one  to Group five.
Today's first lucky number in the  fifth place is one.
Next  the one in the one hundred thousand position
It is 10.  A one and a zero.
Now the one in the thousands position is 2.
Now what is in the  hundreds position? The hundreds place is
Three hundred and now the rest is tens
And ones place.
The tens place is 60
The end, ones place
ones place
- Perhaps 3?
- It's 3.
Congratulations!
Congratulations.  All again.  102363.
Again 102363
There has been just one winner.
Mom said to have some of this rice cake.
Dong Ryong.
We're moving.
Hyung!
Come here!
I want to go to college. I want a tutor too.
Aren't you hearing the chant?
Of course. What do you see me as?
- Where... just every thing you say!
- What crap are you saying.
- Everything I say, you just chew me out and make a big deal.
- Hurry and come out. Let's eat together.
- Do you want some juice?
- You drink some.
Father.
♬  I'm saying I came to love you for a long time. ♬
♬ The only thing I can give you is this candy ♬
♬  Why do birds fly?  ♬
You can just eat what's stuck on your face. Stupid.
Hey Do Ryong Nyong, why do you think it's like that?
What should I do?
What are you doing? Are you waiting for me?