Reply 1988
Now, I will introduce my harmonious family members, who are overflowing with love and happiness.
First, in his sixth year preparing for his college entrance exams,
an emblem of simple honesty and tenacity,
I introduce my oldest son Kim Jeong Bong!
It seems like he went to the library.
Hyper Olympic 50 won (6 cents) per round
Next, a person who resembles me from head to toe,
I introduce to you our family's second son, Kim Jeong Hwan!
Jeong Hwan, say something.
Please don't do these kinds of things.
It's my first time doing it today.
It looks like there's only my wife to rely on.
Our main room's madam, my own cheetah,
my jaguar! Honey, give us a word.
Please...
You brought that from your shop again? How much is it?
980,000 won ($1225).
How unusual of you, you narrow-minded fool.
How can you call your husband a narrow-minded fool?
Please say a word for your narrow-minded fool husband?
Oh, really, I want to hit you but I can't.
It's not because you won't hit me, but you can't because I give you no chance.
What do you mean, I have no chance?
It stings. It stings.
♫ Excuse, excuse me.
♫ You're excused.
♫ Is this the home of Fan-Expert which I can see into?
♫ That's right, right, right. How did you come to this place?
Don't indulge him, Deok Seon. It'll become a habit.
But it's funny to me.
My mom told me to bring this to you. My grandma brought it.
Aigoo, tell her we will enjoy it.
You must be happy. You like your grandma a lot.
Yes.
But she's leaving tomorrow.
Hey! So dirty with your bare hands.
Mind your business.
Oh, this scent. You smell good, Grandma.
Oh, an old person just stinks like an old person.
No, you smell like flesh. Dad smells like this, too.
Your stomach is so slim, so how did you give birth to Dad,
Big Uncle, and my fat aunts?
I gave birth to four kids as big as cows
so my belly shrunk to be this small.
What childish questions from a high schooler.
Grandma, do you know Seong Deok Seon's nickname?
- Don't say it.
- It's Teuk Gong Dae (Special Forces).
A special head that is terrible at studying.
( Teuk= special, Gongbu = study, Daegari =  (provincial word for head )
Then do you think you study well? You only go to protests.
You?
You really!
What are you girls doing?
I told you loud and clear, if you fight again
I will strip you naked and chase you out of the neighborhood. I'll kill you.
Mother, there's nothing uncomfortable, right?
- Then, please sleep comfortably.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Go.
- Yes.
I'll seriously kill you both.
Seong Deok Seon, know that you are alive because of Grandma.
Grandma, what was Big Uncle like? Was he smarter than Dad?
When it came to book smarts, your dad was much smarter.
That's how he went to the best vocational high school in Gwangju.
Your Big Uncle
had to get a job very young so he could support his little siblings.
But now, Big Uncle is the richest. He even lives in America.
Do think it's so easy to have a dry cleaning business in America?
He says that he can just afford to put food on the table these days.
When I think of your Big Uncle,
I still feel a stabbing ache in my heart.
Then who's a better son? My dad calls you every morning.
Why measure such a thing? They are both filial sons.
Your Big Uncle and your dad never fought, not even once.
Do you think they were like you two?
That's because Unni picks a fight first.
Hey!
- Aigoo, again.
- What?
- You, really!
Come out.
Perfect.
Episode 2: One Thing You Are Misunderstanding About Me
Today's Historic Showdown
Be careful.
But what is so urgent
that you have to go back so soon? Since you've come up here,
isn't it good to spend one more night?
Aigoo, I have to hurry and go down and dry the peppers.
Really, there are so many things to do.
Grandma, I'll visit you when winter break starts.
- Until then, be healthy.
- Okay, my child.
But what about Bo Ra? Where did she already go?
She went to the library early. College students these days study really hard.
What library? She probably went to put up protest posters.
Oh my. Are you going to throw this away?
- Huh?
- Yes. You can't use this anymore, Mother.
It looks totally fine. Give it.
- Yes.
- Let me see.
I'll take this and use it as an umbrella container.
Mom.
Why do you take that when there are so many things to carry.
When I go to the countryside I'll buy you something better than that.
Aigoo, why waste money like that?
I can just use this.
You'll be late for work. Let's hurry up and go.
- Hurry.
- Really.
- Good bye.
- Have a safe trip.
I'll carry them.
Mom, please give this to me. I'll carry it.
Since there's a lot of that, give them to me.
- Don't worry about me and go.
- Give it to me, I said.
Give what? Give me that.
Why are you holding all of it? Hurry up and go.
- Ah, really.
- So bothersome.
♫  It's Saturday evening, don't hesitate like that  ♫
(Kim Wan Sun's "Feeling Good Day")
♫  Try dancing with me  ♫
♫  For today, I don't want to talk about tiresome things  ♫
♫  Try dancing  ♫
- I'll get going.
- Oh, are you going?
You'll die if you get caught by your sister wearing that!
Unni drinks alcohol every Saturday. I'll come home earlier than her.
♫  That golden Saturday, that day is today  ♫
♫  Try dancing with me  ♫
Hey, Kim Jeong Pal ( Jeong Hwan's nickname ), how do I look?
We're late. Get lost.
Hey, there are only three minutes left.
This is new clothing. How do you like it?
Isn't that Noona's?
Hey, hey, there are two minutes left. Hurry, hurry!
♫  Yes, let's go, one, two, three, four...  ♫
Hello!
♫  Everyone look at me  ♫
Hello, Go Kil-Dong Ahjussi. ( Go Kil-Dong - character from the Dooly cartoon )
Hey, Hee Dong! When did you come? ( Hee Dong - character from the Dooly cartoon. )
Yesterday. Are you going to school?
My Taek, drink milk and hurry and grow up. You have to grow up and marry Noona.
Special Forces, there is one minute left. One minute!
Do you want to die? Hey!
Sangmoon Girls' High School
Come to school a bit early. Aren't you sick of having your hair pulled in front of the gate?
I've got a rock for a head so I don't feel anything. ( rock head = stupid )
Hey, Wang Jo Hyeon. So what percent did you get?  (Wang Jo Hyeon is the Korean name of Hong Kong actress Joey Wong.)
It's only 45%. I think our love would not come true.
You fool! You wrote it wrong.
- How?
- You wrote your name first. It means that you only like Oppa Byeon Jin Seob at 40%.
Really? Let me do it again.
I should write Oppa's name first.
Byeon Wang Jin Ja Seob Hyeon
- 70%!
- It's 70%!
70%? Byeon Jin Seob likes you 70%? What the heck!
Me too! Me too!
Tom Cruise &amp; Seong Deok Seon
What is this? It's not noodles.
It's spaghetti. You haven't tried it, right?
It's my first time seeing it. You should just make noodles, Hyung-nim.
I have lots of money and nowhere to spend it. I'm going to eat all the food rich people eat before I die.
What are you doing? Are you making noodles? Is that chewy noodles?
I said it's spaghetti!
Alright. Don't open your eyes like Kim Wan Sun ( singer ). It's so scary that I could die.
But then, why is the celebration for Taek's victory held in our house?
What food would his widowed father prepare? I just told him to bring chicken. Taek is also coming.
Is that so? I get to see Master Choi's face after a while.
If I had a daughter how nice would it be to have him as a son-in-law.
I have dibs on Taek. He's going to be my son-in-law.
Isn't Bo Ra coming today? All the kids are coming.
She's joined some academic society at school, so she's late every Saturday. She won't be home until after midnight.
Mom! Where are you?
Bo Ra?
What is that? Why did she come back so fast?
Mom!
Eight, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16.
How old am I?
18. You have two more to go.
Seventeen, 18.
It's over if that breaks. If that breaks your love will not come true.
Hey! Don't even dream of love before you take those braces off!
Be quiet. The fate of my first love depends on this.
I'm going on an MT (membership training) today.
(An MT is a trip for college students to foster friendships between seniors and freshmen.)
I will be going after I pack my things.
W--W-Why an MT all of a sudden?
I don't know. A '84 class sunbae got paid for tutoring so he wants to go to Dae Sung Ri.
( Koreans count class by entry year )
He's such a crazy bastard! Why does he do whatever he wants?
Mom, the thing that was here...
haven't you seen my leggings?
I washed them this morning so I hung them up. They're probably dry, so I'll bring them to you.
Never mind. I'll just wear these pants.
But then Mom, I don't see that.
You know... My jacket.
Where's my jacket?
My baseball jacket.
Ah... That... I took it to the cleaners.
No, no. My denim jacket.
Oh? Where's my denim jacket?
It was here for sure. I even saw it this morning.
Where is my denim jacket?
T-That... Y-Y-You see, Bo Ra...
It was here for sure this morning! Why is it not here now?
Where is my denim jacket?
Ahh... Did I wash it? Wait.
Where is my denim jacket?!?
Seong Deok Seon! I'm going to kill you!
The men's track racing will now begin.
Representing the U.S., it's Carl Lewis.
It's track and field athlete from Canada,  Ben Johnson.
I think the family downstairs is more fun than this.
Let me use your phone! And your directory.
Yes, this is Ssangmoon High School.
Ryoo Dong Ryong's da— no, may I speak to the Dean of Students.
Yes, this is the Dean of Students.
Dong Ryong's dad, please put No Eul on the line.
Yes, hello.
Mom?
Ssangmoon High School
♫ Why don't you know that?
(Lyrics from Sobangcha's "Last Night's Story")
Noona!
Ssangmoon Girls High School
Dae Gwang Computer Game Room
They're starting.
Lewis... Ben Johnson!
Ben Johnson comes in first.
Is he on drugs? He's on drugs.
( Ben Johnson was later disqualified for doping. )
Aish! What am I going to wear? I'm going to kill Seong Deok Seon!
Seong Deok Seon, where did you go!
Aigoo. Where would she go? She would be in school.
I sometimes wonder how she got into Seoul National University.
Here she comes.
Deok Seon.
Where are you going?
- To kill Seong Deok Seon.
- It's right here.
It was here.
I forgot.
I'm back from school.
You're here, Deok Seon. You came really early.
It's Saturday. So I didn't go to C.A. (Club Activities) today and just came home.
Hey, Seong Deok Seon.
What?
Did you go to school dressed like that?
Of course I was. Would I be naked?
Deok Seon, hurry and wash up. Let's go to Jeong Hwan's.
Today we are having Taek's victory party. Jeong Hwan's mom is preparing some American noodles.
This is all wet! What am I supposed to do?
Should I dry it with a hair dryer?
When would you finish drying this?
Why did you wash it without telling me?
What am I supposed to wear today?
Hey! Grow up, will you?
What did you just say?
Grow up, I said. And stop bothering Mom.
You, seriously! You grow up! Always coming in last place!
I'm not in last place! There are still 400 people behind me!
That's something to brag about!
And also, why would a college student who just eats and plays need clothes? Just wear whatever!
So ugly, who would look at you?
Okay, right. I held back so much today. Today is your death anniversary.
Are you pretty, then? Your nose is as big as Namsan Mountain.
Seriously!
I'm back... going to school.
You think I'm a pushover? I'm your Unni. You think you're my friend?
You disrespected me first!
You want to die?
You crazy bitch!
Don't talk to your sister like that.  Try it once more and you will really die.
Hey! Let go!
Say it again! Huh? You really!
This decision will change the next ten years of your life.
♫  Mi Ji's  ♫
("Mi Ji's World" by Cho Yong Pil)
♫  World
♫  let's find it
♫  and leave together
♫  The song
♫  of love
♫  don't stop singing it
It's my wish to meet Yong Pil Oppa before I die.
He's not your oppa. He's two years younger than you.
Aigoo. Once an oppa, forever an oppa.
Hyung-nim. What is this? He's not here yet?
Jin Joo is here.
What smells so good?
You came home early today.
I shouldn't be late on a day like this when Taek's dad is going to buy us food.
And, what's today's menu?
I made spaghetti.
Ghetti, ghetti... What is that?
Spaghetti. It's American noodles.
But how do you eat this?
What do you mean 'how do you eat this'? Everyone eats the same.
But why isn't Taek's dad coming? The noodles will swell.
Isn't Taek's dad this neighborhood's Jo Yong Pil?
The superstar normally comes at the end.
Superstar came.
The door is open. Why is he ringing the bell?
What a suffocating man.
Hello.
Kantapia! ( fictional star in outer space where cartoon character Baby Dinosaur Dooly comes from )
Go to Jeong Bong Oppa's room.
Why did you come now? My neck was about to break from waiting.
You should close up your jewelry shop on a day like this.
Your son earns so much money, you are being silly.
How is that my money? It's Taek's money.
What would Taek spend money on? You just sock it all away.
You should live using some of that money.
Oh, I brought this.
Wow, you even bought two. Honey, put that in the kids' room.
Okay.
Is Taek coming? It's been a long time since I saw him.
He will come.
He doesn't go to school, so he only has friends in this alley.
He wants to rest his head for once.
- Mister Choi, say hello to this.
- Oh my.
What is that?
Taek's father, wave your hand once.
Aigoo, forget about me.
Then, Bo Ra's father can say something.
How about a word from this town's Ugly Sisters?
- It's a camera!
- It's from the broadcasting station.
It films movement.
Where's the ahjumma? There was the most beautiful ahjumma among the three.
Have you perhaps seen our cheetah?
Here she was.
Take that down at the count of three. One, two, three.
You thought I'd take it down, right?
Really! Aren't you going to put that away?
My eye almost fell out.
So scary, how can I live?
- We've come.
Come in.
What about my Seon Woo?
He's coming behind us.
Hello. I've come from school.
Did my son come?
Our Seon Woo, you know that I love you, right?
Yes.
Why isn't my friend coming?
Who?
Aigoo, President Seong!
Aigoo, President Kim!
This is really great to meet you. It's great to meet you! Great to meet you!
Great to meet you!
Deok Seon, thank you for accepting it.
I understand. I know, too.
These two are being ridiculous.
- But why isn't Taek coming?
- Why?
He's a star for sure. He's very late.
I told him to borrow some comic books.
Wow... Deok Seon has a huge liver (is brave).
She treats the Great Master Choi like her slave.
He's only a star outside, do you think he receives nice treatment between them?
They've been friends since they were little kids.
Hello.
Aigoo, Taek, welcome.
Oh my, has Master Choi Taek arrived?
You personally came to a lowly place.
You're really an honor to the family, what a happy occasion.
And say hello to our family's son-in-law.
How can you say that? I'm going to marry Jin Joo to him.
We're first, right, Taek?
Nice to meet you, I'm your new mom.
I'm your new dad.
Forget it. Stop. Taek, hurry up and go in. The kids are waiting for you.
Enjoy your meal.
Taek is all grown up now.
Aigoo, how does he seem like such an adult?
After seeing Taek, our kids seem like babies.
He's still a child.
He only know how to play Baduk. He doesn't know anything about the world.
Come on. All of the world's logic is contained in Baduk.
Do you think Taek doesn't know that? And he's even the best Baduk player in the world.
His nature is probably better than us adults, even.
But how much did Taek receive as his prize money this time?
I heard that it was the biggest competition in Korea.
Fifty-million won ($62,500).
Taek is probably going to have to treat the kids to something big today.
I have no words.
That's so nice. I envy him.
Fifty-million won ($62,500)?
Spicy rice cakes.
Spicy rice cakes. Spicy rice cakes! Spicy rice cakes!
Spicy rice cakes! Spicy rice cakes! Spicy rice cakes!
- Spicy--
- Hey, eat some fried chicken.
I'm fine.
Hey, look at your pale face. Exercise, and don't always stay in the association ( Korea Baduk Association ).
Look at this. Is this your stomach or your back? You are so thin.
Forget it.
Hey, Taek, you're going to China again, right? When are you going? Are you going before your birthday?
Why? Are you going to give Taek a birthday party?
No. To ask him to steal us a bottle of alcohol.
Mom!
Why are you like this?
Why do you ask Taek to get that? Buy it yourself.
He's on a different level than we are. He always receives expensive alcohol whenever he goes to China.
Hey, Choi Taek, don't give it to your dad this time, and give it to us.
Hey. Where are you going?
To get some juice.
You better not tell.
Okay.
Hey, Special Forces. Only bring juice. Don't eat the ham.
It's Hyung Jeong Bong's
I'm not going to eat it.
Land. Land is the best. Buy land no matter what, Taek's Dad.
These days Ilsan ( ref. Ilsan New City, Goyang City, Gyeonggi Province ) is on the rise.
If you don't know anything, don't say anything.
What is there to see in Ilsan? It's all rice paddies.
If you have a substantial sum of cash, the safest thing is to just put it in the bank.
Bank interest is not much...
Yes, the interest has dropped, so it's only 15% now.
But you still constantly get interest. There's no place safer than the bank.
Why stash 50 million won ($62,500) in the bank?
Taek's dad, buy an apartment.
The best apartment in Gangnam. What do you call it. Eum Ma apartment.
Eun Ma. ( Because of different dialect, people from different provinces pronounce things differently )
Eum Ma. Eum Ma apartment.
Eun Ma. Eun Ma.
That's what I said. Eum Ma. Eum Ma. The Eum Ma ( sounds like mom in Korean ) apartment costs about 50-million won (about $63K).
That's crazy. How can an apartment cost as much as 50-million won?
( Eun Ma Apts sold for $600K in 2013 )
The parcel price is 30 million won ($37500)...
How about near Bundang-gu... ?
Ham. Ham.
Do you think such things would happen to us?
Ham.
Anyway, Taek's Dad, I congratulate you.
Yes, thank you.
My kids are busy spending money.
I wonder what kind of luck Taek's dad was born with.
Jeong Bong's Dad, why don't you hurry up and come here. It's not done yet?
So what if he's rich? He doesn't even know how to use his expensive things.
If it doesn't work, give up and come sit here.
Why are you fussing with turning on music in the afternoon?
Then, let's first toast among us!
Congratulations!
Jin Joo.
Does it taste good?
Can you give me just one bite?
Here, here. It's here. It's all still here.
Who is it?
Who is it? I think someone came.
Taek's Father, what did I tell you to buy?
What did I tell you to buy if you get money?
Apartment.
(Yoon Soo Il - Apartment)
Get up. Everyone get up!
Come alive! Come alive!
♫ The starlight flows
♫ as we cross this bridge
♫ and we pass by the windy reed forest
♫ pass pass
Close the door tightly.
They're at it again.
- Who is today's guest singer?
- The people who usually come.
- It's my mom
- And my dad.
♫  With my longing heart, I call you
Hello? Hello?
♫  Your beautiful voice
Yes! Yes!
♫  Always, to me, always, to me
♫  in your apartment
- Good!
- Yes!
Taek, do you have anything you want for your birthday?
That's right. Tell us before you go to China.
Do you even listen to music?
He only listens to Deulgukhwa's music.
That's right. Jeon In Kwon ( lead vocalist of Deulgukhwa ) released a solo album. Should we at least buy you that?
Hey, Kim Jong Pal, you heard, right? Buy it.
No thanks.
Hey! Brazil Spicy Race Cake might close. It closes early on Saturday.
♫  Today, because of foolishness and regret
♫  I came to meet you again
- Where are you going?
- To eat spicy rice cakes.
♫  no one is here
♫  in your lonely apartment
Good bye.
♫   no one is here...   ♫
October, 1988
Yesterday at seven o'clock pm,
the closing ceremony at Jamsil Stadium marked the finale of the Seoul Olympics.
In this Seoul Olympics, in which a total of 159 countries participated,
the Soviet Union took first place with 55 gold medals,
East Germany got second place with 37 gold medals.
And Korea got fourth place in the combined medal rankings with 33 gold medals,
which was the best Olympic result in history, for Korea.
Hey! Hurry and get up!
Why does he always drift to the floor every day?
Get up, Seong No Eul! You have to go to school.
What time is it, Noona?
It's 6:30. Hurry up and eat and wash up.
Hello? Mom.
Did you get up? What about food?
We're eating right now. What about Grandma? Is Grandma okay?
She's not well. I have to stay here few days more. Did you pack your lunch?
I did. What about Dad? Is Dad okay?
He's okay. He's doing well.
Did you wake Unni up?Today's the day she goes to school early.
I don't know. She'll probably wake up on her own.
♫  Young. I have bookmarked with.  ♫
(Lee Sun-hee - Young)
Big Noona, get up. Eat breakfast.
♫  a gingko leaf that's faded away  ♫
Aish, really. Bam. You want to die?
♫  Can't wait to see. Young   ♫
She said she's not eating.
Tell her, "I told you to eat for sure."
She said, "I told you to eat for sure."
Aish!
Tell her to stuff herself.
She told me, "Stuff yourself."
Tell her if she's not going to eat, I'm going to wash up first.
Really... So annoying.
She told me to say that if you're not going to eat, she's going to wash up first.
Tell her if she wants to die then do it.
Okay.
If you want to die, then do it. If you want to die, then do it.
Is it funny? Is it funny? You said die?
Ah! Really! You are both mental patients!
Mom...
Really!
Is there no rank in this house? Why do you wash up first?
You didn't wash up! I'm late, too!
Did I tell you yesterday that I'll wash up first or not?
Then you should've woken up first and washed up.
- What? "You"?
- She thinks that she's a king or something.
- "She"!
-That's right. "She, she!"
You crazy girl, you!
You come here.
Let go, let go!
What? You say 'she' to your unni?
I'm going to tell Mom!
Did you say 'you' and 'she' to your sister? 'You'?
- Hey!
- Let go. Let go!
Don't forget what we planned for this evening.
What?
Look at him acting like he doesn't know. We said that we'll go to the Samyang Movie Theater.
Ah...
Michael saw it and he said that it's totally better than "Two Moon Junction" ( an erotic movie ).
Isn't it too much? What did your mom make?
It's not even fully cooked.
It's better than just bringing instant black bean noodles!
Hey, you know about lunchtime, right?
About what again?
Soccer, you bastard.
I won't play with Crazy Dog again. Do you want me to break my ankle again? And his cursing.
He only has a go with me. He's a total psycho.
It's okay. He's nice.
With what evidence?
He doesn't smoke.
- Does that make him kind?
- Yeah.
- Simple bastard. Are you an amoeba?
- We already told him that you're playing.
Whatever. I'm going to sleep during lunchtime.
Crazy guy. Why do you sleep at lunchtime when we have math, physics, and everything else?
Jeong Hwan said that he'll cover everything for you. Seon Woo, Seon Woo.
Without you, who's going to score the goals? Who's going to?
I don't know. Whatever.
Seon Woo...
I'm going to waste you.
High School English II
Stop reading HR ( high teen romances ), you people.
Aren't you sick of high teen romance?
What is this?
"An Officer and a Princess?"
The captain quickly moved in the direction of her lips.
And he deeply coveted her lips.
She started becoming excited.
What excited her was not his rough lips, but
his sculpted, bronzed, bare chest.
Are you working out your frustrations with this?
What are you talking about? Hurry up and give it.
Hey, get a hold of yourself. There is no such guy in reality.
Sculpted, bronzed, bare chest, my butt.
Hey, Ben Johnson.
Ben Johnson has the greatest body.
Hey, get them no matter what.
Push them whenever the referee isn't looking. Understand?
Yes.
If you guys lose again, I'm going to bust your heads.
- Yes.
- Let's, fighting!
Why aren't those bastards coming?
Aren't you going to hurry up and come?!
You take care of Crazy Dog. You know that I hate those kind of bastards, right?
That nerd bastard.
Get ready.
Pass! Pass!
Come here.
Goal!
I put it in.
Ah, really!
Did you see that? The referee is not looking?
Here, here!
Here, here...
This one was pretty weak. They only kiss.
Throw it away.
Don't disappoint me, please?
Show me your naked skin.
Deok Seon, the teacher is looking for you.
Hey, what should we do?
If you get caught, say that I looked at all of them.
You just delivered them, okay?
Deok Seon.
Yes, Teacher.
Answer the phone. It's your family.
What?
Hello? Who is it?
If it wasn't for Crazy Dog, we would have won, 5:0.
No, 10:0.
Hey, Dong Ryong, what time is the movie? We just have to skip late-night studies, right?
Three o'clock.
Crazy bastard. We should still attend class before we go.
I meant, Crazy Dog bastard at three o'clock.
Move aside.
You guys are really close.
Yes, Hyung. They're my neighborhood friends.
Hey, Student Class President.
You play soccer well. You be the striker from now on.
I said you should be the striker from the next game.
He's so scary. Look at his glare.
I mean... What are you going to do if you glare at me like that, huh?
Are you all that if you're class president?
What is this? Is it a necklace?
Take it off, you bastard. A student shouldn't wear necklaces to school.
A class president should be a role model, right.
Take it off, you bastard. Take it off.
Take it off!
Are you deaf?
Take it off, you bastard!
Hey, next class is drill practice. We're dead if we're late.
Let's go.
This idiot.
See you next time. You're going to die.
Something dropped.
Aish. Let's hurry up and go. We've got that class taught by the dean of students.
Hey, can't you just take it off for a moment?
How can I take it off when it's a keepsake from my dad?
Why can't you take it off? You can just take if off for a moment and put it back on.
So frustrating.
Don't cry. Pack your bags well and come.
Unni...
- Unni...
- It's okay. Stop crying.
Grandma probably went to a good place.
I talked to your teacher, so pack your bags and hurry home.
Unni...
No Eul will come too. We have to make it to the last bus, so we don't have time. Hurry and come.
Seoul to Gwangju
Gokseong
Hey, hurry up and sleep.
It's going to take a long time to get to Gokseong ( Gokseong County, a stop along the bus route and where Grandma lives ). If you get there, you won't be able to sleep.
I understand. I won't cry.
Are you more sad than Dad?
You shouldn't cry either. A son has to comfort his dad.
Let's go.
Is this a mourner's house? It seems like a party house.
This is Grandma's house, right?
Bo Ra.
Did you come? Eat.
Where is Dad?
There are only our aunts.
Is Dad sick somewhere?
Hey, Bo Ra.
Dad...
What are you doing? Say hello.
Elder, this is my first child, Bo Ra.
She's a student of the best college in Korea, Seoul National University.
Hello.
Oh my, oh my. You are Bo Ra?
When did she become a lady?
When she was little she was so smart and good at studying.
It's not as if I had the money to send her to tutoring academies
or give her private tutoring like other fathers.
But she studied well herself.
And she got into Seoul National University.
That's great.
And, this is our second daughter, Deok Seon.
She is the one who came out on television during the Olympics.
You are Deok Seon?
I saw you on television.
Take a picture with us later.
Yes, let's do that.
From what I heard from her,
the picket holding? The competition was very fierce.
Of course, you are on television when the whole world is watching.
So from what I hear, it's only one out of hundreds, no thousands of competitors.
That is amazing.
She's great.
And, the last guy is our youngest, No Eul.
Unlike how he looks, he is such a filial son.
He looks like such a good person.
Hyung, it's me, Jae Yong.
How big your grief must be.
Oh my! Oh my! Jae Yong! This punk!
How long has it been?
You look so much better than before.
Oh, Hyung-nim.
Let's sit somewhere and have a drink.
Yes, I'll sit over there, Hyung-nim.
Unni. Maybe Dad is a cyborg?
How could he not shed a single tear?
Eat up.
It been a really long time.
It has been.
Isn't the soup good? It's thick.
Are adults usually like that? They don't get sad?
Be quiet and just keep frying the patties.
The aunts are the same too. It's their mom. It isn't time to be bragging about rings.
This is white gold.
White gold is plated. Pure gold is the real thing.
Just look at the design.
I pity Grandma.
Aigoo. Hey, go get the younger ones and go sleep first.
I cleaned up the room over there.
But isn't Big Uncle coming?
You called him when Grandma fell ill. He wasn't even able to see her go.
He'll probably arrive tomorrow. It's not like America is somewhere nearby.
And if he can't come, there's nothing we can do.
Grandma is pitiful.
Stop crying. I'm trying to go easy on you, but...
What? I can't even cry when I want to?
Seriously!
Keep it down. There are people watching.
Subway Exit
( Mia Station on the #4 line )
But then, what are we going to do if there are police?
The policemen in the Republic of Korea are so busy, why would they come to a movie theater out here?
That's nonsense.
Sam Yang Theatre
Sam Yang Movie Theater
The police... ? A thief must have broken in.
It's because it's the first day of the movie. It will be okay tomorrow.
- We're coming again tomorrow?
- Well, aren't we?
- Let's go.
- Where? You want to go back to night study?
Am I crazy? Taek's room.
Why?
The sweet honey-like love story that happens beneath the mulberry tree. "Ppong 2." ( mulberry=bbong ) I borrowed that (videotape).
Taxi.
♫  Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, perk, perk  ♫
♫  Stretch, stretch, perk, perk, perk  ♫
♫  Stretch, stretch, perk, perk  ♫
♫  La la la, hop hop  ♫
♫  hop hop  ♫
♫  hop hop hop  ♫
♫  Look at the sky and knock knock knock  ♫
♫  Look down at the ground and stomp stomp stomp  ♫
♫  Look down at the ground and  ♫
I'm going.
Seon Woo.
You're going to be late for dinner, right?
Yeah. Mom, when are you going to Gokseong (County)?
Gokseong(County)? I'm going tomorrow.
I'm planning to go together with the neighbors.
Seon Woo, this will be cold by dinnertime so eat it with cup ramyun. How much is it?
Just give me 500 won (63 cents).
Lunch box.
Eat it with cup ramyun. How much is it?
10,000 won ($12.50).
Do you want to die?
I'm going.
Mother, just give me 100 won (13 cents).
If I have 100 won I could play with the Olympic Heroes for the whole day.
Study.
Mother, please give me 100 won.
Look at you, here like this.
Oppa, get up so that you can eat breakfast.
Hurry and wake up. Eat.
Eat some.
Eat this.
Mix the rice with the soup.
My...
Haven't you made cockles? Or fried patties? How about some oysters?
- For breakfast?
- It's warm so mix it together.
You know I like it.
The spicy beef stew is cooked really well.
Wow. As expected of a nouveau riche family's son.
Here.
Kimchi.
What is that? You only have kimchi?
Nothing besides kimchi.
Curry rice.
Then you should eat what you will have for dinner.
I was going to. I also ate curry for breakfast.
Here.
There's no side dish.
Would there be soup?
None.
Then...
Kimchi fried rice.
Hey, hey. Let's eat mine together.
Aigoo! Sausage. It's difficult to make this taste bad.
Let's try this once.
So salty!
What does your Mom make every day?
I think it's okay.
It's eggshell. It's okay.
At his house, his family environment makes it so there's no way to gain weight.
So salty.
You both know about the second try tonight, right?
I think the police will still be there today.
Hyung's (referring to himself) already prepared for it.
You guys have brains for studying, but you do not possess the wisdom of life.
But what about dinner? And our lunch boxes?
It's all eggshells and sausage, anyway.
I will be buying today. Hamburger, call?
Of course, it's call. There's no time so hurry and strip.
We are three soldiers.
Salute.
Wait. I need to go to the restroom.
What? Already?
Crazy punk!
♫ Stretch, stretch, stretch, perk, perk
♫ Stretch, stretch, perk, perk, perk...
Seon Woo.
You're asked to come, too.
Did Uncle (husband of aunt) come to play go-stop? Because it's not his mother?
Hey, the daughter is like that so what more can you expect from the son-in-law?
These punks, you've done so well! So well!
These seniors who only have a few days before the college entrance exams, huh?
Have you punks gone crazy? Huh?
Can you still be considered student leaders? Can you? Can you?
You are not in your right minds! How could you be here!
Seriously, these punks!
Punk.
Aigoo. Who do we have here? Isn't this my son?
You must be very busy so what brings you here?
- Hello, Father.
- Yes, yes.
I was just enjoying cultural life—
What do are you spouting? What cultural life, you punk!
Instead of studying!
- This crazy!
- Father! Father!
Who? Who is your father?
Your father has died since his insides exploded because you give him so much stress, you punk!
If you're not good at studying then at least you should not cause trouble.
I will kick you, you kid!
Punk. Aiyoo. Aiyoo.
Know that you are all saved because of Seon Woo. Got that?
You all come to my office after your morning assembly tomorrow.
- Yes.
- You understand?
- Understand?
Yes!
I will see you later at home—
Don't even think about coming home tonight! You punk.
Father, I respect you.
Hey, Class President.
See me for a bit.
Hey. Hey.
Thank you. How should I repay this debt?
- Hyung, that's not it—
- Keep quiet.
Hey, great Class President. I said I'm thankful.
Look at this bastard. His senior is talking.
What is this?
Didn't I tell you to take that off?
Take it off, you bastard!
Bastard!
That... is Seon Woo's father's.
That was a keepsake given when his father passed away.
So what?
What do you want me to do?
Are you allowed to do this to your senior just because you don't have a father?
Are you bragging that you don't have a father?
Are you parading around just because you don't have a father, you bastard!
Has this Crazy bastard lost it?
Do you spew whatever you want just because you have a mouth?
Watch what you say, bastard.
It seems like Big Uncle is not going to come. It's almost ten.
The funeral cortege is tomorrow, so if he can't come today then he's not coming.
Dad, get some sleep.
Aigoo. My pretty and kind daughter.
Your dad is fine.
I'm fine.
Dong Il.
What should we do about our poor mother, Hyung?
Our mother is so pitiful. What should we do?
For what was she in such a hurry to go so soon?
What's the hurry!
Now we can't see our Mom!
We can't see our Mom anymore!
Oppa! Why did you just come now?
Why did you come so late?
We waited so much! You didn't even get to see her for the last time!
Mom earnestly looked for you, Big Oppa!
Adults are just enduring it.
Our pitiful mother!
Why did you come now? Why now?
They are just busy doing things as an adult,
and they are withstanding the weight of their age by pretending to be strong.
I don't need things like this. What's the use
Adults also hurt.
I can't live! I can't live without Mom!
Oppa!
Mother!
You didn't even get to see Oppa!
Come here.
Sit down.
Give me your hand.
♫  Will it leave someday, this green youth?  ♫
(Kim Feel + Kim Chang Wan - Youth)
♫  Like a flower which wilts and blooms again  ♫
♫  With the bright moonlight streaming through the window  ♫
♫  The love song of my youth is sad  ♫
Han Il Bank, 20 Years, Seong Dong Il
I'm off.
Jeong Hwan, can't I sleep at your house tonight? The dean of students lives in our house.
Do you think he won't know you're at our house, you idiot.
What are we going to do about that necklace?
I can just not wear it anymore.
But what do we do about your face?
Just worry about yourself.
I'm going.
Go.
But still sometimes, it's okay to be deluded.
If we can make Mom believe that she is a cooking queen
then we can just eat the incredulously horrid tasting lunch box without complaints.
I'm back.
Oh, you're here, my son.
- Aigoo, my child
- Mom, I will be washing up first. You can sleep first.
Okay.
My Seon Woo. You finished your lunch. Was it delicious?
Yeah! It was delicious.
We don't need to rashly insert truth into happy delusions.
Sometimes we have to be deluded to be happy.
Choi Taek 6-Dan (rank in Baduk) has scored another victory in China.
Yesterday at 6 PM, the Shangri-La Hotel in Beijing
was the place of the Tong Yang Cup competition with participants from three countries.
Choi Taek 6-Dan defeated Jeo Bi Pyung 9-dan of China,
after 343 moves, and claimed victory.
Choi Taek 6-Dan returned to Korea at Kimpo Airport this morning.
In addition to his victory, to celebrate his 18th birthday...
Taek's mother must be happy even in heaven.
Can there be another woman like her in this world?
Person, if you die, that's it. What's use of being a filial child to a dead person?
You have to be good to them while your parent is still alive.
Is it a black out?
I think the glowstarter switch must be out. I'll go buy it. Give me money.
While you go out buy 200 won (25 cents) worth of bean sprouts so I can make soup tomorrow morning.
- Don't drink alcohol.
- I understand.
Aigoo, Master Choi!
Did you get off work now?
Hello.
Right, Taek, I think you have to be my drinking buddy today.
Our Taek has already become an adult.
When did you mature?
You're all grown up now.
Ahjussi.
I heard that your mother passed away. I couldn't go ...
I'm sorry.
Why do you bring that up? I might cry.
That's right. Whether she's alive or dead,
the person you want to see the most is your mom.
Gosh, I miss my mom.
Our Taek, when do you miss your mom the most?
Every day.
I miss her every single day.
A mature child just does not voice his complaints.
♫    Together let's    ♫
He only becomes used to being in a situation where he has to look mature.
He just becomes used to the expectant gaze of others.
♫   All of your hurt memories, all  ♫
A mature child is still a child.
♫  bury it deep in your heart  ♫
Delusions are short but misunderstandings are long.
Therefore, delusions could be freedom, but misunderstandings should be forbidden.
♫  Let the past be the past.  ♫
♫  That's what it means.  ♫
♫  To those who have left, let's sing.  ♫
♫  Tell them that you loved them without regrets  ♫
♫ Happy birthday.
♫ Happy birthday!
♫ To our beloved Taek.
Please come home earlier.
Hey, hey, look.
Wear something different, bastard. Are you a grandpa?
We were going to die from hunger from waiting for you. We even called the baduk academy.
- Hurry up and blow. The candles are going to burn out.
- One, two, three!
Hey, hey, here's your present.
- It's finished right?
- Where is it?
Show it. Take it out.
Hey, hey. Do this later. Where is it?
I want to watch Saturday Night Movies. Let's watch that.
Hurry up and take it out.
Hey, look at me.
- Lower the volume!
- You're not going to eat all of this, right? I'm going to take some home.
Look at me. Where is it?
- Hey, it's probably inside his bag!
- Bag, bag!
Bag, bag. Open the bag.
There! There! There!
Oh, oh, oh! Fruit alcohol! You did well.
Mom! The kids are drinking alcohol!
Lower the volume!
Mom, the guys are drinking!
Taek moved to this block last.
Ha Min Books and Toys
♫  Today, from a forgotten friend I got a call  ♫
(Deulgukhwa - Hyehwa-dong)
♫  that he will be leaving far away tomorrow  ♫
After Taek's mother passed away, Taek left his hometown,
filled with the memories of his mother, and came to Seoul.
I don't know why this shy father-and-son pair came to this neighborhood, of all neighborhoods, but
one thing for sure is that the four mischievous kids in this alley gained a new friend.
♫  riding a bumpy subway and finding my way back  ♫
♫  so many things we have forgotten, as we live  ♫
♫  When we were young, this narrow alley looked so wide  ♫
♫  My beloved old friend runs to greet me  ♫
From the time Taek was young, he didn't say much and was quiet.
So he might have found his unusually boisterous neighborhood friends to be too much for him.
♫  The big world full of hope that we dreamed about together, he wants to meet it  ♫
♫  Tomorrow he will leave far away  ♫
♫  Someday on the day that he returns, let us meet again with wide smiles  ♫
♫  Tomorrow he will leave far, far away  ♫
♫  Riding a bumpy subway and finding my way back  ♫
tanning, custom tailoring
♫  So many things we have forgotten, as we live  ♫
♫  When we were young, this narrow alley looked so wide  ♫
♫  My beloved old friend runs to greet me  ♫
Still, Taek was always together with us.
Even though we did mischievous or pathetic deeds, he was always by our sides.
Of course, although he always had a dour, emotionless expression, he was always with us.
Ha Min Books and Toys
The alley can create friendships just with time.
That is how a quiet kid and four loud kids became friends, and
that was how we became five.
You've only had this much, and... I thought you all drink so well.
Hey... Try it once. You'll die.
What do you see me as?
Hey!
Sh*t!
Hey, what should I do?
She's so pretty, Wang Jo Hyeon. (Joey Wong.)
In reality, there is no such woman.
These days who is the prettiest?
Wang Jo Hyeon.
There are no such woman in reality. But I am infatuated with a girl from Jeong Hee Girls' High School.
- She has a bob haircut with pale skin?
How do you guys know that?
All the kids who ride the 20-2 probably know her.
Then, there was another girl at the library. She was a senior in high school and had long hair.
- She goes to a specialized high school for the arts.
- The noona who wears a white cardigan?
- You bastards don't study and only look at women!
(He's imitating his dad)
- She has a beautiful face no matter what. And...
- That's right
-You have more?
Don't you think Deok Seon became a bit cuter these days?
Yeah... A little bit?
Hey... Taek, what about you?
Yeah...
- Hey, Jeong Hwan.
- You are crazy. All of you guys are crazy! Are you drunk?
After drinking such expensive alcohol...
Hey! This bastard farted! Why are you like this?
Stop farting so much already!
Why are you coughing?
What is this?
Oh yuck! Yuck!
Seong Deok Seon
- You read it, right?
- What?
- My diary!
- I didn't read it.
- You read it!
- I didn't. Be quiet.
I'm using my mouth to speak. What is it to you?
- Be quiet.
- Did you read it?
- I didn't read it!
- Mom!
- You read it, right?
- I said be quiet.
- You did.
- I didn't read it.
"That time when everything is dressed in black."
"That time when I become more lonely."
"At this hour even the field flowers have gone to sleep,
but my heart for you will not rest so easily..."
- I will kill you!
- "They say love is about expression."
"So today I'm going to be brave and to him—"
- Really!
- Mom, Deok Seon has a crush on someone!
She gave him chocolate!
With what mind did I write this?
I want to throw it away but I have no place to throw it away.
I can't throw it in the trash, because I'm afraid that someone might read it.
If someone reads it, I'll be so embarra—
You were a cheeky little thing.
Why is a high school student so into boys already?
You read my diary, right?
Wow... Really... What the?
- You read my diary, right?
- No...
- You read it!
- I didn't read it.
Hey, tell me truthfully.
What is with the 'hey' to your husband?
You say 'hey' to me, so why can't I? You read it, right?
I didn't read it.
Who did you give the chocolate to? I didn't receive it.
Really...
Why do you read someone else's diary? Why did you read it?
- Who did you give it to?
- I gave it to you. To you.
Wow... Do you want to die? It was not me.
It is. It's not you?
It was you, for sure.
I'm going to smoke a cigarette.
- It was you!
- It was not!
It's definitely him. He must have forgotten because it's been almost thirty years since.
He used to be really smart a long time ago.
♫ Today again, like an idiot, because of my feelings
(Yoon Soo Il - Apartment)
♫ I came to see you again!
♫ Where no one is!
September 24, 1988
Jin Joo.
Is it yummy?
- Where are you going?
- To you eat spicy rice cakes.
Good bye!
Noona is going on a school trip tomorrow!
Gyeongju Station
She might kill me.
Suncheon High School
Hey! Hey!
Deok Seon, do you want to eat ramen?
Deok Seon! Seong Deok Seon!
Seon Woo is going to wear out the doorway.
I'm leaving.
- What should you do?
- What?
I think he likes you.
Let's go, Seon Woo.
♫  Every day with you, together, us two  ♫