♪In the city of steel,
secrets lie frozen♪
♪We build our walls on opposing sides♪
♪Amid the haze of war, illusions spread♪
♪Reflections in our eyes
reveal what we once were♪
♪The steel forest swallows every echo♪
♪A line of lies, a line of truth♪
♪On the battlefield of fate♪
♪What does it matter
if we stand opposed♪
♪Forge the past♪
♪Into a medal for a brand new world♪
=Higher=
=Episode 9=
Yeah.
Boss.
I've locked those two in the freezer.
They will be popsicles soon.
Not bad.
Boss, one more thing.
We caught a young girl.
A young girl?
- Yes.
- That's interesting.
Bring her to my office.
Understood.
You okay?
What could be wrong with me?
Don't give me that look.
It's disgusting.
Yeah.
Evil lives long.
Look for something to keep warm.
I'm not spending the night
stuck in here with you.
Go out if you dare!
If you get frostbite,
Ms. Mu will come after me.
Right?
Here, put this on.
Don't touch me.
Don't touch me!
You're making me dizzy.
Fine.
Suit yourself.
You have all the muscles,
broad shoulders,
but not one bit of resilience.
You can't handle a bit of pain.
What kind of lab is this?
There's not even an alcohol lamp.
Let me see it.
- What's your deal?
- What's wrong with you?
- What are you doing? That's disgusting.
- You're freezing. I'm helping.
I'm warning you, don't touch me!
- You're freezing. I'm keeping you warm.
- I said don't.
Psycho. You're a pervert.
Disgusting.
Fine. Freeze to death.
Suit yourself.
Pretty girl.
Let me introduce myself.
I own this factory.
My name is Qin Bo.
Don't be scared.
You have me with you tonight.
Mr. Qin.
No rush.
The night is still young.
How about we start with a drink?
I like your style.
Smart girl. I like it.
Don't sleep.
I won't.
You sound weak.
Aren't you usually quick to snap back
and always ready with a comeback?
Come on, give me one.
Shut up.
Wake up.
- I'm fine.
- Chen Jiachuan!
You know
what Xiaotong told me about you?
She said
you had a bad temper.
Stubborn as a mule.
Always quick to lash out.
And impossible to calm down.
Nonsense.
My sister would never
say that about me.
I also heard
Instructor Dong wanted me
kicked out of training camp.
You were the one who stopped it.
You know why he said that?
Because, just like you,
his mind was messed up.
Did you seriously waste your strength
on a comeback?
You really are crazy.
Open your mouth.
Have some candy.
Bai Fan.
Once you get out of here,
find Yaoji.
Crack the files.
Get justice for my sister.
Stop talking like that.
Please.
Tell Yaoji yourself.
We're both getting out of here.
Don't start acting like a coward.
Chen Jiachuan!
Wake up.
♪Past moments blur the boundary♪
♪Will you still stand by me?♪
Chen Jiachuan!
Wake up, Chen Jiachuan!
Come on.
Don't fall asleep. Chen Jiachuan.
Hit me.
Come on, fight me!
Snap back at me!
Chen Jiachuan!
Say something!
Jiang Zhen?
Bai?
You're awake.
Yeah.
How's it going?
Did you crack the password?
- Don't worry about that. Just rest.
- Tell me.
Is the disc decrypted?
There's nothing on it.
What?
Why is there nothing?
Where's the data from
the day Xiaotong was hurt?
I'm getting out of here.
Get out of my way!
Bai Fan.
What's wrong with my leg?
The doctor said
you had an old injury.
This time, the heavy blow and the cold
made it worse. You need proper rest.
Get out!
If you push yourself now,
you could be disabled for life.
Out!
Qin Bo's been arrested.
Before the police got there,
we recovered the chip.
Got it.
You can go.
We got the chip.
The plan can proceed.
Well done.
Our dominance over the world
is nigh.
It won't be too long now.
♪Who will hide fate♪
♪Within the dust of the past♪
♪Understanding love and hate♪
♪Yet refusing♪
♪To surrender to time♪
♪Beyond the dark, colours bloom♪
♪Knowing the end yet still I follow♪
♪Burning all away, even if alone♪
♪If all of this is just a game♪
♪If vows will fade one day♪
♪Then grant eternity to memory♪
♪May the land and faith♪
♪Never be forgotten♪
♪Even as time ages♪
♪Through the endless night♪
♪Braving frost and storm♪
♪Till clear skies return♪
♪Even if fate loves to twist♪
♪And sorrow turns to song♪
♪The world replaced♪
♪Yet starlight still falls♪
♪To bloom once more♪
♪In the faint light, I♪
♪Compare myself to it♪