♪In the city of steel,
secrets lie frozen♪
♪We build our walls on opposing sides♪
♪Amid the haze of war, illusions spread♪
♪Reflections in our eyes
reveal what we once were♪
♪The steel forest swallows every echo♪
♪A line of lies, a line of truth♪
♪On the battlefield of fate♪
♪What does it matter
if we stand opposed♪
♪Forge the past♪
♪Into a medal for a brand new world♪
=Higher=
=Episode 2=
Stop hitting me!
Not the face! Not the face!
He's with us.
Who's this?
I'm Yaoji.
So you two are in it together.
- Third Young Master?
What are you doing here?
You dare hit me?
I'll kill you for that.
Stop it!
Stop!
Jiang Zhen.
How could you trip him?
When did I trip him?
I saw you trip him.
Shut up.
I said you'd be dead weight.
- Telling me to shut up?
- You shut up.
What?
Why are you always causing trouble?
Setting me up again?
I'm not crazy.
Why would I set you up?
I'll hit you!
Hands off. Where are your manners?
Come on.
Go on, hit me.
Get me to a hospital.
Or you'll regret it!
Higher.
A little higher.
- Here?
- Yeah.
How's the lead coming?
I went to where she was last seen.
I only found a car.
(Someone said they saw a girl)
(about her height and build.)
(Someone must've taken her)
(when the car broke down.)
Brother.
Private meeting?
What's that?
Share it with me.
None of your business.
Take care of your young master.
Petty.
Wow, Jiang Zhen.
Look what you did to him.
If only we had some yellow wine.
This stuff
is great for bruises.
What?
Yellow wine.
You stole yellow wine
from the canteen again?
Who stole it?
I went through a lot of trouble
to get this
for your back.
This stuff
is great for bruises.
Hang in there.
Easy.
Ow.
Can't handle a little pain?
Who says I can't?
Easy.
I am being gentle.
Don't be so skittish.
That's fine.
Do more.
Too bad we don't have any yellow wine.
Third Young Master.
You're heavy.
Jiang Zhen, can you even drive?
Darn it.
He got away.
Jiang Zhen, you liar!
Third Young Master.
Mind the waist.
Just my luck today.
We didn't find her,
and I sprained my waist.
No, the lead is gone too.
Third Young Master.
With me here,
we'd never lose the lead.
How's the lead coming?
I know this place.
I've seen it before.
Go on.
The last place the young mistress
was seen was this bar.
Are you the owner?
Yeah, why?
Have you seen this girl?
No, I've never seen her.
Boss, this is urgent.
I said I haven't seen her.
You dressed like a beggar.
You shouldn't be at a bar.
Say it. Will you talk or not?
Alright, I was wrong, sir.
I had no idea who you were. Have mercy!
Spare me, sir!
I prefer something else.
What's going on?
Do your job
or get lost.
Let me look again, sir.
Stop it.
Let me help you.
You're not hurt, are you?
You...
What is it?
My sister's missing.
I came to check the bar.
- Will you talk or not?
- Let me look again. I'll look again!
Let me check again.
Has she been here these past few days?
Yes!
I...
I think I've seen her.
Sir, I've got it.
Private room, second floor.
The one at the very end.
(I must find her before Bai Fan does.)
Feifei, keep me company.
That hit the spot.
Pour me another.
- Keep drinking.
- Alright.
Slow down.
We meet again.
Your nose is sharp.
You followed my scent here?
All thanks to my captain's training.
They look strange, don't they?
This is public.
Watch your manners.
It's alright, miss.
I can't drink anymore.
Darn it!
You're asking for it.
Who are you two?
Are you Nong Qianya?
Am I right?
Are you deaf or something?
Do you know who I am?
Get back here.
Where's the young mistress?
♪The shadowed moon♪
♪The lurking night♪
♪Illusions start to crumble♪
♪The line between truth and lies♪
♪Blurs from sight♪
♪The answer torn apart♪
♪The shadowed moon♪
♪The lurking night♪
♪Illusions start to crumble♪
♪Lie are pieced together♪
♪The illusions shattered♪
♪The cycle has never ceased♪
Are you alright?
Yeah.
Calm down.
He's just a bandit.
Bai Fan.
Where are you taking my person?
What do you mean, your person?
I found her first.
What do you mean you found her first?
Be honest with yourself.
Without me,
could you have found her?
You taught me
that everything has an order.
When will you ever grow up?
Always so scheming.
Ya, turn around first.
Are you out of your mind?
- Will you give it up already?
- Where are your manners?
Do you have no shame?
What does that mean? Don't touch me!
Shouldn't we get out of here?
♪In the city of steel,
secrets lie frozen♪
♪In the cracks of time,
suspense flickers♪
♪You and I
move through truth or illusion♪
♪Side by side, we face the game of fate♪
♪Who will hide fate♪
♪Within the dust of the past♪
♪Understanding love and hate♪
♪Yet refusing♪
♪To surrender to time♪
♪Beyond the dark, colours bloom♪
♪Knowing the end yet still I follow♪
♪Burning all away, even if alone♪
♪If all of this is just a game♪
♪If vows will fade one day♪
♪Then grant eternity to memory♪
♪May the land and faith♪
♪Never be forgotten♪
♪Even as time ages♪
♪Through the endless night♪
♪Braving frost and storm♪
♪Till clear skies return♪
♪Even if fate loves to twist♪
♪And sorrow turns to song♪
♪The world replaced♪
♪Yet starlight still falls♪
♪To bloom once more♪
♪In the faint light, I♪
♪Compare myself to it♪