THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION AND ALL NAMES,
CHARACTERS, PLACES, AND INCIDENTS
ARE EITHER PRODUCTS OF THE AUTHOR'S
IMAGINATION OR ARE USED FICTITIOUSLY.
We're from the hit-and-run team
of Gongnam Police.
The car involved belongs to this company,
and I heard that a family member
of the chairman was in it.
I need to know who was driving that car.
Where can I meet the person in charge?
An accident on Gongnam Road?
What are you talking about?
Mrs. Han.
Give me your phone.
Are there any other traces of me anywhere?
Do you have any texts or my number
on a computer or tablet?
No, ma'am.
Nobody can find out about what we did.
If Yoon-gyeom,
or especially my dad, finds out,
we're both dead.
Do you understand?
What on earth has she done now?
Why did it have to be now?
I can't have
the task force team get exposed.
Change the location for the meeting.
Make sure the press doesn't find out
that So-ra was in the car.
Don't let the police or any reporters
into the company building.
Yes, sir.
Where's So-ra? Is she not home yet?
She's going to stay at a hotel
until things die down, sir.
Why did she go out in the early morning
and hit somebody's car?
What the hell did she take?
Why is she acting so crazy?
Mr. Han.
Yoon-gyeom's here.
LY'S COMPANY VEHICLE FLEES THE SCENE
AFTER AN ACCIDENT ON GONGNAM ROAD
Lee La-el.
I've underestimated you.
She might have to visit
the hit-and-run team at this rate.
Where's So-ra?
Why are you looking for
your wife at my house?
Da-bi is waiting for her mother,
but the police came instead.
Do you not care about all this, Mr. Han?
You must've done a bad job
at managing your family.
So this is my fault too?
Where's So-ra? Tell her to clean this up.
-I don't know.
-Mr. Han!
Come on.
You should work together
in a situation like this.
She's at a hotel,
so I'll go get her.
You two can talk this out.
I'm sure that this isn't
that big of a deal.
Early in the morning yesterday,
on a road in Gongnam-gu, Seoul,
a strange car chase took place.
Two cars were involved in a chase
on a relatively empty road
early in the morning,
as if it was a scene from a movie.
The two vehicles stopped
only after one crashed into the other.
You said it was Han Pan-ro?
What did he send?
Welcome.
It's good to see you.
I think Han Pan-ro knows
that we tried to take
Yoon-gyeom's company shares.
Oh, you didn't have to.
Goodness. This is amazing.
A car should be comfortable.
Sir.
I've got the footage of the hit-and-run.
The perpetrator was So-ra,
and she was with some man.
A man?
Find out who he is.
And check Pan-ro's location too.
Quick.
Yes, sir.
-Congratulations.
-Hello.
It must have been a long journey here.
You must've been busy writing your book.
Everything worked out, thanks to you.
-I think I've got to work harder.
-Thank you.
Hello, Congressman Seo!
It's great to see you.
I've been wanting to meet with you.
It's nice to finally meet you,
Prime Minister Han.
We will mutually benefit
if we formally meet each other like this.
I'm happy about this too.
Mr. Han.
Hello there, Mr. Kang.
I would have given you a call
if I knew that you'd be here.
You're really going to act so friendly
after threatening me like that?
I saw that So-ra was with another man.
What should I do about this video?
Does Yoon-gyeom know too?
Does he know that So-ra was with a man?
Those people are so dramatic.
The Financial Supervisory Commission
thinks that Mr. Kang
is planning something.
Does La-el have
anything to do with this, sir?
I think so.
LY GALLERY CLOSED
THE GALLERY IS CLOSED FOR TODAY
DUE TO PRIVATE ISSUES
A hit-and-run in the early morning?
What the hell is this?
I should get into accidents more often
if it'll make you come running right away.
I accidentally hit a car
after I had some champagne with a friend.
It's nothing really. I was staying away
because it might become a mess.
Which friend?
Since when have we shared
so many personal details like that?
You're seriously going to joke right now?
To be fair, although we don't know
each other's private lives,
we both know what we're like,
so why avoid the question?
But you need to answer my question first.
That's the order of things.
I won't beat around the bush.
Are you having an affair?
No.
What do you think our marriage is?
You know that this gallery
was a gift for
our fifth wedding anniversary, don't you?
The presents for our
20th and 30th wedding anniversaries
have all been decided on already.
I think I have the right
to get a present
on every wedding anniversary.
Our marriage
wasn't a coincidence
or an abstract concept.
I tried so hard to get you.
I made a plan, I made it work,
and I kept it going.
Our marriage…
is the result of my efforts.
So…
if somebody is trying to ruin it,
then I can't forgive them.
Never.
Let me ask you one more time.
Are you having an affair?
No.
Your mouth says "no,"
but your eyes say "yes."
I've been hoping that it wouldn’t be true.
No, not hoping. I've been praying.
So, the only question left is,
-"who is it?"
-I told you, I'm not.
I know exactly what I'm going to do now.
I'm going to find out
who your mistress is.
-Mr. Kim.
-Yes, ma'am?
Well. I see that your conversation
didn't take very long.
That's a relief.
I'll take care of the cops.
Who do they think they are,
trying to investigate you?
Don't worry.
I'll let them interrogate me.
Sorry?
Just make sure the reporters
don't take pictures when I go.
GONGNAM POLICE STATION
Ms. Oh, is it true that you used drugs?
I moved the time for the singer
Oh Seon-hui's drug interrogation.
The chief says you don't need to worry.
He'll cover it up for you.
Go.
CHIEF'S OFFICE
A lot of people
are curious about this case
since both the victim
and the perpetrator disappeared.
So…
I had no choice but to investigate.
I hope you understand, Ms. Han.
It's fine.
I'm not here to be interrogated
but to report somebody.
Sorry?
The car that ran away…
is mine. It was stolen.
Wait…
So-ra?
That car belongs to you?
Hold on, so…
You hit your own car?
My husband gave me the car that ran away.
But it was stolen from me.
I was trying to catch the thief
before my husband found out,
but I guess I failed.
Everything will be fine
once the police catches the driver.
What?
My car is wanted as a stolen vehicle?
Make sure that Sun-bin isn't exposed.
Hide the car,
and send the bodyguard abroad.
What?
Ms. Kim Sun-bin is
still not picking up her phone, sir.
Open this when you feel lonely
and alone.
Inside this box, I've put my plan
to take care of everything.
MR. SEO
Mr. Seo.
You're doing okay, right?
I think Pan-ro and Bon-geun
have been driven apart.
I thought you should know.
Do you want this to get even bigger?
Okay.
Whatever it is that you want,
I'll trust your decision.
You said that there would be a plan
inside the box that you gave me.
There wasn't anything in there.
There is no plan, La-el.
Not having a plan is my plan.
I'll just stay by your side
like a shadow.
Just remember that I'm always with you
no matter what.
What if I…
do something that only a monster would…
or…
something even worse?
Do it if you want.
It's okay.
Hello, Chief Officer.
Did you catch the driver?
Could you tell me
the driver's phone number?
If they're an employee at LY,
then we'll punish them
and take care of everything.
She was getting ready
to run away to another country.
Is she the right person?
Yes.
Hey, miss.
I'll ask you this one last time.
Who did Chairman Kang tell you to protect?
Gosh, don't get any blood on me.
Move.
Oh, gosh…
Where's her phone?
Thanks.
A VIP?
LEE YEON-WOOK
Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
Who are you to be my husband's VIP?
It'll be child's play
to find out who you are.
I can find you in one day.
Let's meet.
I'll go to you tomorrow at noon.
However…
you must release the bodyguard right away.
Mr. Han,
don't worry about the video.
So-ra says that he's
a paid designated driver,
and revealing his identity
won't be a problem.
You said you can find out
who he is, right?
Yes, sir.
Yoon-gyeom, that bastard.
So he used me to threaten his own father?
You don't know what he's planning yet?
No, but I'm in the process of finding out.
Once So-ra meets Yoon-gyeom
on Da-bi's birthday
and confirms a couple of things,
I'll tell you what happened.
I'll take it from here.
Today's a very important day, isn't it?
You have Da-bi's birthday party
and the CMN parent interview.
I'll make sure that you look like
the most graceful parent in the world.
Since when did I like
looking like a parent?
Never, Ms. Han. I'm sorry.
-Make me look tough.
-Yes, Ms. Han.
Really tough.
-Happy birthday, Da-bi.
-Happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
-Happy birthday, Da-bi.
-Happy birthday!
-Thanks.
-Happy birthday, Da-bi.
-Hello.
-Thanks for coming.
-Happy birthday.
When that bitch arrives at noon,
grab her right away.
Watch the road, parking lot,
and the entrance to the kindergarten.
Yes, Ms. Han.
You know, I don't see Sun-bin.
But she'll probably
show up today, won't she?
It's Da-bi's birthday and all.
There's the Parent Association
interview too.
On top of getting ready
for the end-of-the-year events.
She's been absent
for so long, don’t you think?
Don't worry. I'm planning on scolding her.
Let's go.
Hello, Mr. Kang.
All right, please look here, everyone.
Thank you for coming
to celebrate Da-bi's birthday.
Thanks for giving Da-bi so much love.
Please enjoy the party,
and tell me if you need anything.
I'm going to light the candles now.
-Happy birthday to you
-Happy birthday, dear Da-bi
Dam-ri, I haven't seen
that bracelet before.
When did you buy it?
I didn't.
It was a gift.
Are you dating somebody?
You're acting super suspicious.
Hey, Ji-hee, are those diamonds?
No, but it's a new product.
-Is it pretty?
-Yes.
Secretary Kim.
Have you spotted an unfamiliar woman yet?
They're all parents
or from the TV station.
-Hi there.
-Hello.
Hello, Ms. Kim.
We've been waiting for you.
They're about to do the interview.
I heard you've been ill.
Are you feeling better?
Yes, I am.
Wow, look at her.
-Mom!
-Bo-ram!
Ms. Kim!
Da-bi!
Happy birthday, Da-bi.
-You look so pretty.
-Thank you.
Let me look at you, Bo-ram.
You're so cute today.
Have you eaten yet?
My baby.
Are you sure that you've been sick?
Why do you look even prettier?
I didn't think that an actual person
could pull off that dress.
So how on earth are you doing it?
The two of you look even prettier.
Have you had something good happen to you?
Not at all.
She's in the mood to laugh?
You say such nice things.
That's why her face is pretty too.
It's because her words are pretty.
Secretary Kim.
Nobody's here yet?
I'm sure nobody came here, ma'am.
Damn it.
It looks so fancy.
How much is that?
Bring her here.
Mrs. Han would like to see you.
Da-bi, play with Bo-ram, okay?
Okay.
Hello.
-It's been a while.
-You look great.
I hope Da-bi has a good birthday, Ms. Han.
You look so beautiful today.
You're having so much fun, aren't you?
You went off the grid
after telling me something so big.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm sorry.
I saw the news about the car accident.
Are you hurt anywhere?
Why would I get hurt?
The bitch who's coming today
is the one who'll get hurt.
Is somebody supposed to be coming?
A VIP is coming.
So you've finally found her?
I found her.
But she got scared and ran away.
What a coward.
Who says she ran away?
She didn't show up, so she ran away.
It's past noon now. She's not here.
I did show up.
What are you talking about?
I showed up exactly at noon.
What the hell are you saying?
I told you to release
the bodyguard immediately.
Why didn't you do it?
Why did you take your anger out
on somebody else?
Let's not do that anymore.
You…
It's you?
Now I know
why you wanted Mr. Kang's love so badly.
Your birthday was our first day.
It's my birthday today!
Don't ever betray me.
Of course.
Not until the day I die.
I must say, your husband…
is quite a catch.
Ms. Han.
Could we begin
the Parent Association interview now?
All right.
You crazy bitch.
Get your act together.
Do you want everybody to know
that you were fooled cluelessly by me?
Bo-ram and Da-bi.
Do you want to see something fun?
-Yes.
Go on and play.
I missed you so much.
How could you
stop talking to me for so long?
I missed you too.
Very much.
Stay with me.
I'll go to the House of Roses
after the party.
We can't do that anymore.
This will help your task force team.
We're over now.
Over?
What do you mean?
Ms. Han found out.
I don't think
I'll be able to see you again.
There's no way that's happening.
There's no other way.
You're crazy.
You're completely out of your mind.
Dad.
Can you open this for me?
Sure.
We'll talk later.
I'll be going then.
Hey.
I'm going to kill you.
I'll rip your heart apart.
It'll be a pain that's on another level.
I'll make you beg for death.
"I'll make you beg for death."
That sounds pretty familiar.
But I don't think you
have the time for that.
You haven't the slightest idea
what drove me to do it,
why I did it,
or what my next move will be.
You don't know a thing,
so what are you going to do?
Why should I know anything
about your intentions?
You're going to be dead soon anyway.
Here's something to think about.
Why don't you start thinking about
why this is happening to you?
You've never given it a thought, have you?
You've always been
the perpetrator, not the victim.
It's a familiar question for those
who have gone through misfortunes.
"Why did something so terrible
happen to me?"
Such a question always lingers.
But you'll never find the answer to it.
It will eat you up alive.
Why?
Why do you think?
If you figure out the answer,
I just might go a little easier on you.
So-ra.
Talk to me, not her.
-Get in.
-Why should I?
Do you want to leave separately
with everyone watching?
Get in.
Come on, get in.
Just get in.
Let go of me.
Let's talk.
I'm disgusted that you cheated on me,
but why did it have to be her?
Do you know how shitty
I'm feeling right now?
I'll never forgive her.
I'm going to kill her.
I started all this.
She didn't do anything wrong.
Just blame me.
You're worried about her even now?
Not me?
I know how you're feeling.
That's why I'm telling you to blame me.
Unbelievable.
And?
I'm sorry.
What else do you have to say?
Tell me what you want.
What I want?
What I want
is for nothing to have happened.
I want you to not have done anything!
Let's talk inside.
Why should I?
I'm going to my dad's.
Let's go inside first.
I'm going to think about what to do there.
Mr. Park.
Turn the car around.
Grandma.
Honey.
Babe.
Thank you for coming back.
I've given it a lot of thought,
and I realized
that I can't live without you.
Let's start over. I'll do better.
Your secret.
Can you tell me
about the video that I saw?
Fine, I'll tell you everything.
Vice President Kim Yi-sak
is the real bad guy.
He sold GEDIKS over to LY.
I was a new employee back then.
But I had no reason to be threatened.
I've never seen the chairman
of GEDIKS nor his daughter.
I don't want anybody
getting involved in this.
I won't tolerate that.
Why did you start all this
if you're so scared of my dad knowing?
I haven't forgiven what you've done yet.
If you start planning something,
then I truly won't forgive you.
Are you trying to threaten me right now?
Don't take my warning lightly.
Stay here for the night,
but come back home tomorrow.
He told me all about
how Yi-sak sold over GEDIKS.
We could use this data in our lawsuit.
You weren't listening to me at all,
and now you want to help me?
It's not that I wasn't listening to you.
My resolve to sue them with you
has never changed.
Didn't you say
you're going to make So-ra get a divorce?
Nothing that I do with So-ra
will affect our lawsuit.
You're a stubborn one, aren't you?
Do you think human feelings are that easy?
As I've told you before,
I don't have any feelings
toward Yoon-gyeom.
And even if I did,
that's not important.
-Sir.
-Yes?
I have some bad news.
Yoon-gyeom has put together
a task force team
to get listed in New York.
He has professionals working for him.
What about the people
who were supporting the listing?
Why the sudden task force team?
The LY Distribution was a trick.
He's backstabbed us.
That little…
LY PAY COMMEMORATES
NY STOCK EXCHANGE LISTING
LY Pay?
Not LY Distribution?
Both you and Bon-geun
have some of LY Distribution's shares,
but Yoon-gyeom alone
owns the entirety of LY Pay.
Wait, so…
that one's listed
on the New York Stock Exchange?
If he makes it work,
it's only a matter of time
until he takes over the company.
I'm sorry, sir.
I cannot let you enter.
How dare you treat me like this?
Do you not know who I am?
Chairman Kang has ordered
not to let you into the building
until he gives permission.
How dare you?
-Call Yoon-gyeom.
-Yes, sir.
You bunch won't get away with this!
I'm sorry, sir.
Yoon-gyeom, that punk.
How dare he screw me over like this?
He screwed over his father too.
He's really something else.
Gosh, what a creepy little guy.
What is it?
I'm sorry, sir.
You cannot enter
without Chairman Kang's permission.
You son of a bitch!
My son-in-law is a real son of a gun,
but he's your actual son, isn't he?
It looks like he backstabbed
his own father too.
What a fine family.
I mean, there's that video too.
Maybe it runs in the family.
Watch your mouth.
This is happening all because of you.
So you've decided to pin it all on me now?
It all started because you were trying to
bite a chunk off of the company!
LY has always been mine,
you fucking thieves!
Don't you dare cuss at me,
you vulgar bastard!
-You're a worthless parasite.
-What?
A politician parasite
that feeds off of chaebols!
-You…
-Hey!
Watch what you're saying!
You rude brat!
Why you…
Goddammit.
Have you lost your mind?
-Huh?
-You little brat!
What the…
-Sir.
-Let go!
Stop, for goodness' sake!
-Let go.
-What do you think you're doing?
-Let go!
-Stop it.
I said, stop it.
You think you can stop me, you bastard?
You asshole.
How dare you hit him?
LY is mine, you son of a bitch!
You asshole, this is all your fault!
You've lost it, haven't you?
How dare you hit me?
Who the hell was that?
Come over here, you asshole!
Are you all right, sir?
-Gosh, that hurts!
-Oh, that hurts!
You little shit.
LY, THE WORLD'S LEADING COMPANY
She must be truly oblivious.
Okay.
How dare she?
Fine.
LY Pay will be taking
a different approach…
Chairman Kang is on TV, ma'am.
…by introducing an unprecedented
biometric payment system
that uses skin texture
and body temperature for transactions.
LY Pay's historical…
So LY is a global company now.
Chairman Kang is amazing.
Congratulations, Ms. Han.
It looks like you and Chairman Kang
will be quite busy at the end of the year.
I don't want to bother you,
but I can't solve this issue
by myself this time.
Please help me.
Sure, just tell me what you need.
The female bodyguard that Yoon-gyeom
assigned to me is in danger.
She got caught by So-ra,
but I can't rescue her alone
because So-ra probably has a lot of men.
And I can't have anybody
finding out that you're helping me.
What is that?
Shit, it's the cops. Run!
-Go after them.
-Yes, sir.
Ms. Lee, are you okay?
Wake up, Ms. Lee.
Ms. Lee!
Hurry and check where the ambulance is at.
-Check on the ambulance.
-Ms. Lee!
It'll arrive soon, sir.
All right.
Thanks, Myeong-hoon.
I owe you one.
Don't worry about it.
If it weren't for you,
all of us would still be
living like gangsters.
Thanks.
Ms. Lee, open your eyes.
Open your eyes, Ms. Lee.
She needs to be hospitalized
for a few more days.
Things might have gotten bad
if it weren't for you.
-Congratulations!
Congratulations!
Good work, everybody.
This is all thanks to you.
Let's have a drink.
-Cheers.
-Great work!
We're over now.
I don't think
I'll be able to see you again.
Sir.
-Where are you headed?
-I need to go somewhere.
So-ra, that brat.
She can't even
keep track of her own husband?
How useless can she be
to embarrass me in public?
Find where she is, quick.
Yes, sir.
So-ra.
I tried to calm down your father,
but it's not working.
He's on his way to see you.
I'm in front of your house.
I miss you so much.
It's driving me crazy.
I need just a moment.
Let me see you for just a moment.
I can't do that.
Think about Ms. Han.
I know that.
But you're the only one I could think of
on a day like this.
Please, just let me see your face.
I'm begging you.
We're over.
Chairman Kang.
How dare you show up here?
Jin-wook found out about you two.
Don't cause any more problems.
If you don't heed my warning now,
you'll regret it
for the rest of your life.
Please return home, ma'am.
I'll be fine on my own.
Lie down.
I'll be all right.
You seem like a good person.
Do you know
where Chairman Kang's task force team
is holding their celebration party?
Ms. Kim Sun-bin
sent this to your office, sir.
PIAZZOLLA
1968, BUENOS AIRES
It's Piazzolla's bandoneon.
I noticed your scar.
That scar may never fade,
but the heart…
may be healed, little by little.
I hope this bandoneon
can comfort you
just as much as it can comfort
the soul of your late mother.
I missed you.
I can't live without you.
Please don't say that it's over.
Please.
Chairman Kang!
What do you think you're doing?
You think you're entitled?
She's my wife, do you understand?
Honey.
Did I surprise you
by calling you out of the blue?
Not at all. I'm so happy right now.
Let's go look at the view
and have a drink too.
Thanks so much.
Let's go.
Come here.
Calm down, Jin-wook.
How dare you tell me to calm down?
Don't do this, honey.
Why are you holding me back, honey?
You should be stopping him instead!
Jin-wook!
Are you okay?
Don't touch her.
And who are you to tell me that?
She's my wife.
She's mine!
You can't approach her
while you're acting this way.
You're the chairman.
Yet you stole my wife,
and now you're threatening me?
This will be the end of you.
You'll be screwed
once people find out, understand?
You can only yell at me like this
because you're legally her husband.
Then I guess
I'll just take care of it legally.
What?
Are you saying you'll make us divorce?
I'm Kang Yoon-gyeom.
I've always taken everything
I ever wanted.
You're insane.
You're seriously crazy.
You are too, aren't you?
Anyone would go crazy
over a woman like her, after all.
I can't end things with you.
I have a question.
I'm assuming your disappearance back then
was for an intentional purpose.
What were you waiting for?
The critical point.
You mean, when the water boils over?
Water doesn't start boiling suddenly.
Ten degrees.
Twenty degrees and seventy degrees.
Water boils over
when it reaches the critical point
after all its steps.
Then it changes form from gas to liquid,
something entirely different.
Humans are the same.
When we reach the critical point,
we lose our ability to reason
and do things we shouldn’t do.
Drive!
Hurry!
La-el is very close
to making So-ra get a divorce.
Tell Yoon-gyeom
that La-el is Lee Tae-joon's daughter.
Do it as soon as you can.
Doing things we shouldn't do
when we've passed the critical point.
How are you planning to use that?
It'll give me a chance
to change a fate that was God-given.
I won't regret anything,
even if the worst happens to me.
Why did you call me here?
Honey.
You've tried so hard.
I wonder why So-ra hates me so much.
What a psychopath.
I can't just let you off, can I?
It'll be thrilling, for sure.
I'm going to do
my very best to ruin your life.