Hyeon Min, you look absolutely stunning today.
Yes, she really does.
Of course, you'd expect nothing less from the Soonyang family.
That must be several carats.
- What about your honeymoon?
- Here comes the groom-to-be!
Here comes the groom-to-be!
-  Here comes the groom-to-be!
- Oh, my.
Stop. Don't go any further.
- We'll stop here.
- Oh, dear. I'm thirsty.
- Come in and have a drink.
- No, we should...
- Feed us first.
- Come on, guys.
- Hurry up.
- Let's just go.
- Gosh, hold on.
- Keep it down!
- The thing is...
- Come on. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Father, Seong Jun and his friends delivered all the wedding gifts.
They're having a feast at his in-laws' place...
When did you get here?
I was on my way home after playing golf.
But I was starving, so I thought I should stop by.
Your son is getting married.
You must be so happy that you don't even have to eat.
Oh, Father.
Have you prepared a wedding gift for your eldest grandson?
Will you give him shares in Soonyang Corporation?
How many?
I'm sure Father will just take care of it.
Why are you worried about it?
Well, I'm Seong Jun's uncle.
If my gift is too little compared to his grandfather's,
I'll be embarrassed.
Right, Father?
The radish kimchi is perfectly ripe.
It looks like a good person will become a member of our family.
Father.
Can I have more water?
I got it.
What is it?
Seong Jun...
is now backed by his in-laws, who are influential people.
So you need not worry about him.
Father...
will start working on grooming Seong Jun as his successor.
After all, that is the family's rule.
Primogeniture.
We found a brain arteriovenous malformation, Sir.
The location is risky if we perform surgery.
Yes, Mr. Oh.
Let's just give up, Fellow Korean Lad.
I was wrong about DMC.
Like HBO and CNN, I thought cable channels
would soon beat the national networks.
But it can only happen in large countries with a population of 100 million, like the US.
No, you're wrong.
It may take some time, but that day will come soon.
The day when cable networks and various other channels
would produce content that would put national TV to shame. I know it.
It's not a time to give such a leisurely spiel like a prophet.
We must be objective and face our reality.
Objectively speaking, our reality is that
the moment we give up on DMC, Jin Seong Jun will be confirmed for the throne at Soonyang
Then our plan to own Soonyang will be nothing but a leisurely delusion.
I refuse to give up on DMC.
Buy and Sell Home Shopping, the only profitable cable channel,
decided today that they'd sell off the company.
Do you still not understand what it means?
Hyung, it's not like you need a lot of stuff.
Hey, shopping isn't about buying things you need.
It's all about buying things you want.
It means the channel needs a new owner.
And it's time for us to decide who it should be.
Mason, you never disappoint.
What's with him?
- Where are you going? Hey!
- Come with me!
Are you sure we can meet him here?
According to his official schedule, he's abroad on a business trip now.
I bet he doesn't want anyone to know that he's staying here.
If it's top secret, how did you find out?
What I thought was my grandfather's warning turned out to be a lottery ticket.
And an unscratched one, at that.
Let's go.
Allow me to introduce myself, Chairman.
I am Jin Do Jun.
Chairman Jin's youngest grandson?
Yes, I thought you looked familiar.
I heard you went to Seoul National University School of Law.
I told them over and over not to let anyone in.
How did you get in?
Hey! Is anybody outside?
Those fools...
Your security team did nothing wrong, Sir.
I struck a deal with them.
I told them I'd send out a promotional press release
if they didn't let me see you.
Ju Yeong Il, the chairman of Daeyoung Group,
is undergoing artificial heart valve surgery,
but he chose
Soonyang Medical Center, not Daeyoung Medical Center.
There is no better way to prove that Soonyang has
the best cardiothoracic surgery department in the country.
Chairman Jin, that old snake.
He promised me that it'd be kept confidential.
How dare he blindside me like this? Darn it.
My grandfather doesn't know that I'm here, Sir.
And it should stay that way,
because I'm here to tell you how Daeyoung Distribution
can beat Soonyang Transportation and become number one
in the industry, Sir.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Gosh, thank you.
- Oppa Young Ki.
- Hi, Hwa Young.
- Hi, congratulations.
- Oh, my. Mr. Mayor.
You took time out of your busy schedule to join us today.
- Thanks, brother-in-law Ji.
- It's my pleasure.
I see that the groom's father is very excited.
Is it because your son is getting married?
Or is it because of Father's wedding gift?
Gosh, Hwa Young. You have no idea because you don't have kids.
It's better not to know. It really is.
I mean, look at me.
I still have to serve my mother-in-law
while walking on eggshells around my daughter-in-law.
Mom has to live long.
I'm sorry, Jeong Rae.
Hwa Young, that is not what I meant...
- Goodness.
- We'll head in first.
- Let's go.
- You made it, Yoon Ki.
Congratulations.
- Congratulations, Jeong Rae.
- Thank you.
Thank you all for coming.
- Yes, go on in.
- Let's go.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
- Hey!
- Sir.
Thanks.
Okay. It's my oldest nephew's wedding gift.
I should prepare this much.
- Move! It's our turn.
- All right, next.
- She looks gorgeous.
- Hey, hurry.
- Hyeon Min! You look stunning.
- For real!
- Look at the camera.
- You look so beautiful.
- You look absolutely gorgeous.
- All right. In 1, 2, 3.
- Nice, beautiful.
- You look really stunning.
- Look at the camera.
- Oh, my.
Hello.
- Hello.
Would you mind giving us some privacy?
- Not at all.
- My gosh.
I must tell her something.
- My gosh!
- How romantic!
- We'll leave you to it then.
- See you inside!
- See you.
- You look so stunning today.
- Congratulations.
- See you.
You look beautiful. More beautiful than I expected.
That's not what you wanted to talk to me about, right?
It's such a shame.
I want to brag about my beautiful bride.
And you would've been so happy I came together with him.
Who?
Do Jun.
Whom?
The guy you like.
Jin Do Jun.
Do Jun can't come today.
He doesn't have the guts to face my grandfather.
You're not waiting for him, are you?
Stop.
You see, Do Jun
could not handle the DMC deal Miracle took
and decided to hand it over to Soonyang Construction.
This means
that I managed to get my revenge, as you said.
If you knew everything, then why...
I told you.
You truly amuse me.
It's funny how you think you're the only one with a thinking brain.
It's ridiculous that you think you can always have your way.
And you believe that everyone would like you. That's...
I guess that's kind of cute.
Think about it, Hyeon Min.
The world wouldn't be so kind to only you.
Shut your mouth.
Walking out the door now doesn't mean you can go back to your previous life.
You will just become the one whose wedding to Soonyang was called off.
You will never be able to call off this wedding.
You may ditch your pride as it doesn't bring you any money,
but you can never give up on your market value as the only daughter of the Hyunsung Daily family.
I still find you very amusing.
Is this what you wanted to talk to me about?
- Is that why...
- You didn't choose me as a man,
and the feelings are mutual.
Let's keep things that way even after the wedding.
You get what I'm saying, right?
I figured you should know the rules before you joined the game.
Let's play fair and square.
See you inside.
Hello.
Last but not least, the highlight of the ceremony awaits us.
The bride and groom will now march together.
Let us bless the bride and groom with a big round of applause.
Promise me one thing.
Whatever you do, you will not dirty the family register.
The bride and groom will now march.
Father, you need to see this.
I don't think you need to worry about Seong Jun.
He's extremely clever and resourceful.
Is this your wedding gift for Seong Jun?
Well, he's only starting out,
so you should train him well.
Did you think I wouldn't know about this when you knew about it too?
You knew?
What? The land-banking for the New Seoul Town project.
You knew that it was all Seong Jun, not Hyung Young Ki?
My grandson, Seong Jun.
I was right there the moment he was born
instead of his father, who was in jail at the time.
He is my eldest grandson, the one and only.
Okay. Everyone is ready, right?
All right, here we go.
One, two...
Hey, Do Jun!
I'm sorry I'm late.
- All right.
- Hey, come here.
Okay, here we go.
Smile, everyone.
Well, since we were interrupted anyway... Mr. Mayor, do you mind switching?
- With her?
- No, with Mr. Jin.
- Smile.
- You two can switch.
- You can stay where you are.
- No, why should he...
Why? Do you have nothing to smile about these days?
Mr. Jin Dong Ki, please take your hands out of your pockets.
- Yes, thank you.
- Grandfather, you were right.
- Oh, Hyeong Jun.
- I was foolish.
All right. Give me a bigger smile.
I've given up on my goal of buying Soonyang with my money.
All right, here we go. Smile, please!
We'll take it now.
One, two, three.
My gosh, thank you all for coming.
- Congratulations, Sir.
- Congratulations.
- Oh, my. You made it, too.
- Congratulations, Sir.
- Sir.
- Yes?
That little...
I tried to keep my cool but couldn't. I was so fuming mad
that I ran here as soon as they removed the IV from my arm.
I wanted to take it up with you in person.
What's going on? What happened?
Look.
Don't you have enough to worry about with your foolish sons?
Your grandson.
You need to teach him better!
You may leave.
Congratulations on your wedding.
As for DMC, I'm sorry.
How did you think of going up against Soonyang?
You're smart. Why did you make such a mistake?
Grandfather may think it's his youngest grandson's prank,
but I'm different.
"Don't start a fight that already has an ending."
That's what you said.
It doesn't look like a fight that already has an ending.
Yes.
Is this true?
Have the spots at DMC been filled?
Is it true?
That's why I was late for your wedding.
The deadline set out by Seoul City was today,
so I had to wrap up everything for the agreement.
Oh, right. I will not hand over the DMC project to Soonyang Group.
What on earth did you do?
Are you implying
that there is no sensible, legal way
for me to find companies that would support the DMC project
because of Soonyang's meddling cowardly antics?
Is that what you meant, Hyungnim Seong Jun?
Tell me.
How can Daeyoung beat Soonyang
and become number one again in the distribution industry?
Is there a way?
I heard you decided to sell Daeyoung Distribution.
Now is not the time to sell it.
You should acquire another company.
What did you say?
A home shopping channel is up for sale.
You should acquire "Buy and Sell Home Shopping."
Look, SNU Law student.
Don't you know the government's policy after the IMF financial crisis?
Such an aggressive expansion strategy through acquisitions
is a relic of a bygone era.
Daeyoung has no interest
in showbiz, where clowns are busy goofing around.
It's not showbiz, Sir.
It's distribution
and logistics.
Daeyoung's specialty.
It's a mink coat with a classic, timeless design,
offered to you at an affordable price point.
At a glance, you can tell...
People no longer buy what they need. They buy what they want.
Thanks to the home shopping channels that stimulate
the impulse purchase instinct 24-7.
In the comfort of their own home,
with a single click of a button.
That's a given.
As you can see here, the luxurious sheen...
And all home shopping channels
need a distribution company to move goods.
If Daeyoung has a distribution company in one hand,
and a home shopping channel in the other hand...
It'd be like killing two birds with one stone,
killing two flies with one slap,
and mashing two potatoes with one fork.
Am I right?
I suggest you acquire a home shopping channel, Sir.
Then Daeyoung will soon be
the number one distribution company again.
He was very persuasive, so what could I do?
I had no choice but to give in.
Daeyoung is going into DMC.
Sit back and wait.
We'll retrieve the number one title in distribution in no time.
I can't see you out.
Take care of your health.
How petty.
Is this how you treat your guests?
As you ordered, I prepared a share transfer agreement
for Mr. Jin Seong Jun.
Sir!
It's okay. Hold on.
Symptoms include
sudden headaches
and temporary mobility impairments.
Mr. Lee.
Yes, Sir.
About Medical Director Jung...
Let's make sure he'll keep his lips sealed.
Gosh.
Oh, dear.
My children can't find out about this yet.
Oh, I'm okay now.
On behalf of the ten million citizens of Seoul,
I'd like to propose a toast.
Here's to their forever love. Cheers!
Cheers!
- Congratulations.
- Congratulations, Seong Jun.
- My gosh.
- Congratulations, son.
It's sweet.
I guess I'm finally growing up
now that my son is married.
Father. Thanks to all your help and support,
I managed to raise Seong Jun well,
who has now found his better half.
Thank you, Father.
Please say a few words.
Seong Jun and his wife will always remember and heed your advice.
I'm sure they'll live a happy life together and won't let you down.
He's asking for the wedding gift, isn't he?
He is wrapping it up with a fanfare.
The reception is over.
The coronation ceremony has begun.
My advice?
Who wants to listen to this old man nag?
You're all curious about my wedding gift for Seong Jun.
Doesn't anyone here not know
how precious Seong Jun is to me?
My gift is
something Seong Jun had asked for.
Oh, my.
- Manager Lee.
- Yes, Sir.
Thank you.
You asked me to let you take responsibility as a real adult.
Starting Monday, Seong Jun
will work at Geochang Distribution Warehouse.
- Father.
- The notice states that he's now
in charge of the warehouse.
The illegal land-banking of the New Seoul Town.
And we failed to land the construction of DMC.
You should take responsibility, don't you think?
That is what a real adult ought to do.
Father, but how could you...
As for his shares in the company,
we can revisit the issue another time,
but you want him to work at a distribution warehouse?
As of today,
Soonyang
will no longer follow the rule of primogeniture.
Either buy all the shares with your money
or prove your competence and abilities as a leader.
Suit yourselves.
The one who can make Soonyang bigger and better than I can
will get everything,
including my shares
and the right to run the business.
Father.
How could you do this to me? How?
After everything I've done for you and Soonyang...
Young Ki, about your knee...
Director Jung at the medical center said
that the medicines these days worked very well.
Fixing it will be no problem at all.
Just don't miss your doctor's appointments.
If you don't take care of yourself,
- who will?
- Father!
Don't you know whom I love the most
out of all my children?
It's Soonyang.
Oppa Dong Ki, do you know anything about this?
Hey! Jin Hwa Young, you little...
What are you saying? What would I know?
You know, at the wedding, Oppa Dong Ki and Father talked for a while.
- Hey!
- Am I wrong?
- Dong Ki, you little...
- I don't know anything!
Well, if what Father said is true,
Seong Jun himself must know the reason the best.
Hey. Am I wrong, Seong Jun?
That brat...
- Hey!
- Hyeon Min!
- My gosh!
- Hyeon Min! Oh, dear.
Hey! What's wrong with her?
Wake up, Hyeon Min. Open your eyes!
My goodness. Why did she faint suddenly?
- Honey!
- Seong Jun! Call an ambulance!
- Wake up!
- Why did she pass out suddenly?
- Hyeon Min, wake up!
- Hello? We need an ambulance.
How did you teach your grandson?
How dare he come at me like that without even batting an eye?
He has quite a nerve, that kid.
But he sure knows how to catch the whiff of money,
just like you.
He reminds me of the Jin Yang Cheol I met at the repair shop in Incheon 50 years ago.
He takes after you.
I had let my guard down because none of your sons takes after you.
But your grandson got me good.
He sure made me flinch.
I was foolish.
I've given up on my goal of buying Soonyang with my money.
Instead, I'll use what I learned from you.
Okay. Everyone's ready, right?
Here we go. We'll take it now.
I am your grandson. But even against me,
you wielded all the authority and power Soonyang had.
I will also utilize every possible means and methods in my power
and plan to buy Soonyang.
All right. Let's do this, for one last time.
- Smile, please!
- Smile, Grandfather.
We'll take it now.
One, two, three.
Mr. Lee.
Do you think so, too?
Pardon?
That Do Jun takes after me.
Do you think that makes sense?
It went as you planned, Fellow Korean Lad.
Congratulations.
At last, you, the youngest grandson
have a shot at inheriting Soonyang.
I didn't break the rule of primogeniture because I needed a shot.
I'm still intent on buying Soonyang.
I know better than anyone else
just how much
my dear Soonyang family loves and cherishes each other.
What?
They'll show faces unlike any they showed before.
Now everyone has a shot at becoming the next owner of Soonyang.
That's too much money to stay loyal to each other.
It's late.
Stop protesting and go to bed.
Good for you.
You can tell I'm protesting?
Did you have to go and do that on his wedding day of all days?
How shocked must the new bride have been to...
If he did something wrong, you could talk to him nicely
and teach him what he should do.
You have a way of hurting the kids.
Does coddling them make them better people?
His dad is incapable of teaching his son when the boy goes off course.
His uncle is terrified
he'll lose what's his to his nephew and is wary about everything.
And our daughter
thinks less of her father than a stick with poop on the end.
Out of the kids you bore,
none of them have their heads screwed on straight.
Then what about Yoon Ki?
Do you think I don't know?
Why do you neglect Yoon Ki's family?
You gave him the foundation that makes nothing.
What do you think people will say of me?
They'll say that I discriminate the kid that isn't mine.
That nonsense again.
Didn't you hear what I said earlier?
The one who makes Soonyang bigger,
whomever that may be, gets to keep it all.
Remember this one thing.
Yoon Ki.
I fed and clothed him the exact same as I did our Young Ki and Dong Ki.
I stayed up at night, worried for them equally.
It wasn't because I pitied him for not having a mother.
It was so as not to ruin your reputation.
I need you to remember that one thing.
Medical director Jung says it's not serious.
Don't worry too much.
Okay.
You talk to her parents so they don't worry.
I should ask her mother if she's weak or sick.
I know she had a scare,
but what woman makes her husband stay up to nurse her on their wedding night?
He already has a lot on his plate.
You should go home and rest.
Okay.
I put you through a lot today.
We can talk about us later.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Tell your mother.
I'm not the weak one. Her son is.
What are you doing?
That's what I want to say.
What were you going to do?
Were you going to run up and throw a punch?
Why? To take it out on Jin Do Jun?
Were you worried he'd get punched?
Get a hold of yourself.
The rest of your family is just waiting for you to mess up.
They're always preparing to drag you down.
Will you feed yourself to them so easily?
I can't accept that.
Remember.
You're only allowed to show your back in front of me.
Because we at least are a team.
Can you handle it if I show my back?
I warned you that
it's bad for you to overestimate yourself.
If you look down on someone, you end up paying dearly.
This is the only time I'll let you off for hitting me.
It's our wedding night,
so I'll remember it as our burning physical act.
Can I go?
It's my wedding night.
I'd like to sleep in a room that smells like nice makeup,
like a human.
As per the chairman's wishes,
we must reorganize the subsidiaries you own between you.
First, Vice-Chairman Jin Young Ki.
You'll remain Vice-Chairman
of Soonyang Corporation and Electronics, but on top of that,
you now have the same authority to make decisions as the chairman.
Why?
So he can hold me responsible and exile me too if business profits go down?
Executive Director Jin Dong Ki.
You'll serve as vice-chairman of the whole group
and manage Heavy Machinery, Chemicals,
the stock firm, and Soonyang's asset management.
If he's vice-chairman,
does that make him Oppa Young Ki's equal?
Why would you say we're equals?
So what if I'm in charge of a whole lot?
None of them are worth anything.
Heavy Machinery and Chemicals put together
make less than 60 percent of what Electronics does.
Soonyang Department Store
will merge with the hotel and supermarket chains.
The new Soonyang Distribution Group will be a separate entity.
The necessary procedures will be taken care of soon.
What does that mean?
He's giving me a separate group
because I'm married and no longer part of this family?
It's not just a small group.
The hotel chain includes the condos...
Wait, the golf courses, too?
You're taking the main pillar of the business.
You still get to live in the main house, Vice-President.
The separation is a demand
made by the government and IMF.
The future of Soonyang Distribution depends on whether
the supermarket chain goes nationwide.
Chairman Jin
has given you a chance to show what you can do.
To separate the subsidiaries,
it's imperative to sort out the shares and debt obligations
between the main group and Soonyang Distribution.
That is the amount of debt
you must repay your brothers' subsidiaries.
This much?
So you had a hard time?
I did.
If you need that much money,
you should talk to CEO Oh Se Hyeon of Miracle Investment.
It's a company that has the most cash flow in Korea now.
- Put me down.
- Oh, dear...
Do you want me to ask Do Jun for help?
What?
Stop it.
Why do you think Dad threw that bombshell at the wedding?
What?
He'd always been displeased with the eldest brother.
And there's no way Oppa Dong Ki or I suddenly impressed him.
The only change is Do Jun's existence.
Jin Do Jun, Miracle's majority shareholder.
Do you still think I should go to him for money?
Well...
Oh, dear...
Have some tea.
What is it now?
Don't you think you should get the department store
to do something special for Lee Hae In?
He looks like his mom.
Wait, what's this?
What is this?
Who says money can't buy youth?
How is she my mom's age? She's prettier than I am.
Life is so unfair.
Look at Jin Do Jun.
He doesn't have to study for the bar as we do.
He can just inherit a subsidiary,
marry some girl from a rich family,
and live happily in luxury for generations.
That doesn't suit him.
A face like that goes with a fateful relationship with a huge star.
The most pointless thing is to worry about celebrities and rich people.
Are you two that sure you'll pass the second exam?
We might care what Jin Do Jun does,
but I bet he doesn't care about us.
Can you not mind him at all now?
It makes you guys look really bored.
Was mentioning Jin Do Jun something to get told off for?
Please come this way.
Please wait here.
Do Jun.
Mother.
Are you here to see your aunt?
Yes. You, too?
Yes.
Don't I look strange?
What?
Does it show that I tried hard to look young?
No. You look so pretty.
Trust Aunt Hwa Young's eye.
She asked you to work in fashion at the department store.
She doesn't ask just anyone.
- That is true, isn't it?
- Yes.
Mother. Both Hyung Hyeong Jun and I are adults now.
If there's anything you want to do, you should do it now.
You even have a trusted investor.
Right here.
Your dad
became an outcast because he married me.
Now, at last,
I think they're accepting us as a member of the family.
That's how I feel.
At least this time,
I won't get in your way.
Will you please wait here for a while?
Ms. Jin will be here soon.
Ms. Lee, please come with me.
See you.
Go ahead.
We'll show the 1999 SS collection to
celebs of the fashion world and VIP customers.
What is it that I should be doing?
She's here.
I like this color less than the one that came out in the previous season.
Last season's item would suit your skin tone better.
- Yes.
- But you already bought that.
How about the skirt?
I'm not sure. Can I see how it looks at the back?
Sure.
- Well?
- I like it.
Okay.
Go ahead.
You have a great eye.
You really do. I'm envious.
No one can beat time.
Lee Hae In is no longer a star.
She profited enough by marrying into the Jin family.
I heard she was treated like a princess.
She's from a different background.
That's true.
Come on.
So? Did you enjoy the show?
If you have anything to say, please tell me directly, Aunt.
Do not step over the line!
Know your place.
Like this?
Why do you think we accepted your father, born out of wedlock?
And why did we accept your mom without saying anything, who was the talk of the world?
For a single reason.
It was to display the noblesse oblige of Soonyang to the world.
A kind of a showcase.
Don't you dare delude yourself into thinking that you can be a rightful heir.
You guys
are different from us.
I shouldn't be saying this only to you.
That's how people work.
You have to learn by experience not to forget.
Since you're a smart kid, I hope these words were enough.
A department store. A resort. Golf. Hotel.
It's all consumer industry.
I'm sure they took a big blow after the IMF crisis and suffered from a huge deficit.
But he took everything here and gave it to his only daughter?
The chairman is showing tough love for his girl.
I picked out a company Miracle should invest in.
It's the hottest IT venture company now.
New Data Technology.
It's about to get listed on KOSDAQ at the end of the month.
There's a huge attention over the electronic communication field.
Some even presume them to go up by four times the offering price.
What's their business that makes them so hot?
Free internet calls.
You knew, Howard?
It's an unforgettable name.
New Data Technology.
New Data Technology successfully launched their online call service.
Young Jun, bump up the AC!
Did you buy it?
Everyone has bought those New Data Technology stocks.
Hit a new maximum price just ten more times.
Then I'll quit working right away.
Is it that good?
Mr. Kim bought a car after he invested in that.
- A car?
- Yes!
- Really?
- His new car?
It began at 1500 won ($1.50), then got up to 300k won ($300) dollars in six months.
It skyrocketed 200 times.
But it dropped by 98 percent of the highest price in just a year.
Another bearish factor hits the market.
The price plummeted down to 5500 won ($5)
after hitting a record of 300 dollars.
It was the most beloved item that faced the most wretched ending
in the history of the stock market.
A legendary symbol of the dot-com bubble era is none other than New Data Technology.
Wait, do you already have an investment plan?
I doubt it.
Mr. Majority Shareholder here thinks the dot-com fad is a speculative bubble.
Miracle won't invest in it, Rachael.
No.
You clearly told me last time that you won't invest in IT...
I clearly said I will invest when the flower wilts and it comes to fruition.
- When is that?
- Now.
Let's join the wagon.
New Data Technology.
Let me report back on 4-2.
It looks like he has taken interest in stock trading.
He's often visiting stock firms,
and I could tell through his phone calls
that he invested a huge amount in a venture business.
Yes, what was the name again?
New Data Technology?
It's a newly listed IT venture company.
They began at 1500 won, and stock firms presume it'll reach up to 40k won.
Wait, then 300M won  ($300,000)  will give me 10B won  ($10M) ?
Are you sure about this?
How is their business?
IT businesses are the growth driver of the current government.
Where do you think the money they put out before the general election will go?
Above all, the research team of Soonyang Investment is the top of the industry, Vice-Chairman Jin.
Where does Do Jun get all this information?
That young kid is the owner of Miracle Investment?
Did Father break the rule of primogeniture... because of him?
Is the guy that I planted next to Do Jun doing well?
He's been doing well since he returned from his break.
Do Jun is not suspicious of him, either
Call the Business Department of the investment firm.
Tell them to do everything to buy the stocks of New Data Technology.
So? How much do we need right now, Ms. Im?
A total of 400B Won  ($400M) .
It costs 120B won  ($120M)  to make a nationwide chain network for Soonyang Mart.
Also, we have to pay back Soonyang Electronics and Soonyang Heavy Machinery
for share acquisition, 150B  ($150M)  and 130B  ($130M) , respectively.
How much more can we borrow from the bank?
We've already taken out loans to our limit from our primary bank.
I see. That leaves me no choice.
I need to look into funds from Myeong-dong.
The private loan industry agreed not to put any cash into the market.
The interest rate for banks is speculated to go up to 25 percent.
So they'll hold it back until that moment comes...
What's the alternative?
I'm sorry.
Is all you can say as the director of finances that you're sorry?
You may leave.
Director, about the payables for Soonyang Electronics and Soonyang Heavy Machinery.
If they would postpone the time limit of payment
or reduce the interest rate, it'll help us hold out.
Sure, I'll do that for you.
Of course, my only baby sister is in trouble.
Right, CEO Jin. Are you aware of this?
If the stock transactions are incomplete between affiliations,
the separation process will also be delayed.
Is it okay for Father to find out?
What if he makes a scene saying you are incompetent...
Hello? Hello...
Father was harsh on you.
How can golf clubs and hotels do well in this terrible economy?
People show tough love for those they love the most, but it's for those who can take it.
Just wrap it up and come back to the group.
I'll have a chat with Father.
If you need that much money,
you should talk to CEO Oh Se Hyeon of Miracle Investment.
I told you, didn't I?
It's the company that has the most cash flow in Korea now.
No, no, no.
Chairman Jin has given you a chance to show what you can do.
I'm here sitting with you, CEO Oh.
But people are so weird.
They all say the true owner of Miracle is our own Do Jun.
We did begin with his pocket money of 24B won  ($24M)  from Chairman Jin.
What do you think, CEO Oh?
Does he have a knack for investing unlike his young age?
I didn't know you were here for a parent-teacher meeting.
Doesn't it feel unfair?
You brought up Miracle to this day with your own power,
but it has degenerated into a rich kid's trophy.
Everything in this world comes with a price tag.
There is no noble value that cannot be converted into money.
People who dare to say love is an invaluable thing
are people who are like thieves that love free things.
If you cannot buy happiness with money, then it's because you don't have enough.
- So?
- If you need Miracle,
then you can pay the price.
As long as I'm the CEO of Miracle,
we won't cause any influence over the succession of Soonyang.
I'm saying you don't have to mind Do Jun.
I'm with a partner who speaks my language.
I need 400B won  ($400M) . As soon as possible.
Our partnership also comes with a price, CEO Jin.
Give us 30 percent of Soonyang Department Store's stocks as the collateral.
Thirty percent of my shares?
Are you saying the department store is only worth that little?
I'm taking them only as collateral until you pay everything you owe us.
The consumer sentiment will get back on track by the end of the year.
I'm sure you'll work even harder for the collateral's sake.
Right.
You wanted to know if Do Jun had the knack for investing.
Yes.
I put on a huge fight this time.
He insisted that he wouldn't invest in IT companies.
You know, right? New Data Technology.
New Data?
You don't know?
This is the new idol of the KOSDAQ that hit many new record prices as soon as it was listed.
I see.
It began at 1500 won  ($1.50) , then reached 10,000 won  ($10)  in a week,
so that's seven times.
It'll surely rise up to at least 40,000 won  ($40) .
Forty...
I would've been in big trouble if I had listened to him.
- Excuse me.
- Wait.
It already jumped up seven times, yet it can reach 40,000 won  ($40) ?
How is that possible?
It's a shame that Do Jun couldn't see that, but he's still young.
Is that a good enough answer?
Sure.
Excuse me.
What?
Hwa Young paid back what she owes you, too?
She must have paid back what she owes the Electronics, too.
Man, that means we cannot revert the separation of Hwa Young's affiliations.
Our father's only daughter sure is driven!
Where did she suddenly find such a huge amount of money?
Could it be Father?
Miracle?
So the 400 billion won  ($400M)  came out of Do Jun's pocket?
They must have requested collateral for that huge amount.
If she put out a percentage of her Department store shares,
her managerial rights may fall in danger now that her group is separated.
She went on her independent way with over 8,000 employees to look after.
I'm sure she has a plan.
The department store, the hotel, and the golf club.
Find all the cash we can in the Distribution Group.
I'm going to invest in New Data Technology.
CEO Jin, that sounds a little dangerous.
You heard the Research Team of Soonyang Investment, too.
They said it'll go up to 40,000 won  ($40)  within one month.
It'll rise by fourfold!
Also, the Business Department of Soonyang Investment
who has the highest earnings in the industry
has been purchasing the shares of New Data Technology.
While Vice-Chairman Jin Dong Ki, that man who knows these things,
is earning fourfold, fivefold of profit, should I sit around doing nothing but suck my fingers?
But CEO Jin,
you cannot make private use of the department store's fund...
I'm not keeping this for myself.
I'll return the principal and the profit back to the department store in just a month.
Don't worry about it.
Make sure to find 3 billion won  ($3M)  at all costs and invest it into New Data Technology.
CEO Oh, it's me, Jin Hwa Young.
Did you bring some, too?
Did you put in three billion won  ($3M) ?
CEO Jin, listen up.
Once the stocks go up to 40,000 won  ($40)  in a month, you have to sell them without looking back.
There is a false report going around among people in finance saying
it'll go up to 100k won  ($100)  and 200k won  ($200) , but do not linger around.
You must focus on managing the department store.
I am sharing this with you not as a creditor...
A partner.
but as a partner.
How long will this rally of new top price continue?
Up to about 300k won  ($300) .
Come on, not 30, but 300 dollars?
Says whom? Was this in a finance report?
CEO Oh did.
- Me?
- Mason?
If what's moving the stock price isn't their technology or business,
then the answer to this soaring price is evident.
Hosts of manipulators.
Yes.
They'll need the money by the nomination of next year's general election.
If the level of increase remains the same, then it'll go up to 300,000 won  ($300) .
But why 40,000 won  ($40) ?
Why did you tell her to pull out at 40 dollars?
She put in 3 billion won  ($3M) , so she'll make 12 billion won  ($12M) .
Exactly four times.
That's good enough.
It'll make her happy for making money and feel confident about investing.
Miracle Investment, Rachel speaking.
It's Vice-Chairman Jin Dong Ki.
One second.
It's the secretary of Vice-Chairman Jin Young Ki.
He's looking for you, CEO Oh.
I called you out today to be a good brother.
Hwa Young, no.
CEO Jin Hwa Young borrowed money from you, right?
I'll pay that back.
In return,
you can give me the shares of Soonyang Department Store you got as collateral.
I'm guessing you weren't happy that the department store separated from Soonyang Group.
The IMF doesn't know what the situation in Korea is like.
But at this point in time, large corporations must stick together to survive.
We must push and pull each other forward.
I'm sure you've heard the term Korean democratization.
It's the same thing.
Korea needs a Korean way of economic democratization.
Giving work to specific places. Corrupt ties with politics.
Reckless business diversification. Illegal managerial succession.
Things like these?
You do not want the separation of the affiliation
because you're afraid you won't inherit as much.
Hand over her collateral to me.
I demand 800 billion won  ($800M) .
You're going to get twice as much from this?
This is 30 percent of the shares of your sister's department store.
I'll need at least twice as much to betray my partner.
I'll give you twice as much.
Give me the shares for the department store.
I believe Chairman Jin Yang Cheol wanted this separation.
Do you think he'll be happy if the collateral ends up in your hands?
I'm doing everything for my father's sake.
She is my sister, but CEO Jin Hwa Young may be able to run the department store,
but she's not competent enough to run the Distribution Group.
If I walked in her shoes, I would have cashed out the affiliations that don't bring in money.
Well, anyway.
This is the only way to keep the department store together.
Give me the collateral, CEO Oh.
I'll think about it if you give me four times.
Are you saying you aren't looking to sell those?
I see. You weren't after the money to begin with.
You wanted the managerial rights of the department store, CEO Oh...
No, it's not you.
Is it Do Jun?
Onroad, the top internet company of Korea
just announced a technical tie-up with New Data Technology.
When the announcement was made,
New Data Technology's stock price skyrocketed and ended the day at 5500 won  ($55) .
The stock market says if this level of increase continues,
they will become the first company in the history of KOSDAQ
to reach 100k won  ($100)  within the month.
The price went over 40k won  ($40) . It's skyrocketing.
I'm starting to wonder.
Will she feel satisfied after getting what she wanted?
Or will she feel at a loss for losing something she could have had?
I wonder which is more significant.
Do you know how much I lost after selling this at 40k won  ($40) ?
In just a few hours, I lost 4.5 billion won  ($4.5M) .
I lost 4.5 billion won  ($4.5M) !
The rationality of the human mind always tells us to focus on the satisfaction we have.
But desire always stand on the side of the things we could have had.
New Data Technology continues to hit a new high for 55 days in a row.
Look at that. Drop.
We'll conduct an on-site audit for the new four branches.
How does next week sound, CEO Jin?
Drop.
Excuse me.
CEO Jin?
- CEO Jin?
Aunt, CEO Oh told me that you invested in New Data Technology.
Is he really an expert investor?
Do you know how much I lost after I listened to that man's advice?
I see. What a relief. I was worried.
There are hosts of manipulators behind New Data Technology.
- Manipulators?
- Yes.
I hear they'll take the flight up to 300k won  ($300) .
But who knows when this defective aircraft will take the plunge?
But I guess it's high risk, high return.
So it will go up further?
This isn't the time for you to make such aggressive investment.
What do you mean?
Two uncles each came to see CEO Oh.
I guess they were worried about the collateral.
They wanted to buy the department store's shares.
And?
Are you saying he handed it over?
Of course not, Aunt.
We're family.
But CEO Oh is different. You know that, right?
He's willing to do anything if you can pay the price.
Do not lay your hand on the department store's shares.
I don't care who touches it, but I will never forgive them.
Don't stand around like a creditor. Go.
That darned money? I'll pay it back.
Good grief.
I knew it, Aunt.
You surely are different from us.
Tell Director Im to come in right now.
When desire is defeated, it turns into rage and pulls the bowstring tightly.
What's the settlement cost for next month from the businesses in the department store?
- 140 billion won  ($140M), Ma'am.
- Make them into postdated checks.
- Sorry?
- I'm going to invest
those 140 billion won  ($140M)  into New Data Technology.
CEO Jin, that's the department store's...
I am Soonyang Department Store,
and Soonyang Department Store is me!
Invest all 140 billion won  ($140M) .
When the arrow leaves the bow, it flies over to the target without hesitation.
And that target is
always one's own self.
Reborn Rich
CEO Jin, you have made enough. You should stop investing in stocks...
They said it'll go up to 300k won  ($300) .
There will be a photoshoot.
The theme is a female prosecutor.
I'm Prosecutor Seo Min Yeong. Who's calling?
You want me to investigate CEO Jin Hwa Young's embezzlement?
So we're here today as a prosecutor and an informant.
Why not? Am I not allowed to?
Jin Do Jun, that jerk!
Pull yourself together, Jin Hwa Young!
How is Do Jun at fault?
Father.
I must hold a board meeting.
Today's agenda is the dismissal of CEO Jin Hwa Young.
The prosecutor in charge of Aunt Hwa Young's case is Do Jun's college classmate.
Please miss me sometimes
so that the memory of us loving can remain.