Is Xiao Bei here?
No.
Brother, go to this side.
I remember our mother put the cable here.
Come this way.
No?
No
The key is that we can't play the game without internet.
Don't break it.
Brother, I found it.
Where?
Brother
I have to take it if I find it.
Can you reach it?
Why don't you hug me?
You love to be brave.
It's not enough.
Finished
Who did this?
If it's you,
Our mother will nag at most.
If it's me,
At least a feather duster.
This thing has to be searched.
We are teammates now.
Teammates should cover for each other.
is or isn't
Don't be angry.
I'll teach you a new game.
all right?
My cable.
pretty
I told you to hide.
See where you can hide.
pretty
brother
What is this game called?
CROSS FIRE
Cross Fire
Yes?
You want to play?
I'll set up a game account for you.
That's enough.
Now you have your own game account.
But I can't play.
I'll teach you.
Let's start the game.
Xiaobei
Look.
Brother is so amazing.
Come here, Xiao Bei.
According to W,
W
Put your hands on it.
This is going up.
It's down, S is down.
AD is left and right.
Stop, stop.
If you run into the front again,
You jump up according to the space.
I'll catch up with you.
Brother, why can't I jump on it?
Is this computer broken?
Squat down first.
Then I counted 3 2 1.
You jump again.
good
three
two
one
jump
Are you happy, boy?
Shuang
Brother
This game is so fun.
Is it fun?
Brother
I'm telling you.
This game is not fun in general.
It's really fun.
If you move the mouse to the left, you are cutting the left perspective.
If you move to the right, you're looking at the right side.
Brother is so handsome.
I want to come.
Open it.
come
Does it hurt?
I'll help you up.
Did you fall on your butt?
Brother
What's going on?
The way you held the gun was wrong.
Take this pistol first.
On your shoulders.
This is the gap.
Collimating target
Three points and one line.
Okay?
good
Aim!
Here, let me hold you.
Stand still.
Aim first.
See that bottle?
I see it.
Aim for it.
One more shot.
I'm not helping you anymore.
Aim
Calm down.
three
two
one
pretty
I'm hit.
Fierce
You're really talented.
How about this? Do you want another round?
think
But what about your homework?
If you have the final exam,
Can give me the top ten.
I'll teach you how to play.
Alright?
pinky swear
You can't change for 100 years.
Seal
I'm out of bullets.
I'll give you the bullet.
hurry up
I'll cover you.
Where are you going?
Run.
I'll cover you.
I dare you to come here.
Where are you going?
Don't run.
Don't move.
Put your hands up.
That's enough.
Are you acting like a father?
Having dinner
Yes, sir.
Okay, clean the battlefield.
Are you ready to eat?
Come on, pack up.
Let's play another round.
What do you want to play?
I'm telling you,
This is a game.
Take a look.
Your mom has to scold me.
Do you know
You should eat well.
If you do that,
To be as tall as your brother.
Long and long.
I want to be taller than my brother.
Alright, alright.
You must be taller than your brother.
The weather is good today.
Let's eat on the balcony.
good
Remember to wash your hands.
Come on, wash your hands.
eat
What happened last night?
Why does the light bulb keep flashing?
Maybe it's the circuit.
In the property management group this morning,
Many owners are complaining.
Later, the property management said
A lot of communities have such a situation.
To detect the existence of mirror parallel universe.
To solve the problem of neutron decay
Has existed for 40 years.
Between the neighboring worlds,
The subtle repulsive power.
They interact with each other constantly.
son
Wake up.
Interact with each other.
Rather than evolution and development.
I can't do it anyway.
Hello, mom.
Xiaofeng
Did you report to work?
Right away.
I'll be out soon.
What time is it?
Don't be late.
Your father worked so hard
The job I got for you.
Also
Don't forget your portfolio.
Alright. Got it.
Good leader.
Everyone is so busy.
Hello, Director.
The director is here.
Alright.
It's hard.
Everyone has worked hard.
today
To introduce a new colleague.
Xiao Xiao.
Come on.
This is Xiao Feng.
The new comrade of our Integrated Office
Welcome.
well
Welcome
Come on.
Xiao, this way.
Xiao, look.
You can choose any table or chair here.
You must choose one you like.
Choose.
Choose them.
That's right.
You must be responsible.
Help Xiao.
Choose the right desk.
Let's give him the first pass.
Alright.
It's all on us.
Come on.
Take a look for yourself.
Beautiful and graceful.
The key is to fit you.
Director
Don't bother.
I'll just pick one myself.
Whatever you want.
How can this be casual?
I'm telling you,
Choose your office.
Is more important than the choice of the object.
Think about it.
You have to deal with it for the rest of your life.
But you can't be so careless.
Come on.
This is good.
This is perfect.
to take a look at
This one looks good.
Cypress
It's really strong.
The durability of cypress wood.
This is reliable.
Why don't you choose this one?
I believe in Miss Wang.
It can last forever.
This is really good. Look.
What happened
Director, what's going on?
Xiao Xiao.
It's time for lunch. Come on.
It will become a single bed.
It's comfortable to sleep.
Typing is not urgent.
Only those who rest can work.
Sleep well.
In the afternoon,
and
Don't work when everyone is resting.
Will cause trouble.
Go to sleep.
Alright.
Everyone has worked hard.
Good afternoon!
Is this yours?
Have you seen my shoes?
Above ground
Where is it?
I put it here just now.
No, who told you to touch my stuff?
Put your shoes on my desk.
what?
As an offering.
Get my shoes back now.
otherwise
I'll give your phone to Director Zheng.
Alright.
I'll report you for cheating.
Sleep in class.
And discriminates against disabled students.
Are you looking for shoes?
I just saw it was broken.
I thought it was garbage.
So I threw it away.
Where did you throw it?
In the middle of the garbage can on the first floor.
Please tell me.
This time,
It's our choice for the track and field team.
So I hope everyone
Can give full play to their capabilities.
Go to all lengths
all right?
good
Get ready.
Chu song
how could that be?
The shoes are broken.
Go back.
My shoes are broken.
Do you have a backup?
Let me change my sneakers.
a row
Hurry. Go back.
Teacher,
When can we start?
That's right.
Chu song
Why don't you join the competition next time?
Namely
Don't waste your precious time.
Sir, let's get started.
Get ready.
Get set
I can beat you with my bare feet.
Refuse to accept
One more round.
Congratulations.
Barefoot Immortal.
You're stepping on the Hot Wheels.
Why don't I lend you my shoes?
Anyway, I don't need it.
Go away
You're back.
Hurry and eat.
chopsticks
Where are your shoes?
I lost it.
How can I lose my shoes?
Did you make trouble at school again?
Where are the chopsticks?
The sports meeting next month.
My running shoes are broken.
What?
It can't be fixed.
And the nail is bald.
It's only been a few months.
Do you practice sprinting or eating shoes?
That's it.
Xiao Xiao.
You can do that.
Did you practice the piano when you were young?
Your typing speed is fast.
personnel
No, thank you.
Thank you, Director.
I usually touch the keyboard a lot.
I'm familiar with them.
I'm telling you,
I'll take good care of you.
Come on.
I have an important task for you.
Next month,
Our union will hold an event.
I ordered a batch of those bunting.
Check if they're ready.
Especially that color.
I ordered the red one.
Don't be partial.
The red one is very bright.
How do you like my taste?
I must.
I'll be right there.
Hurry up.
This order
Please hurry up.
Okay, hold on.
Thank you
Boss
A bowl of instant noodles.
A bottle of drink.
Two ham sausages.
eighteen
To the man with the paper on the headset.
You want to tell him who bought it?
No need
Someone gave it to you.
to take away
If you don't eat, you will starve to death.
I don't want food even if I starve to death.
It's okay if you don't eat.
But you paid the rent.
You should go back.
Otherwise, you will waste too much.
I haven't planned to go back since I moved out.
You said that.
I'll rent it out.
casual
Lieutenant
Can you be realistic?
Do something serious.
Don't waste time here.
Look at me.
With a job and a future,
The leader values me very much.
Look.
And gave me a big project.
I'm looking for you.
One hundred flags. Come here.
Come on.
Little by little.
Order a little.
Fifteen.
twenty
Look, the quality of this flag is very good.
fifty
It's a big project.
You're amazing.
amazing
Big project.
Look at this flag.
The quality is so good.
I will starve you to death.
Come on.
Stay a bit!
Why is my closet open?
Where's my bag?
Mine is gone too.
It's in there.
Chu song
Did I send it to the wrong location?
What time is it?
No one came.
Don't worry!
The time will come.
Where's Reborn?
They said their team wouldn't let go.
What a good sniper rifle.
Their team will be in the same division as us.
Great.
A teammate becomes an opponent.
In 2049,
My family has arranged a job for me.
I'm not coming.
How could our team?
Then I'll contact 2049.
We can wait two more days for him.
perfect
You have a reason to stop coming.
What if she doesn't come?
You're not working?
Let's go home.
Boss will pay the bill.
to wait a moment
I have an appointment with someone.
You have an appointment with someone.
I remember now.
You are allergic to cats.
Why did you invite people here?
I didn't ask for this place.
She asked me out.
She's so pretty.
You didn't introduce him to me.
Are you still my brother?
He's here.
Pandora
Lu Xiao Bei,
Hello
I said the taxi of Ning Jiang
It's too cruel.
A few kilometers of road,
I can't spend so much on a taxi.
ticket
Reimbursement
Beauty
What do you call it?
S + 1 Su Jiayi
The master I hired
Killer
Hello, Su Jiayi.
My name is Cheng Hao. I'm from...
Waiter/Waitress
Hello, have a look.
Take a look.
What will you order?
What?
This is already
The best coffee shop in Ningjiang.
There are hands to make coffee. Look.
What is there to drink?
No matter how hard you are, you're full.
Is there egg fried rice?
Sorry there is no egg fried rice here
This is the most important e-sports town in East China.
a book is not judged by its cover
There are bad clothes everywhere.
I can't understand.
And this one.
My name is Cheng Hao.
It's not important.
Where is the master?
Something went wrong.
Where are the people?
Less than we expected.
Just tell me
Except us,
Who else is there?
Shake hands.
I'm Cheng Hao.
Ning Jiang, Song Zhongji.
Lu Xiao Bei,
We agreed to combine the strong and the strong.
It's a big deal.
There's a sponsor.
You have a master.
What about the sponsorship?
Where is the master?
The sponsorship fee means
Others need to pay for joining our team.
Understand?
You came all the way here to play with me.
There are a few people.
But at least we can
To be the main force.
You don't have to pay for it.
Let's figure out a way.
You're here.
Give it a try.
You know I'm...
A big V with 100,000 followers on Weibo?
celebrity microblogger
I'll lose my fans if I stay with you.
The round trip fare.
To me on WeChat.
Then I'll make you black.
S+1
My mother, this big sister,
What a wild way!
Have you heard of the Blue Fish Team?
The only semi-professional player
All Women Team.
Su Jiayi is the captain.
The first female gunman in Shanghai.
Then the team broke up because of bad results.
The players went to school.
Get married.
She's the only one
You're still professional.
She's a master?
Call her back.
No need
You can't call him back.
unless
She wanted to come back.
What do you mean?
With her mouth,
All the ten people in the circle have offended nine and a half.
She can't live any longer.
If she still wants to be a professional,
Here
Is her last choice.
He's here.
I have good news for you.
Half a minute ago,
I decided to stay here.
The condition is worse.
The environment is bad.
But think about it.
A few months later, the top story in esports circles
Through the fire goddess Su Jiayi.
To lead the third-rate team.
Into the top professional league.
The design is wonderful.
The story is inspiring.
By then, my fans on Weibo
To one million yuan.
You all have my light.
Hello, everyone.
Today, Su Jiayi came to Ningjiang.
Today is Pandora.
By the way, I'd like to introduce
My Ning Jiang's younger brother, Habi,
Hapi
Say hello to everyone.
Follow me, Su Jiayi. Tonight,
To see Su Jiayi and Hobby.
The two-bedroom house is mine.
I can live here.
Can also rub the computer.
Play games.
My mother.
Is it a place where people live?
You've been saving takeouts for years.
Aunt Bao has something at home.
You didn't come to clean it.
It's not like two days.
Like two years.
Your TV looks good.
Why are you shooting it?
Xiaokang, give her some color.
Master, I'm here.
How does it look?
Konka TV is very high-tech.
Artificial intelligence, have you heard of it?
I can't live here.
There are cockroaches.
I'm most afraid of cockroaches.
So,
therefore
Su Jiayi, goddess of e-sports,
In such a bad environment.
I like the setting.
You still use Derricks?
A little tasteful.
Get up.
This is mine
Lu Xiao Bei,
I'll live here from now on.
what
I live in this room.
Give it to me.
You live in this room.
Where will I live?
Didn't your team handle the accommodation?
I'll give it to you.
I live on the street.
Isn't there a room?
The house
This room
This is a utility room, this is for storage.
I live here.
I'll let you go.
Xiaobei
Aren't you bullying an honest man?
What can we do?
Let her stay in a hotel if she can't.
What about the money?
I'll give you half an hour to pack up.
I'm tired.
I want to sleep later.
Move out of my way
Is there something wrong with your door?
Sister, sorry.
In this room,
Except for you.
Tell you what,
You have three days to fix it.
What are you doing?
to rent an apartment
You live here?
I have to make it clear.
Is to share with me.
Indifferent
How big is the house?
What direction?
It's more than 20.
To the south.
Twenty-one and twenty-nine.
It's all over 20.
How big is it?
Why are you so stubborn?
I don't know. I have no idea.
anyway
It's not small.
It's cheaper.
This is my lowest price.
How about this?
I'll pay for the internet.
We share the water and electricity.
Alright?
I'm not online.
If you don't go online,
What are you doing?
The glasses are so thick.
You are a perfect student.
You can read books every day.
I'm telling you,
It's no use reading.
It's nothing.
Calm down.
You're An Lan, right?
You don't remember me?
I stayed in grade two and went to your class.
At the edge of the platform.
I
Xiao Feng.
No
You don't want to rent it?
Let go of Xiao Feng.
Don't.
Hold on.
Since we are old schoolmates,
You don't need 300, you need 250.
You're only 250.
I'm not staying.
It's so cheap.
Do you have a problem with me?
Who gets close to the vermilion.
Who keeps company with the wolf will learn to howl
Next to you, a repeater,
How did I get into graduate school?
And look down on you.
I have to let you stay here today.
Two hundred and four.
Three hundred.
Two hundred.
Deal
come
please
What about
Which room do I live in?
here
What about
It's very transparent.
Whose boxes are these?
These?
My former teammates
Ex-girlfriend
boyfriend
I'm teasing you.
You're a perfect student.
Give me the key to this room.
key
My ex-boyfriend and I never lock the door.
Look at my room.
There's no door.
Give me the key.
I don't know where the key is.
Give it to me.
good
This is too much.
Find it yourself.
By the way,
The bathroom.
This is the kitchen and the living room.
No, Big Sister.
Can we be polite?
I haven't finished yet.
Don't enter my room without my consent.
Who can enter your room?
We have been classmates for so many years.
Did I look at you more often?
besides
You're not pretty.
Even if you look like a fairy,
You're wearing glasses.
You know I have the Four Eyes.
Just one word.
ugly
Only shallow people
You don't know how to appreciate the meaning of others.
I'll invite you to go to the public.
And dressed up.
To maintain the most basic politeness between people.
a row
I'm telling you,
My body
I will cover it up.
I won't let you take advantage.
first
I have no interest in you.
second
Install a door in your room.
Within two days,
Or I'll cancel the lease.
You have a door here.
I have to have a door, right?
no
No way.
See clearly.
I have installed this door for you.
Why did you put your clothes in the fridge?
The refrigerator has stopped cooling.
So I have to reuse the wardrobe.
Fix it.
It's written in black and white on your advertisement.
The appliances are complete.
I'm still breathing.
Are you finished?
And apply the disinfectant three times.
Four Eyes, I installed the door
To tell you that
You're not the only one who can slam the door.
I will.
feed
Lu Xiao Bei,
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm telling you,
Get this woman out of my house.
Whether I have her or not,
Cheng Hao, calm down.
What's up
She took my room.
I won't talk about it.
She even changed my wireless password.
That's too bullying.
You're on the offline.
My fans are waiting for me.
You're still live.
You have 100,000 followers.
99,000 were bought with money.
Don't think I didn't know.
People like you
Who can't eat the grapes.
I've seen a lot of them.
Cut the crap.
Turn on the computer.
Pick a game for me face to face.
Pick a fight with me. Torture me.
Are you match me?
Do I deserve it?
I want a key.
You asked me if I deserve it.
Hum
Lu Xiao Bei, did you hear that?
Hi.
I recruited a new player today.
Her name is Su Jiayi.
It's a girl.
She's quite special.
You're really good at stirring up trouble.
But it's okay.
She's a good shot.
I trusted her very much.
Recently,
And met a stranger girl.
Her name is Chu Ge.
Is my deskmate.
The girl is really weird.
I can always find a way to get you in trouble.
According to the Internet,
Women are made of water.
Men are made of earth.
This is probably the legendary
The environment is not good.
The Hundred Cities League is about to begin.
But I don't know how to start.
I don't know either
If I fail,
What will I face?
But it's okay.
I won't be destroyed.
I will...
Will become stronger.
Just wait and see.
What are you doing?
Cockroach, look.
cockroach
Give it to me.
No way
There are so many people here.
You're spritzing.
The cockroach was poisoned.
I poisoned you first.
Give it to me.
Cockroaches can fly.
You can't hide from the ceiling.
Come down.
come down
No way
hurry up
Did you eat instant noodles?
How do you know?
Get down. Get out.
Get out of here.
over there
hurry up
Close the door.
What's this?
To catch cockroaches.
What's the principle?
What principle?
Look.
Do not
It's a principle that can't be learned from books.
It's called living wisdom.
You nerds,
I'll never learn it in my lifetime.
Correct!
I should remind you that
Like snacks and instant noodles.
If you open it, you must finish it.
If you can't finish it,
Throw it away.
Except cockroaches,
The mice will kill you.
you
You have to take these out. I won't move them.
You're so scared.
Correct!
This is sprayed with insecticide.
I threw it away for you.
This one hasn't been opened.
I'll help you eat it.
Alright
For the last time,
feed
Are you a liar?
It's me.
Where are we?
It doesn't matter.
By the way, bro,
I want to ask you.
How did you know that Liu Xiang withdrew?
Stop pretending.
You really think you're from 2008?
nonsense
Aren't you from 2008?
I'm seven.
What about now?
Now 19,
Are we really crossing over?
It's not called crossing.
The connection between time and space.
The premise is that
Are you really Xiao Feng from 2008?
I'm really Xiao Feng.
replacement guaranteed if not genuine
How can you believe me?
Send me your championship trophy.
I believe you.
Where did I get the championship trophy?
The troops have been dismissed.
I've stopped playing games.
The troops indeed broke up once.
But they reorganized soon.
Then they took down
The winner of the National Challenge.
To open a new era.
Since then,
Video game competition.
It has a new name.
It's called e-sports.
Give me your address.
Why do you want my address?
I'm sending you a letter.
Why are you sending me a letter?
You don't believe me.
I must make you believe me this time.
a row
Then send it to
No.122, Nanshan Road
Nanshan Police Station.
Lu Tianming, turn to Xiao Bei.
You live in the police station.
This is my dad's office.
feed
Can you hear me?
Hello, are you still there?
feed
The champion.
Am I dreaming?
Or are you dreaming?
what are you doing?
Do you have any paper?
Lend me some.
to wait a moment
You don't have to pay it back.
This is so ordinary.
Do you have a pattern?
The one and only pattern.
No
My family is not a supermarket.
Do you have an envelope?
Why do you need the envelope?
Urgent business
I'm writing a very important letter.
to wait a moment
There's no envelope.
This is unique. I'll give it to you.