How are you?
Are you feeling unwell?
I'm fine
This little guy...
I'm worried that the pond will dry up during the summer vacation
really
Hope it will rain
yes
Hayakame
Did you have breakfast?
I'll come back to see you after the first class.
No! That side is better.
More sunshine
Go over there quickly.
It's not fun here, you see?
It should be fun on that side or the other side.
Kamekichi: I've always thought this should be an orange, right?
Do you think this is edible?
Very hard
Really hard
alright
Very sour
Really
This shouldn't be eaten.
So you decided to work in a company?
right
I will accompany my dad on overseas inspection tours starting in September.
I really hope people like you can stay in college
I will turn my dream of becoming a researcher into
Leave it to the next life to realize
Sorry, sorry.
I can't believe he's gone so soon.
It's really shocking that he left so young.
yes
Maoxiong is obviously much younger than us
Really young
- So pitiful
-What a shame.
No way
Kamekichi
Kamekichi, where are you?
Kamekichi…
(I brought the turtle home, please don't worry)
Good morning, Kamekichi
If this is the script of her life...
Hayakame
Did you have breakfast?
- I'm just an unknown extra
- I'll come see you after the first class.
Sorry, sorry.
The lens won't focus.
A student A
Now please tell us your motivation for applying
yes
When I was a kid
My father would always be there when I got home
Leave snacks on the table for me
Eating the strawberry milk candy from Bell Rabbit House
Makes me feel very happy...
Interviewer B
sorry
Excuse me
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Boss C
Misa
Do you want to watch the World Cup together?
-football?
- Not football.
I'm going to talk to my friends on the college football team
Go to a sports bar to watch a game
- I want to introduce you to each other
- What? I'll be nervous.
- Do I understand the rules?
- Don't worry, I'll teach you.
The extra standing in the corner with no lines
- Your birthday present
-What?
- You have to wear it to work
- Yeah, thanks.
You two are so slow.
- We have a reservation.
-Feel sorry
Sorry, the section chief won't let us go.
Let's go
Oops, I'm starving.
I will never appear in her story
That's how it should have been.
But on September 18, 2015…
Excuse me
She suddenly swooped over
sorry
I said terrible things because I was so flustered.
That scarf doesn't suit you.
Please wait for it to cool down.
I'm really sorry
Minister Suzuki
I'm sorry for saying something rude to you.
Me too
(Minister Suzuki)
What to do Kame-Kichi?
New progress has emerged
Good morning
morning
Your burns...
-Good morning, everyone.
-Good morning
Good morning, Misa
I have disliked you since I was a child
We have never been friends
Good morning, Rina
Congratulations again on your engagement.
Thanks
You were just talking to the business strategy department.
Minister Suzuki, are you going to say anything?
yes
When did you first meet?
On the day of the briefing
I accidentally bumped into him in the elevator
Right
So you and the rich kid
The relationship is so good that they greet each other.
Very good
You actually let the rich kid know you
-Rich kid?
- Minister Suzuki
He is the grandson of the chairman and the son of the general manager.
What?
-Isn't he handsome?
-right
I heard that he filmed our company's commercial when he was a kid.
I have seen it online
That ad?
right
He is very capable at work.
A bit cool but also charming
He is single, right?
Rich Kids…
Back to the point
There was indeed a boss with this nickname before.
It was him
Misa, are you tired of hearing this?
After all, you have no interest in company gossip.
Esaka
Quotation
How's the progress?
I'm starting now
Didn’t I ask you to finish it last week?
Sorry, I have so many other things on my plate.
Jiang Ban, please keep your promise
You are now qualified to teach new people.
So please pay more attention.
Okay, I'll be careful.
Sumiyoshi, you're wearing a new suit.
right
Because the mortgage is crushing me.
I haven't bought new clothes for a long time.
Misa, you've worked hard.
You've worked hard too.
Have you read the information?
information?
(I looked for a bunch of wedding venues
Check out these links!)
Let's go
I always feel it's incredible
No one here knows anything about us
Unbelievable?
I mean...
No one knows you are my fiancée
Give me curry rice, please!
alright
I'll stay at your house tonight.
I started
start
So disgusting
I don't want to breathe the same air as him.
curry…
Why do you think I married you?
The reason why I'm like you
An inconspicuous and boring woman gets married
It's because you are stingy and save money.
"Why should I marry you?"
I will never marry this person
Oh, Misa.
The last time we watched football at a sports bar
You left early, right?
right
You must be feeling ashamed, right?
Ashamed?
After all, compared to the girls around me
To be honest, you are not impressive.
I can understand why you're upset.
But we are not compatible
What others think doesn’t matter
Don't lose confidence
Because the person I chose is you
You are too high up.
I can't wait for you to meet my mom.
When do you want to meet the parents?
Meet the parents...
You can continue to work
But you can't use work as an excuse not to do housework.
Can I show a gynecological and obstetric diagnosis before getting married?
It turns out that women without parents are useless.
When is the offer?
My mother is very busy.
How come I didn't see through this guy's true face?
Look at this
This sticker is so funny
He has an Oedipus complex and is self-centered
Emotional blackmail
Do you know cryptocurrency?
Put the money in the bank now
Just a waste of money and time
There is a kind of Duruchis coin that ordinary people can't buy
But the senior from the football team introduced me to the way
Right
That's a scam
He will be cheated out of all his money.
He's also a super narcissist.
I want to beat myself up
Why am I so ignorant of people?
I envy you guys for having such a good relationship.
Rina
I'm leaving soon. Sit over there.
Why?
Wait, someone is looking for me.
So you just sit there.
I finally finished the quotation.
Youya, listen to me
What's wrong?
Newcomers have poor working ability
I've been helping her with things.
But Deputy Section Chief Sumiyoshi was very tolerant of her.
Only super strict with me
Because I'm a contract employee
She used me as a punching bag to vent her stress
Right?
Um…
Lina, you are so pitiful.
This is work, so I can only cheer up.
Lina, you are so sensible.
But you should speak up.
You're just too nice.
Thanks
Only you and Misa understand me
I started
What can I do to get these two people married?
They will have an affair in ten years
So there shouldn't be no chance now.
What's wrong?
Yeah, I'm having lunch.
- Lina has a fiancé at this time
- I'm eating curry
-Yes.
-Really?
Please give me a large cup.
The other party is a boyfriend with excellent conditions
Working in an advertising agency
In contrast…
He doesn't do housework and has no future
Self-evaluation is like a daily limit
Oedipus complex
No, he can't win.
nothing
Sorry, I was talking to someone. What's wrong?
But as long as he doesn't speak
Looks pretty handsome
Reina, please discover Tomoya's charm.
Can you spare the time?
So happy
He is a nice guy when he is in a good mood.
And he plays rugby so he's got good stamina
Treat him as a human being and you will have expectations
But if you regard him as willful and reckless
A dog that loves to act like a spoiled child and bites people when it is unhappy...
Why would I marry a man like this?
Look
You two really match each other.
You two seem like a perfect match.
no
She really looked down on both of us.
Next time, invite your boyfriend and the four of us to drink together
He is very busy
That's right
There is still a chance
The boyfriend at the advertising agency has a real girlfriend
Damn scumbag!
Rina
After she found out that he was cheating on her
They argued about this for months.
Then Reina got dumped on Christmas Eve
Give me back my time!
Lina is about to break up with her boyfriend
Opportunity is here
My stomach is full
I'm stuffed
Wait, what is this?
I remember
I'm stuffed
-sorry
-Are you okay?
-what to do?
- I didn't notice it myself
I'm really sorry for such a nice suit.
I'll get something to wipe it.
- What a disaster
-yes
Now I understand
She did it on purpose
-Are you leaving?
-Deputy Section Chief Sumiyoshi!
Hey! Really?
I'm sorry, friends!
Are you kidding me?
I'm sorry, it was Misa who suddenly rushed out.
Hirano, are you okay?
-Um…
-Are you okay?
Sure enough, what is supposed to happen will still happen.
I'm sorry
But if there is a replacement...
This is expensive
sorry
- Can't be wiped off
-Destiny can be changed
-what to do?
-I really...
It's really bad.
This suit and shirt are very expensive.
Sorry, Tomoya
Let me compensate you
Need not
It doesn't matter
You didn't mean it.
I should clean it immediately.
Or send it for dry cleaning
I don’t know if it can be washed off?
what?
What are you doing?
Why are you giving it to me?
- You take it to wash.
- Is this your suit?
Very good
I finally said what I wanted to say to him.
Is this the first time? It should be the first time
I am different from the first time I lived.
I can start over
After all, I finally got ten years younger.
Excuse me
What's up?
that…
What's wrong?
I have an emergency
Could it be that...
That's right.
I'll get it to you right away.
Thanks for your help
I thought I would never be able to leave the bathroom.
Don't say that
The restroom on that floor is inexplicably rarely used.
I also asked others for help but they ignored me.
Ignore you?
I heard someone leaving while talking on the phone
That person is definitely Jiang Ban
I'm so sorry
Why are you apologizing?
If someone messes with me, I will definitely fight back
So I'm fine
The same is true when you get help
What?
You are my benefactor
I will definitely repay you
(Bean Game Hall)
-This is delicious too
-Hello
-Welcome
-welcome
Same old thing?
- Bean turtle tea set
-good
- Please go up to the second floor
-OK
- I'm going to prepare now
-Thanks
Sorry for the long wait
Thanks
Please use slowly
I started
This always makes me feel at ease.
Hello
I said something very rude the other day.
A few days ago?
I'm the one who shouldn't apologize.
So you two are friends.
Please use slowly
-May I?
- What? Can you please take a seat?
-that…
- Please speak
- No, you say it first
No, you say it first.
How is your burn?
No big deal
Do you come here often?
I come when I want to be alone.
No, that's not what I meant.
This is the shop my dad brought me to.
Your father?
right
I feel safe when I come here
Minister Suzuki, what about you?
I found this store while doing research
Sometimes I will organize market research reports here
Market research?
（Store product evaluation）
“It’s better to visit people in person than to study the information”
This is what the president taught me.
It's your grandfather, right?
-What?
- I heard from my colleague today
So that's it
Did you know that Bell Rabbit Holdings
A Japanese confectionery shop originating from Sendagi
The "Bell Rabbit House"?
I know
My dad likes the red bean daifuku at Suzutoya very much
That is the taste that has been passed down from the first generation.
The same taste...
I think it's great. So is the strawberry milk candy.
Childhood
The moment you put the candy in your mouth
Do you believe it?
Oh, I remember the advertisement of Bell Rabbit House.
Minister, you are the little boy dancing with the bell rabbit, right?
Who told you about this?
It's my colleague.
I miss you so much
I don't know if I can still find that ad...
Please don't search
That's my dark history.
sorry
You don’t know “that” either, do you?
"that"?
What people call me behind my back
Rich kid?
I thought the rich kid
Only appears in girls' comics or Korean dramas
I didn't expect it really existed.
-Are you making fun of me?
-No
That's a good idea.
Everyone means well when they say it.
Good meaning?
After all, rich kids are usually very cold.
But no matter where the heroine gets into trouble
He will come to rescue her.
This is everyone's dream
And everyone said
Minister, you are very capable at work. It's really amazing.
The reason why I got my current position
Of course it's not because of my strength
But…
You really like Japanese confectionery, right?
I also like the sweet potato yokan in this store.
Here
Can I see it?
Please feel free to
(Ginza "Karia Matcha")
Compared with your information
Mine is like a child's doodle
Nowadays, just search online
It seems that all the information can be found
But you visit the store and experience it yourself
Whether it is the aroma, taste or the atmosphere in the store
This information obtained through your five senses
Absolutely irreplaceable
I think there's nothing wrong with the way you do things.
but…
Compared to Sakura Hall, I recommend the Jintsuba of Gangan.
I can't agree with this
minister
What do you think of Kawataya's soy sauce dumplings?
Why is the rating so low?
It's obviously delicious
The sauce tastes too strong
The taste needs to be lighter to be popular with the public
Senzaki
Is the only choice
Senzaki's soy sauce dumplings are indeed delicious but...
Have you been there?
I've been
-I remember the main store is in Kyoto, right?
-right
But the Tokyo branch is also good
Speaking of Kyoto
Gion Keika limited time offer
The co-branded Japanese-style cafe opens this week
I wanted to go but was too busy with work...
Not what I said before.
I mean you have to go.
(Reina shopping at 17:00)
On this day…
Isn't this place great?
Well, it's so rare for us to have a meal at the hotel.
Everyone is here
Rina
haven't seen you for a long time
how so?
Today is a class reunion
If I had told you in advance you wouldn't have come, right?
-Long time no see, Reina
-haven't seen you for a long time
I'm fine. How are you guys?
Reina, do you work at Suzutoya?
I changed the company.
So cool
Really?
Lina, where is your boyfriend from the advertising company?
-Wait what?
- I haven't heard of it.
What?
I may be here soon
There will be news to announce to everyone
Where did Kobe escape to?
In the blink of an eye, it disappeared
She's still as gloomy as ever
As long as she is there, the atmosphere is heavy
Why would Reina be friends with someone like that?
Lina is so nice
Kobe actually dared to show up
Obviously did something too much
- That's what I mean
-real
Are you guys going too far?
-But it's true.
-Yes.
That woman is so thick-skinned
Misa
Are you really going home?
Sorry, I'm not feeling well.
“You did something so excessive.”
(Class reunion at 17:00)
(Search Facebook)
(Log in or register)
(email or phone number password)
What is the password?
password…
(Kamekichi)
(Login)
(Friend invitation from Yuuto Tanabe)
Tanabe-san?
Sorry for sending you a private message out of the blue
I am your classmate at Toyama Chuo High School
Tanabe Yuto
This book is very interesting. You can take a look at it.
I would like to contact you
Because there's something that's been bothering me.
It's about a letter that Reina Esaka gave me
Share your thoughts with me after reading this
I was shocked by what you said at that time.
But then the more I thought about it, the more I felt
You can't write that kind of letter.
Can we talk?
I am so happy
letter?
Misa, let's go back.
good
Then I'm leaving
Goodbye
goodbye
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
What are you talking about?
He asked me if I was interested in joining the drama club.
He showed me the script for the next performance
The content is really interesting
Are you planning on performing on stage?
No
I just want to help out behind the scenes.
That doesn't suit you, so forget it.
Girls think Tanabe Yuuto is disgusting
If you hang out with that kind of people
I'm worried that people will misunderstand you and him as the same kind.
Although I know nothing about drama
But I think it's great
Glad to hear that. Thanks.
Can you give me your contact information?
sure
I just haven't got your contact information yet.
-Yeah?
-right
Very good
for you
That’s when it started
The whole class started to ignore me.
Kobe is so lonely
- Stop it.
-Um
Eating alone
She will hear it.
(Keep studying! Dad left it to me)
- Look
-good
Feel sorry
I tried to open the window but accidentally bumped into it.
So pitiful
Lina, do you want to have dinner with us?
good
Come on over here
I'll get you a chair.
Rina
- Your bento is so cute
- So cute
- The lunch box is too small
-How come?
- It doesn't feel enough.
- That's enough.
Wait, I want one too.
Too much
Not good
That one doesn't suit you.
This one is the best for you
Good for you
Doesn’t this look great?
It definitely fits your home.
Just buy it back
I feel really good.
By the way, today...
Gion Keika limited time offer
The co-branded Japanese-style cafe opens this week
good
Today I decided to take a one-day food tour
Now that I am healthy, of course I can do what I want to do.
No clothes to wear
Clear weather is expected in Kanto today
Good weather with blue sky and white clouds
The daytime high temperature is around 22 degrees
The weather is very comfortable
-But the sunlight is stronger at noon...
-Kamekichi, what do you think?
Please remember to wear a hat or sunscreen to protect against UV rays
A man who shows up wherever he goes
In real life, he's a stalker.
Northern Japan and Hokuriku
Clear weather due to high pressure
Mostly sunny weather is also expected in western Japan
Okinawa is sunny
Perfect for outdoor leisure activities
The air is dry and fresh, suitable for going out...
(Japanese confectionery)
How many people are there?
Two
Please wait
How many people are there? One person?
Currently needing a waiting list, can you accept it?
I'll bring the menu right over.
- Sorry, please wait.
-good
-How many people can I ask?
-One
Sorry, but we are currently full.
It takes about 30 minutes
that…
If you don't mind
Minister, you are here to investigate as well, right?
Sorry, am I being nosy?
No thanks for saving me time
Thanks
Matcha Parfait is a must-order
But there are also bracken cakes and nerikiri…
I want to eat Dorayaki too
There is also yellow body rain
Oops, it's a hard decision
Do you want to share it equally?
Equally divided?
So we can try many kinds
The efficiency of the investigation will be better
Thanks
-Come
-Thanks
You like roasted tea, right?
You also drink it at Douguitang
right
Drinking this will make me feel at ease.
But people often say I'm an old man
Who says such a thing?
It's ok, just pretend I didn't say anything
I also like
Roasted tea really makes people feel at ease, right?
right
At first I thought he was cold.
I didn't expect him to be so good.
etc.
He is the president's grandson.
He is handsome and capable at work
This kind of character only appears in girls' comics
Is it possible to meet by chance so frequently?
that…
If you don't mind
I met you so many times in a short period of time.
Did he do it on purpose?
Is he ambushing me?
Think about it
He went a little too far in criticizing me that day.
And like he said, I don't judge people.
Whether it's Reina or Tomoya, I only attract bad people
I'm a magnet for bad people
No decent person would come near me
That is to say, this guy
He's probably a super bad guy.
No wonder I always feel like something is wrong
I can't be fooled anymore
Don't make the same mistake again.
After all, Youya was very nice to me at the beginning.
He wears the mask of a rich kid.
Actually a stalker?
Bully? Nervous maniac? Psychopath? Sociopath?
How are you?
not good
What?
No, nothing.
Wait, calm down.
He is a rich kid.
There's no way she'd be interested in someone like me.
What's wrong?
No, it's okay.
-Thank you for coming
-Thanks
Really delicious
Yes
that…
-What's up?
-What are your plans next?
I want to buy some clothes
clothing?
I was so busy organizing that I lost a lot of clothes
No clothes to wear...
-scarf!
-What?
The scarf I made for you a few days ago
I made a very disrespectful comment
I lost that scarf.
I'm so sorry
No, it's not your fault.
If you don't mind...
Please say
I want to buy you a new scarf as an apology
I know a good shop nearby.
What?
(Jiupin Fochuan Greenway)
Just turn the corner and you'll arrive
good
(Top 39,800, Pants 41,000)
that…
I can't afford the expensive shop
This is my apology gift to you for my slip of the tongue.
Need not
I pay for the things I want to buy myself.
So cute
What? Second-hand clothes are so cheap?
Only 500 yen?
-500 yen?
-right
Impossible
It's really amazing
This is my first time in this kind of store
Do you come here often?
I used to come to this kind of store with my mom.
I really can't tell
This yellow sweater suits you very well.
But I don't usually wear bright clothes like this
Really? It looks like a good fit.
Does your boyfriend agree too?
No, he is my boss!
What? That's so funny.
Thanks to the minister, I was able to get a bargain.
Very good
(88,000 yen)
Shopping is so enjoyable
Was it unhappy before?
Um...yeah
When I cleaned the room
Find clothes I like or want to keep
There isn't even one.
I just realized that I always care about other people's views
Wearing clothes you don't like
That was easier for me at the time.
After all, you don't have to think for yourself
But today I realized how unfortunate that was.
You can start now
Anything is fine
If there is anything that makes you feel regretful
Pity…
When I was in the first year of high school, I really wanted to join the drama club.
Although I say that I'd rather be a behind-the-scenes person
But actually…
Do you want to go on stage?
I want to try to be a different person.
But I can't join the drama club now
(Rina)
Is it okay if you don’t answer?
Today is our class reunion
But I won't go
Why not go?
They'll say bad things about me anyway.
Again?
fine
Because my high school life was not good
Now I can't change the past
I can't get back the three years of high school.
Do you know why cacti have thorns?
Cactus thorns?
That's to protect yourself.
Protected from strong sandstorms and scorching sun
and attacks by animals that want to eat them
Cactus cannot move in the desert
Even if the living conditions are extremely unfavorable
Cactus still
Fight in your own way
You might have been helpless in your first year of high school.
But maybe now you have at least one thorn
You can fight back against those who hurt you.
A thorn, eh?
that…
Please accept
I pay you
It's just a small token of my appreciation.
Please accept it
Thanks
Sorry for the long wait
Sorry for asking you out so suddenly
I want to thank you for your help last time
I'm glad you asked me out.
Is he your boyfriend?
Not really
- But you two look like a good match
-No
If I disturb your date
Maybe I should leave?
I'm leaving
Then I'll pass the baton to you.
I think it suits you very well
That dress just now
Which dress was it?
Kobe
If it's love at first sight, just buy it.
The money Kobe earns should be spent on himself
The reason why I'm like you
An inconspicuous and boring woman gets married
It's because you are stingy and save money.
you're right
Buy it
- Sorry, I want this one
-OK
You really bought it
-Which one is better?
- So beautiful
Which of these two do you think is better?
-this
-this?
Okay, this is it.
So cute
- I think it suits you.
-Really?
I didn't know you would smile so happily in the future
We've been working together for so long.
I never really knew you.
sorry
I wanted to talk to you more.
But Lina always sticks close to you
Let me stay away from it
-Rina
-Long time no see, Reina
After all, Reina is like a woman's bad qualities
The all-in-one person like espresso
I thought you wanted to be friends with someone like her.
It means you should be the same
-sorry
- No, you're right.
(Rina)
but…
I decided to end it
Sorry for the long wait
Come
Just leave it to him.
His skills are superb
I can't wait
Will Kobe really come today?
Yes, but I can't contact her.
After all, Misa is very independent.
Lina, you are really a good person.
She did such a terrible thing to you.
Please don't mention that in front of Misa, okay?
I really don't mind at all
Is everyone ready to drink? Let's drink.
cheers!
The stage is set
I won't run away this time.
This stage...
It belongs to me
Rina
People who will cancel their appointments on the day
Just ignore her.
Besides, no one wanted to see her.
Just seeing that face is disappointing.
-Yes.
-right
Sorry I'm late
Thank you for asking me to come today.
Kobe?
Sorry to interrupt you.
You are saying bad things about me, please keep going.
You dress too deliberately.
What are you trying to show off?
Kobe, your personality is still as bad as before
I'm here to ask you...
One thing that has always bothered me
I would like to know...
Why does everyone hate me?
Why do we hate you?
It's your own fault.
My fault?
- Stop it.
-Kobe, you used to like Yuto, right?
But after Yuto fell in love with Reina
You started to use underhanded tactics to bully Reina.
Everyone knows this.
Insidious means?
You ignore the bad things she says about her online
She also threw away her textbooks
I see
Who told you that?
There's no point in you being evasive
Lina told me this herself.
We are all witnesses
She cried in front of us and said she had endured it for a long time.
It's really sad.
So that's it
And you
I also sent a
Should I write this conceited and disgusting letter to Yuto?
You wrote: "If you follow me again
I will report you to the school and the police."
That's ridiculous.
I didn't write to Tanabe-san.
I didn't play dirty tricks on Reina.
- Stop lying.
- That's enough
It happened ten years ago, can we let it go now?
If Misa says she doesn't have it, then she doesn't have it.
That's good, right?
We rarely get together
Let's have a drink today.
Okay, that's it.
Come drink
How can I just let it go?
It was Kobe who created this atmosphere.
Lina, you should say it to her face.
Forget it, please
Rina
Can you stop now?
What?
Stop pretending to be a good person
Playing the victim
Let's change places
It's really uncomfortable to have her around.
Terrible
Is it fun to ruin a class reunion?
-Hello
- Let's go, Reina
-Change the place to have a drink
- Let's go
I agree with drinking happily
But let me tell you one thing
I have never liked Esaka-san in my life.
Kobe classmate
I'm sorry I didn't believe you.
I…
I just...
When I was in high school, I just kept asking everyone
What did I do?
What did I do to make people hate me?
But I can't ask
Because I think it must be my own fault
But now
I just want to praise myself in high school
I don't hang out with people like you.
Obviously I can't do anything by myself
They only unite to attack others
I'm really glad I'm not friends with this kind of person.
Rina
I don't need you
I don't need friends who hurt others and don't care
People who build their happiness on the suffering of others
Not a friend
So I don't need you
Because I believe in my future life
I can make as many friends as I want.
Why?
Why do you always show up?
Although I'm not a stalker nor a rich kid
But at least I can hold an umbrella for you.
I think it suits you very well
That dress just now
Don't look at me like that.
I know I went too far.
What did you do that was too much?
You are here
Welcome home, I want some tea.
Is roasted tea okay?
Don't be like an old man
yes
morning
I have something to tell you
Let's break up
"Huh" what?
Do you have another woman?
She called me.
I have collected the evidence.
Is this marriage fraud?
Or ruin the marriage?
It's all right. Just remember to prepare a generous compensation.
I don't need you to worry.
Actually, I wanted to let you have some free time.
But I found one
There are many men who are much better than you.
So bye.
sorry
Subtitle translation: Peng Minghan