Cheers!
I'm so glad the Shine Muscat daifuku
went over well.
Thank you for your help, Yuto.
Sure.
And with you as section chief,
everyone can speak their mind,
so morale is way up.
-I'm happy to hear that.
-And--
More importantly...
That's not what really matters.
Ms. Kanbe, how are you holding up?
Huh?
What is it with that stupid bitch?
She just waltzes in,
acting like some kind of pregnant virgin,
and then in front of everyone,
announces that she's gonna steal
her best friend's boyfriend and marry him!
I was beyond pissed!
I was this close to knocking her out!
Calm down, Miku.
But seriously... I can't believe
she'd do something so terrible.
You don't need to
put on a smile just for us.
If you need to vent,
we're here to listen, okay?
Yeah.
You invited me out
because you were worried?
Oh, thank you for your concern.
-Oh, not at all.
-Not at all.
I...
feel...
fantastic!
-Huh?
What?
I have no complaints at all.
I've never felt so relieved
in my entire life!
After all, I dumped my total scumbag
of a husband onto my horrible friend.
It doesn't get any better
than this, right?
That's the spirit, Ms. Kanbe.
-Yay!
So true. No other way to put it.
Another beer, please!
-Two?
-Me too, please!
-Me too.
-Bring three beers!
-Okay.
This looks amazing!
Eat up!
-We have tomatoes too.
-I want some!
-With salt.
-Oh, salt!
Sorry for the wait.
It's happy hour,
so please drink as much as you'd like.
-Thank you!
Oh, you're new, right?
My husband works you pretty hard,
doesn't he?
Not at all. He treats me very well.
Here's some of our special ramen,
on the house.
-Wow, thank you!
Here, Ms. Kanbe.
-The meat is ready.
-Thanks!
One more place! Let's go!
Ms. Kanbe, you've had enough to drink.
It's raining, so let's call it a night.
Nah, it's just sprinkling. We're good!
Today, we get to drink all we want!
Yeah! Let's go all the way!
I'm free!
Meat, meat, meat. Meat!
Come on, Reina, keep eating.
Thank you, Mother,
but I've already had enough--
What are you saying?
You'll need some meat
on those bones to have healthy children.
Fish, eggs, vegetables.
I'm home.
Tomo, welcome home.
-Welcome home.
Today, we're having
Matsuzaka beef sukiyaki!
Sit, sit. Over here. Hurry, hurry!
SALE
USA BEEF
Sit, sit. Hurry, hurry.
I have something important
to tell you two.
What do you have to tell us?
I had your fortune read
by a famous fortune teller.
He said if you don't have your wedding
within the year,
your baby will become sick.
Within the year?
Isn't that really sudden?
First of all, you two are doing
everything out of order.
You'd better hold the wedding as soon
as possible before you start showing.
Otherwise, you'll embarrass yourselves
in front of the guests.
As for the venue...
It has to be
where your father and I got married.
Only Fugaen will do!
Look.
See?
Excuse me, Mother,
nowadays, this kind of tacky...
I mean, traditional wedding venues
are no longer in fashion, you know?
What do you mean?
I'm thinking of having
a relaxing wedding ceremony
while vacationing with Tomoya in Hawaii.
Wouldn't that be lovely?
A bright white sandy beach,
a beautiful church, and a sunset cruise.
A vacation? Don't be ridiculous!
This isn't some kind of game.
A wedding is...
an important occasion
to show all of our relatives
that you're a proper woman worthy
of marrying into the Hirano family.
That kind of naive thinking
simply won't do!
Wouldn't a Christmas Eve ceremony
be lovely?
Right, Tomo?
Well, sure.
Mother, it's a little late for Christmas
Eve reservations, don't you think?
I've already booked it.
What?
The person in charge of the venue
is one of my insurance clients.
They just happened to have
a single cancellation.
Wouldn't it be bad luck
to have a wedding ceremony
in a time slot that had a cancellation?
It's fine.
I had the fortune teller look into it.
Apparently, this was meant to be.
So don't worry.
The gifts, the food, and the dress,
I'll pick out the very best.
Just. For. You.
Sorry. I'm getting a call from work.
-Oh?
-Hello. Oh, yes.
Right here, in my stomach...
I have a baby.
Tomoya and I are getting married.
MISA KANBE
LUCKY LOAN
DECLINE - ANSWER
YOUR PAYMENT IS PAST DUE
PLEASE MAKE YOUR PAYMENT IMMEDIATELY
Come on.
What the hell...
I got carried away.
WEDDING
What should I do now?
DIRECTOR SUZUKI
Sorry.
My sister invited me,
and I was going to drop by
once I wrapped things up at work.
No, don't worry about it.
Sounds like you had quite a bit to drink.
Did you make it home okay?
Yes. I'm home now.
You're drunk, aren't you?
-I'm not drunk.
-You're drunk.
No, I'm not...
Yeah, I'm drunk.
I'm very drunk.
Did you have fun?
Yes. I had the best time.
I'm glad to hear that.
If you were there,
it would've been even more fun.
Did you say something?
You are...
Huh?
No...
Well, I guess I'll let you go.
Um...
tomorrow...
do you have some time?
We could get some monaka and hojicha...
Sure! I have... some time.
Then...
see you tomorrow.
Good night.
Have Ms. Esaka or Mr. Hirano
contacted you since then?
Tomoya's been calling me every day.
But I don't respond.
There's been no news from Reina.
I see.
I just hope nothing else happens
from here on.
Well, never mind.
I think Reina's lying about her pregnancy.
You're probably right.
What are you going to do now?
Now?
Do you have anything
you want to do in life?
Yes.
I have a whole list of things
I want to do, one by one.
LIKED BY MISA_0816
CHRISTMAS DECORATIONS ARE UP EARLY!
Welcome.
Hello.
We truly appreciate your help
with the event the other day.
Oh, no, it's my pleasure.
It's lovely.
It's still a bit early though.
Can I go take a look for a bit?
Go ahead.
To tell you the truth, I'm really relieved
that Ms. Kanbe and Hirano broke up.
She didn't look happy with him.
Do you still have feelings for Ms. Kanbe?
I really regretted not saying
anything to her
when she said she was getting married.
Ever since high school...
I had plenty of chances
to tell her how I felt.
I was angry with myself for not doing it.
What about you?
You have feelings for her, don't you?
I...
have some things I need to take care of.
-Hey--
-Well, then.
What is it?
Nothing. I mean...
If you still have some time...
Excuse me! Sorry. I'm sorry.
Come on! What are you doing?
Sorry. Sorry. Please get out of the way!
Let me through!
Huh?
This brings back memories.
You used to come here too, right?
Yes. It's my first time back
since I was a student.
Me too.
So, how many years has it been?
At least...
Twenty years.
Yeah! Time really flies, doesn't it?
-Wait...
-It's been ten years.
About ten years.
Right? You surprised me.
Why don't we go to the library?
Sure.
I never made any friends
all the way through college.
I was alone too.
You too?
I'm not very good at socializing.
Then you can't say anything about me.
In class and the cafeteria,
I was always by myself.
Me too.
What a lonely school life.
It really was.
There was one meal
in the cafeteria that I really liked.
It was the one thing I looked forward to.
Do you happen to be talking about...
-Mentai butter udon!
-Seriously?
-That's all I used to eat.
I also got that almost every time.
Thank you for coming here with me.
Since I heard you went to school here too,
I've wanted to come visit one more time.
Likewise. This is the nicest
day off I've had in a while.
Thanks to you,
I got to check something
off of my list today.
What was it?
Reminisce about my days as a student.
I don't think you're
old enough for that yet.
You're right.
I remember that tree.
In winter, the fruit turned yellow.
That's a daidai tree.
Even after it bears fruit,
they don't fall for two or three years,
so it's considered a lucky tree
symbolizing continuity across generations.
You really know your stuff.
That's because...
this is my lucky place.
This is a lucky spot for me too.
So, I actually did manage
to make just one friend here at school.
My father suddenly passed away,
so I went to his funeral in Toyama,
and when I came back to school...
No...
Where are you?
This pond had dried up...
Kamekichi.
...and Kamekichi was nowhere to be found.
When I couldn't find him,
I lost all of my strength.
And I felt as if there wasn't
a single good thing left in this world.
But... there was a god.
A god who saved my precious friend.
DON'T WORRY
THE TURTLE IS SAFE WITH ME
I don't know who that god was,
but what he did, saved my soul.
It made me believe that if I keep living,
good things are bound to happen.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Won't there be more good things...
from here on out?
Yes, there will.
You should do the things you want to do.
One at a time.
I want to move.
Move?
Yes. I don't need a lot of space,
but I want a place
that just fills with sunlight.
What else?
Well, I want to talk more with my friends
and to travel.
Oh, and I want to get my license.
I want to drive instead of
sitting in the passenger's seat.
You can do all of that.
You think so?
If you wish for it,
even the rain gives way to the sun.
It's strange.
Whenever I talk with you, my head
fills up with the nicest dreams.
They'll come true. I'm sure of it.
Huh?
Let's go.
Huh? No way. Hey.
Director, please wait.
You're too fast! Wait for me!
Wait, this is scary! I'm gonna fall!
Isn't it still too soon for baby clothes?
Well, they're all just so adorable!
I just know it,
it's going to be a little boy
who looks just like Tomo!
It's almost time
for the wedding dress fitting.
Oh, Mother, I really think I should
choose the dress myself.
No way! If I leave it to
a modern girl like you,
you'll have your cleavage and legs exposed
in some shameless ensemble!
I'll pick something decent.
Just. For. You.
Mom, Mom, wait!
Mom! Mom!
What are you doing?
Oh, no, it's starting to rain.
Come on, let's go.
The cold's not good for the baby!
Let's buy a belly warmer later, okay?
Your hands are so cold!
It's chilly, huh?
Yeah... it's just not the same.
I heard!
You went on a date with my brother?
No, I didn't! Did you hear that from him?
No, from Yuto.
He said you two
went to his cafe on your day off.
Who went on a date?
Ms. Kanbe and Director Suzuki.
-Huh?
-No, it wasn't really a date.
But you're a good match.
Huh?
Right?
It's fine.
You're single now.
-Go ahead and find your next love.
-Yeah!
What do you honestly think
about Director Suzuki?
Well, I...
Did you get the invitation too?
What? Reina's wedding?
-There's no way I'm going.
-No way.
I got an invitation too.
Me too.
Of course, I'm not going.
Hey, do you have it with you?
Huh? Oh, yes.
I was planning on
just tossing it in the post box.
REGRETFULLY DECLINE
MIKU SUZUKI
It's the same.
The same?
It's nothing.
I'm relieved things seem
to be going smoothly.
Huh?!
Come on,
just how nice of a person are you?
GROOM - BRIDE
TOMOYA - REINA
Hey.
Hey!
-What?
-What are we gonna do?
The venue we have booked is huge.
What if we can't fill the seats?
Tell that to my mom.
You tell her!
What's with that attitude?
You're making me do the invitations,
the seating arrangements,
and everything else!
I don't have any preferences.
Seriously?
Stop being so fussy all the time.
Excuse me?
I don't want to have a wedding
at a tacky venue in a tacky dress,
and with almost no guests!
Then, why don't we call it off?
What?
If you hate it all that much,
why don't we just call it off already?
Call off...
the wedding?
Or the marriage?!
I dunno.
You wanna come in?
Thanks. It's warm.
I'll make some tea.
Wait, you can't have caffeine
since you're pregnant.
Yeah.
Is hot milk okay?
Thanks.
What is it all of a sudden?
I never thought I'd see you again.
I'm...
thinking about calling off the wedding.
Huh?
Wait. What's going on?
Tomoya is being so cold to me.
I didn't think he was that kind of person.
I don't think he likes me much anymore.
He probably still has feelings for you.
No...
TOMOYA HIRANO
-You can take the call.
-No! That was just an alarm.
Well, you see, this is normal.
Even super lovey-dovey couples fight
when they're preparing for a wedding.
Every couple goes through
it at some point,
so maybe you're overthinking it?
Maybe it's that...
marriage blues or something?
That could be part of it too!
I knew it.
You're just so nice.
Even though I did
something so horrible to you.
Well... just forget about me.
Don't give up on being happy.
It's just...
I sent out the invitations,
but nobody's coming...
I guess I should've known.
I was a liar who fooled everyone
in high school.
And at work, I was a traitor
who stole her best friend's fiancé.
Who would want to attend the wedding
of such a horrible woman?
I guess...
I should just call off
the marriage already.
Wait!
Reina, calm down.
Huh?
It's just... a lot's happened between us,
but look, we've known
each other for so long,
so I'll do what I can to help.
I'll try contacting everyone at work
and Tanabe and Mita and the others again.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah!
I can't move on from this
if it ends on a bad note.
I was upset at the time,
but now I'm happy to wish
you and Tomoya all the best!
Misa...
Misa, you really are Misa after all.
I know I don't deserve it,
but will you do me a favor?
Yes, leave it to me!
The wedding speech.
What?
Sure.
Looks like she's still worth using.
If you say so, that's fine,
but Ms. Kanbe, are you really
sure you want to go?
Okay. See you at the office, then.
Hey, why didn't you reserve
the movie tickets online?
Sorry, sorry, I didn't realize
it was that popular of an anime.
But I got us seats for the evening show.
Okay.
Mommy?
Let's go eat some parfaits.
What on earth are you thinking, Ms. Kanbe?
Why are we going to that woman's wedding?
Yes, I know, but let me explain
the details tomorrow at the office. Okay?
See you then.
So far, I've secured
Ms. Sumiyoshi and Miku.
Why do I have to...
TOMOYA HIRANO
THINK I WANNA CALL OFF THE MARRIAGE
CAN WE MEET JUST ONCE?
We meet again at last.
What's going on?
Just like I wrote,
I'll tell Reina and my mom...
that I just can't get married
while lying to myself.
Marriage is forever, after all.
You remember this place, right?
Since the day I proposed,
my feelings haven't changed.
I know I've hurt you a lot,
but I always have and always will love y--
Lame.
What?
What are you going to do about your kid?
I'll... pay child support or whateve--
You have zero savings and
you're 20 million yen in the hole, right?
Who's going to pay?
Me again?
Or your mommy?
I'll...
pay on my own or whatever...
Have you ever done anything
on your own in your entire life?
When you broke
your classmate's leg back in school,
or when you stole someone's bike,
your mom always cleaned up
after you, didn't she?
How do you know about those--
I'm not your mom,
and I've wasted enough of my life
cleaning up your messes.
What's your relationship
with the director?
I saw you.
-You were...
-What business is it of yours?
Who your ex is with or what she's doing.
Misa, you...
-you're the only one for me!
-Then I'll say this clearly.
I am 200 million percent sure...
that we will never get back together.
For once in your life...
how about you take responsibility
for what you've done?
A restaurant delivery service?
To ensure reliable delivery,
we would very much like
to partner with your company.
Is there any demand for it?
Demand is set to grow exponentially.
And with your help,
we are confident that together we can
pioneer this new market
and achieve success.
Well, if you say so, I'll think about it.
Thank you.
The wedding ceremony, huh?
Did something happen?
No, I'm okay.
Wow, you look great!
I thought you might show up in
a white wedding dress.
I wouldn't do something like that.
Are you really okay?
I'm fine.
Oh, thank you all so much
for coming today.
I bear no ill will,
so please celebrate their new beginning
from the bottom of your hearts.
Thanks for the invite.
This is the kind of energy...
we need for Reina's wedding, right?
I told them those outfits
were a bad idea, but...
Hey, Kanbe...
I've been meaning to tell you this
for a long time now.
I'm really sorry...
for what we did to you back then.
-I'm sorry.
Everything you went through...
it was all our fault.
No worries, it's okay now.
The fact that you came today is enough.
Now then... let's go.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's go.
It'll be okay.
Do you, Mr. Tomoya Hirano,
vow to love this woman,
to comfort and care for her,
in sickness and in health
-for as long as you live?
-Yes, I do.
Do you, Ms. Reina Esaka,
vow to love this man,
to comfort and care for him
in sickness and in health,
for as long as you live?
Yes.
-I do.
Now, the exchange of rings.
Please lift the veil.
And now, the wedding kiss.
MISA
REINA
Now, I would like to invite
Ms. Misa Kanbe,
a close friend of the bride,
to say a few words of congratulations.
Who invited her?
Hello, everyone.
My relationship with Reina
goes back 20 years.
When I lost my mother as a second grader,
Reina found me at the park
and held my hand for as long as I needed.
I still remember the warmth of her hand.
We've been best friends ever since.
Reina always stayed by my side.
When I was sick, when I was healthy,
when I was rich, and when I was poor.
We were together so much
I barely had the time
to make any other friends.
I'm truly happy, as happy
as if it were happening to me,
that my most precious friend in the world
met a man as wonderful as Tomoya.
You often hear people say that
married couples start to resemble
each other over time,
but I think that's not quite right.
I believe we choose someone
who resembles us from the very beginning.
And as proof of that,
Reina and Tomoya are exactly alike.
I think they're a match made in heaven!
Tomoya, please be sure
to keep Reina happy.
Reina, congratulations on your marriage.
And thank you very much.
Next, I would like to invite
Mr. Masafumi Yamashita,
a close friend of the groom,
to say a few words of congratulations.
Where do you think
you're going without a coat?
It's cold.
Let's go inside somewhere.
We are fully booked. My apologies.
My apologies, we are fully booked today.
Sorry, we are fully booked today.
Thank you.
They were fully booked.
It is Christmas Eve after all.
Let's go.
Where?
My house. It's close by.
I can at least make you some hot hojicha.
It's a bit of a mess, but please come in.
Thank you.
Oh, please sit wherever you like.
Director, I see you have a pet turtle.
That's...
Huh?
Kamekichi?
There's no way.
You're right.
It's Kamekichi.
You're the one...
who saved him back then?
Because he was your precious friend.
Why...
Why didn't you say anything
about something so important?
Director...
you're... my god?
Oh, that's right.
Would you mind opening the curtains?
Go ahead.
Did you do the decorations?
Every year, the landlady
helps me put all this up.
I can't help but laugh
when I imagine you decorating the tree.
That's all I could hope for.
As long as you're laughing.
Shall I make a Christmas cake?
You can even bake cakes?
Well, I've never baked one before.
Aren't you...
going to kiss me?
Reina, congratulations on your marriage.
And thank you very much.
Please just help me out a bit.
We're supposed to go
to my parents' this afternoon.
Hey, why don't I call Misa?
I'll get her to help.
Cut it out already.
Misa is the most useful
at times like these.
The number you have dialed is not in use.
Please check the number and try again.
MISA KANBE HAS LEFT
FOLLOWING
KANBE MISA
Hello.
MIKU.SUZUKI
GOING SHOPPING FOR COUNTDOWN PARTY!
How about sea bream carpaccio?
What? Hell yeah!
-Really? You like carpaccio?
-I love it!
Then let's get a lemon.
I'll get it.
-Here.
-And a carrot.
-I'll do my best to make carpaccio then.
-Yes, please.
-Carpaccio. I'm hungry.
-Are you really?
-Roast beef.
-Roast beef?
-You're going to make it?
-Yes, I am.
That's amazing.
-Ms. Kanbe likes roast beef too.
-Oh, really?
Good! Then we'll stuff ourselves
and drink our fill!
-Let's drink!
-Yeah.
I'm so happy
we get to eat your cooking here too.
I'll do my best.
Yes. I'm excited.
-Sorry for the wait.
-Welcome back!
-We bought a ton!
-Wasn't it cold out?
-Miku, please make some hot tea.
-All right.
Oh, that karaage looks delicious!
Would you mind taste-testing it?
Oh, can I?
Hey, are you really sure?
You do realize
he's using his position as the CEO's son
to go after every woman in the office,
from new hires all the way up the chain?
That Noble Son has no shame!
Seriously, that guy, he'll go for anyone.
So just the thought of you getting
caught up with a creep like that...
Oh, you're so cute together.
Oh, Reina!
I'm leaving now. Sit there.
Oh, why?
They need me right now.
So, by all means, sit there.
-Get in.
-Huh? I'm fine in the back.
It's fine, let's go!
Reina? What are you doing this weekend?
So, Tomoya, where do you want to go?
I want to go see it with you!
You're so vocal today.
Like a new member of a theater troupe.
But Tomoya, your virtual currency thing
is going well, isn't it?
As long as we're together,
I'll live anywhere.
I'm sure you'll meet
someone wonderful eventually.
I'm sure you'll find someone
you can trust too, Reina.
Don't worry yourself so much over me.
Find someone nice.
I'm actually meeting up
with Tomoya tonight.
Just tonight.
Just once before you get married...
let's do something bad.
He told me that what happened
with you was a mistake.
I think I'm going to forgive him too.
I'll even forgive you too.
Tomoya and I are getting married.
Reina, congratulations on your marriage.
And thank you very much.
For picking up the trash...
...I threw away.
...I threw away?
Excuse me.
Would you mind getting the tea leaves?
Oh, where?
I think they're in the shelf
underneath Kamekichi.
Okay.
Kamekichi, I'm just going
to grab some tea.
Which one, green tea or hojicha?
-Anything's fine.
-Okay.