=Nothing But You=
=Episode 22=
(Sorry, I Screwed Up)
You didn't
come back last night...
You didn't pick up your phone.
I am... asking you a question.
So rude.
Let me... cook something... for you.
(Liang You'an)
(I shouldn't have said that.)
(I don't mean it.)
(The user has blocked your message.)
(Contacts)
(Liang You'an)
Hello?
(We are all sober now.)
(We are safe. Don't worry.)
(We can play in the tournament.)
(East China Pegasus Club)
(asked us to register now.)
Then do it.
Do you have to report
every trivial matter to me?
You're not a kid.
Do I have to hold your hands
and bring you there now?
(What the heck?)
(I thought)
(you'd be happy to hear that.)
(I even fought to be the first one
to tell you the news.)
(I don't need that attitude from you.)
Sorry.
You did earn that qualification yourself.
I'm happy for you.
Remember to bring Song Sanchuan with you.
(I called him but he didn't pick up.)
(Maybe he's still drunk.)
All right.
(Liang You'an)
(Contact Jiang Jiaojiao
for the registration.)
(It's about the tournament.)
Have some noodles.
You...
Put less. It's salty.
What did I say?
Serve you right.
I only cooked two bowls of...
(New Media Influencers Monthly Ranking)
Among all couples,
you are not among the top 20
most subscribed streamers.
Individually, you're not among
the top 30.
Liang Tao is only slightly better.
All thanks to the energy drink stream earlier.
It's not that bad, Ms. Kiki.
After the tennis stream,
we had a sudden boost of followers.
It's not necessarily a good thing.
You gain a lot of visibility
but without more content
to retain the audience,
they will drop you like a hot potato.
Look.
Your followers are decreasing.
Wake up already.
Did you make the energy drink go viral
or was it the other way round?
Their company has released
more products
and they got the internet users' attention.
No one remembers you now.
But Ms. Kiki,
everyone is copying us.
They market themselves
as an athletic couple.
That's the internet for you.
People copy trends.
I want you to be more
creative and innovative.
Act first. Do something.
Or you'll just
be forgotten and turn obsolete.
Is that what you want?
Liang Tao, your nose
and your round face
can be improved upon.
Do you want to tweak them a bit?
No.
I quite like my face.
Don't rule it out just yet.
Consult a plastic surgeon first.
Your face is your money-maker.
Liang Tao.
Breakfast is ready.
Coming.
I have asked around, Liang Tao.
For an influencer with tons
of followers like you,
you can easily earn
30 to 40 thousand yuan per month.
But you only
give me 2,000 yuan for the monthly expenditure.
Where did the rest go?
Those influencers
either do shady endorsements
or drink and party with rich businessmen.
I manage my account with integrity.
If I'm lucky, I can get 10,000 yuan.
If I do poorly, they will deduct my pay.
10,000 yuan is pretty good.
Where are your savings?
I spent them all.
I have to buy costumes and props
and everything else.
I want you to give me your money
so that I can look after it.
It's not to misappropriate it.
You are a woman.
You need your own savings
to be independent.
Otherwise, when you get married,
you will suffer.
Look at me.
I'm the cautionary tale.
Do you not get it?
You know,
back then,
many men tried to date me.
I don't know what got into me
and I picked a loser to be my husband.
You know
what's the real thing?
Be independent.
Once you're independent,
you won't be taken advantage of by men.
Do you hear me?
Why can't you
do better?
Liang You'an and her mother
will look down on you.
Mom, enough already.
You either complain
about dad or make me feel bad
about myself.
You're not the only victim here.
Yes, it's a miserable life.
Why live it?
Darn it.
Why are you barefooted?
It has nothing to do with you.
Your boyfriend bullied you?
No.
I left my parent's place
to get some air.
You fought with them?
Parents, they mean well.
But gosh, they are annoying sometimes.
Don't take them too seriously.
Why are you playing here?
You were expelled?
Hell no.
I am the top seed of my club.
They will never kick me out
even if they are going bankrupt.
Besides,
we just took part in a tournament
and we won.
Well,
the club did go bankrupt.
So Liang You'an and you
lost your job then?
No way.
The club was disbanded
but the group isn't.
After playing tennis for many years,
I finally know
what teamwork means.
Although it's challenging
to find a practice venue every day,
everyone is in it together.
We are very motivated.
Jiaojiao.
We can't play now.
They asked for an extension.
Check the chat group where else we can go.
Okay.
I have heard about low-budget companies
but this is my first time seeing
a low-budget club.
I feel bad for you.
Bye.
Go look for your tennis court now.
Go fix your slippers too.
You're sick again?
I caught a cold.
The cold medicine
is on the cupboard.
Don't forget to take it.
We need to stock up on cold medicine.
All right?
Do you hear me?
Yes.
No touchy touchy.
I don't need your help.
Why are you drawing now?
Grinding the ink, laying a draft,
drawing, seeking inspiration...
I couldn't draw many prawns
this morning.
Just one would take me 30 minutes.
Time flew by just like that.
Living alone
is boring you?
You know what
my neighbors were doing
when I was drawing prawns?
The lucky ones drove their grandkids to school.
Some have to look after
their children
and their husbands.
And the worst is Miss Wang.
Whose son refuses to work
and leeches off her.
Get up.
Stop it.
I'm not in the mood.
Don't nap in the afternoon.
Otherwise, you'll wake up at night.
Are you trying to gaze at the moon?
I sleep and eat whenever I want.
No one can stop me.
Yes, you were dumped.
That doesn't mean
you can lie in the bed for three days.
Are you trying to hatch an egg?
If not, get up.
I don't care.
(Tennis 4EVER)
(I shouldn't have said that.
I don't mean it.)
You never liked drawing.
What?
My prawn was all alone
so you drew it a companion.
Why?
You're seeing someone now?
Ever since your previous relationship failed,
we have never talked about
this kind of thing again.
For years,
I told you
to focus on your career
instead of your love life.
But you never told me if you
ever looked for another boyfriend.
Mom.
I have a question.
Do you want me
to remain single forever?
Or do you not
mean it seriously?
I was sick
and I had to be operated on.
You were so worried that it would
affect my pregnancy rate.
Isn't it great to be single?
When you're single,
your work, your life, your friends,
they are your business.
No one can judge you
as long as you're happy.
If you have a significant other,
he will meddle with everything.
At first,
everyone might get along with each other.
But when cracks show up,
you will have so much to lose.
You're pessimistic
because of your subjective experience.
There are healthy relationships too.
One where both parties
help each other become better.
Maybe the relationship will not last.
We take a part of each other
and we split up.
But we still come out the better person.
Give me an example then.
Do you know someone like that?
That short moment of bliss
might turn into a long period of grief.
Think about your previous relationship.
What did you get in the end?
A school leaving certificate.
(Ancong Wig Shop)
Keep it on the tab.
♪With my back against the crowd♪
♪I return to my quiet world♪
Why are you smoking?
You're an athlete.
Chuan, she's your girlfriend?
♪All fiery passions♪
♪Are put out by reality♪
♪At the end of regrets♪
Sorry.
That day...
I quit sports.
♪Casting away everything else♪
(Closed, Welcome)
♪How lucky must I be to be with you♪
♪Picking up the pieces
and moving forward together♪
Your cigarettes.
Don't ask me to run errands anymore.
♪Afraid of being unworthy
of the ups and downs along the way♪
♪Can you not leave
without saying goodbye?♪
♪I can't sleep well, even in my dreams♪
Song Sanchuan is ghosting me.
Is he?
But you told me
last night you...
It was a mistake.
I shouldn't have done it with him.
It hurt him so much.
And now,
he blocked me.
He even quit sports.
Wait. I don't get it.
It went sour so quickly.
He blocked you now?
I was trying to wait
until it died down.
So I told him
that last night,
we were drunk, intoxicated.
I told him it was a normal thing between adults,
and that he shouldn't take it seriously.
What the heck?
Why did you tell him that?
You're not a playgirl.
You even rejected Nate,
who you liked.
Why did you say those hurtful things?
Why are you so toxic?
I don't know.
I don't know why.
I was...
It was a lapse of judgment.
Everything just came out of my mouth.
And when I realized the mistake,
I already said
what I shouldn't have said.
Liang You'an, you're a coward.
Do you know
what your problem is?
You come up with tons of explanations
so that you can tell yourself that you
don't have feelings for him.
But
you and he took this leap of faith.
I am happy for you.
You are just brainwashed
by the love-phobic doctrine.
Remember the dark cabin
you told me?
It won't consume you.
You're not
going to die right away
when you enter it.
You know what
you should tell yourself now?
You should tell yourself
that there is another cabin.
When you go inside,
lights will be turned on.
Oh, I should have come inside sooner!
Why didn't I?
Do you see it?
We are friends for many years.
I can claim to be your confidant.
In the past six months,
you have changed a lot.
You rebelled against Jiang Jie.
You threw away the good position
you were offered.
From last year
you would have never imagined that you
would do this this year.
Because I met Song Sanchuan this year.
See?
You know better than anyone else
who made you change that much.
So why resist it?
Stop shouting at me.
I was born this way.
Liang Tao.
How many times
have we had this talk?
Have you looked at your own analytics?
Do you not feel desperate?
You have no followers.
No views.
You didn't do anything new.
I asked you to get a microsurgery
and you said no.
Fine,
give me the result
that can prove your worth.
I did release more videos.
I made sure I talked about
interesting topics and that the quality is good.
Tell me now then.
All the popular videos you have.
The swimming center one,
the energy drink one,
and the Japanese restaurant one.
Which one pulled in more views
because the video quality
was amazing?
None.
Daring is your image.
Give me something out of the box.
Anything.
I don't care how
innocent of a girl
you are off camera.
But when the camera is on,
you will be
the daring girl you are.
I signed you
because you are willing to take risks.
Not because you're good at editing.
Do I make myself clear?
Here, for you.
Are you sure?
What?
No need to play dumb.
I saw
Ms. Kiki and you just now.
I am not playing dumb.
It's consensual anyway.
What?
You know she's married.
You know very well
what you're doing here.
That's only one way to see it.
I'm not ambitious like you.
I don't want to have a breakthrough
on my own.
If I can please Ms. Kiki,
I will receive more investments.
And my career will be smoother.
You are frank.
In that case,
why pretend to be my boyfriend on stream?
I didn't expect
sanctimony from you.
You want to be popular
but you are not willing to grovel.
You think shooting a video with a pretty face
is enough to make you go viral?
I don't need a lecture
from someone who takes shortcuts.
Liang Tao.
It's fine if you sneer
at my choice now.
But after two years,
you might not be more successful
than I am.
Sorry then.
I'm on my period today
so we can't shoot.
Have fun.
The ball bounces back
when you hit it to the ground.
It does this over again and again.
I find solace in the mundane.
But you are a streamer.
You want followers and views.
Are they worth it?
You have been hanging out way too long
with people like him.
I signed you
because you are willing to take risks.
Not because you're good at editing.
Do I make myself clear?
It's fine if you sneer
at my choice now.
But after two years,
you might not be more successful
than I am.
Is it too much to ask you
to buy something for me?
You won't spend
several hundred yuan for me.
Liang Tao and you
are the same. Stingy.
(No Smoking)
Here.
What are you doing?
One of us definitely killed
the other in our previous life.
I killed you, of course.
I don't usually play this.
It was just to change things up.
Shouldn’t you be streaming now?
Aren't you supposed
to flirt with your fake boyfriend?
So nosy.
You don't look like someone
who visits a cheap internet cafe either.
I don't want to go home.
Me too.
That's something we have in common.
Have you eaten?
My treat.
Let's go.
Come. Try it.
I mean how serious can it be?
You're old enough to be independent
even though your parents are getting
a divorce.
I'm just mad.
I have a selfish father.
I asked around.
He sold the tennis club
for no reason at all.
All he cares about
is his career.
Can you blame him though?
He needs to feed you.
If you're not financially independent,
you lose your grounds for argument.
You were born
with a silver spoon in your mouth.
So you find
minor inconveniences unbearable.
I was born to a modest family.
Every day I wake up,
it's a 80-20.
80% of the time, the day sucks.
20% of the time, it's a good day.
If it's a bad day, I suck it up.
If it's a good day, I enjoy it.
I don't buy it.
You have fallen out
with your fake boyfriend.
So you're here to run away from reality.
But it's not a bad thing per se.
Come.
Cheers.
You're one step closer
to seeing through the world.
Come.
That reminds me.
I should do something about it.
(No more couple stream.
This account will cease getting updates.)
Wow.
You're very determined.
You have done it.
Now I have to teach my dad a lesson too.
I hope we can come to an agreement today.
Will you sign this divorce agreement or not?
I don't get it.
Why do you want a divorce?
I want to stop pretending.
You say all women want a man
who can work and look after a family.
It's almost impossible to find one.
But you did it.
Or at least, you act like one.
Unfortunately, my acting skill
is not as good as yours.
So let's call it quits.
I don't want
to spend the rest of my life
in this pretense.
I agree.
Dad.
You always say
that I give up easily.
I got an offer letter
but refused to study abroad.
I'm here to tell you why.
It was because I knew back then
that if I left home,
this family would collapse.
Do you think
I am an idiot
who knows nothing?
Mom was on anti-depressants.
I know that.
I thought by staying here,
I could keep this family together.
Apparently, I just wasted
several years of Miss Chen here.
Dad.
Sign it.
Mom has had enough with you.
(Divorce Agreement)
(Ancong Wig Shop)
An, what's the matter?
You fought with Chuan again?
(Ancong Wig Shop)
I don't care about him.
Mr. An.
I ran away from home.
Can I crash at your place
for a few days?
What happened?
She said
that I was born with a silver spoon
in my mouth.
So I have got to suffer a bit
to balance things up.
She also said
without financial independence,
you lost your grounds for argument.
So I get it now.
I will start
training very hard tomorrow.
I'll prove it to her
on the tennis court.
And you.
Are you quitting for real?
We drank that day for nothing then.
Liang You'an coddled that prick for nothing.
Honestly, what happened after drinking?
How did you two argue?
Stop scratching your head.
Answer me.
Sleep on the couch.
Well...
The tournament is around the corner.
You'll be the captain.
I won't go.
Wait.
Why me?
You're the captain.
How can you ditch
such an important tournament?
You skipped
all the recent training as well.
Do you know?
Liang You'an
has been working tirelessly.
She keeps looking for funding.
For practice venues.
All so that we can train
before the tournament.
Have you eaten?
I'll cook something for you.
Come.
Stop dodging
my question now.
Sit.
Think about it.
Even though the points
will all go to Pegasus,
the victory is still ours.
This is your first serious tournament
after you made the switch from
badminton to tennis.
Are you going to give up like that?
I have been playing tennis for years.
Before Liang You'an came,
I had never thought
that I would ever bring any result.
But look at us now.
Even Chen Zhe
wants to practice seriously now
and get the gold medal.
Don't take our fighting spirit for granted.
Why drop out?
Look.
You don't know what happened
between us.
I...
I don't know who crossed who first.
And frankly, I don't care.
But Song Sanchuan,
if you give up on a tournament
because you are in a bad mood,
then don't blame anyone
when we all look down on you.
I have made up my mind.
In this tournament,
I plan to get a gold medal in Group B.
At your level,
you can strive to get a medal
in lower brackets.
We trained so hard
for this day.
Think about it.
Go to sleep.
I'm talking to you.
Do you hear me?
Jiaojiao.
Mr. An.
Have a good rest here.
Are you hungry?
No.
Let me cook you a bowl of noodles.
I...
Is this family
hard of hearing?
Or is there a problem
with my enunciation?
One, two, three.
Did I slur?
(Ancong Wig Shop)
Wake up.
It's late.
Coach Yan said
that today, we would do some sprinting practice.
Stop bothering me.
I'm sleeping.
Hurry up.
There is no practice venue in the city.
We have to take the bus to the outskirt.
Don't just sit there.
Stop bothering me.
I said, I'm sleeping.
Rot in there.
Here.
This is the place.
Ms. Liang.
It's such a secluded place.
How did you find it?
The tennis courts in the city
are always booked.
The tournament is about to begin
so I try to stick to our training schedule.
Bear with me, guys.
And all the best.
Okay.
This is tough.
Where is Sanchuan?
He's skipping again?
He won't listen to me.
What is wrong with him?
Is he forfeiting the match then?
Get changed now.
Then do ten laps around the tennis court.
Why are you standing here?
Where is Jiaojiao?
He isn't awake?
Have you looked at the time?
He already left.
I...
He is absurd.
He has never been this eager
to train before.
He didn't even tell me.
Oops. Sorry.
Sorry.
Watch what you are watering.
My hand slipped.
Where are you going?
You want to know where we practice?
Tell me now.
Will you come with me or not?
No! No!
I already said no.
Stop asking.
I shouldn't have asked you,
Song Sanchuan.
Just let me win for once.
Oh my gosh.
Enticed?
You can still make it if you run now.
No, you.
You go.
♪If we don't talk about worldly logic♪
♪If we let our feelings go
and not escape them♪
♪Should we continue
on the path ahead of us?♪
♪If all logic and sense♪
♪Point to you in the end♪
♪How determined do we need to be?♪
♪For you to believe it too?♪
♪We always think about♪
♪What we should do♪
♪To avoid mistakes♪
♪It's too rare♪
♪For us to practice caution♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪When I'm by your side♪
♪I can forget about the entire world♪
♪Everything's fine. I'm here for you♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪I wish to go into your heart♪
♪Not afraid of standing
at the same spot♪
♪You're always there when I look back♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪I wish to go into your heart♪
♪I dare to forsake the entire world♪
♪Everything's fine. I'm here for you♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪I wish to go into your heart♪
♪Not afraid of standing
at the same spot♪
♪You're always there when I look back♪
♪With you♪
♪I will become that person♪
♪The person who can act bravely for you♪
♪The person who protects you♪
♪I will become that person♪
♪Smiling while walking toward you♪
♪Not afraid of the storm and rain♪
♪Because♪
♪It's nothing but you♪