=Nothing But You=
=Episode 6=
(Can you buy me a cup of coffee?)
Okay, I admit.
I did want others to notice
something about our relationship.
We were not
in the same department,
the same office,
or even in the scope
of the office's no-dating policy.
How is it a problem?
Besides, don't you girls
like the sense of security
that comes with making
the relationship public?
Wait.
Since when we were exclusive?
I don't recall us
being in a relationship yet.
For now,
but you know
I'm pursuing you.
There's no need to hide it.
I don't like the feeling
of being marked.
I'll make myself clear today.
I reject your pursuit.
Singapore's hot weather
is not suitable for me.
I'm certainly not going there.
So you don't need to consider me
as a potential partner,
whether for dating or marriage.
We're not a good match.
If there's anything
I need to do better,
I can change myself
to your liking.
You don't have to say
these out of fit.
I thought you were mature.
I am mature.
I am a 32-year-old woman
who is independent in my personal life
and capable of handling things
on my own in my professional life.
I have a clear understanding
of myself.
So when someone I don't like
expresses interest in me,
it's a burden
and troublesome matter to me.
I'd rather
have zero emotional intelligence
and reject them outright
than deal with any complications.
Additionally,
you have indeed done well in your career
for the past two years.
From convincing me to quit my job
to
the various arrangements
you've made between us,
you have a conspicuous air
of superiority
that you think
I'll happily accept.
Unfortunately,
I'll have to say no.
My maturity has allowed me
to see through things
and things I don't like.
I hope
I made myself clear.
Crystal clear.
Simply put,
it's hard to satisfy
older women.
When the man is excellent,
she wants to be on an equal footing
than depending on him.
When the man is incompetent,
she doesn't want to associate with him.
I'm curious to know
for a woman like you,
who doesn't like to be marked,
what kind
of partner would you
ultimately end up with?
What is it, kid?
What are you looking at?
Just looking
at what a repulsive person looks like.
So I'd stay away from people like these.
What did you say?
Do you know me?
I'm craving coffee.
Can you buy me a cup of coffee?
Sure, get whatever you want.
Do you know me?
What do you want to drink?
Jin Yi is upstairs.
I'll have two iced Americanos.
What about you?
Four iced Americanos.
One of them with extra ice.
Thank you.
Okay.
That will be a total of 72 yuan.
Please wait a moment.
Was that guy your colleague?
Were you rejecting him?
It's not good to eavesdrop
on other people's conversations.
Why did Jin Yi suddenly come today?
What is it?
Just be prepared.
He's looking for trouble again.
He even dragged me along.
This is the racket.
German made.
It has officially been discontinued.
It's the brand and model
I've been using all along.
Are you using the same one too?
Yes, besides us two,
the other four team members
also use
this model.
The coach counted the inventory
and there is still
about 20 left.
I've been using this racket
since I turned pro
and have never used any other brand.
I'm not used
to using other brands.
How long does it usually take you
to wear out a racket?
It depends on the intensity
of the training.
Wearing two or three rackets a week
is common.
During the game,
I usually bring five rackets.
You used two to three in a week?
Yes.
Is there a problem?
No problem.
I can make some arrangements.
We will use
all our resources
to help you collect
the remaining rackets,
giving you priority to use them.
Priority?
I think they should be exclusively
for my use, no matter what.
Do you have any objections?
You can have them all.
But the problem
is the discontinued racket
will eventually run out.
What will you do then?
Retire on the spot?
That depends on her ability.
If she can find
around ten or eight thousand,
that will be enough
for me to use until I retire.
Okay.
You can leave that racket here
for us to refer to.
Sure, no problem.
I'll wait for your news then.
Song Sanchuan,
why don't you stay for a while?
Young Space also
manufactures
its badminton rackets.
From materials to technology,
they're not inferior to foreign brands.
Didn't you say
there are other players on your team
also using this racket?
Why don't you pick
a replacement option?
That's a good idea.
Matching defective products
with a substitute player.
You should thank my sponsor
for being generous.
Yoyo, send Jin Yi downstairs
and call for an e-hailing taxi for him.
Okay, Ms. Liang.
I want a private car.
Young Space
has its own product line.
Over the past few years, Mr. Jiang Jie
has been trying to establish the company
as a professional in the field.
So our R&D department
has developed many products
for professional athletes to use.
Basically, rackets are divided
into offensive at the top
and defensive types at the bottom.
Previously, you used
an offensive round-headed racket.
Am I right?
You can try these few ones on top.
We use
the latest nickel-titanium alloy fiber
as our material.
But our technical department
made a bold attempt
this time.
It feels a bit heavier
than the average offensive racket.
It puts a little pressure on the hand.
We studied the mainstream trend
of the evolution of racket types
over the past few years,
which is to reduce the weight
of the racket.
But pursuing weight reduction blindly
may not be a good thing.
Sometimes,
too much technological innovation
will reduce the requirements
for the physical fitness of the athlete.
The racket
you're holding now
requires athletes
to have higher upper limb skills
and strength.
In other words,
it's more rigorous
and refined training.
It's not as easy
as it sounds.
There are harder ones.
As for the sweet spot,
we have reduced its size
within a reasonable range.
Expanding the sweet spot
may make hitting
the shuttlecock appears easier,
but the best technique
will always be hitting the bull's eye.
Our technical director believes
that whoever can break
through this comfort zone,
this racket
will become a powerful tool.
So are you saying
I can put this racket to good use?
Young Space chose Jin Yi,
but I still want to choose you.
You know what my psychology issues are.
I'm about to retire.
Do you really want to retire?
Then why are you submitting
your retirement application
while donating money to the hospital?
Aren't you also hoping
that perhaps by helping
one more person
or maybe this is the day
or this once,
you would recover?
Am I right?
Of course,
sometimes treatment
for the psychological disorder
is very mysterious.
Maybe you can go
and ask for a talisman, burn incense,
and find a master to change your name.
Don't call yourself
Song Sanchuan anymore.
Call yourself Song Eighteen.
How about this?
When you go home tomorrow,
stay home and copy the number eighteen
a hundred times
and post it all over your house.
You can look at them every day.
Stimulating therapy
can be very effective.
Do you think
what you're saying makes sense?
Song Sanchuan,
hold on to this racket
and train with it for two months.
Win against Jin Yi
at the championship in two months.
You can do it.
What if I really beat him?
Will you admit that you messed up
in choosing people for the job?
If you beat him,
promise me that you'll sign
with Young Space.
I'll have two potential underdogs
inside and outside.
I don't lose anything.
I almost believed what you said.
It's hard for a merchant to change, huh?
I'm not going to practice.
You can give me a new one.
Mr. Jie,
I've reserved a private room
under Ms. Liang for two people.
Do you want me to tell Mr. Zhang
to wait for you nearby?
No need.
You both can go back after this.
Okay.
I've picked a necklace
as the gift within the budget
of 20,000 yuan you've required.
Don't get reimbursement
from the company.
I'll pay for it personally.
Okay.
Are you okay lately?
What about me?
Did you try
to pursue Nate
because you wanted to go to Singapore
but were rejected by him?
That was a bad sight.
Did he tell you that?
No, it wasn't him.
But the whole company is spreading it.
It looks like his way of doing things.
Nipping it in the bud
before it becomes a problem for himself.
I'll get going then.
You can go home now.
Okay.
(Young Space chose Jin Yi,)
(but I still want to choose you.)
(Win against Jin Yi)
(at the championship in two months.)
(You can do it.)
Is it that nice to touch?
You've been staring at this sweet spot
for half an hour.
Do you want to switch to this racket?
The string tension is clearly lighter.
It's heavier
and the sweet spot is smaller.
If I use it,
all physical abilities and techniques
must be adjusted accordingly.
It's different from the one
you used to like.
It's challenging to switch.
But I think
you can handle it.
Why?
(Y-SPACE)
Isn't this the Young Space logo?
I can probably guess
who gave it to you.
But let's not talk
about the racket's durability yet.
The person will definitely work.
Stop trying
to imply something.
I'm talking about this racket,
not the person.
I meant you'll definitely work it out.
Who were you thinking about?
Don't touch my racket.
Who are you meeting?
Just mind your own business.
How can someone like him exist?
He turned the tables on me,
saying I clung to him
because I wanted to go to Singapore.
Now
even my boss knows about it.
Today,
he was clearly judging me
not to think
about transferring elsewhere
to the point everyone knew about it.
It was as if he mistreated me.
Listen.
I'm being serious here.
Compared to Nate,
even Chen Yiyang looks decent now.
I feel sick
to my stomach
as if I've eaten a fly.
When it comes to relationships,
it's more important to choose someone
with good character.
At least,
he won't maliciously attack you
when the relationship ended.
My head hurts at the thought of it.
I feel ashamed
of my fleeting thought
of wanting to have
a child with him.
I am deeply ashamed.
That's unnecessary.
You were forced into it
by circumstances.
Tomorrow.
I'll finish this job tomorrow.
I made good money this time.
I'll treat you to a night out
and we'll get drunk
(and forget about everything.)
Okay, let's get drunk.
You go ahead and do your work first.
See you.
This guy is so unbelievable.
Where did you come from?
I came to eat.
I saw you
busy making gestures
over the phone from a distance.
I wanted to listen
to what you were talking about.
But
I was afraid of being accused
of eavesdropping.
So, I waited
until you finished your call
before coming over.
It's not good for a kid
to bear grudges too.
Thank you.
Here's your wonton.
Please enjoy.
I've already canceled
my qualifications
as a private car driver.
I'm also
going to stop working
other odd jobs either.
I'm going to train hard
for the next two months.
Do you have enough
new rackets?
Yes.
Thank you.
Why are you suddenly being so polite?
It's making me uncomfortable.
I've been thanking you
since I met you.
Most of the memories
about another person
in the mind are warm.
Actually, I'm not used to it either.
Mister!
I'll order one for you.
Give me a bowl of wonton.
Thank you
for sending me home.
Seesaw.
Are you brave enough to play?
What's scary about it?
Wait!
Wait! Hold it!
Who plays see-saw like this?
We're turning in a different direction.
Slow down! Not too fast.
Please!
Slow down! You're going too fast.
Hold on tight.
Here we go!
♪Should I continue
on this path before me♪
♪If all logic and emotion♪
♪Ultimately lead me
to the answer of you♪
This is more comfortable.
♪Only with you, can I trust♪
Why do you swing so high?
I'm the king of swings
in the neighborhood.
♪To not make a mistake♪
♪So cautiously♪
Hold on tight.
Here we go.
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪I'm by your side♪
♪I dare to leave the whole world behind♪
♪It's okay to listen to you,
as long as I have you♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪I want to enter your heart♪
♪Even if I stand still, I'm not afraid♪
♪Every time I look back, I have you♪
♪I will become that person♪
♪The brave one who can fight for you♪
♪The one who will protect you♪
♪I will become that person♪
♪With a smile, I will walk toward you♪
♪Saying I'm not afraid
of the wind and rain♪
♪It's just love♪
These are the all racket
we could find
that Jin Yi uses.
There's still one more box in Thailand.
How many do we have here?
Sixty-two.
Production has been slowing down
since they stopped making them.
We put a lot of effort
to get these here.
We still have to persuade him
to use our rackets.
If he gets good results
and gets more exposure,
he'll definitely
our products.
Let's put these into the box.
Okay.
Hello, Ms. Chen.
Yes.
Sure, I'll go and see you
at the law firm.
I'll see you later.
Did the boss's wife want to see you?
Chen Ke
wants to have lunch with me.
How about
you pack up all these rackets first?
When I come back,
I'll send these rackets with you
to the badminton team.
Aren't you taking me along?
(Enjoy Wealth)
According to your needs,
this plan is very suitable for you.
You can change
the list of the insured individual
at any time.
This way,
you don't need
to create
a separate account for your son.
I will look into the details later.
Okay.
Thank you, Zhang.
You're welcome.
Excuse me, Ms. Liang is here.
I'll get going, then.
Call me if you need anything.
Okay.
You'an,
thank you for coming.
Sorry to call you out
when your lunch time is limited.
It's okay. I'm not that busy today.
The food is served.
I won't take too much of your time.
I happened to shop around in the area
and saw a set of skin care products.
Take it and try it out.
But this is
too expensive.
You must have spent a fortune on this.
Not at all, you're being modest.
You work overtime every day
and often stay up late.
Consider this as compensation.
All right, I'll take it.
Thank you, Ke.
Last night,
he came home pretty late.
He was out socializing again.
Thank you.
Yes, he has a private dinner yesterday.
Mr. Zhang and I went with him.
But he took a taxi home.
Ke,
Mr. Jie did meet a client
to express his thanks.
Think about it.
Since Mr. Zhang and I
went there with him,
it's definitely
his schedule is definitely transparent.
I'm just having a casual chat with you.
Don't be too nervous.
Eat something.
Okay.
You don't have to reimburse
from the company.
I'll pay for it personally.
Consider it my gratitude
to Alex.
Do you need a ride home?
Okay, thank you.
Okay.
To Linglong Mansion.
By the way,
you suggested last time
that Mr. Jie should go
and watch Jiao Jiao's game.
I thought about it.
If it's on a Saturday,
Mr. Jie should be able to make it.
After all, every Saturday afternoon
is your family day.
If Mr. Jie has something urgent,
he'll definitely reschedule.
Next time, you can let me know
in advance.
I'll make sure
to keep Mr. Jie's schedule open.
It doesn't matter.
We can talk about it later.
Anyway,
I'm actually quite glad
that
you're his executive assistant.
(Shenzhen Xinyi Sports Training Base)
Is this all the rackets?
It's just enough
for this year's tournament.
We have a lot of Young Space rackets.
If you have time,
you can come and pick some out.
I remember when I signed the contract,
rackets were excluded, right?
Yes.
But as a long-term partner,
you'll definitely endorse
our entire product line in the future.
Why not take advantage
of this objective condition?
I'd still suggest you
choose
our rackets first.
Song Sanchuan,
these are your rackets.
Please sign here.
This box is from Young Space.
Song Sanchuan chose
this one last time.
Please check.
It's your latest material
and technology?
These look crude.
Are you trying to give up?
Would you dare to have a match with me
during the tournament
two months from now?
Why are you trying to show off?
I'm not scared of you.
Okay.
Don't chicken out and do anything funny.
I'll ask the coach
to let us be in the same group.
We'll watch and see.
(Shenzhen Xinyi Sports Training Base)
♪The scorching sun♪
♪The cicadas are too noisy♪
♪Fate, don't be so cliché♪
♪Say it and do it♪
♪Breaking through
countless obstacles is great♪
♪You say it's still early♪
♪Listen carefully to tomorrow♪
♪No matter how small it is♪
♪We have a goal♪
♪Hot-blooded fools are the code♪
♪Going against the crowd♪
♪You smile at me♪
♪The pride in my heart♪
♪Just one hug away♪
♪I hear the heartbeat, still burning♪
♪I define my own world,
it's good this way♪
♪How many twists and turns are there?♪
♪I also want to know the feeling
of crossing infinity♪
♪I need it, I really need it♪
♪Everything makes me stubborn
and hopeless♪
♪This test of youth♪
♪Our unique answers,
keep them safe and sound♪
♪Seeing the heartbeat still shining♪
This forehand
was impeccable!
Stop watching
and help your mom serve the dishes.
All you do is talk
without lifting a finger.
You're right.
It's because you make the money.
That's the logic, isn't it?
No problem, Mr. Jiang.
I'll go and get some work done, okay?
I'll get my assistant
to register for a course
for you
to learn how to speak with manners.
I guess you won't be able to live
without your assistant.
You can even find a bottle opener.
You're the mighty boss,
how come you can't find
the bottle opener?
You can't take care of yourself.
What else can you do?
Say that again.
Enough you two.
This is the only day
we get to eat together.
Can't we have
a more pleasant atmosphere?
Besides,
my cooking isn't that bad.
You don't need
to spray your saliva on it
as you bicker.
Mom, let me help you out.
Dad,
your three ways of pleasing mom
are so fake.
First, the fake hug.
Second, picking food for her.
Third, paying with your credit card.
If mom isn't tired of it, but I am.
Do you even know what it is to support
each other without any romance
when you don't have a girlfriend?
Even food can't keep you from talking.
I had lunch with Liang You'an
the other day.
She told me
the progress
of the Underdog project
is going smoothly.
Yes,
it's easier with her keeping
an eye on things.
(Chen Zhe)
Do you want to come out? I'll pick you up.
I'm done eating.
Mom, Dad, I have plans.
So I'm going out for a bit.
Must you go out today?
I'm giving you guys
some alone time together.
See how considerate I am of you.
Mom, I need to use your car.
This place is not bad.
The card was definitely worth it.
No matter how great it is,
I'm the only one accompanying you.
A good meal is worth the wait.
What's the rush?
Hello.
Do you want to play games?
Sure.
Come.
Take a seat.
Please scoot over.
What are we playing?
Shake the dice.
Losers will drink the beer.
I'm good at this game.
Are you pretending not to know me?
What a tacky pickup line.
No WeChat, no phone number.
A meeting like this must be fate.
Let's have fun tonight.
See how clear-headed she is.
Come on, let's drink.
What do you want to drink?
Anything is fine.
It's harder to get drunk
on expensive drinks.
Bring out your full set
of Dragon God Champagne.
Okay.
Here.
Let's open it.
Wait a minute.
Can you help me take a video, please?
Sure.
Hello...
Sorry.
But can you move a bit?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Let's do it again.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Tao, your only Tao.
Today,
I'm going to show you
the legendary Dragon God Champagne set.
Do you really not recognize me?
I didn't recognize you.
But I do recognize your watch.
I find you
very interesting.
You really think highly
of yourself.
I'm not like
the girls
you met here.
I'm here to develop my career.
I have no interest in people.
Don't think too much.
I'm even less interested in you.
That's perfect.
A second-generation rich kid
is not worth my time.
Please excuse me.
(Hello, everyone.)
(I'm Tao, your only Tao.)
(Today,)
(I'm going to show you)
(the legendary
Dragon God Champagne set.)
What is she doing?
She never does anything decent all day.
(So let's keep the momentum going.)
(Which flavor)
(do you like to drink?)
(Liang Shu)
(Hello)
An.
What do you want?
(You're the most reliable one.)
(You always have your phone with you.)
I'm having breakfast at the eatery.
You see.
I don't have enough money
to pay for breakfast.
Can you transfer some money to me?
(How much?)
I need 50 yuan.
Just 50 yuan.
(Transfer 50 yuan to Liang Shu)
Okay, done.
If there's nothing else, I'm hanging up.
I haven't talked
about the main thing yet.
(After Liang Tao resigned)
(from her previous job,)
(it's been three months ever since.)
(She still hasn't found)
(a decent job.)
(You're holding a high position
at your company, right?)
Executive Assistant to the CEO.
(Please lend a hand and arrange a job)
(for your sister there.)
Sister?
My mom only gave birth to me.
I'm the only daughter.
When did I have a sister?
(You're both)
(my daughters.)
At least find her a stable job
with insurance and housing fund.
(That would be enough for me.)
An,
can you do this
for me considering
(how I helped you before?)
Stop right there.
I can't arrange it.
What's wrong with you?
It's already bright outside.
You've had breakfast
and you're still talking in your sleep?
(National Badminton Championships)
(The match is over.)
(Song Sanchuan won.)
A score of 21-15
and 21-10.
Okay.
He won in straight sets.
So he won.
The match is over.
Jin Yi won.
They'll face each other
in the quarterfinals tomorrow.
Mr. Jie will also come
to watch the game tomorrow.
Remember to arrange his schedule.
Okay.
Is Jin Yi steady?
Can he beat Song Sanchuan?
I've already arranged
the media press release.
Jin Yi is the most-watched player
in this tournament.
It's not that Jin Yi
can't afford to lose.
It's that our marketing department
that can't afford to lose.
Tomorrow,
we'll have the results.
(National Badminton Championships)
(Men Singles First Match)
(Song Sanchuan 1: Jin Yi 0)
(Song Sanchuan 2: Jin Yi 0)
(National Badminton Championships)
(Song Sanchuan 14: Jin Yi 10)
Is Song Sanchuan
clueless about the situation?
Aren't they on the same team?
Mr. Jie,
they are teammates and also opponents.
Did you not inform them in advance?
Jin Yi cannot afford
to lose this match.
Mr. Jie, didn't you say
skills and mental strength
are all that matter
in a match?
We can't control
the outcome of the match, can we?
But what I can do is
have a plan and a publicity strategy
regardless of
whether Jin Yi wins or loses.
That's enough talking.
What I want is results.
There must be
no mistakes in this match.
Keep an eye on the situation here.
I'm leaving now.
Okay.
Please send the boss off.
(Song Sanchuan 17: Jin Yi 12)
(Song Sanchuan 18: Jin Yi 12)
(Song Sanchuan 18: Jin Yi 14)
(Song Sanchuan 18: Jin Yi 16)
(Song Sanchuan 18: Jin Yi 17)
(I don't want to play anymore.)
(It's pointless.)
(You've always been the benchmark)
(of my youth training team.)
(But I didn't expect you)
(to end up like this.)
(Stop trying to act tough!)
(If you're really capable,)
(why did Liang You'an sign me)
(instead of you?)
(My highest record
in the past two years)
(was 21 consecutive losses.)
(At that time, there was only)
(one thing on my mind.)
(That I'm absolutely a piece of trash.)
(Why am I still standing here?)
(Song Sanchuan.)
(She said your team had a hidden gem.)
She was talking about you, right?
(Aren't you also hoping)
(that maybe this is the day)
(or this once)
(when you would recover?)
Young Space chose Jin Yi,
but I still want to choose you.
Win against Jin Yi with dignity.
You can definitely do it.
(Song Sanchuan 18: Jin Yi 18)
♪If we don't talk about worldly logic♪
♪If we let our feelings go
and not escape them♪
♪Should we continue
on the path ahead of us?♪
♪If all logic and sense♪
♪Point to you in the end♪
♪How determined do we need to be?♪
♪For you to believe it too?♪
♪We always think about♪
♪What we should do♪
♪To avoid mistakes♪
♪It's too rare♪
♪For us to practice caution♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪When I'm by your side♪
♪I can forget about the entire world♪
♪Everything's fine. I'm here for you♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪I wish to go into your heart♪
♪Not afraid of standing
at the same spot♪
♪You're always there when I look back♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪I wish to go into your heart♪
♪I dare to forsake the entire world♪
♪Everything's fine. I'm here for you♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪I wish to go into your heart♪
♪Not afraid of standing
at the same spot♪
♪You're always there when I look back♪
♪With you♪
♪I will become that person♪
♪The person who can act bravely for you♪
♪The person who protects you♪
♪I will become that person♪
♪Smiling while walking toward you♪
♪Not afraid of the storm and rain♪
♪Because♪
♪It's nothing but you♪