I am thirty-two years old.
I worked for six years straight
at the same company.
It's a pretty stable job.
My net income after tax
should be up to your expectations.
This house was rented under my name.
It's a one-bedroom apartment.
It's about 70 square metres.
Don't want kids? I am fine with it.
Been single for more than five years.
Please consider me
as a top priority.
Don't get me wrong though,
I did say
I do not plan to have children,
but I am very fond of them.
Eel-san is smiling at me.
It likes me.
You like me, don't you?
It's not Eel-san,
it's Ilsa.
Il-sa.
Sha.
Sa. Don't bother. It's fine.
Dear Ilsa
will be one year old soon.
I can't bring myself to give her away.
Yet my daughter
is gravely allergic to dog fur.
I really can't keep it around anymore.
I just wanted to be sure that
whoever adopts her
is someone stable, reliable
and caring.
That's me you're describing.
I took some time to make this for Ilsa.
It's a schedule.
Have a look.
(A day with Liang You'an and Eel-san)
Wake up and get ready at 6:30.
Morning workout at 7:00.
(yoyo)
Bring Ilsa along.
It's alright, go ahead and take it.
Sorry for that.
Don't worry about it.
Yoyo, what day is it today?
Yes, today falls on a weekend.
If there's anything,
talk to me on Monday, alright?
I'm hanging up.
(Eddie)
I'll have to take this.
Be right back.
Mr. Eddie.
Right. No problem.
I'll send it to your email right away.
Yes.
Yes, bye.
Just a minute, please.
I just need to send an email.
I'll be done right away.
Yoyo,
I have sent the file to
Mr. Eddie.
Have a look on his behalf.
I'm really sorry.
Hello. Mr. Jie.
Yes, alright
Please confirm that with Mr. Eddie.
What is your take on having a life?
What does life
mean to you?
(Life.)
(The one taking control of my life)
(has never been me.)
(As a director's executive assistant,)
(Blue flag)
(from filtering work priorities)
(Materials for Mr. Jiang's use only)
(to clearing away minor inconveniences,)
(To-do list)
(I spent all my energy on becoming)
(the loyal shadow of my boss.)
(Gold medal employee - Liang You'an)
(365 days a year,)
(24 hours a day, always on standby.)
(There's no time off for me really.)
(I don't want to do this anymore.)
(Every day, for just 15 minutes maybe,)
(I really wanted to catch a break.)
So I truly, genuinely
wanted to have a dog.
In your application form,
and I was particularly moved by this,
you said that you longed to
get home and open the door
to find someone
welcoming you home.
Yet looking at you now, I guess
you won't have the time even for that.
=Nothing But You=
=Episode 1=
(Hi, Liang You'an)
(Hi, Song Sanchuan)
(Liang You'an,)
(I thought we were going
to have dinner together?)
(Why are you standing me up again?)
Well you see
the marathon is tomorrow.
My boss called for a last-minute meeting
and I have to monitor it on his behalf.
(SPACE)
(You are so dedicated,)
(if I were the boss,)
(I won't be able to leave your side.)
Hold that thought.
After tomorrow's event,
I will apply for a transfer.
No one can stop me.
(Right.)
Ms. You'an,
Mr. Eddie is waiting in the office.
Right.
(Weren't you about to)
(adopt Eel-san today?)
Eel-san thinks I'm too busy working,
so they said, "next please".
But that's okay.
Wait till I get transferred,
I'll apply for adoption again,
and I will succeed this time.
Mr. Jie,
let me talk you through
what's in our contestant goodie bag.
Sure.
Inside the bag,
there will be a pair of
our sports shapewear
that will be featured next season,
a box of energy capsules
and Young Space's
online reload gift card.
This comes up to 300 yuan in total.
The more noteworthy thing is
this hairband.
Our business team
secured this collaboration
with a luxury brand.
This is great.
We must pay attention
to what female consumers
are saying on social media.
Good morning, boss.
Ms. You'an,
something came up.
We'll deal with it later.
(The 5th Shenzhen Intercity Cup
Women's Half Marathon)
(Y-Space Sports)
(Bank of Shenxing, Cool Move)
(The 5th Shenzhen Intercity Cup
Women's Half Marathon)
(Young and moving gives Space for excellence)
(The 5th Shenzhen Intercity Cup
Women's Half Marathon)
Mr. Jie,
it is Bank of Shenxing's president,
Mr. Wang's birthday today.
The one speaking to him
is Smarter Finance's vice president,
appointed externally yesterday,
Mr. Xu Yan.
Mr. Wang,
happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Mr. Xu.
Congratulations.
Mr. Jiang, you're late today.
No problem.
So what happened?
Look,
seated in the middle
is the presenting sponsor Bank of Shenxing.
(Xie Ru, Wang Xicheng)
Nothing wrong with that.
However as the event's main sponsor,
shouldn't we be seated closer to the middle
than Smarter?
(Smarter Finance - Xu Yan
Y-Space Sports - Jiang Jie)
What's up with these placements?
I wonder too.
By the time I came over,
they were already here.
I don't know if they coordinated this.
Change it back.
Can we do that?
The president Mr. Xu even
sat there just now.
That doesn't matter.
Everyone should be properly seated.
In the official group photo later,
our boss
should be seated at his deserving place.
(Smarter Finance - Xu Yan
Y-Space Sports - Jiang Jie)
I'm off to see the pacers.
Watch over this like a hawk.
If the boss asks about anything,
call me anytime.
Do not use WeChat.
I won't be able to hear you.
Alright, Ms. You'an.
Mr. Wang,
let's not stand around.
Let's sit down and chat.
- Sure, sure.
- Have a seat.
Come, sit.
This marathon
that we organised
would require everyone to
work closely together.
Yes.
This is great.
The official pacers for the race
are all in another tent.
Over here are Young Space's
(Relaxation area)
sponsored pacers.
Ms. You'an, I have to say,
your criteria for the selection
set the bar so high.
It's the women's marathon,
and you got them male pacers.
They all look so good.
Who wouldn't be going after them?
Only I have to wear this?
Why?
You could choose not to,
but you can't be the closing pacer then.
What does being the closing pacer
have to do with wearing this?
The wage of a normal pacer is 3,000,
the wage of a closing pacer is 5,000.
Look,
I'll give you a minute to decide
whether you'll put this on.
Running's what we need to do,
why do I need to put this on?
If your face is that important,
then I guess money isn't.
Liu,
- Ms. You'an.
- I'll take care of it.
Alright.
The time carried on everyone's back
is pre-arranged.
Once the gun goes off,
all the contestants will,
according to their running speed,
pick the right pacer for themselves.
The three-hour mark
marathon closing pacer
will decide the number of
finishers for the whole marathon.
An important role.
I guess this bow
isn't really appropriate.
This is an oversight on our part.
This is much better, right?
All pacers,
please head over and get ready.
Thanks.
Hold on.
Don't move.
Stay still.
Okay!
Liu.
Ms. You'an.
What's the matter, Ms. You'an?
Everyone who is providing services
for the event today
represents Young Space.
To service others politely and sincerely
are just the basics.
Whether they earn 3,000
or 5,000,
they made it through their efforts
and will be paid by our company.
Do not think that such money,
or even just a banana
from the supply station,
should you take charge of it,
entitles you
to disrespect others.
Yes, I understand, Ms. You'an.
Go get busy.
(The 5th Shenzhen Intercity Cup
Women's Half Marathon)
The contestants have set off.
The first echelon is
expected to reach
Qianhai 1st Road in ten minutes.
Photographers in position,
get ready to capture shots
of contestants appearing alongside
Young Space's advertisement board.
Thank you.
Hello, Mr. Eddie,
I'll let you take charge of the OB van.
I'm going over to the
5 km stop supply station.
Mr. Jie wants
the airtime of Young Space advertisements
during the marathon live broadcast
to be a total of
not less than 10%.
Alright, good job.
(Half marathon)
They are here.
(Bank of Shenxing - timing point)
Place the cups further apart
for easy access.
Pinch the lip of the cup together
so that the runners can take
little sips along the way.
Thank you.
Good job.
Mr. Jiang,
the few leading runners so far
are all Smarter Finances'
sponsored contestants.
How many did Mr. Jiang bet on this time?
Just three this time.
I heard that you betted on a dozen.
Your tactics are really to
spend huge capital here.
Regardless of the tactics used,
landing bets on the champion
is what really matters.
It's competitive sport,
and that's how cruel it is.
When the winners are decided,
let's see which of us
Tier 1 sponsors
can present the award
to our sponsored contestants.
(You're almost there, go on.)
Hey handsome, let me add you on WeChat.
I'll scan you.
Hey handsome,
if we keep up with you,
we are sure to finish this race, right?
You finish by running, not talking.
So if we run alongside you
up to the finishing line,
will you let us add you?
Alright,
keep up then if you can.
How great it is to be young.
- Let's run!
- Yes!
Mr. Eddie,
I'm at the first supply station now,
our drinking water
and energy drinks
are being consumed faster than expected.
Please ask our marketing colleagues to
hurry up and send more over.
Alright.
- I'll go to the other stops
- Come on!
- and check on them.
- Go on!
Go on!
Come on! Come on!
- Come on!
- Hello Mr. Jie.
Liang You'an,
can those three runners make it?
Press on.
Mr. Jie,
- this is like horse betting,
- Come on!
- it's all about luck.
Let's just wait and see?
Didn't I approve
a budget for five?
Why did we only bet on three?
The money saved
was used to hire male pacers.
Alright, got it.
- That's great! You're doing well!
- Right!
Come on!
We're on our way to the next supply station now.
Go on, good job!
(Isn't he the closing pacer?)
Faster, faster!
(Why is he ahead of his progress?)
Go on!
Run, run!
Come on!
So we meet again, handsome.
Fate brought us here.
You won't outrun us.
We're all marathon lovers,
let's run together.
I'm a pacer, I'm not...
We haven't added each other!
♪Under the hot sun♪
♪Cicadas are buzzing♪
♪Fate can be written afresh♪
♪We walk the talk♪
♪We wish to consistently rise up
to all challenges♪
♪You said it's still too early♪
♪But listen up for tomorrow♪
♪No matter how small♪
♪The goals that we have♪
♪The trick is to be an enthusiastic fool♪
♪Going against the crowd♪
♪You smiled at me ♪
♪With pride coming from your heart♪
♪We need a hug to make it perfect♪
♪I hear my heart beating, bursting with life♪
♪I will define my world♪
♪This would do♪
♪How we would subvert our fate♪
♪How does it feel like
traveling through infinity♪
♪ I need to know, very much indeed ♪
♪How all this could fuel my determination♪
Mr. Xu,
it seems that
our Young Space has
good luck.
Just like that,
we got into the top three.
Oh, that,
all three were chosen by my EA.
She has quite the eye, right?
Congratulations, Mr. Jiang.
Next up, we invite the vice president of
Young Space Group, Mr. Jiang Jie
to give away awards to the contestants.
Round of applause, please.
(The 5th Shenzhen Intercity Cup
Women's Half Marathon)
(Half Marathon - Women - First Place)
(Weibo Trending
Marathon, Building jump-off)
(Female in Young Space sportswear
suspected to jump off a building)
(Shenzhen Hotspot
Marathon venue with suicide victim)
(Mr. Jie,)
(I'm heading to the scene.)
(I've contacted the PR team.)
(Once I get a hold of the situation,)
(I'll take action to manage)
(the negative public opinion.)
(Alright.)
(Report the progress to me in real-time.)
It's a mannequin.
After the contestants passed by,
it fell from the third floor.
Luckily no one was hurt.
The trouble now is,
it is dressed in
Young Space's clothes.
The police were here just now.
It was a false alarm.
Isn't that obvious?
If it wasn't done to hurt others,
it was done to cause a nuisance.
Public opinion is spreading rapidly,
this must have been planned beforehand.
(Liang You'an)
(I don't care at what cost,)
(resolve this immediately.)
(Got it.)
Hello,
(Sponsor - Liang You'an)
I am the sponsor of this marathon,
Young Space Group's representative.
I would like to rent this space,
including this space over here.
How much is the rental fee?
(Due to poor placement,)
(our advertising mannequin
fell onto the marathon route,)
(and caused public panic.)
(Fortunately, no one was hurt)
(or suffered from financial losses.)
(Young Space will take serious measures
to rectify this oversight.)
(We are truly sorry.)
Mr. Jie,
the statement has been sent out from
our official channel.
The public sentiment is settling down.
Our explanation
still holds some credibility.
You must not let your guard down.
This incident will not go away easily.
Our statement addresses the public,
but you still have to find out
where did that mannequin come from.
I applied for access to
the surveillance footage.
As soon as I find something,
I will let you know.
I'm heading back to the marathon venue
to see things wrapped up.
Alright, Mr. Jie.
(Ms. You'an, are you back here yet?)
(We need your help in handling something.)
Alright, I'm coming.
Sir, could you drive faster please?
Hurry up.
(Y-Space)
Have you gotten everything?
Yes.
Ms. You'an,
he asked me for the money,
but I didn't give it to him,
for he didn't follow his running time
as the closing pacer.
That makes his wages
deductible by 2,000 yuan.
I'll take over,
you can go now.
I'm here for the money.
It's true though,
I didn't follow my time.
If you want to deduct my pay,
I have nothing to say.
Take it.
It's been a long day for everyone.
Don't want to make this day
more difficult.
Why?
I wish more than anyone
that today will go well.
I'm not looking forward to seeing
other unexpected incidents happen.
Wait a minute.
Have a sip.
Your lips are cracking.
Thanks.
(Sponsor - Liang You'an)
Thank you.
Hello?
I'm done over here.
I'm coming over.
Don't panic. It's nothing.
Don't worry.
(Weibo Text- Y-Space)
(Apology Statement)
Le, don't worry.
Your mother will be here soon
to pick you up.
Sir, I'm sorry that you
have to wait for me.
I'll be right back.
Sorry, miss.
I have kept you waiting.
No problem.
We're used to it.
(Shenzhen International English School)
Say goodbye to Ms. Sammy.
Goodbye.
Sorry that you have to get off work late.
It's alright.
Who's this little baby
looking so unhappy?
I brought you something.
Look!
I'll put it on for you?
You look so adorable.
Come,
later on in the car,
(EASTIE)
I'll take many nice pictures of you,
alright?
Here, sweetie.
While your mum's still at work,
let's hurry up and
have some fried chicken.
I want a drumstick.
Drumsticks can't be as good as wings!
Look, so good!
I want a drumstick!
Li Zixun likes that too.
Who is Li Zixun?
It's my kindergarten boyfriend.
Don't tell mom.
Boyfriend?
Eat up.
(WeChat message)
(Ms. You'an,)
(Mingyu)
(the big boss will be coming tomorrow.)
(Mr. Jie wants you to help Mr. Eddie)
(to prepare the presentation slides for)
(the marathon sponsorship report.)
Baby,
go ahead and eat up.
I'll watch cartoons with you after that.
Alright?
Did you put it there?
You're home.
I'm home.
Where's Luo Le?
She's in the room, sleeping.
When I called you,
I wasn't actually expecting anything.
But you did have the time.
The marathon came to an end.
This huge task was done.
I can finally apply for a transfer.
For real?
Congratulations!
Did you give my girl
fried chicken?
How come?
Both of us even went downstairs
to sort out the bones
for garbage disposal.
I even opened the window
to air out the room.
There's a smell?
There wasn't.
That's scary.
What are you?
The female version of Sherlock Holmes?
One drumstick,
324 calories.
Chicken breast, 200 calories.
Chicken wing,
224 calories.
Say,
which chicken part did you
feed my daughter?
Fine, I plead guilty.
I am simply a malicious
godmother who used fried chicken
to bring happiness to my goddaughter.
I plead guilty. I'll drink.
After this year,
I will enrol Luo Le
into a boarding school.
Wait,
did I hear you right?
You're out of your mind.
You're putting her in boarding school?
She's so young!
Look,
my job as a nutritionist
is coming into trend recently.
Artists wanting to get in shape,
managers wanting to lose weight.
When work comes,
the group that I follow
will go on for one or two months.
If she's in boarding school,
I'll be able to work with peace of mind.
I told you early on
to move to
my building.
I just happened to
see this agent's social media posting.
There are two units available now.
The price looks alright.
Take your time now to browse through.
I wanted to look for a domestic helper,
when the time comes,
I'll just pay her a bit more
to take care of both of our houses.
She can send Luo Le to school too.
Won't that be great?
Don't feel burdened.
And no boarding school.
Just listen to me.
I've never told you this before,
but the reason I was able to go through
divorce with such determination,
half of that courage,
I got it from you.
Alright.
I think it over again.
I'll go and check on my kid.
Go.
(Marketing Department Entry Form
Name - Liang You'an)
An Cong, what's wrong with you?
There, there.
Quiet down.
I just finished tidying this up.
It'll be picked up later by my customer.
Get up.
I have to ask you something.
Why were you late home last night?
I was busy earning extra money.
Earning extra money?
My son,
we shouldn't be doing illegal stuff.
Just shut up already.
Who's this son of yours?
All you do is indulge in useless fantasies.
Should I really call you father,
would you dare be one?
My good son.
In what universe are there
yolkless salted duck eggs?
Where's the yolk?
My mouth was idling while I was cooking,
so I just dug into it.
An,
the tea you wanted
last week is here.
Get ready to catch.
Okay.
Thanks.
I'll transfer the money later.
There's no hurry.
Talk later.
Sure.
Here's your vinegar!
You're leaving?
Slow down!
You slow down.
Please give me a rice noodle roll.
Hui,
give me two salted duck eggs.
Get it from the cabinet yourself.
Come, have one.
That's good,
you didn't take that.
Do you have anything better to do?
Since I was 18,
this is the only trick up your sleeve.
Even dogs could do better you know?
I was just testing you.
I'm telling you,
never smoke for your line of work.
Okay?
Boss.
Come, come.
Have a seat inside.
(Ancong Wig Shop)
Hey little cutie.
All done.
Let me tell you,
you've had a successful operation,
your report readings are good,
once done with this round of chemo,
for sure you'll be able to go home.
Hey darling,
come and have a look.
Does mom look good?
Mom looks as good as
before she was sick.
She looks even better than that now.
Actually,
I shouldn't have spent this money.
If you hadn't told me that
you will give me the highest discount,
women are the worst
when it comes to discounts.
That's so accurate.
When my wife was around,
she used to say that too.
Your wife...
She left.
Oh no, no.
It's not what you think.
She left me, literally.
She walked away from me.
It wasn't a metaphor.
After she left,
it was just me and my son.
That's my son.
What was I saying?
Many people
question my principles,
they say I am profiting off sadness.
Only I know
what I am doing.
People who are sick,
most of them,
their spirits break before
their bodies do.
So you might as well
tidy up and
walk out with your head held high.
You make yourself look beautiful,
and that's what rebirth is all about.
The total is 300.
I threw in a conditioner for you.
Thank you, boss.
This money here was
placed in my drawer by some kind soul.
It might be a patient,
who happened to see that
it's just me and my daughter,
and donated this to us.
You see one's true nature
after falling sick.
Her father sees me as a burden.
I understand him leaving,
but he left his child too.
What if I pass away someday?
What would happen to her?
You will have to carry on, right?
(Women's marathon pacer recruitment)
Got your eye on any of these?
I'll give you a discount.
How much is this?
You are right.
Every day that I get from now on,
is an extra day earned.
I've got to be happy about it.
Maybe the illness won't come back.
Right on!
Here, this is 300.
200 is enough.
Save the other 100 for your child,
get her some nice food or toys.
Thank you.
Baby,
come on let's go have fun together.
Let's go.
Look at you,
you sell a wig just to lose 50 yuan.
You're the prime example of a squanderer.
Can't you see she's raising a child?
They don't have it easy.
You're right.
If she passes away,
the child will have no mother.
We don't need this 50 anyway.
Take a look at this.
Is this one of your wigs?
No.
Take a good look, is it yours?
I've said it, it's not mine.
Don't get in my way.
Although Young Space isn't
the presenting sponsor this time,
as a solid
Tier 1 sponsor,
our data shows that
we got higher exposure.
Look at our finishers' goodie bag,
the supply drinks,
and especially the bet successfully
placed on the champion,
our effective reach is
in an absolute lead.
Following that, our department
will continue to collect
statistics that are driven by
product sales.
Thanks for your hard work.
Eddie,
Mr. Jie has really trained
and honed you well
to take on big projects now.
Thank you, boss.
Gao Li,
regarding the mannequin incident,
what does the sales department
think about it?
Was it done by a rival company?
It is very likely.
I mean,
no matter which company,
out of what purpose,
Mr. Jiang's
marketing department handled it
extremely well.
It went viral out of all the chaos,
and was steadily pacified.
We got free publicity out of it.
If you were to search 'marathon' now,
all the keywords will be related to
Young Space Group.
Such publicity might not be possibly
achieved even if we spent money on it.
Thank you for the praise,  Mr. Gao.
Luckily,
the meeting attendees today
are all of our own.
Should anyone hear this,
they might think it's an act all along.
Of course not.
Everybody knows
Mr. Jiang always
takes the path less taken.
However this development
might go both ways.
I didn't think that
you would be up for it, Mr. Jiang.
Of course not.
If there is a possibility
that it will cost Young Space's image,
I'll never dare to do it.
This is me.
Timid, conservative.
All these years,
I have the president to thank
for employing me with full trust.
That's for sure.
The branding of Young Space
was built well over the years.
The marketing department led by Mr. Jie
has made the greatest contribution.
The whole company knows.
How did I come to hear then,
that this marathon,
was held together by Liang You'an?
You chose the three runners, right?
And you were still busy going around
to put out fires.
Mr. Gao,
it's all part of my job.
You're being too humble.
With your current abilities,
fulfilling the EA position
for a long time,
is a waste of talent.
I really appreciate talents,
and maybe you'd want to consider
joining our sales department.
Mr. Jiang,
everyone from our company
knows Liang You'an and
praises her for her competence.
I'd like to have her over,
you'll let me have her, won't you?
You'an is not up to the mark yet.
Maybe two more years?
She needs more training.
Mr. Gao, please go on.
We're sponsoring a marathon
to test the waters.
For the future, whether Young Space
will follow Mr. Jie's suggestion
to streamline our production
and focus on these three fields:
running, basketball, badminton,
or follow Mr. Gao's insistence
to maintain this brand for the masses,
that is still subject to discussion.
I will still say this,
it all depends on the data,
the profit sales,
and which of these two departments
can produce more convincing results.
If it weren't for the mannequin incident,
the marathon
could have ended on
the perfect note.
Yet now it feels like
a luxurious banquet spread
with the appearance of a rat.
Everyone feels disgusted
and cannot enjoy the banquet anymore.
Did you hear that just now?
The president asked
for separate proposals.
Gao Li and I
are back on equal footing again.
I'm not having this.
You'an, look into
the mannequin incident
and find out who's behind all that.
Alright, no problem.
I will do so.
The marathon is
my project,
I will see it through.
What's wrong?
Is there anything else?
Mr. Jie,
you promised me that
should I finish these four years,
I will be transferred to
the marketing department.
Do you remember that?
I mentioned it several times too,
but you were too busy
so,
I've filled out the forms on my own.
(Marketing Department Entry Form
Name - Liang You'an)
Alright, you can leave it there,
I'll sign that later.
Thank you, Mr. Jie.
What's up with your hand?
I'm fine.
Look,
the organizing committee was giving out
commemorative gold coins.
The marketing department got only one.
Mr. Jie wanted it to be given to you.
Oh and,
there's someone downstairs
who has been waiting for two hours.
Who's that?
I've never seen him.
I have no idea why he's here too.
He's just extremely good-looking.
Just handsome, that's all.
You've met him,
yet you didn't bother to pass a message?
Don't worry,
I sat him down at the
coffee bar for you.
I even bought him a coffee with my card.
You even used your own card?
I guess he really is good-looking.
Liang You'an.
♪If we don't talk about worldly logic♪
♪If we let our feelings go
and not escape them♪
♪Should we continue
on the path ahead of us?♪
♪If all logic and sense♪
♪Point to you in the end♪
♪How determined do we need to be?♪
♪For you to believe it too?♪
♪We always think about♪
♪What we should do♪
♪To avoid mistakes♪
♪It's too rare♪
♪For us to practice caution♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪When I'm by your side♪
♪I can forget about the entire world♪
♪Everything's fine. I'm here for you♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪I wish to go into your heart♪
♪Not afraid of standing
at the same spot♪
♪You're always there when I look back♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪I wish to go into your heart♪
♪I dare to forsake the entire world♪
♪Everything's fine. I'm here for you♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪I wish to go into your heart♪
♪Not afraid of standing
at the same spot♪
♪You're always there when I look back♪
♪With you♪
♪I will become that person♪
♪The person who can act bravely for you♪
♪The person who protects you♪
♪I will become that person♪
♪Smiling while walking toward you♪
♪Not afraid of the storm and rain♪
♪Because♪
♪It's nothing but you♪