=Nothing But You=
=Episode 31=
(You Had Been Crushing On Me for This Long?)
(How is he doing?)
(How long is his rehabilitation?)
It may take four to five months.
Okay, thanks for the information.
Someone should really fill in his spot.
He'll get it back after he recovers.
Okay.
(The club's official account
has gained 50,000 followers.)
(To be honest, I'm a bit nervous.)
(Many people are just here)
(because of Song Sanchuan's name.)
Right now,
I can't really post any more updates.
Do you want to consider
letting me document his rehab progress?
I won't. Make some other content.
(I don't want him to ruminate about it.)
Alright.
Help us cheer Chuan on.
(Sure.)
(Alright. Get busy then.)
Lunch?
Let's go.
Hold on,
I'm texting Jiang Jiaojiao and Chen Zhe.
Why?
Jiao said,
they want to come with us after
our meeting.
Okay, I'll take my bag.
Why are you coming when
we're just having Food Republic?
What do you want?
I have no money.
My dad thinks
my mom pays my living expenses,
my mom thinks
my dad should pay for it.
When they don't get along,
they don't care about me anymore.
Also, it's not the day where
you are paying me back yet.
I really have no money to eat.
Was it because you
lent me all your money?
It's just for these two weeks.
Can you just help me?
You're kidding me, right?
Chen Zhe, your bro over here
has no money to eat.
Why don't you treat him?
Sure! What do you want?
Go away, I'm not asking you.
What a beggar and a chooser.
I'm not kidding you.
He doesn't own
the money that he has now.
I feel guilty spending it.
I want to change too,
and I want to prove that I can.
Give me a chance.
You're really annoying.
Let me tell you,
I will note down
every single meal paid.
Okay, I know.
Please give me a tofu.
I want tofu too.
I thought you didn't like tofu?
I eat that too.
It's cheap.
I need to be thrifty.
Do you want more...
Really? Just tofu?
Tell me the truth.
How did the public account get
50,000 fans?
Jiao.
They are all real followers.
What's this new trick up your sleeve?
Spend her money, then she pays you back.
How despicable of you.
I really ran out of money.
What do you really want from her?
I recently found out
that these three people have
served as negative examples.
Jiang Jie, Chen Zhe, Huang Yike.
My dad always thought that
he can show that he cares
by buying a bag for my mom.
My mother divorced him in the end.
Well you, all you have left is
just money.
Go away!
Till now, no lady has been willing to
leave their hearts with you.
Regarding Yike,
she recently fell in love with
someone from the swimming team next door.
She applied to be a member immediately,
and spend so much money there every day.
Didn't expect that from her.
She is not single-minded at all.
I want to thank you three
for I understood that
you can't buy sincerity with money.
Peachy really despises
the fact that I've never been poor.
I want her to know that
I, Jiang Jiaojiao, can handle
hard times in life.
Peachy, wait up.
Buy me a cup of coffee.
Put it on my tab.
It's over. This is happening.
This guy really fell for her.
Thank you.
He looks good.
He's very focused on training.
There's no rush to do this.
It's going to take quite a while.
Take it easy.
It's right to use the wheelchair everyday,
especially for the first two weeks.
Apart from coming to the rehab center,
other times, don't work your leg for now.
Okay.
After another two weeks of training,
you'll know how to work it well,
then your movements will come easier.
Thank you for your hard work.
We will definitely work closely
with you on this.
Don't worry, it's our job.
I'll be in your hands.
(Your driver has arrived)
Our ride is here, let's go.
Are you tired?
- Quite.
- Must be.
I'll push myself.
It's okay.
Hello.
Are you the passenger with
the number 7551?
Yes.
Our car is equipped with this platform
to help you get in the car.
Let me help you.
It's okay, I can do it myself.
Let me just help you.
Be careful.
Why, you can be my emergency contact but
I can't take care of your knee for you?
You can, you can.
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
Careful. Don't burn yourself.
Okay. Stop staring at me.
Check out that jigsaw puzzle. Is it nice?
I bought it especially for us.
I'm done.
How's that?
It looks pretty good.
What are you doing?
Who puts a puzzle together this way?
What's wrong?
You don't know how to play with puzzles?
Ah, I've discovered that
the great Liang You'an
has something that she does not know.
Alright. I admit that
it's my first time buying a puzzle.
Let me show you.
When playing jigsaw puzzles,
you should first look for
pieces with right angles.
After pinning down the corners,
you complete the four sides.
Packs of puzzle pieces like these,
they belong to a certain area.
You look at the sample,
find the color corresponding
to the different areas,
then you put the puzzle together,
one area at a time.
Lastly, you'll come back and deal with
the leftover materials.
That sounds like a really sensible plan.
Yeah, I studied tutorials for that.
Is this really your first time?
Yes.
Where would I find the time
to do this last time?
I bought this because
I'm finally out for once.
We can really catch a break
and have a life.
That's true when you think about it.
You're usually working,
and I'm usually training.
Both of us really don't
"have a life".
Why don't
we take this opportunity
to do more things
that we've never done before?
Let's just
randomly pick a piece
out of this puzzle pile,
then,
when the puzzle is completed,
we can both put our puzzle piece of choice
back into the puzzle?
That feels quite ceremonial.
Pick one then.
Pick whichever you want.
♪Passing through♪
I've got mine.
♪The crowd with the years♪
♪Uneventful and looking forward♪
It's this for me.
♪Waiting for the stars after sunset♪
♪Pleasant dreams♪
♪Even in the dark♪
Do you think
we'll both be in the same area?
♪Life going in circles♪
Whether or not will we be in the same area,
we will definitely be in
the same picture.
♪But I've felt the wind♪
♪Let me go wild♪
♪Blow me away♪
♪Like a shooting star♪
What are you working on now?
I'm finding where to place this
over Four Seasons Cafeteria.
Look closely.
But I can't find
where the star was.
Don't do it for me.
Just stick to your area.
Let me handle this, okay?
I take care of this.
♪To meet, to let go♪
♪Tomorrow will be a good day♪
Alright.
I'm going home. Where are you going?
I'll send you home.
So I still have to pay for two
so that you can send me home?
You still have to pay for one more
return ticket too.
I was wrong, bro.
I didn't think it through that day.
When rich people are calculative,
they can really be calculative.
I want to show you through my actions
that I really like you.
If you feel that
we're not compatible, you let me know,
I'll change it all.
For real.
What's this?
You paid for my meal,
I'll buy you snacks.
I scrolled through your Moments.
I saw that you like this a lot.
So I brought you one.
It's your favorite, vanilla.
Have it.
Eat it.
What are you doing?
Don't take it out.
Take out your earbud.
♪One two three, go♪
♪In a city bursting with colors♪
I looked through your playlist.
You listened to this the most last year.
I think you must like it very much.
I don't like it actually.
I just used it to work on a funny video.
I don't care.
You have to finish listening to this.
I paid to record this for you.
Really?
One two three, go.
♪In a city bursting with colors♪
♪We dream all day, it's bright at night♪
♪The boisterous city is
filled with vibes♪
♪Without you♪
You can sing.
This song suits you pretty well.
Of course.
I only have 15 yuan left on my card.
I spent it all
just to record this song for you?
Alright, alright.
I'll take care of your lunch tomorrow.
Have one.
What are you doing?
Does it look good?
It does?
Coach.
Let's add a few more sets today.
You're in quite the state today.
Yes.
I feel the energy coursing through me
with nowhere to go.
Today,
we'll first start with hip stability.
Alright.
Try doing some supine flexion
and extension exercises.
Alright, go.
Support it with your humerus.
When you're doing this movement,
actually your iliopsoas works independently.
Let's do it slowly.
Ten more reps.
Alright, go slow.
Good.
We can now accurately assess
your tensor fasciae latae
and your rectus femoris.
You must keep your body balanced.
Come, let's go.
You'll have to work it here.
Wait.
Coach, you tickle me.
Okay.
Yeah.
I think I'm a gone case.
Why do I feel
so happy just accompanying
my boyfriend for physiotherapy?
I never thought that
I could be this lovestruck.
Am I?
What should I do then?
That's why people say you fall in love.
I am falling.
Why are you calling me?
Our public account these days,
have you looked at it?
There's something regarding Liang Tao.
Liang Tao?
(She is not a rich
second generation at all)
(She's the daughter of a mistress.)
(An illegitimate daughter of
an extramarital affair.)
You...
I asked Coach Luo
for your home address.
What's up?
Give me your mobile.
I'm not born out of wedlock.
I'm not an illegitimate daughter.
Yes.
I faked an identity,
and faked a relationship online.
I can apologize and admit my mistakes.
When I was in primary school,
I couldn't explain it all very well.
That's why I've been changing schools.
Now that this came up,
I don't think I can stay at the club.
You don't need to worry about the club.
No one will ever believe those stuff.
Come back tomorrow.
Everyone misses you.
Can you help me
sync over the account's password
and backend operations?
I'll monitor and delete those comments.
And you,
don't read what's written online.
Liang You'an is not around,
we're in a mess over there.
Don't you slack off.
Have some wafer rolls,
a happy heart will grow.
Come.
Look.
Take a bite, you'll feel right.
It's not a big deal,
it's really not.
Where did you learn these rhymes?
I learned it from Peach Academy.
It's going to be alright.
You'll never need to leave.
Never again in the future.
For you've caught the eye of
the campus heartthrob.
Which school are you from anyway?
Didn't I just tell you?
I'm from Peach Academy.
Alright.
This is for you, campus heartthrob.
Yes, ma'am.
Hello.
(Hello. Where are you?)
I'm at home.
(Let Luo Nian take over)
(the public account for now.)
Don't fire me.
What would I fire you?
Just stop posting for two days.
(Turn off the comments and shares for now.)
Let's observe how it goes for a week,
and then we'll make further plans.
I'm sorry.
I brought the club down.
What?
After all,
it's just a public account of a tennis club.
Who looks at it anyway?
What impact could that have on us?
This won't even last longer than
neighborhood gossip.
(Stop thinking about it.)
(Don't look at it.)
(Just pass it to Luo Nian.)
Jiang Jiaojiao came to see me today.
He said he'll look after the account.
That works too.
Don't stop working though.
Don't try to slack off.
You still need to produce content.
I know.
Is there anything that I can do for you?
Not really.
Thank you, You'an.
No. Thank you, Ms. Liang.
I'm hanging up.
Just listen to me. Put your legs on my lap
and straighten them.
You'll feel more comfortable.
No, no.
I'll hurt you.
Just listen to me and relax.
Don't hurt yourself.
I'm not.
It's good now. It doesn't hurt anymore.
It hurts inside but not the outside.
Why is it so painful this time?
I've never seen you
be in such pain before.
Before this,
on a lucky day,
I'll get to lie in bed for a day.
If I am catching up with work,
I'll take painkillers.
But I forgot to bring
my usual go-to pills.
It's okay. It usually hurts only on the first day.
I'll be fine tomorrow.
What if I rub your stomach for you?
Is that better?
It still hurts.
Stop, stop.
Maybe try going on your phone.
Speaking of that,
is Liang Tao's matter resolved?
Jiang Jiaojiao went to comfort her.
I feel that Liang Tao has a crush on him.
Did you feel that too?
Give me your hand.
The internet said
massaging this point helps.
I wonder if it works.
Do you feel better?
Much better.
Can I ask you,
has your
heart skipped a beat for me?
The first time,
when was it?
What kind of a crush
are we talking about?
Well,
before you fell for me,
the kind where you felt
there was a spark.
I don't want to tell you.
That won't work.
I picked a time when you're
half-conscious, yet you're not telling me still?
Tell me, tell me, tell me.
Okay, I'll tell you.
That one time
when we were swinging and playing seesaw.
You were so close to me,
my heart was just throbbing.
Wait.
Why are you so good at this?
Do you push girls
on the swing often?
What girl? Why would I...
No, I...
No.
No matter male or female,
I've only...
I've only
swung you on a swing before.
What about me?
When was the first time
you had a crush on me?
That would be...
Do you remember
there was once you asked me to stay
then you gave me a fitness test.
So early on.
No, guess it was even earlier.
Do you remember the first time
when I went to find you at your office?
At Young Space.
Then,
I shouted "Liang You'an",
then you turned around.
You had a crush on me since that day?
I still don't think it's that.
The first time when we met, during the marathon.
You were in the tent,
and then you pasted that timecode
on my back.
Your cold, soft hands.
It was love at first sight?
No, but anyway, every time
I was just so nervous when I saw you,
you know?
Are there any more?
There is.
It's that one time,
when I really fell in love with you.
That was when
you covered up the 18-18 scoreboard for me.
Since then,
anyway,
I knew definitely that
I want to pursue you.
That's what it is, you know.
Anything else?
Do you remember
when you came to my house
and asked me to eat wontons?
You said the wontons
will become lumpy soon.
I was on the first floor.
I opened the window and saw you.
Are you not in pain anymore?
I'm much better now.
Chatting works better than painkillers.
Chatting with me works better than painkillers.
Liang You'an.
(I'm out to buy breakfast.)
Where did you go?
I went to buy shampoo.
Wouldn't it be nice if you waited for me?
It's just downstairs.
I can do it on my own.
You're having a meeting soon, right?
Come over here for your breakfast.
I'll take a shower first.
Be careful.
(Nian)
The physiotherapist
has sent me the plans for his next stage recovery.
I forwarded it to your mailbox.
Take a look.
(He told us that before we leave,)
(if anything needed adjustments,)
(we can tell him anytime.)
Okay. After I've received it,
I'll print it out and
talk it over with Coach Yan.
Alright.
(How is he?)
He's well. The therapist said
he is recovering faster than expected.
That's good.
(We are also looking for ways to)
(combine tennis playing techniques)
(with the physiotherapist's plan.)
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
The shampoo fell on the floor.
(Just hang up.)
(Don't mind us.)
(Take care of the disabled.)
Yes, yes.
I'll talk to you later.
Song Sanchuan,
what are you doing in there?
I'm...
What else can I  be doing?
I'm taking a shower.
Right?
Then, are you okay?
If I'm not,
are you coming in to check on me?
That... Never mind.
You seemed all right.
(Top Smash)
Sanchuan has about another two weeks
before he comes back, right?
What do you think about it?
What do you think about
the physiotherapist's plan?
I think that the training direction seems fine.
But regarding the time,
one month?
Doesn't it seem too optimistic?
I think this specialized training
plus athletic recovery training
might need about two months.
I agree.
That means both of us have some sort of pre-judgment
to help him make adjustments.
How about this?
I will follow his framework,
and the time taken will be two months.
I'll break it down a bit more
and show you another plan.
Alright.
Good.
This...
What are you looking at?
At the plan.
Is there a plan on the back of my head?
No. It's just...
there are two white hairs.
Impossible.
What?
You have old eyes I think.
One of us has old eyes,
the other has white hair.
Quite a match, like a set meal.
Think again.
Let me tell you. In this club,
you are the oldest person here,
and the only one too.
Don't you even dare think
I am in your age category.
Who wants to be part of the set anyway?
I'm leaving.
I'm going home to draft out plans.
Bye.
Did you drive?
It's quite congested now.
Must be tiring to drive.
Let me drive.
I'll send you home.
I did drive here,
but did you drink?
When did she find out?
I hid it so well.
(Good morning, Ms. Liang)
♪Moving left and right♪
♪Cruising through the city♪
♪There's always time to meet♪
♪Moving forward and backward♪
It was very difficult to make.
It took me a long time to learn that.
You know how to make balloon flowers!
There's just one?
It took a lot of time too.
I'm terrified of balloons bursting.
It scared me good.
You're that scared?
You're done now.
Your life is being held in my hands now.
Don't, please don't.
That will burst.
Liang You'an.
Please don't.
Really, take it easy.
Wait, I gave you flowers.
Why are you like this?
Listen to me. Give it to me.
No.
Don't.
Don't do that.
The moral of the story is
don't expose your weaknesses easily.
The bad guys will take advantage of you.
You know that now?
Do you know now?
I want hugs from bad guys.
Bad guy hugs.
Wait, wait.
What's wrong?
You'll burst it.
This is the nicest flower
that I have ever received.
Done.
We can hug now.
Hugs are my favorite.
♪Moving forward and backward♪
♪I'm seeking an excuse♪
♪To catch your eyes♪
♪Our frequencies are a bit off♪
♪Sometimes we're pulling,
sometimes in slow motion♪
♪It's strange that it's just right♪
♪It's strange,
our heartbeats coincide every time♪
♪Clumsily going along
the lack of harmony♪
♪The flooding of synchronized love♪
Miss, miss I was wrong.
No, it hurts.
My legs are in pain.
It's painful.
♪ Love me♪
This time around,
you've been recovering pretty well.
Thanks to your solid foundation.
Starting now,
you won't need a wheelchair.
Good.
Before I leave this place,
would it be possible for me
to remove this?
It depends.
We'll work together on that.
I want to start training earlier.
There's no rush.
Before our rehab ends,
don't exert too much force with this leg.
You still have to use your crutch.
Did you hear that?
Don't worry.
Before your rehabilitation
is over completely,
being too impatient
will only bring harm to your
sports career in the future.
You're really good,
you hid so many balloons.
Did you change your shampoo?
You smell good.
I didn't.
I've always used this brand of shampoo.
Now I recall.
Don't worry.
Give it some time.
I've been very cooperative.
I'm sure to recover.
You will.
Look, your name brings you such luck.
Song Sanchuan.
Three horizontal strokes.
[*The shape of the word "san".]
Three vertical strokes.
[*The shape of the word "chuan".]
Your life will be good in any direction.
How nice.
What's up?
Let's play a game, shall we?
Let's play charades.
Guess what am I?
Toad.
Guess again.
Spider.
Ant.
It's an ant.
Guess what this is?
Elephant.
You are so smart.
Bunny girl.
No.
Pole dancing.
Wait, that...
That is the monkey king!
You are right!
This is the itemized bill.
It includes all the payment
for classes, for the physiotherapist,
the consultation plan,
and some consumables.
In the future,
before you return to the pitch,
our physiotherapist will go to your club
and do a professional
technical assessment for you.
The traveling expenses
is also included in this bill
This means that, after we're done
with stage four rehabilitation training,
we should contact you, right?
Yes.
Make an appointment with me
a week in advance,
and I'll make time for that go to you.
Can I have a look at that?
You can bring this bill
back with you.
So who will come with me to pay the bill?
That would be me.
Mr. Pang,
will the insurance company
cover such a high amount
of rehabilitation fee?
That would be impossible.
As far as I know,
most insurance companies only cover 30% of it.
Thanks.
Why are our things more than
when we came?
Can you check if
we left anything in the bathroom?
(If we don't bring this
bottle of shampoo,)
(it won't be that wasteful, right?)
(High-end imported shampoo - RMB289.00)
(This shampoo is so expensive!)
Alright.
Anything else?
That's all.
Okay.
This is the last of our unfinished business.
Let us bring out the last two pieces.
Mine's over here.
It's a dog.
What's yours?
Mine's a pair of slippers.
I really like this puzzle.
Every scene is so healing to me.
Yes, it is.
I feel that every scene in this puzzle
would be us in the future.
We are heading home now.
We'll go back to where we once were.
Are you ready to go and face the court?
I feel reluctant to leave this place and go,
but I really to get back to playing tennis.
♪If we don't talk about worldly logic♪
♪If we let our feelings go
and not escape them♪
♪Should we continue
on the path ahead of us?♪
♪If all logic and sense♪
♪Point to you in the end♪
♪How determined do we need to be?♪
♪For you to believe it too?♪
♪We always think about♪
♪What we should do♪
♪To avoid mistakes♪
♪It's too rare♪
♪For us to practice caution♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪When I'm by your side♪
♪I can forget about the entire world♪
♪Everything's fine. I'm here for you♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪I wish to go into your heart♪
♪Not afraid of standing
at the same spot♪
♪You're always there when I look back♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪I wish to go into your heart♪
♪I dare to forsake the entire world♪
♪Everything's fine. I'm here for you♪
♪You will be loved, you will be loved♪
♪I wish to go into your heart♪
♪Not afraid of standing
at the same spot♪
♪You're always there when I look back♪
♪With you♪
♪I will become that person♪
♪The person who can act bravely for you♪
♪The person who protects you♪
♪I will become that person♪
♪Smiling while walking toward you♪
♪Not afraid of the storm and rain♪
♪Because♪
♪It's nothing but you♪