"Fruit"
(Episode 3: Light)
You're late.
Easels?
I found a cat by the awning just now.
Could someone be secretly feeding it?
Will you keep it?
- Or will you turn it in?
- Chips!
Miss!
No, cats are too dirty.
- I'll throw it out.
- I need the restroom.
Let's get started.
Today we're drawing dark clouds.
Did everyone bring photos?
Chips!
What are you doing?
Give it back!
Miss!
Let's look over there.
Shh, Chips... keep it down.
I'll take you somewhere safe.
Guoshu.
Are you okay?
Come here.
Miss...
It's okay now.
It's okay.
You got hurt?
Take your shirt off.
Take it slow.
No need to take it all off.
Oh, okay.
Bear with it.
It hurts!
It really hurts...
I know. Bear with it.
I can't treat you like this.
Don't move.
Try moving it. See if it feels loose.
Oh.
Thank you, Miss.
At the time, she didn't say much.
Just gently buttoned up my shirt.
In that moment, I felt her warmth,
like she was quietly caring for me.
But at the time...
- I didn't dare ask what it all meant.
- Try moving.
I'll take care of Chips.
Make sure to see a doctor, check that' nothing's broken.
Then...
Chips,
you be good, okay?
I'll be going now, Miss. Thank you.