=Within The Grip=
=Episode 17=
(Have No One to Trust)
The Yunya Temple hosted
a vegetarian banquet for the donors.
I saw Gu Zhaoxi before the banquet.
I chased after him
to the back courtyard but lost my way.
When I found my way back,
I found those people gathered
around the corpse and that pouch.
These represent
our family's sincere gesture.
If you need anything,
please don't hesitate to ask.
Our family will provide full assistance.
Master Chaosheng, the banquet
is about to begin. We should head over.
(Yunya Temple)
(Zhaoxi? Why would he be here?)
Why is there a corpse?
Stop looking! Step back.
Yes, and right inside the temple.
Why is there a corpse here?
Everyone, look!
- Someone's dead!
Stop looking. Step back.
So you were supposed to be
at the temple banquet, but you ran into
someone who looked like Zhaoxi.
That was Gu Zhaoxi.
Zhaoxi was by my side the entire day.
If you didn't mistake him, perhaps
someone deliberately set this up.
(Prince Consort seeks
painters to paint plum blossoms.)
Weren't you the person who set this up?
What do you mean by that?
Wasn't it you two conspiring
to lure me into this trap to control me?
If we wanted to control you,
why would we bother with all this?
You...
You thought the assassin
you hired succeeded
until you later discovered
that Leng Yan failed.
That's why you wanted
to kill Wanniang to silence her.
I still want to help you even now.
Why don't you tell me how you came up
with the idea to hire Leng Yan?
Who told you Zhaoxi wasn't your brother?
And who introduced Physician Li to you?
I truly didn't care about your life.
But the one hiding behind
keeps stirring things up.
If you turn against each other,
he would likely be the real winner.
(Top scholar, General Shen,)
(Crown Prince Yin Zhou, the Gu family,)
(Xuanji Pavilion...
They're all involved.)
For so many years, you've managed
our shops meticulously.
Your desire to become
the family head is understandable.
But the family is one body.
What you've done is no different
from severing your own limbs.
Even if you became the family head,
could you truly secure that position?
But I am a bit curious.
Why did you come to believe
Zhaoxi isn't your brother?
No one put me up to it.
I overheard it
the day I went to report
the shops' revenue to Father.
Master, the task failed.
Physician Qin knows the Mobei terrain
extremely well and escaped.
But he said he would take the matter
of Master Zhaoxi to his grave,
not only to save our family's face,
but also to protect
his brother's last bloodline.
Was that why Xuanwu sought
to pledge his allegiance to you?
Of course not. They didn't find me.
I heard Father intended to betroth you
to Zhaoxi as Xuanji Pavilion Master.
That's when I understood
he was going to hand over
the family to an outsider.
So I went to Gu Xuanwu.
He didn't know I overheard
their talk that day.
Xuanji is away studying poisons.
Wenshuang is into martial arts.
Neither cares about the family affairs.
He knows what's good for himself.
He knew only I could help him
reclaim the Xuanji Pavilion,
so he chose to submit to me.
"Submit to you?"
By standing there useless
when you were set up?
You...
Chaosheng.
Think carefully about this.
After all, I am currently the only one
in the family who believes
that you were set up.
I'm afraid Xuanwu
has been using you from the very start.
What you overheard
was likely what he wanted you to hear.
Physician Qin knows
the Mobei terrain extremely well
and escaped.
But he said
he'd take the matter
of Master Zhaoxi to his grave,
not only to save our family's face,
but also to protect
his brother's last bloodline.
Who's there?
It's just the wind.
Don't worry.
In business, your foresight and judgment
are unmatched by any of us.
But the Xuanji Pavilion specializes in
reading secrets and minds.
Gu Xuanwu just knew
your weakness and used it.
Come out!
Guards!
Catch them!
- Yes.
I brought Physician Li because I
caught a cold after hearing some songs.
Taking him to Zhaoxi
was merely a spur-of-the-moment idea.
I needed a reason to fish
for news about that jade pendant.
Leng Yan was a famous assassin.
I didn't trust the Xuanji Pavilion,
so I went to him privately.
But since Leng Yan's failure
caused no consequences...
But Leng Yan is dead.
That wasn't my doing.
But I discovered Xuanji visited
his home after the incident
and brought Wanniang
to Nichang Workshop.
(Work Contract)
This is her work contract.
The date she arrived at the workshop
was the day after Leng Yan's murder.
She must be involved in it.
You'd already guessed
she killed Leng Yan, hadn't you?
She ordered Wanniang to do it.
That's why she brought her
to Nichang Workshop.
You only found these?
I intercepted the assassins
you sent to kill Wanniang.
No more tests, Chaosheng.
I just never expected
you'd use Xuanji Pavilion agents.
Weren't you afraid the family head
would discover this?
Thank you for your candor today.
If you remember anything else,
come to me at the Fufeng Pavilion.
It's getting late. Sleep early.
Wait.
Since you've discovered Xuanji
visited Leng Yan's home,
I guess you already suspect her.
But do you know she secretly returned
a month ago to see Zhaoxi?
Master, are you heading
to Miss Xuanji's courtyard?
Not yet.
You've long suspected her
and found evidence
linking the missing herbs to her.
But why did you shift focus
onto Master Chaosheng instead?
Why do you think the family head
drew me into this game
and let me marry Zhaoxi?
Using your marriage to solidify the ties
between the Pavilion and the Gus?
Yes,
and no.
Whether Xuanji is really
joining hands with me
or just shifting trouble onto me,
even if everything traces back to her,
who do you think the family head
would deal with first?
Her or me, the outsider in the family?
You mean he might've long sensed
disloyalty within the family?
I received that secret letter
implicating the Gu family.
Chaosheng heard those rumors
inciting against Zhaoxi.
And Wenshuang faced the same.
But I couldn't understand it.
Even with Xuanji Pavilion as leverage,
why let me hold power
with so many Gu heirs available?
Later, I owe thanks to my husband
for something he once said to me.
Instead of waiting
to judge others' intentions,
why not leave them a path to goodness?
I pondered that for a long time.
If the family head entrusted
this matter to any one of them,
it likely wouldn't end peacefully.
Precisely because I'm an outsider,
I have boundaries.
After a lifetime of bloodshed,
the family head is now fading.
He probably can't judge family affairs
by simple right or wrong.
So my priority
isn't finding the culprit,
but securing an ally
I can fully control.
Aren't Miss Xuanji and Master Wenshuang
offering an olive branch?
I need one I can completely control.
What happened?
A thief entered the master's room.
We're searching under orders.
Young Madam, see anyone suspicious?
I just saw someone
sneaking in that direction.
That's Miss Xuanji's courtyard. Go!
The night is deep and cold.
Don't keep my husband waiting.
Let's return.
Yes.
(A Heaven task?)
(How can another Heaven task appear?)
Yuluo's in danger.
I thought you'd be the one
to complete this Heaven task.
(Heaven)
But the Pavilion Master chose me.
I wish you a successful task
and safe return.
Do you truly wish for my safe return?
But rumors say the family head
will reappoint a new Pavilion Master.
You and I...
No, all three of us could
become the next Pavilion Master.
Xuan Qing.
Heaven tasks serve the Son of Heaven.
We all serve His Majesty.
No need to draw lines between us.
It's late. Sleep early.
Why did the family head assign
the Heaven task to Gu Xuanwu?
- Master.
- Is the agent sent to Jiangnan back?
Not yet.
Then depart tomorrow and go in my stead.
I know you find it hard to trust others.
But you saved my life.
I'd never betray you.
Sending me away now means you still...
You really are...
"Saved you."
But that hinges on
whether I truly saved you.
That was your first task in Xuan Unit.
You really think it was a coincidence
that I was there
and brought back the dying you?
No.
Same as the one the family head gave you
during my Heaven task.
During your first Earth task,
my task was to kill you if you failed
or were exposed.
Your task succeeded.
That's why I brought you back.
But when I took my Heaven task,
he assigned you the same one.
You refused and used that opportunity
to become my death guard.
Why?
Master, I...
Depart tomorrow morning.
(Vast Mind, Eternal Will)
Thank you.
Have you decided what to ask me?
Seems you haven't.
But...
I have a question for you.
Ask away.
Why did you sneak into
the head's Zhanchun Pavilion at night?
And why did you come to this mansion?
Wasn't it you who brought me in?
Now, the Xuanji Pavilion...
Where is she going?
That is your question?
Don't drink too fast.
Xuan Qing is highly gifted,
but her nature
is too rigid.
She doesn't belong here.
Isn't she the only person you trust?
Trust?
Since I was a child,
I've been in the Xuanji Pavilion.
The first lesson we were taught was
never to trust anyone.
♪Willows sway in the twilight breeze♪
♪Ancient alleys guard time's secrets♪
♪Bluestones bear life's imprints♪
♪Falling petals, endless longing♪
♪Longing lingers within my heart♪
♪Zither strings sigh
for the sorrow parting♪
♪Past tales nest in my soul♪
♪Affection lingers, unforgettable♪
♪Ink-stained scrolls recall bygones♪
♪Each stroke holds a thought♪
♪Prosperity fades like dreams♪
♪Past tales nest in my soul♪
♪Affection lingers, unforgettable♪
♪Ink-stained scrolls recall bygones♪
♪Each stroke holds a thought♪
♪Prosperity fades like dreams♪
♪Past tales nest in my soul♪