=Within The Grip=
=Episode 20=
(Spark of Love)
The newly deceased Gu Zhaoxi
looked remarkably like me.
Upon investigation,
he turned out to be my brother, Yin Ci,
whom we all believed died years ago.
How could it be?
"Newly deceased?" He's already...?
Was the assassin
back then really Gu Jiang?
What exactly happened?
Gu Jiang, Yun Sui and your mother Lianyi
were from the same sect.
The Xuanji Pavilion was co-founded
by your mother and Yun Sui.
But they both fell in love
with those they shouldn't have.
Lianyi married into the palace.
Your father held
no real power at that time,
so she used the Xuanji Pavilion
to consolidate your father's position.
But that didn't last long.
To secure the throne, your father
married the Right Chancellor's daughter.
Later,
on her way back
to the Tianji Sect to pay respects,
Lianyi was ambushed.
Go!
My lady!
Stop!
Don't run!
Lianyi!
- I'm too late.
- Save Ci!
Ye Lan and Ci are over there.
Go save him now!
Alright.
Lianyi!
I arrived too late and could
only rescue you as an infant.
I searched relentlessly
but never found your brother.
I failed to protect your mother,
and I betrayed her trust.
The Xuanji Pavilion only
answers to the Master's token.
Since Gu Jiang took over,
it's been no longer what it once was.
Someone intended to assassinate you
in such a short time.
If the deceased one was truly Yin Ci,
his death would certainly be suspicious.
That woman involved can't be innocent.
Remember this.
Don't let anyone in the Gu family
discover your identity.
Our priority now isn't damage control.
We must uncover the true mastermind
behind Gu Zhaoxi's murder.
But our people kept watch day and night.
Before this Heaven task, nothing moved
in or out of the Gu Mansion.
How exactly did they
receive task orders?
What have you discovered
about the person I told you to watch?
No leads yet.
With today's clues,
you'll uncover something soon.
Go now.
Yes.
(Fufeng Pavilion)
(Looking back now,)
(on the night
of Zuixian Building's owner's death,)
(Zhaoxi was nearby too.)
(Shen Zetian)
(But I have a feeling.)
(Someone has been guiding
me to investigate this.)
(If these accidents were truly planned
by the Xuanji Pavilion...)
(Heaven)
(It seems I must infiltrate
the Pavilion again.)
(Xuanji Pavilion)
Why isn't Mr. Gu Xuanwu here today?
He's on a task.
Still calling him that?
When he returns, we might need
to address him as Pavilion Master.
Right.
- Dear?
- Honey?
Who would've thought my frail husband
possesses such skills?
Shouldn't you be resting?
Why the night stroll in black clothes?
Likewise.
(Heaven)
Aren't you afraid I'll call
for help, acting so openly?
If you weren't afraid
of being discovered,
you wouldn't be wearing this outfit.
Besides, I doubt you'd want me captured.
That depends on who gets it first.
If I'm not mistaken,
you were the one at the Xuanji Pavilion.
And also the one
who secretly aided Xuan Qing.
Since you already know,
shall we work together from now on?
Intruders in the Shadow Pavilion! Go!
Yes!
Will you trust me?
Depends on who's asking.
I know you won't reveal yourself,
but I don't want
innocents dragged into this.
If you're Zhaoxi or the scholar
coming to find his relatives,
I'd never give it to you.
But I've investigated General Shen.
He's loyal.
He's the only one I trust
in court to solve this.
If you come as his advisor,
then I must ask if I can trust you.
For you, I'd die a thousand deaths.
(Heaven)
The Pavilion's Heaven tasks
are highly secret.
(But they can't appear
by magic in the Shadow Pavilion.)
(I searched everywhere in the room.
No hidden doors.)
(From the outside, no one ever entered
or opened the secret compartment.)
Since nothing can be taken from outside,
that means the mechanism
must be beneath the secret compartment.
If it is through underground passages,
everything will make sense.
Tunneling this entire underground web
without being detected.
You can start investigating
from the capital's drainage pipes.
Go...
and hurry back.
♪Carving a monument of longing♪
♪For someone♪
♪I know the past can never be relived♪
♪Life after life♪
(Fufeng Pavilion)
♪I've failed you♪
♪Pour this worldly brew♪
♪I raise my cup♪
♪Accompany you through ups and downs♪
♪Tears of romance♪
♪You smile so sadly♪
♪It tears me apart inside♪
♪Ask the demons♪
♪Born with guilt♪
♪Laugh at the gods♪
♪I have no regrets♪
♪This sorrow♪
♪Endless tears♪
♪Drunk for you♪
Why ask me to meet here?
Too many eyes.
Any news about those people
I asked you to find?
I found them.
Those beggars stole from a household.
When I arrived, they were
beaten half to death.
I've ordered them to be well cared for.
But why seek out beggars?
You travel widely for trade,
and your connections are vast.
Even the Xuanji Pavilion
couldn't find them, but you did.
You asked me out just for this?
Of course not.
Ensure those are well protected.
I've cleared your name
regarding the Yunya Temple incident
and handed the one who stole your pouch
at the banquet to the officials.
You could have let your servant tell me.
Why ask me to meet here?
Xuan Qing isn't a servant.
Fine, whatever you say.
But what's your real purpose
of asking me out today?
There's a circus performing today.
The new year is approaching.
The streets are getting lively.
I hear there's going to be
a molten iron fireworks show later.
Would you like to watch with me?
That's the thing Wenshuang enjoys.
You invited me to watch fireworks?
Where's Zhaoxi?
I haven't seen him lately.
The iron fireworks show will begin.
- Let's go!
- Alright.
Let's grab a good spot.
Molten iron fireworks.
Master Chaosheng, it's too crowded.
We should head back.
♪Willows sway in the twilight breeze♪
♪Old dreams flow like melodious poetry♪
♪Memories fade like the passing years♪
♪The past events leave us confused♪
Strolling with another man
before our wedding?
Did you assume I wouldn't return
and start seeking replacement?
How was I to know if you'd return?
Of course I made alternative plans.
With you here, I'll always return.
If I journey far again,
I'll tell you my return date.
♪Zither strings sigh
for the sorrow parting♪
♪Past tales nest in my soul♪
♪Affection lingers, unforgettable♪
♪Ink-stained scrolls recall bygones♪
♪Each stroke holds a thought♪
♪Prosperity fades like dreams♪
♪With nothing but memories left♪
He's watching.
How do you know?
You invited Gu Chaosheng out
just for him to see this, didn't you?
Last time, we missed
the molten iron fireworks.
This time, it's perfect.
May I kiss you?
My dear?
- Great.
♪I want to hold tight
this love on the wind♪
♪Even if it's just fleeting joy♪
♪It can become a memory I'll hold onto♪
♪If halfway through, you leave me♪
♪I'd still welcome another storm♪
♪Our stolen moment passes too soon♪
♪Unable to wait for this love to bloom♪
♪Who isn't just a passerby♪
♪And whose only one are you♪
♪Who broke♪
♪Whose heart♪
He's still here?
Yes.
♪Letting tears run wild♪
♪Only then realizing your hand♪
♪Holds my thread♪
Was your trip successful?
I've delivered the item to General Shen.
Good news should arrive within days.
Do you have any suspicions
about the mastermind?
No rush. You may close the trap first.
After all, the one the scroll leads to
likely isn't the true hand.
How have you been during my absence?
Why do I return to see this spectacle?
Haven't you already guessed this?
As for the show, that depends
entirely on your performance.
Our wedding approaches.
Protect yourself well.
This frail body still
relies on your protection.
Why this sudden urgency
to smoke them out?
If my deduction holds,
it's all the family head's design.
Master.
Where have you been at this hour?
♪Willows sway in the twilight breeze♪
♪Ancient alleys guard time's secrets♪
♪Bluestones bear life's imprints♪
♪Falling petals, endless longing♪
♪Longing lingers within my heart♪
♪Zither strings sigh
for the sorrow parting♪
♪Past tales nest in my soul♪
♪Affection lingers, unforgettable♪
♪Ink-stained scrolls recall bygones♪
♪Each stroke holds a thought♪
♪Prosperity fades like dreams♪
♪Past tales nest in my soul♪
♪Affection lingers, unforgettable♪
♪Ink-stained scrolls recall bygones♪
♪Each stroke holds a thought♪
♪Prosperity fades like dreams♪
♪Past tales nest in my soul♪