(All characters, venues, and organizations
in this drama are fictional.)
(Scenes featuring animals are staged
and abide by animal welfare guidelines.)
(Episode 11)
(Chae Moo's Garden)
Grow nice and big.
You're working hard in this weather.
What did you plant?
Peas.
I'm growing more attached to them...
at the thought of raising them myself.
I guess this is why people farm.
But isn't this your plot of land?
Why aren't you planting anything?
I can't because it's too strenuous.
Just plant anything.
I'll water it when I water mine.
It's okay. It's cheaper to buy
in the market.
I don't find this cumbersome at all.
All you have to do is grow nicely.
This is an eye from Ah Rin's rabbit toy.
Arin will be happy I found it for her.
Cho Won, what brings you here?
Is your leg okay?
Why are you carrying such a big bag?
It's so heavy.
Can I stay here for the night?
I ran away from home.
From home? Why?
I argued with Mom.
Mom still thinks I'm a baby.
Does it make sense for her to tell me...
to quit my police job
just because I hurt my leg?
It's impressive and commendable
you're working with the police.
How can she say such a thing?
You must've been upset.
You're truly the empathic type.
But why are you wearing sunglasses?
Because my eyes are puffy...
from the hospital.
I see.
(Restricted Area)
Take my blood.
Take all of my blood and save her.
Hurry up!
She's RH...
Yes, it's RH-O. It's the same as me.
But who are you?
Can't you tell? I'm clearly...
her father.
I'm her father.
Please save my daughter.
Cho Won.
It's me. Do you recognize me?
Dad.
Cho Won.
You and your mom must have had
a hard time because of me.
I'm so sorry.
Of all people, it had to be me.
If you hadn't met Mom,
I wouldn't be here.
I met a brave mother,
so I received all the love I could.
I thought nothing would change...
even if the secret behind my birth
was unveiled.
But I feel satiated...
and warm at heart,
even if I don't do anything.
And we've actually shared blood now.
So don't be sorry.
I'm so glad...
that you're my dad.
Cho Won.
Thank you so much...
for growing up into a fine young lady!
I don't know if I deserve
to hear such a thing!
Are you okay?
Don't cry.
That's enough.
What's wrong with you?
Let me take you to the best room we have.
Okay.
- What? What is it?
- Hold on.
Then Mr. Lee Soon Jae
is my biological grandfather.
That's right. He's my father,
so he's your biological grandfather.
Grandfather and dad, dad and grandfather.
(Dog Knows Everything)
- Hey! Get him!
- Hurry and get him!
Stop right there!
What's going on?
Hyeon Ta!
Wait a minute. Isn't that Hyeon Ta?
Those punks...
What do you think you're doing?
Back off!
I said back off!
How can you gang up on him?
Hey, Hyeon Ta,
why are you letting them beat you up?
You should beat them up, too!
Sir, please stop.
What do you mean?
Hurry and call the police!
Cut!
Cut! I said cut!
Darn it!
Where did he jump out from?
Mr. Lee Soon Jae!
What are you doing there?
My goodness, I didn't know it was a shoot.
It looked like
Hyeon Ta was getting beaten up.
It's obviously a shoot, Mr. Lee.
Don't you know
what these settings are like?
I didn't see any cameras,
so I didn't know it was a shoot.
I'm sorry.
Then good luck.
Good luck, Hyeon Ta.
I'm sorry, Mr. Director.
(Comfortable and unnoticeable
unlike underwear)
Thank you for saving me earlier.
Honestly, I was a little touched.
Hyeon Ta.
Did you bring this gift out of gratitude?
Yes. I read through the reviews...
and bought the one that's highly absorbent
and comfortable to wear.
Just trust me and try using it.
I have nothing to say because
you're actually serious about this.
In fact, I had always felt guilty...
about Mr. Lee going on hiatus
due to the urine-terrorizing incident.
I'm sorry.
Forget it. It's all in the past.
But Soon Jae doesn't need such a thing.
He has no problem going to the bathroom.
He fixed it all in Geoje.
Pardon?
Then if any one of you needs it...
What must you do to be good at acting?
Well...
I've been acting for over 50 years,
yet I still don't know
what makes good acting.
I always say this,
but acting is always incomplete.
So you just keep going.
I love acting, but I'm growing
more and more unconfident.
Wouldn't it be enough
if it makes your heart beat?
Just like how it's important in life.
Do what makes your heart beat.
By the way, who is this lady?
She's a staff on the PR team
at our agency.
But why are you holding hands
with a staff member?
She's a staff on the PR team
and my girlfriend.
We've only just started dating recently.
Please keep it a secret.
Your heart is already beating hard.
Hyeon Ta grew up abroad,
so he finds it difficult
around the older adults.
Ju Hwang, I'm comfortable
with everyone here.
They even promised to keep it
a secret that I'm dating.
Can we visit again after we go camping?
My manager found a great spot
that no one else knows.
I think it's a great idea
we came here today.
Right?
Yes, but Mr. Lee is a bit boring.
I was so sleepy.
Regardless, he's old-fashioned.
I'll bring the car, so wait a little.
What? Boring and old-fashioned?
They're not wrong, but that annoys me.
Are you done?
Yes, I'm all done.
The view here is fantastic.
It's wonderful, isn't it?
Hey, you know I can't drink.
Not drinking beer in front of such a view
is a crime.
Don't you know I pass out when I drink?
But we're the only ones here.
Just pass out.
Try passing out. Do it for me.
Then should I pass out just a little?
Cheers.
This place is so nice.
It's so nice.
What are you doing?
What is it? Why are you hiding it?
Hide what? It's nothing.
Then show me.
I don't want to doubt you.
Why would you doubt me?
Don't go overboard.
Who is it?
Hyeon Ta, let's cut this out
and drink beer.
I said show me!
Have you gone crazy? Give it to me!
Baek Song I, you know you look
more suspicious if you do this, right?
Forget it, so give it to me!
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
If you don't show me your cell phone,
it's over between us.
It's over?
Say that again. What was it?
Hey, say that again!
Song I.
Ju Hwang.
Song I...
died.
Look at you.
Stop looking at me.
You're embarrassing me.
Ok Sook, you should be the one
getting married...
instead of your daughter.
You look stunning, Ok Sook.
Really?
Then should I find a good-natured man
while I'm at it...
and hold a joint wedding with my daughter?
Ok Sook, which one is better?
This one or this one?
I'll go with this one.
My goodness, thank you.
I'll use it carefully
and return it to you.
Hyeon Ta, you were never here.
You suddenly felt ill,
so you went to Seoul last night
to rest, okay?
Are you going to end everything like this?
Are you going to abandon everything
you've worked so hard to build?
Hey.
Think straight!
Ju Hwang...
I'll deal with everything,
so don't worry.
It's okay.
Everything will be fine.
I'll make sure that it'll be fine.
I'll deal with Song I's body,
so hurry and head up to Seoul.
Hurry up!
Mom!
Mom.
You're here.
You must be tired from coming
such a long way.
No, I'm not tired at all.
It's rough preparing for the wedding,
isn't it?
It's rough for Eun Yeong.
I have it easy because I just have
to do as Eun Yeong says.
My goodness, my adorable son-in-law.
Mom, you look so pretty today.
Did you buy something expensive?
Of course.
A doctor is becoming my son-in-law,
so I better look good to my in-laws.
- Right?
- Yes, that's right.
Let's go.
My goodness, I'm nervous.
You're here.
How have you been?
This is my mother.
My goodness, hello.
It's good to meet you like this.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, nice to meet you.
Shall we take a seat?
Mom, you should sit inside.
My parents couldn't wait to meet you.
I love Eun Yeong so much...
that I was curious about her mother.
And seeing you in person,
you're so beautiful and sophisticated,
just as I expected.
I see.
She's in Geoje, right?
Yes, Dad.
I dreamed of becoming an elementary
school teacher when I was young.
So I'm delighted that Eun Yeong
is a teacher.
Mom.
Yes?
I see.
Ok Sook.
What are you doing here?
Something happened
at the family gathering, right?
You even lost my bag.
Hurry and tell me.
Don't hesitate and tell me.
Just what is going on?
Did you fight with them?
Are you on the verge of
calling off their wedding?
I don't think I'll be able
to give them my consent.
Hey, are the in-laws...
that bad?
Are they rude? Are they trash?
That's not it.
The father of Eun Yeong's fiancé...
is my first love.
Ok Sook, there's nothing more common
than first love.
Everyone in Korea has a first love.
It's not a big deal.
We lived together for three years...
before we broke up because
my parents were against our relationship.
But that man...
is the father of her fiancé.
What did he say?
Did he agree to call off the wedding?
He just pretended he didn't know me.
What should I do, Su Jeong?
What should I do with my daughter?
She won't be able to get married
because of me.
I feel so bad for Eun Yeong.
Dad.
My daughter, what are you up to?
I was just thinking of you
and you called me.
Where are you?
I'm having a glass of soju in Gangnam
after the shoot.
My goodness.
Don't drink too much, okay?
Don't worry.
I'm also snacking.
Snacking on what?
I'm having beer as a snack with my soju.
You give me such a hard time, Dad.
I shouldn't give you a hard time.
Dad!
You should have told me
if you were in Geoje.
When did you arrive?
It's been around three or four days.
What about your hospital?
You'll lose patients if you keep
taking days off as you please.
You're so haphazard.
It's because I take after you.
My goodness,
you only take after my bad qualities.
I also take after
some of your good qualities.
Soju with beer on the side then?
Let's do it.
Just look at you.
Okay, may all of you live long
in good health.
Cheers!
Cheers.
Se Gyeong, I feel so apologetic
for everything.
You don't have to feel that way.
Anyway, I'm sorry, Se Gyeong.
Then say cheers with me. Cheers!
She's very cheerful.
For a woman who had her groom run away,
she's very cheerful.
It's a compliment.
Why are you pinching me?
Thank you for seeing me in a good light.
Since I'm grateful, cheers!
You're so likable!
She's very likable.
Dad.
My daughter, what are you up to?
I was just thinking of you
and you called me.
Where are you?
I'm having a glass of soju in Gangnam
after the shoot.
You must be so happy
to have such a bright daughter.
She's very bright
because she takes after me.
You only say that my positives
take after you.
(Ju Hwang)
(A hopeful future with the people!)
I killed someone.
Are you saying that Hyeon Ta,
the nation's idol, killed someone?
Last night, I killed my girlfriend,
Baek Song I.
I mean, tell us in detail...
when, where, and how you killed her.
We argued at the campsite last night.
- I got drunk and used a tent hammer...
- Hyeon Ta!
Hyeon Ta.
Hyeon Ta, what's wrong with you?
Who are you?
Yes.
I'm Hyeon Ta's manager, Hwang Ju Hwang.
Sir, this is nonsense.
Yes.
Hyeon Ta has been working on a film lately
and he's been very stressed.
- He was prescribed sleeping pills.
- My goodness.
So he's a little delusional.
Mr. Hyeon Ta.
A homicide case needs a dead body.
Where's the body of your dead girlfriend
that you mentioned earlier?
I'm not sure.
You're not sure?
- Sleeping pills and delusional...
- Yes.
Mr. Hyeon Ta.
I'm your fan.
Return once you find the body.
Mr. Hwang, you should
take good care of Mr. Hyeon Ta.
You must be really busy.
- Let's rise.
- Let's go.
We're also busy, too.
Mr. Hyeon Ta, I'm also a fan.
One, two, three.
With the lighthouse. One, two, three.
- Hey, I'll take it for you.
- Okay.
Stand there. One, two, three.
What's that?
I knew it.
My prediction was correct.
The victim is Baek Song I,
a 22-year-old woman.
She died from a fracture
on the back of her head.
The weapon used in the crime was
a hammer used for securing tent pegs.
It matches Mr. Hyeon Ta's testimony
from yesterday.
Delusional from sleeping pills?
Are you joking with me?
I'm sorry. I killed her.
I killed Song I...
and threw her body into the sea.
Sir.
I'll request a warrant to arrest Hyeon Ta.
Put him in custody.
Yes, sir.
Hyeon Ta, you're not the type of guy
to do such a thing.
What on earth is going on?
Sir, please stop.
Is something wrong?
Someone I know killed someone I know.
Hey, what does that mean?
A fellow actor killed his girlfriend.
I still vividly remember how they smiled
at each other contently...
when they visited my house.
Did that pink ribbon girl die?
How do you know her?
I saw her in front of your house.
That's unfortunate.
I also saw her at the market yesterday.
But she died the night before that,
so how did you see her yesterday?
Did she die the day before yesterday?
Are you sure you saw her yesterday?
Yes. I was flustered,
so I clearly remember seeing her.
Where did you see her yesterday?
In front of the dried fish store
in Geoje Market.
Just a moment. I'll give this to you.
You should try tasting this.
It's freshly made, so it's nice,
chewy, and delicious.
You should try it.
Thank you.
This looks good.
It's so glutinous. How is it this good?
- It's good, isn't it?
- It's so good.
Sophie.
Don't lick this. You should eat it there.
Is business going well?
Seriously, what is this?
Are you kidding me?
But your business is doing well.
What? What was that?
(Su Jeong Market, B and B)
So you're telling me
to follow that manager...
and keep my eyes on him, right?
Yes. I'm sure he's hiding something.
I've attached a small camera
on your collar,
so just watch him from up close.
Something will be filmed
and recorded on it.
Okay. Good luck, Sophie.
Are you wagging your tail?
What are you doing?
Hey, are you not going to fall for this?
You're cute.
Paw!
Down!
Why must I do this?
Pray!
Life sure is tough.
You're incredibly smart.
Then how about break dancing?
Why I ought to...
Yes. That wench Baek Song I...
said if I didn't give her 30 percent,
she would tell Hyeon Ta everything.
That if she pretends to be dead,
I'll pretend to cover it up...
and use Hyeon Ta's weakness...
to make him sign a slave contract
with your agency to leech off of him.
She said she'd tell him
that everything was rigged.
I got so annoyed.
Then after I do all the work,
you'll take half the sum...
and Song I will take 30 percent.
Then what am I left with?
Yes. That wench Baek Song I,
I killed her.
So what?
Hey, hang up.
Hey, wait up.
Do you like beef jerky?
I'm giving it to you because you're cute.
Well done, Sophie.
So that manager
confessed his crime, right?
He spilled everything out.
But why is this camera wet?
Must I know that, too?
I was just asking.
Why are you getting so worked up?
Do you know how far I went to film this?
I also had a hard time, too.
I let go of my pride a lot.
My goodness, okay. I understand.
The sound wasn't recorded,
so I can't tell what he's saying.
Isn't it this?
"Yes."
"Bésame mucho."
"I sang it."
"Get lost."
Come on. That's not it.
"Yes."
"Did you roll the gravel
in the seaweed soup?"
"Where are you?"
This is what it is. It's the exact same.
What do you mean it's the same?
- "Get lost."
- That's not what he's mouthing.
Look carefully.
"Bésame mucho."
- It isn't "Bésame mucho."
- "I..."
Did you recognize me
at first glance yesterday?
Of course.
I recognized that you were Bong Soon
the minute I saw you.
I changed my name 30 years ago.
I'm Ok Sook now.
So that's why I couldn't find you.
Did you look for me?
I was enlisted right after
breaking up with you.
And I went around looking for you
as soon I was discharged.
I was in the U.S. at the time.
I learned how to do makeup there...
and it became my job.
You eventually became a novelist.
I even read your novel.
I'm grateful that you read it.
When I read your novel,
I could almost hear your voice.
It never crossed my mind...
that when someone who knows me
reads my book,
it can bring my voice to their mind.
Han Su...
I mean, Mr. Jeong.
We can't become in-laws...
Bong Soon.
What would have happened to us
if we had not broken up then?
I've always thought of this.
Mr. Jeong, please stop.
You shouldn't say such things anymore.
We can't let our kids get married.
I'll tell my daughter Eun Yeong...
that I dislike her parents-in-law.
So Mr. Jeong, you should also explain
why the marriage must be called off.
Ms. Song...
Hey, how did you know we were here?
Hyeon Su.
This is my first love.
A woman I loved so dearly.
Bong Soon.
I'm so sorry, Ms. Song.
I should have told you in advance,
but my father's dementia
has recently worsened.
These days, he can't even remember
what happened yesterday.
My father asked for your number,
so I saved it on his cell phone.
But I had no idea he'd reach out
to you like this.
You had a hard time responding
to him, right?
No.
Earlier, my father said...
you were his first love.
But that's because he's been talking
about his first love a lot lately.
Whenever my mother hears this,
she laughs and tells him
to look for his first love.
I guess my father's first love
must have left quite an impression.
He even mentions her name,
that her name is Bong Soon.
The name does sound like a first love.
But who knows?
That name might not be real...
or my father could have come up with it.
Ms. Song.
I'm sorry.
Eun Yeong and I cried a lot, too.
We pitied my father.
Eun Yeong's fiancé's father has dementia?
So your first love has dementia?
But he recognized me so well.
He even remembers things
from the past so clearly.
My goodness, he must have
longed for you deeply.
What did he say?
I mentioned calling off the marriage...
but have yet to hear a response.
But Ok Sook,
have you and your first love
done something wrong?
Did you scam someone?
Did you assault someone?
All you did was love each other.
But still, I can't let them get married
as if nothing had happened.
So do you plan to make your kids
break up like your parents did to you?
Nothing happened.
Just let them get married.
Hey, mentioning your first love...
to your children or anyone else
is unnecessary.
Just keep it to yourself to your grave.
Just keep it a secret as it is.
That's all you need to do.
Have another drink.
Is there a surveillance camera
in this market?
I see.
There are no surveillance cameras
in this market.
And no one has seen the lady.
I mean, if someone who is known
to have died three days ago...
roamed around this place yesterday,
it'll become evident Hyeon Ta
isn't the one to blame.
That woman's scent still remains faint.
Really?
Was she here?
Have you seen a lady
go back and forth near here?
- No, I haven't.
- I see.
Sophie, let's go.
There are traces of her
moving around here and there.
But there's no evidence or witnesses
to prove she was alive yesterday.
I think she deliberately went to places
where nobody was around.
Anyway, it is suspicious.
(Chae Moo's Garden)
(Sun Ja's Garden)
I mean, how are these peas yours?
They're my peas if they're growing
from my plot of land.
How are they your peas?
I worked hard to sow the seeds
and manage the garden.
And you just moved them to your garden!
Why would I go through the hassle
of moving them to my garden?
I didn't move them.
Then why are these peas in your garden?
I don't know either.
The peas must have walked over themselves.
Ma'am!
I heard you filed a report
on the theft of your peas.
The thing is I sowed the seeds,
watered, and looked after them.
And this lady moved all the saplings
to her garden.
I told you I didn't.
They just grew here.
That's it, Officer Hong.
Let's use the polygraph.
I'm innocent, Officer Hong.
Let's do a hypnosis.
And call a profiler or something.
Grandpa.
Hey, I can smell the woman from here, too.
From this garden?
Are you here after hearing about
the theft of my peas?
Peas?
The saplings of the peas
Mr. Im Chae Moo had sown...
are growing in the neighbor's garden.
Hold on.
Someone must have dug up this garden.
The paper that had been in the soil
has come to the surface.
You're right.
Give me this.
Why are you digging the ground?
Chae Moo, your peas moved
to the lady's garden...
because the soil was moved
from here to there.
What?
It really seems so.
Wait, what is this?
When Baek Song I was murdered,
the situation was recorded...
on her smartwatch.
Manager Hwang, who murdered
Baek Song I, abandoned her...
and buried the smartwatch,
which was crucial evidence,
and confessed that he was accountable
for the entire crime.
Well done, Officer Hong.
Hyeon Ta, I knew you wouldn't
do such a thing.
Thank you, Mr. Lee,
for trusting me and finding the evidence.
Thank you so much.
Can I call you "Grandpa?"
Of course, you can.
I'll repay this gratitude to you someday.
My goodness, don't bother.
Grandpa!
Yes?
Did they ask to have another
family gathering?
So are you planning to call off
Eun Yeong's wedding?
It's for my daughter's sake.
And I'll be punished.
Mom, why are you dressed so humbly today?
Are you feeling comfortable
because it's our second gathering?
I'm sorry, Eun Yeong.
There's no need to be sorry.
You look beautiful just as you are.
But I guess it's a little funny.
Two family gatherings?
My fiancé's father has something
to say before our wedding.
Yes.
Actually,
I also have something to say.
We're here.
Hello, Ms. Song.
It's so good to see you again.
Yes, hello.
Honey, you should say hello.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
I'm Hyeon Su's father.
Yes, hello.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Eun Yeong's mother.
Dad, this is your daughter-in-law.
Of course, I know Eun Yeong.
She's the kindest and prettiest
daughter-in-law.
Thank you.
Shall we take a seat?
I heard from my son earlier...
that you came all the way from Geoje.
Yes, that's right.
That must have been tough.
How many days did it take to come here?
Honey, Geoje is in Korea.
It only takes a few hours.
You must be hungry from the long trip.
Our meal will be served soon.
I see, my beautiful daughter-in-law.
But Dad, what did you want to say
at this gathering?
Well...
No one knows about this,
but I have a plot of land in Gyeonggi-do.
You should sell that and afford a house.
Honey, we sold that 20 years ago
for Hyeon Su's education.
Did we?
Well done, my beautiful wife.
But you also had something to say, Mom.
I'm curious as to what it's about.
Well...
Actually,
I wanted to thank you
for accepting the two of us,
who are insignificant,
as part of your family.
I don't think I was able
to thank you last time.
I'd like to treat you to a meal this time.
You want to treat us to a meal?
My goodness, you're wonderful.
Excuse me, Mr. Jeong.
Yes, Ms. Song?
What about Bong Soon?
Wait, how do you know Bong Soon?
Bong Soon died a long time ago.
Dad, get in the car.
Share this with your friends in Geoje.
These are good rice cakes.
Thank you. I'll enjoy them.
Then have a safe trip.
Yes.
We'll get going, Ms. Song.
Bong Soon...
I heard Cho Won is at the inn.
Yes. She'll be going home today.
I scolded her to listen to her mom.
These are pork hocks.
It's the front hocks, your favorite.
Gi Dong.
You should be the one who listens to me.
If you have time to buy me
front hocks like this,
use it to sort out your marriage issue.
Yes. I'll go see her, tell her everything,
and apologize with all my heart.
But I wanted to apologize to you first.
It's unnecessary, so hurry and go.
Well, it'll be hard to ask for
understanding and forgiveness,
but if you're honest,
everything will work out for the best...
because she's the only one
you love right now.
Thank you, Eun Ha.
My goodness, why are your hands
trembling so much?
I took two pills to calm myself,
yet I'm still like this.
Maybe I should have one more.
Why are you taking those pills like candy?
Is it crazy of me to ask you
to hold my hand in this situation?
Seriously.
So why would you come to see me
before your wedding?
It would have been great
if we had never met again.
Anyway, I'm also sorry.
No, I'm even more sorry.
Don't mind me and Cho Won anymore...
and return to the times
when you didn't know us.
Thank you for stepping up to Cho Won
as her father.
Thank you for raising Cho Won
into such a fine lady.
I'll try to become
a better person as well...
Se Gyeong!
Se Gyeong.
So that's what happened.
This is why you ran away from the wedding.
And I had no idea.
So I wondered if you were
having your meals,
whether you were okay,
or crying somewhere.
I had been worried for no reason...
and I pity myself for doing so.
No, Se Gyeong. That's not it.
When did you start listening to us?
I've been meaning to tell you everything.
You're the only one I love...
Wait, Se Gyeong!
What are you doing? Hurry!
I'll get going first...
Mr. Kim!
I'm sorry.
I think I need to go get Se Gyeong.
I'm sorry! Se Gyeong!
Hello.
Se Gyeong!
Se Gyeong, don't go away like that!
Se Gyeong, no!
It's dangerous!
Se Gyeong, I won't chase after you,
so don't leave.
Se Gyeong, no!
No!
Se Gyeong!
- Hey.
- Mr. Kim.
- Hurry and get in.
- Se Gyeong...
- I said get in the car.
- Who? Me? Get in the car?
- I said get in the car quickly.
- Okay.
Mr. Kim, I...
Mr. Kim, where are we going?
Buckle up.
(Dog Knows Everything)
I can't believe you wrote a script
with me in mind.
It isn't easy to produce a drama
without a popular actor.
Lower the ages of the lead roles?
Did Su Jeong give up
on her drama because of us?
You know what?
Let's just produce it ourselves.
Anything is possible.
Cut! Okay!
Soon Jae.
Get up.
Someone call the ambulance!
Your grandfather collapsed.
- What?
- He's in critical condition.
Dad!
He'll be fine.
I must go to Seoul.
Sophie went missing?
It's already been three days.
Just where did he go?
Wait for me, Lee Soon Jae.
You must not die.
Hang in there.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)