[Episode 4]
Oh, Hong Na Ri!
It's Hong Na Ri.
Let's go in.
Hong Na Ri. Believe only me.
Just me.
What does he want me to believe him about?
Are you okay?
What the heck?
Why are you driving like
that in an alley...
Someone almost got hurt. Be careful!
I'm sorry. It was dark,
so I didn't see him.
Hong Na Ri, are you okay?
Yes, well, I'm okay.
Well, that's a relief that
neither of you is hurt.
What are you doing in the middle of the night on the
street? Are cars the only ones that need to be careful?
Oh... I'm drunk.
Did you drink?
Because it's the anniversary
of her death, so a little...
A little?
Doesn't seem like just a little?
Why are you blocking the street and
displaying your dysfunctional family?
I guess we were blocking the road.
So, now you can pass through.
Please drive safely.
Is she cute because she's drunk?
What's wrong with me?
Hong Na Ri!
Yes?
I'm going to Seoul as your lawyer.
I'm going to submit the lawsuit
to the court tomorrow.
The fight starts now.
Lately, she just speaks her mind
but doesn't even answer me.
What is this crazy two-timer?
No, it's more like octopus legs!
You over there. I need
you to stop right there.
I really hate drinking.
Getting drunk makes me a fool.
My aching head makes me mad.
I really hate drinking!
No matter how much I think
about it, I don't understand.
Did you try to get me drunk?
Me?
What do you plan to do by getting me drunk?
Should I give you some
advice as your stepfather?
Stop pretending like nothing is wrong.
It's not like you were together for just 1 or 2 years. Just
think about all the things you've been through together!
You went to the funeral together.
I'm sure your heart must be hurting...
and all that time you spent together!
So what?
Don't get mad.
Comfort yourself. And take
a good look in your heart.
Meditate. Be at peace.
Don't get mad.
Meditate... be at peace. Fine.
And after that? Forgiveness?
What do you mean forgive! That guy!
I won't allow it anymore either!
Even when my eyes are filled with dirt
(meaning when I die), I still won't allow it.
What about when you were all
neighborly and friendly with him?
At that time, I wanted things
to go well with you two.
Starting from today, I totally hate him!
What do you mean you totally hate him?
He lied, came here to drink,
he can't drink or control
himself at his age!
What can he do?
Why? What? Does that upset you?
I can say even more.
He even laughs funny and
makes sounds when he eats!
Just keep acting like that...
I still won't trust you.
Unlike a man, he said bottoms up, but
left some of the drink in the glass.
His shoulders are uneven...
And your hoobae, she met the wrong guy and ended
up coming all the way here to pick him up.
He's the type to burden his woman.
Stop right there!
Hoobae?
I thought you were
totally, completely drunk.
But you still remembered
that you saw my hoobae?
No... I don't know who
you're talking about.
So, watching my hoobae come here to
pick him up, made you feel bad for her?
Ah, jeez.
My head hurts.
Oppa, we're here.
Oppa.
Na Ri isn't answering her phone.
She's busy lately.
Are the wedding plans going well?
I'm taking care of it.
Is Na Ri dealing with a problem?
It's the anniversary of her mom's
death, so she's a bit depressed.
I think I should go see Na Ri.
Later.
[The photos will now be deleted]
Who's there?
Is someone out there?
Someone's in here!
- I said I'm here!
- The war has started, Octopus Leg Lady.
There's someone in here.
Go Nan Gil... Go Nan Gil... Hey!
What time is it?
[Warning... 2 attempts made
to disable secret password.]
[Are you sure you want to delete this?]
[Cancel]
Hong Na Ri. Hong Na Ri.
Even if dirt goes into my eyes—
Should I wake her? No...
Let's wake her... No, no.
Aish.
Uh... You should wake up now!
How's your stomach?
Do you want some water?
She left, she left. I didn't
make a mistake, right?
Hey, Go Nan Gil!
Hey, Go Nan Gil! Open the door!
Go Nan Gil, can't you hear me?
I know you're there!
What are you doing in there? What happened?
The door is locked.
First open the door!
- Why did you sleep in there?
- Why are you doing this to me?
This is indirect murder. What if something had happened to
me while I was locked up? What if I had a cardiac arrest?!
What if there was a house fire? I would've
died locked up in the storage room!
- I don't know what you are talki—
- "I forgot." "I don't remember a thing."
- Don't say things like that.
- So you're saying I locked you in there? Why would I?
I guess your true feelings burst out of you when you were drunk!
Or maybe you pretended to be drunk and did it on purpose!
I said I really didn't do it! I dragged you there
and locked you up? The key is right here...
What's wrong with this key?
Oh, I'm cold... I'm cold.
I'm cold. I'm cold.
So, the reason you got me drunk was for this key. I can tell you
heated it with a lighter, and used tape and things like that.
Are you in your second year of junior high? Why would you
look this kind of thing up on the internet and do this?
- What kind of person do you think I am?
- Then who would it be, at that time?
Last night, you didn't come to my room?
I was locked in.
But someone definitely came to my room.
This is a man's footprint.
And this is me...
Here, closer to the garage,
this is my footprint, and this,
you're caught red-handed.
This footprint is yours.
This was just made.
Look here. This is me. This
is that person. And this...
- That's me.
- It matches. But this one is small.
You're right.
- It is a woman?
- Is it a man with small feet?
- I'm telling you it's a woman.
- What?
Oh, I'm cold... I'm cold... I'm cold.
♪ Tell me, why. Tell me, why. I'm
curious what kind of man you are. ♪
♪ I want you, why. I want you, why.
I keep on closing my eyes ♪
You, if you are going
to my mom, wait for me.
Well, that turned out well. We
can go up to Seoul from there.
I like Seoul the most.
She can't control her feelings.
What is this? Where am I?
Oh, my neck hurts.
Oh, my head.
Oh, you scared me.
What?
Yeo Joo, why... Why are you here?
So you don't remember anything?
Last night, you...
drove us here?
I couldn't carry you up here by myself.
It was late, so I couldn't
ask anyone for help.
So, I came up alone...
I made you some soup, so
get over your hangover.
I mean, I...
I really don't remember anything.
- There's nothing to remember.
- What?
Oppa, if it wasn't for me, Sunbae Na Ri
younger brother may have killed you.
- Younger brother?
- Oh, you have to fix your car.
- My car?
- Is Sunbae Na Ri's younger brother a gangster?
No...
Oppa, if they hit us, we need to get hit. If
they they get upset, we have to bear with it.
Because of the sin we have committed.
Exactly what happened?
Oppa, I'm not someone who is loose with
her lips. I don't want to tell you.
Then you shouldn't have said
anything in the first place.
Hey Yeo Joo... Yeo Joo!
- Hey, Yeo Joo!
- Ow!
Does it hurt?
What is this? How did this happen?
Who did this? Huh?
It's so cold, why did you go in there?
Because I've lived my life
peacefully without secrets,
but there appears to be too many secrets
in our house that I am not aware of.
What secrets...?
There seemed to have been a
lot of issues here and there,
but thanks for staying by my mom.
It's okay to have just done it for a year.
You can stop now.
What do you want me to stop?
You're young! Are you planning
on living here forever?
I told you already, I'm going to stay here
until the trees near the lake grow lavishly.
Why?
What do the trees have to
do with you living here?
Listen carefully... I'm going to
tell you something sincerely.
If a farmer buys a shovel,
what do you think will happen?
He'll probably plow and plant
seeds with the shovel, right?
No one would ever imagine that the farmer would
use that shovel to stab someone in the back.
Me becoming your father is just like that.
What are you talking about?
And... Stop searching my room!
What?
And don't search anywhere else.
You won't find anything anyway.
Are you confident that
nothing will be found?
I could find something
substantial in the garage.
Have you ever thought of that?
You were drunk and shaking with fright.
Look at you, telling lies.
So, while I was shaking all night trying to
figure out who would lock me up and why,
I had a lot of time and found
a lot of things to search.
Before, when I said I wouldn't come
back to the house... I take it back.
Because it's my house. So, at any time
I may stop by, so I hope you
stay anxious and live well.
He's not in a frenzied youth, why
is he aggressive these days?
Mr. President, what are you doing?
We have a lot of filling for the dumpling,
but don't have a lot of the skin.
Darn!
Our dumplings are all handmade.
Our special Hong Dumplings
begin with the dough...
We are now delivering our
dumplings nationwide.
If you buy one, you will get one free...
It's too precious to eat alone—
Why isn't he showing up in the videos?
Just what am I thinking now?
By chance, are you interested in men?
Is this what the Chairman is asking?
Yes, for the past few months,
I've been investigating someone.
Man, it's not like the team is
unskilled, but it's taking them so long.
Ah, this mysterious guy.
I want to know...
About him... Everything about him.
But...
it appears he has a daughter.
That man has a daughter?
Yes.
Then, you may go now.
Please drive carefully.
Wow, time flies! Well...
Jeez!
Lee Seok Joo
You're not telling this to anyone, right?
I'm not.
Hello?
Are you feeling less drunk?
I wouldn't even call that drinking.
Are you eating something
while talking to me?
Yes, sorry, I have to eat something
before I go on a flight.
- Why are you calling?
- I told you I would file a complaint.
Bring your stamp.
- I've got to take a flight, so—
- Yes.
Hello? Hello!?
What's with him?
1-3 Go Nan Gil
Aigoo... Aigoo.
Why does it keep going crooked?
Gosh! It looks like I have
to start all over again.
It might be easier for
you to sew it by hand.
1-3 Go Nan Gil
Hong Na Ri
Why is this here?
Nan Gil!
I told you you can't come here!
Those guys found out my
sister has passed away.
But those guys said they
sent the files to Na Ri.
Yes, thank you.
Did you bring your stamp?
I didn't realize you were
going to meet me here.
You are a lawyer who like
to shock his clients?
These are the documents for the
complaint, read them first.
I've investigated and there doesn't appear to
be foul play with your mother's car accident.
I'll think about filing
a lawsuit against him.
Then, please just sign over
power of attorney to me.
Sunbae!
Hong Na Ri! You're here early.
Oh, please go on ahead.
I will follow shortly.
Oh really?
That's the newest limited
edition suit, right?
Hey, his shoes are amazing!
They're Gucci.
How could you all be so caught up in
outward appearances? I'm so proud!
Oh, but why didn't she introduce us to him?
It's probably because he's not
someone she needs to introduce.
They all knew how cool I am and wanted
to meet me. Why did you ignore it?
They'll avoid you if you do that.
How should I introduce you?
Should I start a rumor that my home life
is so complicated I had to hire a lawyer?
Neighborhood friend.
We were going to be neighborhood friends.
By the way...
What is it?
The red lips? Do you fancy her?
No. Just that they are
staring at me so brazenly.
Is this the first time a
man has come to see you?
Or is it me? Do I look weird?
Did they split because of him?
Lots of couples split after
they set the date these days.
What's the big deal?
I'm going first.
You have a great style.
Why don't you leave before
they stare at you some more?
Just give me one signature and I'll be off.
[The man living in our house]
Later. Get going. I'm off now.
- Hello?
- Uhm...
I am at home.
Why, what's up?
Ah, just wondering if something's going on.
Like what?
A strange document arrived or a
strange person came by or something.
No, nothing like that.
I have get on the flight.
Okay, if nothing happened, that's great.
Ah, now I see why you called.
Why? What?
Are you in the warehouse?
That's it, isn't it?
It's very dusty in there, and
it smells and there are mice.
No mice here. And I clean it all
the time so it doesn't smell.
If you clean it every day, you
must know if anything is missing.
I don't know what you are talking about.
I used to talk to my mom
before each flight.
Her voice was an accident
prevention talisman.
Well then...
Uh... do a great job.
I have never been on a plane so I don't
know what that would mean exactly,
but fighting!
It's quite something for a
national flight attendant.
Perhaps you've become a family with someone
with whom you had the most misunderstanding.
It will be quicker for me to buy the
land from Go Nan Gil, won't it?
He won't sell.
He will sell, 100%. Why?
Swindlers know when it's
the right time to sell.
I hereby declare I've done
everything I can with Hong Na Ri.
Is Na Ri doing alright?
I will take care of everything
so please do not ask anything.
Or try to know anything.
Ah, that Na Ri.
Her engagement didn't break
up over the $30,000, did it?
You are not the type to worry about
anyone, truly. Do you need money?
How can you say that about my niece?
Is that what you think of me?
Finish your drinks and be on your way.
Na Ri doesn't remember
you at all, does she?
My mom's voice was an
accident prevention talisman.
Director, this is Go Nan Gil.
It's my land. It won't do you any
good to drag Hong Na Ri into this.
I have to drag her in, in order
to have you come see me.
Hong Na Ri is your
Achilles' heel, after all.
Furthermore,
don't call me 'director.'
I was your father once.
I will not tell anyone.
About you appearing at
the airport with a man.
I will not tell Dong Jin.
No need for you to put on such an act.
Omo, you didn't know. Dong Jin and
Duk Bong have met each other before.
They ran into each other
right in front of our house.
Duk Bong saw Dong Jin pestering me so they
don't have a good impression of each other.
It's better if you don't tell.
Nothing good could come out of that.
Your younger brother didn't
look so well because of
so many people are running into
each other outside of your house.
He looks too good to be
rotting in the country.
Younger brother? Never mind him.
He is your Achilles' heel.
Student!
Let's go get your bicycle.
Over there.
Student, this is yours, right?
She's not saying anything.
Why are you interfering with this?
I'm only guilty of buying it off
someone who's selling it second hand.
President, is a bicycle like this
common in this neighborhood?
She is in grade 12.
She's been walking since she lost her
bike and she's too tired to study.
If we report this stolen
and call the police,
they will inspect everything
in the warehouse, won't they?
Student, take good care of the bike! Bye!
You look after high school delinquents too?
How does she look like a delinquent?
You are the one who looks
like an adult delinquent.
The price you gave last time, let's
sign a contract on that basis.
I went somewhere expensive and
they even gave me a photo.
In these situations, get it
stamped, take the money and run.
That's the right way.
Does Hong Na Ri know about this?
No. Then the value of the
secrecy would plummet.
I will not tell her until
the contract is signed.
That's not what I mean. Does she know you
and I are about to enter into a contract?
From one point of view, she's
losing what's hers overnight.
She will have to know.
I am that cruel.
What did she say?
Is that what you are curious about?
"He won't sell," is what she said.
By my father's orders, we all
go through this process.
Our family is messed up. We need to have
evidence for our actions if questioned.
You might not know what a family is since
you grew up in an orphanage, Go Nan Gil.
A family is a societal relationship.
It's certainly not beautiful.
Don't fret about being a family when you really
are a swindler. Just take the money and run.
Before your past is all revealed.
I won't sell.
Should I not respond to my
daughter's faith in kind?
That's a family.
A family is not a relationship,
it's just a family.
It's a beautiful father-daughter time.
Still I must buy this land.
Why don't the three of us go at it?
There's a slang word that
I'm using these days.
I have to knead.
"This father is helping his
family's mental health."
Just think of it that way.
Body characteristics: Height-105cm. Weight-16kg. Skinny frame, tall. Other
Characteristics: Was abandoned as soon as he was born. Reserved personality.
Since you said that you've never ridden a
plane before, please enjoy these pictures.
I always sent messages to Mom when I
arrived. It was my good luck charm.
I have to knead.
Kwon Duk Shim. Do you
follow Go Nan Gil around?
I thought it was weird ever since a girl that usually wants
to do nothing but rest suddenly asked for a bicycle.
Do you know anything?
What?
What kind of bicycle I got, if I
lost it, do you know anything?
This girl is exploding with emotions.
It's not like we were that close.
Should I know those things?
Are you getting psychological
treatment or not?
Get out! I said leave my room!!
I think you really need help.
You've worked hard.
These days, you're the
harshest to Do Yeo Joo.
When we were bullying here you always told us to stop being
immature, and that being young and pretty wasn't a sin.
You acted all righteous then.
Why are you like this all of a sudden?
Something happened, right?
- I found out that being young and pretty is a sin.
- Huh?
By the way, something from the court
was delivered to your office.
- Already?
- Huh?
Sunbae, I'll be leaving first.
Since our Team Leader Kwon has lived
in that neighborhood for some time,
you must know about the orphanage?
Well, I think I remember
something like that.
Look at that. You do know.
Go Nan Gil came from that orphanage.
- Client Hong Na Ri, do you know how long I waited for your phone ca—
- Did you file it with the court?
What? How did you know that?
Someone said there was something at court.
That place doesn't do things that quickly. It's
probably some type of penalty or something.
I understand.
Well, that's that, but...
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
This girl only says what she needs to say.
Anyway, Team Leader you...
- Ran Sook!
- I thought I'd miss you!
Omo! Did I say I would
treat you to something?
I must be getting old. I
keep forgetting things.
That's right, Dong Jin did say
that you were a bit absent-minded.
Lead the way! We're going to your house.
I will kill that con man myself!
What, stepfather?
This is the airport. I'm still at work.
Ah...
Let's go and murder that con man.
Why does he use a gigolo
method to trick you?
You should ride the plane
comfortably at this time.
What if he sells the land and leaves?
He's not that kind of person.
Do you want to say things
to make me explode?
That rasc...
I've sold my soul, hoping
to catch that rascal.
Let's go.
He's not a con man. I
think I know who he is.
Shut up.
Go.
Dada Group
That's been here for three or four days.
What could it be?
Uhm... Borrowing money...
No, it's nothing like that.
Dada Group - Kim Do Seok
♪ If I was the sky ♪
Oh, Go Nan Gil.
Hong Na Ri is coming here,
just wanted you to...
- The customer is not able to answer the phone. Please leave your message...
- Aish.
Why am I so nervous? Once you get a
notice from the bank, it's over.
Is it something related to that con man?
Ugh, why am I so nervous?
I have sedatives, want some?
Why would you carry
something like that around?
Yeah, I see why.
So many things happened in the last year...
But what should we do? I
don't know what it is,
but I think you've been
scammed big time this time.
No, words become truth.
Isn't it something related to that con man?
Call him right now. Call that jerk!
Call From: Man Living in Our House
Oh, Hong Na Ri. Where are you?
- I'm in my friend's car.
- But you don't have friends.
I do have friends!
Who is it? Is this a time to
be saying something like that?
- Who's next to you?
- I said it's my friend.
- What are you doing with your friend?
- Don't beat around the bush.
You called me because you know something.
They said they'd hold
my salary on property!
Your salary— Oh, I'm
going crazy, seriously!
They can't do that. They
just sent it to you.
Just sent it? I see, it's a threat.
But how do you know about
it in such detail?
It's those people that I saw at Uncle's
house, right? You two are friends.
A threat? Is it that con man?
Tell him to go!
Hey, you should go, you con man!
Look. I'll go. So don't go.
Your friend next to you
is telling me to go.
Then, let's meet there.
Hey, you're young, but why are you
using formal speech to some scammer?
- Stop the car for a moment.
- Huh?
I can't do this wearing my
uniform, it'll hurt our image.
I don't have any clothes but this.
Do you want to wear this at least?
It smells like formula and vomit.
Dada Group
We've arrived.
- What did he say?
- He said he's coming out.
There's a police station
and a hospital nearby.
If anything, there's always 911. It'll all be okay
since you can just dial that if you get scared.
Call From: Man Living in Our House
Ms. Hong Na Ri.
Man Living in Our House
Take a seat while waiting.
Go Nan Gil is on his way.
I'm on my way so don't say anything.
Even if they give you a
document, don't read it.
Don't sign anything, whatever it may be.
Just wait a little bit more.
If you're scared, count.
I'm Lawyer Kim Do Seok.
Yes.
Don't show them any interest. Don't meet
their eyes. Just look somewhere else.
You must be very curious.
You can ask us anything.
I'm on my way, so don't say anything.
Don't read any documents that they
give you. Don't sign anything.
Please check these documents.
Even if she reads it, it would
just be a difficult step.
To put it simply, Hong Na Ri, your father
made a deal with us a very long time ago.
- My father?
- Yes.
Then please talk with Go Nan Gil.
He's on his way now.
No. We have to speak with you, Hong Na Ri.
Excuse me, you said it was a long time ago.
When did he borrow the money?
You would know if you looked at the documents,
but the first deal was made in 2001.
So 15 years ago...
Fifteen years ago?! Wait,
does that make any sense?
If it was 15 years ago,
th-then I was... What's it called?
Student? No, baby? No, that's not it...
Underage! I was a minor! How could I make
a deal back then? Do you have proof?
I don't understand what you're saying,
but I'm talking about Mr. Hong Sung Kyu.
Isn't Hong Sung Kyu your father?
Hong Sung Kyu made a deal with us using your
mother's land as collateral a long time ago.
Then your father went missing and your mother
was supposed to take responsibility for it,
but then we found out that
she passed away recently.
The daughter has to take responsibility.
If you give up the land in your
mother's name, it will be over.
Hello!
The representative told me
that I must escort you in.
Just give this to him. Tell him to
not even think about seeing me.
Camera 01
I told you not to read the documents.
Why don't you listen to me?
Did you not hear what I said?
Hey, Go Nan Gil. What
do you mean, "father"?
These are fake.
That's just what you think.
Come here.
I'm telling you, all we did
was have a conversation!
Stay here for a minute.
Count to three.
You know that I'm not good
at asking for things, right?
When I ask for something,
then I'm seriously begging.
I'm begging you. Don't
mess with Hong Na Ri.
And also...
This is a threat.
Use your head well.
When you mess with me,
what happened that day can happen again.
Let's go.
Are you fearless or just stupid? Where do
you think this is that you would come here?
I've never heard that I'm
stupid, and I'm really fearful.
So explain everything to me.
What's wrong with your clothes?
They kind of smell.
Don't change the subject. It won't work.
Are we in a relationship where we
can talk informally right now?
I spoke informally with
my father, you know!
Don't think of coming here ever again. All
you have to do is ignore them. I'm leaving.
I asked you to explain what
this situation is right now!
There's nothing to explain.
There's over $1,000,000 worth of debt.
They said that I'm responsible for it.
Why is that your responsibility?
That's the debt that my dad had.
I'm your father! Right now, I
am your father.
So there's nothing that
those bastards can do.
Was it because of this? Is this why you
became my father? You knew about this?
Did Mom know about it too?
Answer me, Go Nan Gil!
What's wrong with you? Are you sick?
Look at that sweat!
Hey, you con man! You stay right there!
You con man! Oh my!
Go Nan Gil. Go Nan Gil,
what's wrong with you?
Get a hold of yourself.
Snap out of it, Go Nan Gil!
♪ Slightly longer hair, looks
like you've lost weight ♪
♪ My concern for you sounds
like a nagging to you ♪
♪ I tease you saying you're not my type ♪
The Man Living in Our House
~ Preview ~
Go Nan Gil, don't speak
informally to me from now on.
- Do you possibly... - Possibly what?
- You know that you can't think of me as a man, right?
She really doesn't remember anything.
I admit it. He was pretty cool then. My heart
fluttered a little. But why does he keep showing up?!
Are you asking because
you really don't know?
I told you to get lost!
Do you possibly...
Why are your fathers the worst!
Send him to jail.
Go Nan Gil knows, too.
What are you saying?
That he's the only person
that I trust right now.
I don't think it's my place to clean it up.
Alright. I'll clean it up.
I promised that I would protect you.
With that promise... Let's go.
My long-term love...
My father...
Is over.