Let's settle
all debts and their interest today.
If you want to kill me, go ahead.
I will take control of all operations.
And here is the list
of the employees' new positions.
I think Mr. Na should work in the office.
I want him to learn
from the lower levels up,
so people won't gossip
that he's soft
and can't even handle low-level jobs.
Na, why weren't you answering my calls?
I'm sorry.
Mr. Na's unable to talk right now.
Who are you?
Why did you answer a call for him?
I'm a farm worker.
Mr. Na's in a meeting.
My name is Onsa-ang.
I'm Mr. Tatsana's girlfriend.
Go tell him
that I have a very important matter
to talk to him about.
I'm afraid that's not possible
because Mr. Na is negotiating
a 100-million-baht business deal.
If there's anything I can help with,
please let me know.
I'm his assistant.
Of course.
I'll tell Mr. Tatsana for you.
Right now, the Secretary
and Madam are in deep trouble.
If you ask for Mr. Na's help,
- you--
- Jan.
Don't bring this up around him,
or I'll be really upset.
But Miss,
when people love each other,
they would never look down
on their partner.
They would only care about each other.
But why do I have to make
Dad's mistake my problem?
Stop talking about this, Jan.
I won't let it stress me out.
Mr. Na.
Where did he go?
Mr. Na?
Mr. Na. Mr. Na.
Uh, are you Ms. Onsa-ang?
Oh, I'm from Paisal Farm.
Where's Na?
Why didn't he come to pick me up himself?
He's still in a meeting,
so he had me come instead.
Please.
Wait.
Your hand.
Put them on before touching the luggage.
Then load them into the car.
Roger that.
So drivers here dress like this?
How strange.
Hey.
Don't worry about me.
Just go take care of Madam.
Don't let Yai do anything to harm her.
Mr. Yai wouldn't do anything to her.
Listen. If you don't go,
I'll go do it myself.
Yes, Jom?
Yes.
Okay.
What did Jom say?
The meeting has ended.
There's nothing wrong.
Please get some rest, Mom.
I'll go out and check.
Watch Mr. Na for me.
I'll hurry there.
Welcome.
Please proceed to the main house.
I'll have someone
tell Mr. Na you have arrived.
Oh, Mr. Na's not here.
He passed out on the farm.
Pin's taking care of him.
Oh, my.
Why did he pass out?
Oh, Mr. Na had to oversee
the farm work as well.
Noi, lead me to him. Hurry. Oh…
Would you like to come with us?
Of course.
Did you not hear what she said?
Stop panicking.
- Let's go. Now.
- Yes, yes.
Please. Please.
I'll tell Mr. Yai for you
that you have a sun sensitivity
and are allergic to grass and hay.
Don't do that, Pin.
He would get upset
and bully me even more.
Don't you remember that when we were kids,
you were always there to save me?
You're…
just as kind as always.
So where is Na right now?
Tell him where to go
if you know where he is.
Jom said he's around here.
Miss, are you hurt?
Hey, are you trying to get fired?
Why would you drive like an idiot?
I found Mr. Na.
Miss. Miss.
Na.
On?
Hey.
Who is this woman, Na?
Tell me right now who she is.
Well, On…
Calm down first. Uh…
And…
how did you get here?
Didn't you say
you'd wait for me in Bangkok?
You told me to wait
and didn't go to pick me up
because you were busy flirting with her?
How dare you cheat on me…
- …with this country bitch?!
- Wait, On.
- Why would you do this?!
- On, On.
- You're the worst!
- On, calm down.
This is Pinanong, the maid's daughter.
Pinanong, the maid's daughter.
Pin who?
She's Pin,
the daughter of the maid.
She's been taking care of me
since I was young.
Pin?
The naive and dumb young maid
you told me about who annoyed you
by following you around?
That's her?
Yes.
Well,
I fainted and couldn't get up,
so Pin stayed to watch me.
We were waiting for someone
to bring the meds.
If you're a maid,
don't act as an equal to the master
or get too close to him.
It's inappropriate.
Na.
I didn't know.
I misunderstood.
I'm sorry, darling.
I'm sorry.
Are you hurt anywhere?
I feel so bad for Pin.
She's heartbroken,
and she got slapped for nothing too.
The wound's still fresh.
Good. Rubbing salt in it like this
will teach her a lesson.
Who is wounded?
Mr. Yai.
I misunderstood.
It didn't hurt much, right?
Pin.
Well… I'm okay now.
You can go back to work.
Oh, wait.
Jan, give me my bag.
This is for you.
Consider it my apology.
On.
You don't have to.
There's no need
to cling to these things, Na.
We bought so many of them in Chinatown
to give to maids and workers, right?
Have it.
It's my gift to you.
Then,
let's get out of here.
I'll introduce you to my aunt.
Alright. Let's go.
When a master gives you something,
why don't you bow and say thank you?
Did no one teach you that?
Or did you spend
too much time with animals?
Pin.
I didn't mean to bring them here.
It was Mr. Yai who ordered me to.
Pin. Pin…
Pin asked me to bring the meds for Mr. Na.
Where did they go?
Still hung up on him?
Come here.
Burn it,
so you can finally move on from him.
And now,
you can forget about him.
Take good care of our Indian cork tree.
- Indian cork. Indian cork.
- Pin.
- Indian cork tree.
- Are you crazy, Pin?
Just how cruel do you intend to be?
How could you burn my Indian cork tree?
It hurt you.
I burnt it for your sake,
just for you to insult me?
That's what I get from doing good?
What is this?!
I planted it myself.
It's my heart and soul.
Back off.
Are you happy now?
Huh?
Let me see your hand.
Did it satisfy you?
So this is
what they call
"To kick someone
and then give them candy."
You intentionally brought that woman
to trample on my feelings.
Are you so satisfied?
Pin.
I never intended to hurt you.
Na has a girlfriend.
I just wanted to open your eyes.
Is it worth it
to give your life to a selfish man?
You don't love anyone,
so you only care if it's worth your while.
But for me,
just being able to love him is enough.
What a stupid theory.
We all want to be loved in return, Pin.
Don't be so infatuated
that you let him walk all over you.
Have some self-respect.
A woman like me
is already low-born,
even without being oppressed.
Come here. Come.
The people around him are all weird.
They're not all there.
I don't believe
he can find someone good to audit us.
It was just a threat.
Oh, Auntie.
Mr. Manager.
Are you two being lovey-dovey right here?
What about you, Mr. Yai?
I heard there was an all-hands meeting.
I thought it was going to be here.
But surprise, surprise.
You were off doing something
with the maid alone.
Be careful.
The workers might lose respect for you,
and it would be hard
for you to control them.
Someone gossips about me?
I'll cut their tongue.
Someone insults me?
I'll slit their throat.
Someone tattles?
I'll cut their junk.
That's easy, Auntie.
And from now on,
Pin is no longer your maid.
Because
I'm appointing Pin to lead the Accounting
and Finance Department of Paisal Farm.
Hey. How could you do that?
Pin studied Home Economics,
not Accounting.
But even you
went to law school
and didn't even graduate.
But I can't do it.
I'm not good at math
and don't know anything about numbers.
Please hire an accounting firm.
Why waste money on that?
Our farm has to save money.
- But…
- I agree.
Pin has a keen eye for detail.
She's the right person for the job.
Also,
I've always let you
handle my personal finances.
Madam.
Pin
is the one I trust the most.
I'll leave it to you.
Good.
You're no longer a maid.
Take the department head's salary
and report only to me.
Good.
Krong.
I know what you're about to say.
Or do you want him
to hire an external auditor?
A naive
but straightforward person like her
can be dangerous too.
What if she finds something?
You seem to know my maid so well.
It's not what you think.
If she finds the gap,
we'll just let her
fill in the gap for us.
Haven't you tormented me enough already?
Idiot.
I'm helping you.
Are you blind or something?
Don't you want to get back
at those people you oppressed you?
I think you just want everyone to think
I'm loyal to you.
So, who are you loyal to?
I don't need to be loyal to anyone.
I just want to live a peaceful life.
If possible,
I just want to disappear from this world.
What do you mean?
You want to kill yourself
because of that unfaithful man?
Have you lost your mind?
I'm still in my right mind.
I have a mother to take care of.
Good.
But if you take an easy way out,
I'll ask for my money back
from your mother.
Don't think you can stiff me.
I'll never forget
your kindness.
I'm going to find a way
to repay all of it.
Cool.
You must audit the accounts thoroughly.
If even a single cent is missing,
all of you must take responsibility.
You do know
that a fierce guy like me
likes to punish hard, right?
Your owner is so dumb.
She's dumb, naive, and stupid.
She's just as dumb as you are.
Ugh, so annoying.
- Watch out, Yai.
- Whoa, Pan.
- Hey.
- Pan, watch out!
Come on, buddy. Don't be so petty.
I'm not being petty.
I'm just mad,
because I don't know why I had to get hurt
for a bad friend like you.
Because we were born
to be together forever, right?
Stop joking.
My friend sent me
the name of the audit firm.
Should I make an appointment?
No need.
I already let Pin do it.
What did you say?
Are you crazy?
Pin works for Madam Krongsuk.
She'd fabricate numbers
if her madam asked her to.
That's want I want to know.
I want to test that girl.
Yai, from the moment
you set foot in this farm again,
everything has been about Pin.
Let me ask you seriously.
Did you come back
to take revenge
and take back what's yours,
or did you come back
just to flirt with Puny Pin?
Hey, are you jealous of me?
Don't tell me you are.
My heart's fluttering.
Don't play dumb. That's not funny.
I risked my life, dodging bullets
and beatings to come stay here with you
because my dad told me to protect you,
not to come see you
take revenge on that Tsunami
for your stupid love triangle game.
That's a waste of my time.
On.
- Hello, Auntie.
- So glad to finally meet you.
Na told me so much about you.
You're even more beautiful
than I had imagined.
You're also different
than what I had imagined.
I thought you'd be younger.
Oh, my. Maybe it's time
for a full makeover in Korea.
You must be
the Permanent Secretary's wife.
Hello.
I am Jan,
Miss On's handler.
Oh, my.
I really can't tell from your aura.
So, how long are you planning
to stay here?
I'll arrange the cabin
in the resort for you.
I don't want to trouble you with that.
You must have booked
a five-star hotel downtown.
It's much more convenient that way.
I'll stay here.
And I'll stay here indefinitely.
But I already told On
a lot of people are staying here.
They go in and out freely.
We're laid back here.
- We don't really have strict orders.
- Yes, yes.
It's okay, really.
Jan's an expert
when it comes to order and discipline.
Jan is my head housekeeper.
She used to supervise maids
and oversee meal preparation
for international guests.
For something this minor,
Jan can help with the training.
As for me,
I will help Na manage this farm myself.
Because from what I can see,
this place still needs a major shape-up.
Okay.
- Right?
- Yes.
Let's help each other.
What is this?
Why is On settling in here?
She said
she's stressed about her dad's illness,
so she wants to relax.
Then why isn't she staying with her dad?
She chose to be with her hubby?
I mean with her boyfriend?
And did she meet Mr. Yai?
Not yet.
He must be busy managing the resort.
Good.
Give me some time to think
about what we should do.
If the two of them meet,
it'll be a mess for us.
Oh, my!
We've seen each other so many times now.
Still shocked every time?
Where are you rushing off to?
Ms. On wanted to rearrange Mr. Na's room
and told me to throw away all the stuff.
So I'm getting the workers to come help.
Sorry.
These curtains look so dated.
The fabric is also low-quality.
They aren't UV-resistant at all.
This blanket is clearly
a low-tier knockoff.
Look at this.
There are even threads sticking out.
And the texture is coarse.
The mattress is stiff too.
You wouldn't be able to sleep.
And what is this?
Look at this, Jan.
This lamp is so tasteless.
- Ugh.
- Oh, my.
How could Na live like this?
Miss On.
Then, I think we should
go stay in the hotel or resort.
It's inappropriate for you
to stay in the same house
as Mr. Tatsana.
Don't be too conservative.
When we were studying abroad,
we slept in the same room
and shared the same place.
And don't you tell Mom about this.
I don't want her to mention
Dad's debt in Na's presence.
I'm ashamed.
Noi told me
you wanted to rearrange the room.
How may I be of service?
Pan, you asshole.
There's no way
I'll keep wearing this lame uniform.
Just you wait.
I'll get back at you someday.
Mr. Yai?
Oh, wait.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
I forgot to ask
where I should move this to, Miss.
Just put it wherever you want.
I'll tell Na to buy new ones.
And go remove the curtains too.
I'll change all of them.
Hurry and take it away.
And the mattress too.
Take it out of there.
I'll overhaul the whole set.
I think this house
needs a lot of renovations.
I'll have to find a way
to negotiate with Yai.
Auntie!
Come with me. Quickly.
Nee! Where are your manners?
Don't you see I'm talking business?
Go save your in-law's life first,
and you can talk all you want.
On?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my.
What happened, On?
How could you hire
a stupid worker like him?
He almost dropped a chair on me and Jan.
I'm really sorry.
My finger suddenly locked up.
Perhaps I've been mowing
the lawn too much lately.
Why waste your resources on him?
Even trash is more useful.
On, if you wanted to move the sofa,
why didn't you tell me
to call in the workers?
But he's a worker too.
He's the one who picked me up
and brought me here.
You're misunderstanding.
- He's not…
- Hey, it's nothing at all.
How dare you treat a master like that?
What kind of staff training
do they even have here?
Whoever hired such crude, untrained trash
is a total idiot.
Just fire him.
Na.
Take On to my room for now.
I said fire him, Auntie!
I'm afraid
we can't do that, Sister-in-Law.
You're just an employee.
Can't you stay out of this?
I'm Tatsana's sister.
And this is
Mr. Chalit, or Mr. Yai,
the owner of Paisal Farm!
- The owner?
- The farm owner?
Tatsanee, why did you reveal that?
I was having fun with
my beautiful soon-to-be sister-in-law.
Oh, man.
Well, since we're already here,
I'd like to formally
welcome you to Paisal Farm,
my beautiful soon-to-be sister-in-law!
Let go. Let go of her.
But you really have sharp eyes, huh?
Look.
Look at her hourglass figure.
Oh, wow, what a specimen.
Come on, come on.
I'll appoint you
as head of PR for our resort.
Let's look after this place as a team.
Wow, a big family full of people
who love each other
is pure happiness and warmth!
No, Mr. Yai. Mr. Yai.
What is this madness?
Can you tell me what is this madness?
Well,
when he was a teenager,
Yai assaulted a worker nearly to death,
so he ran away and disappeared.
But suddenly, he came back.
I'm gathering evidence
to bring him to justice.
Well…
I was trying to find
the right time to tell you.
But you found out first.
I know many of my dad's friends
who are senior police officers.
We can ask them to take him in.
I'll call them now.
Oh, no. You can't do that.
Don't call them.
If word gets out,
Paisal Farm's name will be mud.
He's a part of this family anyway.
Well, Yai has been cut out of the will.
And Mr. Paisal left
the entire farm to Na alone.
Then why are you afraid of him?
Chase him away.
Well, Mr. Yai is Mr. Paisal's son.
I want to give him a chance to repent.
Yes, yes.
And before he passed away,
Mr. Paisal left Mr. Yai in my care.
I don't want to break
my promise to my benefactor.
Please understand me.
And what if he does
something disgusting to Miss On again?
I think we should go home, Miss.
That's good.
No.
I'll stay right here.
But I'll never consider Yai as family.
And don't ever let him come near me.
Right.
Ugh, it's just one thing after another.
Yai alone already gives me
enough of a headache.
And now there's
this elite in-law stirring things up.
This is hell.
Yeah, this is literal hell.
If Pin finds out there's money
missing from the records and tells Yai,
he'd bury us.
I won't let him bury us so easily.
I'll bury him myself.
Pin.
Are you awake, Pin?
- I'm awake.
- Hey, Pin.
What medicine did you give me?
I slept like a log
from yesterday evening until just now.
It's the medicine the doctor prescribed.
You were probably too exhausted,
so you were out cold.
Then I must change my medicine.
I'm a maid.
I can't be sleeping in like this.
And what are you doing?
Why aren't you
cooking breakfast for the family?
Well,
Mr. Yai told me
to audit the farm's financial records.
Why would Yai assign tasks to you?
Why did you get involved with him again?
I didn't want to.
But he's the farm owner,
and he ordered me to do it.
How could I refuse?
Pin.
You swore with me.
Do you want to see me die
the way you swore I would?
But some money is actually missing, Mom.
What did you say?
I compared it to my own records.
There's even some cash
I collected for Mr. Teera myself,
but it hasn't been recorded in the book.
It adds up to millions.
Well, well.
First day as an office girl.
Were you busy
dressing up and putting on makeup?
Is that why you're this late?
Wow.
I think you're the one
who's looking better than usual.
Uh… Hey, I…
I'm this good-looking every day.
What?
It's this late.
Why hasn't that slowpoke shown up?
She's probably destroying evidence.
Are you that jealous
that I'm more interested in Pin than you?
Stop with that nonsense.
I'm not crazy in love like you are.
Here.
I pointed a gun at the Finance staff
and got a backup file.
I'll tell Madam that
Manager Teera's been extorting money.
Mom.
You know Madam is a regular
at the gambling den, right?
It's just a small amount.
There's no way it would be millions.
But the den she goes to
belongs to Mr. Tong.
When I was locked up there,
I overheard that
Madam owes them several million baht.
Our farm business is struggling,
and they're unable
to pay the workers because of this.
If we let this continue,
Paisal Farm will have nothing left.
There is no limit
to what a gambling addict will sacrifice.
Yes.
Pin is right.
I'm terrible.
What I've done is unforgivable.
Madam.
I've put you both through so much.
I've run Paisal Farm into the ground
even though I've tried my best
to keep the last property of Mr. Paisal.
But now, I give up.
Go ahead.
Take me to the police.
Go ahead…
Madam.
Do it…
I give up…
PAISAL FARM'S FINANCIAL RECORDS
See?
You don't have to be an accountant
to see how messed up this is.
More importantly, watch this.
Most customer payment receipts
have Pin's signature.
Some of them were in cash.
But they haven't been deposited
into the account.
Pin might be the one who received
the payments and gave them to Madam,
so Pin didn't know where the money went.
Fine.
Then you wanna bet?
If Pin doesn't show up,
you'll need to quit stalling
and drag all of them to prison.
Okay.
Because I'll win for sure.
Aunt Un?
Oh, Krong?
Noi told me you went out early.
I thought something happened.
So?
So…
we can enjoy breakfast now.
I'm returning the records you gave Pin.
And where is Pin?
She ran away.
Where?
I don't know.
So it's clear.
She intended to run.
Pinanong was an accomplice
in extorting money from Paisal Farm.
She knew about this.
That's why she wouldn't face you.
If you're suspicious of her,
just take me instead.
Then you can kill me,
torment me, or do anything
people like you are good at.
You probably don't know
who paid the medical bills
that allow you to run your mouth
in front of me right now.
It was Madam.
300,000?
Where was she supposed to get that money?
Don't you think
it was the money Bandit Yai robbed?
I don't believe you.
If you give a dog some food,
it will still wiggle
its tail with love in front of you.
But sacrificing your life
to protect your madam
won't give you anything.
But at least
I'm grateful for people's kindness.
I'm not ungrateful like you.
Pin might have gotten away,
but don't think you'll walk free.
I'll send all of you to prison!
Pin extorted the farm's money?
That's ridiculous.
Yeah, she would never do that.
She'd go to the ends of the earth
to return a single baht.
True. I agree with you 100%, babe.
Pin must have been framed.
Un told Mr. Yai herself
that Pin disappeared.
If we want to know what's really going on,
we must find Pin first.
Guys.
If you have friends and family anywhere,
spread the word.
Find Pin around this area.
Let's help out.
- Yes.
- Mr. Yai…
Mr. Yai
It must be Mr. Yai.
He's constantly bullying her,
so she must not have been able
to take it anymore.
Jom.
Stop assuming the worst about Mr. Yai.
It's you
who's blindly loyal to Mr. Yai.
I've got an idea.
Let's call Ms. Jin.
But where's my phone?
My phone.
It's in your hand, babe.
You're all over the place.
Such an idiot. That's why I love you.
- What did you say?
- Oh, I love you.
Call her now, before it's too late.
Pan, pull over. Pull over. That's Pin.
That's not her.
Do you only see Pin or what?
Yes, Dad.
Something bad happened.
Hey, stop. Uncle Pload,
I took control of the farm.
But the madam is being a bit feisty.
Be careful. Don't underestimate her.
Yes.
Mr. Yai?
I heard Pan. What is wrong with him?
He's bloated right now
and farting non-stop.
I gotta go, Uncle. It smells so bad here.
Let go!
Yai.
You're trying to keep
something this serious from my dad?
Yeah.
Don't you tell Uncle Pload
until we find Pin.
So annoying.
Pload, don't be stressed.
No matter what happens, Pan is there.
Mr. Yai will be okay.
Hey.
Pan's not that competent.
Back in school,
he let Mr. Yai
clash with technical students.
And what did he do?
He ran off somewhere.
You've always been hard on your son.
And look at you.
Think about it.
When they were young,
who was doing
Mr. Yai's homework if not Pan?
See? Pan
always has you to back him up.
But does Mr. Yai have anyone?
His mom passed away,
and his dad was infatuated
with a mistress.
I've never forgotten
the look in that boy's eyes
the day he fled Paisal Farm.
How could a life fueled by revenge
be a happy life, Pload?
It's love
that will help heal Mr. Yai's heart.
A love like what Mr. Yai's father had?
Hey.
I asked the officer.
They said Jintana's not coming
to the office today.
She has to make her rounds
to vaccinate animals.
But I've got her address.
What are you looking for?
Does your car have a charger?
My battery died
while I was talking to Win.
I don't know. This is my dad's car.
Yai.
Why are you tearing it? That's my dad's.
How many photos have you torn?
You won't forget him anyway.
Forget it.
I'm not judging.
Let's get back to the farm.
Don't you want to go to Jintana's place?
Win already sent Jom there,
but no one was home.
Then we might have to wait
and interrogate Jintana.
She would help her friend.
She'd never tell us where Pin went.
But I know a better way.
If you want Na back,
give me the one who extorted money
by tomorrow before sunset.
You're too late, Pinanong.
So I burnt him alive,
taking revenge for you in one go.
I never believed you were truly evil,
but now, I'm sure you are.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
I never hated you, Mr. Yai.
Subtitle translation by: Anan Pratchayakul