Episode 9
Are you awake?  Miss Na Ae Gyo?
What are you?
Where are we?
I saved your life. Aren't you quite hostile with your thank-you?
Apparently, your resemblance to Su Ryeon ends with your looks.
Who are you?
I'm  Logan Lee. We met two years ago.
Logan Lee?
I don't know anyone like you.
Instead of talking bullshit, beat it.
Wait a moment.
I'm not trying to hurt you.
I just want to hear what you were intending to tell me then.
If you don't want to die, remove yourself.
You're no match for me.
Up until Su Ryeon's death, with a face like hers, did you pretend to be Ju Dan Te's wife?
By lobbying the Happy Future Party head Jeong Du Man and  government officials,
I know you obtained intel and made a huge fortune.
But two years ago, I am sure you decided to part ways from Ju Dan Tae.
That's why you asked to meet me.
Don't give me bullshit. I never did anything of the kind.
The only person I trust is Ju Dan Tae.
This voice. It certainly is you.
I am Na Ae Gyo.
I have something I must tell you before I leave.
What that bastard Ju Dan Tae did to Sim Su Ryeon.
What kind of person he is.
If I don't do it today, I might never be able to do so.
At the time,
you were sincere. You- you were desperate.
At the time ...
we must have had a spat.   Couldn't I have wanted to dis him out of anger?
I can't control my anger very well.
Then, are you okay if Ju Dan Te hears this?
Ha, let him hear it.
Are you trying to blackmail me with a thing like this?
I'm sorry but
Ju Dan Tae and I have a much tighter and deeper bond than you think.
We even had our children together. Do you think he'd fall for a word like that?
Don't mess around.  Never approach me again.
We meet again.
What's this? Were you in cahoots with him to approach me deliberately?
Clearly, you misunderstand something.
I'm Ju Dan Te's woman and the twin's birth mother.
Ju Dan Tae tried to kill you.
You almost died today.
You don't know when or how you will be disposed of like Eonni Su Ryeon.
But are you going to stand by Ju Dan Tae out of loyalty?
What do you think you know about him to be yakking as you are?
I, too, have been thoroughly betrayed.
Because of him, I was made a fugitive and nearly died.
You, too, will be no different from me.
You know best.  How Ju Dan Tae handles a person he doesn't need any more.
We're giving you a chance to dump him before he dumps you.
Join hands with us, Na Ae Gyo.
Just what the hell are you two?
Seok Hun
Hello?
Seok Hun?  It's Ahjumma.
Nothing happened, did it?  I was worried so I called.
No, I'm okay.  How about you?
Has my dad perhaps done something to you again?
No, I'm fine. Now that I hear your voice, I'm hanging up.
Your children. Don't you want to see them?
Seok Hun and Seok Gyeong. I'll help you to see them.
Isn't it too cute what you're doing?
Are you buying my heart with things like my kids?
If I had something remotely akin to motherly love,
would I have run away leaving the newborns behind?
Being a mom is something I detest most.
Do you know what Ju Dan Tae has done to your children?
They're being abused and live in hell.
Despite that, do you want them to grow up at the mercy of that lunatic?
Don't talk whatever you like about the affairs of another family.
Leave her alone.
You can't let her go like this.
What if she goes to tell Ju Dan Tae everything?
We can't help it if she talks.
So are you giving up? I can't do that.
Even if she talked like that, I saw her eyes trembling.
Let's hope there's the last remnant of motherhood somewhere in her.
Where have you been?  Why didn't you answer the phone?
What, have you got another man or something?
Who tried to kill me? Who's blaming whom here?
Why did you do that,  you son of  a bitch?
The building is sold so you're going to kill me, because I am no longer useful?
I wanted to validate your sincerity because I didn't understand what you did two years ago.
What didn't you understand?
I was in obedient exile in Thailand, just as you ordered.
That was ...
Because Sim Su Ryeon died, I told you to lay low abroad for a while.
Because you shouldn't be seen by others.  But why did you keep avoiding me?
You wouldn't answer the phone or come back even when I begged.
You pretended not to know me. How should I have interpreted that?
Darling. We are amazing partners.
We have been one for a long time.
As long as you don't betray me, I, too, will never betray you.
You mess with me only once, Ju Dan Te.
Do it once more and I'll put a bullet in your head.
Do you understand?
Now I think my Na Ae Gyo has returned.
By the way, you were a tad sexy earlier.
My heart fluttered for a second there.
Shall we have a drink to celebrate our making up?
I was anxious that you might have other feelings. You know very well what you are to me.
We've got to fish something big out of the Cheonsu District development.
At least until then, I won't double-cross you.
Voice Spy
Ju Dan Te's relationship with Na Ae Gyo seems more solid than we thought.
No, I felt a crack between them just now.
She didn't tell him about meeting us.
Contact me anytime if you change your mind. I'll help you meet your children.
What brought you here? Chairman hasn't come home yet.
I came because of his tuxedo for our wedding. I need to check his shoulder size.
Go and do your work.
Yes, Ma'am.
This necklace is your daughter's, right?
We found both your daughter's DNA and the victim's blood.
Where did he put it?
What are you doing in here?
Like a rat in a room without the owner present.
Are you looking for this?
Give it to me. You have no reason to keep it now.
I did everything you told me to.  I sent out the invitations and got the wedding dress.
I'll walk into the wedding as I promised. So give me the necklace back.
Giving it back to you isn't hard. But don't think this is the only card I have up on my sleeve.
What do you mean by that?
I heard Eun Byeol got an IV.
So, was her memory erased well?
How could Dr. Ha test on his daughter the medicine that's still in a clinical trial?
That isn't anything a doctor with a current and valid license should do.
With any side effects,  his daughter's life will surely be ruined and he'll end up in jail.
Ms. Cheon Seo Jin, why is it that you can't understand?
I told you that you wouldn't be able to get away from me.
Accept your fate unless you want your daughter's lost memory back.
Did you get it, Cheon Seo Jin, my darling?
Eun Byeol's Dad
Destiny
What do you think you're doing? Marrying Ju Dan Te?
For Eun Byeol's sake, you did say you wouldn't. Don't you know what an awful man he is?
I know. So what?
What man won't lose it when his fiancée's hooking up again with her ex-husband?
What's wrong with you? Something happened with Chairman Ju, right?
Why is the abrupt change of mind? You don't love him!
Am I a 20-year old kid smitten by love?
Marriage is the best business deal you make in life, so I chose Ju Dan Te.
What happens to our daughter?
Will Eun Byeol accept this marriage?
I am doing this for me.
You left Oh Yun Hui. That's enough.
Over my dead body, I'd see you being happy with her.
- What?
- Why?
Were you clueless that I was this kind of woman? I've been using you all this time.
I needed your blind fatherly love in order to cover up Eun Byeol's criminal act.
I put on an act to pay back Oh Yoon Hui and pretended I was coming back to you.
You're lying.
However desperate you are, you can't be doing this to me.
Stop clinging to me and leave me alone!
I had no intention of going back to you in the first place.
A man who suits me is Ju Dan Te who's wealthy and a gentleman to his core.
Come on, Seo Jin.
Take Eun Byeol and go. To America or wherever, it doesn't matter.
Are you abandoning your daughter, too, now?
My life matters more than my daughter's.
It's better this way for Eun Byeol, too.
So ...
go away before my wedding no matter what!
I ...
am done talking.
Leaving your child
is a grave sin.
You
you've got to protect our Eun Byeol. Now that's the only way.
What are all these?
These are Chairman Ju's wedding gifts.
He got yours, too. Do you want to have a look?
The dress and the shoes you're going to wear to the wedding.
Does he really mean he'll go through with the damn wedding?
Damn it!
Seok Hun, where are you right now?
Je Ni's Mom! Je Ni's Mom!
Oh my, what are all these?
How come did you buy so many prestigious brand-name bags?
These are my birthday gifts from the Three Madams. They cared.
Goodness, all of them?
My, then all the new things you've  been carrying are from the Three Madams, too.
I thought so. I bet you're closer to them than their own flesh and blood.
- They must be heavy. Let me help carrying them.
- No, no need.
If someone sees us, they'll think I'm ordering you around.
Who will? I'm at your service of my own accord.
I, Gyu Jin, am awfully good at doing things like this.
The 21st Korean National Assembly voted me as the ultimate politician of manners . Let's go.
What, manners?
I told you no need. Hey, give them back to me!
Be careful.
Come on, you're a VIP.
What on earth is this?
It's okay. They were going to find out about us anyway.
Let's go.
I see they're two friends hitting it off quite nicely.
They'll be a brother and a sister soon!
Were they like that coming down all the way from the fifth floor?
What was that again?
When their parents set the day of their betrothal, how shameless Eun Byeol and Seok Hun are to be dating?
They're a cute looking couple, though. They even excite me a little.
Chairman Ju, at this rate, your wedding may get called off.
When the two go around like that,  word will spread in no time.
As long as you keep your mouth shut, no one will know.
I'm a strong and silent type, to begin with.
Oh, no. There was Kang Ma Ri at the scene.
The game's over when she spreads the word in her bathhouse.
My Seok Hun isn't at an age where he does things impulsively.
Eun Byeol's tricking Seok Hun to stop the wedding. Any reaction now will further egg her on.
I decline your unsolicited advice in the affairs of my household.
You get lost in that direction.
Chairman Ju. Tell me, it's just between us.
What's the real motive behind your determination to do this wedding?
When your fiancée is falling again for her ex, Ha Yun Cheol,
It can't be that you love Seo Jin. Then is it her share of Cheong Ah Group that you love?
I wouldn't want to use force this morning with an occasion for celebration approaching fast.
After all, you're a member of the Korean National Assembly.
I'm rooting for you. This is true love.
Chairman Ju, you're the true romantist who attains love despite your children's opposition!
I'm almost moved.
I have a bodyguard, too. He's a first-rate martial art practitioner.
Turns out my son is pulling quite a stunt.
I thought he'd grown up from the fearless way he dared me. But he's still a child.
He's a baby who still needs to be cared for in my bosom.
I hear Teacher Cheon is getting terminated from her chair position.
We'll see how competent Ha Eun Byeol  is. Her first test ever, fair and without her mom's help!
In her current state of mind, I doubt she can do well on her test.
I also hear Teacher Ma shut off  her exclusive bathroom, too.
She'll eat the same lunch as we do.
The queen of Cheong Ah Arts School is now disgraced and became a commoner.
Our Teacher Ma is awfully good at such things.
Come on, split, split.
Must you be like this? Why do you bother showing up at school, knowing how things are?
I swear, you have no regard for me at all. School or marriage, you do everything your way!
Don't waste your energy riding in a taxi. The day's barely started.
If you don't want to ride with me, I'll get a car for you.
I hate your guts. You're selfish without a dime's worth of motherly love.
Are you crazy? Let go!
What the hell are you up to?
Do you advertise you're seeing my brother? Is this your silly protest to stop the marriage?
It's not a protest, but truth. Seok Hun and I like each other.
Do you think if you like each other madly, you can stop the wedding?
You'll only get my brother beaten for nothing. In fact, possibly to the point of death.
Him, dying?
You clearly have no idea what a formidable man my father is.
- Do you see these?
- What happened to your arm?
Don't tell me.
This is the true color of your soon-to-be stepfather.
So quit trying to persuade my dad. Just make your mom give up.
I swear, I won't leave you alone if you play my poor brother and get him hurt.
Since we're all here, we're going to vote yes or no on terminating the current chairperson.
Before the voting begins, I'd like to say something.
Cheong Ah is the most prestigious private school foundation in our country.
Fostered by the generous donations and the passion of the previous chairperson, our foundation is now the cradle of education.
Such a reputation has been tarnished by Cheon Seo Jin's incompetence and arrogance.
With that said, I strongly demand the current chairwoman be terminated.
Madam Chairwoman, you may make your statement as well.
I acknowledge the grave nature of my error.
I'm very ashamed of it.
But this isn't a time for strife but harmony. I'll do my utmost best to turn things around.
I can leave the world of vocal music with no regrets, but Cheong Ah Foundation is
my life.
I'll personally turn everything around, and I humbly ask that you give me just one more chance.
We'll begin voting now.
Regarding the termination of the chairwoman
Cheong Ah Foundation : Vote in opposition
Well then,
I'll announce the result of the voting.
On terminating Chairwoman Cheon Seo Jin
Yay:5    Nay:6
Five votes for terminating her,
and six votes against her termination.
How absurd. She's a thief.
What just happened?
With this, we've just decided not to terminate Chairwoman Cheon Seo Jin.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for trusting me.
All of you directors, I won't forget your mercy and will do my very best
to restore Cheong Ah Foundation's reputation.
I don't know how you were able to win the directors over,
but I won't ever accept this decision.
Rest assured that we'll protest the decision and vote again.
Let's go, Mom.
Your father asked us a favor before he passed away.
What was it?
You'll find that my eldest daughter falls short in many ways.
She's ambitious but is still deficient in many aspects.
Once she becomes the chairperson, her mom will try to push her out with various justifications.
Seo Yeong will also cause problems and divisiveness.
Never mind all that. Just trust Seo Jin and help her become strong
so that she will be able to keep her chair position.
Father.
So you don't need to thank us.
Think of your father and be strong.
We have your back.
Father. Oh, Father. Father.
Father, I was wrong.
Father,
forgive me.
Were you here?
Were you looking for me?
They rejected the call to terminate your mom as the chair person. Did you hear?
No, I don't care.
I don't understand why my Mom is so obsessed with the Foundation.
She must not even be ashamed in front of the kids. It's so embarrassing.
Don't concern yourself with what other people say.
Once time passes, people will forget.
Cheer up.
Seok Hun.
You should also lean on me when you have a hard time.
I'll listen to whatever you have to say.
You know how much I like you, right?
Did any of your memories come back?
Do you remember what I told you that day?
No. No matter how hard I think, I really can't.
Can't you just tell me?
Think harder.
Don't you remember whom you met on these stone stairs that day?
Did I?
Who besides you?
You have to remember.
You might have seen Ro Na's real killer.
What does that mean?
Isn't Mr. Park the killer?
You also know what a kind man Mr. Park is.
I'm certain he's being framed.
I didn't believe it either.
Mr. Park isn't a man capable of killing anyone.
As long as you remember, a true killer can be found even now.
Mr. Park will be released, too.
If you remember anything, only to me,
come and tell. Only me.  Can you promise that?
But are you still thinking about Ro Na?
It's not because of Ro Na.
I just feel bad for Mr. Park.
You'll help, right?
Okay. I'll do that.
I'll do anything you want. I'll try to remember.
The day's last music. It'll take you right back to reality. Here  it is.
Eun Byeol, what's wrong?
How did you say Ro Na died again?
She was hit in the head with the Cheong Ah Arts Festival trophy.
A trophy?
Gold Real Estate
Specializing in Cheonsu District  Investment Consulting
I'm Hwang Geum Bong.
I'm interested in looking at some properties for sale in Cheonsu District.
Did you say Cheonsu District?
There's no plan to develop the area yet.
If your interest is investing, I recommend Okpyeong District.
Hold on a second. Let me consult with the investor himself.
Are you sure about the information that Cheong Ah Group is going to invest in Cheonsu District?
Of course, I heard it directly from Mr. Ju himself.
But do be careful about it because the official announcement hasn't been made yet.
Okay, so how much property are you looking for?
Everything you can get your hands on.
-There's going to be a massive increase in value soon.
- Okay.
Do you know Dan Tae Ju?
Apparently, he got a direct referral from Chairman Ju Dan Te.
My investor has his heart set on  Cheonsu District.
Okay.
Where is Cheonsu District?
Chairwoman Song! It's Hwang Geum Bong.
Have you been well? It sounds like Gangnam District is getting developed.
So I'm making an urgent call.
Is that so?
Okay.
Oh, do some research and send the files to my secretary's office.
Lady from Jincheon, do you like the gifts I sent you today?
I put a lot of thought into choosing.
Of course, I love, love them.
You ladies have the best eyes for everything in Korea.
Is that rude wench from last time still bothering you?
You said she lives at Hera Palace with you, right?
After she got some serious scolding from you ladies,
she's on all fours around me. So no worries for me.
If she acts up again, tell us immediately.
How dare a mere assemblyman's wife look down on our Lady from Jincheon?
Forget all that, and why don't you move?
Move?
I just got a call.
I hear a 130-storey commerical and residential complex is coming soon in Cheonsu District.
Did you hear about that, too, Chairwoman Song?
Chairman Ju Dan Te is getting in, so announcing of the area development will come soon.
Did you say Chairman Ju?
He's so fast on such things.
Lady from Jincheon, you, too, should get something for youself.
It'll grow into a district much more affluent than Hera Palace.
Really?
This is indeed hot and valuable information.
Since it hasn't been announced yet,
it must not be that expensive either.
But you should still hurry.
I hear all the good spots are already taken by Chairman Ju.
Honey!
Honey! Honey! Gyu Jin!
Unless you dress me, I can't go to work and look after people and  their livelihoods—. Forget it.
What's with coming in looking like that?
Like a woman who's been around the block.
Did you go to Kang Ma Ri Bathhouse again?
You might as well clock in there every morning.
Did you save a nation in your previous life?
How come did you get so lucky to meet a woman like me?
On the contrary, I couldn't save a nation and hence, I met you.
How will you raise your campaign funds without me?
What? Did you hear something?
Cheonsu District will soon be developed!
The news is about 200 years old already.
Ever since I was in grade school, I shopped for land with my mother.
This is a sure thing. I cleary heard what the Three Madams say with my own ears.
Who are they? The indisputable golden source of real estate.
Chairman Ju already smelled something and is buying off the land there.
Ju Dan Te, that punk, didn't say anything to me.
Is he going to take everything for himself?
Wait a sec.  What kind of savings do you have?
No, no, no. I've got to call Mom right away.
- Yes, yes.
- Right away, today,
I'll throw a party of cuteness,
and collect all the cash I can from her.
This, here, is something very rare.
In two years, it's going to be a hundred-years old.
Well, you shouldn't have gone so far.
And these too.
Well, this is all too much.
Now this.
Have a look, please.
Real Estate Sales Contract
Buyer: Kang Ma Ri
Agent: Hwang Geum Bong
It's just enough for a nice meal.
This just came out.
It's worth $5 million per square feet.
Five million!
- Shall we stamp the seal together?
- Shall we?
Grab it.
Seller: Choi Do Ju / Buyer: Yi Yong Beom / Agent: Hwang Geum Bong
Ta-da!
Congratulations. Now sit and wait for the windfall.
That sounds great!
Although I'm not sure who leaked the information,
JKING HOLDINGS
real estate sales in Cheonsu District are suddenly skyrocketing today.
- Who got the scent and crawled in?
- I haven't been able to look into that far yet.
Hey, you idiot!
When you spend that much for your work expenses, can't you handle a thing like that?
Find out at once whose names are on the contracts and who are the actual buyers.
No, no. First, buy all the parcels of land that I checked out as soon as possible.
- Get going already!
- Sir!
That retard.
By any chance,
Is it you, Oh Yoon Hui again?
My goal has changed.
I want to become really rich.
I'm going to make money like crazy.
Enough to get this penthouse.
What an arrogant bitch.
So you think you can get my penthouse.
Darling, it's me.
I need you to do me a favor.
You've got to handle a pesky woman for me.
That's my speciality.
Tell me about her when I see you later.
Thank you for your call, Ms. Na Ae Gyo.
I didn't know you'd get back to me so soon.
No need to thank me.
How good you're with keeping your promises,
I came to confirm it.
Are you okay with just seeing the kids from here?
What then?
Should I put my arms around them and shed tears of joy?
They're here.
- You're here early.
- You came.
What's this? Is this Ahjumma what you wanted to talk about?
Don't be rude. Ahjumma said she had something to tell us.
What do you want to drink? It's on me.
The strawberry milk shake here is  good.
It's really sweet.
Are you satisfied now?
I don't have a stomach strong enough to be chatting with the person who killed my mom.
Sit, Seok Gyeong.
It's about your mother.
My mother?
Your birth mother.
- She's alive.
- What do you mean our birth mother?
Ahjumma, I'm sorry, but
our birth mother died of sepsis right after we were born.
Know your facts before scamming us.
Do we have to keep listening to this crap?
Your father lied to you.
Your birth mother is alive.
She is the one who gave birth to you.
Are you crazy?
Are you playing with us? This is our dead mother.
No, she really is your birth mother.
It's astonishing how much she looks like the late Su Ryeon.
It may be hard to believe, but it's true. I met her and confirmed a few days ago.
Is this real? Where is she now?
Oppa, do you believe what she says?
She's tormenting us because she's mad I hated  Ro Na.
This kind of a shabby picture can be easily fabricated.
We can just go and ask father.
Do you trust our father?
Do you still not know what kind of a man he is after all we've been through?
Our father is the one who abuses, torments, and controls us the most.
What kind of truth do you expect from him?
Please, don't do anything.
Ahjumma is trying to help us.
She's very near you.
I'll help you if you want to meet her.
When did I say I want to see my birth mother?
Who the hell is she to try and be our mother after all this time?
To me, there is only one mother.
This kind of a fake mother?
I don't need her.
Give it to me straight.
You know something, don't you?
What is it? Tell me!
The one who killed our mom
might be our father.
Are you crazy?
Why would father do that? Why would he kill our mother?
Why?
Because he didn't need our mom anymore.
Our father is that kind of man. He never keeps what he doesn't need.  Even us!
He might throw us out anytime.
So we can't trust him anymore. Do you understand?
There's only you and I in this world.
I'll never  abandon you even if I die.
I will protect you from our father.
If my dad really did that to my mom,
I won't leave him alone.
I'll never forgive him.
What the hell are you doing?
What did you threaten Seo Jin with?
Stop the marriage immediately!
Seo Jin is too precious to be given to a piece of trash like you!
You've done enough.
If I give up Cheon Seo Jin,
that you two will live happily ever after. Tell me so honestly.
Didn't you come back for Cheon Seo Jin's money, too?
So that's how little you can use your hand.
I should've made sure to completely destroy it back then.
I suppose I was too softhearted.
You crazy bastard!
I'm going to do whatever I can to stop this marriage! Even with my own life!
I really admire how gutsy you are.
But I guess you haven't heard anything from Cheon Seo Jin yet.
She's heartless. After all, it concerns your daughter.
Her birth father should know.
What trash talk is this?
I found out.
That daughter of yours killed Bae Ro Na.
What should you do?
A parent should cover their kid's transgressions.
Seo Jin's decided to bear the burn all by herself.
Her love for her daughter is quite something else.
Such a pity seeing you like this all alone.
Go on. Hit me.
Hit me if you think you can keep me from spilling the beans.
I told you to hit me!
Take your daughter and get out of my sight.
Before I hand her over to the police.
I'm going to kill you.
I'm going to kill you, Ju Dan Tae!
Fighting!
I'm going to kill you!
Controlled Area
Restricted Access
I can't read Na Ae Gyo.
She hardly reacted when she saw the kids.
She isn't a type forthcoming with who she really is.
We'll have to keep an eye on her.
Any reactions from Cheonsu District?
As expected, Kang Ma Ri and Lee Gyu Jin dived in.
They're buying into the information they get from Three Madams.
The time has come to act.
Mr. Hong, it's Oh Yun Hee.
I'm selling the property at Number 27 in Cheonsu District.
Can you see if any buyers are there?
As soon as possible.
Yes.
It's about time Ju Dan Tae arrives at the mountain villa.
Voice Spy
Did you ask to see me just to give me the damn wedding invitation?  Jeez!
If Cheon Seo Jin won't divorce you,
you'll probably live with her for the rest of your life.
Do you think I'm crazy?
That woman, too, can't help but marrying me because she knows I know her weakness.
- This marriage means nothing to me!
- Did he say, "weakness?"
It's just an excuse to get my hands on the shares.
As for the land you bought in Cheonseo Distict,
I want you to register all of it under my name.
- Let's do half and half.
- Seventy percent!
Nothing below that!
In return, I'll recover the land Oh Yoon Hui owns.
Don't you think seventy percent is going overboard?
Is seventy percent overboard?
Really?
Fine! It's only until I divorce Cheon Seo Jin.
When are you going to end that marriage?
Once the marriage registration is done, I become the biggest shareholder of Cheong Ah Group.
Once the house is turned over to me, I'll divide it and sell off immediately what's mine.
After I raise the value of the shares to max, I'll wash my hands off them. Don't you trust me?
How can I trust someone who tried to kill me?
If you were me, would you trust?
I already explained everything!
Nobody knows!
Like Sim Su Ryeon, suddenly one day
I may vanish quietly.
Get lost!
I don't feel like drinking with you.
We haven't finished talking!
What temper.
What's wrong with your face?
Who did this to you?
Stop this marriage immediately! It's a crazy thing to do.
Is it because Ju Dan Te knows your weakness? Don't be afraid.
There's no evidence to prove Eun Byeol is the true killer.
How did you know? Did that bastard tell you?
However Ju Dan Te threatens you, hold your ground firmly.
I will take care of Eun Byeol's sleep treatment.
Just say you know nothing.
He has evidence. Eun Byeol's necklace.
It has Eun Byeol's DNA and Ro Na's blood on it.
Even the recording where I confessed everything.
Why are you telling me this now?
How are you going to deal with this alone?
Don't patronize me.
I'm enough to control Ju Dan Tae anytime.
If you just take care of Eun Byeol, I will deal with the rest.
Please leave quietly.
It's my last request.
No way.  I'm not the one who did that, right?
No, it can't be. There's no way.
Why do I keep thinking of the trophy?
It's time for your medicine. Your Mom said you make sure to take it.
If I take this, will my headache go away?
Does your head hurt a lot?
What do we do? You went through the test materials only three times.
My head feels like it's going to burst!
I'm working on my math problems, but the numbers are crawling around in my head!
What if I really go crazy?
You've been doing great so far. Now, Ro Na is gone, too!
This isn't good. Enough studying today and go to bed early.
I'll wake you up early tomorrow morning. Come on.
How is Eun Byeol doing?
She's quite shaken up. Her mother's wedding is coming up, and
I think there's a problem with her memory circuit.
What about the medicine she takes? Does it keep her from remembering?
I already replaced the pills with vitamins, so the drug should have no effect.
She'll remember soon what she did.
No matter how hard she tries, she ends up back to square one.
I feel sorry for her.
Seok Hun
Why did you want to see me?
That there's a real killer who killed Ro Na
- I know.
- What?
Is that..
Eun Byeol?
I have my suspicions, but I'm not sure.
I have no proof either.
I think my father is involved in Ro Na's death.
Cheong Ah Arts Festival
He has the necklace that Eun Byeol wore on the night of her performance.
Ju Dan Tae knows everything. That Eun Byeol is the killer.
He threatened Cheon Seo Jin with that and is going forward with the wedding.
A good item is up for sale in Cheonsu District.
Golden Real Estate,  Licensed Real Estate Broker's Office
Then, of course, I must buy it!
I will pay fifty million more than the highest bidder without fail!
No.  I will bid one hundred million more. I really will.
I will trust you, Mr. Hwang. Yes.
Is it already worth that much?
It's worth all the money we paid to Mr. Hwang.
When the land is truly coming into my hands,
I'll be moving onto the new chapter of my life.
On that parcel, there is going to be a 130-storey residential and commercial complex.
Next to it, Hera Palace will look so tiny.
Wow, really, Three Madams' information is powerful.
Hooray, hooray!
What did I tell you?
Didn't I tell you Kang Ma Ri Bathhouse was the conference room for the Ministers of Land, Infrastructure and Transport?
Who would've known I'd benefit from a scrubbing ahjumma in my life?
Let's send Je Ni's mom several cases of the finest Italian towels.
I'll say.  Honey, we played it perfectly.
Kang Ma Ri Bathhouse?  Is Je Ni's mom a scrubber?
- Alright.
- Gyu Jin, I love you.
Hey, Yu Je Ni!
Do you know it costs over $100 for a piece of that candy?
If your throat hurts, just go to a convenience store and get some mint candy.
Can you mind your own business?
Stop picking a fight and get lost.
Isn't that humidifier from Switzerland? It's an luxury item for someone like you.
Head to toe with designer brands.
You, really shouldn't be doing this.
Did you buy them for me? Did I steal from you folks?
I use them because I can afford them. What do you care?
I have to study so get lost.
Still, that really isn't right.
Your mom works to the bone to earn $10, $20 at a time by scrubbing bodies.
You should be frugal, too! Am I wrong?
What?  Who is doing what?
Hey, did you really not know?
When I heard your mom works with tears and sweat,
I was so moved. That's why I got you some gifts.
Hey, what are you waiting for? Present your gifts.
Bam, bam, hey!
How pretty!
So sore. Why are my wrists so sore?
It's not good if they break down already.
Ahjumma! Are you crazy?
Why are you drying these out in the living room? What if Je Ni sees?
- Ahjumma!
- I did it!
Je Ni!
I, um, what happened here is...
How long were you planning to hide this from me?
If you're too embarrassed to even tell your daughter about it, why do it?
Quit this job immediately!
How did you find out? I wasn't trying to lie to you.
- I'm sorry, Je Ni.
- What are you sorry about?
Did you steal? Did you get money by whacking people?
- No, it's nothing like that!
- Then why do you hide?
I never did a thing  that made me ashamed of myself before you.
Even if you're embarrassed, I can't quit this job.
What did I do wrong?
I did my best to raise you so you won't envy a chaebol's daughter,
and took care of you without any regret. Isn't that enough?
If you don't dry them thoroughly, they'll smell.
If you don't take care of your customers, you'll lose them all.
- Then what will we live on?
- What?
After what happened to Ro Na, I'm no longer scared or ashamed of anything.
I'm not scared of the kids, and I don't care if I don't make it to Seoul National University.
What I'm scared of
is someone who used to be by my side not coming back.
Dad's not even here, so we should be relying on each other.
What's the use of keeping it a damn secret? I'm your daughter!
Do I have to hear about your job from a jerk like Min Hyeok?
Je Ni.
I filled the tub, so come in when you're ready.
I want to see how good a scrubber you are.
Don't forget my banana milk either.
When did my princess grow up like that?
Since I got found out, should I tell her about her father, too?
Or not?
- Mom, what are you doing? The water's getting cold!
- Okay, okay, I'm coming in now!
I don't care for now.
What are you doing? I will do it for you.
Stay still.
I'm an expert who's been doing this for 25 years.
Wealthy CEOs are lining up to get scrubbed by your mom.
Do you not believe in my skills?
Look at all these dead cells! You've been scrubbing others, but you haven't youself, right?
A lot of dead cells!
What dead cells? I wash up every day!
You suck at this.  I'm going to learn how to scrub.
Why would you learn this?
You'll live in nothing but luxury after finishing Seoul National University.
That's why I've been working with great excitement.
Are you listening to me or not?
Lady, you talk way too much.
I won't ask you to pay. Just stay still.
At least for today.
Mom!
- Mom!
- Get your snacks and you should study.
Did you tell Dad to take me to the States with him?
He says he needs to visit his headquarters.
Go and clear your head. It'll be soon school break anyway.
Liar. You're kicking me off to the states so you can get married.
You're supposed to be my mom. How can you do this to me?
Mom! Can you not do this wedding?
Mom, I can't live without you!
Please, don't abandon me!
Mom, I'm so scared!
Eun Byeol.
You're everything I have. So don't get married.
If I must go to the states, come with me then.
As long as I have you,
I can even give up college. I mean it.
Why would you give up college? You worked so hard to get here!
Stop acting weak and do what I tell you to.
I'm staying here to protect you.
To protect you from that devil.
Why?
I told you I'm not mad.
It's fine. Just get ready for your wedding with Cheon Seo Jin.
You're really coming in a few days, right, Mom?
Of course.
I'll be there as soon as I settle the matters of the company and the Foundation.
Don't worry.
Go with your dad ahead of me.
I'm not sure if this is really the best option.
Don't let Eun Byeol catch on.
Don't say anything about me either.
I can never. I can't leave without you.
Let's kill Ju Dan Tae instead and run away. We can be together.
Stop with the nonsense, and get going.
Hurry!
Seo Jin.
Farewell.
Don't become weak, Cheon Seo Jin.
Today's your wedding. Did you send your daughter away without her seeing it?
I guess Ju Dan Te is  a lousy stepfather.
Why don't you mind your own business, and see yourself out of here.
You have no child, no husband. Why are you still here at Hera Palace?
I like it here.
I also like that you can't wait to get me out of here.
I'm also curious as to how happy you and Ju Dan Te will be in that penthouse.
What?
So I want to give you my heartfelt congratulations on your wedding.
See you later, happy bride, Cheon Seo Jin.
Why is the bride's face so puffy? Were you so excited you couldn't sleep?
If you can't wait like that, why didn't you tell me to rush the wedding?
This is what you need, right? You take care of the marriage registration.
I would have liked to rent out an entire hotel,
and made you the ultimate bride,
but your name nowadays is, well...
Harvard Business Review
How to Lead with Purpose
I hope you understand why we're having a quiet wedding at Hera Palace.
Yet, today, you're becoming the owner of the penthouse.
So you should enjoy it.
Did Eun Byeol leave?
The weather in California is going to be beautiful.
Don't you dare say her name.
We might be married, but Eun Byeol won't be your child.
She will never have anything to do with you.
What a pity.
I was so excited that I was getting another daughter.
They're really going through with the wedding.
Ha Eun Byeol left for California.
Left? Ha Eun Byeol?
Where are you going?
Seok Hun
Don't answer any phone calls, Eun Byeol.
5323, stop the car on the shoulder!
Stop the car! Stop!
Don't get out, Eun Byeol.
Are you Ha Yun Cheol?
Yes, what's going on?
You're under arrest as the main suspect of Bae Ro Na's murder.
What?
What are you talking about?
Dad! What's going on?
What are you doing to my dad!
Park Jeong Sik who was detained on the murder charge has confessed everything.
He got paid by you and made a false confession.
Let's go to the station.
Wait! Wait!
Something's wrong. Wait!
Wait!
That's not true!
Wait! I have something to say to my daughter.
Eun Byeol! Grab a taxi and head to the airport now, okay?
- Dad!
- Eun Byeol, I'll be okay.
Don't worry and make sure to go!
- Dad!
- Eun Byeol, you can do it!
Let go of me!
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
t r a p
Secretary Jo: He was just arrested and is being taken to the police station.
Good job.
Eun Byeol
Power Off
Ha Eun Byeol. What happened? What's going on?
Seok Hun. What am I going to do?
Thank you to all of you at Hera Club.
We're finally getting married.
You've suceeded.
You two look good together.
There, the star of the night, the bride!
Noona!
You're wrong, Bae Ro Na.
I'm not letting you take anything away from me.
Neither my dad nor Seok Hun.
Nor the grand prize trophy.
What's wrong, Ha Eun Byeol?
Ro Na. It was Ro Na.
I did it to Ro Na.
Smile.
Smile as if you're so happy you might die.
Sorry for realizing this too late.
I loved you, Ha Yun Cheol.
♫  You keep repeating just the words that you love me  ♫
♫  You only have to say you'll always be there   ♫
♫  To me your tears everyday  ♫
War in Life: The Penthouse II
Welcome to Hell.
You've got to learn some manners, Ahjumma.
I killed her.
I'm going to make you regret this with your whole life.
I kept thinking you don't seem a bad person.
Use me for whatever the reason.
I remember everything.
Are you saying there was someone else?
Why Ro Na died—
There is a trap.  I need you to catch Ro Na's real killer.
I'll take back what's mine even if I twist your neck.
♫  To me who couldn't even keep my promise and ended it.  ♫