Episode 10
Our  Seo Jin is so beautiful.
She is the perfect new bride.
How much did that dress cost?
Pink is truly your color.
For a marriage that may dissolve anytime, why would anyone spend so much on a dress?
- Are you happy?
- Very happy.
I wish you that happiness forever.
Thank you for coming, Oh Yun Hui. We have a special connection, right?
We worked together,  and you are a Hera Club member.
On top of that, you are my beloved wife's high school friend.
And Ro Na was our children's friend.
Why mention Ro Na on a day like today?
I made a mistake. I beg your pardon.
You probably haven't gotten over the sorrow of losing your precious child.
I am okay.  Congratulations.
Seoul Gangnam Police Station
Mr. Ha Yun Cheol, did you really cover up the crime?
Did you really? What was the reason?
Well.  Thank you to everyone from Hera Club who came to celebrate our wedding.
We will live well, loving, respecting and cherishing each other.
Teacher Cheon, please say something.
What's wrong with your expression from earlier?  You look like you're being dragged to a forced labor camp.
I'll say.  Your face is pale and drained of blood.
Are you feeling sick?
- That's—
- She must have been so nervous she couldn't sleep a wink last night.
She's very sensitive.
Are you all right?  It will be over soon.
Still, we've got to have a toast, shall we?
Assemblyman, would you make the toast?
- Awesome.
- Shall I?
In truth, my wedding toast has a way of getting couples divorced and making them enemies.
It's amazing that their marriages imploded within a year.
However, these two people will be different.
Shall we toast?
Beautiful and—
It's my mom.
Miss Mi Ja, Oppa Gyu Jin is in the middle of doing something now.
Huh? Doctor Ha?
Are they saying that he is the real murderer of Bae Ro Na?
What did you say? Who is the real murderer?
He says Dr. Ha is the real killer of Bae Ro Na.
The real killer is Dr. Ha? Dr. Ha, the gentleman we all know?
Hey, turn the TV on right now. Hurry up!
What is this?
A new suspect is arrested in the murder of Bae Ro Na at Chong Ah Arts School.
The identity of the suspect arrested
is shockingly the victim's stepfather.
"Mr. Ha", suspect in Bae Ro Na murder case, is arrested.
Mr. Ha is a CEO at the Korean branch of a well-known foreign pharmaceutical company.
No.
He's also suspected to have paid off a fake culprit to cover his crime.
No!
According to Gangnam police, Mr. Park who was arrested. . .
Why are you shocked?
was identified as the real murderer.
He is a person for whom you have no concern now.
The police arrested Ha where  he attempted to flee.
You. . .
the detailed motive for his crime  is still unknown.
How do you like my wedding present?  I arranged it as a surprise for you.
So far, Ha has neither acknowledged nor denied his crime.
Eun Byeol.  Eun Byeol. Ha Eun Byeol!
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
Take me quickly to the police station.  Hurry.
What about Mom?  Where is she?
You know she's having a wedding ceremony. It's almost over.
What wedding ceremony? With whom?
What do you mean whom? It's Seok Hun's dad, of course.
Are the two really getting married? After she kicked me off  to America?
Didn't you know? I guess I shouldn't have said it.
Eun Byeol, don't cry.
You know I am here.  I will never desert you.
It's Seok Hun.
Don't open the door.
I don't want to see him. Don't let him into the house ever again.
Student Seok Hun is here.
Get out. I don't have anything to say to you.
What's the matter?  Did something happen, you two?
Your memory has returned, hasn't it? You remember, don't you?
Jerk! Was it all a lie?
That we should date and you liked me?
What the heck were you trying to get out of me by telling lies?
I want to hear the truth.
What did you do to Ro Na? Tell me.
Tell me. Tell me now!
I don't know. I didn't do anything.
Stop talking about Ro Na! I'm sick of it!
Teacher Jean, get him out of here now. Right this minute!
You should leave now. Eun Byeol can't get worked up like this.
Over here! Help!
Ha Eun Byeol, I'm going to find out.
I'm going to get to the bottom of why Ro Na died!
Ha Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol.
What am I going to do? I remember everything.
On the day of the Cheong Ah Arts Festival. What I did.
How could he kill his stepdaughter? Then he demanded a divorce and left you!
What a rotten jerk.  Worse off than a dog. Are you alright, Yun Hui?
Ha Yun Cheol has always had bad luck.
How did you end up getting tangled with that piece of shit?
Gangnam Police Station
Yun Hui! Let's get you divorced immediately!
I can get you about 100 million in alimony.
I still can't believe it. How could he do such a thing even for Eun Byeol's sake?
He must've done it because of Eun Byeol. She and Ro Na were no ordinary rivals.
No way. Did he harm Ro Na to get Eun Byeol the grand prize?
The day Ro Na became that way was the day of the Cheong Ah Arts Festival.
That's why he's scary. How unfortunate for Eun Byeol.
A murderer for a dad, and a con artist for a mom.
Chairman Ju, did you really have no idea?
Not at all. This is all very shocking to me as well.
Is it true that Ha Yun Cheol put you up to make a false confession?
Yes, with five million in cash and on the condition that he'll treat my sick daughter.
You aren't the killer, are you? Who put you up to this?
- Was it Ha Yun Cheol?
- No. Nothing like that ever happened.
I- I'm the murderer.
You're not going to tell the truth till the end.
Everything..
he made me do it.
He said he'll provide for my family for the rest of their lives.
So I had no choice. I'm sorry.
Yun Cheol, do you admit to the murder of Bae Ro Na?
I do.
Bae Ro Na..
I killed her.
The reporters are watching. So I can't give you a lot of time.
I understand.
Thank you so much, Captain.
Eun Byeol's dad.
What happened?
Why are you here? People will get suspicious.  Leave quickly.
Ju Dan Tae must have threatened Mr. Park. I thought marrying him would take care of everything.
I never would've thought he would do something like this.
I thought he might.  What about Eun Byeol? Did she leave?
She came home. Teacher Jean said she's with her.
- It's dangerous for her to be here! Hurry and send her to the States.
- You worry about yourself!
Just hold your ground and say no.
I'll see Mr. Park and persuade him to reverse himself somehow.
I already admitted to the crime.
Are you crazy? Are you really trying to be a murderer?
It's true that I wanted to kill her.
I thought about doing it a few times and went to her hosptial room.
I couldn't bring myself to do it.
But it drove me crazy because I felt it was my fault that Ro Na died.
In a way, I'm glad that things turned out this way.
Do you think I married Ju Dan Tae only to see you like this?
Don't worry about me. Just get your head straight.
Ju Dan Tae won't stop here. He'll drag Eun Byeol into this anytime.
That jerk. I'm going to kill him.
I'm willing to take on this burden.
You just protect Eun Byeol. You can do that, right?
Seoul Gangnam Police Station
How do you feel?
Now that your ex-husband is a criminal.
I wondered. While falling for Ha Yun Cheol again,
why would you still go through with the wedding with Ju Dan Te?
Who says I was falling for him?
I wasn't.
I suppose I no longer have the reason to dirty my own  hands with blood.
Since Ju Dan Te will give your family a nice send-off to Hell.
What?
With Ha Yun Cheol sitting in prison, do you think your daughter will be safe?
That'll only ruin you. The truth won't change.
What are you saying?
Well then, I'm off to see a detective.
He's offering a briefing on Ro Na's real killer.
Just how many more times will the real killer change?
Don't tell me . . .
Does she know?
Are you back? I hear Dr. Ha is at the police station.
What's Eun Byeol doing?
She won't come out of her room. Clearly, she's more shocked knowing her mother is married.
Why did you tell her that? She has enough to deal with already. What was the hurry?
Apparently, Eun Byeol has her memory back.
What was that again?
Eun Byeol remembers the day of the Cheong Ah Arts Festival.
She came back home alone early in her blood-stained dress.
How did you know that, Teacher Jean?
There's no secret between Eun Byeol and me.
Didn't you know? She's much closer to me than to you, her mom.
But relax.
I'm on Eun Byeol's side. Whatever I saw, I didn't see it.
Hi, Eun Byeol.
Sorry I didn't tell you about the wedding in advance.
- Mom—
- I don't want to hear it.
I should study and go to Seoul National University like you want me to.
Look at me when you talk to me.
Why aren't you asking about your dad? Aren't you curious?
I heard he killed Ro Na. He committed a crime, so he should be punished.
What?
What did you just say?
It was all over on the news. That Dad confessed.
Isn't this what Mom and Dad wanted? That's why you erased all my memories.
Do you really?
Do you really have your memories back?
Did you think you could wipe out my memories?
You should've done a clean job and erased them all for real!
Did you expect a thank-you from me since Dad turned himself in, instead of me?
Is that really the way you should talk?
Do you have any idea of the things your mom and dad did for you?
When did I ever ask you to do them? I never wanted you to.
You and Dad did what you did on your own. So why hit me?
I'm much tougher than you think.
Why bother feeding me the medicine? I would've gladly forget it if you'd asked me to.
- Ha Eun Byeol!
- What!
Didn't you know that I'm a monster?
On the day you left my grandpa and ran away, I was the one who fled from him as he was dying in the rain.
I was memorizing English words even at his funeral!
How could I not go crazy and be sane? It's you who made me this way.
Still, I didn't tell a soul,
regardless how I hated you for killing my grandpa.
Because you're my mom.
Because I had to protect you, I kept my mouth shut!
How could you marry Seok Hun's dad?
Didn't you know that I'm fond of Seok Hun?
What? What do you mean you're fond of Seok Hun?
Mom, what the hell do you know about me?
Apart from my grades, academic performance and demerits, you know nothing about me.
Get out. Out!
Out already!
Get out! Get out!
Eun Byeol, no!
No!
Let go!
Eun Byeol! No!
Mom's wrong!
Mom did wrong. Please don't do this, Eun Byeol!
- Mom did wrong.
-  Mommy!
The truth is I'm so scared.
Now I'm going to be taken to the police station.
My life is all over now.
No. There's got to be a way. Do I look like someone who can't keep you safe?
I won't ever let you and your dad get hurt. Trust me.
I really didn't mean to kill her.
I mean it. I remember it clearly now.
I picked up the trophy in rage.
The next thing I knew Bae Ro Na rolled down the stairs.
I heard the ringtone of a cell phone somewhere,
and that woke me up.
Did you hear a ringtone of a cell phone?
I keep hearing the ringtone in my ears, and it drives me crazy.
Mi, re, sol, fa, mi, mi, mi, re, si.
Then . . .
- Are you saying there was someone else?
- I don't know.
I got so scared I ran away.
If I'd moved Ba Ro Na to the hospital quickly, she wouldn't have died, right?
I can't believe she died when she was hit on her shoulder.
Shoulder? Was it her shoulder? Not her head?
I'm positive it was her shoulder.
Ro Na died from her head wound after being hit with
the trophy.
No, I didn't hit her head.
- I'm positive.
- Are you sure you remember it correctly?
I remember it so clearly now it gives me the creeps!
Why don't you believe me?
Tell me everything. All the details.
About what happened on that day. From the beginning.
Slowly. And everything.
Na Ae Gyo's relationship with  CEO Jeong Du Man was more than a casual business relationship.
There's something else.
What is this key for?
- Have you been waiting for long?
- Are you coming in only now?
Heavy traffic on the roads.
So did you get Oh Yun Hui's land?
In fact, I'm going to start negotiating tomorrow.
I'm curious about something.
When did you quit smoking?
Didn't I tell you?
I couldn't stop coughing for a long time. So I quit.
Did you?
Good for you.
Perhaps, it's because I am seeing you after a long time,
something about you is not quite familiar.
When you hold your wine glasses,
you always use your left hand. Now I see you're using your right.
You used to get mad at me, saying I made you use your right hand like Sim Su Ryeon.
I've lived all my life imitating Sim Su Ryeon. I guess I've grown used to using my right.
Right.
When you confirm things, does that make you feel better?
It's not like that. I was standing the entire time at the wedding.
You know about my suspicions. I have the habit of confirming and yet confirming again.
You're even more appealing to me today, Na Ae Gyo.
Should I stay the night here?
It's your wedding night. Don't give your wife a reason to get at you.
You should learn self-control to get Cheong Ah Group in your hands.
Staying out on your wedding night?  How inconsiderate.
Isn't this a marriage in form only anyway?
What nonsense.
I'm fully ready to be happy with you.
Don't touch me.
Owing to your suprise gift, Eun Byeol couldn't go to America.
For the time being, I'll stay in my place with Eun Byeol.
I came to tell you that.
Your place? I'm quite hurt.
Our marriage's registered, so we're officially a couple. And this is your home.
When your home is here, where do you say you're going?
As you want, I'll give you Cheong Ah Construction.
I'll just think I got struck out by a fradulent marriage and a big chunk of alimony.
In return, give back to me Eun Byeol's necklace.
Cheon Seo Jin, clearly, you got it wrong big time. I have the winning streak here.
It isn't time for you to be barking like a dog.
You crazy bastard, just give me the necklace!
This is the manual of our marital arrangements.
Read and follow them carefully.
Manual of Marital Arrangements:
Handle my children's college admission while I handle their discipline. Send Ha Eun Byeol abroad.
I'll have you handle all the household affairs in the penthouse.
Use separate rooms. Detailed daily report.
I dismissed  the helpers already.
Impeccable public appearances. No helpers. Daily rising at 5 a.m.
- What?
- To play the role of my children's new stepmom faithfully,
I figured it'd be better for you to not have helpers around.
Oh, naturally, you can't see Eun Byeol without my permission.
Are you crazy?
Eun Byeol is my daughter, and now she has only me to take care of her.
See if I care!
Why should I concern myself with Ha Yun Cheol's kid?
Did you already forget what happened to Sim Su Ryeon when she tried to protect her girl?
So sorry. I lost it again.
This is why you should listen to me.
I've been thinking.
The Cheong Ah Medical has quite substantial business potential.
Why don't you hand that over to me as well?
What are you? A gangster?
Hands off on Cheong Ah Medical and its Foundation!
Why are you getting mad?
I'm too scared to even talk to you, Ahjumma.
Who the hell are you really?
You eyed on my wealth from the beginning. Didn't you?
Obviously, you see me as some pushover.
I'm the eldest daughter of Cheong Ah, Cheon Seo Jin.
I won't give you a dime more than Cheong Ah Construction!
Be grateful for my generosity and get lost.
Mind your manners.
I'm warning you, Ahjumma.
I want a divorce at once. I can't live even a day with you. Proceed with the paperwork now!
I  decide when to meet and separate. How many times must I remind you, stupid woman!
It's you, stupid!
Did you think I'll go down alone?
I'll tell the world you killed Sim Su Ryeon. You trash, murderer!
Ahjumma, you've got to learn some manners.
Let go!
Let go! You damn trash! Let go!
Let go! Let go!
What?
Are you scared?
Hence you've got to watch your mouth.
Sim Su Ryeon, too, died acting up crazy. She didn't know better just like you.
But I say my fun with you will be different from what I had with Sim Su Ryeon.
Golden Real Estate
Specializing in Cheonsu District Investment Consulting
I'm Hwang Geum Bong.
You become rich when you're with Golden Real Estate.
I want to buy the real estate at Number 27 in Cheonsu District.
A number of people have  already expressed their interest in the property.
About fifteen people have already put down their down payments.
Can I interest you in another property?
No need.
It must be the one at Number 27.
I've come from here.
You know him, our chairman?
Cheong Ah Group Chair: Ju Dan Te
Oh, Chairman Ju Dan Te.
You already know we have seventy percent of the land in Cheonsu District.
There's a way we can help each other out.
What do you think?
Are you in?
Go and check what the circumstance is.
Understood.
Let me make this clear for you.
I have no intention of turning my back on Ju Dan Te. So stop stalking.
If I see you ever again, I'm taking you to Ju Dan Te.
You will never.
If that was your intention, you would've already exposed my identity to Ju Dan Te.
Do you want me to?
Should I live up to your expectation?
Be honest. The truth is you can't trust Ju Dan Te either.
He's a man who mistreates his children and killed his wife. Do you want to die like Sim Su Ryeon?
Quit butting in. If I live or die, what do you care?
Why do you want to buy Number 27 in Cheonsu District?
Use me for whatever the reason is.
You won't be able to buy the land without me.
Because I own it.
I have no business joining forces with someone like you.
I put my life on the line for money.
I'll wipe out anyone in the way of what I'm trying to do.
I put my life on the line for this.
The wrongful death of my daughter.  I will avenge her blood.
I'll wipe out anyone who gets in the way of this.
Na Ae Gyo suggested auctioning Number 27 in Cheonsu for the highest price.
Auction?
Why bother with an auction?
Let go!
Come!
- Come down!
- Let go! Let go!
Let go!
I said let go!
This is the only place you deserve in the penthouse.
This is for the transfer of the ownership of Cheong Ah Group.
You won't take one step out of here until you sign it. Got it?
Say hello to her.
Ju Dan Te! Open the door!
Ju Dan Te!
Did you think you'd be okay when you betrayed me?
For what you did to me,
I'll pay you back.
You can look forward to it.
Ju Dan Te! Open the door! Ju Dan Te!
Ju Dan Te!
Sim Su Ryeon.
Is this your revenge?
By handing over to me a rotten trash like Ju Dan Tae?
Seoul Gangnam Police Station
I won't be long.
We're still married on paper,
so I thought I should come and see you for once at least.
Did you hate my Ro Na that much?
To the point of wanting to kill her?
I don't plan on making excuses.
I did it all for Eun Byeol.
What's so wrong about wanting to protect my child?
You would've done the same.
You're right. I was like that, too.
I did anything  as long as it was for Ro Na.
But with the passage of time, I realized.
That if you commit a sin, you'll somehow be punished.
No matter how much you deny or run from it, it'll catch up with you in the end.
Don't fool yourself into thinking you made the best choice for Eun Byeol.
What about my Eun Byeol?
She didn't do anything wrong.
See? Our divorce paper. I'm going to turn it in today.
Now really,
we have to part ways.
Even if it was for a short time, you and Ro Na
I wished happiness for you two.
I was foolish.
My Ro Na
is just like you.
That's why she was so affectionate.
What?
To make certain you get the most severe sentence,
I'm going to do whatever I can starting now.
I'll make you regret to the point where you tear at your own heart.
You  must.
Because you sent your own child to death.
Wh- what are you saying now?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you this sooner.
But still, I'm much relieved.
Since Ro Na left without knowing anything.
If she'd known the person who killed her was her own birth father,
how much would her heart have been torn into shreds.
Oh Yun Hui, what are you doing?
I have one last favor to ask of you.
Go to our Ro Na and
tell her just once with all your sincerity that you're sorry.
Your daughter's gone not ever being cared for as a child should've been.
I feel so sorry for her.
At least, you can do that much, right?
Oh Yun Hui, tell me so I can understand.
You're lying, right? You're lying to make me miserable!
I ask that of you.
Oh Yun Hui, don't go!
What are you saying right now?
Yun Hui, Yun Hui, it's not true.
Yun Hui, stop it now. What are you saying?!
Yun Hui, don't go! Don't go, Oh Yun Hui!
What are you saying!
Oh Yun Hui! Don't go!
What are you saying now!
Get the smartest kids from the law firm.
Make sure they're on standby to go straight into Ha Yun Cheol's defense.
They say you really don't know what's in the heart of a man.
How could Doctor Ha do that?
Did he want to divorce Oh Yun Hui because of his guilt of having killed her daughter?
Seriously, he gives me the creeps.
Do you really think a nerd like him could kill a person?
He hardly has what it takes.
Why are you suddenly saying something different now?
Earlier, you were the loudest calling Ha Yun Cheol a rotten bastard.
Well, that's because
Oh Yun Hui was next to me, but in any case,
he's not the type to kill someone.
I'm building a team of defense lawyers for Ha Yun Cheol.
Only the top-notch lawyers from my father's firm.
Are you crazy?
What if the word gets out that you helped such a shameless man?
Your re-election will be off the table!
Didn't you see yesterday?
Cheon Seo Jin ran out of her own wedding seeing the news. What could that mean?
She's willing to risk her entire wealth if it's for Ha Yun Cheol.
It's exactly that. This great opportunity
should be seized by our law firm.
Do you think Teacher Cheon was shot in the head or something?
Why would she risk everything she has for her ex-husband?
I have a feeling.
That with this one chance, I, Gyu Jin
will be filthy rich. That kind of feeling.
Feeling, my ass.
Just drink this.
We're the only people who don't use helpers in Hera Palace.
That's why I'm trying to figure out ways to make money.
Once Cheonsu District explodes in value, we'll also move up to the 130th floor
and into the penthouse.
The penthouse? Really?
Say, we get about five apartments.
The monthly rent alone there is about two or three million.
Gyu Jin!
Cheers!
That's why we need to go all in on this.
Noona. I need money.  Every day the price of land is going up,
but I am dying without a down payment.
Why are you so lovable?
Is this  the trend these days?
Is this the furniture company that Sim Su Ryeon used to run?
The famous Number 27 Cheonsu District.
It's pretty big.
I've always wanted to come here once.
I'm starting to want it.
I want to try running it.
The sales are respectable. It's a business place everyone wants.
Did something good happen today?
You even brought me to a place like this.
This is my apology for jumping down your throat yesterday.
Everything is going perfectly according to my plan.
I've already got Cheong Ah Construction in my hand.
I think I'll easily have Cheong Ah Medical, too.
How are you doing with the purchase of the land? Going well?
-  I'm thinking to raise the price.
- How?
To make people flock with the smell of money,
I pulled a little prank.
The price of land isn't decided but made.
Something we've been doing all this time.
This is Na Ae Gyo I know.
Congratulations, Darling.
You're on the verge of realizing the business of your life time, Ju Dan Te Village.
You also won't need to live in hiding any longer,
and live as Na Ae Gyo with confidence.
This.
Here.
What is this?
A gift?
What the-, you startled me. What is this?
Cheon Seo Jin's lifeline.
Until the house is settled, I want you to have it.
Cheon Seo Jin is feverishly looking everywhere for this.
Is this necklace the evidence?
Does Cheon Seo Jin also know?
Knows what?
That her daughter isn't the killer.
What are you talking about?
Why are you so surprised?
Who are you trying to fool?
Cheon Seo Jin is more naive than I thought.
As if on cue, when you lusted after Cheong Ah Group the most,
Cheon Seo Jin's daughter killed someone.
Was that really a coincidence, you think?
Who most benefited from that incident?
It's you.
Did you kill her?
Na Ae Gyo!
28th Cheong Ah Arts Festival
Teacher Ma Du Gi
Teacher Ma, how did it go?
I'm sorry. The judges were so involved I couldn't do anything.
Get to the point. To the point first.
Who gets the grand prize?
The grand prize winner is Bae Ro Na.
Bae Ro Na? Why to a bitch like her—
Hey, Ma Du Gi, you. Are you doing things right?
Seok Gyeong can still win the gold trophy—
She can easily get the stupid gold trophy without your help.
Our deal ends here. Got it?
She bothers me just like her mother. Bae Ro Na, that annoying little bitch.
Na Ae Gyo?
Ringtone: Dvořák: Symphony No. 9 ‘From the New World’, IV. Allegro con fuoco
Ha Eun Byeol?
What is that?
Mister.
Mister, please call my mom.
I'm hurt right now.
Of all people, why is it you?
Out of all people, why do you win the grand prize?
If it weren't for you, the free pass to Seoul National University could be my Seok Gyeong's.
Why are you being like this?
I'm wondering if you can concede a little for Seok Gyeong's sake.
You see, I love my daughter
very much.
Please save me. Please.
Please save me.
At the sight of you, I always felt unlucky.
But still, this is because you've conceded.
Ha Eun Byeol. Who knew?  You would help me out like this.
If this works out right, I can get rid of the two annoying bitches at once.
I'm indeed a lucky guy.
I brought the most similar looking suit from the car.
Good.
Delete CCTV files?
Where have you been? You've gone a while.
Why are there so many people at the bathroom?
Now, I'll welcome Chairwoman Cheon Seo Jin  onto the center of the stage to announce the judges' decisions.
Someone is dead!
Je Ni!
Fire Alarm
There is a person here!
No, no, not here!
Don't go over here!
Do you think I killed her?
Bae Ro Na? Why such an erroneous assumption?
Am I really wrong thinking that?
Is there anyone who knows Ju Dan Tae better than I do?
Try fooling a ghost.
Either way, Bae Ro Na proved to be a pretty useful child.
As much as Min Seol Ah.
Because those children who were nobody died at a time they did,
I could so easily get my hands on Sim Su Ryeon and Cheon Seo Jin's assets.
Are you listening, Oh Yun Hui?
Voice Spy
Ju Dan Tae, was it you, who killed my Ro Na?
Who on earth did it? What did all of you do to such a young child?
Welcome to hell!
Do you see now what kind of a man my father is?
That's why I warned you all along  not to go through with the damn wedding.
You better be careful.
You might not be able to come out of here alive.
Like my mom.
I keep hearing that sound in my ears I feel like I'm going crazy.
Mi, fa, sol, fa, mi, mi, mi, re, si.
Na Ae Gyo
Na Ae Gyo?
Eun Byeol. Eun Byeol, Wake up. Quick.
Wake up! Quick!
Mom, when did you get here?
Sing the ringtone you said you heard  that day.
You said you heard a ringtone on the stone stairs. Sing it as you remember it, quick.
Why?
Just sing, quick!
Mi, fa, sol, fa, mi, mi, mi, si, re, mi.
What are you doing? What's wrong?
That bastard was there. I'm certain of that ringtone.
You aren't allowed to come to the 85th floor without the Chairman's permission.
Take her back to the penthouse immediately.
It's okay, Eun Byeol. It'll be okay.
Let go! I'll go on my own two feet!
Mom. Let go!
Let go! Let go!
If you show up before my daughter one more time, I'll kill you then with my own hands.
You need to be up by 5 a.m. tomorrow.
You won't be able to get much sleep. But you'll still be making my favorite soup, right?
I hate Teacher Cheon, but what I hate even more is seeing Dad happy.
If you're happy after killing someone, that's cheating.
Auction: Number 27 Cheonsu District
You're making it look too obvious.
How much cash did you prepare?
Why would I tell you that? Everyone here is my competitors.
Do you even know who the owner of this land is?
Of course, it's Chairman Ju. This is the furniture company Su Ryeon used to run.
My goodness, your information is still way down there.
The owner of this place is no other than Oh Yun Hui.
Yun Hui?
Why didn't she tell me? We're the next-door neighbors.
When it comes to money and land, there can be no best friends.
The rumor is that you're awfully close to Oh Yun Hui. I guess not.
I thought it was the friendship of the century!
Mind your business. You two stick together because you have no friends.
That's not true.
-That's not true.
-You're jealous.
Mother,  how much did we bring?
This much.
Only 3 million in won?
Try adding another zero.
- Then thirty  million?
- Hey!
How thoughtless are you? You might as well sing it through an amplifier.
Is this property worth as much as thirty million?
According to Gyu Jin, it's worth more than thirty million,
so I borrowed money by putting up my Gangnam building as collateral.
Don't be so obvious, okay?
All Gangnam speculators with money have gathered themselves.
Dash to 2nd Gangnam
Since Ju Dan Te raised the stakes of the auction, sell it at the highest price.
I wonder how much Ju Dan Tae is willing to bet. He'll try not to lose the land.
Just wait, Ju Dan Tae.
Even if I have to twist your neck, I'll take back what you took from me.
He has a different necktie and a collar.
He changed his clothes.
Why?
Secretary Do, I need you to find someone for me.
Her name is Na Ae Gyo. She's probably someone close to Ju Dan Tae.
Find out what their relationship is. Quickly.
So many of you expressed your interest in the property at Number 27 Cheonsu District.
Therefore, I invited all of you at one place like this.
Only to one of the super VIPs especially invited here,
I'm going to sell the property at  Number 27.
On behalf of the owner of the property, I'll begin the auction.
Starting bid is 10 billion won.
- Eleven billion!
- Twelve billion!
Thirteen billion!
- Fifteen billion!
- Here is 15 billion!
- Twenty billion!
- Here is 20 billion!
Twenty billion and one hundred million!
- Twenty-three billion.
- Twenty-three billion!
- Twenty-five billion!
- Here is 25 billion!
Has Je Ni's mom earned that much? Darn it.
- Thirty billion!
-  Thirty billion was the bid!
Why won't you give in already?
For whose sake?
Thirty-three billion!
Is that woman insane?
Mother-in-law, let's give up. We're already beyond our limit.
Please let go of our greed.
Thirty-three billion. No more bidding?
Shall we close the bid? It's sold at 33 billion.
If I give up at this point, I'm not Lee Gyu Jin anymore.
It'll be okay if we sell it to Chairman Ju and double the price.
Forty billion!
Forty billion?
Honey!
He has some gall.
I'll buy it at 40 billion.
Forty billion was the bid!
Would everybody else give up?
Well, well, alright.  At 40 billion,
I'm going to say it's sol—
Fifty billion.
Fifty billion?
Come on, there is a standard market price.
Ten billion in difference?  It's too big a gap.
However good the location is, that's absurd!
You'll lose money when you sell it later.  Are you an amateur?
Even if I lose money, it's my money I lose.  So worry about yourselves.
How about it?  If no one else is going to bid, let's stop here.
The remaining balance is supposed to be paid right away. Where could I borrow 50 billion?
I give up.
Come on, Mom!
By the way, who are you?
Are you an individual investor?
I'm from Cheong Ah Group's Investment and Development Team.
Cheong Ah Group?  Are you sent by Chairman Ju?
What is this? Are you playing us now with money?
It's 5 billion in won for the down payment.
We'll draw up the actual contract with the owner present tomorrow.
I'll pay off 45 billion, the remaining balance tomorrow as well.
The property is sold at 50 billion!
Who on earth is she?
She said she was from Cheong Ah Group.
In the end, Chairman Ju is going to get all, even the golden land.
He sucks.
Ju Dan Tae, that lowlife.
I hated seeing him on his high horse, and I wanted to stomp him good.
I'm so upset.
But doesn't she seem quite familiar somehow?
She has a cold air about her and looks very familiar.
I can't quite put my finger on where I've seen her.
I know, right?
Yeah.
Finally, we got the property at Number 27.
No matter how I think, 50 billion is too expensive. Fifty million would've been a windfall.
All the land we own will skyrocket in price like crazy starting tomorrow.
Cheonsu District will be hit by a storm.  I guarantee it.
My car's here. Hanging up now.
Do you still have something to say?
I keep thinking you don't seem a bad person.
But seeing how crazy you are about money, I can tell you really are Ju Dan Tae's person.
I no longer expect anything of you, nor will I come looking for you anymore.
I hope you never get in my way again.
What a pity for Su Ryeon's sake.
She was too gentle a person to have been used and killed by a person like you.
I hope you live the rest of your life filled with guilt towards her.
What is this?
You said you wanted to see her.
Follow me.
Hurry and get in, Cheon Seo Jin!
Will you be okay?
I have a secret place that even Father doesn't know about. Don't worry about me.
I'm helping you because of Ro Na's mom.
What are you doing? Hurry, get in!
Get in quick!
Why did you want to see me?
Oh Yun Hui, save me.
Please save me, Yun Hui.
What are you saying? Explain so I can understand.
The person who caused Ro Na's death is indeed Eun Byeol.
Eun Byeol did it.
I've committed a grave sin to you and Ro Na, too.
But there's a trap.
Ju Dan Tae is somehow involved in all this.
I need you if I want to catch Ro Na's real killer.
Help me, Yun Hui.
Advanced Mathematics
Seok Hun.
It's me.
These are the pictures of Na Ae Gyo's whereabouts for the past few days.
She's made no special outings other than to a restaurant.
You don't need to keep an eye on her anymore.
Understood.
Wait.
I feel so sorry for  Sim Su Ryeon.
She was too gentle a person to have been used and killed by someone like you.
Thank you.
For still remembering me.
What are you doing?
You're Su Ryeon!
You're indeed Su Ryeon!
Don't think about running away anymore.
I'm sorry for recognizing you so late.
War in Life: Penthouse II
How beautiful now that you acknolwedged you've lost.
Sim Su Ryeon is dead.
I couldn't forgive myself for leaving for the airport ahead of you.
I'll never forgive you.
I can't guarantee Eun Byeol's safety.
Please let me kill him myself.
Didn't Sim Su Ryeon also know before she died?
The game's over.
Use the penthouse as a collateral and get a loan.
Did Na Ae Gyo deceive the Chairman?
I'm going to kill Na Ae Gyo!
Na Ae Gyo died last night.