And now, to announce the results of the judges' decisions,
I'd ike to welcone Chairwoman Cheon Seo Jin on to the center stage.
Episode 6
Let's welcome her with a round of applause.
Where on earth is Eun Byeol?
I saw her taking a bunch of pills earlier. What if she fainted somewhere?
- I don't see Bae Ro Na either.
- The bronze award for vocal music goes to
Cheong Ah Arts   senior students, No Ji Ah and Cho Bo Mi.
Why isn't Ro Na picking up her phone?
- The winners are being announced.
- Hey, be quiet.
The award ceremony goes on just fine without her. So will you pipe down already?
You did really great today.
You were totally cool.
Here.
Thanks.
Do you want to grab some pasta tomorrow?
I'll wait by the gate after school.
I'm busy tomorrow.
Then I'll wait until you come.
I missed you too, Ro Na.
The highlight of the 28th Cheong Ah Arts Festival.
Given to the most divine voice
in vocal music.
The grand prize goes to...
What I want is the trophy for the grand prize.
So, it doesn't matter whose name is in the envelope.
You just need to say my name.
Student Bae Ro Na.
Excuse me! There, there, there!
Someone!
Someone is dead!
I'm telling you someone is dead!
28th Cheong Ah Arts Festival
Min Seol Ah.
I'm sorry.
That I took your place.
Forgive my mom.
You don't need to be sorry.
Here, this, this way!
Down there! There!
- What's going on?
- Oh, my.
What's going on?
Oh my!
What happened?
What's that?
Oh, Ro Na! What happened to you?
Ro Na!
Ro Na, Ro Na, please open your eyes! Why are you like this?
You're scaring me. Please open your eyes! What's wrong, Sweetie?
Put her down, down, huh?
Do something! Please!
Please help my child!
Ro Na!
Hey, Ro Na! Can you hear me?
You've got to stay awake!
Ambulance! Ambulance, quickly!
Hurry, hurry!
Hello? Yes.
Send an ambulance immediately. Please hurry!
We're at Cheong Ah Arts School.
A child is hurt. A child
is losing a lot of blood—
Ro Na!
Oh my, Ro Na!
Min Hyeok. Min Hyeok!
No, no!
Don't worry. She's going to be okay.
Don't look.
She has no pulse, and she isn't breathing.
Step back, back!
- Someone  killed her.
- Ro Na
Ro Na, please!
This- a homicide. Isn't this murder?
Shut up! My daughter isn't dead.
Why should my Ro Na be dead?
Ro Na is still warm!
She's still warm!
Close the school gate right now!
Stop anyone from leaving  until the police gets here!
None of you will take even a single step until the police arrives!
What are you doing, not closing the school gate?
Yes!
What's this noise?
Fire! Fire!
Teacher, Students!
There's a person down here!
No, my baby!
No!
What about Eun Byeol? Didn't she go with you to the back?
I said not to leave!
Where did the fire break out?
No!
Will she be okay?
I'll meet you up as soon as I can bring some order to the scene.
You'll be okay, right?
Hurry and go!
911 Emergency Vehicle
Be careful not to touch a thing.
Anything can be evidence.
Who is it there?
Aren't you hungry?
Can I get you anything?
No, I don't want anything.
How come did you lock the door?
Are you in a bad mood?
I said I didn't need anything! I'm fine!
I just need to rest a little.
I'm just exhausted.
Okay. Get some rest then.
No, no.
- Check the blood!
- Here we go.
Get the defibrillator ready. Charge it to 120 joule.
Shot!
No.
Get the operating room open immediately and get a hold of the Neurosurgery Unit!
Quick, get her to the operating room!
Mommy is sorry. I was wrong, Ro Na!
Don't leave me!
Did anything come up?
So many people rushed out all at once.
In fact, it's going to be difficult to locate unique footprints and other evidence.
How long are they going to keep us in here?
We're busy people, you know!
If she were your daughter, would you say the same?
Someone would think she's your biological daughter.
What makes you feel so guilty that you want to run away without getting questioned? You're hiding something, right?
What did you just say?
Seriously!
Come on, you're an assemblyman. Do something!
Hey! Let go!
How dare you two treat an assemblyman in this way?
Chairman Ha, do you know what time it is now?
Let us go home already!
All the people in here are well known enough to be recognized simply by their names.
You shouldn't worry about any of us running away. And we're happy to answer any—
A child!
A child was hurt.
She is on the brink of death right at this moment.
I'm going to catch the culprit myself.
Whoever that may be, I'll pursue them till the end.
I'll bring them to the justice they deserve.
Not even a single ant can take one foot out of this room without an alibi.
So I advise you all to cooperate as best as you can.
I'd been in my seat in the auditorium since the moment the Festival began.
I only went to the bathroom once. You can verify that with the people here.
I, too, was seated  in the same row as my husband the whole time.
I heard you arrived first at the scene, Chairman Ju.
Is being fast a crime too?
And strictly speaking, it was the security guard who first came to the scene.
I ran there after I heard Security Guard Park screaming.
Every single one of us
saw each other in the auditorium. Am I right or what?
- Yes, that's true.
- We even drank coffee together while the judges made their decisions, right?
- Yes.
- We were together to the end.
Je Ni said Eun Byeol was nowhere to be seen in the waiting room.
Shouldn't you be looking into that first?
Now that I think about it, why haven't we seen Eun Byeol since earlier?
I didn't see her in the athletic field, either.
Eun Byeol wasn't feeling well, so she went home early.
Did you say she went home?
Did she go home without hearing who the grand prize winner was?
That doesn't sound like Eun Byeol.
She was a strong contender for the grand prize. She wouldn't have left even if she fainted.
I sure hope Eun Byeol didn't take her medicine on a day like today.
You all know Eun Byeol depends on the power of her medicine every time she performs, right?
She wasn't feeling well because of her nerves.
Don't tell me. Are you suspecting my  Eun Byeol?
No one should be ruled out.
Neither you, Ms. Cheon nor Eun Byeol.
Don't worry.
I'll check on Eun Byeol the moment I get home and have her undergo the questioning herself.
Your daughter, Eun Byeol, too.
Are you happy now?
Let's get the people with clean alibis go home first.
No Entry
It's the wing that came off the trophy which is the suspected weapon of the crime.
Did you say a trophy?
The victim had the marks of getting hit by a trophy once each on her shoulder and head.
Most of the blood loss occurred especially in her head wound.
Where is the rest of the trophy?
We were unable to find the rest of the trophy at the crime scene.
As a priority, we'll zero in on locating the crime weapon that's missing for now.
And I suggest closing the school for the time being.
With the authority I have as a chairperson, I'll do my best to cooperate.
Do you happen to know if anyone in school was on bad terms with the victim?
Seeing they deliberately set off a false fire alarm to remove the evidence,
I suspect it was someone who knew the school fairly well.
Is there anyone that comes to your mind?
How little do you think of  the great  Cheong Ah Arts School to say a thing like that?
Are you implying we might have tampered with the crime scene?
Nothing like that necessarily.
At any event, I ask for your cooperation.
We will.
Why are you being so sharp?
Do you really keep this up? Are you a cop or something?
Or are you Bae Ro Na's real dad?
Fine, make sure you find the culprit for Bae Ro Na's sake.
Spend all night searching high and low.
Restricted Entry
It belongs to Ro Na.
How is she? Did she wake up?
Are you  Bae Ro Na's guardian? The patient just woke up.
Ro Na?
Ro Na, it's Mom.
Come on, open your eyes.
Ro Na? Ro Na, Mom's here.
It's me, your mom. Can you recognize me?
Ro Na?
Who did this to you? Just who on earth did this to you?
Ro Na.
This is yours. You won the grand prize, Ro Na.
Hurry, you should get up soon and celebrate with me.
Be strong, Sweetheart. Okay?
Be strong. You can do this.
It belongs to Min Seol Ah.
Give that trophy to Seol Ah.
I was so mean to you this whole time.
For that, I'm sorry.
Ro Na?
Ro Na? Ro Na, wake up!
Ro Na! Ro Na! Ro Na! Ro Na!
Hello? Hello!
Somebody! Somebody, come quick!
Ro Na! Please wake up. Please don't die!
Ro Na! Mommy's here, Ro Na, please!
Ro Na, don't die!
Don't die! No, no!
- Ro Na! Don't leave me behind!
-  I'm going to work on her.
It's my fault.  I must have been crazy.  I don't want anything.
Doctor!
- Yun Hui!
- No! No!
Madam!
Ro Na! Ro Na! Don't die!
Ro Na! Don't go! Mommy's sorry!
200 joules, charge!
Ro Na! It's my fault.
No! Ro Na! No!
Why are you still up?
I had something to ask you.
About Ro Na,
did you do that to her?
What are you talking about now?
Why would I do such a thing?
Don't lie to me.
You had something to do with it, I'm sure.
When Min Seol Ah died, and even when Mom died, you acted as though nothing happened just as you do now.
Nevertheless, I know.
That both Mom and Min Seol Ah,
you killed them.
My mom!
Why did you kill her? Why?
Because you wanted to marry someone like her?
Or because she was Min Seol Ah's real mom?
By any chance, if you're doing something bad to harm Ro Na—
I never would've thought my son created such a ridiculous fantasy in his head.
How dare you speak that kind of bullshit to me?
Take your hands off of him!
Neither my brother, nor am I a thing for you. You have no business beating us!
Good timing. I had something to ask you.
Do you know whose necklace this is?
It's Eun Byeol's.
She had it on earlier when she was singing.
Why on earth do you have that with you?
It was on the floor in the auditorium.
You two, go to bed.
Don't touch a thing.
Anything can be evidence.
- Assemblyman—
- When you know I'm an assemblyman, do your job right!
Hey, do you know how much a bundle of spinach is?
So, this belongs to Ha Eun Byeol, huh?
Where is it? I'm sure I put it in here.
Where did I lose it?
Are you in?
You're home late.
Something came up. Did Eun Byeol eat dinner?
She didn't eat. She washed up and went to sleep as soon as she came home.
Probably she didn't have an appetite because she was too tired. It's late, go to bed.
Anyhow, I don't see Eun Byeol's dress.
I'm sure she had it on when she came home, but it's not in her closet.
She must've put it somewhere! How's that important this late in the night?
Right. Get some rest.
No way.
It can't be my Eun Byeol.
It can never be her.
Director Do, how is Bae Ro Na?
What?
Are you sure there is no chance of her waking up?
Really...
Did you do that?
What are you saying? I was throwing it away because I was mad that I didn't get the grand prize.
Then what is this? The blood on the dress?
Tell me everything. Don't leave a single thing out. What did you do to Ro Na?
Is Ro Na... dead?
No, right? There's no way she would die.
She's such a tenacious person!
No, no. No. No.
Get it together and answer my question!
Did you do it?
Tell me, Ha Eun Byeol!
She kept taking my things.
She was always in my sight, and worse, she badmouthed you, Mom.
She said that you slashed her mom's throat.
That you lost to her mom.
But, honestly, I wasn't planning on killing her!
That's the truth. Please believe me!
It's ok. Just pull yourself together.
You've got to get it together, Eun Byeol!
Calm down.
It's all over.
I'm a criminal.
Probably the police will soon come for me, right?
No. I want to go to the police station myself and tell them everything.
That I did it.
College or singing, it's all over for me now!
Hey, I won't let your life messed up. Never!
I won't allow it! I, your mother will protect you.
Whether Bae Ro Na lives or dies,
that's not important. You just need to keep yourself not connected to the incident.
If anyone asks, just say you don't know anything. Understand me?
What if someone saw me?
The CCTVs are all over the school!
I'll take care of it. You don't have to worry about anything.
I'll get rid of this dress too.
Then all is fine. There will be no evidence.
The trophy.
Trophy?
Your trophy for the Cheong Ah Arts Festival.
Where did you put it?
In my locker.
What?
Do Not Enter-POLICE LINE-Under Investigation
Another unfortunate incident occurred yesterday at a profit organization, Cheong Ah Arts School.
At the CAA Festival which is regarded as the most grand tradition of the school,
the female senior student who won the  grand prize
fell into a coma before she could even hold her trophy.
The police are focusing on the possibility of someone committing the crime out of hatred.
They'll narrow down to a suspect out of those who were present at school.
Cheong Ah's chairperson Cheon Seo Jin switched all classes to virtual learning,
and she expressed her wishes to cooperate fully with the investigation.
There is significant damage to her brain. It doesn't look good.
You should prepare yourselves for the worst.
Yun Hui.
This won't do. I'll get you a hospital room, go lie down even for a moment.
I'm fine.
I've got to find the person who did that to my daughter first.
What did the police say? Have they not found any evidence at all?
They're still investigating. But not yet.
The culprit had to be at the school.
How is it that they can't find any evidence? That makes no sense.
It's strange that the fire alarm was falsely activated too.
I  can't trust the police now.
I need to go to the school myself.
What are you going to do when you're in this condition?
Let's trust the police and wait for now.
I asked someone I know to put in a word to the police.
They'll contact us as soon as they find evidence.
I really can't trust anyone.
I'll catch him myself.
Do you think I'll let the people alone who hurt my daughter like that?
Yun Cheol, what am I going to do if Ro Na dies?
What am I going to do if she dies?
I feel like I'm going crazy. What do I do, Yun Cheol?
No, no. My Ro Na.
Please save my Ro Na, Yun Cheol. Please.
Yun Hui, Yun Hui.
Yun Hui! Yun Hui, Yun Hui!
What are you doing? Call Doctor Jeong!
Bring a respirator!
Su Ryeon, don't take my Ro Na.
Kill me, but let my Ro Na live. Please.
- Please.
- Breathe.
Don Giovanni a cenar teco by Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart
Stilnox (Sleeping medication)
M'invitasti e son venuto!
Don't think about anything and sleep.
Have you seen my cell phone?
I got rid of it, just in case. I'll get you a new one.
Don't answer the calls from your  friends for the time being.
Keep in mind. You're going to forget everything in the past.
When you wake up from your sleep, it'll all have gone out of you.
Eun Byeol had it.
The evidence that you killed Eun Byeol's grandfather.
Did you like my video present?
Chairwoman, Cheon Seo Jin?
Which bastard is it?
Don't hide like a coward and show yourself!
So did you forget about it?
I mean my grandfather's accident.
What are you talking about?
I took the medicine because I missed my grandfather so much.
Explain to me in a way I can understand!
Authorized Personnel Only
When did you get here?
Today.
How is Ro Na?
Is she still unconcious?
Cheon Seo Jin and Eun Byeol's movements are suspicious.
Tell me everything you know.
I took this picture at 5 a.m. this morning.
Where is she going that early in the morning?
With a bag in her hand.
The stranger thing is, she didn't have anything when she came back.
Furthermore, she came back with Cheon Seo Jin.
Then by chance...
The trophy... I need to get that trophy back.
It will be the end when that gets discovered.
The police just finished their investigation at the crime scene.
Are you sure?
Apparently, they came to a dead end in finding evidence since their initial investigation failed.
They are withdrawing from the scene, leaving only a minimum number of officers.
Cheon Seo Jin?
Ha Eun Byeol
Did you see that?
Ms. Cheon.
What are you doing here?
Well, what are  you  doing here at this hour?
Were you looking for something in the dark classroom with the lights off?
I'll say. I smell somthing fishy here.
What were you ransacking in there, like a thief?
What do you mean ransacking? Me?
What?
The locker behind you
seems like a perfect place to hide something.
Move aside.
There you go.
Hurry and open them. You start with the ones on the left.
I'll break open the ones from the right.
Wait!
I'll open Ha Eun Byeol's.
What the heck? There's nothing in here.
There's only a few  left.
It's here!
Whose locker is it?
Ju Seok Gyeong! I knew it.
Let's go grab this wrench.
Let's go. Hurry.
What are you doing here?
Let go! I said let go of me!
Do you know who my dad is?
I'm not going!
Dad, where are you? Seok Gyeong is...
Seok Gyeong is being dragged away!
What happened to your hand?
I was in a rush opening the lockers.
How did you know?
Eun Byeol called me.
Were you the one who rang the fire alarm?
No.
I couldn't even imagine then.
Is it really Eun Byeol?
Did our Eun Byeol really do that to Ro Na?
She didn't, right?
I don't want to believe it either.
Why didn't you tell me sooner? You should've told me first!
How could I?
You're Oh Yun Hui's husband now.
I can't believe it. How could she?
How could my Eun Byeol do something like that?
It's already happened.
Even if you don't want to believe it, you have to accept it.
No, no way.
This can't be happening.
You were the one who put the trophy in Seok Gyeong's locker.
That means you don't want Eun Byeol to be arrested either.
As her dad, all you did was disappoint her all the time.
Will you just watch as your daughter's life is getting ruined?
They'll find out Seok Gyeong isn't the true culprit soon enough!
So get it together!
Yun Hui is never going to give up.
She's going to keep searching until she finds the real culprit.
In the end, she's going to find out it's Eun Byeol.
When that happenes, our child's life is over.
Save her. The only person who can save our Eun Byeol
is you.
Eun Byeol's dad, please.
What do you want me to do?
I can't do it anymore.
I feel sorry for Yun Hui.
Seeing Ro Na  in the hospital bed like that is driving me crazy!
I heard there's no hope for Ro Na anyway.
I heard it from Doctor Jeong.
That they'll declare her brain dead tomorrow.
If that's the case, shouldn't the living go on living?
What are you trying to say now?
There's only one way to make Yun Hui give up.
Making someone else the culprit while Seok Gyeong is buying time for us.
Cheon Seo Jin!
For me, right now,
Eun Byeol is the only thing I can see.
I'm only going to think about Eun Byeol. I'm her mom.
And a mom has the responsibility of protecting her child.
If something goes wrong with Eun Byeol, my life is over, too.
Damn it!
Why did you do that to my Ro Na?
Did you hate Ro Na that much?
Just hate me then! Why did you do that to Ro Na when she is innocent?! Why?! Why?!
Ajumma, are you crazy?
Why would I do such a thing?
- Why did you do that?
- What do you think you're doing?
Who are you to accuse my daughter of a crime?
You stay out of this.
Seok Gyeong tried to kill Ro Na.
A trophy with blood on it was found in Student Ju Seok Gyeong's locker.
It can be presumed to be the instrument of this crime, so investigating your daughter was inevitable.
A trophy?
We heard your recent relationship with Bae Ro Na wasn't good, because of the incidents of school violence.
You threw paint on her and even locked her in the bathroom.
- About that—
- That incident is completely different from this.
Seok Gyeong really isn't  the culprit. I can prove it.
Detective, the analysis of the fingerprints on  the trophy just came out.
There were many different fingerprints on the trophy,
but Ju Seok Gyeong's fingerprints were not found.
No Match
I told you. I said it wasn't me!
Someone put it in my locker to mess with me.
Who? Why?
It must be someone holding a grudge against me.
Seok Gyeong is not the culprit.
This is a photo taken in the waiting room right before the announcement of the grand prize.
Here, Seok Gyeong is clearly in the photo.
Will this be enough as conclusive evidence?
And who's missing in the photo?
They are Ro Na and Eun Byeol.
We estimate the time of the incident to be right before the announcement of the grand prize.
So it can't be Ju Seok Gyeong.
How dare you people tarnish our family's good name?
This is defamation.
I won't let this incident go unaddressed.
Let's go.
So Eun Byeol wasn't there.
I just remembered Ms. Cheon picking up a necklace at the crime scene.
A necklace? What did it look like?
It was very elaborate with a large gem.
I think it was a sapphire.
I can't remember it well.
Sapphire?
Didn't you know?
I thought she would've given it to the police as evidence, for sure.
Oh, gosh.
Yun Hui.
Why are you so surprised?
I thought no one was home. Didn't you go to the hospital?
I came to pack a few things.
Where did you go?
To the company. I had a lot of work stacked up because I couldn't go to work for a while.
How was your visit to the police station?
Seok Gyeong's fingerprints were not found on the trophy.
I see. No other evidence was found?
Seok Gyeong didn't do it.
Apparently, someone was trying to frame Seok Gyeong.
Who would do such a thing?
I know, right?
I'll go to be with Ro Na now.
You should rest at home tonight.
Sure.
Yun Hui, tell me if you get too tired. I'll take over at any time.
It's not true, is it, Ha Yun Cheol?
You must never do that to Ro Na. You absolutely mustn't.
Ha Eun Byeol, why did you do that?
Why did you do that to me, Ha Eun Byeol?
Ha Eun Byeol? Why did you do that to me?
Come with me.
Chairwoman isn't home yet.
It doesn't matter. I'm here to see Eun Byeol.
Eun Byeol isn't feeling well right now—
How are you feeling?
I heard you were sick. You really don't look well.
I'm alright.
But... what brings you here?
You heard what happened to my Ro Na, didn't you?
Yes.
I have something to ask you about.
Did you meet Ro Na just before the awards ceremony that night?
No.
I heard you and Ro Na were the only people who weren't in the waiting room.
So where were you then?
I didn't feel well, so I was in the nurse's office.
Really?
You did meet my Ro Na that night, didn't you?
Tell me the truth.
What happened between you two? Hurry and tell me the truth!
What do you think you are doing right now?
How dare you do that to a sick child?
Why is Eun Byeol sick, anyway?
- What?
- Eun Byeol is the only one who avoided the police station with the excuse of being sick.
So I came to ask her directly.
Ha Eun Byeol, answer me. You met with Ro Na that night, didn't you?
Tell me the truth. What did you do to my Ro Na? Hurry and tell me!
I don't know. I don't know.
Stop! Stop tormenting my daughter and get out right now.
Get out! Get out!
You better say what you did to Ro Na!
Come out! Come out!
Are you going around suspecting every kid in Hera Palace?
Seok Gyeong first, and now Eun Byeol?
Seok Gyeong has a firm alibi.
The only one whose alibi hasn't been confirmed is your daughter.
I'm sure the police will confirm it.
Ah, why haven't you returned Eun Byeol's dress yet?
What?
I went to the dress shop earlier, and they told me Eun Byeol's dress was the only one not returned yet.
Can I see her dress?
You've gone insane. Do I have to show even a thing  like that to you?
Yes, I've gone insane.
How could I be in my right mind when my child is lying in that state?
I will have to see that dress. You still have it, don't you?
Why? Do you think there may be blood on that dress?
You like things to be precise, too.
Where is the dress?
Teacher Jin.
Bring Eun Byeol's dress.
Yes, Chairwoman.
Here it is.
Delusional and suspicious.
If you have time for this nonsense, why not spend it nursing your child properly, instead?
Teacher Jin, see the guest out.
28th Cheong Ah Arts Festival
Make another one just like it and make sure I can pick it up tonight, no matter what.
Yes, I understand.
Yun Hui even came into my house and demanded to see Eun Byeol's dress.
She's suspecting our Eun Byeol.
What will we do if everything is found out?
Please, please do something.
Find a solution, please.
Gangnam Police, currently investigating the incident of Miss Bae of Cheong Ah Arts School,
Noona!  Noona!
are focusing on Park who has just turned himself in.
- Noona!
- What, what, what?
For goodness sake, stop yelling.
...was repeatedly humiliated
I can't even go to the bathroom and pee at night.
so became vengeful and on the day of the incident, impulsively...
They're saying the real culprit turned himself in.
I'm talking about the culprit responsible for Ro Na's case.
What! Who is it?
Park, the security guard for 20 years at CAA School
The security guard with the sharp, smiling face.
On the day of the incident, an in-school festival took place. Looking for witnesses.
You mean, Mr. Park?
That makes no sense. He's the nicest man I know. Why would he?
This is why you can't know what's in a man's heart.
Multiple Personality Disorder, something like that.
Though it took a while, it's a relief that the culprit is captured.
Pretended to be the first witness in fear of people's suspicion
If they didn't get the culprit, Oh Yun Hi and Ha Yun Cheol would've gone crazy
and pestered everyone at Hera Palace with their questioning.
Such a damned school. It shows no consideration for its seniors with their college entrance exams ahead.
Still, Mr. Park as the culprit  makes little sense.
The life of the student victim is in danger. Police will reinvestigate  the crime scene.
How could a man too scared to clean up a dead bird do such a thing to a person?
What was your motive? A grudge or financial gain?
I was repeatedly ignored and verbally abused by the child.
So I did it in a moment of anger.
Are you claiming you committed the crime in the heat of passion?
What happened?
How can the security guard be the culprit?
It's okay, Eun Beol. Don't think about anything.
Of all people, why does it have to be Mr. Park?
He was so nice to us.
When I'm this sorry for the man,
how am I supposed to live on?
The Gangnam police investigating the case stated the culprit provided the evidence and the motive of the crime.
In the very near future, the police added
Oh, Mister.
that it'll make the results of its investigation public.
Stop drinking.
Leave me alone. I can't go on like this without getting drunk.
Why didn't you tell me it was Mr. Park?
He was closer to me than my own father.
I know. That's why I'm doing my best.
His sentence will be reduced as much as possible.
I can't bear this feeling of being a monster.
I'm going crazy because I feel like this is all my fault.
You can mock me all you want. When this is how I'd end up,
you probably want to curse me for having hidden Eun Byeol from you.
Yeah. You might have been right.
I can't stand myself either.
Stop drinking. Nothing's going to change with you being like this.
Every night, I dream of Ro Na waking up.
I'm so anxious I'm going insane.
If Bae Ro Na wakes up, everything will have been in vain.
Our Eun Byeol will get arrested by the police.
I'm scared. I'm so scared.
I'm so scared I'm going to die.
Eun Byeol and I will die because either of us can endure this.
Pull yourself together.
That's the only way we can protect our Eun Byeol.
What are you doing?
Can you really protect Eun Byeol?
I'm going to protect her with my own life.
Our Eun Byeol.
Even if that means you have to kill Bae Ro Na?
Answer me and say that you'll protect her.
Say that you'll never let Eun Byeol's life be ruined, no matter what.
If you can't do it, I will.
Even if I have to kill Bae Ro Na with my own hands,
I'll save my Eun Byeol.
Cheon Seo Jin!
It's because we lived our lives all wrong.
Both of us are responsible.
Even if there's one chance out of ten million of Ro Na's waking up,
because of that one ten millionth chance
not only Oh Yun Hui but we, too, can be made miserable.
Is that what you want?
Yun Hui
Felony and Homicide Team 2
Mr. Park, as it is,  we're completing our report of your case. Do you have any objections?
No, I don't.
Is it you?
Is it really you?
Did you really do that to my daughter?
I'm sorry. I committed a grave sin.
Why did you do it?
Why the hell did you do it? What did my daughter ever do to you?
Why the hell did you do it? Why? Why?
Why!
Tell me! Tell me!
Please calm down.
If something happens to Ro Na, I'll never forgive you.
I'll kill you!
I swear I'll kill you.
I'm sorry, Yun Hui.
I guess our fate ends here.
I thought I'd never betray you again.
Please never forgive an asshole like me.
Restricted Area
Authorized Personnel Only
No way, look, look!
Take a look.
There are so many comments about Bae Ro Na.
Miss A of Cheong Ah Arts School: Who Is She Really?
Everyone sides with Mr. Park, saying how bad it must've been for him to kill her.
Even so, public opinion is so harsh toward a dead person.
Do you know what I hate seeing the most?  A powerless person abusing power.
Being a piece of scrap metal, how dare did she act as though she were gold?
She let it get to her head. While she had nothing, she got to live in a place like Hera Palace.
Even in her death, she gets badmouthed.
Son, you just need to get ready for your SAT.
You're doing everything I tell you to, right?
Of course.
The number of people who follow me is already fifty thousand. Fifty thousand!
Isn't that awesome?
Can he really make it to SNU's (Seoul National University) School of Music, if he does what you tell him to?
Don't you believe me?
Do you think I, Gyu Jin became an assemblyman  now  of all times for no reason?
I've worked so hard with Assemblyman Kang for the past year to introduce this bill.
Special admission for an influencer.
This may go away at the end of the year.
Min Hyuk, you must make it to college by way of this.
My aide is doing a good job of maintaining your followers. You just need to follow around your mom and do volunteer work.
Just take pictures to the best of your ability.
Okay.
All the other kids are in a state of loss because of Ro Na's incident.
It'd be great if Min Hyeok used this chance to climb to the top.
This is why they say a crisis is an opportunity.
Of course, of course.
Mommy's here.
My Ro Na, you must be cold.
Bae Ro Na
It took a while sorting out your belongings.
I did everything I need to.
I'll be there soon, to where you are.
Is dying that urgent?
Let go.
I'm going to my Ro Na. I can't send her off alone.
Do you think I let you live so you can be like this?
I said I'll punish myself with my own hands.
I'm saying I'll go for the crime of killing Min Seol Ah!
Even if you die, you should reveal the person you made Ro Na like this first!
The real culprit is someone else.
Real culprit? And who would that be?
Ha Eun Byeol.
Everyone, do what you need to do and come back by 3 p.m.
Who are you?
Sim Su Ryeon?
How have you been?
It's been a while, Ju Dan Tae.
War in Life Penthouse II
There's nothing stopping me right now.
Can't we start over again?
No!
I've got something really juicy on Cheon Seo Jin.
That's the only way.
I think I'm really liking you now.
Who dared to ask you to do that?
You've got to have a character.
Hello, I'm Sim Su Ryeon.
That person knows all of Ju Dan Tae's secrets.
Is it Logan Lee, that bastard?
Plead, plead again.
On your knees!