♬～
(Kinta) Ha!
Don!
(Natsume) Mikita!
Natsume!
Parallel world?
(Narration)
Why did you have an affair? Because I know.
Yamacchi also came here yesterday ➡
We'll meet at the hotel tomorrow at 9am.
Mikita. I didn't think he was this stupid.
Shoe...
<I was holding Mikita ➡
I was turning away from the small discomfort.
(Recall) Broccoli and spinach look like it ➡
Lots of folic acid.
Location dials are good, but if they continue, they may end up being nutritionally unbalanced.
<But I'm going to live in separate worlds.
It's clear.>
<Natsume didn't come to the mix on Saturday night.
Minakawa Mikita, who is active in a married couple ➡
I've been close to Hirata Natsume.
It's the same as that time.
Natsume Where did you go?
<This means they lose each other ➡
A couple who ends up living in separate worlds ➡
A story that you can meet for a little while every night.
♬～
Right now.
Hmm, it's tasty.
(Maple) All of these vegetables were picked today.
Something feels relieved. Hahahaha.
I have a replacement. Thank you.
I'm full. Hahaha.
Tough!
Shattering Shattering...
Kachan!
Ahhh.
Why don't you stay overnight?
I agree.
Hey mom?
Didn't you feel lonely alone?
Hmm, honestly➡
One person is free and it's easy.
Haha.
I think I understand a little.
If it's good, then
I'm fine to come back then.
yeah?
♬～
(Voice in the heart) Three minutes of the worlds mingling together➡
That time, Natsume was probably at the hotel with Yamacchi?
Ah!!
I'll put the key in the mailbox.
These are pants.
Natsume What is this?
Ahhh.
Let's calm down for now.
Let's take a shower.
Ah!
♬～
It's mine.
Whew. Ping pong! (Interhon sound)
yes.
Ah, Ko-chan. Well.
It's no use coming here.
Was it you?
Will we meet tomorrow at 9am? With Natsume.
(Maruyama) Sorry for keeping you waiting.
♬～
Um ➡
9am yesterday, where were you?
yes? Ah... here though.
Ah... well, that's right, in this world.
What is Natsume?
(Riko) Maruyama-cchi. (Maruyama) Welcome.
Ah, Riko-chan.
Was that Mikita-san there?
Ahhh, a bit. That's fine.
I liked Natsume today...
It's a Natsume special, so I'm very particular.
Huh?
(Maruyama) Sorry for keeping you waiting.
thank you.
It's still a bit bitter.
Natsume special?
It's Campari Soda.
Based on herb liqueur ➡
Natchan has always been my favorite.
When did you say Natsume?
When did you remember?
(Riko) I see, they're in the same hometown.
Huh? Ah... local?
Have you not heard it?
I would have liked to go without the filming of the Yamacchi Association.
What? Wait a minute, what meeting?
Yamacchi's Association. Yamacchi's Association?
This is an agricultural experience we do in our local area.
Agricultural experience?
Ah... sorry.
In other words….
Natchan is a childhood friend.
childhood friend?
♬～
Fixed the hotel ➡
Is 9am at 9am?
Haa...
It's nostalgic, this feeling.
Have you managed to take a little breather over the past two days?
Yeah.
Haha.
Natchan. Huh?
When my husband passed away ➡
I might say something like this today.
I want to protect Natchan.
Haha, Kou-chan?
I want to protect it.
Hahaha, wow, that's reliable.
With that toddler troll ➡
What was Kou-chan stuck behind me?
♬～
Don't mess it up.
I could protect Natchan now.
Oh. (Riko) Scary, scary, scary...
Replacement!
OK?
Me...➡
I made a lot of weird misunderstandings.
I'm jealous of my childhood friend.
That jealousy is not wrong.
Huh?
I love Natchan more than I love him.
Ohhh. (Riko) Ahhh!
I've always had a crush on him.
This... (Riko) Let's do it again.
It's a punishment game. (Riko) What? Punishment game...
a little bit.
Kou-chan.
♬～
sorry.
But it's because I'm serious.
I would never make Natchan feel sad.
I'll feed you anything you want to eat ➡
He doesn't even give him a bad smoothie.
Maybe I didn't like it.
Because Natchan...
Maybe it's not that I didn't like smoothies.
Let's go back for today.
Are you going to run away?
Ahhh.
I agree.
I've just run away.
♬～
Why didn't you say it?
Tough!
Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang...
Natsume!
Shoe...
Huh?
♬～
I see, the mix is ​​only in this room.
Shoe...
♬～
Natsume.
Where is it? Natsume?
Shoe...
♬～
sorry.
Sorry, Natsume.
Natsume... (Tamura) Hey, Mikita, Parallel World and ➡
I've done some research into the relationship between the universe.
Tamura.
Sorry for doubting a lot. What? What?➡
What... what's wrong? Me ➡
Space garbage floating in space No ➡
It's less than that. Tamura-san...
what up? Wow, what what? Huh?
(Imai) You shouldn't stimulate it. Stimulation?
Something that reminds me of Natsume-san ➡
Please don't say it at all.
(Moriya) Oh, everyone. Aim for the next project, summer ➡
I'm thinking about moving forward. Please don't aim for summer.
Yes, let's make it winter at least.
(Moriya) What? Aiming for summer...
(Tamura/Riko) Ah! Natsume...
Is this the future?
I don't know if it was the car the detective said.
Ah, that's what it is.
Ah.
♬～
You've stuck, it's a reward.
ah.
I can't get away with this anymore.
Ah, did you feel a little refreshed at your parents' house?
Yes, thank you. Haha.
Natsumecchi. Huh?
When hanging out the laundry, do you also dry men's pants?
It's gross. What is it? that.
It's safe to not be thought of as a woman living alone.
The entrance lock must be double locked and the door scope...
(Moriya) What? Are you starting now?
♬ Nibun (Aoki) back dancer's movements ➡
The client doesn't seem to like it.
Clients would like to make adjustments by the end of the weekend.
What, does that mean re-shooting?
(Aoki) What, it's not a problem that can be solved by editing...
I understand. I'll take a retake.
Are you planning on gathering dancers again?
Natsume P Are you really saying it? (Aoki) As expected from Natsume-san.➡
You will accept any order ➡
That's helpful! (Moriya) But ➡
There is also a general schedule adjustment.
Please consult us regarding delivery dates.
Thank you. (Imai) Please.
(Aoki/Natsume) Please. (Moriya) Yes please. ➡
I think it would be fine to fight more.
Not just the agency, but the staff too.
Huh? Well, sometimes I'm overexplaining my emotions ➡
I sometimes get a big quarrel though ➡
What is the relationship of trust with friends?
I think that's how I make it.
yes.
Hmm.
I also often got into a fight with my wife, haha.
But I can't do anything about it anymore.
He passed away 10 years ago.
Huh? Ah, I didn't know.
Uh uh uh uh.
Every time, we fight over something unimportant.
But let's say what we want to say ➡
Because I bumped into a lot ➡
I think the bond between the couple has become stronger.
Being close and building relationships ➡
Sometimes it's different.
That's right. Thank you very much.
(Moriya) You're welcome. Haha.
Haha.
welcome….
Right. Natchan.
I thought he might come again.
Haha, that's not the case.
Campari Soda. Natsume special.
Um, Ko-chan, I'm sure...
Don't say it. What?
I don't want a reply right now.
If you just want an answer ➡
It's certain that it will be 100% off.
So the reply is ➡
It's fine when my blueberry fruit grows.
That blueberry ➡
It'll take another five years.
That's fine.
♬~(BGM in the store)
♬～
I wonder if Natsume will come to the mix tonight.
Tick...
Tough!
Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang...
Ah... Natsume.
sorry.
I wanted to meet you very much.
Sorry I ran away the other day.
Today I came to talk properly.
Thank you, Natsume.
We are
He was a good partner at work, right?
Ah...
At work?
Me ➡
He was running away from facing Mikita properly.
I couldn't say I don't like smoothies either.
Huh? Junk sweets etc.
I also want to eat chicken with oil twig ➡
I want to drink alcohol at my own pace.
It's about Natsume's health.
Did you notice?
Everything that he said was for me was for Mikita.
What does that mean?
Mikita always says ➡
I wish I could be the person who liked Mikita.
So I also suppress my feelings ➡
I started to swallow everything.
Since then.?
♬～
We're at the same workplace so you can pretty much understand it.
It would be more convenient to be able to grasp each other's actions, they are a couple.
Why do you decide that way?
Oh, so that we can live together for a long time later➡
Take two days a week to rest on your liver.
On a day off of liver. Umm...
a little bit! Already ➡
Stop moving forward at your own pace.
This one is definitely more convenient.
At that time, I thought that no matter what I said to Mikita was useless.
It's better for children to get up early. You can also record your basal body temperature to get pregnant...
Take it easy now!
Ahhh... that's oily.
I didn't want to be managed that way.
No, I'm planning on managing it...
Us ➡
The couple remained unfinished.
By bumping into one another,
If the bond between husband and wife becomes stronger ➡
Honestly, we only have 3 minutes a day.
It's difficult to become a couple.
Natsume What are you talking about?
Today is….
I came to say that.
Mikita.
Thank you so much.
Natsume!
Shatter Kata... Kachan!
Shoe...
Uuh...
♬～
Natsume.
It's Mikita after all.
I live in my own world alone and have a strong sense of self-conception.
Trunk is just too thick.
<What Natsume said the other day is what I meant ➡
I understood it by now.
Uuh...｡ Haaa.
♬｢encore｣
♬～
but….
I was wrong.
<Living separately in two worlds ➡
I finally realized that mistake.
<From that day onwards, Natsume ➡
No longer appears in the mix.
(Manner mode)
uncle?
What does that mean?
The car that took place in the hit-and-run incident ➡
Found in a forest 10km away.
It was a stolen car.
A stolen car? In other words: ➡
Crime Purpose ➡
I consider it a murder due to grudge.
Does that mean someone was hated?
Do you have any thoughts?
No, it's not Mikita.
Because in Mikita's world, I was the one who died.
At the same time in two worlds, at the same place➡
Different people were killed.
If the target of the perpetrator is ➡
If it's the lives of both of us.
The trunk thighs are also dangerous!
The culprit who killed Mikita?
Is it me next? You did it!
We must have been killed by him.
(Moriya) Is that the truth? Natsume is in danger.
Ugh...
I'll do anything to help Natsume.