[Delicious Love]
[Episode 11]
Zheng Dao.
What's going on?
Why are there women's shoes?
Zheng Dao, come and eat.
You must be Xu Duo.
I'm Shen Ying.
I'm making breakfast.
Do you want to eat with us?
What are you making?
You'll find out later.
Come on.
You came uninvited again.
Have a seat.
Wait.
Your relationship advances too fast.
What's wrong?
You were caught in bed,
and dare not admit it?
I think you...
Am I dreaming?
Dr Xu,
don't make a fuss over nothing.
Sit.
Okay.
How is it?
The Eight Treasure Rice made with my secret recipe is not bad, right?
Ying.
Didn't you tell me before
you would only cook this for me?
I'd say this to whoever
wants to eat my food.
Humph.
By the way,
this Eight Treasure Rice Congee
strengthens spleen and stomach, and soothes the nerves.
It's suitable for people who are
overweight or suffer from nervosism.
Yes, that's right.
Shen Ying,
why did you go out of your way like this?
What are you celebrating?
Of course I'm celebrating our Gourmet colomn
becoming the No. 1 among all the magazine columns in China.
I have nothing to do with it then.
Congratulations on you becoming a big shot in the domestic dessert domain.
Tastes good.
Shen Ying,
I didn't expect you to cook so well.
No wonder you have attracted my
distant and cold friend.
He asked me to specially bring back
limited edition women's shoes from abroad.
Xu Duo!
You're awesome.
It's the least I can do.
Police investigation.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say
can and will be used against you in a court of law.
Well,
leniency to those who confess; severity to those who resist.
What happened?
You stayed out all night.
You didn't come home all night.
All night!
Did you go to Prince Ye's hotel
or Mr. Zheng's room?
My stomach suddenly hurts.
What a lame excuse.
Tell us.
They drank themselves
under the table last night.
Then I went to pick them up.
That's why I've been restless until this morning.
You haven't slept the whole night?
Don't talk nonsense.
But the key point is...
which one of them
made you go out
in the middle of the night,
since you're so lazy?
Anyhow...
it's not Chubby.
Then it must be Zheng Dao.
Do you really like him?
Oh no, no, no...
-What should we do? - Zheng Dao is not easy to deal with.
Then...
you are in a relationship?
I don't know.
Zheng Dao...
is not bad.
He's just a bit dark-skinned.
Why is Zheng Dao so funny?
He's got a great sense of humor.
Who are these two girls?
Why did Zheng Dao take pictures with so many beautiful girls?
You have nagged me
168 times today.
I'm so annoyed.
Stop it.
Hi, how have you been today?
Are you hungry?
May I buy you dinner?
Have you eaten?
I accidentally ordered a double meal.
My treat.
Morning. Eat...
No.
It's not morning, but evening.
Do you want to have dinner? Shall we go?
Forget it.
I'd better not disturb her.
Shall we have dinner together tonight?
Miranda, are you looking for me?
Come in.
How is your special feature
Taste and Flavor going?
It's going well.
The shop has been chosen.
The only thing left is to go there in person.
Well done.
Ye Zhiqiu takes a very early flight
to go back to Italy tomorrow.
So soon?
Ye Zhiqiu is a top dessert chef.
He is very creative.
Maybe
we'll have another chance to work together.
You and Zheng Dao go see him off tomorrow,
on behalf of Isen.
I know you two are good friends.
If you see him off,
he will be very happy.
No problem.
That's good.
I'm leaving then.
Go.
Chubby.
Why are you here?
To see you off.
Come on, let me give you a ride.
No need.
I've already booked a taxi.
If we cancel it now,
it's not fair to the taxi driver.
You really don't need it?
Zheng Dao.
Come.
This letter
is about everything Shen Ying likes.
I wanted to leave it at the reception.
Since you're here,
I'll give it to you directly.
Thank you.
If I have a chance to win her over,
I will still seize it.
Okay, I got it.
All right.
I'm leaving.
Shen Ying,
take care of yourself.
Don't make me worry.
Be assured.
When you arrive,
remember to call me.
OK.
Zhiqiu,
take good care of yourself over there.
Have a safe trip.
-Enough. -Bye.
Move over.
Here.
Go.
Bye.
Take care.
Have a safe trip.
Bye.
What were you two talking about so stealthily?
Nothing.
I'm neither stupid nor blind, okay?
Did you two make some shady deal
behind my back?
I suddenly remember
there's something to do in Fang's restaurant.
Come with me.
Let's go.
Why are we going to Fang's restaurant?
I have to clock in.
Think of it as dispatched work ordered by Director Zheng.
Mentor,
you must be hot.
Hurry up.
Let me take it.
I'm not hot.
The sun is scorching.
Don't get burnt.
I'll block the sunshine for you.
Take a rest.
This one looks good.
Don't touch. I'm modifying it.
You do shoot great photos.
By the way, mentor,
are you hungry?
No.
No means yes.
Okay.
I know.
Wait for me.
No means yes?
Are they looking good?
Choose one.
Do you want this or this?
I'll have a try.
Let me help you.
I'll pick a color that suits you.
Here, open your mouth.
I'll do it myself.
Thank you.
Does it taste good?
Have some more.
Coming.
Shen Ying.
Shen Ying!
Bai?
Fang is taking care of grandpa in the hospital.
So he has no time to take care of her.
Li Bai,
obey Shen Ying these days,
and study hard.
Got it?
Got it.
Just tell grandpa to rest well in the hospital.
I'll behave here.
Grandpa behaves better than you, okay?
Go.
How is it going?
Grandpa Li is not doing well.
It's not convenient for Li Bai to stay at my place,
so I brought her here.
Thank you for all the trouble.
Don't mention it.
Bai and I are good friends, okay?
Go back to your business.
I guess Fang
must need help.
Okay, I'm off then.
Bye.
Take care.
Ying.
Let me tell you a secret.
Go ahead.
Are you in love with someone?
How did you know I was going to tell you this?
I'm smart.
Tell me which handsome guy it is.
Show me the photo.
Ying.
It's...
Fang Siwei.
Bai,
Mr. Fang is indeed an excellent
and charming person.
He deserves your love.
You don't object?
Why should I?
I think true love
shouldn't be restricted by the outside world.
Thank you, Ying.
Why are you thanking me, silly girl?
I should thank you.
Your purity and courage
are like a mirror,
reflecting the cowardice and prejudice
of adults like us.
Shen Ying,
I know who you like, too.
Zheng...
Stop.
Just keep it to yourself.
Okay.
All right.
I'm going to sleep.
Go to sleep.
I'll keep it a secret for you.
Okay. Hurry up.
Bai needs to grow taller.
Good night. Good night.
Go to sleep.
Let go!
Let go of me!
It's impossible for us.
Don't come to me again.
Good morning, Director Zheng.
We're going to be late.
Hold on.
Director Zheng, Miss Shen Ying.
Hello, Mr. Zheng. Hello, Miss Shen.
Hello. Hello.
He was fine yesterday.
What happened?
Did I offend him?
Hurry up.
I'm late.
Oh, Shen Ying.
I'm sorry, Shen Ying.
Director, you're here to get water too?
Yes.
Well,
you're acting weird today.
You're oversensitive.
What are you doing?
You wrinkled my shirt.
Fan,
I have a question for you.
Shoot.
I have a friend
who has met some relationship problems recently.
Besides me and Zhuang Yan,
what other friends do you have?
It's not a real friend.
She is
a reader or a fan of mine.
She left me a message.
She said
she has encountered a problem recently.
She was close to a man.
But then this man
treats her very well at one time,
and becomes cold at another.
He's cold and hot. Near and far.
Is he a love-rat?
Not necessarily.
It's just basic operation.
Confession of love
is what only kids do.
Adults should
play hard to get.
So,
just press him onto the wall.
It's not me.
It's my reader.
Okay, your reader.
Be straight forward.
Press him.
And ask him,
"what do you mean?"
Does it have to be so direct?
It's up to you.
Okay, thank you, Fan.
Guan Guan, please...
Yes, stand up a little.
You were blocked a bit.
Hold on. Let me check.
The morning ones came out, right?
Thank you.
We're done for today.
Let's call it a day.
Time to go.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you, Guan Guan.
Let me hold it for you.
Okay.
It's okay.
Let me do it.
Mentor.
Thank you for your hard work today.
-The equipment... -Send the equipment back when it's ready.
I have something to tell you.
Look after this.
I'm going to pick the photos.
Zhuang Yan.
Take this.
I'll treat you to dinner tonight.
Zhuang Yan.
I like you!
I said I like you, Zhuang Yan.
I'm willing to give my life to you.
I thought
I could take good care of you.
Now I understand.
I need you more.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Don't you think before you speak?
Zhuang Yan, I'm serious.
Don't come over.
Zhuang Yan,
can you give me a chance?
I don't understand what you're talking about.
Zhuang Yan. Zhuang Yan!
What?
That way.
Work hard.
Is Zhuang troubled?
What's wrong?
Isn't Ying busy today?
No, not really.
So I came to care about
my dearest sister.
I remember you have
a photo needing editing here in my place?
If you're not busy,
I'll take my time then.
I suddenly remembered
I have an emergency
to deal with.
I'll leave you alone then.
You don't care about your sister anymore?
I'll melt you with my warm heart at home.
No more words. Bye.
Fan.
Are you thirsty?
No.
Are you really not thirsty?
I think I suddenly want to have a drink.
I'll leave you to it.
I'll take it.
Yu Sicheng has confessed his love.
But Zhuang still doesn't take it seriously.
Should we
go through fire and water for our best friend's happiness?
My dear,
just stay put, okay?
This is only the beginning stage of a relationship.
It's painful and bitter, but kinda sweet when you savor it.
It is hard to resist or to stop.
Don't mess it up.
What bitter and sweet?
Aren't you worried?
I'm vexed to death.
Take care of yourself. Make a pot of jasmine tea.
Have some purple-heart radish sesame candy
and stay put quietly.
That alone is helping your friend
pursue her happiness.
What are you talking about?
Can you bear to see Zhuang
having no appetite all day
and no sleep all night?
Mind your own business.
Zheng Dao.
Director.
Where is he?
Fan Jian.
Tell me.
Your mother gave you a pretty face.
Why didn't she give you
a matching EQ?
In the end, your uncle has to worry about it
and improve your level.
Uncle,
how do you think I could win his heart?
Look at Zhuang Yan.
She only sang a song, but she made Yu Sicheng crazy about her.
What about you?
Zheng Dao told you to give it a try.
But you were casual like a man.
When he suggested to have a try,
you just retorted.
What else could I do?
You mean
I should have given it a try?
I mean
you kiss him directly.
Strike while the iron is hot.
Occupy his heart,
disturb his thoughts,
and succeed in one go.
Please enlighten me, uncle.
Didn't he ask you to write the next special article?
You just play cute with him
and ask him to work together with you.
If you keep doing it,
there will be a chance without doubt.
That makes sense.
I guarantee your progress will be rapid.
No need for further chatter.
Got it.
Director,
I don't know how to write this article.
Can you have a look of it for me?
Okay.
Well,
it's already pretty good.
Just keep writing like this.
You can write a good article.
Really?
But I still don't understand.
How about
telling me some more?
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
I dare not go there alone.
How about
going together with me?
I forgot to tell you.
As for exploring the restaurants, I'll go with you all the way
and decide which products to choose.
That way you can write the article faster.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
It made me nervous.
Alright.
I'm good now.
See you.
It's just a little failure at the beginning of the battle.
I will never
flinch at such a small blow.
Didn't the ancient scholars say,
to win a man's heart,
you need to win his stomach first?
I don't believe
I can't conquer him.
Shen Ying,
who are you going to conquer?
I meant the article.
I said I'm going to conquer this special article.
Come on.
You can do it.
I can do it.
Your drawing is quite good.
This is the food map I made myself.
Don't underestimate it.
You'll see how great it is.
Good, let's start from here.
Today,
let me, the genius food editor,
show you
a taste of the mortal world.
Let's go.
Boss,
I want a portion of fish balls.
A large portion. Original flavor.
Pick the chewy ones for me.
I like chewy ones. Thank you.
Thank you, boss.
Take it. You'll have nothing to say.
How much is it?
Ten Yuan.
Okay.
Men are simple.
If he has seen all the loftiness,
take him to taste a touch of the mortal world.
When he's in a suit,
take him to experience the grassroots life.
Anyway,
they just want a woman
who allows them to be a kid again.
The fish balls here are something
you must eat when you come to the university night market.
If you don't eat this,
you've come here in vain.
Hot!
Yummy.
Slow down.
Don't worry.
They're all yours.
Next stop,
I'm going to take you to this place
that sells great roasted ribs.
Okay.
Roasted ribs. Roasted ribs.
Right over there.
Let's go.
Excuse me,
here are the roasted ribs that you ordered.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
Thank you, boss.
Eat up.
The ribs here are really delicious.
After I first had them,
I kept thinking about them for three whole days!
Really?
Look at you.
You look like you've been starving for three years.
Director Zheng,
you don't usually eat alone, do you?
When you eat alone,
you have to show all your passion,
so that people around you can feel it too.
Really?
You can have my portion too.
Don't give it to me. Eat.
It's really good.
I don't think it suits my taste.
Why not?
You haven't even tried it. Try it.
Based on my years of experience,
it really doesn't suit me.
Fine.
I'll eat it for you.
Here.