[English subtitles are available]
[Delicious Love]
[Episode 20]
Sign this
and put it on the table.
That's it.
Hello.
May I know how to get to the chief editor's office?
I'm looking for Miranda.
Hello, madam.
May I know your name?
Do you have an appointment with the chief editor?
My name is Han Feizi.
I have an appointment at 2 p.m.
Yes, Ms. Han.
Hold on.
I'll get someone to take you there now.
No need.
Are you looking for Miranda?
-I'll take you there. -Yes.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Thank you, Ying.
You're welcome.
Let's go.
Watch the steps.
Are you Shen Ying?
You know me?
Sort of.
What's wrong?
Is there something on my face?
No.
I just think you look familiar.
I might have seen you somewhere.
Hello, Miss Han.
We finally meet.
I was about to pick you up.
Thank you.
This is my superior, Miranda.
Hello.
I'm back to work.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Nice meeting you.
Hope we can meet again.
We will meet again.
Okay.
Bye.
I'm leaving.
Go ahead.
Miss Han, this way please.
Okay.
I...
Boss.
Yoyo.
This is not expensive, boss.
I...
Boss.
Fang.
You’re finally here.
Please talk to Mr. Fang.
What are you doing, Fang?
There's no need.
It's nothing serious.
Here.
What happened?
Nothing.
It has nothing to do with you.
It has nothing to do with me?
Fang,
we've been through thick and thin together.
What can't be solved?
Enough.
Yu Sheng
wanted to buy Si.
Haven't I already refused him that day?
He came again today,
saying he's going to offer me the same salary and benefits.
He put it so nicely.
Who does he think he is?
What's his condition?
They'll have the right to decide the dishes.
They are targeting me.
What about you?
When is the acquisition date?
The day after tomorrow.
He want to do this before the Golden Fritillaria Competition.
His intention is quite obvious.
He doesn't want us to participate in the competition.
Then he can buy Si at a low price.
We can’t give him the chance.
Mr. Fang,
I don't want to sound dramatic,
but since I joined Si,
I've taken everyone as my family.
I will never leave Si no matter what.
Nor will I.
Two points.
First,
if you work here,
don't be dramatic.
Second,
let's fight against him.
OK.
Fang,
don't worry.
Let's hurry.
You must not want me to be late
when I judge a competition for the first time.
Of course not.
Get in.
Everything here is fantastic.
Is it that beautiful?
That's because you're by my side.
These
are not as good as a tenth of you.
Are you Zheng Dao?
Yes.
It's really you.
I've heard so much about you.
Hello, and you are?
Hello.
I'm Qiang, the chef of Beauty from the North.
Are you here to participate in the competition too?
Yes.
I represent Restaurant Si this time.
I've been a big fan of your blog.
I've read every article you wrote,
especially the one about French...
I'll go ahead.
Okay.
Shen Ying.
Manager.
What a coincidence.
Long time no see.
Look at that person.
Really? It's right ahead.
Let's go and have a look.
Isn't that the opinion leader in the international gastronomy field,
Han Feizi?
Yes, that's her.
She has a high degree of recognition
in this industry.
I admire her very much.
No wonder
other judges are all kept as a secret.
She just came back from abroad.
Only she was revealed beforehand.
Not for a long time.
She has drawn a lot of attention for the organizers,
as she was announced as a judge very early.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Come on.
We meet again.
So you are Han Feizi.
Why?
Don't I look the same as my pictures on the Internet?
It seems that
I should criticize
those photographers.
No, no, no.
I mean,
I just didn't expect
the one I met
at the reception that day was you.
I told you
we would meet again.
Miranda told me
you were judging as an opinion leader
in the gastronomy area
on behalf of Isen.
Yes.
But I still feel inadequate.
So I need to learn from you.
Okay.
I have something to do.
Shall we talk later?
Okay, no problem.
She's so charismatic.
Mr. Yu.
We meet again.
You're still so pretty.
She's so pretty in person.
She's pretty and famous.
Yes.
Han Feizi came back from France
to participate in this competition, right?
I heard she rarely appears on public occasions abroad.
I heard that
the scandal
related to the chef of Si
has something to do with her.
Really?
Excuse me.
Zheng Dao.
Long time no see.
I'm back.
Look.
they are still very close.
It's just bickering between a couple.
Don't you know a couple never holds grudges
for too long?
You are right.
Maybe Han Feizi came back this time
to make peace.
That chef will surely win this time.
You can't say that.
Ms. Han,
I'm a reporter from Southern Cuisine.
It's such a great stunt
that you come back this time.
How do you feel about
being a judge this time?
First of all,
I must thank
the organizer's approval and invitation,
which allow me to have a chance
to meet the masters in China.
I can't say I'm a teacher
or that I can comment on them.
But I think everyone here
has a passion for gastronomy.
I hope we can learn from each other.
For example, this chef by my side
is a chef that I admire
and like very much.
Ms. Han, you're too modest.
Looks like
many stories will happen this time.
So in this competition,
is there someone you pay special attention to
or whose performance are you looking forward to?
I just mentioned it.
The one next to me is the chef of Si.
It happens that
we went to college together.
When we studied in France,
we used to exchange views quite often.
I learned a lot
from him.
You flatter me, Ms. Han.
It was not really an exchange of views.
It turns out that you know each other well.
This competition offers such a good opportunity.
Will you two consider to cooperate?
Of course.
It would be best
if we can have such a chance.
I don't have much time.
Thank you for the invitation, Ms. Han.
I'll leave you guys to it.
It seems like the schedule of this competition is really tight.
Why didn't he tell me
Han Feizi is his ex-girlfriend?
Is he
afraid that I'll feel inferior after I find out?
Why is she prettier
and better than me?
What's wrong?
A beauty has worries too?
Don't pry into a beauty's affairs.
Knowing too much
is not good for you.
Okay, I got it.
But
the audition will begin soon.
There's not much time left for a beauty to sigh.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Let's go.
Food tasting is like selecting good movies.
Different personal tastes
naturally lead to different reviews.
Everyone can give their own reviews
based on their personal preference.
We have beef tallow hot pot in Chongqing,
various kinds of soup in Guangzhou,
and West Lake Fish in Vinegar Gravy in Hangzhou.
Classic eight major cuisines and
countless local specialties
constitute the major part of
the profound Chinese food culture.
The Sichuan Cuisine alone
contains 24 flavors
and hundreds of classic dishes.
Now
Golden Fritillaria Competition begins!
Great!
Here we go.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes.
I’m back.
Zhuang. Fan.
Even you look down on me.
The whole world looks down on me.
That restaurant
is really interesting, isn't it?
Yes.
Ying.
You're home?
Wash your hands and eat.
Zhuang Yan, hurry up.
Don't be so noisy, okay?
Okay.
Slow down.
Why didn't you turn on the lights?
It's so dark.
I'm starving. Come on.
What's wrong, Ying?
What's wrong?
Don't be upset.
There is nothing that can't be solved by a good meal.
Right?
There. There.
Today,
I feel aggrieved.
What happened?
It's okay.
I can give your head a massage if you can't take it anymore.
You're so annoying.
Alright, stop crying.
Don't cry.
I thought
I was pretty,
excellent,
cute,
and adorable.
Yes.
Everyone thinks so.
But I met Han Feizi today.
She's probably, possibly, maybe...
a little too pretty.
That's true.
I also saw her today.
She is pretty.
You met her too?
Yes.
That day she came to find Miranda.
I also saw her that time.
Yu Sicheng was there too.
He saw her too.
Yes, I did.
Well,
is this Han Feizi
really pretty?
Did my eyes deceive me today?
No, they didn't.
She is pretty.
She's elegant, too.
Hello.
Hello, Miss Han.
Shengshi Group called us again.
He called my number this time.
It seems that he has figured out who are around you.
Just ignore them
and stay away from them.
Okay.
Mr. Yu.
Han Feizi has something to do with Zheng Dao.
You mean
they are old acquaintances?
Yes.
When studied in France,
they were a couple.
So,
does Zheng Dao's plagiarism incident
have something to do with Han Feizi?
Yes.
Here are some examples of the domestic news.
It was really a big thing at the time,
so there was a lot of media coverage.
Although we can’t contact Han Feizi,
she
is not totally useless after all.
Yes.
Find a familiar media
to spread the news.
Remember,
don't give yourself away.
This time,
I need it to be the No. 1 hot topic on social media within an hour.
I'll send you the relevant materials.
The price is the same as last time.
[Trending in the city]
[Plagiarism of the Director of Isen Magazine]
Senior food critic Zheng Dao is suspected of having plagiarized
the work of the international food critic Han Feizi.
Zheng Dao was expelled from a famous French gastronomy competition.
How is it possible for him to plagiarize?
There must be some misunderstanding.
We are not sure about it.
Don't spread rumors
when there's no final conclusion yet.
I hope they come out and clarify it.
Hope we won't be used by someone.
Don't jump to conclusions.
Ying.
The news says Director Zheng plagiarized.
Is that true?
[Are you okay?]
He must be in a bad mood now.
My superficial comfort
won't help much.
I should leave him alone.
Come here.
I have something to tell you.
Well...
Something happened again.
It's about you.
Be prepared for this.
I don't need to be prepared for such things.
A rumor like this will soon be drown out.
But it still affects your reputation.
Aren't you going to refute it?
It's not the first time someone started a rumor about me.
Why bother?
I'm really fine.
The champion of the competition is...
Mr. Zheng Dao.
Welcome.
Thank you so much.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Zheng Dao
from China.
I'm so happy to be here
to receive this honor.
This is my first time to win the championship.
I've been in this city about two years.
I love this city.
This city...
Sorry, sir.
For some reasons,
we'll cancel this championship.
Sorry.
The dish Feizi
is named after me.
I have nothing to do with Zheng Dao.
Although we were together before,
but we've already been separated for a long time.
I'm sorry.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Han Feizi.
There were some false comments
on Weibo today.
I want to clarify the whole thing
by this video.
Zheng Dao and I were college classmates.
We were also boyfriend and girlfriend.
When we were in college,
we liked to try delicious food
and taste each other's cooking.
On my birthday,
Zheng Dao made a dessert named Feizi
as my birthday gift.
I really liked it.
That conniving little...
-I'm speechless. -He taught me how to make it.
Zheng Dao didn't plagiarize any work.
I chose to betray love
when faced by the choice between love and career.
You're back.
Look what I've prepared for you.
Wow.
What is this?
This is
named Feizi.
It's named after you.
I made it specially for you.
I want to make it
the last dessert in the competition.
Haven't you been busy with the competition lately?
How do you have time to make this?
I see you've been too tired from preparing for the competition.
I want you to relax a little.
And I want to tell you
there's no need
to compete with the determination of winning.
When we go back China,
with my ability,
I can surely give you a better life.
We don't have to stay here.
I will win.
And I will stay.
Okay, you will win.
Try it.
Is it good?
Great.
Happy birthday.
Zheng Dao didn't plagiarize any work.
I chose to betray love
when faced by the choice between love and career.
Lastly,
I hope you won't be blinded by the rumors
and learn the truth.
Don't hurt innocent people anymore.
Thank you.
Han Feizi is like a goddess.
She's such a perfect match for Director Zheng.
I agree.
She comes out to clarify it,
which means she still loves Director Zheng.
I wonder if Director still loves her.
You scared me.
I think
Shen Ying and Director Zheng are the best match.
You guys
are too shallow.
Ying.
Ying!
Ying,
don't care about what they say.
Don't take it to heart.
Of course.
We'll always support you.
You don't need to be afraid of anything!
That's right.
Ying.
Just ignore them.
We all support you.
Come on.
She came out to clarify it for the sake of Zheng Dao,
regardless of the others' criticism to her.
I can't just stand by and watch.
I'm the girlfriend.
Ying.
Where are you going?
Current girlfriend versus
ex-girlfriend.
Don't talk nonsense.
Miss Shen is here.
Ms. Shen.
What do you think about
Zheng Dao's plagiarism?
Step aside.
Stay away from Ying.
The truth will come out sooner or later.
Zheng Dao didn't plagiarize.
That's right.
Ms. Shen,
as Zheng Dao's girlfriend,
what do you feel about
the fact that his ex uploaded a video
on Weibo?
Are they getting back together?
Han Feizi must still love Zheng Dao.
Otherwise, she wouldn't have stood up to clarify it.
Zheng Dao will surely be very touched.
He's handsome and she's beautiful.
And they both are outstanding.
I'll definitely ship them.
First of all,
I'm very grateful
that Miss Han could come out and clarify it for Zheng Dao.
Secondly,
even if she didn't release this video,
I would believe in Director Zheng all the same.
Director Zheng
has a unique perspective on food reviewing.
His cooking skills are excellent, too.
So there's no need for him to plagiarize.
Yes, it's not necessary.
Shen Ying,
are you with Zheng Dao
because of your career?
Yes.
Zheng Dao is the reason
that my career is complete.
Shen Ying,
is Han Feizi going to
affect your relationship with Zheng Dao?
If Zheng Dao really plagiarized,
how would you face him?
Sorry, I have something to do.
Wait, one more question.
Wait no more!
Ying, go!
Excuse me.
Stop chasing.
Seriously!
I'll leave the rest to you.
Zheng Dao made a dessert named Feizi
as my birthday gift.
Zheng Dao didn't plagiarize any work.
I chose to betray love
when faced by the choice between love and career.
Lastly,
I hope you won't be blinded by the rumors
and learn the truth.
Don't hurt innocent people anymore.
Shen Ying,
are you with Zheng Dao
because of your career?
Zheng Dao is the reason
that my career is complete.
Shen Ying,
is Han Feizi going to
affect your relationship with Zheng Dao?
If Zheng Dao really plagiarized,
how would you face him?
Sorry, I have something to do.
Do you also
choose to be with me
because you want get something from me?
Shen Ying.
Tell me
what are your real thoughts.
Is this video real?
Go back and rest early.
The competition is tomorrow.
See you.
First of all,
I'm very grateful
that Miss Han could come out and clarify it for Zheng Dao.
Secondly,
even if she didn't release this video,
I would believe in Director Zheng all the same.
Director Zheng
has a unique perspective on food reviewing.
Yes.
Zheng Dao is the reason
that my career is complete.