You're gonna be smoking hot.
Me? With these nerdy glasses?
Once you've encountered
three misfortunes,
your life will then totally change.
Why the fuck did you do that?
We're on campus.
You can't just race around.
What's wrong with you, Four-eyes?
Leave me alone!
The Faculty King and Queen Contest?
As for the queen from our faculty,
we got Lin.
As for the king,
we're choosing you.
I don't know that song.
- You haven't heard that?
- Hey, Nu!
Hey.
You're here?
Yes, Chain.
Your outfit is so cute.
A compliment from a friend
doesn't count.
Well, I mean it, though.
He's so much more adorable
without glasses.
Well...
He really is.
Chain!
Hurry up. We're performing soon.
Don't be late, okay?
I'll get ready for my performance, then.
I'll see you when I'm done.
Hey,
let's go inside.
I'm feeling it.
Let's go.
I wanna know
if Chain's performing today.
Yeah.
But if you want a fight,
please don't.
I just wanna talk to him.
There won't be a fight.
I'll take that as a promise from you.
Do not fight here in my club.
Okay.
Ton,
thank you so much.
Everything's alright.
Don't worry.
Hey, trust me.
He's fearsome to lots of people.
You're safe now.
Don't worry.
Right?
You're exaggerating.
Just do what you need to do.
Hey, lover boy,
what are you staring at?
Right,
looking satisfied, huh?
Is something making you happy?
Thought it was someone else.
You're looking at Chain's sister,
aren't you?
She's getting prettier every day.
Can I get her if I hate her brother?
Hey, Sun's probably going for her.
Just do whatever you want.
Hey, where are you going?
To the toilet.
Wanna come see my pee?
I won't steal that chance
from your ladies.
Hey,
I know where Chain is now.
- Cheers!
Yay.
Hey.
You...
I forgot that
you're allergic to alcohol.
Oh, I forgot that, too.
Did you bring your pills?
Gosh, who would bring them to a club?
What should I do now?
- It's itching everywhere.
- Don't scratch it.
Thanks a lot.
Nu.
Yeah?
I'll go get Lin her pills.
She's allergic to alcohol.
Oh...
You're going to the mall?
No, not the mall!
Lin's allergic to alcohol.
Oh,
so you're going to sleep and snore?
Come on, we were just here.
Gosh.
You're out of it.
You guys are giving me headaches.
Hey, I'll be back.
Don't go anywhere
or drink any more alcohol!
Got it?
Oh,
cheers!
Come on.
Oh...
Stop it.
What?
You're going to the mall?
Cheers!
You seem unwell, Lin.
I'm throwing up.
Hey...
Hold it back.
I can't.
It's coming out.
But...
You can just do it here.
I can't go anywhere else.
I really can't hold it back anymore.
Why are you giving me your hands?
To hold your vomit.
Come on, you don't need to do that.
You want me to see you
throw up on the floor?
What if someone records you
and uploads it?
It'll forever be on the Internet.
Can you handle that?
Come on,
I'll take it with my hands.
It's okay, I can wash my hands.
Why do you have to care
about me this much?
'Cause...
you're my dear friend.
I'm sorry, Ploy.
You should've told me you'd come
so that I'd be with you.
I missed you, Sun.
Why didn't you call me at all?
I've been waiting.
Can't avoid a creep
when you're drunk, huh?
I really missed that night.
Should we try to rekindle
our feelings
on that night?
You tell me, Sun.
My room or yours?
- You should come with me.
- But if you can't wait,
we can just do it in the car.
Come on, Sun.
Maybe later. I'm busy.
You're completely drunk, you know?
Where are you going?
Just leave already.
- I'm not leaving.
- Sun,
let go of my friend.
Isn't it too late to be a hero now?
You're...
always late.
I told you to let him go.
Don't make me repeat that again.
I don't care
if you repeat it a thousand times.
But let me tell you one thing.
Don't tryna get on our nerves
'cause you have haters everywhere.
It's time to get...
my revenge.
Don't worry, Chain.
I'll make sure
to take good care of your friend.
Hey!
Come on.
- Come with me.
- To where?
Just come.
Let go of me!
Just sit here.
I'll get you some water to sober up.
No need.
Just leave me alone.
- Let me go!
- Can you stop moving
and just stay still?
I won't stop.
Who do you think you are
to tell me what to do?
I'm older than you.
What?
You're older than me?
Whoa.
Let me take a closer look.
Hey!
If you won't stop doing that,
I can't tell you what's gonna happen.
You think I'm scared?
You should be.
But I am not.
What!?
Last night, did we...
Shit!
What kind of cursed luck is this?
[Misfortune number three]
Four-eyes!
Four-eyes...
Right, I don't have his number.
Actually,
I don't even know your name.
Hey!
If you won't stop doing that,
I can't tell you what's gonna happen.
You think I'm scared?
You should be.
But I am not.
You think
you could just ditch me like that,
Four-eyes?
You've been bathing for hours.
You'll be late for your class, sir.
Can you please submit
my college withdrawal form?
I don't wanna go there anymore.
Did you forget, Master?
If you don't go to this college,
you have to go abroad.
Do you really want to be
with your mother there?
No!
I don't!
I don't wanna be with Mom.
- Ouch...
- Are you okay, sir?
Do you want me
to book a doctor appointment now?
Ruj,
don't ever say the word 'doctor' again,
understand?
Yes, sir.
But...
why?
Please don't ask me anything for now.
So,
I don't need to submit
your withdrawal form anymore, right?
Not today.
I'll sleep on it first.
I have no idea
if things will get even worse.
[Candidates for
Student Council President]
[Vote number two for
Chotirat Phothongkham
from Progress Makers]
We ordered a ton of copies
of your posters.
We're also ordering
some standees and banners.
If the school billboard
weren't so expensive,
we would've already chipped in
with our classmates
to put up a campaign sign for you.
You're taking this so seriously.
Of course we are.
We won't let Gundam win
and be the president.
But didn't you tell me to participate
so it would increase
our class' chances of winning?
Why does it have to do with Gundam?
I'm sure you know
that I have no intention of doing this.
All I want to do is study for my exams.
We know.
That's why
we're trying our best to help you.
As for Gundam...
I mean...
If one of you could win,
it'd be better if that person were you.
Do you know
why we want you to win this election?
Why?
You're smarter, wiser,
and nicer.
I mean, you're the right choice.
Exactly.
More importantly,
we hate Gundam.
The right choice is
the one who wants to do it.
Gundam wants to do it,
so I think he deserves this
more than I do.
You should help him, too.
Of course, we will.
We will help you, too.
It's just that...
you come first,
and Gundam comes after.
Don't worry.
You can trust us.
You sure?
- Of course!
You should go study for your exams.
We'll take care of the rest.
(Watch on www.kisskh.do to support Admin)
Go ahead.
- Hurry.
- You can go now.
Come on.
Tell me what problems
you want me to fix in our school.
I'll solve them all if I win the election.
What issues do you think
our school is having?
- The toilets!
- Toilets?
Okay...
- They're not enough, right?
- Yeah, and the water seems dirty.
Dirty water, got it.
Anything else?
- The food's expensive.
- Expensive food...
Okay, the canteen managers
need to know it.
Right.
Expensive food...
Anything more?
Give me a second.
- You can tell me anything.
- Right!
The trash!
- The trash?
- Yes.
Okay, got it.
There's too much, right? And...
What's wrong with you?
Fine, tell me what you want.
I'll make sure to write it down.
This soon-to-be president
will solve it for you!
Tell me.
I don't need help,
but you do.
What? Why?
Something happened?
Well...
Someone's trying to cause you trouble.
The posters you put up last night...
Damn, they just put theirs
on top of yours.
What? Who would do that?
I'll show you this.
Show me.
Tell me when you're done.
Hey, here it is.
Shit.
Frong! You again?
This mother...
Hold on.
That's my phone.
I know.
Frong!
I'm gonna get you!
You wanna fight or something?
If you really want to win the election,
you should win it fairly.
Dirty tricks are not acceptable here.
It wasn't me.
Quit bullshitting!
Your face's literally on mine!
How come it wasn't you?
Do you have any idea
that I used all my savings
to print these posters?
No one's helping,
and you're causing me more trouble.
Goddamn it!
This sucks!
I'm sorry.
You should've realized this was wrong
before you even did it.
You think I can't hurt you?
Take it easy.
I'm not only sorry,
but I'll make it up to you, too.
Make it up to me?
You think you can just give me money,
and that's it?
- You motherfucker!
- Hey!
What do you want from me, then?
You're so hard to please.
I just...
don't want you to cheat
when you're still young.
It'll be too late when you're older.
You're such a good guy, huh?
Yeah.
I know.
But everyone else doesn't.
I...
don't expect to be recognized.
But if you want to be
the student president,
everybody should know
you're a good guy.
What are you talking about?
I came to talk about the posters,
not to get compliments from you.
As for the posters,
I'll print more of them for you
in full color and 4D quality!
Right,
what's your plan for the campaign?
What are your policies?
Show me.
Maybe I can help.
What?
What do you mean?
You're my rival!
But I don't wanna be that!
I will never be.
What? What did you say?
Let's just do this.
All you need to do
is remember that
if I help you, you'll also help me.
What are you talking about?
I'm so confused.
Listen to me
carefully, okay?
I don't want to be student president,
and I don't want
those three school protectors
to use me to make you lose.
Therefore,
I'll help you,
the unrecognizable good guy,
win the election and be the president,
so I can focus on
studying for the entrance exams.
Got it?
So you, who are my rival,
are helping me?
Yes, secretly.
You can be sure that a wise guy like me
can absolutely make you the president.
Do you have a deal?
How could I say no?
I'm really sorry, Nu,
for leaving you last night.
It was my fault.
I couldn't stay.
Chain also got into a fight.
Luckily, we found him in time.
Otherwise, he would've been more hurt.
Who did he fight with?
Sun and his friends.
Why do they hate him so much, though?
You look pretty drained, too.
Are you okay?
Well,
I've got a fever.
I was probably too drunk last night.
Ouch...
You were dancing your heart out.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Right.
It's good that you let your worries go,
but you should've known your limits.
- I need to go now.
- Hey! That's Sun!
Where are you going?
Aw, he's so hot.
You're burning hot,
but you're still here?
- Hey...
- Wait.
Oh...
What's going on?
Why did he take Nu with him?
Right, why?
I told you to let me go!
Wherever you're taking me to,
I'm not coming with you.
If you don't stop acting up now,
I'll carry you in front of everyone here.
Don't you think I won't do it?
Last night,
I already did that once.
What do you want from me?
I...
Can't you just talk to me?
At least tell me your name.
What are you gonna do with it?
We should at least know each other.
My name's Sun.
I already know that.
I also know that you're an English major
from the Faculty of Arts,
a close friend of Chain's sister,
and a faculty king
for the Faculty King and Queen Contest.
Were you spying on me?
I just wanted to know you.
You must already know my name.
I do,
but I want to hear it from you.
I'm Nu.
Nu?
Wait up!
Take off your shirt.
I said, take it off.
Why do I need to?
What are you gonna do?
Open your mouth.
Do it.
Open your mouth now.
Look.
You've got a high fever.
I'll lower your body temperature
so that you can rest after taking a pill.
I've got a fever,
but do you know who did it?
I told you
to stop, remember?
You didn't listen.
I was drunk
and wasn't in my right mind.
I wouldn't have known
what I was doing.
You were fully aware,
yet you didn't hold back.
Didn't you feel any shame at all?
I did,
but I couldn't help it.
You were so damn hot.
That's enough.
Stop talking.
I'm going back to my class.
I've checked your courses.
You don't have classes now.
I'm going home, then.
Hold on.
You can't leave yet.
You gotta get better
and feel stronger first.
Take your shirt off.
If you don't do it now,
I'll do it how I did last night.
Fine, I'll do it.
I'll go get a towel.
Just hurry and do what you want.
But...
don't do what we did last night again.
You're sick. I won't do it.
Once you're better,
I'll definitely go for it.
Stay still.
[Why did Sun take Nu,
our faculty king, with him?]
[They even held hands]
[Sun's never done that with anyone]
[Exactly! Something's going on]
[Are they dating?]
[Since when? I'm positive Sun's single]
Chain!
What's going on between Sun and Nu?
I have no idea.
No one knows.
I guess we have to ask Nu, then.
But he hasn't picked up any of my calls.
If this happened before now,
I would've been more helpful to Nu.
Look at me now.
I can barely take care of myself.
I don't know
what's between you and them,
but I've warned you, Chain,
about Jon's ex.
And today,
it's finally getting back at you.
About Sun's ex,
I admit that I was in the wrong.
But Jon's ex...
I didn't have anything to do with her.
Jon and I...
can no longer be together, Chain.
If you want to cry,
just let it all out,
but don't assume things just yet.
There might be a solution
to your problem.
Chain, you...
You've always said that
since we were in middle school.
"Every problem can be solved."
But we can really solve any problem
as long as we stay calm.
Yeah.
What?
That was it? Seriously?
Is that really enough
to end a friendship
and go after each other?
Not to offend you,
but this is all crap.
You'd never get it
unless it happened to you.
See? You're still defending them.
Did that wound do nothing to you?
Fine.
Whatever.
But I know...
that you guys had been good friends.
Sun, Jon, Zak, and Man...
They helped us a lot
when we lost our parents.
That's the reason
I can't hate them.
When things are good,
they're incredibly amazing.
But when anger strikes,
they won't freaking listen.
And...
What's between you and Nu?
What do you mean?
I mean...
When you're with him,
something's off.
You like him, don't you?
Yeah.
Knew it!
I never get it wrong.
However,
this time, your enemy is Sun.
Can you really handle that?
Well,
with your help,
I think I can.
Hold on.
You want me to help you get Nu?
You've been hit on by millions of men.
I'm sure you must've picked up
a trick or two.
Come on.
Fine, then.
Since my brother's begging me,
I can't say no, can I?
Sun, what are you doing?
I just want to know...
if your fever is gone.
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
You can't do that.
You're still ill.
I'm better now,
and I don't want
any treatment from you.
Ouch...
See?
You wouldn't listen to me.
To heal fast,
you've got to treat the right place.
Got a wound?
That's where the cream goes.
Does that mean...
I have to apply the cream to...
Gosh.
Don't be scared.
This is part of the treatment.
Can't I really do it myself?
I'm a doctor.
You're just a sophomore medical student.
There's no need to be embarrassed.
I've seen everything
and every inch of you.
That's enough.
Stop talking.
Whatever you're doing,
just do it quickly.
Spread your legs.
Ouch...
Can't you be more gentle?
I'm doing it in the most gentle way.
Me?
Yeah, you!
Help me make Nu
fall in love with Chain, please.
I made a promise with him,
but I've got no idea what to do.
Do you happen to know anything?
Well...
I'm not sure if it's gonna work,
but...
should we give it a try?
Bring it on!
- First!
- Yep.
You need to arrange a dinner for them.
- Oh, okay!
- Make sure the food's good.
Got it.
Second,
they need to see a movie together.
- A movie?
- You know, like...
In a cold room,
Chain could be a gentleman...
Yeah?
And give Nu a blanket!
Like this.
Yeah, something like that.
You know, being a gentleman.
Now, the 28th thing...
This should be enough.
You've got too many of them, Ploy.
What? These are just the basics.
I've only told you
one-third of everything.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
- For real?
- Of course.
You've got all these plans.
Who are you planning
to do all of these with?
[Orange juice: 35 baht per bottle]
Hi, Lin from Class 7.
I'm Ploy from Class 8.
You know me?
Of course I do.
I've seen you
at every morning assembly.
Why are you selling orange juice here?
I just...
wanna help my mom earn more money.
This location won't work.
What about selling it at my place?
Oh, I'm good.
I don't wanna bother you.
So...
I'll help you here, then.
I'm really good at this, you know?
[Orange juice: 30 baht each,
100 baht for three]
What are you trying to do?
Increasing the sales!
You need competition
to make your product more interesting.
Orange juice! It's cheap here!
Thirty baht per bottle, or a special offer
of three bottles for 100 baht!
Wait...
You sure you got that right?
I guess.
You're so funny.
If you like it,
should I come every day?
Orange juice over here!
Thirty baht per bottle,
100 baht for three!
One bottle, please.
Would you like three?
It's 100 for three bottles.
Okay, then. I'll get three.
No one.
I'm not doing them with anyone.
Come on.
You sounded so suspicious.
Who's your crush?
Hey, Lin.
Aside from conjoined twins,
we're the only people
that can't be separated.
If I were to have a crush,
you'd know it first.
Well...
You're right.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Okay.
♫Those eyes of yours...♫
- ♫Make my heart shake♫
- Wait,
this song...
♫Just one glance,
and love begins to wake♫
It's your favorite song!
I know it's your ringtone.
- ♫As we draw near,♫
- Yeah, I really like this song.
- ♫There's one thought I can't forsake:♫
- Let's check it out.
Okay.
♫If I spoke the truth I could not fake,♫
- ♫Would your anger break?♫
- What's going on?
- Why is Chain singing this song?
- ♫Even if...♫
- He knows it's your favorite song,
- ♫The world falls apart,♫
- so he's singing it for you.
- ♫I will stand by you through every part,♫
- Why would he do that?
- ♫Holding you close within my heart♫
- You should ask him.
- ♫And loving you strong as long as I last♫
♫My world froze
when I looked into your eyes♫
♫Through all weathers,
I'm ready to fight with you by my side♫
♫That single gaze from you
opened my mind,♫
♫Showing me what love truly defines,♫
♫And now I just wanna say, "I love you"♫
- Aw...
- He's so handsome.
Nu...
Did you like it?
I did.
[I like you]
[Next episode]
Mr. Playboy, didn't you say
you'd never get into
anything long-term with anyone?
I just wanna get back at Chain.
He stole my girlfriend,
so I'm just stealing what he wants now.
As I won the Faculty King
and Queen Contest last year,
I'd like to give you some advice
on your uniform.
Can you please listen to me first?
I'm sick of your lies!
Remember,
you and Chain
are incomparable!