LIKE FLOWERS IN SAND
1989 NEW YEAR'S
KOREAN SSIREUM CHAMPIONSHIPS
OH DU-SIK IS A GOOFBALL
Welcome
to the 2023 Dano Ssireum Championships,
live from Geosan, the home of ssireum.
Right now, a Taebaek-class match
is being held in Geosan Arena.
Heo Han-cheol,
from Hamwon City Hall Ssireum Team,
secures a victory
with two decisive throws.
Now, the next match is…
Gosh, I can't believe
these two are going head-to-head.
In the blue satba
is Kim Baek-du
from Geosan-gun Ssireum Team.
He's 32 years old, stands at 178 cm tall,
and weighs in at 78 kg.
After being discharged from the military
in 2019, he placed fifth
in the Taebaek class
in the last Chuseok Championships.
He was once called a rising star,
being the center of attention,
but sadly,
he has yet to earn
the champion title thus far.
However, I hope he wins
his first champion title
in this match today.
This match today
might be the last ssireum match
of my life.
Blue satba,
Geosan-gun Ssireum Team's Kim Baek-du!
2023 GEOSAN DANO SSIREUM CHAMPIONSHIPS
EPISODE 1
SSIREUM PRODIGY, KIM BAEK-DU
THE MECCA OF SSIREUM
GEOSAN-GUN SSIREUM TEAM
This time, let's get a few shots
of them doing ssireum.
- A round of ssireum. That sounds great.
- Yes.
Let's see who we want in the picture.
Hey, Kim Baek-du!
Baek-du, come here.
Why does he always pick me
for things like this?
Baek-du, he's calling you.
- I know. Be quiet.
- Okay.
Come on, Kim Baek-du. Now!
Trust me. I didn't want to do this either.
But they forced me to.
- Let's just get it over with.
- Okay.
He's no match for him.
- Will it work?
- It looks cool though.
Dong-seok is so fit.
Come on, sir.
Why would you take photos from there?
Don't worry. You look great.
That's not what I mean.
That angle is just dehumanizing.
From that angle,
my butt will look too big.
Oh, come on.
Nobody's going to know whose butt it is.
They're going to know.
The size is different.
He's got a point, Coach.
It'll be better if he looks nice too.
Please make Baek-du
look nice in the photo too.
I'm not a butt model, you know.
Why are you fixed on that angle?
Don't think about the camera.
Imagine you're actually doing
a round of ssireum. Try to look natural.
Just throw him naturally.
We'll take care of the rest.
Dong-seok, be natural.
- Okay.
- Just be natural.
I'll buy you some chicken later.
I already have dinner plans today.
Knees up.
- Wow.
- Go!
- There you go.
- Nice.
- Attack him.
- Hold on.
Not too hard!
That was rough.
- That was awesome.
- Too rough.
Darn it. I said to go easy.
Do you think Lim Dong-seok will win
the championship again?
We never know.
You see, it's hard for us too.
We can't predict anything
until our wrestlers are on the sand…
We can't… Gosh, Baek-du!
Could you please be quiet?
It's not a mouth exercise, is it?
Jeez.
Why do you have to be so loud?
By the way,
he seems so familiar somehow.
Because he was famous as a kid.
Right?
I knew it.
Wasn't he featured on TV
as a ssireum prodigy?
Sure, but not anymore.
By the way, sir,
please write a good article on Dong-seok.
Sure.
- Sir?
- Yes?
The article.
Oh, the article.
Of course. Don't worry about it.
Lim Dong-seok must be doing
a lot of interviews these days.
He speaks
much more eloquently than before.
Oh, don't even get me started.
News, variety shows…
Everyone wants to interview him now.
Look.
These are the texts
asking if he's available.
Excuse me for a second.
What the hell?
Hey.
- Hey, Seok-hui.
- Hey.
Hey, man.
GEOSAN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
42ND ALUMNI REUNION
Excuse me, ma'am.
Is that car your customer's?
The sign clearly says "no parking."
What are you doing?
Five, six, seven, eight…
Shouldn't you be training now?
Sixteen, seventeen, eighteen…
Did you give up on the game or what?
No, why is this here?
Hey, have you really given up?
- Hey.
- Oh, for goodness' sake!
What do you mean, "give up"?
I've been training until just now.
Oh, I see. I thought you skipped training
because you were feeling hopeless.
- All right. Take it easy, man.
- Wait, Cho Seok-hui.
Pay the reunion fee.
I was going to.
- There. I had…
- Hey, wait!
- too many coins at home. Bye.
- You little…
It's all done. Cho Seok-hui…
Check.
OH DU-SIK
You can pay here.
I'm working for the owner.
One set menu and a bottle of soju.
It's 10,000 won.
One second.
My goodness.
Please wait a second.
Gosh, what's wrong with me?
Jeez.
Where did it go?
Where is he going?
Here's your change, 40,000--
What? Where did he go?
OH DU-SIK
Let's drink.
Sure. Let's drink.
Hey, Baek-du.
You're too hasty, you know.
At the New Year's Championships,
you should've waited
before using the technique.
You shouldn't have just pushed it.
No, that's not it.
The problem is his satba skills.
Stop letting others reach your satba!
- Ssireum isn't charity.
- Enough.
He also gets too flustered
when the opponent lets go of his satba.
- Why are you like that?
- Why?
Could you stop lecturing him
like you're all ssireum champions
or something?
You all quit before your beards grew in.
What do you even know?
What?
We're just feeling bad for him.
- He's right.
- Yes.
He used to be so good as a kid,
and yet he never won any championships.
Because it's not for everyone.
- Hey!
- Hey, Champion Kwak!
- Hey, come on.
- Get over here.
Are you still not drinking?
You've retired already.
Grab a drink with us.
Drink with us.
You need the universe's blessing
to be a champion. Am I right?
You seem relaxed.
The game's in two days, and you're here.
You must be confident.
Guys, do you want to hear something funny?
- Sure.
- What is it?
One of the juniors on my team said
that he wished to compete against Geosan.
He kept going on about it.
So I said to him,
"Are you sure? Lim Dong-seok is good."
And guess what he said?
What did he say?
It can't be something nice.
"Come on. I'm not crazy."
"Not Lim Dong-seok, no."
"I want to wrestle Kim Baek-du."
Because that would be
a guaranteed win for him.
What happened to the prodigy, Kim Baek-du?
I mean, kids used to be scared
to wrestle against you.
It feels like that was in a past life.
Right, Kwak Jin-su!
What? You got something to say?
You didn't pay the reunion fee.
Oh, come on.
- Pay it.
- Pay it now.
Hey, pay the fee now.
- Are you okay?
- Water.
- Give him water.
No, that's alcohol.
That was alcohol?
Du-sik!
You didn't even come.
Oh Du-sik.
Oh Du-sik!
Du-sik!
Sik.
Oh Du-sik.
Du-sik.
Goodness.
Slow down when you turn a corner.
Okay?
Are you okay?
I said, are you okay?
Kim Baek-du, are you okay?
Yes.
I'm okay.
You can just go.
Are you sure?
If I leave, you'll regret it.
You.
- Are you…
- Come on. Get up now.
Gosh, you scared me.
Oh, please. Don't be dramatic.
Mom, why…
What are you doing there? You scared me.
You wouldn't get up,
so I was checking if you'd died.
Gosh, you ruined my morning.
When did you get back last night?
Last night?
When did I get back?
Don't you remember?
Did you drink yesterday?
Drink?
Did I drink yesterday?
How did you even come home?
Right. How did I come home?
Stop repeating my questions.
I'm the one asking, you brat.
Just come on out
and have breakfast already.
Gosh, get out now.
- Jeez.
- Go.
Come on out now!
Coming.
Where…
So this is why it was aching.
When did this happen?
Move aside. Make way, everyone.
Watch the car.
I think it's that way.
Darn it.
Choi Chil-seong…
is dead.
Goodness. What is going on?
Hey, you over there.
What now?
- Going to training?
- Yes.
- Do you remember last night?
- No.
You're the one that made me drink…
Right. Hey, check this out.
Is this from yester--
Never drink again, even after you die.
Even the king of the underworld
will get mad
at your alcohol blackouts.
Hey. Did I do something stupid last night?
Goodness. You have a serious problem.
Do you really not remember anything?
- Last night…
- I'm going to retire!
If I don't win
the champion title this time,
I'll retire.
Who is he talking to?
Come on, Coach.
I didn't drink a single drop of alcohol.
I'm 100% serious right now.
I have witnesses here too.
Guys, you're the witnesses, okay?
Anyway, if I…
If I ever
take this back later,
then, I won't be Kim Baek-du anymore.
You can call me… Well…
Ji-ri.
You can call me Kim Ji-ri, then!
Kim Ji-ri sounds good.
Kim Ji-ri. I like it.
Mount Jiri is a good mountain.
But doesn't it sound a bit strange
as a person's name?
Go and explain to the coach what happened.
- Explain what?
- What do you think?
About retirement.
You said that because you were drunk.
You're weird when you're sober too,
but when you're drunk,
you say a lot of dumb things.
You should apologize to your coach.
"Dumb things"?
What can you do after retirement?
Start a business? Be realistic.
Geosan Patrol Car Number Two.
Head to the accident site immediately
and cordon it off.
Anyway, go tell him you're sorry.
I've got to go now.
Bye, Kim Ji-ri.
That's not a dumb thing to say.
We'll begin the meeting
for the 2023 Dano Ssireum Championships…
What are you worried about?
Just think that this is for the best.
Don't you have compassion?
This is not about compassion.
Number three, Lee Ho-yeong.
I'm actually saying this
for Baek-du's sake.
To be blunt, holding on to false hope
is just a waste of time.
What if he never wins a title?
Then, will you take responsibility
for his life?
Come on. If he was that hopeless,
I wouldn't have kept him until now.
Number 21, Shin Gi-beom.
Sorry, I've got to take this.
Jeez.
- Hey, Coach Park.
- Hey!
How's Lim Dong-seok doing these days?
Dong-seok?
Well, of course.
He's as vigorous as ever.
That boy is a human bulldozer now.
He's in excellent shape.
Gosh, I really hope
he won't be one of our first opponents.
Well, what can you do?
Someone has to go against him.
Now, Geosan-gun Ssireum Team.
First, Lim Dong-seok in the Taebaek class.
Number 29.
Lim Dong-seok is number 29.
Next, Kim Baek-du in the Taebaek class.
28 KIM BAEK-DU
29 LIM DONG-SEOK
- Good work, guys.
- Thanks.
- Let's see.
- Wait, look at that.
Jeez.
What are the odds?
Seriously, from the preliminary round?
I heard Baek-du said he'd retire
if he didn't become the champion.
This doesn't look good.
Baek-du.
Hey, Dong-seok.
Can you give us a second?
That's not how you do it.
- What do you mean?
- Come here.
Your left hand is wrong. Come here.
I'll show you.
- Did you grab my leg satba?
- Yes.
- Keep your body close.
- Okay.
And push me with your left hand.
You've got to push me.
Watch how I do it.
Close up and push.
Did you see how easy that was?
I threw you over just like that.
Right.
- Do you think you got it?
- Yes.
Adjust the technique to fit your body
and keep practicing.
- Left hand?
- You can come back now.
Use your left hand.
Don't let it idle. Push.
Good. That was great.
Baek-du.
- Come here.
- Why?
Have you lost your mind?
"Push with your left hand"?
Do you want to be pushed by his left hand?
What do you mean…
28 KIM BAEK-DU
29 LIM DONG-SEOK
What did I just do?
Please keep us updated.
Sure.
Found anything from the car?
There's no ledger.
Even the dashcam was ripped out.
How about his phone?
- Is it not there?
- No.
But I definitely saw him
holding a phone yesterday.
You saw it too.
Seriously,
maybe this place is cursed or something.
Isn't it strange?
This man has been off the grid
for almost a year
and then, he suddenly comes here to die.
- This is just…
- Excuse me, detectives.
Is that car over there yours?
Yes. Why?
It's just that it kind of looks familiar.
Come on.
There are tons of cars
that look like that.
You're right.
Actually, my uncle had
the same car until last year.
He lost his license after drunk driving,
so he has to walk everywhere now.
By the way,
which department are you from again?
- Good work, guys.
- Well done.
Keep doing as you learned.
I should've used a Clenched Interception.
- Jeong-hun.
- Yes?
Could you speak quietly when we head home?
- Fine.
- Let's go eat.
- Hey, just be loud.
- Let's go.
- Good work.
Let's go.
Gosh, I'm tired.
- Beom-su.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
All right.
Baek-du, aren't you coming?
Go ahead. I'll join you soon.
28 KIM BAEK-DU
29 LIM DONG-SEOK
Why him, of all people?
- Hey.
- Hey there.
- You're here.
- Hey.
- You came.
- Continue what you're doing.
- Hi.
So who is Baek-du's opponent again?
His name is Lim Dong-seok.
He's on the same team.
Apparently, he's the best
in the Taebaek class these days.
Where is he from?
Where was it? Gongju?
Gongju has amazing chestnut bread.
Chestnut bread is tasty indeed.
Oh, boy.
Speaking of which,
last year's Baekdu champion
of the New Year's Championships
was from Gongju too.
Gongju is on fire these days.
Geosan is now all washed up.
Come on. We've got Jin-su.
Come on. He's retired.
Plus, Jin-su wrestled
in teams from the Seoul metropolitan area.
He's practically an emigrant.
Do you think Baek-du can be the champion?
That's not the problem.
You see, I had a dream a few days ago.
GEOSAN 08
And I saw Jun-hui in the dream.
- Jun-hui?
- Yes.
In the dream,
I saw Baek-du hurrying somewhere.
I got curious
and watched where he was going.
Then, I saw Jun-hui standing there.
He was beckoning Baek-du over.
It was a dream,
but I felt like he shouldn't go there.
So I tried to shout,
"Baek-du! You shouldn't go there!"
But my throat wouldn't let any sound out.
- I couldn't say anything.
- Oh, dear.
Even after waking up from the dream,
something didn't feel right.
Something bad might happen to Baek-du.
Don't be silly. It's just a stupid dream.
You said my dreams were visionary.
You even said
you'd buy one of my lucky dreams.
You better not mention this to Tae-baek…
What was I saying?
- What?
Something about Tae-baek.
- Right.
- Tae-baek?
Is Tae-baek coming tomorrow?
Well, this might be his son's last game,
so I'm sure he will. Right?
- Sure.
GEOSAN COUNTY OFFICE
No, he won't be here.
Really? Are you sure?
Yes. Since Geosan's hosting such
a big game for the first time in a while,
the association invited him
- to the game, apparently.
- But why did he turn them down?
I'm not sure.
I didn't hear further details.
Well, isn't it obvious?
The great Kim Tae-baek is too proud
to see his own son
being humbled in front of everyone.
It'd be mortifying.
Little did he know this would happen
when he was acting all haughty back then.
What's that?
- Tomorrow's welcome speech?
- Yes.
All right.
Let me see.
"Hello, ladies and gentlemen."
"Welcome to the region of passion
as hot as the scorching sun in June."
"I'm the governor of Geosan-gun,
Hong Man-sik."
I like the opening.
"I would like to extend
a warm welcome to all the teams
that have come to Geosan to participate
in the 2023 Dano Ssireum Championships."
No, leave it. I'll take it.
Hello.
Governor of our safe Geosan,
Hong Man-sik, speaking.
Yes.
What?
Hold on. What did you just say?
Where?
Seoul?
At the office?
What a strange woman.
Why is she using that in the shade?
Come on. We've all been there.
On rainy days, we sometimes forget
to fold our umbrellas
before entering a subway station.
She'll realize what she's doing
after she pokes someone's eye with it.
- Right.
- You're right.
She's leaving.
- What was that?
- No idea. She has the ears of a fox.
What does that mean?
Coach, are you leaving?
No, don't mind me.
- Hi, Coach.
- Hey.
Hi.
So how are you feeling?
Good. I'm feeling great.
That's great to hear.
I'm in excellent condition.
How funny is it?
What do you mean?
I'm talking about the tournament draw.
What a twist of fate, right?
It's a tournament.
That means we'd be matched up eventually.
But still…
Come on, Coach.
I'm Kim Baek-du. You know me.
There was a time
when nobody could hold a candle to me.
Of course I know that.
I know you used to be quite great.
Actually, I've been thinking
I wanted to go against Dong-seok.
That I stand a chance.
But I made a mistake.
- What mistake?
- I accidentally
shared my secret skill with him,
- and now he's slightly ahead of me.
- Oh, no!
What a shame, you know?
No way!
Why did you do that?
If you hadn't,
you would be the next champion.
I know. I would be the champion!
- About what I said
- What?
over the phone the other day…
Oh, that. Don't worry about it.
I know it was the alcohol talking.
Right.
What's wrong?
Did you actually mean it?
C-O-F-F-E-E.
I swear there was only one "E"
when I learned the word.
Anyway,
missing this one "E"
gave me quite some trouble.
Yesterday, someone drowned
in a reservoir in this town.
And apparently, that person had
some coffee here before it happened.
The next day, the detectives…
God, those damn bastards.
At first, they suspected
that I poisoned his coffee or something.
Then, they ran out of things
to pressure me with,
so they started picking on the spelling,
asking why there's
only one "E" in "coffee."
That's why I'm correcting it now.
Because I don't want to be wronged.
You don't seem surprised at all.
I mean, most people would
at least pretend to be surprised
if they heard about someone's death.
But you seem very calm,
as if you knew about it already.
I didn't expect this.
Anyway, that's what happened.
You know they say,
"A soft answer turns away wrath."
But because they were so rude to me,
even if I did see something,
I wouldn't have told them.
Hey, I thought you went to Seoul.
No. I'll leave in a few days.
Shouldn't there be one "E"?
Why are you changing it?
EMPEROR OF SSIREUM, KIM TAE-BAEK, EMBARKS
ON A NEW CHAPTER AS A GINSENG DIGGER
What in the…
Why is she using that?
The sun's gone down already.
How strange. Goodness.
Mom!
Hey, no need to run.
- Jeez.
- Why is she using that in the evening?
Hey.
- Have you eaten yet?
- No.
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
Jeez.
What's the matter?
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Come on. Hurry.
- I'm so hungry.
- Fine. Let's go.
Hey, you carry this, okay?
If you're so hungry,
why didn't you get yourself some food?
What are you doing? Come on.
Mom.
You know I have a game tomorrow.
I can't just eat vegetables.
It's not like you never won
because you didn't eat meat.
Goodness. There they go again.
The babies were switched at birth again.
It doesn't happen that often
in real life, you know.
- Jeez.
- Maybe it does.
I might have been switched too.
Who knows?
Maybe your real third son is
some successful 140 kg
Baekdu-class wrestler now.
He and I might've been switched at birth
in that ward.
Don't be ridiculous.
Why not?
Geum-gang is a Geumgang-class champion
and Han-ra is a Halla-class champion.
So Baek-du should be
a Baekdu-class champion too.
I'm the only one.
I'm the only lame one.
If you're gonna keep talking nonsense,
just go to bed.
Mom.
About tomorrow's game…
What about it?
What about tomorrow's game?
Never mind.
What is it? You're making me curious.
Nothing. I was going to say I'm nervous.
Isn't it strange?
- What?
- The detectives from Seoul.
Why did they come all the way here
to check the scene?
You're still on that?
Didn't they say yesterday
that they were just passing by--
Hey! Driving four hours from Seoul
isn't just passing by.
And I definitely saw that SUV
in front of the restaurant the other day.
Something's definitely fishy.
Okay.
2023 GEOSAN DANO SSIREUM CHAMPIONSHIPS
- Gosh, it's been a while.
- Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks for your hard work.
Thank you all.
- Hey, Kim Tae-baek's here!
- Thanks.
- He hasn't changed one bit.
- He really hasn't.
What's going on?
Didn't you say he was in the mountains?
- I was clearly told he wouldn't come.
- But he did.
And he's not even alone.
Goodness, Champion Kim Tae-baek.
- It's been a while, Man-sik.
- Ma…
Right.
I'm so honored to have you here.
Cut it out. You're just embarrassing me.
Let's have a seat.
Hello. Thank you.
Healthy bean sprouts good for your body…
Did I add too much sugar?
Try it.
What do you think? Too sweet?
- No.
- Really?
To me, it's perfect.
And I never even measure.
By the way,
the arena is not so far from here.
Why don't you go and cheer for him?
No way.
Why would I go all the way there
to watch those boring matches?
My gosh. Jin-su said the exact same thing.
But today's game is not like other games.
Today might be that day for Baek-du.
What day?
What do you mean?
Jeez, you really don't know anything.
Today, Baek-du…
What the heck was that?
You've got to be kidding me!
Are you serious right now?
This is my heart and history!
Come back here!
I'm going to find you and kick your butt!
Okay?
Jeez.
Let's go, Kim Baek-du!
- Go, Baek-du!
- Let's go!
I bet you had no choice
but to behave growing up.
You never challenged your dad, did you?
If I were you,
I wouldn't have even dreamed of doing it.
Don't be ridiculous.
The final boss in my family
isn't even here today.
This won't do.
- What are you doing? What?
- Nothing. I'll be right back.
- Where are you going?
- I know.
- He's going to poop.
- There goes Mr. Poop.
He should put that energy into the match.
I'm already tired
from putting the satba on.
What's going on?
Who is he talking to so seriously?
Baek-du!
Come on. You're up soon.
Sure. I'm coming.
Nice Clenched Interception!
- It's a Lifting Throw.
- Lifting…
Sir, two of our wrestlers
will be competing in the next match.
Is that so? Two wrestlers?
Wait, two?
Now, the next match is…
Gosh, I can't believe
these two are going head-to-head.
In the blue satba
is Kim Baek-du
from Geosan-gun Ssireum Team.
He's 32 years old, stands at 178 cm tall,
and weighs in at 78 kg.
After being discharged from the military
in 2019, he placed fifth
in the Taebaek class
in the last Chuseok Championships.
He was once called a rising star,
being the center of attention,
but sadly, he has yet to earn…
I'm going to retire.
That wasn't just some random
drunk babbling the other night.
I accidentally spilled out
what was on my mind.
I've been thinking about it
for a long time.
"What's the point of continuing
something I'm so horrible at?"
This has been weighing on me.
This will be it.
If I fail to be the champion again,
I will quit for real.
Blue satba,
Geosan-gun Ssireum Team's Kim Baek-du!
Jin-su told me
that Baek-du said
if he didn't become the champion today,
he was going to retire.
That damn brat.
How could he not tell me?
Contending against him is
Champion Lim Dong-seok
from the same Geosan-gun Ssireum Team.
He's 24 years old,
stands at 185 cm tall,
and weighs in at 79 kg.
He's won
a whopping six championships
in the Taebaek class.
Darn it.
Is Coach Park's hand cursed or what?
How the hell could he mess up
the draw like this? God damn it.
Baek-du. Don't underestimate experience.
When he was wearing a diaper,
you were already in your satba.
You're much more experienced.
Okay.
Blue, red.
Champion Lim Dong-seok
is certainly on a streak now.
- Go, Baek-du!
- Since winning
his first champion title in 2021,
he's always been at the top.
Right. Champion Lim Dong-seok
never really stood out
when he was in high school.
Since Coach Yeon Sang-cheol,
the coach of his current team,
recruited him,
his skills have improved drastically,
bringing him to where he is now.
The coach must be so proud
of his keen eye for talent.
- Even now…
- Grab satbas.
He's coaching him.
That's not why.
When two wrestlers from the same team
compete against each other,
the coach is supposed to coach
the wrestler in the blue satba,
according to the rules.
Gosh, he's going to lose.
Why would he let him
grab his satba so generously?
That kind boy is
certainly going to Heaven.
Baek-du, don't let him get a head start.
They stood up.
He's trying a Lifting Throw.
Will he be able to throw him over?
Lim wins the first round
in just five seconds!
Lim Dong-seok didn't use
the Hook skill, which is his specialty.
Instead, he lifted Kim
as soon as the match began
to throw him, but it didn't work out.
- That was amazing.
- So he let him down
and hooked his ankle.
That was incredible.
Baek-du, hold his satba tight.
Pull yourself together.
Even if you end up losing,
you've got to give it your all!
You don't want to lose and retire
by fumbling.
Then, you'll regret it
for the rest of your life.
Baek-du.
Hey, Kim Baek-du!
Don't be scared.
- Stay strong.
- Okay.
- Do you know what I mean?
- Yes.
All right.
If Lim wins this round again,
the match will be over.
Let's go!
Let's go, Baek-du!
Hold the satba tight!
GEOSAN-GUN
LIM DONG-SEOK
Knees up.
Stand up.
A hook!
Lim lifts Kim for a Lifting Throw.
But Kim holds out.
Hold out!
There you go!
A counterattack!
Kim Baek-du!
He wouldn't let him win
with the same technique.
Kim seized the chance
and scored with a counterattack.
Don't get excited.
- Come here.
- Okay.
See? You just needed to focus.
This is the last round.
- Hold onto the satba.
- Okay.
Dong-seok is tall.
So push him down.
- I did.
- Don't talk back.
Hold onto his satba, okay?
Breathe.
- Don't worry. You got this.
- Okay.
Let's go!
See? He can do it.
Gosh, my heart is racing.
- He's getting the hang of it.
- I'm so nervous.
Blue, red.
- Focus.
- Okay.
Hold onto his satba, okay?
- Let's go!
Kneel down.
- Baek-du may win.
- I know. Baek-du is determined today.
Ready.
Knees up.
Stand up.
Hook!
Yes!
Hold out!
Both wrestlers fell at the same time.
We never know.
He won.
No, we don't know yet.
What now?
VIDEO REVIEW
They'll review the video.
Did you see it? Did he fall first?
Of course not! Baek-du definitely won!
What's wrong with the judge?
We don't need a video review for this.
This is not right.
Come along. Turn.
Take position.
According to the video review,
the blue-satba wrestler's elbow
touched the ground first.
The winner is the red-satba wrestler!
This is not fair!
No, this is not right!
Are you okay?
I said, are you okay?
No.
I'm not okay.
This time, I'm not okay.
It's for the best.
It's not like you were going to wrestle
for the rest of your life.
This is for the best.
We're closed…
for today.
I heard Baek-du lost unfairly today.
We're out of coffee beans.
The guys had a meeting here
after watching Baek-du's match…
- Right. You don't drink.
- I do.
Sometimes.
Did you watch Baek-du's match too?
Why would I? It's a waste of time.
I heard he did a great job today.
But he lost because of an unfair call.
It wasn't an unfair call.
From where I was watching,
I saw Dong-seok turn him over properly.
Baek-du's elbow
did touch the ground first.
So you watched it.
Did you watch it in the arena?
There's something
I've always wondered about.
What is it?
Why do you hate Baek-du so much?
Did you have a fight?
Or did he not pay you back?
No.
Then, why do you hate him?
I heard you've been friends
since you were little.
We're not friends.
I have never thought of him as a friend.
Baek-du was much closer
to this other kid than me.
What's all this?
Who? Du-sik?
How do you know Du-sik?
How can I not know?
Ever since I moved here,
I've heard that name hundreds of times.
This is great. I've always been curious.
About what?
Is there a story behind Du-sik's family?
What do you mean? There's no story.
Come on.
I've seen people here wince
whenever they hear Du-sik's name.
Something happened, right?
How strange. Who put this here?
What is it?
What is it that freaks everyone out
whenever Du-sik is brought up?
Don't ask me. I don't know either.
Yes, you do.
I know you two were bosom buddies.
- What friends?
- Bosom buddies.
What? Am I wrong?
Well, I guess we kind of were.
Are you okay?
I said, are you okay?
Come on. Get up now.
Only Du-sik has that.
Has what?
You know, what you just…
Du-sik is a girl.
- What?
- Du-sik is a girl.
Are you okay?
Hey.
Are you…
by any chance… I'm asking just in case.
What?
Are you Du-sik?
You are.
You're Oh Du-sik.
LIKE FLOWERS IN SAND
You're not Du-sik?
Why do you ask? Why do you want to know
where her family is from?
Just think about it.
If you were Du-sik,
would you like to come back here?
Shouldn't you be training?
I've retired.
Retired? When?
Did you really quit ssireum?
What are you going to do
other than ssireum?
Who is it?
Who is this new person?
I'll be the new general manager
of the Geosan-gun Ssireum Team.
I'm Oh Yu-gyeong.
Subtitle translation by: Sunyoung Baek