I'm going to confess
to the girl I like.
Me too.
I'm going to confess
to someone I like.
(Dear My Name)
Ji Woo, look here.
You said you wouldn't shoot
my face. Stop it.
I have to do an interview.
Help me out.
How does it feel for your name
to sparkle for the first time
in five years?
At first, I was disappointed
that he doesn't have my name.
It feels awesome.
Do you like it that much?
What do you like so much?
He just suddenly...
(Jae Ha Yoo)
How did you know
about my hideout?
Your hideout?
It just looked pretty.
I'm impressed you know that.
Others think it's scary.
It looks beautiful
from the inside.
Do you go there often?
Yes.
This is a secret.
Only I know about that place.
What a pity.
Now, I know about that place.
I'll make an exception.
Since when...
were you named?
It was in middle school.
I was lying down
on the tennis court.
You remember in detail.
I do.
It was an unforgettable moment.
Five years, was it?
You must've waited
for a long time.
You're wrong.
I'm still waiting.
Still.
You don't know
how this feels, do you?
What a pity.
It's a nice feeling.
By the way, why did you ask?
-Well...
-If it's because of me,
you don't need to worry.
I guess
fate breaks down sometimes.
I'm hungry.
Do you want to ride in the back
since you're hungry?
"Do you want to ride
in the back?"
Hey.
He grabbed your hand
and rode the bike?
Isn't it obvious, then?
But he didn't actually
grab my hand.
He probably just wanted
to befriend me.
That's why he touched you?
Then he's definitely a playboy!
I mean... Place your hand here.
He grabbed it and said,
"Do you want to ride
in the back?"
He made my heart skip a beat.
It's hot in here.
Hey, the playboy is here.
What were you giggling about?
It's none of your business.
Gosh, at this rate,
you guys should just
live together.
I should go home.
Hey, good luck.
Why did you buy so much?
Sae Rom, you're having dinner
with us, right?
No, I need to go.
We're having stir-fried pork.
-Yes!
-Your stir-fried pork
is the best.
But I really can't.
-I'm meeting my ex.
-What?
Why?
What was that reaction?
Why would you meet your ex?
I don't think you know,
but there are steps
to breaking up.
She's meeting her ex?
How could she say that
in front of her boyfriend?
Fine, he's too handsome
to get over.
I'm leaving.
Hey, Sae Rom!
Are they not in a relationship?
Should we have pizza,
your favorite?
Yes, pizza!
Do you like pizza?
I didn't know that.
Why are you following me?
Don't meet him.
I get that you're worried,
but I'm meeting him for closure.
What if you get hurt again?
How many times has it been?
By now, you should know
how to avoid them.
What you're doing
isn't being nonchalant.
It's really pathetic.
Then what do you want me to do?
I want to meet my soulmate,
but he's nowhere to be found.
I feel like the only way
to find him is
by pretending to be nonchalant
when I'm actually pathetic.
I wonder if I'd be going
through this had I been named.
What?
Do you think those who are named
have no worries?
There are countless options
in our lifetime.
It'd be nice
if at least
finding your soulmate was easy.
What if it's easy
but you just don't know it yet?
What?
That's your problem.
You try to find the answer
in all the wrong places.
You need to look around you.
What are you saying?
Never mind if you don't get it.
So what's the answer?
-I don't know. Don't follow me.
-Wait up!
I want to be alone.
Goodness.
Wake me up in ten minutes.
You can sleep for 15 minutes.
All right. 20, it is.
You're wrong.
I'm still waiting.
Still.
If it's because of me,
you don't need to worry.
I guess
fate breaks down sometimes.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were sleeping.
I like this song.
Hey.
Why are you drinking alone?
I guess I'll have one can less.
Thanks.
I'm going to confess
to the girl I like.
Who is she?
It's a secret.
Come on.
Me too.
I'm going to confess
to someone I like.
Who is it?
Well...
Remember what we talked
about last time?
Right, we talked
about men liking men.
Actually...
That's about me.
What?
I've never thought of it.
But I realized
the important thing is
about liking that person,
whether it's a guy or a girl.
I found myself liking him.
Thanks for this.
What?
Does he think Ji Woo is a guy?
Let me help.
It's okay. I can manage.
You might trip.
Are you this kind to everyone?
No, I'm not good at being kind.
Being kind isn't a game.
It's not about being good at it.
I'm good at playing games.
Was that a joke?
It truly felt strange.
My heart fluttered
for someone else
other than my dream soulmate.
You are kind.
By the way,
I have a question.
Dear my name
whom I've been waiting for
without realizing it...
Just like the name
engraved on my arm,
I think I'm broken as well.
What do you think
about a guy liking another guy?
What?
Can't believe it!
We were so carefree when we were alone.
Shall I ask Jae Ha to move out?
Feels like having a one-sided love for a long time.
Were you telling me you love me last time？
I'll call you when I find it.
There's only one thing that I don't know.
No, two.
It's already too late
when I know it.
I'm going to confess to the girl I like.
Who?
It's a secret.
My name.