It's Mr. Seo.
My investigator's in there!
Jeong Min's in there!
Other than the head injury
and the injection mark,
we found no external traumas.
Sodium pentothal?
I have Mr. Seo's
call history from yesterday.
You cannot continue
Seo Jeong Min's autopsy.
- Based on what grounds?
- Destruction of evidence.
You can't perform the autopsy...
since you killed him.
The last person Mr. Seo called...
was you!
(Call History)
Mr. Baek Beom,
you're under arrest...
for the murder of Seo Jeong Min
as of now.
You have the right
to remain silent...
and to deny saying anything
that can be used against you.
You have the right to an attorney.
And you may request a review
of legality for confinement...
to the competent court.
What's going on?
Prosecutor Kang,
what are you talking about?
Who killed whom?
Please leave, you two.
What about the autopsy?
It's been a while, Dr. Baek.
Let us go.
Let's get ready.
You must remain in the office
until the autopsy is over.
Get out. This is my office.
He might destroy evidence,
so don't let him touch anything.
Okay.
What happened, Hyun?
The last person Mr. Seo talked to
before he died was...
- Baek Beom.
- What?
Dr. Baek doesn't have
an alibi for last night,
and we found sound evidence too.
The autopsy probably started.
Let's go.
(Medical Examiner Baek Beom)
Thank you for coming over
in such a short notice.
Current time, 10 o'clock on the dot.
I will begin the autopsy.
Right side of the forehead,
laceration.
"Right side of the forehead,
laceration".
Two needle marks on
the brachial artery of left arm.
"Two needle marks on
the brachial artery of left arm".
How old do these look?
I'm not sure.
But they don't seem too old.
- Take a good picture.
- Yes.
Do a close-up too.
Overall, I don't see
much external injury...
or any damages done
by an external force.
He has short nails too.
Okay. Let's cut him up.
Rib cutter.
(Rib cutter: equipment used
to cut through ribs)
Scalpel.
Send this down to
Toxic Substances Division.
Let's shave his head.
This is too much, Hyun.
I know.
But you have to watch it.
You must keep your eyes on this...
to reveal the truth.
This is the last story...
that Mr. Seo is telling us.
Around the laceration of
his right forehead,
I see bleeding under his scalp...
and linear fraction of skull.
(Bleeding under scalp:
Caused by scalp skin damage)
(Linear fraction: A fraction that
causes lines on the bone)
I also see subdural hemorrhage
where he bled under the scalp.
Does that mean
he was severely injured?
(Subdural hemorrhage:
Epidural bleeding)
It's too early to say so.
Let us wrap up.
Thank you, Professor Pyo.
Prosecutor Eun Sol of
Seoul Eastern District.
I've heard a lot about you.
Nice to meet you, Prosecutor Eun.
- What do you think?
- First off,
I don't see anything else
other than the head injury...
and the needle marks.
If there was a physical fight,
there should be assault marks
or oppression wounds...
that can show how someone else
was involved in his death.
But there's nothing like that.
I'll have to refrain from
sharing my thoughts...
until we have the result from
the Toxic Substances Division.
Yes. I understand.
You said everything was done.
Where else will we find
better evidence than this?
- Hyun.
- No, it's still not enough.
If we get into this in a hurry
and then end up losing him,
- we'll never be able to get him.
- There's no way we'll lose him.
The security footage shows that
he stole the drugs.
Jeong Min, we're almost there.
Trust me and give me
just a little more time.
Take this.
Tomorrow's your birthday.
It's So Hee's birthday already?
Right, you said your birthday is
the same day as Ms. Han.
You gave her the same birthday
at the orphanage...
because you didn't want her to be
made fun of for not knowing the day.
You remembered that?
Jeong Min, I can never give up
on Ms. Han's case...
and my brother's case.
I will find out the truth
no matter what happens.
Baek Beom, that jerk.
I thought this was
enough to get him.
I couldn't protect him.
It's not your fault.
- Don't be so hard on yourself.
- It is my fault.
I was too indecisive.
I just kept him waiting.
I'll never make
the same mistake twice.
Make sure you change
the formalin for the fixed tissues.
(Fixed tissues:
tissues fixed with formalin)
(Formalin: a type of preservative)
This is so wrong.
It's not like he's a criminal.
What's going on?
What are we going to do?
Dr. Baek will be turned into
a suspect for this case...
and will be escorted
to the prosecutor's office.
He could've gone to the office
himself to be questioned.
He is a public official...
who's been working here
for 10 years.
Actually, that is exactly why
we need to detain him.
He's an expert who has worked
at the National Forensic Service...
for over 10 years. He knows
everything about forensics.
He may not run away,
but he surely can
attempt to destroy evidence.
What?
We should get going too.
Okay.
You two.
Are you really going to
do this to Dr. Baek?
This is so wrong.
Well, we are also...
Prosecutor Eun, I'm so sorry
that you got hurt last time...
and got stuck in the autopsy room
because of me.
But that's my fault.
Dr. Baek even stitched up your hand.
Don't you think this is too much?
Prosecutor Eun.
Investigate thoroughly
and objectively,
and please reveal the truth.
I promise to do that.
Darn it.
Do you have some lab-made alcohol?
Here it is.
Aren't you angry too?
This is just wrong.
Of course. This is
an insult to the lab.
This is so insulting.
Exactly.
They shouldn't do this to Dr. Baek.
Total nonsense.
They don't trust my lab results
and take all the samples?
- What?
- They even took the blood samples.
They did. Those and
the tissue samples.
They even cleaned the autopsy room.
As if we'd collect
whatever they dropped.
Doctor, stop drinking.
I think you had enough.
This?
Oh, no, it's not alcohol.
It's mineral water.
Can I have some?
Darn it, it's alcohol.
Mr. Kang.
Mr. Seo's call history
for the last three months.
Thanks.
(Call history)
Hyun, do you really have to do this?
There's something you don't know.
June 11, 2018.
2pm.
You talked to Mr. Seo.
(Call history)
7:30pm.
You left your home.
You took a taxi...
to Gangil-dong
where Mr. Seo lives.
At 8:35pm...
at Gangil Junction,
you got out of the taxi.
(Taxi meter charges)
(Direct debit)
Then at 9:05pm,
you entered his apartment block.
There's no security camera
on that block.
You must have known already.
But a dashboard camera
in a parked car...
was recording at the time.
Jeans and a hoodie.
Based on a comparison
with the base of a traffic cone,
the man's shoe size is 285mm.
Isn't that your size?
Mr. Seo opened the door,
and you went inside.
I bet that...
you had an argument.
What's the reason?
My sister died because of you!
Tell me! Just tell me.
A medical examiner?
You're a medical examiner?
You're a necrophiliac.
That's what you are! A necrophiliac!
How many lives did you take?
How many? Tell me yourself.
- Tell me yourself!
- Is there evidence?
Evidence?
You're done for. Do you get that?
You're done for.
You pathetic fool.
Wait.
You pushed him from behind
when he was distracted...
and slammed
Mr. Seo's head on the floor.
Then you injected him
to disguise it as suicide.
Then you took the glass
to destroy evidence.
Then at around midnight,
you returned home.
Don't write a novel
based on my life.
I'll see how long
your hypocrisy holds up.
Mr. Baek, why did you
meet with Mr. Seo?
I didn't see him.
Shall we talk about
motive for murder?
Mr. Seo recently procured
some evidence.
10 years ago,
at 11:02pm on June 4, 2008,
Seon Hospital's drug storage room.
You couldn't have forgotten.
On that day too,
someone died.
Kang Yong, a thoracic surgeon
at Seon Hospital.
My older brother.
Do you remember?
Wasn't he your best friend?
I bet it's the one day
you want to erase from your life.
Since that day,
you quit practicing medicine...
and chose to deal with dead people.
Did you think that...
you could hide the truth
of that day by killing Mr. Seo?
I investigated this case
for 10 years.
Now, I will wrap it up.
Do you know...
what grudge a person holds
when they are killed?
It's the fact that
the last thing they saw...
before they died was
the face of their murderer.
While doing autopsies,
you looked into the eyes
of many dead people.
The fear left in their eyes.
The hatred,
the resentment,
the grudge.
You saw them all.
You killed my brother, didn't you?
With the same drugs as these!
While performing autopsies,
you wondered...
who did it, how,
and who could be so evil!
But the real root of evil...
is you who's sitting here!
Why did you do it?
Why did you kill him?
Were you that afraid...
that the truth about Han So Hee
and my brother would come out?
Is that why you killed him?
Tell me.
Hyun.
- Open the door.
- Mr. Kang.
Let go. Stop it.
Do you know
how many people you killed?
Get the master key!
Kang Yong.
Han So Hee.
Seo Jeong Min!
- Let go!
- You can't play me!
I will not...
let you off.
This is the end of your life.
Mr. Seo's death...
will not go in vain.
I will investigate this case
jointly with the murder of...
Seon Hospital's surgeon, Kang Yong.
Same perpetrator, same MO.
You hid it for 10 years,
but not anymore.
I'll ask you one last time.
Will you confess?
I refuse to give a statement.
Okay.
Do whatever you want.
Put him in detention.
- Hyun.
- I'm sorry.
I couldn't tell you.
The secret you kept for 10 years...
was this?
It must've been so hard...
for you.
Guess what?
Knowing there's a truth
that I had to uncover...
kept me going.
That's why I must...
close both of these cases.
Poor Mr. Seo.
My heart breaks for him.
Calm down, Mi Young.
By the way, how could he die
so suddenly like this?
How?
Are you all right? Don't cry.
What on earth is going on?
Did they really arrest Dr. Psycho?
But how is he related
to Mr. Seo's case?
- It doesn't add up.
- You know how Dr. Psycho...
turns crazy when it's a homicide and
goes all out during the autopsy?
He can guess how
the victims were murdered.
- It's all based on his experience.
- Gosh.
Don't try to force
the pieces together.
But something is fishy.
Why was he the last one to talk
to Mr. Seo on the phone?
On top of that, there are security
camera footage and taxi routes.
Evidence against him is
more than enough.
Why are you reading that?
We already arrested the suspect.
A long time ago, Mr. Seo worked...
in the specialized narcotic unit
at Seoul Central District Court.
- Really?
- Yes.
Quiet.
Hey, be quiet.
I don't want to inject you guys.
You're a medical examiner. What do
you think about being a suspect?
Do you admit to all the charges?
Why did you murder an investigator
of the prosecutors' office?
Say a word to the deceased's family.
The arrest of a medical examiner
for the murder of an investigator...
has put the public in shock.
Both the prosecution and the NFS
are flustered by the incident.
The prosecution...
announced that they plan to file for
the arrest warrant this afternoon.
The prosecution directed all of
its resources to prove the case.
They announced
that they will investigate...
What now? What will happen to him?
Did you hear from Dr. Pyo Yoo Seong?
I don't think he's going to
take any calls from the NFS.
What?
We must do something
to help Dr. Baek. Please, sir?
We can't just sit here and watch.
("Suspect A Exercises
His Right to Remain Silent")
(Public Servant's Murder at Home)
It happened 10 years ago.
It was concluded as suicide.
But you want to bring
that up all over again?
Mr. Seo was investigating
the case from 10 years ago.
This is his second crime
after finding out about...
Mr. Seo's investigation
with the same MO.
We need to combine these two cases.
The victim was my older brother.
What?
What are you trying to say?
You're a prosecutor.
How can a prosecutor connect
his brother's case with another one?
To us, this will be considered
a personal revenge. Got that?
The suspicion is well-grounded,
and I have been gathering evidence.
Hyun, this isn't like you.
The day I put on my gown,
I kept this case
in a corner of my heart.
You became a prosecutor
with that intention in mind?
You did a very good job
concealing your true intention.
I'm sorry.
Are you going to carry this out
no matter what?
If this goes wrong,
you'll lose your job.
I'm prepared to do so.
You can't lead the case since it's
your brother's. What now?
I was hoping
you'd lead this investigation.
Me? You want me
to lead the investigation?
This act of nonsense...
should end with you.
What do you think about this,
Prosecutor Eun?
With this case,
either Prosecutor Kang
or Dr. Baek...
will end up facing the bitter end.
I'm aware that
this is a difficult case.
Do you think you can do this?
If you don't want to take this on,
be honest, and tell me.
No.
I'll do my best on this case.
I'll reinforce impartiality...
and investigate the case together.
- You're confident, right?
- I can prove his crime.
Okay.
A medical examiner from the NFS
murdered two people in total.
And like nothing happened,
he's been performing autopsies...
and worked there for 10 years.
Baek Beom.
His eyes did look unusual.
How dare he murder
an investigator from my office?
(Public Servant's Murder at Home)
Why are you here?
Did you watch the news?
Hey.
Why did you have to take Beom? Why?
Look what happened to him after
working with corpses all his life.
I'm sorry.
Don't let me catch
a sight of you ever again.
And seeing what has happened to him,
he'll never return to the NFS.
Uncuff him, please.
Why are you lying?
There's more, isn't there?
- You're hiding something.
- I refuse to answer.
Do you not realize
what's happening to you?
You shouldn't be taking
this stance right now.
I don't care.
If you keep this up,
you'll be indicted for murder.
Do you not care
about your future, Dr. Baek?
My future?
Nothing is certain in our future.
Except for the fact that
everyone will die one day.
What about the autopsy?
- What?
- Do you have the initial report?
What about the head injury
and the injection mark?
- What else did he find?
- It hasn't come out yet.
Is that what
you're curious about now?
Forget it then.
The arrest of a medical examiner...
- What's that?
- for the murder of...
an investigator
has put the public in shock.
- The prosecution and the NFS...
- Things must be hard at the NFS.
The prosecution...
announced that they plan to file for
the arrest warrant this afternoon.
The prosecution directed all of
its resources to prove the case.
As a proud investigative agency
of Korea,
they revealed their determination
to solve the case.
(Stella)
Forget it.
Mr. Jang.
Wait. Did you come here alone?
Yes, I brought fried chicken.
Fried chicken?
I can't even eat that.
It must be hard.
Gosh, you're going through a lot.
This is nothing.
Things happen when detectives
are working on the field.
It's all part of the job.
- You saw the news, right?
- Yes. Just now.
But what's going on?
Do you remember
when you were framed for murder?
Dr. Baek didn't even sleep
and raised the maggots.
You remember, right?
Yes, of course.
I'm always thankful for that.
Dr. Baek has a terrible personality,
but he wouldn't kill anyone.
Of course, I know he's terrible.
I know all about him,
but I also know that
he wouldn't do such a thing.
Then can you take action this time?
Take action? Me?
No, I need to recover.
It hurts here.
Please help us.
"Us"? "Us"?
- Stella is on our side.
- What?
- Are you getting discharged? Okay.
- I must get going now.
- Hurry.
- Okay.
Darn it. Who are you? No.
Who are you?
You scum. You little...
Who's there?
Hey, hey. Hey, you. My goodness.
Are you all right?
(Lieutenant Cha Soo Ho)
Gosh, this wound is bothering me.
Hey.
Are these the convicts Mr. Seo
arrested at the narcotics unit?
Yes. Gosh, those are
some nasty criminals.
Most of them are still serving time.
- What about the ones that got out?
- There are only a few of them.
One of them seems fishy.
He was released on parole
for being an exemplary prisoner.
He lost touch
with the parole officer.
"Jang Tae Joo".
Tae Joo, that jerk.
He was getting ready to "fix
some people up" once he got out.
Fix them up how?
He said that he at least
killed hundreds of dogs so far.
He told me that killing people
wasn't that much different.
He's a total psycho.
Wait.
He killed dogs?
All the evidence so far
points to Dr. Psycho...
I mean, the suspect.
Do we have a report of the scene?
They didn't find any noticeable
footprints or fingerprints.
There wasn't even
a speck of dust in the house.
Did Mr. Seo's call history
show anything odd?
Nothing much.
Why do you think Mr. Seo
called him to come over?
Think about it.
Even we have never been
to his place.
What do you think
went on between them?
That's why Baek Beom
is refusing to give a statement.
No one knows what happened
between them,
and the dead can't talk.
I found out someone
who has a grudge on Mr. Seo.