(Episode 28)
How small a clue may be, as long
as it's relevant to the killer...
Why do you think the killer wasn't
caught 30 years ago?
The police utilized a lot of
manpower to catch the killer.
Do you know...
how Yoo Han Cheol who killed
26 people was caught in 2003?
We checked 50 bus routes, thousands
of subway security footages,
and 300,000 telephone
circuits thoroughly.
Deploying people isn't the answer.
Dr. Baek.
- You're hanging onto minor things.
- Minor things?
Do we rate the wounds on a body?
Well, why don't we do both?
The NFS will follow up on your lead.
And we can investigate
her acquaintances and hometown.
Please check the network record
from the base station...
near the convenience store
and her home around the time...
she had gone missing.
And check the alibi of every man
in their 50s near the location.
Yes, sir. I'll get right on it.
We cannot overlook
the possibility of a copycat.
The Internet is where the copycats
get most of their information.
We're searching every website
regarding crimes.
Sure, you can continue
with that lead.
Is there anything we can use
from the investigation 30 years ago?
You can hear all about that
in person.
Do you know what I got the most...
when I was investigating
the Wuseong Serial Murder?
- "You still haven't caught him?"
You must have gone through a lot.
That time, I was diagnosed
with degenerative arthritis.
I'll be in this wheelchair
for the rest of my life.
There were times we got close
to catching the culprit.
Remember? There was a survivor.
- You mean Lee Kyung Ja?
- That's right. Lee Kyung Ja.
The tip of the knife missed
the heart by a whisker.
That's how she survived.
She climbed down to where
the houses were and made a report.
We were all dispatched and blocked
every single route.
But we lost him in the end.
We should've caught him then, right?
We tried everything we could
at that time.
Our captain...
Was her name Um Ji Hye?
You know the first victim?
He even went to her house
and slept in her bed.
He wanted to meet her
even in his dream.
- My goodness.
- Darn it.
- You should've been more careful.
- I'm sorry.
- Are you all right?
- Look at this. It's all ruined.
- That's all right.
- I'm sorry.
You may go.
I feel terrible for Captain Ham.
The higher-ups pressured us
to catch the killer.
His detectives complained
that they were struggling.
He was caught in the crossfire
and ended his own life.
The article left
by Captain Ham was...
the first victim's photo.
Director Park.
It's about Wuseong Serial Murder.
The first victim, Um Ji Hye,
from 34 years ago.
You performed the autopsy.
(Name: Um Ji Hye)
That's right.
Yes, I did the autopsy.
I think it was my first case
at the NFS.
The knife touched the rib, right?
Right here. This one.
34 years ago, the killer...
wasn't good at using the knife. He
stabbed the bones in several places.
Did you find any traces of
the knife on the bones?
Looking at the cuts, I think
the blade must've been destroyed.
That's a possibility. However,
we didn't have the technology to
detect the substances back then.
Dr. Baek.
If you need to see me, come to
the headquarters. What is it?
Find me a body. Okay?
Her name is Um Ji Hye.
This is urgent.
- Hold on a second. Dr. Baek.
- Yes?
Are you asking me for a favor?
What?
Remember this? The recording...
Thank you.
I want another recording like this.
"Do me a favor." How about this?
Can you do it for me?
Okay, okay. Here you go.
- Get out, you jerk.
- What?
- Get out.
Get out now.
Luckily, the family buried the body
and didn't cremate it.
I sent the address
to Mr. Jang's phone.
I think it's over there.
Dr. Baek, it's really spooky here.
We might see ghosts.
Dr. Baek!
That's just mud.
And your face is scarier.
Come quickly.
I think my foot got stuck.
You need to hold me.
Wait. My goodness. Darn it.
The soil must be very wet.
- We might have a chance.
- What? What chance?
Request for its substance analysis.
It's urgent.
- I think that might be right.
- Can you pass that over?
His looks are a separate matter.
He's known to have a temper.
When you search...
Sir.
Gosh, what brings you here?
I came here to tell you
something important.
Okay, please come this way.
Welcome. What brings you here?
This.
These are the files on the guy
we were chasing 30 years ago.
I see.
Here.
Kang Chi Soo.
He was 24 years old back then.
His height was 180cm.
His shoe size was 260mm.
This fits the profile of the killer.
I met thousands of suspects.
I can't forget about him
even until this day.
Talk, you jerk!
It's you, right?
You're trying to get your number up
by arresting innocent people.
Do you think I don't know that?
- What?
- Don't patronize me.
Do you have evidence?
- I asked you if you had evidence!
- You scumbag.
He was released
due to lack of evidence,
but he left the country right away.
But we heard that a few years ago,
he returned to Wuseong.
What? If that's true,
something is definitely brewing.
- Locate Kang Chi Soo right now.
- Yes, sir.
But by the way,
only the writer can read this.
I can't read his handwriting.
Back then,
we wrote up reports by hand.
I'm known
for my terrible handwriting.
Actually, we were having a hard time
reviewing the past documents.
What do you say?
How about you lend us a hand?
We're old now.
I'm not sure if we can help.
Don't say that.
You already helped us a lot.
- Let's do this then.
- Gosh.
(Soo Photo Studio)
- Excuse me. Did the owner change?
- Yes?
No, it's the same owner.
- I see. Really?
- Yes.
I just thought that
it didn't taste the same anymore.
Oh, do you not like it?
No, no. It's better.
- Please enjoy your meal then.
- How long have you been...
- working here?
- It's been about six months.
Name, Kang Chi Soo.
He's 54 right now and still single.
He went abroad
and majored in photography...
after the Wuseong Serial Murder,
then came back five years ago
and opened a photo studio.
Where was he
on the day of the incident?
Kang is a bit unusual.
He does not use a cell phone.
That's why he was not found
on any base station records.
And he's always
on the same schedule.
He opens his studio at 10am,
eats lunch alone
at a nearby diner at 12pm,
closes the studio at 8pm,
works in the darkroom
until late at night,
and comes home after 12am.
He's very meticulous.
Seems obsessive.
The murderer is the same.
He always made the same knot
and did everything the same way.
Also,
this alleyway has...
no security cameras.
Goodness.
There's a possibility
he chose that place on purpose.
That photo studio has a darkroom.
All lights are blocked out.
- It's a perfectly secretive room.
- This is rather interesting.
The first victim, Um Ji Hye.
Let's redo her autopsy.
What?
- Why?
- Murderers make...
the most mistakes
on their first murder.
Redoing her autopsy?
- With a 34-year-old body?
- Back then, something was left out.
- What is it?
- I have to look at the body first.
There's no need. It's decomposed.
You won't find a thing.
Are you suggesting that
we should be inattentive?
Doctor Baek, watch your language.
What did I say wrong?
I'll take the responsibility.
Prosecutor Eun.
Are you sure it'll be okay?
It won't be easy
to persuade the family.
If there's even a little possibility
that a case or a suspect...
from the past
has anything to do with this,
then shouldn't we reinvestigate it?
I'm curious to know what we'll find.
That's a waste of time.
Well, at this stage, I agree...
with Prosecutor Eun that
we should keep all possibilities...
on our minds as we investigate.
- Prosecutor Do.
- I'm sorry, sir.
I will take care of the result.
Prosecutor Eun, you can
work with Lieutenant Cha...
and get the project going
by persuading Um's family.
We'll keep digging
behind Kang Chi Soo.
Okay. Let's get to work.
Goodbye.
Hello?
Excuse me.
Hello.
You have the wrong house.
There's no one here...
Oh, it's not that.
We're from Seoul Eastern District
Prosecutor's Office,
Ms. Im.
(Im Sook Ja, 69 years old,
first victim, Um Ji Hye's mom)
- You can have some juice and go.
- Ma'am.
We have something
to discuss with you.
We reopened the case.
We'll take in the murderer and...
I don't care
if he gets caught or not.
So don't ever come back.
I finally forgot all about it.
- Why are you doing this again?
- You never forgot.
Not even once.
That teddy bear over there.
The Wuseong Serial Murders.
From 1984 to 1988,
over five years
in the Wuseong-dong area...
That is...
the same teddy bear
that Ji Hye had...
on the day of her death.
One of our detectives...
still keeps...
Ji Hye's picture in his wallet.
This time,
we will catch him for sure.
Please.
Help us out.
Goodness, Ji Hye.
I'm not sure if we'll even find
pieces of her bones after 34 years.
I know.
- Goodness.
- Look at this.
My goodness.
She must have a deep resentment.
She didn't even decompose.
How is this possible?
Adipocere.
- What?
If you get buried in a humid
and sealed place,
the fat in the body gets hydrolyzed
and turns into...
fatty acid and glycerin.
And when ammonia gets combined,
the body becomes wax-like.
It's kind of like soap.
- And decomposition stops too.
- Did you expect this?
The soil has a lot of moisture...
and has a lot of minerals
like magnesium and calcium.
It's the ideal condition.
Bring it back as it is.
- Hello.
- You're here.
- Great work.
Current time, 3:45pm.
Let us begin the autopsy.
Adipocere.
"Adipocere".
Show me the pictures
from the past autopsy.
We'll look into the chest.
It's way too decomposed.
Would we find anything in there?
Chest area, multiple stabs.
"Chest area, multiple stabs".
Multiple cracks and fractures...
in shoulder blades and ribs.
Loupe.
What is he doing?
Scalpel.
You two, come here
and start scraping.
Scrape everything off of the bone,
and request for substance analysis.
I don't think we need to
stick around any longer.
Keep watching until the end,
and let me know
if you find anything.
Yes.
- Start scraping.
- Right.
What are you doing?
There is something
stuck on the bone.
We're going to scrape it all out
and get it analyzed.
What can you find out with that?
We'll only know
when we have the result.
(Partners for Justice)
(Photo Studio)
- Excuse me.
- Yes, hello.
I need a picture for my ID.
You can take a look in the mirror
and go sit over there.
Okay.
Where is your restroom?
I really need to go.
Sir.
That's the darkroom.
Oh, really?
Goodness, I really have to go.
Here you go.
That'll be seven dollars.
Okay.
Looks good.
Taking ID pictures is the most
difficult thing in the world.
Here.
Here's your card.
Thank you.
Come again.
Yes.
I'll hand it over to the NFS
to be analyzed.
Investigator Yang speaking.
I checked the fingerprint
on the credit card.
- Is it a match?
- No.
It's not a match
to the Wuseong killer.
What? What did you say?
That can't be. It must be wrong.
- Check again.
- Give me that.
It's Do Ji Han. It's not a match?
- Are you sure?
- I'm positive.
Okay, thank you.
What is happening?
Sir, something must be wrong.
It's a partial print.
We can't be 100-percent sure.
- It's not over yet.
- What do we do now?
(Wuseong Serial Killer Victims)
(Survivor, attempted murder)
A witness.
Let's fight to the end.
(Lee Kyung Ja)
I even changed my name
to get away from it all.
I have nothing to say.
Did you hear that
we found another victim?
Yes.
There were 10 victims 30 years ago.
No one knows
how many more there will be.
Seong Hye Bin, the 11th victim.
She was just 20 years old.
Your age at the time...
was 20, right?
Even if I wanted to help,
he was wearing something
over his face.
I really didn't see anything.
I don't remember much.
There still is a way.
Breathe deeply and slowly.
Once you fall asleep,
you'll go back 30 years in time.
I was on my way home.
There's a man over there.
Just go by.
Just go by. Just go by. Just go by.
It suddenly went bright.
It's like I've become blind.
I can't see.
I hear something.
He's digging with a spade.
He's digging the soil.
I made a noise,
and he's coming over.
Please save me.
His face is all black.
He keeps looking at me.
He's looking at me.
He won't say a word.
Gosh.
Dr. Baek.
Hey.
What is it?
The substance on the adipocered
body's ribs is carbon steel.
(Carbon steel)
Steel? With carbon?
Not stainless steel?
Kitchen knives
aren't made with carbon steel.
What blade is it?
- What are the specs?
- 1080 carbon steel.
Find all blades made with
1080 carbon steel.
In the middle of the night?
Searching all the knife shops
will take...
at least 2 to 3 days.
- Pack all the dummies.
- What for when we have no blade?
- There are blades.
- Where?
There just are.
Get packing.
- Be careful.
- Watch out.
- What's all this?
- How do you live here?
These are real blades,
so be careful.
This is crazy.
This must be why
he never comes home.
You're not here to ogle. Let's work.
- Hold tight.
- Okay.
1, 2, 3, die!
Measure that.
Depth 10cm.
Length 4.5cm.
It's too thin.
Measure.
Length 1.7cm.
No match. Next.
Gosh.
I don't think he'd have used that.
Is this too big?
You did well.
You won't have to come here again.
Okay. Thank you.
Take her home safely.
Yes, sir. Come with me.
(Soo Photo Studio)
This is crazy.
- Mr. Yang.
- I don't see Kang Chi Soo.
He should be in his darkroom now,
but he closed the studio
and disappeared.
What?
Can we confirm
if Lee Kyung Ja's home?
I'll call and check.
Hi, it's Cha Soo Ho.
Did the witness, Lee Kyung Ja,
arrive home safely?
What?
Okay... Just a moment.
She got out of the car
and went off on her own.
He called to see if she's okay,
but she won't pick up.
- What?
- What happened?
- Keep trying.
- Okay.
Measure that.
Depth 15cm.
Length below 3.5cm.
Width 0.6... Doctor.
This is it.
We got it.
I almost died.
The military M7 bayonet.
Made with 1080 carbon steel.
I didn't turn the lights off.
(Partners for Justice)
She was the 11th target and only
survivor of the Wuseong murders.
I told you to catch the killer,
and you lost the only survivor?
Do you think they'll disband
the task force team?
The facts the body leaves don't lie.
Your assumption is interesting too.
I'll check for blood.
It's all blood.
- It's done.
- It's over. We got him.
It's all my fault. I'm sorry.
What on earth had happened?