(Episode 22)
Heart diseases are the second
leading cause of death in Korea.
It is common...
but is also dangerous
at the same time.
As the average number of years
increased, the prevalence rate...
The prevalence rate has been
increasing rapidly.
Patients who have coronary artery
disease and renal failure...
may recover quickly...
What's going on? Can't you see
that I'm giving a lecture here?
We meet again, Dr. Lee Hye Seong.
- What's this about?
- On June 11, 2018,
did you meet with Mr. Seo?
I don't know him.
On June 2, 4, and 5, 2018...
at 3:24pm, 8:17pm,
and 6:50pm respectively,
you and Mr. Seo talked on the phone.
Should I continue and explain
why you two talked?
It was to trade the security camera
footage of the drug supply room...
in Seon Hospital with the record
that you punched into...
- that room 10 years ago.
- You made me do it.
Let's talk in private
before it gets messier.
I have everything.
Everything? What do you have?
The box tapes.
- What?
- To cover up your crime,
you cleaned the place spotlessly...
with box tapes.
But a piece of the tape...
was found on the scene...
with saliva.
Darn it.
You can't hide anymore.
Ms. Lee Hye Seong, according to
the Article 250 of Criminal Code,
you're under arrest for
the murder of Seo Jeong Min.
- What's going on?
- She's arrested?
You may refuse to make a statement
and consult to an attorney.
You may also file to review
if the arrest was lawful or not.
- Round her up.
- Yes, sir.
It's been you...
all along.
(DNA Analysis)
(The subject's DNA matches
with the suspect's DNA.)
The DNA from the tape
in Mr. Seo's house floor.
The DNA matches with yours, Ms. Lee.
You won't be able to
lie anymore now.
On the night of June 11, 2018,
you visited the victim.
Give me some water.
(Zolpidem)
Why did you...
have to go that far?
Why?
I couldn't hold it back anymore.
This was from 10 years ago,
so it was difficult to find.
I also pass along
Prosecutor Kang's advice.
He wants you to stop doing this.
(Psychotropic Drugs Registration)
Mr. Kang's instructions end here,
but I won't let you walk away
until we catch Baek Beom.
- See you later.
- You said this was the last time.
Don't get the wrong idea
just because we made a trade.
I'm an investigator
at the prosecutors' office.
I heard you're aiming to become
the hospital's director.
Your license will be revoked.
You think that'd be possible then?
(Drug Storage Room)
(Zolpidem)
What brings you here
all of a sudden?
I did everything you asked me to do.
- Let me walk away now.
- Have you gone mad?
For whose benefit?
Do you know how much
it took for me to get here?
You got here
thanks to money and power...
while covering up
your medical malpractice.
What?
You blamed Baek Beom for
your malpractice 10 years ago.
Did you think I had no idea?
But I have no idea...
why he took the blame
for what you've done.
What?
You shouldn't even
be called a doctor.
You're just a criminal.
Wait, no.
Are you a murderer?
You killed someone with your hands.
Who do you think you are?
Who do you think you are
to talk to me like that?
Don't say another word
and just do as I tell you...
if you don't want to get locked up.
I'm glad you're here.
Give me a second.
He brought it upon himself.
You injected two shots
you prepared into him,
then rubbed Mr. Seo's
fingerprint on the syringe...
to make it look like
he killed himself.
Then you destroyed evidence.
Your lies...
have come to an end.
I killed...
I'm a doctor.
I save people.
But...
But what...
have I done?
You can stop pretending.
You may have escaped...
taking the responsibility after
killing someone in an operation.
But not anymore.
Your eyes look similar...
to Yong's.
I used to like him 10 years ago.
But everyone had their eyes
on Han So Hee.
Both Yong and Beom.
They both liked her.
What was so special about a nurse...
who was from an orphanage?
When I heard...
she was on the verge of death
because of a car accident,
I hoped that Yong would
finally notice me.
My life ended...
when he died.
I couldn't sleep a day
without pills.
I couldn't live.
I mean it.
My life could have been
better than this mess.
It's all because of Baek Beom.
No.
You brought it upon yourself.
So make sure...
you pay for what you've done.
(National Forensic Service)
My goodness, this smell.
I know you missed it.
I didn't. It smells awful.
You don't even put a mask on...
because the scent provides
information. Didn't you miss this?
It's the smell of your home.
Since when did you
become so talkative?
Welcome back. Your father
had been worried about you.
Doctor Baek.
- You're here.
- Welcome back.
- Take this.
- What is this?
- Tofu.
- Who eats this nowadays?
- Don't you have soy sauce in here?
- Forget it.
Gosh.
Excuse me.
Darn it.
Lee Hye Seong of Seon Hospital...
- admitted to her crimes.
- Learn to knock.
Hey.
I have a favor to ask.
(Autopsy Result, Hangook University)
These are the autopsy result
and pictures...
of someone who died 10 years ago.
I wanted to ask you
to go over it again...
without asking who this is.
(Autopsy Result,
Hangook University Hospital)
(Cause of death: Suicide)
This person was left-handed.
- Pardon?
- They've been writing...
with their left hand
for at least 15 years.
Then...
What about this needle mark
on their left arm?
Was that done by someone else?
A left-handed person couldn't inject
something on their left arm.
Don't write a novel.
This person has 4 needle marks
on their body, not 2.
Look.
Even a left-handed person
could inject themselves there.
Then did this person commit suicide?
Wrong question.
It should be, "Which one of them
was injected by themselves?"
2007...
2007... 2008...
2008.
Let's see.
Found it.
Yes?
Prosecutor Eun, I found
Kang Yong's medical records.
It was May 26, 2008.
He was prescribed with antibiotics
and a tetanus shot.
He was pricked by a needle
while operating.
Doctor Kang.
Two injections.
(Prescription Record)
Your older brother...
was left-handed, right?
Look.
On the back of his right hand
were two more injection marks.
These are records of the injections.
(Injection marks)
(Prescription Record)
Those were injectable
with his left hand.
Your brother.
Type of death.
Suicide.
As the lead prosecutor
on the 10-year-old case,
that is my conclusion.
(Injection marks)
It's all my fault.
Prosecutors are human too.
We make mistakes.
No, sir.
I'll take responsibility.
And do what?
Will you really resign?
If we resigned over one mistake,
how many of us
do you think would still be here?
You're supposed to
take this office after me.
Let's say I didn't hear this.
No, sir. I have...
no right...
to prosecute.
The injection marks...
on my brother's right hand.
Did you find them?
What?
Did you think I wouldn't recognize
a photo of my best friend?
Mr. Seo.
I was going to see him that day.
I'm Seo Jeong Min from
the Prosecutor's Office.
Do you know what day it is today?
It's Han So Hee's birthday.
He wanted to tell me
something about So Hee,
so we arranged to meet at
the orphanage they were from.
He didn't show up.
He had met So Hee at the orphanage.
She was like a mom to him.
He never lived far from
the orphanage.
Does Mr. Seo's grudge...
against Lee Hye Seong
have something to do with me?
It's 10 years old.
It was hard to find.
He got something on her.
He threatened her with it
to get the security footage...
of outside the drug cabinet...
on the day my brother died.
He thought it was
decisive evidence that...
you had killed my brother.
We found this
when we searched your place.
If you'd killed my brother,
you wouldn't have
kept it for so long.
Why did you steal the drugs?
I regained consciousness
a week after the car accident.
That's when I realized
So Hee was dead.
I wasn't in my right mind.
What have you done?
Why are you the only one back?
- Let go of me.
- Where's So Hee?
How... How could you...
I'm pregnant.
It's Kang Yong's baby.
It had to be you, didn't it?
You selfish jerk. So...
So you killed her?
Tell me. Is that why you killed her?
Yes.
It's all my fault.
I should've stopped her.
I should've stopped her
from the start.
I got too greedy.
So I...
There's no point, Yong. It's over.
Her fetus.
It was a girl.
You don't know anything.
That was the last I saw of him.
Then...
what were these?
(Succinylcholine, sodium pentothal)
It was for myself.
I couldn't do it.
I turned into a coward.
That's it.
Now I get it.
It took me 10 years...
to find out the truth.
(Partners for Justice)
(Ligature Marks:
Marks left by tying)
Dad!
Goodness, again?
This is driving me crazy.
Dad.
Dad. Dad?
Gosh, no way.
(June 18, 3:04am,
discovery of Yeom Sang Goo's death)
(Yeom Dae Sik,
Yeom Sang Goo's second son)
Gosh, why isn't he answering?
(Dae Sik)
Hey, come on. Answer the phone.
(Yeom Dae Chul,
Yeom Sang Goo's first son)
You answer it. You know
I worked until late today.
I just came back
from my shift at the restaurant.
Gosh, why is this brat calling me
in the middle of the night?
- Hello?
- Dae Chul.
Wake up. Dad passed away.
What?
- What did you say?
- Dad is dead!
There's something you don't know.
Director, you're here.
Was there anyone
who came for a visit?
No, no one came to
visit the patient.
Right. A while ago,
a prosecutor visited.
A prosecutor?
About what happened 10 years ago,
that wasn't the whole story.