(Episode 31)
I told Mr. Baek that Han So Hee...
is alive.
I thought that was the least
I could do to ask forgiveness...
for what I had put him through.
Mr. Baek will find Han So Hee soon.
You must make your decision.
(National Forensic Service)
Dr. Baek, are you sleeping
in here again?
You'll really freeze to death here.
What? He's not in here. Where is he?
The number you have dialed
is not available at this moment.
What's going on? Where did he go?
- Hello.
- Wait.
Have you seen Dr. Baek?
He's probably sleeping
in the autopsy room.
No, he's not in the autopsy room
or his office. Something is off.
Great, he's not in here either.
Have you seen Dr. Baek this morning?
Sure, I'll be visiting you
this summer.
- We'll look forward to it.
- Are they your parents in the US?
Mom. Dad. This is my colleague,
Mr. Jang. Say hello to him.
Hi, Mr. Jang. Thank you.
- Nice to meet you.
- What's going on?
It's a great honor for me to
work with Dr. Stella Hwang.
She's the toxicologist in Korea.
She's still a little girl to us,
but thank you.
You must be very proud of her.
Mom. Dad. I miss you.
- "Mom"? "Mom"?
- We miss you too.
You should go to sleep now.
- We love you.
- Good night.
Good night.
Pretty impressive.
No, no. I was so nervous
to speak in English.
Your father is involved in this.
Han So Hee...
is alive.
(Dad)
Where's So Hee, Dad?
It's all over.
They already had a funeral for her.
After that accident
with that girl, So Hee,
I shouldn't have let
you be like that.
I should've done everything to...
(Partners for Justice)
(Lack of evidence: it refers to
inadequate evidence for test sample)
- Good morning, Stella. How are you?
- Morning.
Stella, are you doing anything...
for summer vacation?
I think I'm going to
visit my parents.
To America.
As a matter of fact, I'm going to
a criminal reference in LA.
- Reference?
- Yes.
You mean conference?
Yes, so...
It's an international criminal
conference that's like a reference.
How about this?
Since I'm going to the US,
should I say hello to your parents?
Say hello?
- To my parents?
- I can say hi to your mom and dad.
No.
- "No"?
- No. Why do you want to...
meet my parents?
- "Why"?
- I'm not looking...
for anything serious.
Sorry.
Goodness, what a nosy parker.
I went too far again. Goodness,
I overstepped my boundary again.
Gosh, you and I are nothing.
Meet your parents?
Okay. Have a good day.
Enjoy your summer vacation.
Stupid.
We will continue
the criminal trial...
in the Criminal Collegiate Division
for case number 218382.
Prosecution.
You may question the witness.
Did you talk to the victim,
Seo Jeong Min,
on the day of the incident?
- Yes.
- What was the call about?
He had something to tell me about
Han So Hee. He wanted to meet.
However, you didn't have a chance
to hear what it was about.
I found out later...
what Seo Jeong Min
was trying to tell me.
Han So Hee is alive.
That's what he wanted to say.
So Hee is alive?
That's nonsense.
She died 10 years ago.
Goodness, Prosecutor Kang.
Have you been well?
- Let me hug you. I missed you.
- Goodness.
Gosh.
- I missed you too.
- Okay.
You should come
by the office some time.
We really missed you around there.
Sure, I'll do that.
- How are you doing, Hyun?
- Well, you know.
I put my studio on the market.
I'm going to stay
with my mom for a while.
I see.
Oh, right.
Did you know too?
That Han So Hee was alive?
Right, exactly.
Is... Is that even possible?
Didn't Mr. Baek's girlfriend die
in a car accident 10 years ago?
Well, I found out...
she had been in a vegetative state
for 10 years.
Oh, my.
How could...
that be?
Then what about Dr. Baek?
He found out only recently.
Don't do this here, and go back.
It's all my fault.
After my wife had passed away,
I was in pure torment.
I deserve to be called trash.
I shouldn't have done
what I did to you.
Why are you doing this now?
Whom are you trying to show this to?
No one.
No one has to watch what I'm doing.
I just want to soften your anger.
I still have nightmares...
whenever I think of you.
Just go.
I'm so sorry for what I've done.
Please forgive me.
- Just go.
- I'm so sorry.
- Go.
- Please, forgive me.
Go!
Sir!
I'm so sorry!
- Please forgive me.
- Just go.
- Let go of me.
- I'm so sorry. Forgive me.
Sir, please.
Sir!
Go!
(Comments)
His driver is pretty feisty too.
You should just let him off.
I'm sure he paid you a lot.
I guess there are many ways
to rip money off of people.
I'm glad you held back.
Stockholders will cast their votes
without feeling too conscious.
Those pests.
Hey, drive properly.
Did you take his phone?
Yes. He has to put his phone
in the trunk while he drives.
I added that to the contract too.
Make sure you drive well, you idiot.
You should've behaved.
Pardon?
It happened between adults.
Lawyer Han.
Let's take care of this
like experts.
You can go out and get some air.
I'll remove you from
Sungjin Group's counsel.
Are you saying it'll be fine
as long as I stay quiet?
It's like bringing a knife
to a gun fight anyway.
You know that very well.
It'll only hurt you.
You can take a vacation.
Thank you.
I'll put my trust in you.
And let's grab dinner
after the general meeting.
My treat. Sure.
(Director Oh Man Sang)
Who else should I call?
Okay. Next...
Excuse me. You cannot come in here.
I have something to tell you.
You may leave.
Lawyer Han. What are you doing?
I'm here to see Director Oh,
not you.
What? What do you want to say?
- Apologize.
- For what?
Do you want me to state
what happened on that day?
So what?
Apologize and get your punishment.
You people...
really love an apology.
Okay, fine. I'll apologize.
I'm so sorry.
But I thought you wanted it too.
Anyway, how should I express...
my apology to you?
We're used to seeing
people like you.
Okay, fine. I made a mistake.
I'll give you what you want.
What did you say?
Director Oh,
this must be a misunderstanding.
Lawyer Han, don't be like this.
Do you love money that much?
How much did you expect to get?
Tell me.
I don't need your money.
Oh, really?
Then do you want me
to just apologize?
What should I do?
Should I kneel down?
Hold a press conference...
and apologize
within tomorrow morning.
Tell everyone...
what you have done
and turn yourself in.
- What?
- If you don't,
I'll do it myself.
But...
I thought you wanted it too.
Anyway, how should I express...
my apology to you?
I'll take care of her.
(Seoul Eastern District
Prosecutor's Office)
Hello.
- They're here.
- Hello.
Hello. Come in.
It's inside.
Hello.
Hello, Chief Ma.
You came out here yourself?
- Yes.
- Where's Doctor Baek?
He suddenly took the day off.
He never does that.
He took a day off
in the beginning of this month.
That was a business trip
to Jeju Island.
National Forensic Service
isn't stationed in Jeju Island,
so he has to go there for an autopsy
whenever something happens.
It's not like criminal cases will
wait for him to be back at work.
We'll have to keep working.
- Right.
- Yes.
How does she look?
What's wrong?
I...
know her.
(Defense Counsels' Bench)
Hello.
She was a lawyer
on Oh Man Sang's counsel.
Yes, you're right.
She was in the courtroom.
Don't you remember her?
It is her.
How does her body look?
We can know for sure
after we conduct an autopsy.
Current time, 10:05am.
I will begin the autopsy.
No injury found on the face.
No injury.
(Name: Han Ji Won)
Dermal necrosis.
There's a blister.
Looks like a burn.
Left arm, a burn.
Jang.
It's 325g.
Heart, 325g.
Scalpel.
Her heart is clean too.
I don't see any arteriosclerosis.
She was very healthy.
We found nothing.
She has a burn on her arm,
but it's a small burn that has
nothing to do with her death.
And she has no injury
anywhere on her body.
And I see nothing weird
in her internal organs.
Then what's her cause of death?
We'll know more in detail after
we go through chemical tests,
but for now,
there is a possibility
that it'll be unknown.
An unexplainable death?
Goodness, that's bad.
There's nothing
we can find on her physically.
Then why did she die?
We don't always find the cause
through an autopsy.
Goodbye.
I'm sure there's more.
What do you mean,
So Hee is alive?
She was in a PVS...
(PVS: Persistent vegetative state)
for the last 10 years.
Then she's hardly alive.
How much do you know
about that case from 10 years ago?
Do you want to know what happened?
At this point? Why?
It was fun to see you get wrecked...
without knowing anything.
Just live on...
without knowing a thing.
Live with that pain.
Yes.
Why do I want to know now?
You're arrogant to the end.
Do you think you're so great?
Is that why...
you took the blame for
my malpractice 10 years ago?
I just wanted to
give you an opportunity.
I knew that you liked Yong,
and that his death tortured you.
I can take the punishment alone.
Beom.
If I tell you,
are you sure you can take it?
I detected a change
in her brainwave.
I want to run another brain PET-CT,
but I need her guardian's consent.
(PET-CT: Positron emission
tomography-computed tomography)
(Consent for Brain PET-CT,
Guardian's signature)
I was never going to tell you...
about the stupid scheme...
that Yong came up with.
Where are you going?
What's all this?
You resigned?
Just...
let me leave quietly.
What are you talking about?
Thank you...
for everything.
You.
You're pregnant.
How did you know?
You thought I wouldn't?
Beom.
Does he know?
Does his father object?
No.
It's not like that.
It's just...
I made my mind up.
If you leave like this,
Beom will chase you
to the end of the world.
Do you love him enough...
to leave him for him?
For him,
can you do anything?
Yes. I can.
Then tell Beom that...
it's my baby.
- What?
- That's the only way.
Yong was greedy to the very end.
He couldn't stand the result...
and killed himself.
Yes. So Hee's fetus that died...
10 years ago...
in the car accident.
It was yours.
(National Forensic Service)
Beom.
I...
Where's So Hee?
She's at a nursing hospital.
Let's go.
You cared for her for all this time?
I thought that would be the way
to make up for my sins.
I'm sorry, Beom.
It all happened because of me,
because of my foolish greed.
I ruined everything.
So Hee's like this...
because of me.
Beom.
Are you okay?
It means nothing now.
I died 10 years ago.
(Death Due to Multiple Assaults
of Rich Housewife)
You killed your wife.
Who are you making a killer?
How dare someone like you...
Is this how you hit your wife?
Live by the law,
or we'll meet again.
I checked Han Ji Won's call history.
- I found something strange.
- What is it?
She spoke to a producer
who works in the newsroom.
I called the producer,
and she had an important tip.
She said it was on Sungjin Group's
Director Oh Man Sang.
See? I told you that
Oh Man Sang would be involved.
What was she going to tell?
The producer doesn't know.
She died before they could meet.
Let's bring...
Oh Man Sang in and get a statement.
You really are an outcast.
- Kids these days are funny.
- A member of...
a team of lawyers
that defend Sungjin Group,
one of Korea's largest companies
was found dead.
Investigative authorities...
ordered the NFS do an autopsy
to identify cause of death.
As the team managed information
with a very sensitive nature...
The daughter-in-law
of a serving congressman...
was found dead in her home.
The prime suspect...
The title of Sungjin's chief legal
counsel is yours when you retire.
You're the only one who can manage.
Yes, sir, I understand.
I know just the right person.
Employees at her legal firm
voiced great sorrow and sympathy...
at the plight of their colleague.
Yes. It's about time that he called.
They say it's unconnected.
Hello, sir.
How have you been?
It's been a while.
You retire soon, don't you?
You remember all sorts of things.
Thank you.
I retire in about three months.
I should get ready to move.
Yes, yes.
Would you like a view of the river?
(Seoul Eastern District
Prosecutor's Office)
Hurry up.
Ms. Eun. Oh Man Sang's here.
Is he?
The problem is...
That's why we play golf.
- I'll take you out one day.
- Thank you.
Would your deputy chief
like to join us too?
I'm so sorry.
I'd love to tag along but
I don't know how to play.
- I'm into soccer.
- I'll hire you a professional.
A woman.
A month of lessons
and you'll be a pro.
That's right.
A woman?
You need to be careful around women.
You always end up here
because of them.
You're quite funny, Mr. Do.
Chief.
You're keeping my reference
witness a little too long.
It's been a while, Ms. Eun.
You know where
the interview room is.
Why are you here?
You're still as passionate.
Okay then.
Shall we go?
Yes, of course.
Ms. Eun, you stay.
Pardon?
Chief, what are you...
They gave me this.
He brought photos taken
the day before and...
the day Han Ji Won died.
His alibi is airtight.
We need to investigate to see.
Ms. Eun. Drop this case.
I reassigned it to Mr. Do.
I followed this case
starting at the crime scene.
Now you're reassigning the case?
See, that's why it can't be you.
You hold a grudge.
If you're like this, people will say
we're targeting Mr. Oh...
or that we want revenge.
I can stay objective.
Ms. Eun, the chief's right.
Let's be cautious.
Cases involving conglomerates...
aren't that easy.
They're complicated
and hard to prove.
They have so many resources.
Yes, that's right.
I'll be the lead prosecutor
of the case,
but let me keep her on.
I'll use her information
and leave out the grudge.
This is why I like you, Ji Han.
Go ahead. Do what you can.
Dr. Baek.
I've never seen you drink alcohol.
Han So Hee.
Did you see her?
Is something wrong?
No private conversations.
Stop.
Oh, no. Not you too.
I already had a though day as it is.
Gosh. Ma'am, give us
another shot glass, please.
It's definitely Oh Man Sang.
It has to be him.
But it's worse than
Kwon Hee Kyung's case.
I think Dr. Ma will conclude
the cause of death is unknown.
Dr. Baek. Are you listening?
See that couple over there?
What a cute couple.
Did they just start dating?
What a surprise.
You're pay attention to the living.
What do you think will happen
if the truck behind them hits them?
What?
That's what I see.
I see which bones will be damaged,
which bones will be fractured,
and how they'll die.
That's the life I led for 10 years,
and it became a part of me.
I didn't feel anything...
when I saw So Hee again.
No. That's a lie.
You're lying to yourself.
The Dr. Baek whom
I've seen so far isn't like that.
Whenever you open your mouth,
you spit out harsh words,
and you don't know
how to be social at all,
but that's not the real you.
- Don't write a novel.
- I'm not writing a novel.
To me, the last two months
have been real like documentaries.
Before I met you,
I thought it was all over
after we die.
Corpses. Autopsies.
Just the very thought was scary,
and I wanted to avoid it.
But after seeing you,
I realized that...
I shouldn't avoid it.
Someone's life can be seen
through the corpse.
And there's someone
who can recognize it.
Don't avoid it.
Keep trying until the end.
This is what you taught me.
(National Forensic Service)
The National Forensic Service...
has taken keen interest
in this very case.
That's why I, the chief, am
in charge of this case.
I see. I'm sure of it.
- Last time...
- Dr. Ma...
has become more enthusiastic
than before.
We have found out the cause.
- Yes, I can see what you mean.
- As you can see,
we only proceed our procedures
based on accurate scientific claims.
Did you find anything?
Nothing, nothing. Total nothing.
What should we do?
- What? You found nothing?
- No.
I didn't find any drugs
or any toxic substances.
She's completely clean.
Except for the drugs or toxic
substances, there's no other lead?
First of all, we don't see
any external injuries...
that could lead to death.
Secondly,
we didn't find any fatal diseases
from her organs.
That's why we checked
for toxic substances.
Then is the cause of death unknown?
An autopsy doesn't always lead
to a cause of death.
He has an ironclad alibi.
If the cause of death is unknown,
we'll get nowhere
with our investigation.
Where's Dr. Baek? Where did he go?
I think Dr. Ma and Dr. Baek seem
to have switch places.
Dr. Ma always works late,
and Dr. Baek has fell off the radar.
And today, he took the day off.
It's his 1st day off ever since
he started here 10 years ago.
- I see. A day off?
- Yes.
(Yujeong Hachery)
(Gongneung Food Stall)