(knowledge) Qianqiu
You like that child, don't you?
(Hosho Chiaki) “I love you”?
(Lina) Anka is leaving➡
It seems like it has happened and from now on
Let's all three do our best!
(欬)
I really want to be in a movie directed by you. ➡
sky….
I... I've always wanted to apologize to heaven. ➡
I want to talk to you properly for once. ➡
Please contact me if you like.
today movie
It was an audition, right?
(Minami Seten)
Only what I have experienced➡
Useful
I thought maybe I wouldn't be able to get into it.
All you have to do is experience it all with me.
Ten-chan, come with me.
But for acting
To have them do that...
It's not for acting.
Eh...
I don't want to give Ten-chan to anyone.
I want it to be just for me.
Yeah~!
Are you that surprised?
Because… Chiaki-san and I?
The moon and the soft-shelled turtle
Whale and sardine?
I like it.
Kind and straightforward➡
About Ten-chan, who works hard.
Ten-chan is
what do you think about me?
Ah, Chiaki-san…➡
He was... a very important senior...
Is that all?
Don't run away.
Look at me properly.
dislike?
So do you like it?
Then➡
How about trying it out?
Until the audition ➡
It feels like you're using me.
I can't believe it's used...
I feel bad for Chiaki.
That's not true.
♬〜
I want to do my best.
So that you can fall in love with me.
♬〜
So➡
please.
♬〜
If it's okay with me...
happy.
♬〜
Ah, uh... Chiaki-san.
what?
actually
It's my first time dating someone➡
So that...
good.
I felt relieved.
(Inner voice) ≪What? This is...➡
That... that's what it is≫
≪Anyway, I have to close my eyes≫
♬〜
From now on, I'll call you heaven.
Please call me Chiaki too.
Chiaki….
Ah, sorry
After all, I might not be able to do it!
Okay. Wait until you get used to it.
♬〜
Tonton Tonton...
(Satoko) Heaven. ➡
Be careful with your fingers.
yes.
≪Forever
I was afraid of falling in love with someone
(Reminiscence)｟No… no, no｠
｟Stop it! Stop it...｠
≪But with Chiaki-san...≫
｟Stay with me｠
Bang (door sound)
I'll do this.
(Aura) Huh? ➡
Did you think it was serious?
That Chiaki.
♬~(In-store BGM)
Click (sound of oil lighter)
He's a child I want to cherish.
♬~(In-store BGM)
Fine, I don't need it.
Huh?
That's good➡
I found someone like that.
♬~(In-store BGM)
Ah~ah
I wonder if I'll ever be able to fall in love again.
What happened?
Actually ➡
I happened to meet a girl I used to like.
Huh~.
telephone number
I forced myself to give it to you➡
There's little hope.
He's unusually bearish.
I am➡
Because I hurt that child.
｟Senpai, if you have a hard time➡
Please rely on me anytime｠
♬〜
｟Well then...｠
｟Please comfort me｠
♬〜
｟No, no... stop it｠
｟Please stop it! ｠
♬〜
⦅sorry⦆
⦅bread! ｠
｟This is too terrible｠
♬〜
(浬) Those days➡
Tough things happened one after another➡
Sigh…➡
Something was wrong.
oh dear
That's not an excuse though.
♬〜
(Ara) I really regret it. ➡
I did the worst thing.
♬〜
There's no need to give up, right?
Huh?
Tell me how you feel.
If you are now
You can do better.
♬〜
Chiaki~!
Stop it, it's annoying.
Stop being annoying. Hurt.
📱(Manner mode)
(浬) It's an unregistered number.
What are you doing? Get out quickly.
📱(Manner mode)
Yeah.
Gacha (door sound)
Tap (mobile phone operation sound)
Bang
yes.
📱 Late at night
Sorry, this is Nanse.
Ah... thank you.
No way
I didn't think you'd contact me.
Akira-senpai, I'm sorry about what happened the other day.
Don't apologize.
It's all my fault. ➡
📱 Like that
Hurt the heavens...
I've always regretted it.
📱 About that...
Because I'm okay now.
That's why Akira-senpai too.
Don't worry about it anymore.
I wanted to convey that properly.
♬〜
thank you.
📱(浬)But
I never imagined that Heaven would become an actress➡
I was surprised.
I myself am surprised.
Hehe, what is that?
Hehe.
Bang
Someday➡
I wish we could be on the scene together.
📱 That's right.
See you then.
Also.
Tat
♬〜
Did it work?
Haha, that's good.
terrible.
I really like it.
Haha.
Ah~ I love it! Hmm!
That's why it's annoying.
(Aura) I love it.
It's annoying.
≪I'm glad we were able to talk properly≫
≪Let's report to Chiaki-san next time≫
♬〜
(Female) Eh, sports test
I'm not confident at all.
(Female) Neither do I.
(Female) Because it's like jumping backwards➡
Why not?
(Female) What is backward jumping?
(Female) Huh, something like that...
What? What?
(Female) Haha.
(Female) Why? what up?
(Female) Hey, look at this.
(Anka) Tsk.
(Female) He's appearing again.
Ugh.
(Female) Really
I want you to be careless➡
The treasure will last forever.
(Female) That's true.
(Female) It's just the face.
(Xing Xia) Baosheng Qianqiu?
(woman)
Why did you decide to do this job?
(Anka) What happened to Hosho Chiaki? ➡
Isn't it cool?
No~➡
Hosho Chiaki is
It's better to stop.
(Anka) Eh, why?
Because he's a scumbag.
Hey Hibiki.
(Hibiki) Yeah.
Yeah, I'm super curious.
Please tell me in detail.
Bali!
Jijiji... (sound of light bulb flashing)
(Tanuma)
You read the script, right?
Yes, of course.
(Tanuma) This work is a climax
There is a scene of intense sex. ➡
Minase-san is also active as an idol.
It seems like you are doing it➡
Images etc.
Is that okay?
Yes, it's okay.
I want to do my best as an actress.
I want to try anything.
thank you!
(Tanuma)
Hahaha, nice, you're in good spirits.
♬〜
📱(Message reception/Silent mode)
(Chiaki's voice) "Are you coming to my house today?"
♬〜
(Voice of Heaven)
“The audition is over➡
I’ll ask you now.”
♬〜
Ping Pong (intercom)
Welcome.
sky?
Chiaki-san already
I can't invite you to my house.
Haha, don't say that.
Come in.
Sorry to bother you.
Yeah.
thank you.
today
It was the final audition, right?
how was it?
After all, "Are you prepared?"
Confirmed.
Are you ready?
a little bit
It's a work with a lot of wet scenes.
Show me the script.
yes.
From the office
At first I was stopped, but ➡
If you can appear in a popular work
The range of work will expand rapidly.
I work as an actress
It's really fun.
So no matter what
I want to seize the opportunity➡
That's what I thought.
From now on
I want to do my best in any role.
♬〜
Sigh… Sigh… Sigh….
Bang!
Chiaki-san?
I see.
I hope you pass the audition.
yes.
Well then, excuse me.
Yes, good night.
Brororo… (engine sound)
📱(Ring tone)
📱(Tanuma) Yes, yes.
Director Tanuma➡
It's been a long time. How are you?
Actually, fold in➡
I have something to tell you...
Director (Suzui) Tanuma
The audition results have arrived.
yes.
Unfortunately, it didn't work.
is that so….
But the only one who made it to the end was
That's amazing. ➡
Also
Let's do our best at the next audition.
thank you.
(Voice of Heaven)
``Audition of director Tanuma's movie, ➡
I fell...”｡
≪Don't be depressed
I have to work hard on the job in front of me≫
Pan Pan Pan!
Okay.
(piano sound)
This is how I feel now.
(Hachimura) Huh?
Don't you understand?
(Hachimura) I understand, your tone and everything.
Let me hear your tone too.
Hey, please.
(Director) Cut! Okay!
(Staff) Okay. ➡
That's it for this scene.
Next move.
(Director) No, Mr. Minase
This play was so good.
Is it true?
(Hachimura) I was shocked too.
Eh, I'm happy.
(Director) No, thank you very much.
Mr. Hachimura, thank you for coming this time.
(Hachimura) Yes, this is it.
Thank you again.
Chiaki-san, what happened?
I wonder if the sky is falling
Because I thought so.
Ah, so why bother...
Thank you...
Come.
♬〜
Wait... Wait, Chiaki-san!
The audition is
Is it already over?
Huh?
what do you think about me?
♬〜
forever
It's still "Chiaki-san".
Tell me.
If you don't put it into words properly➡
I'm anxious.
I….
♬〜
The reaction…➡
Can I look forward to it?
♬〜
Day ➡
Look here.
♬〜
I like Chiaki.
Sigh….
terrible…
I'm so happy that I feel like crying a little.
♬〜
About me
Please don't hate me.
Huh?
♬〜
I can't help but hate it.
absolutely?
Will you always be by my side?
I'll always be by your side.
thank you.
That's a promise, absolutely.
♬〜
｟Director Tanuma Actually➡
I came in to talk to you...｠
｟A girl named Ten Nanse➡
audition
I think I have received it➡
The child is really
Apparently it's not suitable for sex.
｟The office
It's like they're forcing me to accept it.
♬〜
Heaven I love you.
I love you, really.
Never leave me.
Does Ten have a boyfriend?
I'm glad to meet you. You look fine.
Do you know who your partner is?
It's Akira though.
Stop it!
Is heaven lying to me?
The original manga ``Salvation, Nest Eater''
Including “Comic Seymour”➡
It is currently being distributed at various electronic bookstores.
Please read the original story along with the drama...
(2 people) Please enjoy.