(Bench Part)
♪Hey, I say, someone behaves today♪
♪Oh, I thought it was someone else♪
♪Really extraordinary♪
♪The cutie in the mirror♪
♪Oh, looking a bit arrogant♪
♪Every day, I sleep in and feel drowsy♪
♪Sleepy and hungry.
Whose alarm clock got hit♪
♪Only the body is lazy,
and the spirit is very nice♪
♪Sun's up high, but I have my posture♪
♪As I walk, I sway overly♪
♪I believe that I can fly♪
♪Turning around and smiling,
I look silly and cute♪
♪Baby, don't be shy♪
♪If I want to laugh, I will♪
♪Ha ha ha ha ha♪
♪If I want to play, I will♪
♪Um um um um um♪
♪If I want to make a fuss, I will♪
♪La la la la la♪
♪What are you looking at me for♪
♪It's none of your business♪
♪If I want to laugh, I will♪
♪Ha ha ha ha ha♪
♪If I want to play, I will♪
♪Um um um um um♪
♪If I want to make a fuss, I will♪
♪La la la la la♪
♪What are you looking at me for♪
♪Na na na na na♪
=Hilarious Family=
=Episode 16=
(Du Ruyu's heart flutters for a hero)
(Master Guo's unhappy out of jealousy)
Boss,
you just moved back like this?
My own home is the best.
Besides, my mother said
the Young Lord's mansion
has a feng shui problem.
No sane person lives there.
But I still think
that mansion is more elegant.
Right, we should have them
reconstruct this place
like that mansion.
Look at your room.
It's basically the same as before.
You can't say it's the same.
It's clearly identical.
Did they think we were nostalgic?
But it's fine.
Boss, you left your purse out of place.
Why are you following us?
Your purse was left at my room.
By the way, what's your name?
You can call me A-Si.
A-Si?
Miss, what's your name?
What's wrong? The money is missing?
No.
Isn't this the purse
A-Si gave you back then?
Don't you have something to do?
Go to work.
Boss, this thing
is called a token of love.
You can't just leave it anywhere.
You have to think carefully about it.
A token of love, huh?
It is.
I've never paid for meals.
- Let's go.
- Go.
He is not dead?
Well,
you have to have something sweet
after eating something salty, right?
It makes sense.
Do you like it salty or sweet?
I like a lighter taste.
Hello?
Then it's tasteless.
- It has no taste.
- Sir? Sir?
- I think...
It really is you! You're not dead.
You're the dead one.
How dare you talk to him like that?
No, it's great.
Why didn't you die then?
Boss, she's provoking you.
No.
Don't you remember me?
It's me. You robbed me last time.
What are you looking at?
This is robbery.
- Give it to me.
- No.
I remember now.
It's you.
Where's that kid?
- Who?
- What kid?
The one who hit me on the head.
He hit your head?
On guard!
I lost my sense of taste
because of that, you know?
Now you've brought yourself
to my doorstep.
Come with me.
- No, no. Help!
- Come.
Go.
- Stop!
- Help!
In broad daylight,
three grown men are bullying a girl.
(Lu Jiang)
It isn't right.
Boss, here comes another one.
It's okay.
Old man, I advise you
not to meddle in this.
Get lost now.
Watch this!
It fell.
Boss, you're bleeding
from the head again.
Boss.
It's the sword's aura!
Sword's aura?
Go.
- Sir, don't go, sir.
- Let me go.
Don't go. Stop.
Miss,
spare others when you can.
Be careful in the future.
I'll take my leave.
Thank you, hero.
Great, Mr. Lu didn't kill anyone.
Mr. Lu!
That thug didn't die.
What thug?
The one you knocked dead
with a bat last time.
No, we all thought he was dead,
but he wasn't.
I saw him on the street.
I remember now.
He's not dead?
Are you sure?
Absolutely.
But a hero drove him away.
Otherwise,
I would have brought him here.
So, he's not dead.
I'm free now.
You are here.
A man was looking for someone
with a portrait.
As soon as I saw this,
a familiar feeling hit me.
80 percent familiar.
- An old friend from Qing City.
- Huh?
Who is this?
Isn't this you, Mr. Lu?
Me?
H-How is this possible?
No wonder it looks familiar.
It's me?
Is this me?
It's you, Mr. Lu.
You were quite skinny back then.
Those eyes don't look like mine.
Mr. Lu, this is the hero who saved me.
And then, those people saw...
Buping.
Buping?
Father.
Father?
Buping.
Father, father.
Father.
Buping,
I've been looking for you
for a long time.
I never expected
to meet you here, father.
Why are you here?
It's a long story.
The day after I left home,
I accidentally killed a thug.
It was Peilan
who took me in.
Brat!
So you just hid after killing someone?
No.
No, it's a misunderstanding.
Master Lu,
you saw
the very thug just now.
He didn't die.
He didn't?
You shouldn't hide,
even if he didn't die.
This is called evasion.
Father, I'm sorry.
I was too strict with you.
I asked too much.
It's okay.
Stop weeping!
You are a man,
and you should man up.
Alright.
Does it hurt?
You should have at least said goodbye
when you left.
I almost went crazy looking for you.
You've had a hard time, Buping.
It's okay.
No, I mean...
Well, I'm fine. Really.
If it hurts,
you should compress it with cold water.
I can see that
you're deeply concerned for your son.
But you
shouldn't
make such a scene in public.
No, Master,
this is the way my father loves me.
No one knows a father
better than his son.
Does it hurt?
Father, I've also
been through a lot recently.
You've grown up.
Peilan... How about
we take you home, and then you can talk?
No need.
Buping, pack up, and go home with me.
Wait, father.
I-I-I can't leave now.
Why is that?
Because...
I...
I-I still have work to do.
Work?
Mother.
Where is Lu Buping?
I haven't seen him since this morning.
Where did he go?
Lu Buping.
Mrs. Chun,
t-this is my father.
Father, this is Mrs. Chun.
He is your father?
I am Lu Jiang.
Thank you for taking care of my son
during this time.
Steward Lu, why didn't you say a word
that your father had come?
Steward Lu?
You are a steward here?
So this is the unfinished work
you mentioned?
Instead of
being the patriarch of the Lus,
you came here to become a steward?
You are really something.
Who's that?
M-M-Master...
Master Lu!
You are?
I-I am Chun Keling.
I have seen your portrait.
Can I shake hands with you?
Mother, I have shaken hands
with the martial arts alliance leader!
W-W-What?
Martial arts alliance leader?
Master Lu,
why did you come to our house?
To find my son.
Lu Buping is your son?
Mother, how could you
let Master Lu's son be a steward?
What steward? Don't spout nonsense here.
You even made him sleep in the woodshed.
Do whatever you have to do. Go.
Master Lu, don't listen to her.
My daughter likes to joke.
Just leave.
Mrs. Chun, sorry for the disturbance.
We're leaving.
Go.
Don't go just like that.
Father!
- Mr. Lu!
- I'm not leaving.
I-I'm not leaving.
You're not leaving?
Why?
Father,
I've been away from home for so long.
I think I've found
my purpose in life.
So... so I don't want to quit.
Are you trying to make me angry?
Is my son
only worthy of being a servant here?
Father, there's no shame in it.
Shut up!
Go back with me.
Go.
Father, father,
it's not that I don't want to go.
- Go!
- Father.
You're my only son.
I won't leave.
You have to take over as patriarch.
Father, I won't go.
- Come with me!
- No, I won't.
Go!
Peilan,
leave them there. I'll fold them myself.
It's okay, Mr. Lu.
You are about to leave.
Yes.
Didn't think the day'd come so soon.
It's good.
When you just came to our house,
you were scared every day.
It's better now.
In retrospect,
everything seems like yesterday.
Yes.
I just started
to feel like this was home.
And now I have to leave.
I-I will make you some more food
that you love to eat.
Peilan.
I want to stay with you a bit longer.
If I don't do that now,
I may not have another chance.
Peilan,
I'm about to leave.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
Mr. Lu,
I wish you joy.
Is there nothing else?
Come back often.
I don't want to leave.
I can't bear to.
Mr. Lu,
your father is right.
You can't be a servant all your life.
You are the only son of the Lu family.
You will be a hero.
But I don't care
about being a hero at all.
The only thing I care about is...
I will beg Mrs. Chun.
I'll ask her to convince father
to let me stay.
Mr. Lu!
Mrs. Chun.
Buping?
Look at what you did.
Why didn't you tell me earlier
that your father's
the martial arts alliance leader?
You even pretended to be a beggar.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Chun.
You are sorry?
The one who should say sorry
is me.
I made you do so much work earlier.
After you leave with him,
you have to take good care of yourself.
No, Mrs. Chun,
I don't want to leave.
You don't?
I've been with you people for so long.
I-I already have feelings for everyone.
Especially...
Especially you, Mrs. Chun.
Please let me stay.
Yeah, it's been so long.
How can we not have feelings?
Mrs. Chun, can you talk to my father
and ask him to let me stay?
To let you stay?
It's okay if I can't stay forever.
I just need a few more days.
I just want to stay with you
for a little longer.
Mrs. Chun, please help me.
I...
Do you really want to stay?
Then I'll talk to him.
- Mrs. Chun.
- Master Lu,
are you used to living in Keling's room?
It's a very nice place.
Thank you, Mrs. Chun.
You're welcome.
I have something to discuss with you.
What's it?
It's about Buping.
Please come in.
Okay, after you.
Buping.
Master.
I brewed a pot of good tea
for your father.
Where is he?
He's talking with Mrs. Chun in the room.
Why did your father close the door
for mere talking?
My father didn't close it,
but Mrs. Chun did.
Did she?
They don't seem to be talking.
Master, wait. Master.
Mrs. Chun,
about Buping,
I was about to ask for your advice.
Buping's mother was gone
since he was a child.
I didn't know how to raise him properly.
But this time,
I found that he has been deeply attached
to you people.
Could you tell me how you get along
with Buping normally in private?
And how do you communicate?
Uh, well...
I think the most important thing
is to respect
the thoughts of children.
And when you're with them,
be like a friend.
Respect?
Respect.
That's not right.
I asked him to go back
and take over as patriarch.
Don't I respect him?
Once he returns
as the patriarch,
everyone will respect him in every way.
I've been looking for him
for so long, Mrs. Chun.
I really didn't expect
that he would actually be here
as a servant
and take this
as his life goal.
No.
Buping is a sensible child.
Master Lu, you are a blessed man.
Mrs. Chun,
you don't have to speak for him.
I know my own son.
Master Lu, listen to me.
I came here to ask
if you could
let Buping stay.
I-I am not asking you
to let him be a steward.
I just feel that
since he's been with my family
for a long time
and we're attached to each other,
we all hate to see him go.
Please let him stay a little longer.
Mrs. Chun,
all things must come to an end.
He...
Master Lu, what's wrong with you?
Nothing. It's an old illness
from when I was young.
I'm fine.
Y-You should lie down.
- Take some rest.
- I'm fine, really.
No, don't push yourself.
Just lie down.
- Mrs. Chun.
- Lie down quickly.
Did I just hear
"lie down"?
Did I mishear?
I heard it too.
It can't be, right?
It can't be.
Young Lord, the Chuns
have already moved away.
They did?
Which idiot let them move away?
D-Didn't you let them move away?
I said that out of anger.
Your Highness?
Father, what brings you here?
I heard
you drove the Chuns away.
No, father, it's a misunderstanding.
Are you stupid?
What then
if Fourth Prince is back?
Actually, we can't
blame Young Lord for this.
The Chuns were planning to move anyway.
What's it to you?
I bet this was your bad idea.
- Father, I...
- And you.
I thought you had grown up.
But it seems that you're still hopeless.
Your Highness, it's not like that.
I am talking to my son.
You have no place to interrupt.
I noticed that
since you've been with him,
he has become a good-for-nothing.
Listen.
If Fourth Prince gets angry
when he's back,
you go take the blame yourself.
Did you hear me?
Yes.
Please calm down.
I'm going right now
to apologize to Chuns.
I certainly won't let Fourth Prince
blame you and Young Lord.
You'd better stick to your words.
What are you looking at?
Get lost!
Mr. Lu loves eggs the most.
I should cook more
to let him eat them on the road.
Miss Peilan.
Mr. Li.
The house has been reconstructed.
It's exactly like before.
Yes.
Mr. Li, what brings you here so late?
I came to see Mrs. Chun.
A few days ago,
Young Lord and you
had a small misunderstanding.
I came to apologize.
Mr. Li, did you hurt your face?
I…
I accidentally fell.
I fell.
I don't want to eat it.
It's not that.
Remove the egg shell
and rub it on your face.
The swelling will go down soon.
Mr. Li?
Thank you.
When you are away from home,
you must take good care of yourself.
(It turns out that in this world,)
(there is still someone
who cares about me.)
(On the day of Guiyou, it is sunny.)
(Today, a girl)
(walked into my heart.)
Fancy, but useless.
- Master Lu, are you done practicing?
- Mrs. Chun.
You washed the clothes?
Let me help you.
I can do it myself. Thank you.
I saw it was sunny today,
so I thought I should wash the clothes.
I can do it myself.
I'll do it with you.
You're just
like a young lad in spirit.
Mrs. Chun, you are flattering me.
No, I'm being sincere.
Thank you.
Ruyu, don't be deceived by him.
I see it now.
You practice swordsmanship
where Ruyu is.
You're showing off to her.
He's tricking you.
Stop flaunting yourself!
What are you doing?
Didn't you see?
He was clutching your clothes
with that smirk.
He's taking advantage of you.
What's your problem?
You have no shame.
It's Ruyu's underwear.
And you were pinching them.
You shameless old man!
Are you out of your mind?
These are Master Lu's clothes.
Mr. Guo,
you got me wrong.
You washed his clothes,
and they are underwear.
Lu Zhensheng, listen.
Lu Zhensheng? I'm Guo Zhensheng.
You even got my name wrong.
Master Lu is our precious guest.
Don't make a fuss here.
It's embarrassing.
Master Lu, give me a hand.
I... Mr. Guo.
Mr. Guo, here.
Don't mind him.
Mr. Guo.
You want me to help you
wring clothes? Disgusting!
He is really sick. Just ignore him.
Mrs. Chun, is it really okay?
What's not okay about it?
Miss Peilan.
Mr. Li.
Why are you here?
I was passing by.
What a coincidence to run into you!
Indeed.
Miss Peilan,
the egg you gave me last time
was very useful. Look.
Right? Master taught me about that.
Master?
He is really awesome.
Look, I...
It's alright.
What do you mean by "alright"?
It's worn.
It can still be worn if patched up.
I have to buy groceries.
I'll be off now, Mr. Li.
Uh...
She's really a provident girl.
Make way, make way.
Martial arts alliance leader?
How much do you get paid a month?
It's just a title
with no money.
So what's the use of that?
It's just a name, right?
I have my share of profits every month.
Will you just shut up?
Master Lu,
what's with that chest pain of yours?
It's a lingering illness
from when I was young and reckless.
You have to be more careful
in the future.
Being reckless?
He is just feeble.
The pickled cabbage fish soup is here.
The pickled cabbage fish soup!
Master Lu,
this pickled cabbage fish soup
was personally made by me.
Come and try it.
There might be a lot of fishbones in it.
Be careful.
Okay.
It's okay.
Try some.
Be careful. It's hot.
It's amazing!
Mrs. Chun, did you ever learn to cook?
What are you talking about?
I never learned it on purpose.
I just...
I just love to cook.
My four daughters
are quite picky.
Right.
But ever since I hurt my back,
I haven't done much cooking.
Right. At our age,
we are scared of hurting our backs.
Yes.
What's there to be scared of?
You have a doctor here.
Mother,
I have something to tell you.
Can you let Keling
stay in Peilan's room?
I study every night.
She's too noisy,
and I can't concentrate.
Why don't you just study less?
This is?
This is my third daughter, Chun Banxia.
Hello, Master Lu.
She loves reading.
It's good to read.
She's promising, Mrs. Chun.
- Right.
- Unlike my naughty son.
He won't study, no matter what.
She not only loves to read,
but she also has medical skills.
Really?
You've also learned medicine?
You're also interested?
I have roamed
the martial arts world for a long time.
I've never seen a female doctor.
Your daughter is really extraordinary.
I'm flattered.
When I was young,
I wanted
to learn medicine wholeheartedly.
But then I felt,
as a man,
I should practice martial arts.
I thought
learning medicine was very difficult.
I didn't expect it to be
not challenging at all.
So I simply gave up medicine
and practiced martial arts.
Why am I saying this?
Let's eat.
It's getting cold.
I just don't understand.
We study medicine to save people.
- How could that not be manly?
- Excuse me!
- It's hot!
- At many critical times...
Watch out.
Keling, be careful.
Be careful.
Are you okay, Keling?
I should have carried it.
It's my honor
to serve Master Lu.
You're too kind.
- Sit down.
- At...
At many critical times,
we step forward.
Father, let me get you some soup.
Buping, someone is speaking.
Let him finish his words.
Master, continue.
We step forward,
having no time to eat or drink.
- You can drink mine.
- Thank you.
Come on. Just try it.
Keling,
can you let me finish my words?
This way, I'm likely to lose breath.
If you want to speak, just speak.
So talkative.
Come on. Let's eat.
At many critical times,
we, the doctors, step forward
and save one life after another!
As a man of prowess,
you only know how to kill people.
And we save people!
My father didn't agree
to let me stay in the end.
Peilan,
I'm giving this comb to you.
After I leave,
every time you use it,
you can think of me.
There is just one thing
I have never told you about.
I like you.
Is this a bit too abrupt?
Peilan!
Peilan.
Mr. Li.
Did you buy some buns?
I love buns the most.
Do you want to have one?
Sure.
It's delicious.
Then I'll go home first.
Peilan.
You offered me a bun.
I also have something for you.
What is this?
Last time I went to the street
and saw a shoe shop.
I found these shoes
suited you very well.
Take them.
No, thank you. I have shoes.
I know. They're just
a token of my appreciation.
Take them.
I can't accept this gift.
Are you belittling me?
No.
Then you should take them.
I can't.
Mr. Li, please take them back.
- I...
- Try them on quickly.
You... I don't want them.
Wait, you...
I'm not going then.
I...
Does it fit well?
I-I guess so.
That's good. Then you must wear them.
I'll go ahead then.
Thank you for your buns.
Mr. Li!
No, Mr. Li!
Why did he give you shoes?
I don't know.
I've never given you shoes.
He refused to leave
if I didn't try...
It's your feet.
What could he do if you said no?
At that time, I was...
Do you really not understand?
What?
My heart.
What's this?
I like you.
(Do you really not understand?)
Peilan.
Mr. Lu.
I heard you didn't have dinner.
I specifically made you some soup.
I'll leave it here for you.
Thanks, Mr. Lu.
Come here and try it.
I made it especially for you.
I-I'll eat it later.
Are you still mad?
Not at all. Why would I be mad?
So...
Uh...
What do you think
about the thing I mentioned earlier?
What to think about?
The thing I told you earlier.
Mr. Lu, I don't know.
Do you like me?
Or do you not?
Just tell me.
I am leaving soon anyway.
Mr. Lu,
I just feel really confused.
Can you give me some more time to think?
I see.
I'm not good enough for you.
I wish you happiness.
Mr. Lu!
Do you know?
Master Lu,
the martial arts alliance leader,
now lives in our house.
To be precise, he lives in my room.
Don't you think it's awesome?
Pretty awesome.
Boss,
why hasn't A-Si contacted us
for a long time?
I-I don't know.
Maybe he went on a long trip.
Then when will he come back?
How am I supposed to know that?
Will he never come back?
Then let him be.
You drink first. I will buy some more.
What to drink?
Nothing.
What're you drinking?
I don't have anything.
I am not drinking.
What's wrong with her?
It was just a punch.
And what are you doing,
running away without a word?
(Yuanyang Temple)
Don't make a sound.
Or it'll cost your life.
You are driving me crazy.
I've been nervous all day because of it.
Then there's one more thing.
Say it.
I like you.
The first time I saw you,
I fell in love with you.
(I left the palace just to find you.)
(Although I kept getting hurt,)
(as long as I'm with you,)
(I'm very happy.)
(Yuanyang Temple)
The falling flower intends
to follow the flowing water.
Draw a knife to stop the water,
and the water flows even more.
The flowing water has no intention
of loving the falling flower.
How can I leave home with ease?
Why?
Why can't the sun
and the moon ever meet?
No.
When the weather is clear,
the sun and the moon shine together.
Why are our hearts so far apart?
Is it the arrangement of heaven
or the jesting of fate?
I hate this arrangement of heaven.
I hate this jesting of fate even more.
Go on and be as happy as you want.
Leave me alone to grieve.
Master!
Buping!
- Buping!
- Master!
Master!
=Hilarious Family=
♪Your smile is like the spring
with newly sprouted leaves♪
♪Passing through the continuous time♪
♪I am still longing♪
♪Gentle and soft yearning♪
♪She emerges from all things♪
♪So peaceful and distant♪
♪The wind gently blows♪
♪Scattered at the end of time♪
♪I hope that every flower here♪
♪Has never been forgotten♪
♪Facing away from
the ancient windmill in the twilight♪
♪I tugged your heartstrings♪
♪You said you would sing in the wind♪
♪The wind gently blows♪
♪Scattered at the end of time♪
♪I hope that every flower here♪
♪Has never been forgotten♪
♪Facing away from
the ancient windmill in the twilight♪
♪I tugged your heartstrings♪
♪You said you would sing in the wind♪