(Bench Part)
♪Hey, I say, someone behaves today♪
♪Oh, I thought it was someone else♪
♪Really extraordinary♪
♪The cutie in the mirror♪
♪Oh, looking a bit arrogant♪
♪Every day, I sleep in and feel drowsy♪
♪Sleepy and hungry.
Whose alarm clock got hit♪
♪Only the body is lazy,
and the spirit is very nice♪
♪Sun's up high, but I have my posture♪
♪As I walk, I sway overly♪
♪I believe that I can fly♪
♪Turning around and smiling,
I look silly and cute♪
♪Baby, don't be shy♪
♪If I want to laugh, I will♪
♪Ha ha ha ha ha♪
♪If I want to play, I will♪
♪Um um um um um♪
♪If I want to make a fuss, I will♪
♪La la la la la♪
♪What are you looking at me for♪
♪It's none of your business♪
♪If I want to laugh, I will♪
♪Ha ha ha ha ha♪
♪If I want to play, I will♪
♪Um um um um um♪
♪If I want to make a fuss, I will♪
♪La la la la la♪
♪What are you looking at me for♪
♪Na na na na na♪
=Hilarious Family=
=Episode 9=
(Peilan seeks attention on her birthday)
(Li Tengyun needs to die for his master)
It is a bit cold. I need to
remind mother to put on more clothes.
Everyone, come have some peaches.
Mr. Lu.
- Peaches?
- Come on.
I just washed them. Have one.
Eat quickly. Or else,
my mother will find out later.
Lu Buping.
Mrs. Chun, have a peach.
What are you doing here?
Have you swept the yard?
I'll do it now.
Being lazy when there is a chance.
Mother, eat a peach. I just washed them.
Where are the others?
They probably didn't hear me.
I'll call them later.
Quite sweet.
Why are you looking at me?
Do I have something on my face?
No.
Peilan.
What's wrong, Mother?
Have Chun Jinrong come to me.
She wasn't back
until the middle of the night.
She is becoming more unreasonable.
He kept me waiting inexplicably
till the middle of the night.
If he can't come,
he should at least explain it.
How come Young Lord is so arrogant?
Even if you are pretending
to play hard to get,
y-you need to show up at least.
Jinrong, Mother needs you.
Why?
I don't know either.
Maybe about what happened last night.
What's the point in asking about it?
Jinrong, you should go.
Otherwise, Mother will get angry again.
So annoying.
I washed peaches
and put them in the living room.
Do you know you are blocking the way?
Are you blind? Move!
Mr. Lu, Mr. Lu, don't be angry.
Jinrong is not targeting you.
Is there anyone else?
She...
- I just feel that she...
- M-Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu, have a peach.
Does it taste good?
Yeah.
Right.
Open it.
Okay.
Mr. Lu, where did you pick this up?
I bought it.
I specifically asked Master
to buy it for me.
Why did you ask him to buy it?
It's your birthday today, isn't it?
I need to give you a gift, anyway.
Mr. Lu.
Why did you know it's my birthday?
I just asked Master.
Thank you, Mr. Lu.
- You're welcome.
- It's so beautiful.
D-Do you like to eat
soft peaches or hard ones?
I like hard peaches.
Me too.
When I was a child,
my father would take me
to the market to buy those
large red peaches every year.
When I am rich,
I'll buy you a peach mountain.
You can enjoy them
however much you like.
That's too much. How wasteful.
Take a bite and throw it away.
Peilan.
Banxia, have a peach.
Thanks. By the way, Peilan.
I'll get one for Master too.
Lu Buping.
Can you come to the pharmacy
and dump the medicinal dregs later?
Sure.
Lu Buping, when talking to others,
looking into their eyes
is the basic respect.
Hasn't anyone taught you this?
- Wait, wait.
- Also,
regulate your emotions before you speak.
I...
She doesn't know it's your birthday?
She spoke to me like that?
Simmer down, Mr. Lu. She's nice.
- Peaches.
- Keling.
Peilan, have you heard
that someone stole children
near Guantou Temple?
No, I haven't.
Once I catch them,
I'll teach them a lesson.
Wait. Can you finish them
as you took so many peaches?
Mother. I'm leaving.
Where are you going, Keling?
To study.
That girl.
She drove me crazy.
Have you eaten yet?
Not yet.
Well, this is for you.
No, thanks. Mr. Lu, you eat it.
How about I break it open?
We can share it.
It's okay, Mr. Lu.
I don't want to eat it now. You eat it.
What family members are they?
It is your birthday today,
but an extra peach isn't saved.
It's not like that.
They have their own business.
And it's just a birthday.
Not a big deal.
Forget it. Have this half.
(Harmony Brings Fortune)
Osmanthus cake.
Yes.
Wait a moment. Free of osmanthus.
Young Lord, the men at the gate said,
last night Mr. Li was at the gate,
calling for you all night
until he lost his voice.
Didn't they drive him away?
He refused to leave,
saying he must see you one last time.
He almost alarmed His Highness.
Li Tengyun.
Young Lord, I had previously not
lived up to your expectations.
But I guarantee
there won't be a next time.
Young Lord, considering my loyalty,
please give me one more chance.
Are you done? You've seen the last time.
Leave now.
Young Lord, you can't leave.
Please give me one more chance.
I'll count from three.
Please let me
stay at your side and assist you.
Three.
This time, I will definitely
help you deal with Fourth Prince.
- So you'll have no worries.
- Two.
I'll definitely help
get it done once and for all.
One... Once and for all? Tell me.
I...
Go on. How do you
get it once and for all?
I... How about we...
What do you mean? Murder?
It's feasible.
There is a saying that
if you're not fierce, you can't make it.
It's hard for us to tame Chun Keling.
But you can't...
Then I ask you how you will kill her?
First, we can climb over their wall.
Find Chun Keling's room.
Take the chance to kill her
when she's asleep.
That simple?
It doesn't seem difficult.
Okay, it's that simple, right?
Go ahead. Now go. Do it.
No, Young Lord. I didn't mean that.
Don't we have assassins in our mansion?
What do you think
our Lord Ling's Mansion is? Assassins?
If we don't have any assassins,
then we'll have to make long-term plans.
Young Lord.
Mr. Li is so resourceful.
You should learn from Mr. Li.
- Learn from Mr. Li.
I'm flattered.
Mr. Li said,
"Murder is simple."
You go and experience it.
Anyway, you must
bring back a corpse today.
If it's not Chun Keling's,
then it's Mr. Li's.
- Yes.
Wait a minute.
Young Lord, as specialists
only master their own fields,
I'm really not suitable. I...
Haven't you always wanted a chance?
- I...
- What's more,
you can try out your own idea,
and see if it works.
If it works, I'll invite you back,
and respectfully call you Mr. Li.
I...
Peilan.
Mr. Lu.
- You bought so much.
- Yeah.
- Let me help you.
- Thanks, Mr. Lu.
You're welcome. Give them all to me.
It's not my fault.
You are always blaming me.
Jinrong, are you going out?
Your older sister is so impolite.
She might not be in a great mood.
- Jinrong.
- Xiaoxiao.
Let me greet your mother.
No need. Let's go.
What's with your dark circles?
Don't ask. I'll tell you
in the carriage.
- Banxia.
- Peilan.
She is even more outrageous.
You are her elder sister.
We are family. I am used to it.
Peilan, what are we eating tonight?
I've made tofu soup.
Tofu again.
Tofu again. She could make it herself.
It's odd for a family
to speak so politely.
Do they consider you
as part of the family?
You were carrying so much,
but no one offered to help.
They all have their own things to do.
Well, caring won't hurt.
Mr. Lu, calm down.
I get anxious when you're upset.
You... You're the only carefree one.
Don't you like to carry? Keep on then.
Like carrying that much.
Give me.
(Where am I headed?)
(Am I going to kill someone?)
(Am I dreaming?)
(I'm shooting myself in the foot.)
(Should I run away now?)
Young Lord said if you dare to run,
you will be executed on the spot.
Who wants to run away?
Move.
- Peilan, are you free now?
-Master.
I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Sorting out veggies.
Never mind. I will do it myself.
What are you doing?
I am whisking tea, right?
Of course not. It's scenting tea.
Evenly sprinkle these jasmine flowers
on top of the tea leaves.
Then mix.
Scent for 15 minutes,
then take it out and mix again.
And scent for another 15 minutes.
Repeat it nine times. Understand?
I got it, Master.
I'll leave it to you. Thank you.
No problem.
You can go back to your work.
I didn't expect
your Master looks innocent,
but would also boss you around.
Why didn't he ask Banxia to do it?
Banxia has to prepare the medicine.
Is that so?
Before preparing the medicine,
she needs to read some books and learn.
You're always finding excuses for them.
Let me help you.
Okay.
How do we do this anyway?
Peilan, put aside
the jasmine tea for now.
It's fine. I can do it.
No. Can you first help me wash herbs?
When washing herbs,
don't soak them too long.
Or else, there will be no effect.
If not soaked, they won't be clean.
Weigh this carefully.
- Understood.
- Thank you.
It's okay, Master.
Look, no matter how good
you are to them,
nobody cares about you.
Mr. Lu, please stop it.
Today is your birthday.
Since you woke up
this morning until now.
they've treated you like that,
Mr. Lu, what exactly
do you want me to do?
It's not about what you should do.
Why should they order you around?
Are you their servant?
As the saying goes,
"Only crying children get candy."
I'm not asking you to cry right now.
Peilan, Peilan.
I am already sad
and you are still criticizing me.
I'm sorry. Let me help you.
Come on. Don't cry.
I'm so upset.
It's okay. It's okay.
Lu Buping.
What are you doing?
I... Well...
You bullied Peilan?
- No.
- No, Mother. Mr. Lu didn't bully me.
Then why are you crying?
I got sand in my eyes.
Mr. Lu is helping get rid of it.
- That's right.
- Lu Buping, I'm warning you.
Don't think you can bully Peilan.
I'm watching you.
Whoever bullies her will know.
Mother, Mr. Lu really didn't bully me.
Then what's wrong? Let me tell you.
You can't cry on your birthday.
It'll bring bad luck.
Mother, do you remember?
How could I forget? I gave birth to you.
Mother, what do you want to eat?
I'll make it for you.
Today is your birthday.
You buy whatever you want to eat,
and I'll cook for you.
Let's all have a good meal together.
Make it lively.
Lu Buping, don't slack off.
Alright.
Mr. Lu. My mother remembered it.
What's so special about that?
She should remember.
I need to grab groceries.
I'm going to steam rice for Mother.
Didn't you buy groceries already?
Mother likes chicken.
I'm going to buy one for her.
Near the place where chickens are sold,
there are buns?
Yes.
Okay.
Let's keep an eye on it here.
Observe it for a while.
No one should be able to discover us.
Mr. Li.
Miss Peilan.
What are you doing here?
I... Where are you going?
It's my birthday today.
I'm going to buy a chicken.
Wish you boundless happiness.
- Congratulations.
Thank you all.
Then I'll leave you. Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
When will we take action?
At night. Who would kill people
in broad daylight?
Mr. Li said
we can't kill people during the day.
What are you doing?
Young Lord asked me
to record everything you do.
Let's go. Hurry up.
It's an ominous sign.
Mr. Li said, "It's an ominous sign."
Why do you record everything?
(Happy Birthday)
Clean properly.
It's all dust everywhere.
Mother, why didn't you tell me earlier
about Peilan's birthday?
I'm all flustered.
My plans are disrupted.
It's already good enough I remember it.
I have to remember
the birthdays of four of you.
But none of you can
remember my birthday.
What are your plans?
Do you want to
put the word "fortune" in the middle?
Or the word "longevity"?
Aren't you highly educated?
Why are you asking me?
Fine, just write "longevity."
Where's Chun Jinrong?
She rarely stays at home.
Everything in the house
only needs me to arrange.
On this day of good weather
with a happy event, don't quarrel.
Just shut up.
Wasn't it you who asked Peilan
to wash those herbs?
The pharmacy is bustling
early in the morning.
I totally forgot.
I tell you.
Only I can order my daughters around.
Sorry.
Peilan, you are back.
How do you think our decoration?
You didn't have to
go through all this trouble.
What's the trouble?
I think it's still lacking.
Do you think
there are enough lanterns outside?
That's enough.
Hang up a couple more.
It's enough, Mother.
Mother, let me help you.
Hang one here.
- Come on, I'll do it.
- Here.
Mr. Lu, my mother is cooking for me.
Everyone is busy for me.
Do you know there is
something fishy
when things suddenly change?
Mr. Lu, you're really
misunderstanding everyone.
Suddenly having a day off,
I'm still not quite used to it.
Rest well for the day, alright?
I'm going to help my Mother.
You.
Mother, let me help.
Bring the vegetables over to me.
Okay.
My birthday is even more boisterous.
Mother, who are we waiting for?
There is a mysterious guest today.
Mrs. Chun.
- Yao Wen, Yao Wu.
- Happy birthday to you, Peilan.
- Thank you.
- What brings you here?
Boss asked us to come
and celebrate Peilan's birthday.
Which boss?
Keling called us
to celebrate Peilan's birthday.
Thank you. Please come in and sit.
Okay. Alright. Let's go.
Is there anything to eat?
Yes.
Mother, let's go in too.
What's the rush?
There are still visitors.
More?
Hello, Mrs. Chun.
A-Si.
Happy birthday, Peilan.
Thank you, A-Si.
Let's go. Let's go.
Mrs. Chun.
Xiaoxiao.
We should have invited you home earlier.
Jinrong, why didn't you
bring Xiaoxiao home earlier?
Don't be polite.
Peilan, rouge.
Rouge?
Happy birthday.
Thank you, Xiaoxiao.
How do you know?
Your sister told me.
Jinrong.
Could I forget? Happy birthday!
Alright, please go in.
Mother, everyone's here now.
Let's go in.
Not everyone's here yet.
What's the rush?
Ruyu.
Ms. Zhang. Why did you bring a gift?
This is Matchmaker Zhang who I met
at the Marriage Bridge. Greet her.
Hello, Ms. Zhang.
- It's Peilan, right?
- Peilan.
Peilan looks a lot like you.
Like me, right?
A beauty.
Xu, you came. Finally.
- I miss you so much.
- I miss you too.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Okay.
- Come on.
- Quickly, take this.
- Okay.
Congratulations.
Please go inside. This way.
Thank you. Thank you.
Mother. Mother?
Hold on, Mother.
Come. All the sisters, here.
Let me tell you all.
The fish Peilan cooked
is absolutely delicious.
I'm going to check on the dishes.
Hurry up.
- Peilan.
- Mother.
When will it be ready?
It's almost ready, Mother.
Is it time for the toast?
No, I mean the fish.
Fish? Well...
I'll cook it after I finish this.
Alright, hurry up then.
I've been praising you to my sisters
that your fish is amazing.
Alright, Mother.
By the way, the wine is running out.
You need to go get some more later.
Alright, Mother.
Mrs. Chun.
How could I have forgotten about you?
You don't have to go.
Make a few more dishes.
Lu Buping, you go get the wine.
Quickly, please.
I'll go to the front
and greet the guests.
Alright, Mother.
This is not a birthday party for you.
Why wouldn't it be my birthday party?
Clearly they are using your birthday
as an excuse to treat guests.
I thought they had changed.
It's okay, Mr. Lu.
Anyway. They're here for my birthday.
What are you doing then?
I... I'm fine.
Why are you always staring at me?
It's been a day.
When are you going to do it?
Didn't you hear it's her birthday today?
Do you think that's appropriate
we commit a crime today?
It's not Chun Keling's birthday, anyway.
You're not going to kill her.
Listen, you'd better not urge me.
I'm under great pressure.
I don't know what I might do.
Mr. Li said
he was under great pressure.
Stop taking notes.
If you have time for this,
can't you help me instead?
Young Lord said no help is allowed.
You.
Bro, it's getting dark.
They are tired. Why not...
Why not take your body back?
Why not wait a little longer?
- Take it.
- No, thanks.
Why are you being polite with me?
This fish is so delicious.
You keep it for yourself.
If I want to eat,
I can ask Peilan
to make it for me anytime.
I not only ate but also took it.
What's the big deal?
Aren't we old friends?
I'll feel so embarrassed.
Chun Peilan, today is your birthday.
Your family has treated you like that,
but you don't have a single complaint.
You always make excuses for them.
Is there anyone
who remembers what you have done?
When you do all these chores,
is there anyone
who comes to help you? Except me.
Why are you the only one
who is wronged in this family?
Why should the good child
always be bullied?
Mr. Lu, please stop it.
My mother will hear it.
Peilan, I've made up my mind.
I'm going to take you to Dali.
Anyway, there will be
no soldiers to catch me.
Let's start all over there.
Find a hidden place to live a good life.
I never allow you to do
these chores anymore.
Will you come with me?
Mr. Lu, please stop it.
I can't leave my family.
Are they your family members?
It was you who was yelling out just now.
Mother.
Mrs. Chun, I have something to tell you.
Say it later. Peilan, come over. Hurry.
Chun.
Our Peilan has grown up safely.
She remains so capable and sensible.
Rest assured.
She takes good care of all of us.
You must continue to bless her,
and also bless our whole family.
Mother.
Peilan, in front of your father,
I will give this to you today.
I can't take it off. Lend me a hand.
It's on your wrist now.
Mother, isn't this our family heirloom?
This is the treasure
left by your great grandmother.
I never took it off
during the hardest time in our family.
You need to keep it well.
But my sisters...
Don't worry about them.
Among the four of you sisters,
you are the most gentle one,
with the best temperament.
Since childhood, they all knew
how to fight for what they wanted.
Only you think about helping others.
Okay, Mother.
Being able to be sisters
with you is their luck.
Keep it for all of us. We'll be at ease.
What I am most worried about is you.
You are too kind.
I'm really afraid you will be wronged
when you are married.
Sometimes I think
how great would it be
if you could talk back.
Mother, I won't get married.
You blamed me
for what I've done today, didn't you?
No.
As you know,
we finally moved to Jianglin.
But we have no one to rely on.
It is better to have near neighbors
than distant relatives.
It's good for our family to interact
more with our neighbors.
I am getting older day by day.
But I want our house
to be lively.
But I am incapable.
Thank you for helping me today.
Peilan, you have worked hard.
Mother, I'm fine.
If there's anything I don't do well,
don't take it to heart.
Mother, I understand.
I know you understand.
You're my best daughter.
I said you couldn't cry today,
but you're crying.
I've told you it'll bring bad luck.
Come on. Wipe your tears.
I forgot it.
Look.
I bought such nice peaches
at a place far away.
Only you can eat them.
Mother.
Fine.
Stop crying. Stop it.
Mother.
Take your time. Don't open your eyes.
I dare not open.
Where are we going, Keling?
Almost there.
Turn around. When I count to three,
you can open your eyes.
One, two, three.
Peilan, this is the birthday present.
A peach tree.
Thank you, Keling.
Peilan, I know
every year on your birthday,
you would think of
Father giving you peaches.
I was young when Father died
and didn't remember much about him.
From now on,
when you celebrate your birthday,
I'll give you peaches on behalf of him.
My dear sister.
Where did you dig this from?
Did you ask for permission?
It's from A-Si. It's actually his idea.
Happy birthday, Peilan.
Thank you, A-Si.
But I think I need to tell you
that this is actually a cherry tree.
Didn't you say it is a peach tree?
I thought it is a peach tree.
No. I also love cherries.
It's nice Keling had that intention.
Jinrong.
Here, this is a sachet from me.
Open it and see.
Have a look.
I embroidered all of this myself.
As a girl, you shall
pay attention to makeup.
It's expensive.
Jinrong, don't waste money on it.
Peilan.
Banxia. Master.
Peilan, I think
the most precious about a person
is not whether he has money
or how much money he has,
but his spiritual world.
So I chose this.
How pretty.
Right. When you go out
and see flowers and plants you like,
you can pick them
and put them on your bedside table.
It can enhance your taste.
Thank you, Banxia.
I happened to need a jar
for growing green onions.
Very suitable.
As long as you're happy.
Happy birthday.
I'm sorry about this morning.
It's nothing, Master. Thank you.
What is inside? Pills?
They can boost your beauty,
and replenish your energy and blood.
Guo Zhensheng, are you crazy?
Who gives medicine as a birthday gift?
No. It's a supplement, not a medicine.
What supplement?
I think you have ulterior motives.
Wait. How can I have ulterior motives?
Mother, I'm really at the age of
needing supplements.
Mother, Mother.
- How do I explain it?
- Nothing.
No. I really like cherries.
Mother. Master. Stop chasing.
It's naturally so.
Peilan stays in the kitchen every day.
Not a big deal. Stop quarreling, please.
Master. Mother.
(Happy Birthday from Lu Buping, Guo Zhensheng,
Chun Keling, Chun Banxia, Chun Jinrong, Du Ruyu)
♪Passing through the continuous time♪
Thank you all.
I'm really happy.
♪She emerges from all things♪
Mr. Lu, have a peach.
Mr. Lu, I'm really thrilled today.
You are content with this.
Also, I understood one thing.
Family members might not always
talk about you,
but they always
keep you in their hearts.
This is what they are supposed to do.
This is what it means to be a family.
Aren't they the earrings I gave you?
Yes, I've put them on. Look pretty?
I have such a good taste.
About going to Dali,
I thought it over carefully.
You can consider it.
Mr. Lu, now I
just hope to take good care
of my family.
And I hope you and my family
can all stay safe and healthy.
This is my biggest desire now.
Pretty good.
So, in your heart,
am I considered a family member?
Of course.
Really?
So what do I rank?
Second.
Second?
Because I think
Mother and my sisters
rank first in my heart.
Ranking second is pretty good.
Ranking second is good.
There's no others ranking second?
No.
But Master ranks third.
=Hilarious Family=
♪Your smile is like the spring
with newly sprouted leaves♪
♪Passing through the continuous time♪
♪I am still longing♪
♪Gentle and soft yearning♪
♪She emerges from all things♪
♪So peaceful and distant♪
♪The wind gently blows♪
♪Scattered at the end of time♪
♪I hope that every flower here♪
♪Has never been forgotten♪
♪Facing away from
the ancient windmill in the twilight♪
♪I tugged your heartstrings♪
♪You said you would sing in the wind♪
♪The wind gently blows♪
♪Scattered at the end of time♪
♪I hope that every flower here♪
♪Has never been forgotten♪
♪Facing away from
the ancient windmill in the twilight♪
♪I tugged your heartstrings♪
♪You said you would sing in the wind♪