(Bench Part)
♪Hey, I say, someone behaves today♪
♪Oh, I thought it was someone else♪
♪Really extraordinary♪
♪The cutie in the mirror♪
♪Oh, looking a bit arrogant♪
♪Every day, I sleep in and feel drowsy♪
♪Sleepy and hungry.
Whose alarm clock got hit♪
♪Only the body is lazy,
and the spirit is very nice♪
♪Sun's up high, but I have my posture♪
♪As I walk, I sway overly♪
♪I believe that I can fly♪
♪Turning around and smiling,
I look silly and cute♪
♪Baby, don't be shy♪
♪If I want to laugh, I will♪
♪Ha ha ha ha ha♪
♪If I want to play, I will♪
♪Um um um um um♪
♪If I want to make a fuss, I will♪
♪La la la la la♪
♪What are you looking at me for♪
♪It's none of your business♪
♪If I want to laugh, I will♪
♪Ha ha ha ha ha♪
♪If I want to play, I will♪
♪Um um um um um♪
♪If I want to make a fuss, I will♪
♪La la la la la♪
♪What are you looking at me for♪
♪Na na na na na♪
=Hilarious Family=
=Episode 20=
(Fidgety Banxia gets suspicious)
(Jinrong wants to go public
with her romance)
Reviewing the old and knowing the new,
one can be a teacher.
Mrs. Chun, in my opinion,
you don't look your age at all.
Well...
Stop flattering me.
I'm not.
You really don't.
Really?
By the way, Mrs. Chun,
someone wants to take me as a tutor.
So, you are leaving?
We agreed long ago
that I'd leave after a few days.
Okay.
Chun Banxia, focus.
Reviewing the old and knowing the new,
one can be a teacher.
What are you reading?
What are you doing here?
The road is right here.
Can't I stand here?
Still reading The Analects?
You'll never get married
if you continue like this.
Give your mother some peace of mind.
It's none of your business.
I'm trying to be nice.
It's time for a meal.
I don't need you to do that.
As an educated person,
how can you be so coarse?
Get lost! Now!
Okay, Miss Banxia.
Pushing an educated person
until she needs to use force,
you are really something.
Reviewing the old and knowing the new,
one can be a teacher.
Mr. Shen,
please have a salted duck egg.
Thank you, Madam.
Miss Banxia.
Please.
Who allowed you to eat with my bowl?
What's all the fuss about?
What's the problem if he uses it?
Hurry up and eat.
I'm not hungry. I'll go to the pharmacy.
It's still early. Why are you rushing
to the pharmacy?
You went the wrong way.
Yes.
Miss Banxia, just eat first.
You wouldn't be cautious
and unwilling to dine with me,
would you?
Shut up.
Mother, I'm going to the pharmacy
to tidy up the herbs.
Well...
Don't save food. I'm not hungry.
What herbs need to be sorted
at the pharmacy?
Are you asking me?
Banxia has left. Why are you still here?
I haven't even picked up the bowl yet.
So what are you waiting for?
Where are Jinrong and Keling?
Still sleeping.
It's so late,
and they're still sleeping?
Don't leave food for them.
Really?
Then I'll eat it, okay?
Mr. Lu, can you finish it?
I can finish it.
Can you eat this much?
Take out some for them.
It's all saved, Mother.
Just eat.
Jinrong,
no one saw you as you came, right?
Was it necessary to make me
enter from the back door?
No, it's not.
I really can't stand this kind of
sneaky life.
Yes, I know, Jinrong.
I know we've been together
for a long time.
But isn't it quite good
for us to drink tea
and chat together?
What's so good about it?
We've been together
for a long time.
And we always hide
in the Spring River Restaurant,
drinking tea.
Don't be mad.
Here. Drink some tea and calm down.
Now, I'm sick at the sight of tea.
Then we're not drinking it.
Have some snacks.
My mother is arranging blind dates
for me now.
Do you think I should go or not?
Y-You definitely can't go.
You are already with me.
And you are seeing other men?
Do you think it's appropriate?
No, it's not appropriate.
It's certainly not.
But how should I tell my mother?
You can just say you don't want to go.
But you know
my mother's temperament.
I wouldn't dare say that.
Why don't you go tell her?
Me?
Will it be appropriate
for me to talk to her?
You should talk to her.
Then how about
I go talk to my mother,
and you go talk to your father?
My father?
Jinrong,
c-can we not bring this up?
Aren't we quite good the way we are now?
Don't be angry.
Here.
Look at this. Look at it.
Do you like it?
Young Lord, I don't want these.
These are not the reasons I am with you.
Tell me what you want.
I can have someone buy it.
I want you to tell others
about our relationship.
Well...
Jinrong,
isn't it enough for the two of us
to be together?
Why do we have to let others know?
Besides, are you with me
just to let others know?
Can't we let others know
that I am with you?
Yes.
Our relationship was unstable
when we were first together.
I understand that you
didn't want to make it public.
But it has been a long time.
Is it going to be like this forever?
Yes, tell me
what you want me to do now.
It's not about what I want now.
It's about what you want.
I...
Okay, l-let's not talk about this.
Let's drop the topic, okay?
Then I have nothing else to say.
Neither do I.
I should go back now.
(Jiren Pharmacy)
Master,
do you have a minute?
Yes. What's the matter?
Master,
I think I've contracted
some kind of disease.
I'm itching all over.
(Ancestral medicine)
It's only natural that a man who lingers
in brothels gets sick.
Well, that's true.
Master, what do you think?
Is my condition severe?
Why are there so many bites?
They are all over your arm.
These are flea bites.
Don't worry.
Fleas?
How can there be fleas?
I'm usually very clean.
I take several baths a day.
Master, can you take another look?
I think there might be more on my back.
People can see us.
Follow me, Mr. Shen.
Please come in.
Be careful.
You look slim when you're dressed.
But you're actually quite muscular.
You have a good figure.
Where have you been?
Why are there so many bites?
Tidy yourself up.
Don't worry.
I'll prescribe you.
One dose is for a bath,
and the other is to be taken orally.
Thank you, Master.
No problem.
How much does this cost?
Two taels.
Two taels?
Banxia, it doesn't cost that much.
Wait.
Two taels are fine.
Master,
I didn't bring money.
Can you put it on my account?
You!
It's okay.
Mr. Shen is a guest of our family.
After the medicine is ready,
I'll let...
I won't go.
I'll send it over to you.
Scald your intimate clothing
with boiling water.
Thank you so much, Master.
Take care.
Don't mind him.
It's okay.
Annoying.
Another tub of water
so early in the morning!
I-I'm sorry.
Are you still angry?
I'm not even angry.
What do you have to be angry about?
Don't be angry.
You can be angry for a while longer.
Feeling better now?
Here.
Is it sweeter than usual?
And you spit the seed.
So you've
prepared all these.
And these.
Are you satisfied?
They are okay.
Just "okay"?
Don't be angry anymore.
How about this?
Yes.
I might be a little grumpy
this morning.
It's because I was anxious,
and those words
jumped out of my mouth.
No, actually,
I also had my faults this morning.
If you realize
you have your faults,
it's something we can talk about.
Pour a glass of wine.
Okay.
Let's finish this glass
and let bygones be bygones.
Okay.
Young Lord,
frankly speaking,
I envy you.
You do?
What do you envy me for?
I envy you for not considering
anyone's feelings
or anything.
You haven't seen it
when I'm feeling troubled.
Born in Lord Ling's Mansion,
what could possibly trouble you?
You wouldn't understand.
Hardship in royal family.
How tough could it be?
Forget it.
What do you mean by "forget it?"
I'm afraid it will take me three days
and three nights
to tell you the whole story.
Really?
It's not my fault.
I didn't mean it.
The door was unlocked.
What could I do?
It was just a glimpse.
I didn't get hurt.
Miss Banxia.
Are you done with your bath?
No. You're here.
Miss Banxia, what can I do
for you?
My apologies.
It's not your fault.
If we must blame anyone,
it's probably the loose door lock.
So, you're not going to tell anyone
about this, right?
Of course.
I also care about my reputation.
After all, I'm the one
who suffered, right?
As long as you promise.
You can rest assured of my part.
I just hope
you won't tell anyone either.
Me?
Of course I won't.
That's good.
What are you laughing at?
Who's laughing?
You laughed.
I didn't laugh.
I didn't expect that
while you seem calm
and composed on the outside,
you've got
this overwhelming desire inside.
Are you out of...
Jinrong,
don't you think
my life is bitter?
Bitter.
It's too bitter.
If my mother were still alive,
I would...
Young Lord, I understand.
I totally get it.
I understand you completely.
I understand you so well.
You miss your mother.
I miss my father too.
Actually,
when my father was alive,
our family was also considered
a big family.
My mother would not
have had to sell tofu.
I wouldn't have to stay at home,
looking after my younger sisters.
Don't you think
that my life is even more bitter?
I resented fate.
But since the moment I met you,
I've felt like
the luckiest person.
Young Lord,
thank you.
Jinrong, rest assured.
I will definitely be good to you.
I believe you.
Do you think
we will be together forever?
Of course.
Then let's get married.
Getting married? Well...
Young Lord,
how about we first
make our relationship public?
D-Didn't we agree
not to talk about this?
What's wrong with you, Young Lord?
I'm a girl.
I don't want to push you like this.
But I'm already 29 years
and 18 months old.
I can't wait like this anymore.
Do you understand?
Jinrong,
I have to be honest with you.
You don't look like you're
29 years and 18 months old at all.
Believe me. Here.
I toast you.
I'll drink first.
Jinrong,
this wine is really strong.
Again?
Can't you change your approach?
I don't understand.
Why are you always avoiding this matter?
Can't you man up and face it?
Get up and talk to me.
Let's have another drink.
Fine.
You're pretending with me, huh?
Listen to me closely.
Starting tomorrow,
I will agree with my mother
to go from house to house
for blind dates.
You!
No, I feel even more dizzy
when I get up.
Dizzy?
How about now?
- I feel like vomiting.
- Vomit it out.
Vomit it out.
Vomit.
Dizzy?
I want to vomit.
Mr. Lu,
why are there fleas in this house?
Fleas?
There can't be.
Aren't you itching?
No.
But now that you mention it,
it does seem like a bit.
What will you do if so?
Take a bath. What else could it be?
I've taken a bath.
It doesn't work.
What are you talking about?
T-T-Taking a bath? What bath?
What else could it be?
That's right.
What do you mean?
I'm discussing
the insights of bathing with Mr. Lu.
What insights can you share
when it comes to bathing?
Lu Buping, my mom wants you.
Go ahead.
Where?
Anywhere.
Shen Wangyan,
a man should keep his word.
Don't try to play tricks
behind my back.
That was a misunderstanding.
We made it very clear at the time.
Yeah.
I didn't say anything.
You are overthinking.
You better have said nothing.
Peilan,
I wrote a poem for you.
I will read it to you.
Don't read it, Mr. Lu.
Stop. It's too embarrassing.
What is embarrassing?
What do you mean?
N-Nothing.
- What is embarrassing?
- I'm getting the food.
What did you mean, "embarrassing"?
What are we having for dinner today?
What...
What was that?
What were you guys saying?
What did you mean by "embarrassing"?
Master,
look at my arm.
These look like fresh bites.
Yes, they are.
Do you have bites anywhere else?
Well...
There too.
What were you saying?
It's nothing.
Master, I'm leaving now.
Don't tell anyone else.
Naughty.
What were you saying just now?
It's nothing.
Tell me.
What did you say?
It's a bit vulgar.
Tell me.
Jinrong,
I've thought it through.
I want to make it public now.
Do you think
either one of them doesn't know about
the relationship between us?
Is this making it public?
This reveals my attitude, doesn't it?
I see.
So in your heart,
I can be casually dismissed like this?
Alright, you guys go ahead.
I'm leaving now.
Jinrong,
listen to me.
Whether to make it public or not
really doesn't matter to me.
I want to make it public too.
I'm just afraid
if my father finds out,
he won't agree.
If he doesn't agree,
we won't be able
to see each other again.
You are unwilling to make it public
because of your father?
Well, he... my father...
He... Well...
You should have told me earlier.
I thought it was something else.
Young Lord, you have to trust me.
As long as I meet with him,
I will definitely win him over.
Think about it. I'm proficient in music,
chess, calligraphy, and painting.
What I mean is that
I've always been well-liked
by my elders since young.
Young Lord, don't worry.
As soon as he meets us,
he will definitely agree.
T-This won't work.
Young Lord,
how will you know if you don't try?
Jinrong, you can do it.
Young Lord?
Okay.
Jinrong, from now on,
let's face it together.
Really?
(I've taken a bath.)
(Stop. It's too embarrassing.)
(I'm leaving now. Don't tell anyone else.)
(It's a bit vulgar.)
Enough!
Are you out of your mind?
Yes,
I saw you taking a bath.
But you didn't lock the door.
How is that my fault?
Y-You're not the one at a loss.
Since I was young,
I've never seen a man taking a bath.
And I've never seen a man naked.
I'm the one at a loss, okay?
What are you saying?
She said she saw him naked.
Miss Banxia,
didn't we agree
not to talk about that incident?
Yet you brought it up
at the dinner table.
I thought you could keep it a secret.
I didn't expect you...
Banxia,
why did you watch him bathe?
If I said I was joking,
would you believe me?
No.
Look at you.
You didn't believe me.
Are you happy now?
Now everyone knows.
I don't want to talk to you right now.
Stay away from me.
Actually, I don't really care.
But I suggest you
not to take it to heart.
Stay away from me.
You were who saw it,
and who spoke about it.
Now you're yelling at me?
Aren't you a bit irresponsible?
Plus, we are living
under the same roof now.
We see each other every day.
How about we let bygones be bygones?
Shen Wangyan,
ever since you came to my house,
I've had an uneasy mind.
An uneasy mind has brought me bad luck.
I will kick you out of my house.
Look at that cheap look of yours.
Go away.
What did I say?
(Lord Ling's Mansion)
Jinrong.
Young Lord.
You're finally here. Today, my father
is having a banquet at home.
Are you confident?
Like holding the handle.
What does that mean?
Okay. Let's go.
Come on.
Your Highness, please.
Good.
Let's have a drink together, then.
Jinrong.
With so many people here,
can you handle it?
- Trust me.
- Good. Good.
I'm sure.
You're quite lucky with ladies, huh?
Father.
Why are you here?
I can see...
So rascal.
This is...
This is the eldest daughter
of the Chuns, Chun Jinrong.
She just dropped by.
The Chuns?
The Chuns related to the Fourth Prince.
Greetings, Your Highness.
I'm Chun Jinrong.
No need for formalities.
We should have known each other
a long time ago.
Yes.
I heard about you
from the Young Lord before.
Now that I've seen you,
I've found that
you really have an impressive demeanor.
You're like a star
descended from heaven.
Your Highness, I'll toast you.
Your Highness, I will also toast to you.
No rush.
Today, I am in a good mood.
Let's take turns.
Chun...
Jinrong.
Make yourself at home.
Make sure to keep her company.
Yes.
How is it?
A good start is half the success.
Like holding the handle.
Great.
Your Highness,
thank you for your generous hospitality.
I have no way to repay you.
I'm willing to dedicate a dance
to express my gratitude.
Good.
Let's have another drink.
Leave.
Father?
You're awake.
Has everyone left?
Yes.
Father, have a cup of tea to sober up.
You rascal.
Father,
actually,
I have something to talk to you.
Go ahead.
I kind of
want to get married.
You've thought it through?
Well,
you're not getting any younger.
Let me help you arrange this afterward.
What kind of girl
do you hope I marry?
I don't have high expectations for you.
You should find
a gentle, kind,
and filial girl, and that's good enough.
That's what I've been thinking.
Father, rest assured.
My future wife and I
will both love and respect you.
Actually, I don't have high expectations
for myself either.
Marrying a commoner's daughter
is enough for me.
That's okay.
A daughter
from a mid-ranking official's family
can also match you.
Father,
what if her family has no official rank?
What do you mean?
For example,
a commoner's family.
Who are you talking about?
No one in particular.
Just, for example,
Chun Jinrong, who just danced.
You want to marry a dancing girl?
No, she's not a dancing girl.
She is Chun Keling's elder sister.
Well, Chun Keling
is the Fourth Prince's woman.
She is kind of connected
to the imperial family, right?
The Fourth Prince is different.
He can do whatever he wants.
Who do you think you are?
Are you a match?
No, is she a match?
She is.
Pah!
Tell you what,
if you dare bring this up again with me,
I'll break your leg.
Father!
Father, please listen to me! Father!
Coming.
Miss Banxia, long time no see.
Mr. Xin.
Please.
Mrs. Chun, thank you
for taking care of this matter.
Don't mention it.
Mrs. Chun, please stay.
We'll meet again.
Mr. Xin, take care.
Mother,
what is he here for?
He is here for Mr. Shen.
He said their master
wants to hire Mr. Shen as a tutor
for 20 taels a day.
They want Shen Wangyan?
It seems that Mr. Shen
is really someone.
Puff!
Banxia,
aren't you an educated person?
When did you become so crude?
Mother, let me tell you
what kind of person Shen Wangyan is.
He is just cunning and crafty.
It might be him who invited Mr. Xin.
Chun Banxia,
I noticed that you have been
very critical of Mr. Shen recently.
Well, you saw him...
He hasn't blamed you.
But you are still relentless.
You might let Shen Wangyan go with him
and not stay in our house anymore.
I don't plan to tell him.
You shouldn't, either.
Go.
Go create your own world.
Do you really want me to go?
Mr. Xin said
they would pay you 20 taels a day.
It's 20 taels.
Do you know what that means?
Master couldn't earn that much
in a month.
And Mr. Xin is no ordinary person.
The one he serves must be very powerful.
Don't you need to meet such people?
Aren't you going to file an appeal?
You must have someone support you.
That's right.
Right?
No time to lose.
I'll pack luggage for you.
But
I can't bear to leave you.
Don't push it.
Banxia,
seeing you so reluctant to let me go,
I've decided not to go.
Are you out of your mind?
It's very late now.
Do you plan to stay here for the night?
Leave tomorrow morning.
You've been here since you came back.
You didn't respond when I called you.
What's wrong?
Let me stay alone for a while.
Tell me what's happening.
Mother,
I want to go back to Qing City.
Why?
Mother, can I not get married?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Mother, you're right.
I shouldn't have eyes on my head.
I couldn't see myself clearly.
I'm arrogant and ambitious.
I'm worthless.
I'm old.
What nonsense
are you saying?
What indeed happened to you?
Mother,
His Highness won't let me
be with the Young Lord.
You and the Young Lord?
Sorry, Mother,
I should not have hidden this from you.
We moved to Jianglin
so that you could
marry into good families.
If he's not your Mr. Right,
there are other families.
I used to think
I wanted that kind of life.
But then I realized
the person I've fallen in love with
matters the most.
But we can't be together
just because of
our unequal social status.
You have always been the best.
I even feel the Young Lord
does not deserve you.
Unequal social status
is not your fault,
but theirs.
They missed out
on a good daughter-in-law.
Given your conditions,
you'll definitely
marry into a good family.
Alright, don't cry.
(Jianglin)
(Keep simplicity and nourish the heart)
Mrs. Chun,
farewell.
Didn't you say you weren't leaving?
Your words yesterday
made a lot of sense to me.
I need an appeal to Emperor.
This place is very good.
But I have more important things to do.
You clearly have your eye
on the 20 taels a day.
Chun Banxia,
did you tell Mr. Shen about that?
Mrs. Chun, don't blame Miss Banxia.
She did it for my sake.
After all this time,
I haven't helped you much.
I feel ashamed.
Don't say that.
I'm not stopping you from leaving.
You have your own important matters.
I'm just a little worried about you.
Don't be too aggressive
when you are out there.
Wait a moment.
I'm going to get you some travel money.
- Mother...
- Shut up.
Mrs. Chun, there is no need.
No need for too much.
Shen Wangyan, how can you be so brazen?
You will take the money?
You've seen it.
It's madam
who insisted on giving it to me.
They may not know
what kind of person you are,
but I do.
Miss Banxia,
you know me that well?
Shut up.
Well, I won't tease you anymore.
I owe you an apology.
Miss Banxia,
I've met many educated people,
but not many are as stubborn
as you.
I knew you would say that.
People who pride themselves
on being high lack passion.
Those who are tactical lack backbone.
You are just perfect.
You have principles for the world
and a passion for life.
You are quite adorable.
What tricks are you trying to play now?
What tricks can I play?
It has always been you
taking advantage of me, hasn't it?
Shen Wangyan...
Mr. Shen.
Mr. Shen,
take this money.
Take it.
I hope you get what you want.
Mrs. Chun, I don't need the money.
Just take it.
I really don't need it.
He's right, Mother.
He will get 20 taels a day later.
Mrs. Chun,
I have taken a lot of money
from you before.
I want you
to have this book.
Thank you.
I have been a bother for a long time.
As we part today,
I don't know when we meet again.
Mrs. Chun, take care.
You take care too.
Come and see us when you have time.
The Chuns always welcome you.
Not me.
I welcome you.
Miss Banxia,
take care of yourself too.
I hope to see you again in the future.
Banxia,
what is this about?
(Music Collection)
Vulgar.
You don't need it anyway.
=Hilarious Family=
♪Your smile is like the spring
with newly sprouted leaves♪
♪Passing through the continuous time♪
♪I am still longing♪
♪Gentle and soft yearning♪
♪She emerges from all things♪
♪So peaceful and distant♪
♪The wind gently blows♪
♪Scattered at the end of time♪
♪I hope that every flower here♪
♪Has never been forgotten♪
♪Facing away from
the ancient windmill in the twilight♪
♪I tugged your heartstrings♪
♪You said you would sing in the wind♪
♪The wind gently blows♪
♪Scattered at the end of time♪
♪I hope that every flower here♪
♪Has never been forgotten♪
♪Facing away from
the ancient windmill in the twilight♪
♪I tugged your heartstrings♪
♪You said you would sing in the wind♪