♪Hey, lover♪
♪Don't sneak a peek
at the present moment♪
♪Singing, sha la la la♪
♪With you, fairy tale and carriage♪
♪Oh, my sweet lover. Sweet lover♪
♪It's you who turns the sea breeze warm♪
♪And touches the doves sleeping
in the coconut forest♪
♪You are my sweet lover. Sweet lover♪
♪The bell wakes up my deeply loved one♪
♪Sha la la to forever♪
♪Hey, lover♪
♪Don't sneak a peek
at the present moment♪
♪I want to sing sha la la la♪
♪With you and me to forever♪
=The Furthest Distance=
=Episode 15=
Dr. Qin.
Mr. Yang.
I'm here for a checkup.
You should go to the checkup department.
But I have trouble with my heart.
Aren't you an expert in this field?
I think only you
can cure my heart disease.
Blood pressure is normal,
and so is your heart.
Why do I always
feel shortness of breath?
Anything on your mind?
Just have a good rest.
That makes sense.
I always feel like there's a thorn
stuck in my heart,
making me uncomfortable.
I'll refer you to a psychologist.
But the thorn
might be in my eye.
You should see an eye doctor.
Dr. Qin.
Before I came here,
I looked up some information about you.
I admire you a lot.
You are so affectionate,
single-minded,
and nostalgic.
So I have a question for you.
Mi Su is so important in your heart.
Can you fall in love with Su Ying?
It's none of your business.
If you just see Su Ying as a substitute,
leave her as early as you can.
After all,
you are just a passerby in her life.
Now the passerby is you, not me.
Dr. Qin, don't be childish.
We both know
that your tricks work on young girls.
But they don't work
on women like Su Ying.
You and I are both adults.
Your so-called gentleness is cheap.
It's worthless.
Have you finished?
Do you know the biggest difference
between you and me now?
You're ordered around by others at work.
But I am completely different from you.
Only I tell people what to do.
No one can tell me what I should do.
Good. Let's start the next examination.
Open your mouth.
Stick your tongue out.
Wider.
Your tonsils are inflamed.
Talk less.
Have you decided
on your work for competition?
Not yet.
How about hearing my suggestion?
Go ahead.
The glass house.
I didn't know much
about this competition before.
So, I did some research online.
And I found out that it is remarkable.
I studied its preferences and style.
I think glass house accords with it.
But...
Moreover, it is an art appraisal award.
The glass house is not only your work,
but also your wish.
Didn't you mention your story
with the glass in the interview?
So, from any aspect,
the glass house is the best.
I just think...
Listen to me.
(Conference Room)
I announce
that I've decided
to use the glass house
as the entry for the ADA Competition.
Everyone can start preparing materials.
We must compete at our best.
No worries, Ying.
Right.
Go for it.
- Go for it.
- Come on.
Go for it.
According to the one-month investigation
by engineers and the survey team,
this sea area
has obvious development advantages.
According to the overall assessment,
they're marked in red and green.
Red represents the highest score.
So this area
got high scores.
Yes, the bay, as a natural barrier,
has a large beach area.
It is suitable
to develop the Seaview Garden project.
Well, let's locate
the Seaview Garden here.
But in that case,
the glass house Miss Su designed
has to be demolished.
If you just see Su Ying as a substitute,
leave her as early as you can.
After all,
you are just a passerby in her life.
Now the passerby is you, not me.
Qin Yunsheng made this glass house
for his ex-girlfriend.
It's important for him.
For humans,
the hardest thing is making choices.
I want to see how he chooses
between the present and the past.
I see. I'm on it.
(I'd like to see)
(how deep your love is.)
Hey.
Why are you here?
You don't want to see me?
Yes, I do.
This glass house
is my competition entry.
I need you to sign some paperwork.
You don't have to come for this.
Well, I want to see you.
Okay.
Sign it.
Here.
(Authorization Agreement)
What a good handwriting.
I can stay for 30 minutes.
I'll take a break
and get you some water.
I want to clean the glass house
with you.
♪Hey, lover♪
♪Now is the best time♪
♪With me, sha la la la♪
♪With you, the evening glow is pinkish♪
♪Oh, my sweet lover♪
♪Sweet lover♪
♪It's you who turns the sea breeze warm♪
♪And touches the doves sleeping
in the coconut forest♪
♪You're my sweet lover♪
♪Sweet lover♪
♪The bell wakes up my deeply loved one♪
Okay, it's all cleaned up.
It's so comfortable.
You have three minutes left.
What can we do in three minutes?
♪The starry sky reflects♪
♪The color of your pupils♪
Well,
we can do this.
♪I want to sing sha la la la♪
♪With you and me to forever♪
I've made an appointment with Dr. Qin.
The day after tomorrow
we'll go to glass house
to take photos
and videos for the competition.
The video is quite important.
It can give judges a good impression.
Right, so I asked Huixuan
for help in shooting.
If so, we'll have nothing
to worry about.
That's right.
Ye, send me
the pre-preparation materials.
Ying, it's all here.
It's all printed out.
Take a look.
(Are you working on something?)
The introduction needs to be adjusted.
Why does she not reply to me?
Has she blocked me?
Qin.
Mr. Li.
Oh, my.
Your house becomes so beautiful.
Thank you.
It's really good.
Wait. I'll get you water.
No, I'm fine.
I have something to say to you.
This area is planned
to be developed into the Seaview Garden.
Developers have already come.
I'm looking for property owners
to sign the house relocation agreements.
Relocation?
Take a look.
There is no problem with the money.
(House Relocation Agreement)
This company is well financed.
Homeowners can benefit from his plan.
Mr. Li.
I cannot move.
Don't worry. It's a big company.
The demolition compensation
will satisfy you.
It's not a compensation issue.
Well, tell me
what else do you require?
I'll pass your message on to them.
My requirement is
I won't move.
Qin, people often
regret what they have decided.
Do you know why?
You made your decision too soon.
I have made my point.
No, no rush.
How about this?
I'll give you more time
to think about it.
Don't rush to make a decision.
Think about it. I'm leaving.
Think twice about it.
So beautiful.
(Piyixia)
I have inquired about the development
of the Seaview Garden.
What's going on?
It has been going on.
But they considered
another sea area before.
Suddenly, they switched to this area.
Really?
Besides,
here's one more important thing.
I think it's necessary to tell you.
The developer of the Seaview Garden
is Tiandi Corp.
Tiandi Corp?
Yang Zhengwen's company?
It's him.
He gave you a hard time?
He'll demolish the glass house.
I knew it.
It's obviously intentional.
It's an extensive relocation.
Who knows what will happen?
An extensive demolition?
How much will they give?
Is this a matter of money?
No.
This is also a work by Su Ying.
She will use the glass house
as her competition entry.
So I can't let them
tear down the glass house.
Does Su Ying know about this?
She does not know yet.
She is already busy preparing
for the competition.
I can't distract her.
Anyway,
I can handle it myself.
Good guy.
Anyway, no matter what happens,
we got your back.
Right.
Mr. Yang, except for Qin Yunsheng,
other property owners have agreed.
Just as I thought.
No problem. We can wait
until he acts.
Mr. Yang, Qin Yunsheng is here
to see you.
He is on the move.
Let him in.
Yes, Mr. Yang.
Please.
Dr. Qin, what brought you here?
Let's sit and talk.
Save your false courtesies.
Are you in charge
of the demolition project?
Yes, is there any problem?
I'll not let you tear down
the glass house.
I'm sorry, but no offense.
Usually, when we
go through a demolition,
the property owners
who want more compensation
will say the same thing as you.
Do you think
I'm here to negotiate with you?
No, I mean, that is your right.
You should negotiate.
That's alright. Just name your price.
Is it a matter of money?
Dr. Qin, I understand
that you don't want to seem material.
But unfortunately,
we're living in the material world.
Everything has its value, and it should.
So does the priceless stuff
under specific conditions.
So, it's okay. Don't be shy.
Make an offer.
I will not demolish the glass house.
Dr. Qin.
I'm kindly reminding you
that the Seaview Garden project will
take at least two years.
In this process, your house will be
on a construction site.
Water pollution, air pollution,
noise pollution, and light pollution.
Are you sure you can handle it?
I have already told you
what I wanted to say.
Mr. Yang, why bother talking so much
with him?
The land of the glass house is not his.
He only has a right to use.
Just for fun.
It's okay, no need to mind him.
Let's talk to the rental party.
Okay.
What if I shoot the video
with the Inception's style?
The cool shots will be eye-catching.
Inception?
Or,
like the Matrix's style,
full of Sci-fi feeling.
Or maybe the Butterfly Effect.
Looks mysterious.
Xuan, I think
it's too rational, rigid, and cold.
No emotions.
Too rational?
Because the glass house
seems aesthetic and artistic,
full of life.
Make a people-oriented video,
starting with emotions.
When you're in the house,
you feel like you're dreaming,
but it's real.
You understand?
Well, the feeling of love.
Just like you get a feeling of love
upon seeing the glass house.
The feeling of love?
Have you ever heard
that love is the best source
of inspiration?
What is the feeling of love?
You haven't been in love for too long.
That's all.
I'm going to have dinner with Dr. Qin.
Remember, the feeling of love.
You are leaving now?
Relax a bit.
The feeling of love?
What's wrong, Huixuan? Feeling down?
I'm thinking over the plan
for the glass house.
I believe you can do it.
By the way, have you not been
checking your phone much recently?
Yes. You were looking for me?
No, just asking.
Stop thinking about it. I will take you
to eat something delicious.
I'm not going.
I should go back
and think about this shooting.
The feeling of love.
I'm leaving.
The feeling of love?
Recently, everyone has been busy
with the competition.
Even Huixuan came to help.
You must feel happy, right?
You also come to pick me up from work.
How was your day?
It was quite good.
We're going to the glass house
for shooting the day after tomorrow.
Are you okay with that?
Yes, I'm totally okay.
My video is too rational?
It's not aesthetic or artistic?
(Your new video broke the record
for likes. Congratulations.)
(I found a really good source material.)
(I want to send it to you.)
(Are you busy now?)
(Sorry, I've been busy
working on a case recently.)
(I'm fretting over finding inspiration.)
You finally replied to me.
(Scrat)
Alright. You have been working hard.
(Fight Hard to Win)
(Do you think my video is too rational?)
(Scrat)
It's a bit.
But that's not a disadvantage.
I think making the video
you like is the most important.
(Fight Hard to Win)
(Thanks.)
(Scrat)
Trust me. You'll get better.
And remember I'm your loyal fan
when you succeed.
(Fight Hard to Win)
(Gotta go.)
(Scrat)
Alright, but don't overwork.
A great author once said
there are three secrets
for staying happy,
namely, food, sleep...
I have food.
And love.
I have enough sleep.
So all I need is sweet love now.
(Scrat)
I also feel the same way.
I hope
we can have sweet love.
(Fight Hard to Win)
Let's go for it.
Go for it.
Let's go for it?
What did she mean?
What?
A blind date?
Didn't you tell me yesterday
that love is a source of inspiration?
I have thought about it carefully.
I should start trying
to have a relationship.
Why blind date?
I searched it online.
A blind date is efficient.
What have you done?
I have found some men on the internet.
You can also introduce some to me.
Look, I made a form.
I wrote all my requirements on it.
Du Huixuan, you're not preparing
for a show recording.
Love is about feeling, not efficiency.
It has to be efficient.
If I decide to love,
I have to consider it for the long term.
I refuse ineffective love,
so I need a blind date.
Blind date?
Huixuan.
Go on a blind date?
Why?
Do you have any requirements
for your date?
He shall be 1.8 meters tall,
kind-hearted, with stable job.
That's okay.
Common interests and hobbies,
such as collecting action figures,
loving home design,
loving watching football.
She prefers a fan of Manchester United.
That's good.
This is very important.
(Reject younger men.)
Reject younger men.
Why?
Because younger men are not okay.
My requirements are realistic.
Otherwise, how could I
have chosen a few candidates
among so many people?
A few candidates?
I'll meet them this afternoon.
Don't. You meet them today?
I've chosen the location.
I'll meet them at a coffee shop.
I can meet them all at once.
Is there a time limit
for your blind date?
It's a consequence of my work.
Listen, Huixuan.
You don't even know these men.
I can go with you.
I can also protect you
and be your bodyguard.
Yes, that's a good idea.
He can help you discern other men
from a man's perspective.
Right, that's true.
You don't have to.
I've interacted
with so many people at work.
I can deal with it.
I'm leaving. See you tomorrow.
Give it to me.
Thank you.
Ying, I...
I get it.
Go ahead.
Thank you, Ying.
Miss Du, I heard that you resigned.
Being a general director is not easy.
Quitting is an impulsive decision.
I was not on good terms
with the producer.
Given your appearance,
you look emotional at work.
You have to ask yourself
why the producer couldn't get along
with you.
He has a fan? How old is he?
So, you're saying it's my fault?
Yes, it's no big deal
to change your temper.
As you know, in this society,
it's hard to survive without a job.
Fortunately, you met me today.
I'll read your fortune for you.
Let's see how your luck is today.
Fortune telling?
You'll meet a kind person today.
Here is my business card.
Come to me
for a luck prediction next time.
I'll give you a 20% discount.
It's good to resign.
You can be a housewife.
In fact...
Wait, let me finish.
Women shouldn't go to work.
It's great to be a full-time homemaker.
Actually, I...
Hold on, I have to take this call.
(Interpreter of All)
So arrogant.
Fine, I get it now.
Sorry, I'm a bit busy.
Here is my business card.
I am very interested in you. Call me.
He's not good for you.
You'll look for a job, right?
Yeah.
Good.
After all, we both can't live
without jobs.
You're unemployed?
My job involves fitness, exercise and...
Do you like it?
I like a girl
who loves sports.
He's not good,
not a match.
Hello, are you Miss Huixuan?
Give me your business card.
Nice to meet you.
Please have a seat.
Thank you.
You're too kind,
even bringing me flowers.
No, I just saw an elderly man
and a child selling flowers
by the roadside.
It instantly sparked my sympathy.
So, I spontaneously decided
to buy a bouquet for you.
So considerate.
Do you like it?
Yes, beautiful.
Miss Huixuan, according to your profile,
I know you love to play football.
I don't like to play it.
I enjoy watching football.
I also like it.
Really?
Which team do you like?
Manchester United.
So do I.
No way.
What a fateful coincidence.
Messi is a good player.
His skill of dribbling...
Messi is
in Paris Saint-Germain.
Sir, please sit properly.
It's a bit dangerous.
Well,
let's go watch a football match
together next week.
Great.
Ye, do you know where Mingshi has gone?
He doesn't reply to my messages.
Yes, I have a document he needs to sign.
He might have gone to the organizer.
I don't know either.
Good afternoon.
Dr. Qin.
It's all yours.
Dr. Qin brought something delicious.
Cookies.
Thank you, Dr. Qin.
You always get us something.
This is your hot chocolate.
I'll get fat.
Dr. Qin is so considerate.
He knew Ying couldn't drink coffee
and specially brought her hot chocolate.
Exactly, Ying, we also want
to drink hot chocolate.
He'll buy some for you next time.
- Thank you, brother-in-law.
You're welcome.
Brother-in-law.
This is for Mingshi and Huixuan.
- Huixuan is not here.
- Didn't she come to help?
She went on a blind date.
Really?
Let's go. I'll get my bag.
Okay.
It's yours now.
Thank you, Dr. Qin. Thanks.
It's so sweet, Dr. Qin.
Today's date is perfect.
She's rich and has no dating experience.
You will know how I use tricks
to win her over in three days.
Sorry for the wait.
No.
Where were we in our conversation?
Football.
Right.
There's a quote that I really like.
Plato once said
humans were originally born
with four hands and four feet.
But after we were born,
we were split in half
and became the way we are now,
with two hands and two feet.
So, we spend our entire life
trying to find the other half.
I see.
Miss Huixuan, can you give me your hand?
I want to check your palm lines
to see if you're the other half
I'm searching for.
Sure.
Take your hand off her.
Don't touch her, you bad guy.
Why are you here?
I'm here to protect you.
I'm afraid you'll meet bad men.
He's one of them.
He's not.
Mind your language.
Seriously?
Let's hear what you said.
(You will know)
(how I use tricks
to win her over in three days.)
You...
What about me?
Miss Huixuan, it's a misunderstanding.
Really? You're a bad man.
Let's go, Huixuan.
Wait, my purse.
What's all the fuss?
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Without you, I would have been conned.
The blind date is so unreliable.
Their resumes are decent.
But none of them is suitable.
Actually, there are many ways
to be in love.
Sometimes online dating is reliable.
At least, I don't need
to drink coffee online.
I've drunk too much coffee
this afternoon.
Well...
How unreliable these blind dates are.
For the ones online, you can chat first
and then meet them.
Forget it. It's bad luck.
I'll help Ying with her things first.
Let's go.
How did your blind date go?
I don't want to talk about it.
You failed
to find the right one for you?
I originally wanted
to find a sweetheart.
But I haven't even met a decent man.
Luckily, Mingshi appeared in time.
Otherwise, I'd be cheated.
Mingshi?
Then you should really thank him.
Or he could be your boyfriend.
Be serious, please.
I've been in bad luck.
So I failed.
I could set you up with someone.
Okay.
But I'll think about it later.
By then, my bad luck could disappear.
Okay.
I underestimated Mingshi.
Mingshi is reliable. He's a good guy.
They would be a perfect match
if they got together.
I know.
Wait.
How did you know
I would set her up with Mingshi?
Did I tell you that he likes Du Huixuan?
No, you didn't.
Then how did you know?
You can't hide when you're in love.
Even if you cover your mouth,
it will show through your eyes.
So,
only Du Huixuan is unaware now.
What a fool.
Welcome!
Feel free to look around.
Okay, thank you.
What is this?
This is eryngo.
It symbolizes strength.
Cute.
Look over here.
Sunflowers represent the pursuit
of happiness.
It looks as radiant as me.
Your smile looks more brilliant.
You're a smooth talker.
Just like you.
Will you buy sunflowers?
Sure.
Is this pretty?
Pretty.
Are you taking a photo of me?
Let me see if you made me look ugly.
(Mr. Li)
There's a phone call.
Let me take it.
Hello, Mr. Li?
Qin.
Since you only have a land use right,
the lessor
explicitly requested
an early repossession.
An early repossession?
Yes.
I just received the notice.
Moreover, the lessor is adamant
about it.
He needs you to move out immediately.
Mr. Li, I'm busy.
I'll come find you later.
I haven't finished speaking.
I want daisies, violets,
and the eryngo over there.
That's all, thank you.
Okay.
You can pay by scanning the QR code.
What happened?
My phone ran out of battery
after the call.
Let me pay.
It's done.
Okay, we'll contact you.
Good, thanks a lot.
Goodbye.
Let's go.
Mr. Li.
What happened?
Finally, you're here.
Come on. Don't get angry.
Take a seat and let me explain.
Listen to me.
About this matter,
it's not my fault.
Among all the owners in the community,
you're the only one
who rejects the demolition.
So, many owners come here
to make a fuss.
They're afraid the project will fail
and they won't get compensated.
They can't damage my house.
Yes, there are so many owners.
You never know who might be ill-mannered
and capable of anything.
Let's not talk about the paint now.
There's another urgent matter.
The lessor contacted me.
He's going
to reclaim the land use right.
He won't rent it to you anymore.
My contract hasn't expired yet.
They said they could compensate you
for the breach of contract.
All the owners here have agreed
and signed,
except for you.
Qin, to be honest,
if you don't give up,
it will baffle me.
Well, I'm pleading with you.
Please do me a favor.
Do me a favor.
Mr. Li.
Can I ask for your help?
Okay, go ahead.
For one month.
Please protect the glass house for me.
I will move out after a month.
Alright.
I will pass your message
on to the leaders.
But it's hard to say if they agree.
So, please, Qin.
Think well about it, okay?
Mr. Yang, Qin Yunsheng said
he wanted us to give him one month.
Is he tempted
by the conditions you proposed?
I don't think so.
He just wants to buy more time.
Let's proceed.
Got it.
Go to the glass house.
Dr. Qin. You are busy.
Are you here to help
or to check the damage?
Come on.
This house is Su Ying's work.
Your trick won't work for me.
What brought you here?
Actually, I came here a few days ago.
When I saw this house,
I started
to understand your persistence.
We both have someone in our hearts
who can't be forgotten.
♪You make the changing seasons♪
♪Meaningful♪
♪You make me long for♪
♪Meeting you again♪
♪I want to get close to you♪
♪If we care each other
like the wind to the leaves♪
♪Passing by and letting go♪
♪Leaving behind empty expectations♪
♪Unsurprisingly♪
♪It's courage replaced by helplessness♪
♪A short departure.
I wait for a long time♪
♪If we are free
like the wind pushing the clouds♪
♪Coming and going quickly♪
♪Yet spreading loneliness♪
♪Thousands and thousands of times♪
♪I plunged into the crowd to find you♪
♪Look at me. Trust me. Wait for me♪
♪It's me, silently confessing♪
♪It's me, waiting for the wind
to come and say♪
♪That you come close and retreat
over and over again♪
♪But my heart pumps involuntarily♪
♪I rely on it or forget it♪
♪You come and stir up my mind♪
♪By your side♪
=The Furthest Distance=