♪Hey, lover♪
♪Don't sneak a peek
at the present moment♪
♪Singing, sha la la la♪
♪With you, fairy tale and carriage♪
♪Oh, my sweet lover. Sweet lover♪
♪It's you who turns the sea breeze warm♪
♪And touches the doves sleeping
in the coconut forest♪
♪You are my sweet lover. Sweet lover♪
♪The bell wakes up my deeply loved one♪
♪Sha la la to forever♪
♪Hey, lover♪
♪Don't sneak a peek
at the present moment♪
♪I want to sing sha la la la♪
♪With you and me to forever♪
=The Furthest Distance=
=Episode 14=
(Good Match)
It's not that sunny here.
So beautiful here.
It's so comfortable.
Now, we are
at the lover's pavilion
which the island is famous for.
Legend has it that lovers
who hang a pair of bells here
can lock their love forever
and never be separated.
Let's hang a pair.
You want to do it?
I want to do it with you.
(Qin Yunsheng, Su Ying)
We are tied together.
Are you thirsty? I'll go buy some water.
(Qin Yunsheng, Su Ying)
This island is really nice.
You really know how to choose.
I could stay here for a month.
There are many other beautiful sights
on this island.
Where do you want to go next?
I don't know. It's good to go with you.
Then,
go to your inner world.
You're already there.
You're so amazing.
Who's calling me? Huixuan?
Hello.
Miss Su, hello.
The hotel has a new available room.
Do you need this room?
It is available.
What?
The room.
Hello, I need it.
I'll keep it for ten minutes.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Let's go.
Hello, I am Miss Su.
Is there a vacancy?
Hello, here is your room key.
Thank you.
(Evacuation Plan)
This place is huge.
Yes.
And there's a bed curtain. Look.
The balcony is so big.
The view is so amazing.
The view
is indeed very captivating.
What sound?
It might be the sound of my heartbeat.
Sorry.
Our manager will be here soon.
Sorry to have troubled you.
Huixuan, there is a restroom here.
- Ying?
Ying?
Dr. Qin?
Are you two coming back or going out?
- Coming back.
- Going out.
What?
- Coming back.
- Going out.
Going out or coming back?
Miss Su, I'm sorry.
I didn't expect you two
to need the room in such a hurry.
It's fine.
Of course it matters.
It was a serious fault on our part.
We gave the room card to you
before it was even cleaned.
It affected your stay.
How about this? I'll give you
a 30% discount on the room rate.
Thank you.
Okay. Our room is now clean.
I wish you a pleasant stay.
Were our rooms cleaned?
We'll have a dinner
together tonight, right?
We're going there now.
Chen, help me prepare something.
Isn't Ying's room card with us?
Ye, let's go and buy some drinks.
We're going to buy some drinks. Go.
Isn't the room card with us?
Let me squeeze in.
It looks good.
- Send it to me.
- I will send it to you.
How was it? Did any of you
have any romantic encounters today?
There were quite a few handsome guys.
But no romantic encounters.
You were luckier than I was.
Today I met a creepy old man.
Really?
Luckily, Chen was there
to drive him away.
if it had been a handsome guy,
would you have driven Chen away?
It was not impossible.
Try it. The mangoes here
are exceptionally tasty.
This mango is so big.
Thanks.
Right.
I've been craving this for a while.
Let me feed you first.
I'll feed you.
So sweet.
- It's especially for Dr. Qin.
- Try it. Is it yummy?
It's so delicious.
I can't watch them. So sweet.
I'm envious of you.
Don't be envious of me.
You used to be busy.
Now you've resigned.
You can think about
starting dating.
I haven't found the right one yet.
From my perspective,
finding a date is harder
than picking a topic.
What's so hard about that?
If you look hard enough,
you're sure to find one.
Maybe he's right in front of you.
What are you talking about?
- Huixuan.
- The barbecue is here.
It's just cooked. Try one.
The barbecue is right in front of us.
I think
we should all toast Ying
for organizing this island trip for us.
Right.
- Come on.
- Drinks.
Here you are.
I'll also make a toast.
I have a lot of fun with you guys.
This drink represents
the renewal of Huixuan.
Let's drink it and forget
our worries, okay?
No more worries.
Alright.
- Drink up.
- No worries.
- Cheers!
No more worries.
Do we need some music?
Yes.
Right.
Not exciting enough.
I'll go play some.
- Yunsheng is well-prepared.
- He is multi-talented.
I found this.
You can play guitar?
A little.
Okay.
♪You're my sweet lover♪
♪Sweet lover♪
♪The bell wakes up my deeply loved one♪
♪Sha la la la, it's forever♪
♪Hey, lover♪
♪Don't sneak a peek
at the present moment♪
♪I want to sing sha la la la♪
♪With you and me to forever♪
Get him.
Do you want to see a magic trick?
No.
Say you want to see it.
Three.
Two.
Ye, I really want to.
I knew you'd want to see it.
Open it.
There's nothing, right?
The time to witness magic.
Blow.
Open it.
Isn't it magical?
Ye, you're really amazing.
How did you do that?
You're being so fake.
Are you an actor?
I'll give you this keychain.
Thank you for today.
I was just doing what was right.
It is a small matter.
No need to thank me.
But it'd have been better
if he had been a handsome guy.
If he is a handsome guy,
you must not come over.
Imagine.
A beach,
a handsome guy
and eight-pack abs.
Enough.
If that's the case,
let me do a trick for you.
You can do it too?
Let me start it.
Come on.
Watch closely.
There's nothing, right?
Nothing.
And nothing on the back, right?
Get ready, and watch carefully.
Okay.
What?
There's still nothing.
You dare trick me?
Chen, you dare trick me.
Thanks.
Huixuan, are you happy today?
Yes.
That's good.
What's wrong?
May I ask you
if you regret resigning?
I wouldn't say I regret it.
Just a bit of a pity.
I've been
with the House Design for six years.
Not being able to continue with it,
and instead saying goodbye in this way.
I think you have nothing to regret.
You've made House Design
popular these past six years.
But at the same time,
it made you successful.
I remember you once told me that.
Persistence itself is meaningless,
but during the process of it,
it is meaningful
to improve yourself and create value.
After so many years of practices,
you now understand planning
and can do promotion and editing.
Aren't you a one-person team?
Well then, use the encouragement
I gave you back then to encourage me.
But after hearing your words,
I do feel a lot more relieved.
If you ever feel
life is not going as planned,
it's actually you are granted
a long vacation.
At this time, you should enjoy
the holiday and get plenty of rest.
When the holiday is over,
greet the new beginning.
I want to start over,
but I don't know what to do next.
I haven't thought it out yet.
Just do what you love to do.
Like,
experiencing a sweet love.
Why does everyone tell me to be in love?
Worrying I can't get married?
How can it be? You are so excellent.
Cheers.
To my beauty?
Yes.
No matter what decision you make,
I will support you.
I will stand by your side.
Mr. Yang, here's all the information
about Dr. Qin
that you wanted me to find.
(Personal Information)
He had a beloved ex-girlfriend, Mi Su.
To fulfill her wish,
he asked Miss Su
to design the glass house.
This video was cut
into the show at the time
and got a high click rate.
It's been so long
since I watched the stars relaxedly.
It feels like the stars
are so far away from us.
Someone once said
the atoms formed during the Big Bang
were the same as the ones in our bodies,
so they are not far away.
Because we are stars ourselves.
We are stars ourselves?
Quite romantic.
Yes, it is.
I wish we'd be like this forever.
Me too.
Do you know
the thing I've enjoyed the most
since my childhood is watching stars?
I want to travel to every corner
of the world to see the stars.
Why?
Because I believe
each star has its own story.
I feel they are talking to me.
Well.
Pick one
among these many stars
to represent our story.
The brightest one.
That one?
Name it.
Me?
Naming it.
How about Peanut Brittle?
Sweet.
Alright, Peanut Brittle.
I know you're not usually romantic,
but you're always surprising me
and being romantic.
I just hope
you are happy
every day.
Thank you for liking me.
I am very happy right now.
Besides watching stars,
what do you want to do?
I want to do this.
♪You make the changing seasons♪
♪Meaningful♪
♪You make me long for♪
♪Meeting you again♪
(Fight Hard to Win)
(A new update, waiting for your advice.)
(Scrat)
(Sure.)
You can't skip breakfast to lose weight.
Bread with an egg
is already a scientific breakfast
for losing weight. Eat it.
I'll eat then.
Huixuan,
the sandwich here seems pretty tasty.
Take a bite.
Really? Is it better than yours?
I guess it's not.
Check your phone.
Ying opened up about their relationship.
What?
This is too sweet.
Give it a like!
I've already liked it.
What should we comment?
May you be together forever.
I want sweet love too.
(Su Ying, love is a happy thing.)
May you be together forever.
That's so corny.
Director, what are you happy about?
What are you two happy about?
What are you happy about?
- Perfect match.
(Su Ying, love is a happy thing.)
Don't you know breaking up
is not something to joke about?
I am not joking.
Our relationship
is getting more and more tiring somehow.
It's filled with quarrels
and explanations.
Since you started working,
we have almost never had
a good time together.
You make progress and I support you.
You say this is
for a better life for me.
I am moved.
But I always come after your job.
You have never put me first.
Never.
At first, I would argue with you,
but gradually,
I am used to it.
Used to being ignored by you.
You often say
I am your haven.
What about me?
Where is my haven?
Look, we brought back delicious food
for you from the island.
Thank you.
Try this one.
This one is particularly good.
My favorite.
Thank you.
I have a gift for you too.
You couldn't go with us,
but I brought back
the sound of the sea for you.
Listen to it.
There really is a sound.
By the way, there is also the jet ski.
You must play with us next time you go.
It's okay.
She couldn't make it this time,
but she can join us next time.
Because Ying often organizes
such activities for us, right?
Here's my gift for you, Tian Mei.
It's a lucky rope.
I hope you are always lucky
and things go smoothly for you.
Thank you.
I want it too.
Can I forget the two of you?
Here, Chen.
Thank you, Mingshi.
I knew you wouldn't.
I wish you all the best.
I've been receiving gifts
from you since the day I joined.
I'm hesitant to take more.
No problem, because we are family.
Right.
Yesterday, Ying's package arrived.
(To Su Ying, from ADA Committee)
Sent by the ADA Committee.
ADA? Isn't that the most famous award
in the industry?
- Yes.
I know it's very difficult to win.
Is this an invitation for Ying?
Is she going to participate in it?
It must be.
- That's amazing.
- Amazing.
I'll notify her right away.
I'll call her.
What are you talking about?
- Ying.
This is an invitation
from the ADA Committee for you.
I already know.
So you will really participate?
They sent me an email
about it last week.
But weren't we working
on a case at that time?
You've succeeded
in both career and love.
Right. How could you be so calm
about such a big thing?
Yeah.
This is just an invitation,
not an award announcement.
Even if it's just an invitation,
it's still a great recognition.
Yes, if I remember correctly,
it's probably the only major award
you haven't won.
Don't worry. This time
Ying will certainly win it.
- Of course.
- Yes, she will.
This invitation is not only
a recognition of me as an individual,
but also of our entire firm.
You're right.
So let's hold a meeting
to discuss it right away.
- Hurry up.
- Let's go.
By the way,
I have something to tell you.
Come in.
What's it?
Mr. Yang of Tiandi Corp once came by.
Yang Zhengwen?
It seemed he would like
to work with you on a case.
The firm has a very full workload now,
so we're not considering it for now.
But after all, he is...
I know what you will say.
No matter how big or good the case is,
I won't take it.
Let's discuss
which work to use for the competition.
Express some opinions.
Ying has too many successful works,
so it's hard to choose.
Right.
Ying, I think
the KNK building is very famous.
We can consider it.
And the courtyard converted
from an ancient building is so popular.
It's full of tourists.
I think the glass house
is quite suitable.
Think about it. The ADA competition
focuses on humanistic care.
Many previous entries exhibited
small yet beautiful buildings.
The KNK building
and the courtyard are famous now,
but they look so commercialized.
The glass house is not a large building,
but the story behind it
is very touching.
I think it is more in line
with the spirit of ADA.
What do you think?
(Garden Road No. 123)
You came just when I needed you.
Mingshi told me right away.
You have so many works.
Have you decided which one to choose?
Not yet.
Let me tell you. I think the glass house
is the most suitable.
The glass house.
I think it is very in line
with the theme of this competition.
Are you considering Dr. Qin?
I just feel
it's not good.
After all, it was a gift for Mi Su.
But it is also your work.
Yes,
but...
Does Dr. Qin know
you are going to compete?
Not yet, I didn't have time to tell him.
Huixuan, are these
the mangoes you ordered?
Right.
These big mangoes are great.
Go and share them with everyone.
Okay, I'll go cut them.
Okay.
Aren't they the mangoes from the island?
I found a supplier here.
Really?
Very convenient.
Send me the seller.
Okay.
It's very convenient.
They provide delivery upon ordering.
Great!
Dr. Qin loves these mangos.
Dr. Qin again.
The mango is ready.
- So soon.
- Thank you.
I'll leave you guys.
Here you are.
So sweet.
This mango tastes so good.
(Fight Hard to Win)
(I've posted an update.)
(Is it professional enough?)
(Scrat)
(The editing is good,)
(and it's very professional.)
(Fight Hard to Win)
(Thank you.)
(Scrat)
(You work hard as your name suggests.)
(Why did you choose this name?)
(Fight Hard to Win)
(My name has "Hui".)
(My bestie's name has "Ying".)
(I chose them as a pun.)
Hui.
Ying.
Fight Hard to Win.
[*Ai Pin Cai Hui Ying]
(Fight Hard to Win)
(I'll recommend super sweet mangoes.)
Who are you chatting with?
You look so happy.
Let me tell you.
I recently met
a very interesting person.
Who?
I have created a video account online.
I regularly update it with videos
on home decor.
This person often leaves
comments for me. Look.
Scrat.
And he is very interesting.
He always disagrees with me,
but he also often provides
constructive ideas.
Most importantly,
his name is Scrat.
Do you know? It's a little animal
I like from a cartoon.
What a coincidence!
You were just chatting with him?
Du Huixuan,
you seem to be heading
towards an Internet romance.
How is that possible? I don't even know
if the one is a man or woman.
I just find our conversations enjoyable.
You've chatted for so long.
Of course, it's a man.
Which woman would chat
with you for so long besides me?
You're right.
Then,
what do you think?
I...
What are you hesitating about?
You rarely meet someone
who is so in tune with you.
Seize the opportunity, and go for it.
Let me tell you,
love is a game for the brave.
You have to be bold and step forward.
For a girl with little experience
in relationships like you,
you have to be a bit bolder and braver.
You have to have that kind
of passion of young people, right?
Just give it a try. Wait.
Then I will...
In that case...
What's wrong?
I mean, in that case,
you will miss out on many better men.
Yes, missing out on many better men.
So you can't try carelessly.
Why are you acting weird today?
It's not me acting weird.
I just forgot it.
Some time ago,
I saw a lot of news
about Internet fraud.
Let me tell you, it's really scary.
They target not only your money
but also you. It's terrifying.
Let me tell you.
It might be a wolf in sheep's clothing.
Is it that terrible?
It may be even worse.
It's very likely
that it is someone around you.
Let me tell you.
You are in the light,
while he's in the dark.
It's very easy for him to deceive you.
So it's really unreliable.
You must be careful.
It reminds me of someone.
Is it probably Mr. Liu?
It's very likely.
It might just be him, right?
You must guard
against such villains, okay?
That's right.
Right?
Believe me. I won't lie to you, right?
So the guys you meet in real life
are more reliable. Do you know?
Don't chat with him anymore.
I must be careful in the future.
What are you doing?
I've sat for too long,
so I need to do some stretches.
Young people are full of energy.
I'll leave you guys.
What's going on with your studio today?
Why do you all seem so weird?
Really?
It might be the mango.
Eat it. You just ate a little.
Look, you left so much. Eat.
(Meichi International Hospital)
Why are there mangoes
in the hospital?
(Premium Mangoes)
Premium mangoes.
We can't underestimate them.
Why is everyone afraid of the mangoes?
You don't understand.
All doctors know this.
"Mango" indicates being busy.
Wherever a mango appears,
it gets incredibly busy.
Isn't this just a pun?
You can see it that way.
Yisen, I beg you.
Handle them now.
No, I can't.
These were sent by Su Ying to Yunsheng.
We can't just get rid of them.
It's not busy now.
[*A pun.]
Is that okay?
Can it work?
Why did them get sent here?
Sorry, wrong delivery spot.
Take it with you. Do your work.
It's a call from the ED. I gotta go.
Hey.
A new patient.
(Su Ying)
Hello.
Have you got off work?
Soon.
Did you get the mangoes?
Yes.
Everyone enjoyed them very much.
That's good.
Sorry, Dr. Qin.
It's okay.
Look at this happy man.
There's only one expression left
after returning from island.
It's a silly smile.
Really?
Look at yourself now.
You had a really good time
on the island this time.
I'd be happier without your surprise.
So something really happened.
Share it with me now.
If I do it,
won't you post it on your Moments?
Can I? Am I that kind of person?
I'll take that as a yes.
Here's a call.
Who is it?
Hello.
Hello, Dr. Qin.
How is everything going?
It's going smoothly.
I've already started my shift.
So dedicated.
Aren't you the same?
Let's have hotpot tonight.
Okay, I'll reserve a table.
No need. Come eat at my place.
Okay, see you tonight then.
See you tonight then.
Eat yours.
You've arrived.
So many ingredients.
I'm preparing food.
Let me help you.
Okay, go wash your hands.
I'll get an apron for you.
Okay.
Dr. Qin.
It's a habit.
Thanks.
Let's start the surgery.
Okay.
The fish is cooked.
Let's take a look.
- So awesome.
- Is it good?
Do you know how to debone the fish?
I'm going to show it to you.
Look. First of all,
remove the head
and the tail.
Then,
let it relax.
Relax?
Yes, let the fish relax.
Even fish needs massages?
Of course.
Okay, take its bones out.
How is it? Cool, right?
Have a look.
Okay.
How did you do that?
I have many strengths.
It's unraveling.
I'll help you with that.
Dr. Qin,
I have some good news to share with you.
Okay.
I got an invitation
from the ADA Competition.
You look this happy.
Is it a prestigious award?
It's very prestigious.
Which of your works was chosen?
None yet.
They have only invited me so far,
but as for which work
to use as an entry,
I have to select one myself
and then report it.
Have you decided yet?
Not yet. I had a meeting
to discuss it with them today.
What did they say?
Look, there's the KNK building
that you know.
But it may be too commercialized.
It doesn't quite fit the theme
which is humanistic care, so...
And the Cloud Corridor.
But it emphasizes returning to nature.
It's not suitable, either.
And then, the Starlight Music Hall.
But it's highly-designed.
I feel it lacks something.
And...
Is the glass house okay?
Yes.
How about choosing it?
It's done. Have a look.
Let me look.
How come you are so good at sewing?
Because it is a basic skill of doctors.
You know how to do everything.
Are you hungry?
Shall we eat then?
Okay, let's go.
I'll serve you some food.
(City Planning and Design, with Focus
on Simplicity and Nature)
(Past Award Works Exhibition)
Hello, Miss Du.
I'd like to consult
with you about something.
(New Friend, Tian Mei)
(Friend Verification Passed)
(Hello, Mr. Yang.
I'm Tian Mei from the SU Design Firm.)
(I told Ying about your last visit.)
(She mentioned our firm
had too many cases at the moment,)
(so we will not consider collaborations)
(regarding cases for now.)
(If there's anything that you need me
to communicate with Ying)
(or if you need my help,)
(please tell me.)
(Thank you.)
(Yang Zhengwen, General Manager)
(Personal Information)
(He had a beloved ex-girlfriend, Mi Su.)
(To fulfill her wish,)
(he asked Miss Su to design
the glass house six years ago.)
Kevin, help me make an appointment
at Meichi Hospital for tomorrow.
(Meichi International Hospital)
I got it wrong last time.
The mangoes were for me.
These are the gifts
Su Ying wanted to give you.
- Thanks.
Thank you, Dr. Qin.
Dr. Qin, are they candies for good news?
Then you have to give a gift.
If you get married now, I'll give you
a big red envelope right away.
Dr. Qin.
Mr. Yang.
I'm here for a checkup.
You should go to the checkup department.
But I have trouble with my heart.
Aren't you an expert in this field?
I think only you
can cure my heart disease.
♪You make the changing seasons♪
♪Meaningful♪
♪You make me long for♪
♪Meeting you again♪
♪I want to get close to you♪
♪Even if you are far from me♪
♪If we care each other
like the wind to the leaves♪
♪Passing by and letting go♪
♪Leaving behind empty expectations♪
♪Unsurprisingly♪
♪It's courage replaced by helplessness♪
♪A short departure.
I wait for a long time♪
♪If we are free
like the wind pushing the clouds♪
♪Coming and going quickly♪
♪Yet spreading loneliness♪
♪Thousands and thousands of times♪
♪I plunged into the crowd to find you♪
♪Look at me. Trust me. Wait for me♪
♪It's me, silently confessing♪
♪It's me, waiting for the wind
to come and say♪
♪That you come close and retreat
over and over again♪
♪But my heart pumps involuntarily♪
♪I rely on it or forget it♪
♪You come and stir up my mind♪
♪By your side♪
=The Furthest Distance=