Your Majesty
You can't go
Get out of the way
Your Majesty
You went even though you knew there was an ambush
You are always wise
Do you think I went to find Shen Qianye
just for the sake of love
Your Majesty
You have other plans
Shen Qianye is Xihe
The only person in this world
who can clear my name
Then you must stay alive
to prove your innocence
I have no choice now
I can only take a gamble
Gamble
What are
you betting on That even if she hates me to the core
she still has a little affection for me
This little affection
is my only hope of survival
Qianye
Come with me
I hate you
You know it
I know
Then why are you here
Because you didn't kill me last time
The tip of your sword was off by an inch
I regretted that inch
That inch
was my last tolerance towards you
Then why didn't you
stab here this time
All those ambushes outside were set by me
Because I'm also taking a gamble
I bet you believe that I love you
I bet you'll come to steal my wedding
I bet you'll fight Pei Lang
And then I'm going to stab you at this moment
I want you to also taste the feeling of being betrayed
You won the bet
But I also won
Don't move
You're crazy
Don't think that the self-torture trick will work
I can give you my life at any time
But if I die
the murderer will go unpunished
Let me make it clear
I am not the only one
practicing forbidden techniques
The Xi family's affairs have nothing to do with me
The murderer
is someone else
How can I trust you
I will take you to a
place where you can see the truth
If when we get there
you still think I am the murderer
then kill me with your own hands
Look in this direction
You are going to the Changqing Temple
There is a statue of the Changqing Goddess in the Changqing Temple
It was only used in the election of kings
The person chosen by the goddess is the King of Cangwu
How can the statue prove your innocence
The Evergreen Goddess statue has another purpose
What is it
The secret
You
The cold has entered your body
Go and rest first
When you wake up
I'll tell you
Rest quickly
Rest
Give you a chance to run
A mere hairband
I'm afraid it won't be enough to bind the prince
My black hair
will bind my heart  We'll be together till old age If
you move
I'll wake up
Your Highness
You've been badly injured in the battle with the prince You
'd better take the medicine
When will it be your turn
To teach this prince how to do things
I dare not
Pass the order
Make every effort to search for the traitor Pei Su
Remember
You must not hurt Shen Qianye who is in his hands
If you can't find him
I understand
I'll go right away
This time
I will never lose you again
General Cheng
The spy reported
The prince is making every effort to search for Pei Su and Shen Qianye
Sure enough
The prince has already taken action
Everyone
You must find them before the prince
Otherwise
You will be in great danger
Yes
Go
Pei Su
You lied to me again
You
lied to me again
How could I believe you
How could I
What did I do to offend you again
Where have you been?
Are you afraid that I will leave?
I am afraid that I can't kill you
Don't you love pears the most?
Eat pears
Don't bite your tongue
Xihe
Believe me