Please allow me to lead the troops
Bring back the rebels
and leave it to you
Have you really given up on that woman
A woman who doesn't know what's good for her
How can she be compared with the country
Father
Everything in the past
is because your son didn't know how to judge people
I have been secluded for several days
and I have finally realized it That
's not love
What is it
I am unwilling
On what basis
Only by what basis can Pei Su get her love
Obviously, I am the crown prince of Cangwu
I am unwilling
I am unwilling to lose to him
Well said
This is my good son
Lang'er
You must remember this feeling
Go
Take back everything that belongs to us
But
This is
the last chance your father will give you
What's the matter
You have worked hard
over the years
Thank you
for becoming the Pei Su you are today
I know it's not easy for you
Tomorrow morning at the latest
King Cangwu will take action
This time
I will protect you
The Xi family has guarded the statue of the Evergreen Goddess for generations
and is only loyal to the true King of Cangwu
Sir
You said that such a small matter
can be left to our servants
Why bother coming out again
This young man is wrong
Marriage is a lifelong event
According to the old customs of Cangwu
Only with the presence of the husband
can the couple be of one mind
and their love
last forever
The shopkeeper is right Let's take it
Okay
Sir
Someone wants to see you
They said they have something important to discuss
What is it
It's the king's man
He's here
Pei Lang
Lang'er
You've deceived your father again
Fortunately, no one knows a son better than his father
The blood array
starts
Sacrifice to the blood array
You killed the high priest
You guessed it right
You are worthy of being my good brother
The grudge between you and me
will end today
Do you think I've lost just like that
Lang'er
Father is sorry
No
He wants to sacrifice Pei Lang
Pei Lang
Ah He
I'm sorry
Give it to you
I'm leaving first
Whether you are Xihe or not
As long as I can see you
Xihe
You are a natural born general
I cherish you
Respect you
How can I trap you in the boudoir
If I return safely
We will be together for a hundred years
If you die on the battlefield
I will never marry
Still smiling
It's all your fault
Look at it
It's really cute
Look
Ah He
Remember
No matter when
I will never break your wings
Pei Lang
Good brother
It's your turn this time
Pei Su
Make him extremely sad and happy
unstable
Then you can take back the Wood Soul
This is my Wood Soul
The King of Cang Wu
has to
come here quickly
to find his father
Father
set out
It is
Ah He
Your mother is ignoring us again
Who said that
You, the general
are busier than me, the king
Don't let her kiss you
Let's go
Run, run
Pei Su
Don't run
Run, run
Stop
Be careful
Slow down
Stop
Let's go, stop