The medicine is taking effect
Take it away
Yes
Why did Mr. Huang come so late?
I've been waiting for you until now
Really?
Miss Shen
You guys take it easy
Don't kill her
Wait a minute
When I find someone to catch the adulterer
she
must be alive
Miss Shen, don't worry
We brothers will do the job
Are you still unsure?
We will definitely do it properly for you
Yes
OK
You'd better keep your word
If anything goes wrong
You won't get a penny
Do you understand?
I understand, I understand I understand,
I understand
Then I'll leave my sister to you
Have fun
Miss Shen, take care
There really is such a good thing
in this world
Little sister's brothers are here
Brothers are here
Where are they
Yes
Over there
Come quickly
Don't run
Stop
Stop right
there
Stop Don't let her run away
Stop right there Get out of the way
Stop her, quickly
Don't run
Get out of the way
Someone's dead
He's the king's favorite brother
We can't afford to offend him
Yes
Stay away
The smell on her
Could it be that
she's been favored by the prince
I'm afraid she's in great danger
Yes
A bunch of trash
Qian Ling
Your sister is really hanging around here
Dad, don't you know
That damn girl Shen Qianye
is out having affairs with wild men every day
Ruining the reputation of my Shen family
Today
I'll make sure you see her true face
Someone
is here
Even if I have to dig three feet into the ground
I'll find Shen Qianye for me
Yes, yes
Let's go
Shen Qianye
As expected, her blood can suppress my poison
This person is useful to me
You know me
I also know that you are the unfavored legitimate daughter of the Shen family
Your illegitimate sister almost killed you today
It
's none of your business
You two
Go over there and take a look
Yes
What are you doing
Listen
They are looking for you
If I throw you out to them now
Do you think they will kill you
Look at what are you looking at
Get out
Leave
Don't let go of that side either
Search carefully
It seems he needs my blood
Have you searched over there
Go over there and take a look
Your Majesty
Qian Ye is at your disposal
I only beg Your Majesty
to save Qian Ye's life
You look so weak
not as heroic
as when you bumped into me today
I don't like it
What on earth do you want
To be a slave in my house
You are so outrageous
Get out
Hurry up, hurry up
, hurry up
This is
the mark behind the murderer's ear that night
The one who wiped out my entire family
It was him
Second Miss
Eldest Miss and the others are here
Let's go back quickly
It's okay
I'm just waiting for her
The second young lady,
the eldest young lady
, bumped into the prince in Chaomu Tower that day
and was punished by the head of the family to be grounded for three days.
Now that the deadline has arrived
she can't wait to come
obviously she is holding a grudge against you
you who have just recovered from a serious illness
really can't
Shen Qianye
you bitch without a wood soul
Shen Qianye, are you crazy
what are you doing
I'll beat you
self-righteous
brainless and reckless
Shen Qianye
I'll beat you
colluding with a brothel
shameless
Dad
I'll beat you
Second Miss, please stop beating me
bullying the weak
bullying the good
Eldest Miss
enough
I'll let you die knowingly
Miss
You are really stupid
Miss Eldest
In the mansion
You must not do that
Miss Eldest, please spare the Second Miss
Sister
Qian Ye gave you so many chances
to kill me
but not only could you not
you got yourself into trouble every time
Will it be the same this time
You die, bitch
Miss Eldest
Miss Eldest,
please don't get excited You must not do that
Look, everyone knows There is still a
hierarchy between
legitimate and illegitimate children
When you die, I will be the legitimate daughter
King
Your Majesty
my people
How dare you kill
King
Prince, please calm down
I
She and I are sisters
I was just joking with her
You really have planted a soul mark on me
Do you believe that I, Your Highness
, can come and save me at any time
Prince
Prince, please calm down, please calm down
Please, Your Highness
shut up
I really didn't mean it
Miss
What's the point of hooking up with the prince
You're gone and there's no coming back
Miss, you can't say that
If that little bitch
used some seductive tricks
to become the princess
This
You're right
I have to go find my father quickly
and get her back
Hold it in my own hand
Shen Qianye
You want to marry better than me
Dream on
Go
You are so bold
You even dare to plot against this prince
What is the prince saying
I don't understand
Deliberately provoke Shen Qianling
Want her to kill you
Just to see if this prince
will go to save you
If you go
You just get rid of the Shen family
If you don't go
It means that you, a spirit slave
are not important to this prince
You can
slip away openly
Anyway, you won't lose
Prince
Really smart
You are also very smart
But this king does not like people who are too smart
You are wrong
I want to get close to you
To find out the real culprit who killed my family
What are you laughing at
Your Majesty
The Crown Prince has arrived
And he must see you
His Majesty said he wants to see the Second Miss Shen
Follow me
What wind
Brought His Majesty here
Uncle Prince
I was entrusted by my father
to ask you about someone
The Second Miss Shen
Shen Qianye
What do you want her for
I heard that you kidnapped the Second Miss Shen
The Shen Mansion reported this matter
to my father
and burst into tears
He said you kidnapped his daughter as a spirit slave
The Shen family has no other requests
but they hope you can let her go
and let her return home safely
Where can Shen Qianye be safe?
It's hard to say
So you really brought her back
Uncle Wang
It doesn't matter how ridiculous you are on ordinary days
But this is the daughter of an official in the court
How could you do this
Qianye
Your Highness the Crown Prince
Your Majesty