[English subtitles are available.]
When I was first left alone here...
I couldn't stop thinking about
when I would go back home.
Then I got a job at the
Meteorological Observatory.
[Observation Supervisor: People in charge of
astronomy, geography, math, weather
and leakage detection in the Joseon Dynasty.]
Doctor Hong, you're still working?
Someone may think that you're
doing all the work here.
What book are you reading?
It's Lee Soon-ji's book.
It always astonishes me.
He calculated the astronomical constant and
calculated the lunar and solar eclipse dates.
It also gives us the exact calculation
of the orbits of the five planets.
Are you suggesting something
rather strange to the people?
What do you mean?
Like the earth we live on
is rotating.
And that it's round shaped.
It's true.
If the earth is rotating...
Then everyone would feel too dizzy to stand up.
Round-shaped? Where do you see that?
But, why are you laughing?
If you look from very far away,
you can see it.
What?
How beautiful is the ti-wan
[Ti-wan: a 17th century Korean term for Earth]
that we live in is.
Have you seen it from afar?
Earth seen from afar is so beautiful.
Many people from where I used to live
were curious about Earth
and wanted to visit it.
This is the method we used to come to Earth.
We transformed one of the smaller planets
[Terraforming: transforming the planet.
Changing the environment of other planets and satellites
into something suitable for human and plant life]
to make it similar to Earth
and travelled to Earth only when
its orbit was closest to the sun.
[Perihelion: the position nearest to Sun
on planets, comets and artificial satellites orbiting the sun]
This would occur every 404 years.
If I miss this time,
would I need to wait that long again?
There's no definite answer.
The orbit could change due to gravity.
What's more, if I don't go back this time
sooner or later, I will most probably disappear.
I’ll probably die.
[My Love from the Star Record 17]
Cheon Song-yi, the things that you want to do...
Let's do everything in advance.
In advance?
Yeah, in advance.
Let's do everything in one month.
Why?
Why do we have to do everything
in one month?
Why?
I have to leave.
What do you mean?
Huh?
Where will you go?
Where?
To where I’m from.
In one month...
I must return...
Leaving?
You're going back?
♫ Finally I see you at a glance ♫
Yeah...
Okay.
Go...
♫ Everything has changed greatly ♫
But if you go,
♫ You divides my world into two ♫
when are you coming back?
Tell me.
♫ When you breathe ♫
♫ I feel a warm breeze ♫
I am good at waiting.
♫ When you smile ♫
♫ I see a shining star ♫
One year?
♫ You are there ♫
♫ one and only ♫
Two years?
♫ Sometimes you lean on my shoulder without words ♫
Ten years?
♫ For me ♫
♫ it’s a happy moment ♫
You're not coming back?
♫ With you ♫
After you're gone,
♫ time flows or stops ♫
you're not coming back?
♫ I couldn't take eyes off you ♫
Is that why
you said all that about being selfish?
♫ Nothing else I can do ♫
Is that why you did that, you jerk?
You…
♫ If only you have me in all your moments ♫
You're the worst guy I've ever met!
♫ This wish arouses waves of emotions about you ♫
One month?
♫ If only you have me in all your moments ♫
Good job, everyone.
- See you later.
-Good job.
You're going back to Seoul, right?
Give me a ride.
I'll be going home then.
-Good job.
Hey, Cheon Song-yi.
Can you turn off the music?
I'm not in the mood for it.
Okay.
Beom! This is my car.
Sorry, she said she's not in the mood.
Do you have, 'As If I were Shot'?
No, 'I'll Get Lost, You Go Your Way'.
No, no.
Do you have 'Never Let You Go'?
The biggest comet in the century,
AISON, has fully disintegrated.
The comet has triggered nuclear fusion
as it approached the Sun. I disappeared
for it can’t bear the solar heat and gravity.
Disawusi is revisiting Earth after 400 years.
It's approaching Earth's orbit.
According to NASA, Disawusi's
orbit overlaps with Earth's orbit.
Wait!
The biggest meteor shower
of the century is approaching.
Hey, why are you wearing sunglasses at night?
Why's she like that?
Was she dumped by Min-joon?
This Manager Do,
I'll kill him with my own hands
She is a bit disobeying.
Director!
Her phone is turned off.
Is she crazy?
Suddenly she disappeared?
She did that in order to take the revenge
for leaving her alone all by herself last time.
I think that’s the case.
Hey, we're changing actresses
How dare she behaves like this?
Who?
Cheon Song-yi's manager.
Well, good timing!
What are you doing...
Cheon Song-yi is in the hospital now.
Due to the mistakes the team made last time,
Cheon Song-yi fell off from the wire.
Remember, right?
She had organ damage and pulmonary embolism
and went under surgery
You said NG 9 times.
Well, but you eventually picked the first one.
It seems that she didn’t feel well since then.
So, we regret to inform that she is hospitalized
due to fever and abdominal pain
and will not be able to film today.
We want her to be healthy more than anything.
Schedules can be changed
Let's re-schedule.
Yes.
Re-schedule, ok?
[Special Effects(on-site official): Lee Shin]
The number you dial doesn't exist.
Please check the number again.
You are late.
Yeah.
I volunteered at the animal shelter.
I see.
Dad says you're winning an award
for young business leaders.
Well, I'm not so qualified but that’s how it is.
Congrats.
You are amazing.
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to Han-kyung’s grave with mom.
You want to join us?
Oh no, I have plans tomorrow.
I'll go alone later.
He will be sorry to hear that.
He used to like you more than me.
Goodnight.
Okay.
Hey! Stop crying. Let's talk!
Look at me.
You made a wish for me, Grandma.
I've learned how to love.
It was a terrible thing.
It hurts.
My heart is aching.
Help me.
Where are you going this early?
I feel stuffy. I’ll go jogging.
We need to talk.
I've got nothing to say to you.
You should at least answer my phone call.
What's the point?
You're leaving in a month.
This is why I said it's not going to work.
Yeah! So, I bugged off!
I also said I'll let go.
Then you came out of nowhere to be my manager.
You made me float in the air and kissed me.
Who’s that?
Because you had me worried!
You signed a contract with the wrong man.
How is Jae-kyung a wrong man?
There were rumors about you getting engaged.
I think I might as well get engaged.
What?
Why do you care?
You're leaving in a month.
I'm going to get engaged with just anyone
on the date of your departure to show you.
Do you mean that?
Hello?
Where are you Song-yi?
I am jogging.
Don't work so hard yet.
It's not that hard, where are you?
Stop there!
Professor!
It’s really you.
To see you in this kind of a place!
Who are you...
Don't you know me?
I'm Go Hye-mi
I took your class 2 years in a row
When I first met you,
I said you look like my ex-boyfriend, Sam-dong.
Yeah?
I deliberately got an "F" in your class
just so I could retake it
Don't you really remember me?
Well...
No way, I feel so sad now.
I almost got kicked out of the house
because of that grade.
Oh, I see…
Perhaps...
you can't recognize me because I got prettier.
I lost some weight
and I hear that I look more mature these days
Ah.
You have something on the face.
Wait a minute...
I am okay.
Professor,
are you okay?
Yeah.
I am okay.
Professor, did you buy a cell phone?
You were carrying around a pager before.
You're getting some progress now.
It happened that way.
Then...
Can't you let me know your number?
I will text you later.
That is a bit...
Please? Please?
Please let me know.
Okay? Huh?
010...
Do Min-joon, didn't you say you have something to say to me?
Huh? Yeah.
What are you going to do?
I have time right now.
You want to talk now or
not see me forever? Choose one.
Bye.
Who the heck is that visor lady?
She looks like a fake Cheon Song-yi.
What happens if you don't go?
Can't you not go?
Can’t you?
Okay.
Yeah, I don't know where your home is.
Let's say that your home is somewhere.
But a person doesn't have to live at hometown.
Most of the people in Seoul are not natives.
They have their homes in provinces,
but Seoul is like the second home to them.
This is on a different level.
I don't know what level that is.
I don't know! And I don't want to know.
You said that you've lived here for centuries!
Why now?
You lived here just fine!
Right after you met me.
Right after I'm about to do something.
We haven't even had a good date.
Why now?
Can't you just... Stay here with me?
If you won't, then don't get me flustered.
Because you can just leave...
But I have to stay and live here...
Where you've left me behind.
Here.
♫ I sing your name over and over ♫
So
if you're leaving, then leave quietly.
♫ My tears create an ocean of love ♫
And leave me alone.
♫ You're always by my side but I don’t know ♫
If that's what you want...
♫ I hold you waiting for long//telling sad stories ♫
Then I will.
♫ How many such tears are left ♫
♫ Tell me, to love or to leave ♫
♫ The rain turns into tears that interrupt my sight ♫
He was about my age when he died.
That's true.
I wondered if it would be possible to live
after losing a child.
Yet this much time has passed.
However
wasn't Han-kyung unable to drink?
Yes, it’s true.
That's right.
Then why did he drink and drive that night?
The next day was my graduation.
He said that he would definitely be there.
He was suffering from depression.
We found out later from the forensic report.
Chemicals were detected.
It was medication for depression.
Because he can’t go well with the girl he liked.
So perhaps... that might have been
the choice he made.
The brother I know wasn't that kind of person.
Something... went wrong.
[Civil News
“Punish Countries Selling Weapons of Destruction”]
[S&C successor Lee Han-kyung
dies from drinking and driving]
[Forensic report shows that Lee Han-kyung’s
blood alcohol concentration is 0.053
Drunk driving confirmed
Amitriptyline, chlorpheniramine and so on are also detected in the blood
sedatives, as well as painkillers and antidepressants.]
Chlorpheniramine.
[Anti-anxiety and antidepressant medication
are found in Han Yoo-ra’s forensic report]
[As expected,   amitriptyline, chlorpheniramine, etc.are tested.
The sedatives, analgesics and antidepressants are detected.]
I’m Lee Hui-kyung.
Nice to meet you. Se-mi has told me about you.
What’s reason for you to tell me this?
Regardless, he’s your big brother.
I feel the need to stop him
because he is my brother.
I need to know how far he’s gone.
[Sky Mental Hospital
23, Cheongpo Road No.97, Yongsan-gu, Seoul]
You eat all the fat.
I'm just gonna eat the collagen.
You do the oddest things.
Tomorrow let's go eat pork rinds.
I really can't get any older.
If that's your goal,
then you shouldn't be drinking any alcohol.
I'm drinking this because I'm sad.
Anyhow you got your way back into
the movie scenes.
You met your dad who you
had been missing so dearly.
Why are you sad?
Let's have a drink.
You know I can't drink alcohol.
What does it matter? Just us.
Drink this and let it out.
It would have been nice if it never started.
Just face it.
You asked me
how I lived alone for so long?
Was it not lonely?
Yes, I did.
It wasn't that lonely when I lived alone.
However, after having a person to love
for the first time,
realizing that I'll have to leave soon,
it's now becoming very difficult.
I feel like I'm the only one left in the world.
If I go back, I’ll turn it back to
the time before I met that person.
Then I wouldn't be touched
regardless of how much he tried to move me.
I wouldn't like him.
Just thinking about the days when he's not here,
I feel like I going to die from loneliness.
What's going on with the lights?
You should stop now.
It's so dark.
What should I... really do?
What…
Is it a blackout?
Yoon-jae,
look for some candles.
What is this?
I shouldn't have given him any alcohol.
I thought he would only make some
objects move or something.
Things have gotten out of control.
There isn't much time left.
What?
Why must I be here?
Why must I... be with you
wasting this precious time?
This is not what I want to be.
I think one second is precious now.
Why would I…
Be here with you?
This is not where I want to stay.
Not here.
Damn.
So you speak from your heart when you're drunk.
Now I know your true feelings.
30 years of friendship means nothing
when a girl is there.
What?
What are you doing over there?
What are you doing?
Move!
What?
I came out to see Cheon Song-yi's face.
What are you doing over there, you hypocrite!
Move! That's Cheon Song-yi's spot!
Stop. Let's go inside.
Can't you find a better place to use your power?
What the heck…
I shouldn't have made him drink.
What do I do now?
Move!
Oh my gosh.
When did you come in?
Who told you that you could be here?
Wake up right now!
Leave!
One, two, three!
Well…
You still don't get it?
You leave me no choice then. I've tried.
What happened?
He said that he never drinks.
I don't want to be with you, Lawyer Jang.
I…
With whom?
Who do you want to be with?
Cheon Song-yi.
[Civil News. Northeast News.
Ton-xin News. National News.]
The kind of person I hate the most is the
one who loses his memory after drinking.
Sleeping somewhere other than
their home after getting drunk.
Can’t remember anything
he has done the night before.
What makes a human?
It's free will that defines human.
But…
But they lose themselves to alcohol
and they do something against their will.
Ah...
My gosh.
What... happened?
That’s what I said.
So, what happened? Do Min-joon.
No, I
remember exactly last night..
Exactly so drunk that
you were knocked out on my bed.
I don't remember that well.
Did I do that?
I couldn't have done that.
I don’t remember anything.
That's why you said you wouldn't drink
even if you die.
You teleport to anywhere you want.
You don't even remember what happened.
You…
Stay a little farther.
You're...
I'm what?
I
can't think straight.
Then what about this?
Leave!
I don't want to see you ever again.
Are you kidding me?
Why did you just kiss me then?
Does this make you mad?
What?
That's exactly how I feel.
You confuse the heck out of me
when I'm not doing anything.
'I have to go.'
'I can't come back.'
Do you know how bad and selfish that is?
You need to know that.
Song-yi!
I'm coming in!
No!
Why not?
I don't feel like talking.
Go.
I just want to borrow some lotion.
I didn't bring any.
I ran out!
Just let me rest!
You're so cheap!
What? Why aren't you leaving?
Do your teleport thing.
Go!
That…
It's not working.
What the heck? You came like that!
Why can't you leave?
Mom and Yoon-jae are outside!
What are you going to do?
Wait up.
What's wrong with me?
Is it because of the hangover?
What the heck?
Were you lying about your power and alien thing?
Don't talk to me.
Is it because of
that kiss I gave you?
No!
What kind of superpower is it?
After kissing, you get sick to death.
You are not much better than human beings.
This girl is really...
What superpower...
You scared me.
Who were you talking to?
Talk to whom?
What are you talking about?
You were talking to yourself like that?
That's strange.
[Trophy and suspicion sounds simiar.]
I got the trophy last year
at the acting award ceremony.
Won't you get out?
Ah, right. Yoon-jae,
did you try calling dad?
I gave you his number a while ago.
I told you,
he's your dad,
but I don't remember.
Why now, making things awkward?
Hey.
Even if it's awkward, he’s still your dad.
No matter how comfortable you are with,
next door neighbor is just a neighbor.
And no matter how awkward, our dad is our dad.
You think you were dropped from the sky?
Hey. Are you some sort of an alien?
Hi.
Hello.
[Sky Mental Hospital]
Are you going to get in trouble for this?
You don't even have the right to get a warrant.
I'm trying my best.
And… the fact that I was moved to
the Public Trial Department.
He knows it.
He must have let his guard down.
I have to strike to get the evidence.
I didn't think he was an aggressive type.
Detective!
I have a warrant.
Show me the way.
Hurry up.
We've told you already.
There's no such patient.
How are you going to compensate for our lost?
Min-joon!
Oh, Yoon-jae.
Are you going out?
Yeah,
to my mom's house.
My sister is in her lowest mood.
It's hard to be with her.
Okay,
see you later.
Min-joon.
My sister may look like a strong person,
totally not minding anything.
She's not like that though.
She's really soft inside.
I don't know what happened with you two.
But she hasn't been eating
or sleeping for days now.
♫ Finally I see you at a glance ♫
Do Min-joon.
What are you doing right now?
♫ Everything has changed greatly ♫
♫ You divides my world into two ♫
I…
Why do I feel that time is so short
♫ When you breathe ♫
No matter it’s one month or ten days,
♫ I feel a warm breeze ♫
let's...
♫ When you smile ♫
I really like you...
♫ I see a shining star ♫
Do Min-joon.
Do Min-joon, are you listening?
Yeah, I'm listening.
I don't know if you can hear me or not.
But I'll say it anyway.
I've been thinking...
I think I overreacted.
When I was young,
I was famous for being spontaneous
I have never liked a singer till the end.
I liked H.O.T.,
then liked Sechs Kies,
then liked G.O.D.,
and then liked Shinwa.
You know,
I switched among about five different
fan clubs.
Anyway.
I have no consistency.
If I think about it,
I think
I would be able to forget you right away.
So that there would be no regret.
If I send you away without doing anything,
I think I would have some regrets.
So,
let's do the things that will take
others three months, a year, or two years.
Let's do them in a month
like you said.
So,
after we've done everything we wanted to do...
Even if it's just one month.
I might get tired of you.
That's how I am.
Do Min-joon.
What?
Do Min-joon
What is it, Cheon Song-yi?
Help me so that I could forget.
Help me so that I won't have regrets.
Help me so that I could be good to you.
Please help me.
Okay.
But.
How can I
forget you?
Did you hear me?
Were you listening?
Let's go for a trip tomorrow.
If we stick together the whole day,
I might get tired of you
I could dislike you.
Are you listening to me?
Let's go travel.
You scared me.
You said to meet when it's bright.
It's still dawn.
Then what about you?
I...
Just in case I'll be late.
Me too.
Shall we go?
Okay.
After all, we get time now.
Let's hold hands.
Umm... why not?
Well,
find another hospital.
But then,
who could be the person who told
the detective about that hospital?
I do have someone
in mind.
I will call you back.
Do you have some time?
Why?
What is this about?
There is someone that you must see.
You open it.
I need to eat right now. I will call you back...
What?
Yang Min Joo went missing.
What happened?
Go in.
Your wife is waiting.
She has a lot to ask you.
Where are you, Song-yi?
I'm jogging.
Don't overdo it.
I'm not, where are you?
Won't you stop there!
Are you with Do Min-joon?
Last time in the hospital,
if I wasn't hallucinating
because I got hurt in my head,
You suddenly appeared in front of me.
That's true.
12 years ago, that day
you disappeared really fast
and stood on the other side of the road.
That's also true.
At first,
I thought you were weird
and dangerous.
Even when you were protecting
Song-yi from my brother
I thought that you were planning something.
But I know now.
Why you said those words to me.
The accident that hurt Song-yi a while ago.
I think it was my brother.
I know.
I think my sister-in-law
is locked away in a mental hospital.
Help me so that I can get her out.
If I meet my sister-in-law,
I would be able to know more things.
Investigate the hospital.
They will probably get my sister-in-law out.
Because she is not in the list of patients.
Yes, I understand.
Yang Min-joo is not here
I also have many things to ask you.
Yeah.
I got it.
In any case,
thanks.
What was that?
Who is it?
Was it that young girl you met at the park?
The one squealing for your number?
No.
Then?
Then a different girl?
I told you it isn't.
I have to practice on my script.
Will you help me, Manager Do?
I can't do acting.
You don't have to act.
Just read the script.
My other managers used to do this for me.
Scene 71?
Yeah.
Diet? Don't!
I told you!
I don't want even one gram
of you going away.
For me,
you are the perfection
you're the prettiest women
that I know.
Young girls are just noisy and bothersome.
I don't need them...
What's wrong with this line?
It's just how it is.
Next paragraph.
Give a back hug?
What's wrong with the script?
You will do all these when you film?
I have to.
There's no way around it.
Should we try practicing?
Try doing what?
Next line.
Aren't you going to do it?
Let's stop.
Why?
Where are you going?
Let me go with you!
I'm staying right beside you all day long
Did you get tired of me?
My sister was never in a relationship.
So, she doesn't know anything.
I'm doing this so that I could
get sick of you faster.
If we see everything,
then we won't have any more fantasies left.
It's not like I've dated once or twice
The thing between man and woman,
it's all the same.
Even when dad left us, I heard that
it was harder for my sister than my mom.
She piles up regrets and can't let go of love
That's her type.
She likes puppies so much
but she doesn't have one.
She's scared to lose it
Because she is afraid of that.
I've done my share of playing in the past
So, I won't cry about love and feelings.
I'm quite rational and straightforward.
Do Min-joon!
Why did you call me like that?
Where did you go?
I went out for a walk because I felt stuffy.
I was shocked.
I thought you left.
Where would I go?
I have a feeling that you will just go away.
What I'm saying is
you can go.
But I was afraid that you would leave
without saying good bye.
I know I'm rational and straightforward.
But if you leave without saying byes.
I won't leave.
I'm not leaving you.
I'm going to stay.
What do you mean?
I'm saying I'm not leaving.
Even after one month or two months.
So,
don't be worried.
Is it okay for you not to go?
What is more important is
if I don't return this time
I will most likely disappear.
It's likely that I will die.
It's fine.
Is it really okay?
♫ You're my destiny ♫
♫ You're my everything ♫
♫ I can do nothing but watch you ♫
♫ I call your name in silence ♫
♫ You're the one my love ♫
Diet? No!
I told you!
Young girls are loud and annoying.
♫ Finally I see you at a glance ♫
They are all useless.
Kiss.
♫ When you breathe ♫
No,
♫ I feel a warm breeze ♫
what if he passes out again?
♫ When you smile ♫
♫ I see a shining star ♫
Give a back hug.
♫ You are there ♫
♫ one and only ♫
♫ Sometimes you lean on my shoulder without words ♫
♫ For me ♫
♫ it’s a happy moment ♫
♫ With you ♫
♫ time flows or stops ♫
♫ I couldn't take eyes off you ♫
[Always by Your Side]
♫ Nothing else I can do ♫
Aren't you saying it?
Let's stop.
♫ If only you have me in all your moments ♫
Why?
Where are you going?
♫ This wish arouses waves of emotions ♫
Let's go together.