[English subtitles are available.]
I must be crazy.
Choen Song-yi, I…
Don’t talk nonsense while in others’ dream.
Right.
I’ve been alone for long
and the body becomes unsatisfied.
It’s time to get married.
The dream is honest.
You bad guy!
Welcome to my dream.
I’m cold.
Cold…
Everything is settled?
Nobody saw you, right?
Yes.
Greed has always been a problem.
Or I don’t need to take great efforts.
Why did I make such a dream?
What did we do
in the dream?
It’s none of your business.
It must be related to a man.
I don’t lack of anything.
Last month, I kissed Jo In-seong,
in the movie.
You don’t need to explain.
It seems you know Jo In-seong,
but why don’t you know Cheon Song-yi?
You have a TV set with such a big screen,
but why didn’t you watch TV?
Every time you turn on it,
you can see me in every program.
So people called me the tap.
I only watch news.
The news you like is coming.
At around seven o’clock, many people witnessed
[At around seven o’clock,
UFO appeared in the air above Gwanghwamun.]
the UFO in the air above Gwanghwamun.
What? UFO?
How could it possible?
Hold on.
So you like
UFOs and aliens?
I can’t believe you are so childish.
The UFO was flying randomly…
[Has the same flying way of UFO]
[Kang-wan. Gamyeong.]
It appeared half a month ago.
It’s like a cucurbit, or a plate,
or a washbasin.
It flew in the air and made people confused.
[Lee Hyeong-ug. Kang-wan Kamsa]
Last night, a bowl-like object in green light
appeared and got people in a panic.
It must be a bird.
No,
a bird doesn’t light
and fly that quickly.
Do you think I should report it to the prince?
Shouldn’t we?
Lord lyu, shall I say,
an object with green light
like a plate, a cucurbit, or a washbasin
suddenly appeared and flies quickly,
and it’s not a bird?
It’s not easy to say.
Now the state is in regime change
with tense atmosphere.
The king is sensitive.
Lord, it’s a bad omen.
And now the people are unstable.
You’ve served the court for a long time.
The instability is to be resolved.
A larger event
may disguise it
People are usually easy to change their mind.
It’s the eternal truth.
So,
is there anything happened?
There is a rumor in the region
What is it?
A Seo girl became a widow
and killed herself at her 15.
Her husband’s family reported it to the court
for paragon monument.
But she was seen alive
and return to the parental home
accompanied by a strange man.
You mean they played dead for paragon monument?
Families with paragon monument benefit from it.
Sometimes, pretending death happens.
Get two results if it’s true.
Lord Choi!
Search and investigate the Seo family.
Catch the girl pretending paragon of chastity.
What are you doing?
Do you know what this place is?
It’s said your daughter is hiding here.
She committed the crime of cheating
by playing death for paragon monument.
Hand her over.
My daughter is dead.
Do you want to open the coffin?
Search thoroughly.
Catch her once you see her.
Yes.
Madam.
Lord, Ui-hwa…
Did she escape?
You asked me to kill her.
How could I kill my own child?
I trusted you
and believed you could send her away.
She went to find the man who came with her.
She said she couldn’t do harm to her savior.
Get up.
Lord, aren’t you an emissary?
Aren’t you a ghost?
Why are you lying here?
Please open your eyes.
You said you would protect me.
Lord.
Make way.
Back off.
Not found.
Over there.
If the UFO in the news is real,
why doesn’t it have an alien?
It’s sensible only when there is a superman
to defeatthe bad guys or help the poor ones.
Why should aliens help earthmen?
It’s none of their business.
Don’t you know aliens?
They’re intelligent lives in planets out of Earth.
Superman is an alien too.
Why does the superman have to save others?
Extreme altruism is a mental disturbance.
I mean…
You can help each other among your species.
But you can’t ask an alien for help.
Are you an alien?
No.
Do you have superpower?
Then why are you so serious?
Nobody is asking you for help.
[My Love from the Star Record 5]
[The world is beautiful because of me.]
Do you know why I moved to this building?
Because I can see that place clearly.
It’s the most expensive place in our country.
Placing ad in that place takes 100 million
a month.
So the most popular star’s picture is hung there.
Now, it’s me.
I didn’t know there is an ad board before today.
You are thick-skulled so you didn’t know me before.
It took me nearly 12 years to be placed there.
Before sleeping, after getting up,
being blue,
feeling hungry but being unable to eat,
after I see it,
I feel pleased and full.
When I was criticized and hurt by people,
I feel comfortable
on seeing my beautiful smile in the picture.
This is me.
Let me tell you how to avoid getting hurt by others.
Don’t give or take anything.
Don’t expect anything.
No disappointment, no hurt.
What’s the point of living in that way?
No one has ever come to your house, right?
It’s seems you don’t have a friend.
Do you have a family?
Is it lonely
by living like an island?
A dozen reporters are waiting at the door.
More than half of people
living downstairs know you.
A lot of people
like the manager, assistants and fans are around you.
But now you are here alone.
I’m not alone because you are with me.
If they take a picture, it’ll be exciting news.
The idiots.
Everyone, I’m Cheon Song-yi. Now I’m like this.
One meter distance.
So mean.
Thank you for your treat.
It doesn’t matter.
Please enjoy.
Thank you.
Nothing found from the investigation, right?
Maybe it’s not suicide,
but people take it as suicide.
Many actresses can’t get well with their peers.
Nobody will kill herself because of that.
Moreover, Han Yoo-ra got Lo Soo-yeong’s bouquet.
The one commits suicide wouldn’t do that.
How did you know it?
Did you see that?
I heard it from those who went to the wedding.
That’s not the point.
The point is that Cheon Song-yi
has nothing to do with the case.
So what?
People hope it’s related to her.
You are a new one.
People don’t care about the truth.
They just want a punching bag.
Someone should be responsible for the case.
What about Cheon Song-yi?
What if she is innocent?
Who will be responsible for her?
Which media are you from?
It seems I met you before.
Maybe
you are not clear about it.
Wow, the chicken is delicious.
Lee Hee-kyung is eating chicken there.
Let’s buy
some chicken and beer, okay?
I’ll have it when I feel blue.
Go to sleep. Don’t bother me.
But…
What’s that?
What do you mean by last three months?
Sorry to read your diary,
but where are you going?
Or is it because you are sick?
No question.
My goodness.
Maybe I can’t fall asleep on sofa.
I have insomnia.
Artists are always sensitive.
So many artists have insomnia.
Moreover, I’m not used to new beds.
Give me some books.
There was a ceramic rabbit.
He fell in love with a girl
and saw her dying in front of him.
The rabbit swore he would never love someone.
I
love you.
So I want to grow up quickly
and then you can see the beautiful grown me.
[But answer me,
how can the story have a happy ending without love?]
I’ve found everywhere
yesterday,
but I really didn’t find a note or letter.
[Envy]
What’s wrong?
[Detective Park]
Hello.
Han Yu-seon. Han Yu-seon.
What do you get?
What is it?
Jae-kyung.
You are early.
You spent the night outside.
Shh.
I went to Cheon Song-yi’s. So many reporters.
She can’t get out. But I can’t do anything.
I’ve told you.
The event is under investigation. Wait and see.
It’ll be troublesome if people recognize you.
Why did you go?
If it’s not suicide,
did Han Yoo-ra die because of Song-yi?
What will happen to Song-yi?
It’s none of your business.
I’m leaving now.
Okay.
I’m leaving too.
Stop.
The girl has nothing to do with you.
You can’t do anything.
Darling.
What did he do when I went to the police station
on a wheelchair three years ago?
He followed her since the girl
went to Milan for the posters.
I should have split up with him at that time.
What’s your meaning of being alive? Why?
For love, dad.
I seldom begged you.
But can you help her?
Do what?
Rich people can solve any problems
no matter with money, or power, or strength.
Please help her.
When I feel her hardships,
I’m really painful.
I think that’s heartbroken people mentioned.
Consider it as helping me.
Darling.
Yes.
Take my new golf club.
We don’t have such a son.
Darling, please calm down.
Get back and clean yourself up.
I can’t just let it be.
She must be very sad now.
You are smelly.
Good morning.
I see. You can’t feel good
since you were too exciting to sleep well.
sorry.
What are you doing? It’s horrible.
Help the legs to be thinner
because I ate instant noodles last night.
One more person slept here,
but the room changed a lot.
Really?
It becomes much brighter
because I’m here, right?
I hate the room in a mess.
Get up and tidy it up.
By the way, 1111.
What?
The password of my house is 1111.
I changed it into the simplest one.
It’s useful by doing this.
Blood circulation helps me become smarter.
Are you crazy?
Oh. Ah.
Dad.
Ah!
Excuse me. I should ring the doorbell first.
I saw the shoes of a woman,
but I didn’t expect it’s Cheon Song-yi.
I was shocked.
Mr. Jang. Are you scared?
I’m Cheon Song-yi from next door.
He’s an enthusiastic person.
I had some trouble yesterday.
He helped without hesitation
and let me live here temporarily.
Please don’t think too much.
Oh. I see.
What’s that?
These are
dishes cooked by my wife
for him.
What are they?
I don’t have a meal with my dad.
He already came here.
You can be impolite but not unfilial.
Am I right, Mr. Jang?
Yes, I think so.
Just have a meal together.
I haven’t had a meal at home for a long time.
Thank you. Dad.
Mrs. Jang is very skillful.
The dishes are delicious.
Shut your mouth and eat.
How could I eat with my mouth shut?
Am I right, Mr. Jang?
Yes, I think it’s difficult too.
You really don’t regard yourself as an outsider.
You’re too young to understand.
You are my neighbor.
A neighbor is like a friend
We are not outsiders.
You really didn’t live long.
Longer than you.
You’d better show me your ID.
The fish can’t be turn over during eating.
What?
People said turning over the fish during eating
will cause ship on the sea turn over.
Who said such ridiculous words?
My dad.
So, put it there and enjoy it.
You’ve watched that all night, anything?
I’ve contacted the CCTV company.
They said the record can’t be edited.
But if someone take away the record on purpose,
they can create a fake record.
But this is the original copy.
It seems there is no sufficient proof.
No matter how, the case is almost settled.
What?
Reading documents for all day will never help.
We have to get out for clues.
Han Yu-seon contacted me in the morning.
I just came back from her.
She gave me this.
Suicide note.
It’s suicide. You don’t need to insist.
I was scolded by her family because of this.
This is the autopsy.
Amitriptyline and chlorpheniramine
[Forensic Report]
are found in blood test.
All are sedative, analgesic and antidepressant.
She took the medicines in the long term.
Medicine was not related to her death.
The direct cause of death is drowning.
Since we have found the suicide note,
the case can be settled now.
Please the related office
to identify the handwriting.
Keep all this in secret before getting the result.
Will the family accept it?
Yu-seon cried when seeing
her sister’s handwriting.
That’s solid evidence.
We didn’t find the suicide note yesterday.
But it appears all in a sudden today.
It’s suspicious.
So you think she was murdered?
Generally, if one was murdered,
there must another one
who can gain benefit from the death.
But in this case,
we can’t find the people who can
gain benefit from Han Yoo-ra’s death.
Over!
Good.
It’s well prepared.
You’ve provided sufficient data
[When will Ms. Cheon speak for Han Yoo-ra case?]
on the information and plan in 2014
of the five countries in Western Europe.
Who did it?
It’s me.
Damn it!
I finished it with Lee Hee-kyung’s help.
Lee Hee-kyung has worked here only for 15 days.
We’ve gained a lot in this short period.
Oh.
Lee Hee-kyung.
You don’t look good. Anything’s bothering you?
I’m fine.
By the way, why can’t I see Mr. Yoo recently?
I sent him to Gyeong-num
He even did that kind of thing.
What? Why?
It doesn’t matter.
He was indiscreet. I wanted to punish him early.
Anyway,
let me know
if anything or anybody is wrong.
Fighting.
Mr. Yoo looks like a good person.
What a pity!
Generally,
if the families didn’t agree on an autopsy,
and there’s sufficient evidence,
the case can be confirmed as suicide.
The detective is a new one.
He has been trying to investigate.
But he still hasn’t found useful evidence.
What’s his name?
Our detective Yoo Seo looks thinner.
Did you investigate over night?
I’m fine.
You should have been a presenter.
Your face fits the job.
Why do you have to be a detective like your father?
I have to go out, mom.
Tell me, what is your first case?
Actress Han Yoo-ra Case.
What?
Really?
Hey.
Why didn’t you tell me early?
Mom, why are you shouting?
Your brother.
He is in charge of Han Yoo-ra suicide case.
It’s not proved to be suicide.
Why? It’s reported on TV.
People are scolding Cheon Song-yi.
What is the probable result?
It’s under investigation. I can’t disclose it.
We are families.
I won’t tell anybody else.
Tell me.
No, mom.
It’s serious. All lights were broken.
Did they fight?
Yes.
-Right?
-Yes.
Cheon Song-yi pushed Han Yoo-ra
and broke the light, right?
It seems right.
It seems?
Are you telling the truth or not?
We were in the dressing room and…
So you didn’t see it with your own eyes?
Then why were you so sure while on TV?
Can we see the CCTV?
What’s it?
Han Yoo-ra was the one throwing things.
The lights were broken themselves.
Hold on. This is the man on the ship, right?
Toothbrush, floss, hand cream,
false eyelashes.
I can’t understand why she needs these
while staying at home.
Phone chargers are sold here.
Why are you laughing?
You asked for tuna,
-is it of this brand?
-Hello. Darling.
Fermented soy sauce or traditional soy sauce?
Yes, I see. Darling!
What’s wrong?
Recently,
we are very close.
We’ve known each other for over 30 years.
It's the first time for us to have a meal together.
It seems you misunderstood me.
I don’t mean something else,
but to confirm
if Ui-hwa has something to do with the woman,
or they are just alike.
I’m telling the truth…
False eyelashes. Over there.
Why didn’t you tell me earlier?
I’ll be right there.
Send me a message.
-Go together
-Follow.
I don’t know.
You are back.
Stop that. It looks like a crazy ghost.
Did you buy a phone charger?
OK.
Are the reporters still outside?
-Yeah.
-How many?
Several.
Are they homeless seriously?
So boring to stay at home.
Where are you going?
Nothing special.
I’d see if our National Goddess is alright.
Is she still sexy and beautiful at night
and pure and sweet during daytime?
Will you come together?
The bottle is broken.
Why is it broken all in a sudden?
Stop standing here. Clean it up.
The splinter may hurt me.
Should I do it?
Yes. Remember the rubber gloves.
You got a message.
I can read it later.
It may have lots of messages
since it’s powered off last night.
[Beom]
It’s annoying.
Pick up the phone.
You are so wordy.
Beom.
It’s out of power.
What’s wrong?
Seems Han Yoo-ra’s sister found the note.
The detective said they can’t confirm it.
But the reporters are in a mess.
If things continue, you will be ruined.
What should we do?
I’m hanging up.
What’s wrong?
I’m leaving.
I have to tell the reporters
it's not because of me.
I can’t hide here.
I didn’t do anything wrong.
Are you alright?
Of course.
Why?
It’s not me.
God knows.
Han Yoo-ra knew it too.
So I’m fine.
I don’t mean that.
Don’t move.
It shouldn’t have been because of me.
If it’s really because of me,
what should I do?
It’s not because of you.
Stop having a bee in your head.
Don’t move.
Stay here.
Take a rest, okay?
It’s not a bad place.
You don’t trust me?
I’m sorry.
But I have to go to the class.
Hey, kids.
Will you come in or not?
Wait a second.
I’m talking about it.
Because of you,
I can’t focus
on study.
Did I fall in love with you?
I’m sorry.
But I can’t accept it.
I have to do exercises,
the diary,
and the homework.
It’s not the right time for love.
Good luck.
Is life originally so hard?
How about meat sauce noodles?
Seafood noodles are better.
-Half meat sauce and half seafood.
Life can be easy if you want.
But if you would live hard,
it’ll be extremely hard.
Excuse me. NS for wound cleaning.
Injector for wound cleaning.
Ethyl alcohol and wipes.
Spun cotton and cotton ball.
Disposable adhesive tape.
Or medical bandage.
May you speak slowly?
Purified water for wound cleaning.
It’s easy for life if you only love yourself.
When you begin to love others,
life will become hard.
Why so many?
A bandage will be enough.
Disinfect it first.
Disinfect?
Hey.
Give it to me.
It’s okay.
And
the reporters have left.
Thank you
for allowing me to live here
and telling me it’s not because of me.
It gets into the heart.
That’s it.
No time for preparation.
It unexpected, unconsciously, and inexplicably
enters into the heart.
Why do you know so much?
In a word,
I understand you.
First love is confusing.
You will always think a lot.
Sometimes, you may think you are crazy.
Am I crazy?
What am I doing?
We really didn’t say anything.
We were just playing quietly
and posted comments online.
You just posted comments quietly?
They beat you without telling you the reason?
And you were all beaten in this way?
Yes.
So I think it’s ridiculous.
He said something when he started to beat.
“Do you know Cheon Song-yi?”
Yes.
He may be a huge fan of Cheon Song-yi.
Name?
Non?
Are you really a huge fan of Cheon Song-yi?
Why are you staring at me?
Why did you do that?
Is it really because they scolded Cheon Song-yi?
You are still young.
Is an actress worthy of your fighting?
You like Cheon Song-yi?
She hasn’t been completely done this time.
She got hair pulled by others for a man.
It’s obvious she has a bad personality.
Generally,
family education is important.
You can’t say that.
Who are you?
They are kids.
But you are adults.
How can you talk in that way?
She got hair pulled by others for a man.
Have you seen it yourself?
Do you have evidence?
Strictly speaking, you are spreading rumors.
Who are you?
A huge fan of Cheon Song-yi.
Yun-jae, did you have dinner?
Are you crazy?
Don’t be like that, brother-in-law.
Your mom called me.
She said
it's bad for her to be recognized.
So I came here on behalf of her.
Wake up.
She has some other plan.
What’s it?
Try all the way to make a match.
This is the happiest thing for me.
Don’t misunderstand it.
You will never have a chance
if it’s not because you’re rich.
So I feel lucky to be rich.
Normally, our family won’t go broke.
In the case, your mom will like me forever.
Your sister is hard, you know?
I will be responsible for you and your mom.
So, call me
no matter what happens.
God.
Stop being like that.
You naughty boy.
Yun-jae.
Have dinner together.
Enjoy.
I didn’t prepare it well.
It’s great.
Thank you, Mrs.Cheon.
It’s a feast?
Do we have something to celebrate?
I called Song-yi just now.
She doesn’t sound well.
I intended to take some porridge to her,
but she said she will go to sleep early.
She will begin to work tomorrow.
So fast?
She should take more rest.
She is a responsible person.
Song-yi gets
all good things
from me,
not just beauty and willpower.
Yun-jae.
Hey.
I know my daughter well.
She looks strong,
but she is soft in the mind.
I know.
I mean it’s an opportunity for you.
What?
Goodness.
You can’t be so naïve.
For a woman,
she will easily love the man
who protects her
when life is hard for her.
Do you understand?
So,
take the opportunity.
Understand?
Hae-sin will cancel the ad
to be taken this morning.
They just offered the final report.
I’m going crazy.
They tried every way to beg us to be the model.
We finally agreed,
but they refused us.
Why are they
so…
Here you are. Why don’t you take more rest?
I have the Hae-sin ad in the morning.
About it…
-Tell them I can’t go.
-What?
I used
the magic cream.
But it makes my skin tight.
Tight?
Completely tight.
They gave me that kind of thing
but said it’s good.
Nobody will buy the products.
Yes. They are impolite.
Tell them
I won’t be the model for their products.
No way.
I won’t take that ad.
I refuse them
But Song-yi.
The leading role
is an orphan driven out from the rent house.
Is this a bit luxury?
Kid, you’d better give up this prejudice.
Orphan can wear beautiful clothes too.
The leading role does so many work,
but she can’t pay for the rent,
all because of clothes and bags.
In this case, we have to work very late.
What are they doing?
It doesn’t work.
We didn’t receive any information.
Why didn’t you tell us in advance?
It’s decided just now.
It’s a leading role.
Why don’t you…
You are going too far.
I didn’t do anything wrong.
The seniors made the decisions.
I’m just telling their decision.
What will we do?
There is a scene about studying abroad.
So, deal with it as she’s going abroad?
Yes.
Please say something and let her accept it.
What should I say?
What should I do?
I really don’t know.
Beom, start the car.
What?
I read the play.
Maybe something bad happened to the writer.
The scripts are not acceptable.
I don’t want to continue.
Tell them,
Cheon Song-yi can’t accept the play.
Cheon Song-yi refused it.
You, make it clear.
Tell them I will never come here.
I refused them.
I will never work with the photographer.
Don’t come. Tell them one more time
I am not willing to take it.
I refused them.
Anything else need to refuse?
I’ve refused people all day long. Hungry now.
Do we have some plan tomorrow?
No.
It’s great.
Order chicken and beer for me.
Buy it now and it will arrive when we get back.
Okay.
Hello. No 2301, Building A, Gold Apartment.
Chicken and beer…
You can’t?
I see.
What?
Even chicken refused me?
Now a woman like me can’t have some chicken?
No, Song-yi.
They are too busy and no more order.
It’s Cheon Song-yi.
You have work tomorrow. Don’t eat that.
You received my message?
My brother is the detective for your case.
They don’t have any evidence now.
Everything will be fine after the case.
Thank you.
You are the best.
They are going too far.
How can they change the leading role
all in a sudden?
What do they want?
Se-mi, something urgent about
changing the leading role.
Will you come to the TV station?
What’s wrong? Who is that?
Mom slipped down on the ice surface.
Ankle fractured.
Go take a look.
Go.
I’m bored to be here.
I agreed to sleep with you.
Sorry.
Are you okay by yourself?
Of course. Let’s go.
[Jae-kyung]
Jae-kyung.
Song-yi.
Where are you?
Home now?
Yes.
Why are you calling at this time?
I heard you moved to Gold Apartment.
From Hee-kyung.
Yes.
I visited a friend living there.
I want to see you before leaving.
I will go downstairs soon.
Not necessary.
Is it room 2301?
How did you know it?
It’s said many reporters were out of your house.
All people living there know your address.
My friend knows too.
Right.
May I come and have a cup of coffee?
And I have to tell you something.
Mr. Do Min-joon.
Yes, who are you?
I’m from Yeongdeungpo Police Station.
What’s the matter?
Have some questions to ask
about Han Yoo-ra’s death.
We should have invited you to the office
as a witness.
But the case is urgent
and we don’t have too much time.
Let’s talk. Just a moment.
I see.
Where will we go?
I heard you are a professor.
Lecturer.
Teaching in college is the professor.
I went to the college during the day
to confirm something.
It’s said you won’t continue the classes.
Will you leave?
Personal affairs.
You graduated from Harvard?
You are my first Harvard passenger.
What a stubborn traffic jam!
May I come in?
Sure.
Please come in.
I have a question.
Where were you on the day of the event?
How did you get on the ship
without an invitation?
Really a murderer?
Hey.
Do Min-joon.
If they take a picture, it’ll be exciting news.
The idiots.
Everyone, I’m Cheon Song-yi.
Now I’m like this.
One meter distance.
So mean.
Distance of one meter.
Get closer.
Whose girl is she?
So beautiful.
It’s beautiful.
What a beauty!
-=Next=-
My daughter is badly wounded, can you see?
What on earth are you doing?
You only need to hide when you make a mistake.
Do you intend to get the second career?
How about being my manager?
What do you think about Song-yi?
Don’t think.
Cheon Song-yi is my girl.
You thought you were ready for leaving
without hesitation,
but one people is left there.
The one who I thought has disappeared forever
appears again in front of me
after a long time?