=Dark and Dawn=
(The Unique Her: Women's Trilogy)
=Episode 15=
Ye Xiao'ai, slow down.
Did you find out
something huge?
Then what is he so afraid of?
Why did he let me go?
A guy like Li Jin
has surely done more than one bad thing.
I just played a little mind game.
He panicked, as expected.
Xiao'ai.
My queen.
My lovely wife.
You're absolutely amazing.
Listen to me.
No matter what happens,
no more keeping secrets from me.
We can talk it out,
or it's all for nothing.
I get it.
Put your shoes on.
Let's go home.
Mr. Lin,
the authorities have confirmed
that the smuggled fabric purchase
has nothing to do with you.
You're officially cleared.
Mr. Lin, you're back.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Xiao'ai was so worried
that she couldn't sleep.
It's just a minor issue.
Not a big deal.
She got drunk last night.
Drunk?
Hello?
You're back from your business trip?
I'll handle the company matters.
Don't make decisions on your own.
You're lying.
(Xiao'ai,)
(Lin Qiqi)
(I have a fever.)
(Can you come see me?)
Where's Qiqi?
She said she has a fever.
I came to check on her.
I'm fine now.
What about dinner?
I'm not hungry.
Since you're already here,
eat before you leave.
Is your work at Dielian
going well?
I...
I'm planning to quit
and start my own business.
Starting a business isn't that simple.
Do you not trust me,
or do you not trust yourself?
You need to think this through.
If you fail,
I might not be able to help.
I'm not as capable as you think.
A lot of times,
I can barely fend for myself.
Uncle,
we're family, right?
Of course.
Families should share the good times
and the bad times.
You can take care of me,
and I
can take care of you too.
That's the best kind of relationship.
Don't you agree?
You want to drink?
Today,
I'm really happy.
I hope that in the future,
we can be more honest
with each other.
What are you doing?
Let go of me, Li Jin!
Is it beautiful?
Yes.
Which is beautiful,
the flowers or me?
Both.
Uncle,
I have a question for you.
I want to know
how to tell someone
that I love them.
Come with me.
Let go of me, Li Jin.
Let me go.
Li Jin, you scumbag!
You psycho!
Let me go.
What will it take for you to let me go?
Unless you die.
No.
Even if you die, I won't let you go.
Don't touch me.
You're my wife.
If I don't touch you,
who else would I touch?
Your mother's death
wasn't an accident.
It was suicide.
You were right.
I had something to do with it.
I'm responsible
for your mother's death.
You can't stop me.
I'll surely succeed this time.
Mei.
It's way too risky. What if...?
There is no if.
Look at these debts.
Look at these debts!
If I fail, I'm dead.
I have everything ready.
I will succeed this time.
Sen,
Su Mei will surely become
the most successful one.
Just help me this last time.
(Apparel Industry Debt)
This is the last letter your mom left.
Take a look.
♪Get ready♪
♪To leave this troubled world behind♪
♪Say goodbye to the past♪
♪Waiting♪
♪No more secrets hidden in my heart♪
♪To discover♪
♪Love is unfolding♪
♪Wind softly blows to the dazzling sky♪
♪Chasing the endless blue sky♪
♪I won't be trapped in a single moment♪
♪Trying to change♪
♪Roaming the whole world♪
♪Gentle breeze on my face♪
♪Fresh thoughts fill the air♪
♪Stars after the dark♪
♪Lost in wonder beneath the stars♪
♪Love slowly arrives♪
♪Declaring freedom in every moment♪
♪An endless adventure ahead♪
♪Always transforming♪