♪Fleeting illusions♪
♪Beautiful yet fragile.
Bewildering the people♪
♪Shedding a single tear♪
♪In exchange for your shattered heart♪
♪If you can live in peace,
it should be worth it♪
♪I should have no regrets
as I encountered you♪
♪Reunited. If time does pass,
I won't allow you to be alone♪
♪Returning to the good old days,
already dispersed with the wind♪
♪The only one left behind is you,
with a radiant smile♪
♪I'm willing to endure hardships♪
♪To protect you
for the rest of your life♪
♪Even if we're not meant to be
in this life, see you in the next♪
♪I'm willing to endure
a thousand years of winter♪
♪In exchange for your warm smile♪
♪May you have a smooth journey ahead♪
=Yong An Dream=
=Episode 14=
Did you know
that Zhao Chong was arrested?
I do.
Wuzhou relayed the news to me long ago.
If so, why didn't you tell me about it?
I'm Zhao Chong's first contact person.
Will they find evidence related to me
after they arrest him?
Will he rat me out?
You guys still want me
to run errands for you?
You want me to die?
Don't worry.
They have no evidence at all.
Zhao Chong wouldn't say a single word
even if it meant he would die.
Really?
Do you think I still have time
to handle Madam He for you
if you were to be in trouble?
Now, I just want to see
the 5,000 gold taels
as soon as possible.
The materials meant for
the West Canal's reparation
have been delivered.
Inspect and verify them quickly.
Got it.
Lay it straight.
Brother, what do you think?
I must prove myself
during the next fall hunt.
I'll show it to Father.
Here.
I'll give it one more try.
The fall hunt is still very far away.
What about the homework
you received lately?
How's your progress?
Don't bring that up.
I feel frustrated
whenever I think about it.
I feel giddy
whenever I step into
the study room.
And, I feel drowsy too.
I feel terrible.
Brother, I'm in trouble.
I didn't copy a single word of
the essays Grand Tutor told me to copy.
I'll help you out.
Really, Brother?
Thank you.
That's great.
I'll practice a little longer.
-You do expect me to help you out, huh?
-Brother!
Just you wish!
I'll go back now.
Your Highness.
Cousin.
Cousin,
how's the case with Minister Shen?
We're still investigating the case.
Minister Shen is my mentor.
He would never do
such a thing.
Why don't I make a plea for him
in front of Father again?
Your Highness, I have a piece of advice.
As the crown prince,
you're a ruler
and a subject of His Majesty as well.
This concerns the imperial court.
One's claims have no place in it.
You need strong evidence
to prove your claims.
If so, Cousin,
I hope you can get
to the bottom of the case
and uphold justice for Minister Shen
as soon as possible.
I'll do my best.
If you're free later,
why don't you stay here
and join me for a meal?
All right.
He's taking so long to see His Majesty.
The sun has already set.
Maybe he was obstructed
by something.
Let's not wait for him anymore.
We can eat first.
Miss,
let's wait a little longer.
Qingxi,
there's something off about you lately.
What do you mean?
You're siding with outsiders now.
Miss, who said so?
Official Lu went to the palace
to see His Majesty
for Master's sake too.
Preparing dinner for him
and waiting for him to come home
serve as our thanks.
I wasn't referring to today.
You and Yang Zong spoke in turns
when we were returning to the city.
Don't think that I couldn't tell.
And,
weren't you worried about me
spending time alone with Official Lu
before this?
Miss,
that was because
I didn't know Official Lu back then.
After my thorough observation,
I think Official Lu
is sincere to you.
What about Di's sincerity
when he first married Sister?
All of us saw it ourselves.
Although Father
objected to their marriage,
he acknowledged it lastly.
Qingxi,
I know you're doing this for my sake.
But if he can't even express
his sincerity in words,
how can I believe
that blurry feeling, then?
Miss.
My lord,
this time...
This time, it's all on you.
If you do fancy Miss Shen,
you have to tell her.
Think about it.
What she said just now
didn't reflect
her feelings for me.
And,
it seemed like she was in a bad mood.
If I act recklessly,
it'll backfire on me
and cause me to lose all hope.
Do you think you're conducting...
Lower your volume.
Do you think this is a trial?
You're taking your own sweet time
at handling it, huh?
This concerns one's relationship.
Miss Shen is getting
more and more obvious with her hints now.
How could you still lower your head
and try to look for clues?
Listen.
If you keep this up,
you'll lose
that last sliver of hope.
Miss, stop drinking.
Let me pour you some tea.
What did His Majesty say?
His Majesty said
he would release your father
as long as the culprit shows himself.
If he releases him now,
he'll alert the culprit to our presence.
His Majesty also said
that he would
give your father extra care.
Understood.
Thank you, Official Lu.
Official Lu,
we've prepared your cutlery for you.
Qingxi!
Miss,
you haven't eaten either, am I right?
Come, let's eat together.
Delicious.
Of course.
Miss Shen
made it for you personally.
No wonder it's so delicious.
So, Miss Shen, you can cook too.
You should eat up, then.
You guys can enjoy your meal.
I'll go and prepare extra dishes.
I wonder
how my sister is doing?
I remember she once said
that she was
the happiest person in the world
on her wedding day.
Who would expect
her relationship,
which she cherished more than her life,
would be gone in just a few years?
It vanished
like a candle flame
embraced by the wind.
You're drunk.
Li Di!
That scoundrel.
My sister was nice to him.
Yet, he betrayed her.
He let her down
and harmed the Shen family.
If I were to find a husband
in the future,
I would definitely keep my eyes open.
I won't find a guy
like Li Di.
Shen Zhen,
don't worry.
You won't encounter a person like him
as long as I'm around.
You're the same as him.
Me?
You don't dare to own up
to what you did.
You kissed me,
yet you denied it.
And, you pretended
not to remember anything,
I told you already.
What did you say?
Are you trying to
bear the responsibility
just because you kissed me?
Who said I needed you
to bear the responsibility?
If I want to get married,
I must get married
to a guy who truly loves me.
So, how do you feel
about me?
♪The past is like a painting,
just a moment♪
♪Who added the stroke between the eyebrows?
So it was you♪
Stop drinking.
♪It was carved into the heart,
a scar that cannot heal♪
Shen Zhen,
I'm just bad
at expressing my feelings.
Don't be angry.
Actually,
♪How can one have it all in this world?♪
I do fancy you.
♪Everything is clear
but it's hard to untangle♪
Bottoms up.
♪How can one have it all in this world?♪
♪How do I share the same horizon with you♪
♪Although there's no hate or love
between us♪
♪How many can let bygones be bygones?♪
♪How can one have it all in this world?♪
♪How do I share the same horizon with you♪
♪Although there's no hate or love
between us♪
♪How many can let bygones be bygones?♪
My lord.
Speak.
I found the place you wanted me to find.
Come and take a look for me.
What do you think about this painting?
Does it look like her?
It does.
It's literally her.
My lord,
I'm afraid Miss Shen
will pop out of the painting
if it gets any more similar.
But I keep feeling like
something's lacking.
I think I can improve upon
her eyebrows.
Am I right?
My lord,
it's already midnight.
You've drawn so many paintings of her.
You should rest now.
There's no need to rush.
My lord, what's the matter?
This time,
I must do my best.
I must let her feel
my sincerity.
(Baixiang Pavilion)
Madam, thank you
for all the fragrances you gave to me.
I shall gladly accept them.
You don't need to stand on ceremony.
You may go ahead.
I shall take my leave.
Official Zhou.
She's not Lan.
Aunt, thank you for the trouble.
Chuyi,
send Aunt back to the palace.
Yes, sir.
Miss Lan, we're in trouble.
His Majesty already issued
an imperial edict.
He told me to finish the reparation
of West Canal in ten days.
If not, he'll remove me
from office.
I only have ten days, you know?
How could I possibly finish it by then?
His Majesty is pressuring me
while Zhao Chong is imprisoned.
Miss Lan, can you make a plea for me
in front of Benefactor?
I want to quit.
Let me resign from my post
and return to the countryside.
Actually,
you ran plenty of errands for Benefactor.
You've contributed a lot to his cause.
Benefactor's big event is imminent.
I think I can do you that favor
as long as
you gather the necessary gold.
After all, you know how capable
Benefactor is.
Think about Xu Wei.
If so, Miss Lan,
thank you for the trouble.
I'll come up with a way
to gather the necessary gold
as soon as possible.
It's so beautiful!
Be careful.
How did you find
such a beautiful place?
Does someone draw here?
I prepared that.
We shouldn't let such a gorgeous view
go to waste.
Maybe
you would be in the mood to draw today.
Official Lu,
why do I feel like
you're a different person today?
Is that so?
Yeah.
As long as you like it.
Isn't that my mother's jade bangle?
It looks so exquisite.
Did you hire a silversmith to repair it?
I repaired it myself.
I started repairing it
ever since we went to Wuzhou.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
He could've completed the deed
with one phrase.
If she says yes, he can marry her.
If no, just forget about it.
What's with all the extra effort?
He's trying to get a bride, you know?
It's different from doing a business.
All men
desire beautiful ladies.
Good luck.
Come.
Stand guard at the entrance.
Tell me immediately
if Madam is back.
Yes, sir.
We're husband and wife.
I'm doing this for my own good,
which is for your own good.
You should contribute to my cause
and help me gather
the 5,000 gold taels for now.
(Divorce Letter)
A divorce letter?
There's even an official seal on it?
Zhou Shu'an,
you did put in a lot of effort
just to see our divorce.
(Title Deed)
Shen Ran,
I didn't expect you
to be so wary of me
right now.
Why is there a normal brush like this
hidden within the secret compartment?
This is my rubbing.
I saw Mrs. Li entering
an empty house.
I was worried about her.
That's why I followed her.
You shameless scum!
Master,
someone robbed your house
in Minqin Alley.
Maybe
Xu Wei isn't the only mastermind here.
In Wuzhou,
we arrested a wealthy merchant
named Zhao.
We'll know the result
after interrogating him.
You guys were investigating me?
(Li Residence)
Madam!
- Madam!
- Qingli!
You're finally back.
Ran,
I'll give you one last chance.
Give me back the secret letters,
hidden accounts,
and the money I kept
in the money house,
and I can let bygones be bygones.
You'll still be my dearest wife.
All of those were
evidence of your crime.
I've already handed it to Zhou Shu'an.
How can I get them back?
Don't tell me you really thought
you could become
the wife of the Censor-in-chief
after toppling me
and clinging on
to Zhou Shu'an?
Zhou Shu'an has a high position
within the officialdom.
He has plenty of noble ladies
to pick from.
How could he fall for you?
He was just using you
to aid him in investigating the case.
After the deed is done,
he'll rise up the ranks
and cast you away!
Don't forget.
You're no longer
the daughter of the minister.
You're still able
to act all high and mighty
all because you're my wife.
It's all thanks to me!
You're nothing
without me.
You and your lies!
Do you still think
I'm the innocent Shen Ran
who's in love with you
and is willing to be coaxed by you?
How dare you hit me?
You traitor!
I'm so nice to you.
How dare you collude with Zhou Shu'an
and harm your own husband?
Do you know your fault?
You don't have the right to say that!
I have.
You put it so nicely.
You framed my father
and caused him to be imprisoned.
Not only that, but you also
tried to marry my sister off
as someone else's mistress.
I was totally wrong about you.
I thought
that we could be together forever
even if you had nothing in life
as long as we were
in love with each other.
I never expected you
to be the vilest
and most despicable person
I've ever met!
I'm despicable?
If only I killed you
sooner!
You want to kill me?
Fine!
Your father, that old fool!
He was so stubborn
and inflexible!
I only get a meager salary
from him every month!
Who'll sustain the family
if I don't make extra money?
Just you wait.
You'll be executed for your crime alone.
And, the mastermind behind you
will be punished too.
You have to gather
a large sum this time,
am I right?
It's not too late
to head to the Imperial Censorate
and reveal the mastermind to them.
That's right.
If not, the mastermind
will never let you off
when things go south.
Fine. Shen Ran,
if I can't survive,
I'll drag you down with me!
Understood?
Where is it?
Tell me!
Kill...
Even if you kill me,
you won't get what you want.
Li Di,
you're done for.
Do you have a death wish?
Let's perish together, then!
Fish stew with no coriander.
Meatballs without orange peel.
Prepare an extra plate of honey
for the marrow cake.
The steamed pork must be
cooked at a suitable temperature
so that it's soft and sticky.
My lord, don't worry
since you already
assigned the task to me.
I was worried that you might
miss out on the details.
You already told me thrice.
By the way, my lord,
I should test the dishes
just in case they don't taste good.
Hurry and bring her here.
Got it.
I'm starving.
Mister, over here, please.
Please.
What's with all the dishes?
Qingxi,
didn't you say
you have something important
to tell me just now?
Am I right?
Let's go.
You can tell me all about it.
All of these are my favorite dishes.
As long as you like them.
Zhen!
Brother Su Heng?
I finally found you!
Little Black.
You blockhead!
How is it?
How are you and your family doing?
I rushed back after hearing
what happened
to Uncle Shen.
But I couldn't locate you
no matter where I went.
Where did you go?
I'm fine.
Brother Su Heng,
many things have happened lately.
I'll tell you all about it later.
I'm glad that you're fine.
Isn't that Official Lu?
Did you only notice me by now?
Official Su.
Brother Su Heng,
do you know Official Lu as well?
We met each other
in the imperial palace long ago.
His Majesty even told us
to spend more time with each other.
Official Lu,
seems like you're holding
a banquet today.
I wonder if it's convenient
for me to attend it?
Of course.
We're a family.
We're a family?
Yeah,
We're a family.
Official Su, make yourself at home.
Brother Su Heng,
when did you come back?
Will you be leaving again?
Not for some time.
I'm here to see
if I can help
Uncle Shen out.
Don't worry.
Now that I'm back,
you don't need to be scared.
Official Su, were you
close friends with Miss Shen?
Uncle Su was my father's best friend.
Official Lu,
Miss Shen
was the childhood friend
I told you about.
We were engaged before we were born.
Brother Su Heng,
that...
That was a joke we cracked
when we were young.
We shouldn't take it seriously.
Our parents wanted it,
and the matchmaker
already did the deed for us.
And, no matter what,
we're considered childhood friends.
Why shouldn't we take it seriously?
I...
Since Official Lu is here,
he can be our witness.
I, Su Heng,
will only marry you as my wife.
When it comes to a relationship,
it depends on both sides.
Official Su, you have to respect
Miss Shen's will too.
Zhen.
I know.
It's been so many years since we met.
We might not be as close now.
But I'll be staying in the capital
for some time.
Let's take it slowly
and try to get along,
okay?
That's right.
The ability to get along is
the most important thing among people.
However, the current Miss Shen
might be different from
the person you remember.
Do you understand?
I like Zhen no matter
how much she has changed.
Brother Su Heng,
my father has been caught in a plight.
I'm in no mood to talk about that.
Please don't bring it up again.
You're right.
If so, we can talk about it
after Uncle Shen has been
released from prison.
Zhen, don't worry.
We'll come up with a way
to save Uncle Shen.
Thank you, Brother Su Heng.
The dishes are getting cold.
You're right.
Let's eat.
Zhen,
your jade bangle looks nice.
You mean this?
It's an item left behind
by my late mother.
However, someone broke it
before this.
Luckily, Official Lu repaired it for me.
Which immoral guy broke the jade bangle?
How dare he break such
an important object?
Zhen,
tell me who he is.
I'll get back at him for you.
It's already fixed.
Let's eat.
- This is your favorite.
Zhen,
have mine.
There's no fishbone in this.
Although Miss Shen loves fish,
she doesn't like fish belly.
I...
Zhen,
didn't we always fight for the fish belly
when we were young?
Times have changed.
People do change too.
These are just small habits.
Zhen,
it's fine as long as you like it.
If so, you should also respect
the thoughts of other people,
am I right?
It's fine.
I'll have both.
(Huafeng Restaurant)
I didn't get to taste the dish.
What do you worry about?
Have you had your fill?
I'll take you to a great restaurant
for an extra meal.
What will we be having?
Do you want mutton
or beef?
Qingxi?
Mr. Su!
I finally found you two!
You guys...
I'm Official Yang Zong
of the Magistrate Office.
Greetings.
Greetings, Official Yang.
- Mr. Su!
- Qingxi.
Let's go and bring the carriage here.
The carriage?
Zhen,
where are you guys living now?
She's living at
the Imperial Censorate now.
Why are you living
at the Imperial Censorate?
Miss Shen participated
in the investigation of Minister Shen's case.
Now, she's an important witness.
She's living
at the Imperial Censorate for now
so that we can ensure her safety.
Zhen is a girl, you know?
You're making her
live at the Imperial Censorate?
It's inconvenient for her.
Zhen, follow me back
to the General's Residence.
Let's return to
Cavalry General Residence.
I'll see who dares to bully you.
Let's go.
Brother Su Heng,
calm down.
They're doing this for my sake.
And, since I'm participating
in an investigation,
I should obey the rules.
Let me send you there, then.
Let's go.
We're already here.
Miss Shen, you should rest early.
Zhen,
I'll look for you tomorrow.
It's fine.
Brother Su Heng,
I'll look for you some other day.
All right. I'll wait for you.
You guys should head back first.
I'll make a move first.
Let's make a move too.
I'll wait for you.
Shen Zhen.
Let's go.
There are so many candles here.
♪Fleeting illusions♪
What's going on?
It's a secret.
♪Beautiful yet fragile. Bewildering the people♪
♪Shedding a single tear in exchange
for your shattered heart♪
What's going on?
Do you like it?
I do.
Should we have a look inside?
♪I should have no regrets as I encountered you♪
♪Reunited. If time does pass, I won't allow you to be alone♪
♪Returning to the good old days, already dispersed with the wind♪
♪The only one left behind is you, with a radiant smile♪
♪I'm willing to endure hardships♪
♪To protect you for the rest of your life♪
♪Even if we're not meant to be in this life, see you in the next♪
♪I'm willing to endure a thousand years of winter♪
♪In exchange for your warm smile♪
♪May you have a smooth journey ahead♪
What are you smiling at?
Was I smiling?
Are you guys hiding something from me?
Let's go.
Let's hurry!
Wait for me!
Oh, heavens.
I'm just one step away, you know?
You didn't have to rain on my parade.
This darned passing rain.
These aren't raindrops at all.
These are daggers!
They pierce through our hearts!
What did you draw?
Our lord pulled several all-nighters
just to prepare these paintings for you.
Initially, he wanted
to give you a surprise.
After that, the passing rain came.
Shen Zhen,
let's go back.
You'll catch a cold if you stay here.
Since it's meant for me,
I'll accept it, then.
Forget it.
They're ruined anyway.
The painting is ruined,
but the intention of the artist isn't.
Am I right?
If so, I'll draw them again
next time.
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
(Lanyue Pavilion)
Miss,
you've been in the bathtub for an hour.
And, you've been smiling
the entire time.
Does the bath make you that happy?
I'm happy.
- I'm happy.
- You're happy, huh?
If so, does Official Su
make you happier?
Or does Official Lu
Of course it's...
I'm not telling you.
You're not telling me?
I'll take a guess, then.
I think
it's Official Su.
You're wrong.
It's Official Lu.
So, it's Official Lu?
You said that yourself.
- I didn't say that.
- Qingxi!
You still don't want to admit it?
It's Official Lu!
Follow me back.
I'll provide you with everything
I can provide to you.
The sky in the northern desert is blue.
The clouds are so low
that I can touch them with my hands.
I wish to see them for myself.
Seems like you're blaming me.
Can you truly provide me
with what I want?
The only thing you can provide me
is that piece of sky
that is unfit to be seen.
Do you wish
to take me as your wife?
By the way,
you will have your wife soon.
Do you have feelings for him
in your heart??
I do.
I know you're lying to me.
If so, what about
our relationship last year?
Was it just a temporary relationship?
I can never forget
your kindness.
If the afterlife does exist...
You know that I don't believe in that.
I've made up my mind.
Do not pester me again.
We shall
never see each other again.
♪The old scenes entering my sight as the wind blows♪
♪Reminded of the past, the polished mountain♪
♪The story has been written, but who am I reserving my time for?♪
The road to the north of the desert
is far.
Take care.
♪It's a name that love and hate avoid♪
♪Using my shattered heart to make it up to the tear you shed♪
♪To get rid of the ups and downs♪
♪If there's no debt, there's no reincarnation♪
♪If it's not you, both joy and sorrow feel out of place♪
♪Missing out on each other in our past lives♪
♪We have to be together in this life♪
We shall
never see each other again.
My lord!
My lord?
My lord, what's wrong with you?
Do you feel sick?
I dreamt that she left me.
My lord, you must be
referring to Miss Shen.
My lord, this means that you have to
cherish your opportunity.
You have to stop
hesitating.
Was that what it meant?
Isn't it obvious?
If you keep hesitating,
she'll leave you for real.
(Tie in one's dream,
calamity in one's life.)
(I think I believe it now.)
(The heart-piercing pain
is too real to be false.)
Ran,
you're finally awake.
Where's Qingli?
Even now,
you're still thinking about her?
You do have a great relationship
with your servant.
Ran.
Ran, we're husband and wife.
We're birds of a feather after all.
I know I did Father-in-law
wrongly.
But if they wish
to use Father-in-law,
I can't do anything about it.
Who are they?
You wouldn't end up like this
had you reported them
to the authorities last time.
Reporting them to the authorities
is the least of their concerns.
Ran, trust me.
Do not trust the Imperial Censorate.
Now,
write to Zhou Shu'an.
Tell him
to return all those things to me, okay?
Why are you worried
that your crime evidence
is at the Imperial Censorate
when they're not afraid...
It's because they're more terrifying
than the authorities!
Ran, they would kill me
if they knew that I was hiding
so many pieces of evidence.
They won't let you stay alive either.
Come with me.
Write to Zhou Shu'an,
okay?
Come.
I'm not going.
Come with me.
Let go of me!
You!
Ran, listen to me.
Write to Zhou Shu'an.
Ran,
give me your thumbprint.
I won't let you take over my shops!
You!
You're a parasite!
Before this, you sucked
my father's blood!
Now, you're trying to suck mine!
You're a loser
who will never achieve anything in life!
You deserve to be a lower-class citizen!
You said I sucked blood, huh?
Fine.
I'll show you.
(Shen Ran)
Come.
This is how I suck your blood.
♪The old scenes entering my sight
as the wind blows♪
♪Reminded of the past,
the polished mountain♪
♪The story has been written,
but who am I reserving my time for?♪
♪It's a name that love and hate avoid♪
♪Using my shattered heart
to make it up to the tear you shed♪
♪To get rid of the ups and downs♪
♪If there's no debt,
there's no reincarnation♪
♪If it's not you, both joy and sorrow
feel out of place♪
♪Missing out on each other
in our past lives♪
♪We have to be together in this life♪
♪No matter what danger is ahead,
we shall face them together♪
♪Looking forward to our union♪
♪As we sleep on the same bed♪
♪Dreaming about the good days♪
♪Missing out on each other
in our past lives♪
♪We have to be together in this life♪
♪No matter what danger is ahead,
we shall face them together♪
♪Looking forward to our union♪
♪As we sleep on the same bed♪
♪Dreaming about the good days♪