♪Fleeting illusions♪
♪Beautiful yet fragile.
Bewildering the people♪
♪Shedding a single tear♪
♪In exchange for your shattered heart♪
♪If you can live in peace,
it should be worth it♪
♪I should have no regrets
as I encountered you♪
♪Reunited. If time does pass,
I won't allow you to be alone♪
♪Returning to the good old days,
already dispersed with the wind♪
♪The only one left behind is you,
with a radiant smile♪
♪I'm willing to endure hardships♪
♪To protect you
for the rest of your life♪
♪Even if we're not meant to be
in this life, see you in the next♪
♪I'm willing to endure
a thousand years of winter♪
♪In exchange for your warm smile♪
♪May you have a smooth journey ahead♪
=Yong An Dream=
=Episode 5=
(Xu Wei was introduced to Earl Suning)
(by Li Di.)
Ran,
I brought you
some treats from Yanhua Inn.
Come and have a bite to eat.
I drank a little too much yesterday.
I was too selfish.
It was all my fault.
I didn't tell you about
Zhen,
because I was worried that you
will feel worse.
I know.
It was my fault as well,
please don't take it the wrong way.
Why would I?
It's the thought that counts.
Don't worry,
I will find every possible way
to save my father-in-law.
Regarding Zhen,
I will go to the governor's office today
to make an inquiry.
That won't be necessary.
Yesterday, I went
to the magistrate's office.
This case has been transferred
to the magistrate office.
They say,
she might not be missing.
The kidnapped wife
might not be Zhen.
Is that so? That is a relief.
After that,
I also went
to see aunt and uncle.
I never thought
that uncle was in cahoots with Xu Wei.
My father treated them so well
for nothing.
Xu Wei?
Is he the assistant minister
of the revenue section?
He is.
Do you know him?
I am just an official.
How could I possibly know
the assistant minister?
What about aunt and uncle?
How are they doing in there?
Both of them were subjected
to physical punishment.
They were bloody all over,
but the magistrate office
will continue their review of this case.
But we don't know
what else can they possibly find still?
They are truly guilty
for such terrible crimes.
Now that father-in-law is in this state,
they are trying to harm Zhen.
Serves them right.
Exactly.
People like that should be
severely punished.
Here, drink some tea.
Missing?
How could Uncle Lu go missing?
The reason is still under investigation.
Official Lu, we cannot postpone
Wuzhou's plans any longer.
We have to depart now.
No, master, the missing person's case
has yet to be solved.
Do you have the portrait
of the criminal?
If this suspect
really looked like this,
I guess he would have been caught
the first time when he did the deed.
I guess it was because Miss Chen
was in too much shock
when giving her a description.
It was all over the place
and the artist simply didn't know
where to begin.
I even thought
of following up on questioning today,
but the Chen Residence wouldn't even
let me through their main gate.
They just said the suspect had two eyes,
one nose,
and a mouth.
If we find the suspect,
then we can depart for Wuzhou?
Let me try then.
What are you trying?
Miss Chen is in shock,
so she might feel frightened
at the sight of men.
If I am the artist,
I might be able to make her
feel less defensive
and remember more of the details.
You can then catch the suspect sooner.
You?
I have been drawing since young.
I am Li Mo's student.
It's done.
What do you think, Official Lu?
But master,
the magistrate office
never had a female artist.
When you searched me last time,
the female court official told me
that Official Lu thought
that men and women each
have their own strengths.
Anyone who is willing
and passes the tests
would be able to handle the tasks.
Oh right,
hold on.
Let me go!
Stop shouting, missy.
Let go of me!
Come here.
Ling'er.
Go away.
Go away, all of you!
I don't know.
All of you, go away!
Leave!
I don't know.
I know nothing of it.
I don't know anything.
Master, hopefully, Miss Chen won't get into
a state of frenzy
and hurt her.
Drink some water.
Go away.
You filthy woman!
I have experienced the same.
One day before my birthday,
my father had been sent to jail.
Our house has been sealed off.
It should have been
a day of celebration,
but in just one day,
I have lost everything.
All that I hear
were the meanest words
that I have never heard before
in my life.
Even my closest aunt
has sent me away to be a concubine
for an evil man.
I managed to flee from one's evil grasp,
just to be confined in the courtyard
by another fierce villian.
What I felt
was the same as yours.
I never knew
that someone this unfortunate
works in the magistrate's office.
Official Lu,
have you tried
to seek justice for her yet?
If you are weighed down by work,
the Governor's Office
could be of assistance.
Official Lu has already
sought justice for her,
so worry not, sir.
How fortunate this lady is
to have met Official Lu.
Although I was the one getting hurt,
I had to pretend that
I was fine.
I did not have a choice.
I must save my father.
I have to let those who hurt me
get the punishment that they deserve.
Although that might be
a difficult path to take,
I am determined to go down that road.
Yet what good does it bring
when they are punished?
Ling'er, you are not in the wrong.
What is right and wrong is clear
to our souls.
If our hearts don't waver,
nothing can change.
Do not live for the lives of others.
Do it for yourself.
For the things that you like,
and also
for your parents
who are worried about you.
How is my daughter?
Ling'er is alright now.
Thank you.
Get investigating.
I have heard of your
tragic circumstances,
luckily Official Lu
has sought justice for you.
Don't worry, young lady,
if you meet anyone evil again,
please come to the Governor's Office.
All of you heard what I said?
We were just separated by a door.
Official Lu!
Miss.
- Official Lu! - The Governor's Office has
an undeniable responsibility
in catching evil-doers!
Official Lu, your pen.
I made that story up only for the purpose
of helping little Miss Chen
to let her guard down.
I do admit
that I was exaggerating a little.
If I wasn't at Cheng Garden,
I might have already been kidnapped
by Xu Wei.
You were the one to save me
and protect me, Official Lu.
I was the one who can't tell
the good from the bad and
misunderstood you.
We have arrived, master.
Fine.
You can hold on to that pen first.
Official Lu, I have made a mistake.
I'll let Yang Zong send you back to
Cheng Garden.
What a grudge-holder.
This prescription is for...
Our family has been treating people
for years,
and would like to compile a medicine book.
We are buying these herbs
to test out our medicinal recipes.
I see.
Chun'er,
go get the medicine.
We need one last herb.
Give me that.
Give you this?
Official Zhou!
The imperial censorate
is working on a case.
Official Zhou.
What are these?
These are just some ordinary herbs.
Have I broken
any laws?
We know that Mrs. Li is known to be
the city's top fragrance master,
little did we know,
you're making poison.
The imperial censorate
treats their suspects
pretty well.
They are received as honored guests,
and given hot tea.
I did not treat you
like a suspect.
But all that you have said
sounded exactly like that.
If I don't do this,
would you
have come here with me?
What is it really, Official Zhou?
As the lady of the Li residence,
I don't think it is appropriate for me
to be alone with Official Zhou.
You know that you are the lady of
Li residence,
yet you try to poison your husband.
Is that appropriate then?
Official Zhou,
you are such a highly-ranked official
who holds so much power,
how could you say such nonsense?
If you don't want others to know,
better to have never done it.
Official Zhou,
you can either lock me up now,
or I would have to leave.
You knew that Li Di and Xu Wei
are in cahoots.
They plan to kill your sister Shen Zhen
through the hands of Earl Suning.
But you had no proof,
so you wanted to slice up Li Di
with your own hands,
to get revenge for your little sister.
Yet, Mrs. Li, you have only
some parts of the story.
Do you know why the construction plans
are at the Earl of Suning's residence?
I would like to know.
Earl Sunning only confessed that
he knew the construction plans
of your father
was kept at Jin Money House.
He took it out
to save your father.
He wouldn't be so kind.
That is why.
There is still a lot more to this case.
Why are you telling me all this?
I fear you may die
before avenging yourself.
I won't say more.
Mrs. Li, you are a clever person,
you would know what next to do.
I will take leave now.
My dear lady girl.
You are late.
Waiter.
Sir, the usual?
Sure.
We'll go upstairs.
Waiter, wine.
Coming.
You get going.
Alright.
He is inside.
There is a secret door.
Search for it.
Yes, sir.
Why are these vase cabinets
not pushed back to the wall?
Deputy Minister Xu,
you came pretty early today.
We have prepared some snacks.
Magistrate Office on the case.
Anyone resisting will be
executed on the spot.
Untie them.
Mr. Xu.
What are you doing?
Stay still.
Lu Shiyan.
Deputy Minister Xu.
We haven't met in a while.
Well, as the empress,
do you not have access
to the best fabrics?
You had to have me
find these for you?
Not everything from the palace
is the best.
A lot are there to fill the numbers.
They thought we were kept here
and knew nothing about
what good quality looks like.
You're living your life now.
You married into
the Duke Zhengguo residence,
and you can go anywhere that you like,
and do whatever you want to do.
What is this that you are saying?
You've been the empress for so long,
why do you still
have these kinds of childish thoughts?
If the emperor hears this,
I wonder what His Majesty would think.
His Majesty handles so many affairs
each day,
I don't even
get to see him once a month.
He wouldn't bother himself with this.
Your Highness.
Your Royal Highness.
What is it?
You can tell us.
The eldest princess
is no stranger to us.
Your Royal Highness,
Deputy Minister Xu
got into trouble again.
What horrible trouble did he get into?
He was arrested
by the magistrate's office.
It is about him forcibly abducting
the commoners' daughters.
It is not a small matter either.
Let me go check with
the magistrate office
and understand what's going on.
Sister,
although Yan is in charge
of the magistrate's office,
but as his mother, you better not
be involved in this.
Xu Wei is getting himself into
so much trouble these days,
I am getting tired of it.
Just let him be then.
But Earl Ning'an is here already.
He is waiting outside.
I am not seeing him.
Come, let's sit down.
He thought that since I am the empress,
his son is then well-shielded
to do whatever he liked.
Have him go home.
Tea, please.
The Earl of Ning'an's residence
has only this son.
I think they must be very worried.
I remember when he was young,
he was quite the good boy.
He studied well too.
Perhaps he is just making
temporary mistakes.
Did you not hear, sister?
He abducted the commoners' daughters.
It is not the first time.
Eunuch Lou, deliver my verbal decree.
Have the magistrate's office enforce
the law impartially.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
What a pity.
He had potential.
Let's drink tea.
Lu Shiyan!
Enough now.
Eunuch Lou is here.
Eunuch Lou, save me, please.
Eunuch Lou, save me!
Eunuch Lou.
I pay my respects, Eunuch Lou.
You are exempt from formalities.
I am here to deliver a message
to you from the Empress.
Although the empress is compassionate
towards her relatives and descendants,
she will never tolerate wickedness.
Since knowing that Deputy Minster Xu
has been committing such harmful deeds,
her heart is broken, and
wishes the magistrate's office to
punish him without mercy.
Impossible.
Impossible!
That's impossible, Eunuch Lou!
There must be a misunderstanding.
My aunt wouldn't!
She wouldn't leave me in this state.
Something must have went
wrong, Eunuch Lou.
I wouldn't dare deliver the empress's
decree wrongly.
Since Deputy Minster Xu is in the wrong,
you should admit to your crimes
and receive punishment.
Cease your futile pleas.
I have delivered the message.
I would let you carry on
with the hearing.
Goodbye, Eunuch Lou.
Do you plead guilty
or not guilty?
Bring them over.
Kneel.
What he said just now,
you heard it, right?
So what now?
Are you going to
confess or not?
I will, I will.
Sir, sir,
I will confess.
I will confess to everything.
Stop him!
How ungrateful!
Days before,
he told me that
he wanted some young girls
to be sent to Wuzhou.
It was all his idea.
It was all his, sir.
It was all him.
He made me do this.
Sir, it was him.
Wuzhou.
He made me do it.
Xu Wei thought
he had the empress to support him
and could do whatever he liked,
and go beyond the law.
Little did they know, the empress
has always been fair,
how would she show favoritism?
Judging by Xu Wei's crime of
forcing people into prostitution
and abducting young women,
I feel that the death penalty is considered
a light sentence for him.
He is the empress's nephew,
and yet he dared commit such deeds.
Regarding Earl Suning,
who gave him orders
till he would risk being beheaded
to steal the construction plans,
and gifted Shen Zhen to Xu Wei?
Lu Si's residence has been
raided in Wuzhou,
he is currently missing.
The girls that Xu Wei abducted
were to be sent to Wuzhou as well.
What you meant is
there are still hidden factors
in this case?
Wuzhou seems
to be quite a piece of the puzzle.
Official Lu, I am sorry.
Please have some tea.
Did you catch the suspect?
We did.
Who was it?
The main culprit is Xu Wei.
Xu Wei?
That Xu Wei again?
What was his punishment?
Death penalty.
Really?
I can then be free!
I can go see my sister,
we can go to Wuzhou now!
Don't meet her at Li Residence.
You can go to Baixiang Pavilion instead.
You cannot tell your sister
any news
that came from our side,
including the trip to Wuzhou.
Do you understand?
Why?
What are your concerns?
Did you mean
that my brother-in-law introduced
the Earl of Suning to Xu Wei,
and worked together
to sell me to Xu Wei?
But he is my brother-in-law!
They were your paternal aunt
and your uncle too.
Human nature could
be this evil sometimes.
We all have to be careful.
My sister wouldn't be like that.
That I believe.
However,
if she knew about all these,
what would she do?
I guess my sister
would be extremely heartbroken.
Don't cry, I mean...
Don't cry, don't cry.
Please don't cry,
I am begging you.
Shen Zhen, I am begging you.
Don't cry, Shen Zhen.
If you keep on crying, I will...
I am going to faint now I guess.
What you are saying is real?
I am certain.
Where is Zhen now?
Ran!
Zhen!
Ran.
Zhen,
I am so worried about you.
Ran, I am well.
I heard from the magistrate that
you have been abducted.
Are you in any way hurt?
No.
I was in his secondary residence
this whole time.
You and Official Lu?
Zhen, even if you are doing
this for father,
you shouldn't just marry him simply.
What are you saying, Ran?
I almost
got abducted by Xu Wei.
Official Lu saved me twice
from Xu Wei's hands.
He let me stay in his
secondary residence just to protect me.
I see.
I would have to thank him properly then.
It was all my fault
that you had to endure
all these hardships.
How have you been, Ran?
Same old, same old.
I am just worried about you and father.
Do the people in Li Residence
treat you well?
Is my brother-in-law good towards you?
Everything is good.
Don't worry.
I made a new fragrance,
come and have a look.
I've heard that my brother-in-law
had been promoted,
so he should be treating you
even better, right?
You were the one who had gone missing,
how are you asking so much about me?
What are your coming plans?
I plan to stay on
at the secondary residence.
When Official Lu is working on cases,
I will then go with him.
He will protect me.
When the magistrate's office
is working on cases,
it wouldn't be appropriate for a woman
to tag along.
Ran,
let me tell you about it.
The magistrate office has working women.
Anyone with an expertise
who is able to contribute
will be allowed to
assist them in investigations.
There was a missing case not long ago,
and the suspect's drawing
was drawn by me.
The magistrate's office found him
that very night.
You are so great, Zhen.
Alright then.
Investigating cases is dangerous.
You must pay attention to safety.
Don't worry, Ran.
I am very smart.
Look at our Zhen, all grown up.
(Alright then,)
(just stay safe and sound)
(beside Official Lu.)
(Let me handle all the other affairs.)
(I wonder when will I see you next time)
(after we depart for Wuzhou.)
(I hope that you)
(would be able to protect yourself.)
What is up with all of you?
You didn't cry?
Why would I cry?
My sister knows nothing.
On top of that,
regardless of what my brother-in-law
did to me,
he treats my sister
pretty well on the usual days.
This way I am not worried.
When are we leaving for Wuzhou?
I said Yang Zong
and I will go to Wuzhou,
but I didn't say that you could come.
Official Lu, how could you be a man that
eats your words?
These were all just your thoughts.
Master,
why not let her come
with us to Wuzhou?
This trip is dangerous.
It is not a trip that she should make.
Give me my medicine.
Fine.
I guess
I have to support her
for the rest of my life.
I have lost in this round.
I had fun.
Yan, you have improved in playing Go.
Thank you for the compliment,
Your Majesty.
How are you still acting so formally?
Have a seat.
We can do away with these formalities
when in private.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
How is your mother?
My mother is well,
thank you for asking, Your Majesty.
Great, great.
Eunuch Gao.
I am here.
Go and get
the snacks that Wuzhou presented
as tribute.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your mother
loved these snacks since she was little.
Bring some of these along for her
when you go home.
I am aging, perhaps,
and I think of my youth a lot.
I feel very nostalgic.
Your Majesty is in the prime of life,
not even yet close to aging.
Is that so?
Yes, Your Majesty.
I guess some people
might see me as old and decrepit.
You have done well in Xu Wei's case.
These kinds of parasites
are better off dead.
Yes, Your Majesty.
You have made a great contribution.
What would you like as a reward?
I am just doing my job,
so it is not anything great.
However, I do have a favour to ask,
and would like to get Your Majesty's
permission to do it.
Tell me.
I would like to make a trip to Wuzhou.
Before this,
I had some questions regarding
the presented construction plans.
After finding out that there is a copy
of Shen Wenqi's plan
at Lu Si's residence in Wuzhou,
I have sent people out to get it,
but I have yet to receive a reply.
It has been puzzling me for a while,
so I would like to make a trip myself.
I have heard of
news regarding Wuzhou.
It would be good for you to make a trip.
You can handle
the specifics on your own.
I obey Your Majesty's orders.
Master, The identification document
for Wei Jian the merchant
is ready.
Regarding
his wife, Qin Qing, however,
I wonder if Master
has any suitable candidate in mind.
His wife?
Go and look into our female officials,
compile and send in their names and
portrait drawings.
Yes, master.
Official,
what wife?
What was the wife about?
Tell me.
I could be of help.
Stop bothering me all the time,
and you would have had helped me enough.
If you won't tell me,
I'll start crying.
When I cry,
your master will feel sorry for me.
So,
our master, wants me to find him a wife
as his identity disguise.
That is all to it.
So Miss Shen,
can I leave now?
What do you think about me then?
Miss Shen, have you been
someone's wife before?
Do you know how it is to be a wife?
To avoid being noticed,
you would have to stay in the same room
with our master,
would you be willing to do that?
If I could save my father,
I am willing to...
I am willing to learn.
Madam.
Did Sir sleep in his study chamber
again last night?
Yes, Madam.
He has been working tirelessly
on the West Canal,
so from night to dawn, he had been busy
in the study chamber.
Alright.
You can go.
Yes, Madam.
(Chunxin fragrance?)
Madam,
these are the accounts
for Chunxin fragrance.
Who's knocking?
Madam,
master sent you some fragrance powder.
Let me have a look.
It's my favourite Chunxin fragrance!
He knows me well.
Master has been
coming over pretty frequently.
I think it won't be long
before he
brings you back to his residence.
Of course.
Shen Ran causes trouble for him
every day,
and that made him
irritated and distracted.
He could only relax whenever he
comes over.
I just wonder
when will he
make the decision
to kick Shen Ran out of Li's Residence.
I am not even in a rush,
why are you being impatient?
Didn't master just say,
Shen Wenqi just got into an accident.
If we do that,
we would be seized of our weakness.
However,
what would Shen Ran think of
the master buying me my favourite
fragrance
from her shop?
How would she react?
Madam.
You can go home.
I would like some alone time.
Official Zhou.
I was here to report to you,
but you found your way here.
Did you know this all along?
That's interesting.
All I knew was
what you have already known all along.
Perhaps
I can give Mrs. Li
a better suggestion.
Leave this man.
No need for Official Zhou
to concern yourself with our
household affairs.
If you have the time and energy,
please direct it
towards solving my father's case.
(Wenxiang Bordello)
Sir, they are here.
Do a little walk for me.
Sure.
Do you like that, young sir?
I do.
Young sir,
we know how to do that as well.
Young sir.
Alright.
These two can go and rest.
We only need one.
No, but...
We don't have money for the rest of you.
How annoying.
He's poor!
I will help you change, sir.
Just sit down and have a chat with me.
Miss, you can stop pretending.
We have learn to read people
from experience.
You saw through my disguise.
I guess you are here
to ask
how could you please a man, right?
I...
All I wanted to know was
how to be someone's wife.
This is easy!
First of all...
If you can teach her well,
this is all yours.
Please have a seat, miss.
Come.
Hello, sir.
Is this your idea?
No, not mine.
I will look for someone else.
I'll look again.
I have yet to finish my dance.
What a pity that there's no qin player.
The atmosphere will be lacking,
but that isn't too big a problem.
I said I won't bring you.
Maybe you will change your mind
after watching me dance.
It's such a beautiful dance,
even I, as a woman, was mesmerized.
I was looking for a wife,
not the kind who you have learn from.
So all I have learn was for nothing?
You don't have to
waste your time anymore.
This trip is dangerous.
Just stay put and wait for me
in Cheng Garden,
please?
Have you found a suitable candidate?
Even if the candidate is a suitable one,
you might not
trust her fully.
When you are secretly looking
for the construction plan,
that could pose danger.
The magistrate office's goal,
I know it very well.
This also concerns
my father's innocence.
I will do my best.
I already have a plan.
Are you trying to navigate
through Wuzhou's
dangerous people and places
while handling the people around you?
Also,
Official Lu, if you leave,
I am left alone in Cheng Garden,
who knows
if Xu Wei has an accomplice?
What if I am in danger,
who would protect me?
Since my father's incident,
troubles have never left my side.
Thanks to you that I lived safe and soundly
till this day.
You kept on saying that Wuzhou
is dangerous,
but why do I feel that
being by your side
is the safest place where I can be?
Do you really have to go?
Unless you found
a suitable female official.
However, you
couldn't even find one.
So why not pick me?
First of all, I know how to draw.
If you want to make investigations,
I can draw you suspect portraits.
Second of all, Uncle Lu recognizes me.
When he sees me,
he will surely hand over the
construction plans to me.
Am I right?
Yes.
Official Lu,
do you think my reason is sound?
Master, it sounds pretty logical.
Get packing then.
Thank you, Official Lu.
Guess my lessons paid off.
Your wife shall now leave.
Qingxi.
- Qing Xi!
- Miss!
Official Lu said yes!
He agreed.
Really?
I did this and this and this,
and this,
and this.
Miss, are you sure
that Official Lu
promised you wholeheartedly?
He wasn't just reacting out of shock?
Of course not.
He is the great commanding
Official Lu.
How could he be surprised by anything?
He must think that I am
suitable for him.
Suitable for him?
Even if I am not suitable for him,
it must be
my efforts that he witnessed.
Anyway, given time,
I will become the best candidate.
Why are you not paying your respects
to the Eldest Princess?
I pay my respects, Eldest Princess.
You are...
We are staying here temporarily.
I don't care if you are
staying temporarily
or even permanently,
you would have to pack up immediately
and leave this place.
This place belongs to Duke Zhengguo,
which does not accommodate
vile individuals like you.
Eldest Princess,
there must be a misunderstanding.
What happened was...
Miss,
Her Highness has requested
that you leave,
so you have to leave now.
Don't try to talk back.
Leave.
Don't dirty Duke Zhengguo's place.
Miss.
♪The old scenes entering my sight
as the wind blows♪
♪Reminded of the past,
the polished mountain♪
♪The story has been written,
but who am I reserving my time for?♪
♪It's a name that love and hate avoid♪
♪Using my shattered heart
to make it up to the tear you shed♪
♪To get rid of the ups and downs♪
♪If there's no debt,
there's no reincarnation♪
♪If it's not you, both joy and sorrow
feel out of place♪
♪Missing out on each other
in our past lives♪
♪We have to be together in this life♪
♪No matter what danger is ahead,
we shall face them together♪
♪Looking forward to our union♪
♪As we sleep on the same bed♪
♪Dreaming about the good days♪
♪Missing out on each other
in our past lives♪
♪We have to be together in this life♪
♪No matter what danger is ahead,
we shall face them together♪
♪Looking forward to our union♪
♪As we sleep on the same bed♪
♪Dreaming about the good days♪