She tried to kill me,
and yet you helped her escape.
If that's how it is,
then I won't go anywhere.
Where is Ve? Make her talk.
‪PREVIOUSLY
I'm going to see Ms. Ve now.
I'll call you.
Mom,
I know where Ve is now.
No one's ever
humiliated me like this before!
Are you sure it's Teacher Rawee's house?
Hello, Prae, it's me.
Ve, Teacher and Im are dead.
Ms. Ve.
What you talked about with Mr. Pete
wasn't about me,
but about the fire
at Teacher Rawee's house, right?
Well…
You turned off my phone.
That's why Prae had to call you.
You were trying to hide this from me?
Why would you do this, Mr. Ki?
Why did you do this? Why?!
No matter what, the fire
must be connected to Kanisorn and Singha.
I went to the house
before coming to the hospital.
Auntie, please tell me
who came to see Teacher.
I told you I don't know.
Auntie, but if someone
hadn't put out the fire in time,
your house would've burned down too.
Are you just
going to let the culprit go free?
If I tell you,
you have to leave me alone, okay?
I saw several men come with a woman.
One of the men
is a politician's son or something.
His name is…
Sajja or something.
Wait, Ms. Ve.
Mr. Ki. Mr. Ki.
You already know
who killed Teacher, right?
That's why you chose to hide it from me.
All those times you kept apologizing,
you were really just
helping your mother, weren't you?
When you said you loved me,
it was just to make me weak,
to make me stupid,
so I'd forget
what your mother did to my family.
In the end,
you just wanted me
to be the one who loses.
That's what you wanted, isn't it?
Ms. Ve.
- Ms. Ve…
- Don't touch me!
Everything I did
was to protect you, Ve.
How are you feeling, Ve?
Prae, is it because of me
that Teacher and Im had to die?
Don't blame yourself.
It's my fault, Prae.
It's all because of me.
It's because of me, Prae…
Listen to me, Ve.
Teacher and Im died because of
Kanisorn and Singha, not you.
Did Mr. Ki know about this?
Of course he did.
He knew everything,
but chose to lie to me, Prae.
Why?
I used to think
I could forget everything because of him.
But in the end, I was just a fool.
He fooled me, Prae…
Those people will pay for what they did.
It won't be long, Ve.
You'll see.
We're sorry
we couldn't do more for you, Teacher…
But I swear,
the ones who hurt you
will be punished.
STAFF ONLY
Ms. Ve.
Mr. Pete? What are you doing here?
Ki said you disappeared.
So, he sent me here in case I'd find you.
Ms. Ve.
Ms. Ve. Ms. Ve.
Tell Mr. Ki I can take care of myself.
No need for anyone to babysit me.
Ki didn't tell you
about Teacher Rawee and Im
because he was worried about you.
Worried?
I don't think I can believe that anymore.
Wait, Ms. Ve.
Let's talk.
I have nothing to say to you.
Then will you talk to me?
I'm sorry, Ms. Ve.
I'm the one who told Ploy about you.
I wanted to talk to you about my sister.
What Miss Ploy
wanted to talk about is also important.
That's why I--
Please don't blame Mr. Pete.
I promise I won't tell anyone
I met you today.
Not even Grandma.
I understand that
your sister's case is also important.
But didn't Mrs. Manee tell you anything?
Grandma said Ging was poisoned.
But I didn't believe it.
I thought she just had a grudge
against Ki's family.
So she told me to ask you directly
if you're still alive.
That's why I asked Mr. Pete
to bring me to you.
You're the only one
who could tell me the truth.
I already told Mrs. Manee
that before Ms. Ging passed away,
her primary doctor said
she had been doing better and better.
But suddenly, her condition worsened,
even though
she was still seeing the doctor.
The doctor also found it strange.
That's why Mrs. Manee
believes Ms. Ging was poisoned.
If she really was poisoned,
shouldn't there be some kind of evidence?
It's been two or three years
since Ms. Ging passed away.
But at Liangsuttha's house,
there's nothing to connect to it anymore.
GINGYOK'S
Ging's medicine.
- Here.
- Thank you.
See? Sorting the pills
like this makes them easy to take.
I'm glad you like it.
Anything you buy me, I like it all.
Wait.
Yes?
That's my sister's.
But Mrs. Sorn told me to throw it away.
Then don't tell her.
Just say you already did.
I will find out the truth about this.
The teacher I sent to look after Kita
didn't have any issues, right?
None at all.
Kita's adjusting well to new people.
And Ms. Ve?
She said she could take care of herself.
I guess she just needs time.
Maybe she'll understand you.
It's my fault
for not telling her
about Im and Teacher Rawee.
Still, thank you for helping me out.
But there's still a lot you don't know.
Like what?
About Ms. Ging.
About Mr. Pete and me.
What was that?
Oh?
You were going to tell Ki about us,
weren't you?
That…
we've been seeing each other, Ki.
Huh?
So,
you and Pete…
No, no way…
You don't know how to say it, right?
It happened so fast,
it caught us all off guard, right?
Are you crazy or something?
Why did you suddenly tell Ki we're dating?
Or do you have a crush on me?
Right?
Me? Have a crush on you?
I said "seeing each other," not "dating."
Whenever we're through,
we can just go our separate ways.
Then why did you tell Ki about it?
You're the one
who was going to tell him about Ging.
That's why I said it.
I told you, didn't I?
If we don't have clear proof,
don't say anything to Ki.
But Ms. Ging was his wife.
He deserves to know.
Or do you suspect Ki too?
I already
sent Ging's medicine in for testing.
We'll know the results soon.
I don't care what the results say.
I still believe Ki had nothing
to do with poisoning his own wife.
Yes?
The lab results are in?
Puth.
Is something wrong?
Nun, I want to know why you married him.
I…
- Uh, ouch!
- Why?
What's wrong? What happened to you?
I'm fine.
That's not true.
Why do you have medicine?
What did he do to you? You can tell me.
Puth…
A man who loves his wife
can do whatever he wants to her.
- Puth…
- If you do anything to Nun…
Singha didn't do anything to me.
Stop bringing up nonsense.
There's nothing between us anymore.
Leave me alone. Go away.
Nun.
Go!
Singha,
if he won't leave, then let's go.
You wanted to leave
because you were worried about him?
No. I just… I just wanted you
to know I chose you.
I'm not involved with Puth anymore.
I'm a sane man,
not a fool!
I can see clearly that you still love him!
I'm done. I'm going home.
Hey.
Going home?
I helped your mom
get rid of so many enemies.
If I wanted your mom gone,
all I'd have to do is snap my fingers.
And then she'd be gone.
Then who would you turn to for help?
Huh?
Stop, Mr. Singha!
What did you do to Ms. Nun?
Why do you care?
- Ms. Nun.
- Ouch.
Ms. Nun.
What did you do to her?
You're a gopher. Why are you sticking
your nose in a husband-wife matter?
Hey, anyone outside?
Yes, boss.
Take him away.
This way.
I had Ging's medicine tested.
The rest are just regular heart meds.
But there's one that isn't.
You mean potassium?
If a healthy person
takes that amount, it's fine.
But for someone with heart disease,
it's very dangerous.
I heard about that too.
I'm starting to believe Grandma now
that Ging didn't die accidentally.
Someone must've
deliberately triggered her condition.
Someone had to have switched her meds.
Then you should keep this evidence safe.
Wait until things are clearer.
I believe we'll find out
what really happened.
Rest well in a better place, Teacher.
I'm starting to believe Grandma now
that Ging didn't die accidentally.
Someone must've
deliberately triggered her condition.
Someone had to have switched her meds.
Take a break and take your medicine.
Just leave it there. I'll take it myself.
The doctor said
you have to take it on time.
Dad's blood test result?
It's you?
Pete told me you came to the temple,
so I came here.
I already told Mr. Pete
I can take care of myself.
And I don't need any more help from you.
I want to apologize.
I don't want you to misunderstand me.
About Teacher Rawee and Im's funeral,
I'll handle everything myself.
Then get ready to take responsibility
for hundreds more funerals.
How many people have died
because of your mother?
But we don't have any solid evidence
about Teacher Rawee.
There may be no legal proof.
But someone saw Singha
at the teacher's house with a woman.
And who else
could that be if not your mother?
Do you have anything that confirms
it was my mother?
Have you ever seen
anyone catch a real demon?
Exactly. Your mother
and Singha are the demons.
Let's go, Ve.
Haven't you hurt her enough?
If there's anything I can do to help,
just tell me.
If you really want to help me,
sign the divorce papers.
So, Mrs. Sorn,
you've decided not to go abroad?
Yes.
I'm not going anywhere.
And from now on, Kirin won't be
making any decisions for the company.
Then who will you have
manage things instead?
Don't tell me…
Yes.
I'm appointing Nunnalin
as the next president of the company.
There will be an official announcement
at the project press conference.
Mom, last time some board members
weren't on board with me.
Don't worry about that, Ms. Nun.
I've taken care of it.
No one will challenge your candidacy
as president of the Suttha Group again.
Isn't that right?
Nun, you're lucky
to have a husband
who supports you so much.
Nun.
Why are you standing here? Just go inside.
Mom, I think you should
change your mind. I…
I'm not suited to take over your position.
You need to believe in yourself, Nun.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Singha will support everything.
Didn't you see today?
Not a single person objected.
Remember, today,
you will become successful in everything,
both career and family.
That's not true.
Do you know that I…?
No need to say anything.
We'll talk later. Right now, go inside.
Let's go.
Go.
Mrs. Sorn.
I have something important
to talk to you about.
There you are.
Why haven't you answered my calls?
I've had a lot on my mind.
But right now,
you need to stop thinking and go.
Grandma just told me
about your company's press conference.
Do you even know
what your mother is planning?
If you've got something to say,
say it now.
Haven't you noticed
how unhappy Ms. Nun looks lately?
It's nothing.
She's just not confident about
becoming the new president. That's all.
The event is about to start shortly.
Please make your way inside, everyone.
Instead of being happy to see Nun
rising up, what is this?
You only care about your own interests.
Do you even realize
that Singha has been hurting Ms. Nun?
What are you talking about?
When I dropped off her clothes,
I saw bruises all over her body.
Singha's been abusing her.
Mrs. Sorn.
Stop being so jealous.
Stop twisting stories
and feeding me nonsense. It's annoying.
Singha loves Nun dearly.
And if that were really happening,
Nun would've packed up and left long ago.
So you think I'm lying
because I'm jealous of that brat?
Are you gonna deny it then?
You just can't stand
to see me walk by myself again.
Take a good look at yourself.
You've been useless for a long time.
If you don't believe me,
you'll regret it someday.
What? Are you threatening me now?
It's not a threat.
The truth will come out eventually
about you and me,
and about our child.
Go ahead and try.
But when the time comes
and anything leaks out,
don't say I'm heartless.
- Move.
- Sorry.
Mrs. Sorn gave a strict order
not to let you into the event.
What?
My men made it very clear,
dear brother-in-law.
You're not needed here today.
You arranged everything
for my mom today, didn't you?
Of course.
My wife's about to become president.
Of course I had to take care of it all.
You can go home now.
Whoa. Calm down.
- Move.
- Ki, stop.
So this is why
you and Mom
kept today's event a secret from me.
Nun's still your sister, isn't she?
Maybe it's time
you start learning to sacrifice.
It might help you be a better brother.
Ki, come with me.
- Come on, Ki.
- Please.
Ki.
Ki, I didn't want it to be like this.
But I couldn't go against Mom.
About you
giving everything back to Hathai,
you can just forget about it.
Nun.
I just want to warn you.
Mom is trying
to cut you out of the company.
All the board members
who used to support you,
they've all changed sides because of…
Singha.
What did you say, Nun?
Your mom's planning to remove Ki
as the president?
So the announcement today
about the new president
isn't about Ki?
That's right. It's not Ki.
How could she do this?
Ki, don't let this happen.
If Mom really wants
to cut me out of Liangsuttha,
there's nothing I can do.
So this means you end up with nothing.
Then everything
I worked so hard for meant nothing?
What do you mean you worked hard?
About that Ve woman and your mom.
What are you talking about?
What about Ve and Mom?
Let go of me.
Mint.
Mrs. Sorn wants you inside, Ms. Nun.
As for you, you're not needed.
If they buy a lot,
we'll give some freebies.
Mrs. Sorn.
Why didn't you tell me
that Ki wouldn't be
the new president of Suttha Group
and that you plan to remove him
from Liangsuttha completely?
Just a moment.
Why are you making a scene here now?
I helped you take down Ve
so you could get rid of her,
and now you betray me
and leave Ki with nothing?
Then what was the point of me
doing everything to marry Ki?
You don't need to marry him.
And you'd better keep your mouth shut.
Unless you want to disappear like Ve.
Are you threatening me?
It's not a threat.
You've already seen what happened to Ve.
If you want the same, just say the word.
I'll make it happen.
Mom, it's time.
Today,
aside from the Model Gen project,
I also have an important announcement
regarding the Suttha Group.
Is it about the new president?
That's right.
It's time for someone
to take over the role from me.
After all I've done for the company,
working hard,
solving countless problems,
facing attacks and slander,
but in the end, as you can all see,
pure gold doesn't burn in the fire, right?
At last,
the person who tried to
destroy the Suttha Group has lost.
And now it's time for me to step down.
Are you stepping down to announce
your relationship with someone?
What are you talking about?
Someone sent a photo
of you and your secretary
to the press group chat.
They say you two
have been together for a long time,
and that you're stepping down to make
the relationship public. Is that true?
- Here it is.
- This one?
- Here.
- This photo.
Isn't this right?
Where did you get those pictures?
Can we also interview your secretary?
- He's there.
- Is it true you're seeing each other?
Uh, well…
So what exactly is the status
between you
- and Mrs. Kanisorn? Wait.
- Uh, I… Hey.
Please comment on the relationship.
- Here.
- Come on.
- Please answer, Mrs. Kanisorn.
- Mrs. Kanisorn.
What is your relationship, exactly?
There will be no other interviews today.
We will only speak about the Suttha Group.
- Mrs. Kanisorn, please wait.
- Everyone, please remain calm.
- Please don't leave.
- Mrs. Kanisorn.
I'll be waiting to see
what else gets exposed about you.
Ms. Ve?
You sent those photos
of you and Mom to the press, didn't you?
I didn't.
Then who else
would have pictures like that?
It was just you and Mom.
If it wasn't you, who could it be?
Hey, take care of this.
I would never hurt Mrs. Sorn or Ms. Nun.
Yes, Mom?
It seems he won't admit it easily.
What should we do?
I'll take care of it.
She said she doesn't want
any more scandal involving you.
Hey. Handle it.
Hey, follow him!
Nun, get back inside now.
The event's not over.
Maybe you should go back in and
announce your relationship with Uncle Pat
instead of my appointment as president.
Today is an important day for you.
Don't let anything distract you.
Napat is an outsider.
He will never matter more to me than you.
Understand?
Come on. Come with me.
Hey. Do you think if Ve knew
about today, she'd show up?
That's why I asked you
to come see the event with me.
Why are you parking behind the hotel?
Well, you saw the front lot was full.
- Wait. Isn't that Mr. Pat?
- Huh?
Mr. Pat. Mr. Pat.
Mr. Pat.
Hey, can you call an ambulance?
It's time for me to step away
from the Suttha Group
and pass on the most important role,
president of the company,
to the most important person in my life,
my daughter,
Ms. Nunnalin Liangsuttha.
Say a few words of thanks
to everyone here.
Thank you all for coming to this event.
Thank you.
Very good, dear.
Alright.
To ensure confidence in the new president,
please enjoy a presentation
of Nunnalin's past accomplishments.
What is that?
Regarding the hit-and-run case…
- Hey.
- What?
The truth is,
I wasn't the one driving that night.
- It was Nun.
- Oh?
I didn't kill anyone with my car.
- What's going on, Ms. Nun?
- Please explain.
- What's happening?
- That's all for today's event.
No, the event isn't over.
- Look. It's Mr. Kirin and his wife.
- What?
I didn't come here today
just as Mr. Ki's wife.
I came as the daughter of Mr. Terdthong
and Mrs. Kitinee Liangsuttha.
I'm Hathai Liangsuttha.
Don't think you'll get anything back.
‪NEXT EPISODE
Well, you turned yourself in
and got out on bail.
You just need evidence
to support your case.
And I believe
Mintra definitely has something.
May I take Nun back home for a while?
Why should I move my toy somewhere else?
Did you just call Nun a toy?
You don't have
to force yourself like this.
No matter how much
you try to hate him, you can't.
You love him.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon