Please take care of me
at my new workplace, the Suttha Group,
Mother.
You really are Hathai.
I don't care why you came back.
I'll return everything to you.
Whatever you plan,
your mom will never let it happen easily.
If you do nothing,
she'll strip Ging's legacy clean.
Kita will get nothing.
Hey.
I'm sorry I made you upset.
PREVIOUSLY
How did you all get in here?
Why is it Ploy?
How did you end up here with her?
I had an appointment with her.
But after she drank some wine,
she turned out like this.
I have no idea what's wrong with her.
It's like someone
spiked the wine or something.
Madam asked me to tell you
to enjoy your drink while you wait.
She should be here shortly.
Thank you.
Miss Ploy? How did you get here?
Leave.
You're being used by my grandmother.
Is Mrs. Manee setting me up?
Leave, if you don't want trouble.
Thank you for the warning.
Why would Grandma do something like this?
What? Why is it you?
You were tricked into coming
to see Teacher Ve, weren't you?
My grandmother
is using you as another pawn.
So this is all a setup?
Are you alright, Miss Ploy?
I'm fine. You should go now.
Game over.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Miss Ploy.
What are you doing?
You think I'm hiding someone?
Yes. We think you're hiding someone.
Just tell us, Pete, where's Wanvela?
You all barged in here
thinking I was with her?
And am I?
You too.
You found a way into this room
to catch Ms. Ve in the act?
What kind of husband are you?
Don't you trust the woman you love at all?
If this is a misunderstanding,
then I apologize for intruding.
Wait.
What?
Or are you about to confess something?
Aren't you the one
who should be confessing, Nun?
Don't think I don't know
what you're up to.
You worked with Mrs. Manee
to trick me into coming here.
You must think I'm so awful
I'd take advantage of a woman.
Is that what you imagined?
Do you think I'm really like that?
Fine, maybe I'm not the best guy,
but I'm not so low that I'd do something
without thinking.
Or are you saying
you don't have any feelings
for Wanvela at all?
Someone like you, who's never known
real love, wouldn't understand
that people can have
pure intentions for each other.
Let go of your bias, Nun.
You might actually
find more happiness in life.
Oh, you're all back already?
I prepared a late-night meal for you.
I was worried
you'd be hungry when you got home.
Oh, Mother and Nun,
you can stay and eat too.
I made enough.
You must've rushed back to prepare
all this as a cover-up, right?
Cover-up? For what?
Why would I need to cover anything up?
It's not like I did anything wrong
or had any bad intentions.
Mr. Ki,
let's eat before the food gets cold.
Are you hungry?
Aw, Nun,
I thought you'd stay and eat with us.
And you, Mother?
Will you head upstairs or eat with us?
I don't understand how you could
take someone like her as your wife.
It's because of love, Mother.
Someone like you
could never truly love my son.
Enough, Mom.
We're married now.
Can't we all just get along?
You expect me to play nice
with an employee
you made your wife?
Never.
But as far as I know, you used to be
Mr. Terdthong's employee too, didn't you?
And you ended up living in this house
as his mistress, right?
Mom!
- Mom.
- Let go!
Didn't you hear her disrespect me?
Why are you upset over the truth?
Or is it that, as time passes,
people forget their own pasts too easily?
Wait, Mom.
Don't you see she's insulting me?!
Ms. Ve.
I think you should stop now.
If you don't cross the line first,
I'll stay in my place.
Then we won't have an argument.
What is it?
I told you I'd keep my promise.
I'm transferring my first asset to you.
Please sign to acknowledge receipt.
I'll handle the rest.
This is…
I'll explain the details later.
I hope you'll accept it.
Alright. I'll accept it.
What's this emergency meeting about?
Please have a seat, Mrs. Manee.
You'll find out soon.
Is Ki joining this meeting too?
According to the email,
the majority shareholder will be coming.
It's not Mr. Kirin.
What do you mean?
What are you doing here?
Don't tell me
you're Kirin's representative.
I'm here as
the majority shareholder of Jade Biz.
Hm?
Mr. Ki transferred all his shares to me.
The folder in front of you
contains the details.
You…
- Grandma.
- What right do you have
- to take Ging's shares?!
- Grandma.
- You shameless thief!
- Grandma, please.
You shouldn't speak like someone
who's never done business, Mrs. Manee.
Changes in shareholders
are a normal part of any company.
But not here!
Not in my family's company.
I will never let anyone
snatch it away so easily!
Grandma, please.
If you were capable,
you would've figured out
a way to buy the shares back
and reclaimed your position long ago.
Besides, the reason this company
made it through the crisis
is because of the other board members
and Mr. Ki, my husband, as well.
You need to let go of the idea that
this company still belongs to your family.
What Ms. Wanvela said
is right, Mrs. Manee.
This company doesn't belong to you alone.
JADE BIZ
MEETING ROOM
I was foolish to think
you'd be different from Kanisorn's family.
You're just another greedy person
wanting what belongs to others.
Both Ging's man and Ging's shares!
I was nearly foolish enough to think
you truly wanted my help.
But in the end, you went behind my back.
You didn't do any of this for Ms. Ging.
You're selfish
and you did it for yourself.
You!
Grandma. Grandma.
Ugh.
Are you going to fight
to get back what your sister lost?
Or just let them take everything away?
I think if you're still
in this state of mind,
perhaps it's better you step away
from the company for a while.
What did you say?
From this moment on,
you're no longer involved
in the company's affairs.
I'll inform the board
to remove you from all company positions.
Huh?
- Wanvela!
- Grandma.
- Let go of me.
- Enough, please, Grandma.
- Enough.
- Didn't you hear?
- That woman removed me from our company!
- Grandma.
- Grandma, enough.
- Let go.
- Let go of me! Wanvela!
- Grandma.
You're really okay, right?
Yes.
I never expected
Mrs. Manee could be that vicious.
If Miss Ploy hadn't intervened last night,
you would've been wrongly accused.
That's why I came to see you today.
Why?
Because I think
Mrs. Manee hates me even more now.
I don't want you to get dragged into this.
And besides, I'm married.
Let's only see each other
if we really have to.
Does it really have to be this way?
Or is this what Ki wants?
It's not because of Mr. Ki.
It's because of my own concerns.
Please don't blame him.
Alright.
If it gives you peace of mind.
Mom.
What is it, Nun?
You…
- Grandma.
- What right do you have
- to take Ging's shares?
- Grandma.
- You shameless thief!
- Grandma, please.
Did Ki really give Gingyok's
Jade Biz shares to Wanvela?
What about your plan to merge Jade Biz
with the Suttha Group now?
Mrs. Manee must've been furious,
no wonder she lashed out.
That Manee woman
is just a fake high-society type.
She thinks
she's better than everyone else.
But when her interests are threatened,
she shows her true colors.
Mr. Ki is unbelievable.
He just got married and already
transferred his shares to an outsider.
If this goes on, won't he be
giving everything away?
I don't think it'll go that far.
Ki's not the kind
to blindly fall for a woman.
But with someone like Wanvela,
you never know.
She might be able
to manipulate him completely.
Call a board meeting immediately.
Don't tell Ki about it.
Yes.
And you, Nun.
Don't say a word to your brother
unless you want our family to fall apart.
Alright, jump in.
Mr. Ki's taking Kita to a tennis lesson,
then out shopping.
They should be back by late afternoon.
Good. What about the board meeting?
Everyone will gather here shortly.
I guarantee no one else knows about it.
- This way, please.
- Thank you.
Is there something urgent
to discuss here, Mrs. Sorn?
I'd like to talk to all of you
about appointing a new CEO.
Are you stepping down?
I'll still support the company.
But I want young blood,
like my daughter's, to take the lead.
Mom…
I want to finalize this
before the official vote.
What about Mr. Kirin?
Excuse me.
I thought you were preparing him for this.
You all know Nun
is the daughter of Mr. Terd.
And now,
she's the only true Liangsuttha. So,
I think she's the most suitable person
to become the new CEO.
But I disagree.
It's outdated to choose leaders
based on bloodline.
I vote for someone with true ability.
If it's Mr. Kirin, I'll support him.
I feel the same.
So I'll excuse myself.
No one leaves this room
until we finish
this discussion with Mrs. Sorn.
How did you get involved, Mr. Sajja?
I'm Mrs. Sorn's partner.
We're allies. Of course I'll support her.
Please have a seat.
Have a seat.
Regarding supporting Ms. Nun,
I have no issue with it, Mr. Sajja.
So, I'll take my leave now.
Thank you.
This way, please.
‪Through here.
Why are you doing this to us, Mrs. Sorn?
I just want your cooperation. That's all.
Nun, wait outside.
I need to settle this.
What is this?
See for yourself.
This is evidence of bribery
from your rigged land auction deal.
And for you,
this is evidence linking you
to the forced eviction fire case.
Hmm…
three years ago, was it?
It's hard to recall.
This kind of evidence
isn't hard for us to find.
If you help me, I'll help you.
I'll pretend I know nothing.
I'll turn a blind eye to this.
Of course, Mrs. Sorn.
You have my support.
Alright then.
At the next meeting,
I'll vote for Miss Nun.
I'm sorry Grandma hurt you.
But you didn't have to
remove her from the company.
She did it because
she loves the company so much
that she couldn't stand to lose it.
I'm not upset about the physical attack.
But I had my reason for removing her.
What reason?
I can't explain it to you now.
Once I've resolved what I need to,
we'll talk again
about your sister's shares.
Because I never wanted them
in the first place.
I heard from Grandma
you have a grudge against Aunt Sorn.
If you don't love Ki
but you married him just to get revenge,
don't you think
you've let hatred consume you
way too far?
Sometimes, people don't have many choices.
Anyway, I should go
find Mr. Ki and Kita now.
Excuse me.
Who are you really, Wanvela?
Thank you, Mr. Sajja.
Thank you, Mr. Singha.
I've always been fair to everyone
I've gone into business with,
Mrs. Sorn.
You helped me, so I help you.
Especially my son,
once he heard this involved Nun,
he was eager to help right away.
Thank him, dear.
Thank you.
I'll be waiting for the day
you become CEO of the Suttha Group.
After that, I hope our two families
will have some good news to share.
Of course.
Then I'll be going now.
Goodbye.
Mom,
what did Mr. Sajja mean by good news?
You'll find out when the time comes.
For now, just focus
on your upcoming position.
But Mom,
I don't have what it takes to be a CEO.
Whether you do or don't doesn't matter.
There's no way I'll let Wanvela
interfere with the company,
just like she made Manee
lose her mind at Jade Biz.
Did someone
visit the house today, Aunt Kob?
Oh, no one.
These are for Miss Nun,
Mr. Pat, and Mrs. Sorn.
She ordered several cups today.
- Alright.
- And Master Kita's pizza is warmed up too.
I'll go take in the laundry now.
Is Mom calling a board meeting?
I'm not sure
what she's discussing with them.
Why wouldn't she want you to know?
Could it be about you
transferring Ms. Ging's shares to Ms. Ve?
Or maybe she met the board members here?
What did they talk about?
Mr. Ki, is the pizza done?
Is something wrong?
It's just finished.
You know, you could've taken
Kita out for dinner instead,
so you wouldn't have to
come home to heat up pizza.
Kita just wanted to finish
the pizza he ordered.
Which is a good thing,
my son's learning not to waste food.
That'll make it easier
when he moves into his new home.
New home?
I'm looking for a new place.
So we can move out when the time comes.
Is something wrong, Aunt Kob?
Oh.
Nothing.
I just wanted to say.
Since you moved in with Mr. Ki,
the place has been so neat.
The bed, the closet, everything's tidy.
When Mr. Ki lived alone, it was messier.
I just don't like when things are messy.
So I clean everything.
Are you taking the laundry?
Oh, yes, yes.
Is she suspicious?
Ah.
I was about to go to bed.
I just wanted to ask you to go with me.
Hey.
- You mean you want me to sleep--
- Aunt Kob came into the room
and got suspicious
about the things inside.
If you don't sleep in there sometimes,
I'm afraid she'll find out the truth.
Won't you feel uncomfortable?
It's just one night.
But if you're worried
about people getting suspicious,
then I might have to stay with you often.
Let's just get through tonight first.
Let's go.
Hey.
Someone's watching us.
That was close.
Whoa, hey.
What are you doing?
Taking you to bed.
You don't need to go this far.
People will get suspicious.
- Let's just go to bed.
- Ah.
Mr. Ki, put me down.
We're already in the room.
No one's watching.
Here.
You can sleep standing up?
Impressive.
I'm trying to find a way to return
the Suttha Group's shares to you.
- Why bring that up now?
- Well,
because every minute
I spend with you is meaningful.
And I don't want you to ever regret
the time you've spent with me.
That's why I've been trying so hard
to achieve this goal.
But the problem is
my mom is watching me closely.
She already found out
about Jade Biz shares I gave you.
What if she finds out
you want to return everything to me?
She'll be upset.
But I'm still her son.
I believe she'll forgive me.
Don't worry.
I think if you stay in this room,
I won't be able to sleep.
You stay here.
I'll sleep with Kita.
Wait.
Are you mad at me?
I'd rather hate you.
Because if I did,
I wouldn't have to
feel so guilty about myself.
If you're not mad at me,
if you don't hate me,
then how do you really feel about me?
Or you…
Mr. Ki? Mr. Ki?
Mr. Ki. Mr. Ki.
Mr. Ki! Mr. Ki!
Mr. Ki!
The patient is now stable.
What happened to my son?
Why did he lose consciousness?
Does he have a history of drug use?
No way. Ki would never touch that stuff.
Is there something wrong, Doctor?
His blood test
shows a high level of amphetamine.
That caused the symptoms you saw.
Mr. Ki would never use drugs.
Someone must've drugged him.
Because every minute
I spend with you is meaningful.
And I don't want you to ever regret
the time you've spent with me.
I'd rather hate you.
Because if I did,
I wouldn't have to
feel guilty about myself.
Then how do you really feel about me?
Mr. Ki.
Please be okay.
For dinner, Mr. Ki asked me to reheat
pizza for Mr. Kita.
As for the other dishes,
Ms. Ve cooked them.
The three of them ate together.
No, after dinner,
Mr. Ki didn't ask for anything else.
In the evening,
I saw Mr. Ki reading for a bit,
then he took Ms. Ve back to her room.
Yesterday, Ms. Ve
was the one who stayed
with Mr. Ki the whole time.
- Ve. You!
- Hey! Ugh!
- You!
- Mrs. Sorn,
what are you doing?
I found this in your bag, in Ki's room.
You went through my stuff?
If I hadn't,
how would I have found it, huh?
I checked with everyone in the house.
Yesterday, you were the only one
who made food for Ki.
Is this what you gave my son
that almost killed him?
I didn't do it.
- Those drugs aren't mine either.
- I don't believe you.
I had it tested.
It's the exact same drug
found in Ki's system.
Did you drug my son?
- Why did you do it? Why?
- Mrs. Sorn!
- Don't, Mrs. Sorn.
- Why did you do that to my son?!
- Why?
- I said I didn't do it!
- Uncle Pat, help me!
- Mrs. Sorn, please stop.
- You!
I'm telling you again
I didn't do it.
And I would never do such a thing.
I'm not like you, who goes around
drugging people in the house.
What are you talking about?
Dad.
Dad! Dad!
Someone, help him!
Who knows?
Maybe you're the one who drugged Mr. Ki
and you're trying to frame me.
Are you insane?
Mom would never do something like that.
But Mrs. Sorn has done
unexpected things before, hasn't she?
You're the one who found the drugs.
Who's to say they were really mine?
You're the only one saying that.
Everyone in the house
is just as suspicious.
Stop blaming others.
You're the only outsider here.
The only one who would want
to harm this family.
I'm not going to let myself
be accused like this.
No matter what, I'll find the evidence
to prove who drugged Ki.
You didn't do
what Wanvela is saying, right?
Don't be ridiculous.
What kind of mother would hurt her child?
Miss Nun, even if
Mrs. Sorn had issues with Mr. Ki,
she would never go that far.
Then who else could it be?
It was her. It was Wanvela.
I'm sorry.
I know I promised not to come see you,
but when I heard Ki was drugged,
I couldn't stay away.
I needed to come.
It's okay.
Mr. Ki still
hasn't regained consciousness.
And about Mrs. Sorn accusing you
of drugging Ki…
What do you think?
I think someone in the house
wanted to frame you.
To make you fight with Ki.
You're accusing someone else's
family right inside their home?
Just like how people here
keep trying to frame Ms. Ve.
I didn't realize
you were so blinded by love
that everyone else seems evil to you.
What about the other day at the hotel?
Wasn't that some wicked plan?
Pete.
Mr. Pete, please stop.
There's no point arguing right now.
Of course.
Not until we have solid evidence
to catch you red-handed.
Once Ki wakes up,
he'll tell us who did it.
And when that time comes,
you won't get away.
Don't worry, Ms. Ve.
I'll help you.
But for now, let's go check on Ki.
Yes, I was going to check on him too.
I hope he wakes up soon.
Hello, Auntie.
Hello.
Pete, you should go.
Ki's not awake yet.
Leave this place now,
and stay away from my son.
Auntie, doing this won't change anything.
Ah.
I have to do it for Ki's safety.
That girl is dangerous.
She made Ki end up like this.
Ki. You're awake.
Do you know that you were drugged?
Me? Drugged?
Yes, the doctor said
they found drugs in your blood.
Can you remember
how you could've taken them?
Do you recall anything?
No one drugged me, Mom.
What are you saying, Ki?
I took them myself.
When I saw his blood test, I was shocked.
There was a very high amount of drugs.
I want all of Ging's shares
in Jade Biz back
before I accidentally
leak Kirin's blood test results.
I came here for you, Dad, Mom.
NEXT EPISODE
But what should I do now?
Please don't blame yourself.
None of this is your fault.
Soon, we'll vote
for the new company president.
I'll nominate Nun.
I want you to resign.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon