ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, GROUPS, AND
ORGANIZATIONS IN THIS WORK ARE FICTITIOUS
SCENES WITH ANIMALS ARE STAGED
ACCORDING TO ANIMAL WELFARE GUIDELINES
Do you know that it's because of you
that our custodian just stopped cleaning?
Have some coffee.
It's for what happened in Seoul last time.
Sure.
Dae-bum.
You know what?
It won't be the worst thing
to grow old working here together, right?
And we only have one guest. Bom.
-And that lady.
-Right.
Ms. Lee. That's only two guests.
-And Jun.
-Gosh.
Stop it.
If you think about it,
not being able to work in Seoul
isn't something to be sad about.
The air is polluted there.
And people are always stressed over work.
Right. And the rent is expensive there.
Exactly.
The rent in Seoul is insane, right?
When does the result come out?
I don't know. Why do you ask?
Don't look for me on that day.
I'm going off the grid.
You're going to have to promote this area
to the outsiders for us.
You should do it
while we have a tenant there.
I've already posted it online,
so let's give it some time.
Really? You already did that?
Of course.
Hello.
-Goodness. Officer Kwak!
-Hello.
-Have you been well?
-Of course.
Here, Father. This is from Mother.
-Gosh, what's this?
-Have a seat.
-Have some coffee before you leave.
-Sorry.
-I have somewhere to be.
-Really?
-I'll come again next time.
-Mu-cheol.
I was going to ask you a favor.
What about?
You know my building, right?
Sure.
Can you patrol around my building
every now and then?
Did something happen?
Some punk drew hideous graffiti
on my building last night.
A graffiti?
What did it say?
It was something along the lines
of "I'm going to kill you."
Goodness.
We don't even have CCTV in that area.
I apologize.
I'll be more vigilant from now on.
Yes. Please keep an eye on it if you can.
-Of course.
-I feel so relieved
-thanks to you, Mu-cheol.
-Sure.
Gosh, my head.
I don't feel well.
What's this?
It's dried pollack soup.
That's nice.
Who did all this?
Grandma wanted to thank you
for bringing Dad home.
Also, thanks for the pencils.
It's that student from the library.
What is that?
What happened to me?
What did I do yesterday?
WITHDREW: 400,000 WON
REMAINING BALANCE: 4.5 MILLION WON
What? 400,000 won?
When did I withdraw 400,000 won?
What happened?
WITHDREW: 500,000 WON
REMAINING BALANCE: 0 WON
Zero?
Ma'am, I came here yesterday, right?
Are you finally sober?
What's up with your face?
I withdrew cash from here, didn't I?
Don't you remember fighting the ATM?
You! You took my money!
Give it back!
Give me back my money!
Damn it. Give it back!
-Gosh.
-Give me back my money!
What's wrong with you?
Why are you hitting this?
Is your hand okay?
This thing ate up my money
and it won't give it back.
I have so much more money than this.
I was right to be worried
when you bought those liquor earlier.
You can only withdraw up
to 400,000 won a day.
You can't withdraw more.
Why not? It's my money.
Well…
Come back again when you're sober.
No. I have to withdraw the money now.
-Immediately!
-Hey!
Sober up.
And go to the bank downtown tomorrow
to withdraw your money.
Right. I can always go to the bank.
Thank you so much.
Gosh, your money. Hey!
You're leaving breadcrumb trails
with money.
You've got a rough night ahead of you.
Why are you acting like this
in the middle of the night?
-I'm so sorry.
-Goodness, gracious.
You shouldn't be out this late
wandering around drunk.
-How will you take care of the money?
-I'm sorry.
Gosh. Put the money in here.
Goodness. Here.
-Now go.
-What?
Why are you giving this to me?
Here, you can use this.
If you want to give me money,
give it to me when you're sober tomorrow.
Why won't you take it? I'm loaded!
Just put your shoes back on and go home!
-Go! Go home!
-No. I don't want to.
Hurry up and go!
-Bye, bye.
-Gosh.
-Goodbye!
-Goodness.
The liquor drank you last night.
So I… and the money…
And the plastic bag…
I put it in a black plastic bag
in case you lose it.
When I was walking by here again,
was I carrying the black plastic bag?
You didn't come back
until the store was closed,
so I wouldn't know.
Did you lose it?
Hurry and visit the bank again.
You might've left it there.
Thank you.
Chang-su!
Come out here for a moment.
Goodness. What brings you here?
There's a lot you're upset about
because of me, right?
-Sorry?
-I understand.
You must've been irritated
about losing the building.
-That's not true, sir.
-Is that why you did it?
-Sorry?
-What did you say?
What are you talking about?
I'm asking if you guys did that
on my building last night.
-What?
-What's this nonsense?
On a witch-hunt again?
Get lost. We have a business to run.
You guys are busted.
This here.
Be honest with me here and
tell me what you did with this last night.
Ridiculous.
That canister?
NO PARKING
We wrote that.
Why?
Do we need your approval
to write that over there?
Why are you trying to pick a fight
with ridiculous accusations?
What did you say?
How dare you take that tone with me?
Is it a fight you want?
-All right then.
-Please.
We'll both be
on the prime-time news today.
-Please stop.
-Come over here!
-Goodness, gracious.
-Calm down, please.
-Come here.
-I apologize.
A black plastic bag?
Who would put their money in there?
Why?
-It wasn't here?
-If it was,
someone must have taken it.
It's money in a plastic bag.
Would it be possible to check
the CCTV footage for the ATM?
We have some procedures.
So please fill this out
and come back tomorrow.
-So the stamp…
-Is there any way I can see it today?
This is really urgent.
That won't be possible.
Please fill this out
-and come back tomorrow.
-Seong-man.
-Isn't she the one you searched before?
-Please, I need it today.
I'll go and watch it in a flash.
Don't mind her.
So what were we talking about?
Seong-man.
Loans are different
from lending money to a friend.
-Next in line, please.
-Hold on. What's going on there?
Hey, how about just 20 million won?
-Next in line.
-Please.
-Please, I'm begging you.
-What's wrong?
Hello. We met the other time.
Hello.
Do you know what time you were here
approximately?
What time was it?
Why ask for the footage
if you don't even know the time?
It's fine. We can just look for it.
Here. Isn't this you?
This is you, right?
-Goodness.
-I think that is me.
Why are you crawling in?
You seem… What was wrong with you?
Hey, she was drunk.
Goodness.
Why did you come in drunk
looking to withdraw money?
What's that?
Oh, my goodness. Look at you.
Are you talking about
that black plastic bag?
This must be it.
You're holding it like a purse.
I thought it was a purse.
You're struggling.
I don't think you…
It seems like you couldn't
remember your PIN code.
I'm sorry.
-He's right.
-Gosh, that startled me.
I don't think you withdrew…
Where did you go?
Oh, you fell. That surprised me.
Gosh, this is annoying. Just skip over.
Goodness.
-Did you get the money or…
-She must have withdrawn it.
Stop here.
-There you go.
-You got the money.
Why would you withdraw
so much money late at night?
Goodness.
You should have put it in your wallet.
Why would you put it in a plastic bag?
You didn't leave the money.
You're supposed to pull the door,
not climb on it.
Gosh, this is annoying. Fast forward.
And you just left like that.
Thank you for showing me this.
I think you dropped it on your way back.
You should look for it.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Hold on!
-Who is this?
-What's this?
-Something flew by.
-Play it.
-What?
-Something flew by.
-Is that me?
-Who else would it be?
-You tripped again.
Someone came running.
That long-haired guy is Dae-bum.
Why would he be here at that hour?
This punk.
He picked up the money, but not you.
Look at her.
Look how relaxed she is
now that her exam is over.
I wasn't sleeping.
-Hello, Yeo-reum.
-Hello.
Mr. Librarian, could we talk for a moment?
Sure, of course.
Where are you two going?
Go back to sleep.
-Where are you going?
-Go to sleep.
Why are you leaving me all alone?
Did we…
We met yesterday, right?
Yes.
Let's talk over some cold drinks.
Thank you.
She doesn't remember seeing you yesterday.
Really?
By any chance,
do you remember the black plastic bag…
that I was carrying?
Of course.
We watched the CCTV footage from the bank,
and you took
the black plastic bag with you.
I was…
carrying it for you
so you wouldn't lose it.
What about that?
Could you tell me
what happened then in detail?
She's been freaking out
because she lost that plastic bag.
What?
Please tell me.
Last night,
you tripped in front of the bank.
-What's with her?
-Gosh.
My money.
Are you okay?
Mr. Librarian.
How did you come to find me
from so far away?
I'll carry this in case you lose it.
I'll give it back.
I'm a bit drunk.
-I'm a little bit drunk.
-Right.
Are you okay?
Goodness.
I've seen this happen before somewhere.
Sorry?
Where was it?
The library!
Yes! The library!
Why do you always show up
whenever I'm drunk?
-When did I…
-Ready.
-Sorry?
-Ready?
Ready! Why do you appear before my eyes
Whenever I'm drunk
-Everyone!
-Come on, let's go.
Why do you appear before my eyes
Whenever I'm drunk
Blah blah blah
Why does your face keep
Appearing in my mind
You're going home now, right?
-Home?
-Yes.
The billiard club?
Yes.
That's not a home.
Gosh, that hurts.
Nothing happened on the way home, right?
In the morning,
my face…
You guys didn't
have a fight yesterday, right?
Mr. Librarian.
What brings you all the way here?
You didn't take this with you.
There's something
I've always wanted to ask you.
Okay.
-Is it okay if I ask right now?
-Sure.
On the day
we slept in the library together…
Sorry?
What?
Do you seriously not remember that day?
That's not what I mean.
We slept together
in the library that night.
We didn't sleep together.
-We slept in different rooms.
-Forget it.
That's not the issue here.
In the morning, did you hear me or not?
What was I supposed to hear?
The trickle.
I do not understand
what you're talking about.
Stop acting like you didn't.
That really hurt.
Why did you just do that to me?
Why do you keep pushing me?
You almost tripped, so…
You've been pushing since a while ago.
You didn't even use your hand,
but you used that plastic bag!
Am I that filthy?
Am I possessed or something?
Look at this. You're avoiding me again.
Please.
All I want to do is live my life.
All I want to do is live my life
drunk like this.
So please just leave me alone!
I'm so upset.
Indeed. I'm also wondering
what I'm doing here right now.
Please. I beg of you.
It's nice to meet all of you.
That hurts.
Is my nose gone? I think it's gone.
No, your nose is still intact.
My nose.
But there's a scar.
You just dodged, didn't you?
-I'm sorry.
-So it's true.
So it's true that everyone hates me here.
Well, you were…
It's fine.
Today is the last day.
Hold this. Grab this.
So how old are you?
I'm 28 years old.
For real?
We're the same age!
Hey, we're the same age.
Hey, follow me. I'll buy you something.
Hey, come with me.
Hurry up.
We're here. Finally here!
We're here! It's this place.
Hey, buy everything you want to eat.
It's on me.
I don't think we can right now.
Why not?
The store is closed.
ANGOK SUPERMARKET
We have some liquor left in my house.
-Let's go!
-I'll be going home from here.
What?
No!
I can't take that. No!
Hey!
I told you to take this with you!
You threw me that bag and just left?
Yes.
This means
that you dropped the bag somewhere
on your way home.
I am sorry.
I should have taken you
back to your home safely.
No, it's fine.
Anyway, thank you for last night.
I told you so.
I told you nothing good will happen
if you live there.
Yeo-reum, goodbye.
That looks painful.
What happened? Tell me.
-You want to know?
-Yes.
Goodness.
If I wasn't there,
she couldn't have watched the footage.
I begged Yeong-sam to let her watch it.
Weren't you tired from driving that night?
But you still went out?
I was only out for a walk.
Dae-bum sure is young.
Why do people act like that
when they're drunk?
Tell me about it.
Drinking always gets the best of us.
She lost all her money,
so she'll be drinking again today.
The way I see it,
she'll never find that money.
She lost all her money? How much?
-Fifty million won?
-"Fifty million."
Not that much. She lost five million.
Five million.
Then she should call the cops.
You think that'll help her find the money?
Even if I don't try to kick her out,
she can't afford to live here anymore.
Ji-yeong, I'm heading out.
Where?
-I might run late.
-Where are you going?
He's acting weird.
What's so weird?
Why are you always making a fuss here?
Get out of here.
Me?
"Master yourself, master the enemy."
If you know yourself and your enemy,
you'll never lose.
I don't know what you're fighting,
but I hope you win.
Good luck.
Hey, Ji-yeong. When do you get off work?
-In two days.
-Goodness.
Where are you?
Let's see.
Why did I withdraw money when I was drunk?
Hey, did you not see where I put the bag?
Remember, Yeo-reum.
Darn it.
Please.
Please be it.
Please, I beg you.
Damn it!
GRANDMA WANTED TO THANK YOU
FOR BRINGING DAD HOME
ALSO, THANKS FOR THE PENCILS
Anyone home?
Who is it?
Oh, my. Hello.
Goodness. What brings you here?
Come on in.
-Hello.
-The place is a bit of a mess.
Sit here.
-Thank you.
-I finally got to meet you again.
I was curious how you were.
-So?
-Well,
I was wondering
where your granddaughter is.
You didn't meet her?
She went to your house this morning.
No, I didn't.
So you didn't.
By the way,
did you try the dried pollack soup?
She randomly called me in the morning
and asked me
how to make dried pollack soup.
I see.
It was delicious.
I hope she cooked it well.
When did the two of you become friends?
-I'll be going now.
-All right.
I picked some tomatoes recently.
-Give me a second.
-It's fine, ma'am.
Just wait here a bit.
You really don't need to get it.
I'll get going.
Wait.
Here, take this.
My granddaughter.
Please take good care of her.
Let's start here and search
everywhere I could have gone.
I must find it.
I will find it no matter what.
Could I look in your plastic bag?
Gosh!
-What are you doing?
-I lost something.
Announcement to all residents.
The lady that lives by the stream
in the billiard club has lost her money.
She says it was lost when she was wasted
from liquor last night.
If any of the residents
find a black plastic bag
holding 4.5 million won,
Please report it to the community center.
I repeat.
If any of the residents find
a black plastic bag with 10,000 won bills,
please notify the community center.
Ms. Lee.
Well…
Here.
Where did you find this?
Last night,
I took it home by accident.
What?
I thought that I gave it to you.
You said you gave it to me before.
That I took it.
I'm sorry.
You know
I've been looking for this all day.
Darn it.
Did you just not care
since it's not your problem?
I am sorry.
I clearly asked you this afternoon.
I remember asking you.
Anyway,
thank you for finding it.
Grandma told me you came looking for me.
Why were you looking for me?
Nothing's wrong anymore.
The problem is solved now.
So I can go, right?
By the way…
thank you for the dried pollack soup.
Sure.
But be careful.
You can end up dead drinking like that.
Do you…
want some ramyeon?
Sorry?
I'm sorry,
but can you wait just a minute?
I think I need to go buy some ramyeon.
Let's go together then.
I don't want to stay alone
in someone else's home.
Sure.
Who is it?
Excuse me!
Hey, Heo Jae-hun! What are you up to?
You knew it was me?
Why would you wear a mask
when it's so obvious?
Do you know him?
No. You don't need to know him. Let's go.
Wait. What do you mean?
Hello.
I'm Heo Jae-hun, Bom's classmate.
But why were you in that building?
Well,
Bom doesn't come to school often
so I was worried,
and I kind of missed her.
Stop spewing nonsense.
-Let's just go.
-Wait.
Where are you two going?
To buy ramyeon.
Really? That's great.
I make the best ramyeon.
-If you…
-Don't follow us.
Hey, let's go together.
I'm a master at it.
-I said get lost.
-But you have to try.
Let's go together.
What happened to you?
Were you looking for Yeo-reum's money?
Yes.
-Did you find it?
-Yes.
Really?
Impressive. I thought it was a lost cause.
So you gave it to her?
Yes.
Don't you think you're meddling
too much in other's business?
-This isn't like you.
-Ji-yeong.
I'm hungry.
This place is so cool, Yeo-reum.
It's like a studio in New York.
New York, my foot.
I thought you were injured before.
Are you okay?
I'm strong, so it's fine.
Should I cook the ramyeon there?
-I'll cook it.
-No, it's fine. I got it.
You two don't even lift a finger.
You'll be dazzled when you try my ramyeon.
So, does the water boil
from you running your mouth?
-Actually, fire does that.
-So annoying.
I shouldn't have let you tag along.
Is it okay if I call you Bom?
Sure.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Bom.
I'm sorry.
-I'm so sorry.
-What?
All of a sudden? Why?
About visiting your home
and misunderstanding you.
I'm sincerely sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
I was the one being mean.
You had to pay a lot for the dog
because of me.
That's fine.
I'll pay you back as much as I can.
Are you saying you're going to
get revenge on me?
That's not what I mean.
-Yeo-reum!
-Hey!
What happened?
I didn't do anything.
This is…
It's because there's a leak in the pipe,
and it's only taped up.
-Hey, what are you doing?
-Move your hand.
You're going to have to throw that away.
The pipe is shattered.
Really?
I'll go to Mr. Bae and get a new one.
-Stay here.
-No need.
We agreed that I'd fix these things.
What? That's ridiculous.
Just wait here. I'll get you a new one.
-Let me tag along.
-Hey.
Just stop getting in the way,
mop up the floor,
and watch the dog properly.
Hey!
-I'll leave it to you, then.
-Yeo-reum!
What's your name?
Mr. Bae!
Who is it?
Gosh, you're here.
Mr. Bae, how could you be like this?
I know.
-I'm sorry.
-You should be.
The water pipe shattered
so she can't use the water there.
The sink was breaking down.
Shouldn't the landlord
be fixing it for the tenant?
-You're talking about that?
-Then what?
It's fine, Bom.
I can fix it myself.
-Just give me a pipe for the sink.
-No way.
I'll fix it.
I should be the one fixing it.
You two can head home first.
I'll be there with the parts.
-Mr. Bae.
-Yes?
You better hurry. We need to cook ramyeon.
All right. I'll hurry.
Yeo-reum, you should go with Bom.
Let's go.
Bom!
Bom, come out here!
-What do you want?
-Just come down here.
Who are you? You come down too.
Okay.
You're so annoying. What do you want?
Look who's here.
You're the kid from the library.
He's my son.
Say hello to the grown-ups.
Hello.
Hey.
He really wanted to see Billiard Lady.
Me?
What's up with you all of a sudden?
Anyway, I brought some things you can use,
so why don't we bring these up?
Hello, I'm Bom's friend from school…
Great. Good to see you.
You carry the heavy things with me.
Bom and Yeo-reum.
You can just move the small things.
And Jun. You know what to do.
The lights.
Are you giving those to me?
They're nothing special.
Try carrying this.
-It's light.
-Well…
You're giving her
all of this for free, right?
Of course it's for free.
You're giving me all of these?
-It's not much anyway.
-Let's just go up.
-Go up.
-He's the generous type.
That's not heavy. Come here.
Get the big things first.
Come over there. Grab this.
Geun-ho. What are you doing over there?
Come and eat.
Geun-ho.
You can never go outside, okay?
Should we place it next to the bed?
The lights are working well now.
Thank you.
Look at you. You're pretty good, Bom.
I'm the only one who knows
how to do these things at home.
Hey, Bom.
About the part-time job I offered you,
that's between us, okay?
What's with you today?
Does Yeo-reum have something on you?
Like what?
You didn't…
Did you hear something?
So there is something, then.
What do you mean?
Yeo-reum! It's working now.
Did you fix it?
-You can fix things like this?
-What a surprise, Bom.
Tell me something you can't do.
I knew it when I saw you
ripping off that tape.
You're like Macgyver.
Why does he keep talking?
The door downstairs doesn't lock,
so I'll go take a look.
-Excuse me. Here.
-It's fine.
-You gave me so many--
-Hold it.
There. It's sturdy now.
Here.
It's fine.
I also brought you a lock chain.
-You have to keep your doors locked.
-Okay.
You saw the hideous graffiti.
-Please take this.
-No need.
Just think of it as an all-inclusive deal.
-But still, it's too much.
-It's all right.
They are all used products anyway.
Just use them well and return them later.
I almost forgot.
Hey, Jun!
He's bringing it.
I'm sorry.
About what?
He broke open his piggy bank
to buy this for you.
Why are you being so nice to me today?
Yeo-reum.
What I'm about to say right now
is a bit embarrassing for me.
Well…
Goodbye.
My son loves to go to the supermarket
in the morning to buy pastries.
And on his way out of the store today,
he picked up the money. Your money.
He's the one who found it?
Tell me about it.
Isn't it a relief
that my son picked it up though?
Where did he find it?
Well, actually…
-Right here.
-Here?
No way!
He picked up a plastic bag
loaded with money on the street,
thinking that this was
a gift for him from the heavens.
He's read too many comic books.
SEON-A BILLIARD CLUB
But…
Mr. Librarian had it.
That was because
my son heard the announcement
that my dad made,
and that made him realize
what was going on.
After hearing that, he got scared
and ran over to Dae-bum.
And I went to the PC cafe with it…
What's ridiculous is that he went
running to Dae-bum, not to me.
I've been meaning to ask.
Did Dae-bum mention my son
when he gave you the money?
No, he didn't.
I wanted to ask you a favor.
I don't want anyone
to know about what Jun did.
Of course. I won't tell anyone.
Thank you so much.
And I'm very sorry.
I'll be going then.
It's…
It's not Jun's fault.
After all, I'm the one who lost it.
And don't worry.
I'd be too embarrassed
to talk about what happened.
Thank you so much.
If there's anything you need
or something that needs to be fixed,
call me immediately, okay?
Thank you.
SEON-A BILLIARD CLUB
Hey, Yeo-reum.
Look how much better it looks.
It finally feels like a home.
Indeed.
Mr. Bae finally did some good today.
Is that pizza?
-Yes.
-I've been craving this.
I'm hungry. Can we eat it?
Of course.
Hey. Why are you still here
when you're not even cooking ramyeon?
-Get lost.
-Stop being so stingy about food.
By the way, what's the dog's name?
He doesn't have one yet.
Really? Then let's give him a name.
Well, I actually have a name in mind.
What is it?
His fur is snow white,
so how about Gyeo-ul, as in "winter"?
Named after seasons, just like us.
That's brilliant!
-Really?
-Yes.
What? That sounds weird.
How about this?
What about Demian?
"Demian"? Demian, my foot.
You just keep eating your pizza.
Where's Demian?
-You want pizza?
-Hey!
-Don't give him pizza!
-You can't give him pizza!
-Demian can't…
-You like the name, right?
You called him Demian.
-I did? When?
-You did.
-I said Gyeo-ul.
-So it's decided, Demian.
-I called it Gyeo-ul, right?
-She said Demian.
I like Gyeo-ul better.
You see? She likes Gyeo-ul better.
PARKING LOT
-Hey, Jun.
-Yes?
-I'm heartbroken.
-Why?
How could you tell Dae-bum first
and not me?
I'm very upset.
Dad, what about that?
You go bring it.
What's this?
Dad!
-What?
-That.
Open it.
THANK YOU
FROM YEO-REUM
Gosh, this lady.
It's fine.
The Billiard Lady gave it to us
to say thank you.
-Really?
-Yes. You can have it.
-Jun.
-Yes?
You can't tell Grandpa
what happened today.
Sure.
Dad. I'm hungry. Can we also have pizza?
Gosh, you brat.
What kind of pizza do you want?
-Bulgogi!
-Deal!
-You order it. You have their number.
-Okay.
I thought everyone in this town…
No, I thought everyone in
this world hated me.
I don't remember anything else,
but I do remember this one thing.
That is…
hatred.
I wanted to leave this place,
so I wished all my money was gone.
In my world, I was the victim.
And they were the assailant.
But the opposite happened today.
Where did you get those tomatoes?
Your Grandma
gave me these.
Really?
When did she give you these?
Yeo-reum.
Did you know this is where Dae-bum
used to live when he was young?
No.
To be exact, his family ran
the billiard club in this building.
Then who is Seon-a?
Seon-a is Dae-bum's older sister.
Apparently, his older sister was
an absolute genius.
SEON-A
You must have heard about Jun.
It was my fault for not telling you.
More people die from loneliness
than starvation these days.
You should go out and meet someone.
Are you two married?
No. We're not.
He's too competent to be here
working for a countryside library.
You must care about him a lot.
We've spent a long time together.
You're finally going to make it to Seoul.
Come with me.
Subtitle translation by: Jea-Heon Chung