ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, GROUPS, AND
ORGANIZATIONS IN THIS WORK ARE FICTITIOUS
SCENES WITH ANIMALS ARE STAGED
ACCORDING TO ANIMAL WELFARE GUIDELINES
Grandma!
-Grandma!
Please stand back.
Grandma!
Grandma.
Grandma…
CURSED HOUSE.
YOU MUST DIE.
What happened?
What's that?
Hey, this is our building!
Which one of you will accompany her?
Excuse me.
All three of us will.
Yeo-reum.
Bom.
What do I do now?
It's okay.
It'll be okay.
He didn't do anything wrong!
-Please!
-Bring him.
-Wait.
-Please move aside.
-Please stand back.
-Wait.
-Please move!
-Hey!
-Hold on. What?
-What happened?
-Geun-ho!
-What's happening?
Geun-ho, it's going to be okay.
Stay calm, okay?
-Don't worry.
-It'll be fine.
No.
She still feels warm.
Grandma.
Grandma, you can't go like this.
Don't go, Grandma.
What do we do now, Grandma?
ANGOK FUNERAL HOME
Let me know if you need more of them.
Okay.
And you can wear this shirt.
Thank you.
Yeo-reum.
Why is life like this?
Why do bad things keep happening?
-Hello.
Bom.
Are you okay?
Yeo-reum.
You need to come with me
to testify as a witness.
Right now?
Yes. We got in touch with Bom's father,
and he'll be here soon.
Then…
could I wait until he gets here?
Yeo-reum.
I'm okay. You can go.
Hey, come on in.
Dae-bum.
What do we do now?
I mean,
I uploaded the thesis on arXiv,
and Holland read it.
Professor Holland read the thesis.
I see.
He wants to talk to us.
We arranged a call for later today.
-Really?
-Yes.
I'm so nervous as to what he'll ask.
-Eun-mi.
-Yes?
Prepare some sample questions, okay?
-All right.
-My goodness.
VIOLENT CRIMES TEAM
How do you know the victim?
I'm close with
her granddaughter.
Why did the victim
visit the billiard club today?
We weren't supposed to meet today.
I've been teaching her Hangeul these days.
Hangeul?
About the guy next door.
Why was Geun-ho there today?
I don't know.
Did he visit the billiard club often?
Not really, but…
Excuse me, Detective.
My kid has
never been to that place.
Geun-ho.
-Geun-ho.
Are you okay, Geun-ho?
Nothing's wrong, right?
-You're not hurt, are you?
-How did it go?
Geun-ho confessed.
What?
-What do you mean?
-That's ridiculous.
Confess to what?
He's already confessed
that he killed the old lady.
-Take him.
-What are you talking about?
He didn't murder anyone!
Geun-ho.
Geun-ho!
-You didn't murder the lady, did you?
-Take him away.
Continue with the investigation.
-Sir.
-Yes, sir.
-He's just lying
-I know you didn't do it, Geun-ho.
because he's afraid of the detectives.
He's just lying.
-Please stand back.
-Stop.
-What's going to happen to Geun-ho now?
-Look at me, Geun-ho.
Stop it!
-Stop it!
-Take him away.
Hold on, Miss.
-Please don't do this.
-Miss.
-My kid was with me at the time.
-Please stop.
He was having a meal with me.
He was with me when it happened.
-Ma'am.
-Can you please tell them that?
-Let's go outside and talk.
-I saw him.
I saw Geun-ho
leave the billiard club.
His clothes were stained red.
At first, I thought it was red paint.
I was rattled, so I ran into the building.
And on the wall…
SLUT. WHORE. DIE. GO AWAY.
There was graffiti everywhere on the wall.
And…
Ms. Jung was lying on the floor.
Ms. Jung.
LEAVE THIS PLACE
Oh, here he is.
It looks like he's hesitating.
That's how he went in.
And here comes Ms. Jung.
He was inside before she arrived.
He was waiting for her to come.
You said he drew
graffiti here before, right?
Yes.
You should have reported him back then.
Ji-yeong.
Bom's grandmother passed away.
She passed away in the billiard club.
They say it was Geun-ho.
I can't believe what's happening here.
-Hello.
-Hey.
The higher-ups are convinced
that he's the culprit.
The CCTV footage shows him
running out from the building
covered in blood.
-Could you help?
-We also have a witness,
-so it's quite conclusive.
-I'll do it.
You. Why didn't you report him before?
Why?
Why didn't you report to the police
about the graffiti?
Sorry?
They said you knew everything.
Why did you call my mom
to your house without even reporting that?
-Why?
-Why are you being like this, Jeong-hun?
I'm sorry.
If you just reported him.
this wouldn't have happened.
That fucking retard murdered my mom.
-That motherfucker…
-Jeong-hun!
-Calm down.
-Dad.
-Hey.
If you just reported him,
if you just said something,
my mom wouldn't have died.
Fuck!
Jeong-hun.
Don't be like that
when you're in mourning for your mother.
I'm sorry.
Hey, this is all your fault.
You killed my mom!
Come on, Dad. She didn't kill her!
Don't you dare come around here.
You better not show your face around here!
Do you hear me?
-Hey.
-Calm down.
-Come by later.
-Get out of here.
-I told you to get out!
-Calm down!
Dad.
-Calm down.
-Dad.
Calm down, okay?
Please.
ANGOK FUNERAL HOME
Don't beat yourself up
over what Holland said.
Even as it is now,
it's worthy of research.
Hawking Radiation.
You can't provide a solution
to that just yet.
Even Holland said
that he doesn't know.
Okay?
JUNG YEONG-SUK
SON: KIM JEONG-HUN
GRANDCHILDREN: KIM BOM, KIM HA-NEUL
Bom.
ANGOK FUNERAL HOME
Hey, you should eat too.
Okay.
What about Bom?
She doesn't want to eat.
She hasn't eaten anything since yesterday.
You got here fast.
No, don't get up.
I'll stay for a bit.
-Then you should eat.
-Later.
I can't believe this happened.
Did you come here directly from Seoul?
Yes.
What about Dae-bum?
Keep this a secret from him.
A secret? Why would you keep it a secret?
He's occupied with an important…
Keep it that way for the time being.
Okay.
I can't contact him anyway
except through you.
I thought Yeo-reum would be here,
but she's not.
Don't even get me started.
Things got really messy.
Why?
I thought she went home.
QUANTUM PHYSICS
Bom.
Bom, my goodness.
This is all too sudden.
I'm sorry.
I only found out
when I went to see you at work.
Bom.
Why are you here?
You should go eat with Bom.
Bom, get up.
Your friend is here. Eat with him.
Get up.
Why are you being like this?
Can you help her so she can eat?
She hasn't eaten anything since yesterday.
Bom.
Your friend is here. Eat.
Please eat something, Bom.
Stop forcing her.
Your grandma hated seeing you skip meals.
Think about how she'd feel
if she were to see you like this.
Are you going to be selfish until the end?
Eat for your grandma, not yourself.
Here.
What's this?
It's a gift for Jun.
I've had it in the car for a while.
Ji-yeong.
The other one is yours.
You haven't slept, right?
Hey, what's with you today?
I just wanted to thank you.
What?
For driving up to Seoul for me…
and for being my friend all this time.
I mean, this is…
Are you okay?
Anyway, I won't treat you
so harshly from now on.
I'll keep it to a minimum.
But you know, people don't change easily.
See you.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'll end you.
Goodness.
What wrong idea?
Ji-yeong! What wrong idea?
What the…
Get them some more food.
All right.
Jeong-hun.
How dare you show your fucking face here?
-Jeong-hun.
-Get the fuck out.
-How dare you?
-Stop.
-Get out!
-Calm down.
-I'm going to kill him.
-Please calm yourself.
I know you must be heartbroken,
with your mother passing away.
What the fuck did you say?
We know! We know how you feel.
We feel the same way.
-Stop it.
-The hell you do, you pieces of shit!
But!
But please know this.
My Geun-ho…
Geun-ho didn't do it.
-I'm going to kill her.
-Come on, stop.
-Let me go!
-Please believe in me!
Come on, stop it guys.
Please believe me, Jeong-hun.
-Get out!
-Come by later.
-You have no right to be here.
-Get the fuck out of here!
-So just get out!
-Hey!
-Get out!
-Come on.
This is just as hard for us!
-We're barely holding up!
-We know.
I get it. Let's talk outside.
-Hey.
-Come on. Gosh.
Let's talk outside.
-Hey, Seong-min.
-Yes?
Hear me out.
Geun-ho may hurt himself,
but he would never hurt someone else.
How could he have done that to her?
I know, Chang-su.
This is absurd.
But still, you can't come here
and cause a scene!
Why not?
Why can't we?
Our Geun-ho is wrongfully in jail.
How do you think he'll hold up?
What if something bad happens to him?
I get it.
I understand, so let's talk outside.
-Seong-min.
-Chang-su, I get it.
But let's not talk here.
-Let's talk outside.
-This is just so wrong.
They're unbelievable.
-Hello, Professor.
-Did you eat?
Yes. Professor.
Dae-bum is acting strange.
How so?
He kept mumbling
in front of the board all day,
and he suddenly ran to the library.
Really?
Ahn Dae-bum.
Sorry?
Sounds like he found the way
back to his own little black hole.
Let's see what he brings out from there.
-What about Seong-cheol?
-He's taking a break.
Good.
He should be taking a break.
Eun-mi.
Last year's conference files
should be on Seong-cheol's laptop.
Can you send them to me?
I'll text it to you.
Yes, ma'am.
2021 CONFERENCE PRESENTATION
SEND FILE
I sent it.
2021 CONFERENCE PRESENTATION
PROFESSOR LEE
Sir, I've posted it
on the university forums.
Good work.
ANGOK FUNERAL HOME
I'm sorry.
Ms. Jung.
I'm so sorry.
When you get to heaven,
please meet up with my mom.
She would love you.
After my dad passed away,
I asked my mom if she was sad,
and she told me this story.
She told me that life is like
traveling on a bus.
That on this bus of life…
my parents, friends, and acquaintances
are all passengers.
And that one point or another,
they all have to get off.
I sincerely hope you go to a good place
and finally be able to rest in peace.
Okay.
She will go on her final journey now.
Let's wish her a safe journey
with a silent bow.
All bow.
I don't know if my mom
truly believed what she said.
Maybe she had to believe that
to keep herself going.
That parting ways
is a natural part of life.
You may rest.
I'll be closing the door.
Ms. Jung.
Whenever I saw you,
you reminded me of my mom.
I won't forget
everything you did for me.
Ms. Jung.
Goodbye.
Safe travels.
You're home.
I've been waiting for you.
-Can we talk for a bit at my house?
-No.
I have something to give you.
-Please come with me for a minute.
-No, I have nothing to say.
I'm so sorry.
-Why are you being like this?
-Please.
-I won't take much of your time.
-I don't want to.
I'll be really quick.
Come in.
Come on in.
Please have a seat.
What do you want to drink?
Actually, do you want something to eat?
-You're hungry, right?
-No, I'm not.
This.
This is a petition.
Can you please sign one for us?
No, I can't.
Hold on.
Please.
I understand that it may be difficult
for you to sign this.
But please.
I'm grasping at straws here.
When I imagine
my poor son shivering in fear behind bars…
Ma'am.
It's Geun-ho that drew the graffiti
on the building.
But Geun-ho didn't kill anybody.
Stop doing this to me.
Wait! My kid lost
his glasses the day before,
so he wasn't wearing his glasses.
Without glasses, he's practically blind.
How could he have drawn the graffiti?
-Please don't do this.
-Miss, I beg you.
I'm begging you. Please sign this.
Here, sign this.
Do you even hear yourself?
How could you be so selfish?
Bom's grandmother died because of Geun-ho.
That's not true!
When you told me about the graffiti
in the billiard club,
Ms. Jung said
that Geun-ho was a good kid.
And that I shouldn't
report him to the police.
But that Geun-ho went and killed her!
Don't you even feel bad?
How can you only think about your kid?
Geun-ho didn't do it!
Ji-yeong.
-Are you coming from the lab?
-Yes.
You look exhausted.
I'm fine.
Dae-bum hasn't even
been sleeping or eating,
solving problems all day.
Compared to him, I'm not doing much.
I see.
The thing is…
Why do I feel bad?
Why would you?
I called to tell you
that there's going to be
a committee meeting…
and that we need Dae-bum here.
How is that your fault?
Right?
Goodbye, then.
Bye.
Ji-yeong.
Hey, Bom.
And Ha-neul.
Can we talk for a minute?
Bom, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Ha-neul, I'm sorry.
I've never been a proper dad to you guys.
I apologize for that.
I'm never going to drink again
and I'm only going to live for you.
I'll try my best, so please forgive me.
Please give me one last chance.
I'm sorry.
Get up, Dad.
Gosh.
Hey.
We only have each other now.
With my mom gone too,
you guys are all I have.
Here.
This is condolence money from the funeral.
This will cover our expenses for now.
I'm starting work tomorrow.
I'll be coming home late after work
from now on.
I'll really do my best.
Here, take this. I'll entrust you with it.
Take care of Ha-neul too.
I'm sorry.
Take it.
A, B, C, D, E, F, G, H, I, J, K…
KIM JEONG-HUN
KIM BOM
Grandma…
I miss you.
SEON-A BILLIARD CLUB
When I first came here,
I had…
nothing left to lose.
I had no idea how to go on…
and my confidence was at rock bottom.
Then…
I made friends in this town.
Bom.
Jae-hun.
Ms. Jung.
Dae-bum.
They helped me smile again.
Every day I spent here was like therapy.
However…
I shouldn't have come here.
If they never met me,
Dae-bum wouldn't have had to
be reminded of this painful past,
and Bom's grandma would have
lived a long and happy life
alongside Bom and Ha-neul.
I never…
should have come to this place.
Let's wrap up
what Dae-bum is looking into for now.
-Okay?
-Yes, sir.
All right.
Let's not go too in-depth.
Hello.
Welcome.
-Professor.
-Yes?
Is it okay to leave Dae-bum like that?
What do you mean?
He's researching without even sleeping.
That's his true side.
I guess you didn't know.
He can't stand not knowing something.
-Eun-mi.
-Yes?
He's gone into his own world.
Just like old times.
Seong-cheol is the one who posted
the accusations on the forum.
Why would Seong-cheol do that?
Professor Lee told him to.
I think Professor Lee asked the dean
to arrange a meeting with Holland
in order for Dae-bum to meet him.
I mean…
What do you mean by that?
What I mean is
Professor Lee is trying to keep
Dae-bum here to have him
write his thesis.
-Ji-yeong.
-Yes?
You'll have to find a place
to stay with Dae-bum.
Yeo-reum.
Gyeo-ul, she's back.
Gyeo-ul.
Come here, Gyeo-ul.
Have you been well?
He's acting like
he hasn't seen you for ages.
Thank you for taking care of him.
It was nothing.
Gyeo-ul.
Yeo-reum.
I might leave this place soon.
What?
My parents want me
back in the States again.
Did you tell Bom?
No.
Bom is going through a lot, so I couldn't.
I'm immature and childish.
So I don't know if I should be beside her.
Yeo-reum.
I'm afraid
that we'll grow apart.
That I'll be forgotten.
Jae-hun.
Just let those growing apart grow apart.
Just let those who hate
hate you.
But as for me,
I'll treat you as my friend
no matter where or when we meet.
When we meet again,
I'll put on a big smile
and give you a hug.
I'll greet you happily.
I'll ask how you fared
and tell you that I missed you.
To me…
you were a good person.
Yeo-reum.
And…
I'm sure Bom thinks that way too.
Yeo-reum.
Thank you.
Hello?
Seong-min.
Are you happy?
What?
What's this out of the blue?
Why am I unhappy when I'm in Seoul?
Hey, is something wrong?
I miss how uneventful it is in Angok.
Gosh.
Uneventful, my foot.
The town is a total mess right now.
Is this about Dae-bum again?
I don't know what to do with him.
Dae-bum must be sad to hear
that Yeo-reum is leaving soon.
-What are you talking about?
-You didn't know?
Yeo-reum is leaving Angok soon.
Hello?
Ji-yeong. Are you there?
It's been a while.
I missed you.
It's hard, right?
Have you eaten?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for even apologizing.
Yeo-reum.
I know that it's not your fault,
but I blamed you for it.
I kept telling myself I shouldn't,
but I was so resentful…
because I felt so bad for my poor grandma.
It feels so unfair,
so it makes me furious.
When I try to eat, I get angry.
When I try to sleep, I get angry.
Even just breathing makes me angry.
So…
let's see each other later.
Later.
Okay.
Dae-bum.
Hey.
Let's talk.
Wait, I have to read this part.
Yeo-reum is leaving Angok.
What?
Yeo-reum was involved
in a big incident while you were here.
She hasn't told you, has she?
SEON-A BILLIARD CLUB
What did Bom's grandma do wrong?
-Why did you kill her?
-Grandma is in danger!
Run away!
Geun-ho has been weighing on my mind.
Look what he drew on the walls.
I told you it's not him.
Could you tell us what this is?
It really sounds like
he's telling me to run away from someone.
I think someone is impersonating
Geun-ho with this graffiti.
Do you think my kid painted this?
My kid who is in jail at the station?
Geun-ho, you didn't kill her, right?
You killed her, didn't you?
Subtitle translation by: Jea-Heon Chung