The Which Is Yours
I'd like to call Zhang自己
flies
Once again
Is Hongjun sent?
Mengen
I really hope
Lam save you
your every detour
5th但是
Thank you, young master.
Let us go.
Are you a rich person?
Old man.
Su Feng.
Don't forget our position at the domain.
What's that?
Stay here
when you're in joy
Little Horse
Don't be afraid of helpingady to you.
Put down the weapon.
You must seal his mouth first.
Don't let him in.
If so,
Spare blood again.
And soon,
be a nobody and help him.
Hurry.
Let's go.
Brother.
That dateade will always be лишia.
And Tia...?
You will never tell me.
You are pregnant?
No.
I already have a baby.
My mom is gone.
If something happens,
I can still give birth.
Ah.
Just listen to me, Fatty Kang
I've made all know
this world is too cold
Our family
co-op
OK
Can you heal me
Mummy
How are your back pain?
OK
Your back pains
Incredible
It's fine
I walk alone
And you小心
My hands are large
Okay.
I'll leave you, okay?
Lady Jun?
What would be your problem?
That's why I invited you through.
How?
I was afraid of being alone.
I was really afraid of being alone.
I remember when we were little,
we used to go to the lake together.
iba is Playing so ему
Ichi's a little strange.
When we were in the boats,
we met the big things,
plus a book火沙
I didn't know
I'm sorry you.
I neither Leé, nor uncle c게요.
I'm so tired.
Why are you crying?
I'm not going to search again.
It's not a search.
There's a big deal.
Really?
Yes.
It was all recorded from the entrance.
Then it was dropped.
Then I could see the whole hat.
I think there are about 300 people on the mountain.
I think there are two hundred guns.
There's a house on the left
from the entrance.
It's over 10 meters high.
There are ten windows.
There are two windows on the hill.
There are two guns.
It's different from the other guns.
It's a big gun.
There's a house on the right side of the door.
It's over five meters high.
There are five windows.
There are two windows on the hill.
There are also two big guns.
My god.
Wang Ji is so lucky.
My son.
It's hard for you.
You remember it so clearly.
Aren't you afraid?
I'm afraid to death.
But I have a way.
I put all my attention on one thing.
I remember it so hard.
I'm not afraid either.
I'm dead.
Fortunately, there are no war.
Otherwise, these guns and guns
will be in the hands of the Red Army.
Chief.
Actually, we must go in from the front door.
Is there any other way?
Yes.
Where?
In the climbing forest.
Chief.
Go up from here.
Then you can go into the city.
But it's so steep.
Who can go up?
When I was a kid,
I often went to the mountain with my dad.
I went up first.
Then I gave you a rope.
I also said that
this mountain looks scary.
In fact, I caught a lot of enemies.
When the mountain is big,
they will climb over me.
If Gu Azi takes someone to climb up,
and goes into the village,
we will be in trouble.
Our comrades will definitely think about it.
Chief Han.
I want to ask you a question.
Go ahead.
We just go in like this.
They won't kill the old man, right?
No.
Black Pan is Wang Ji's hostage.
He dare not move.
As long as we quickly control the bag,
within half an hour,
Black Pan will definitely be fine.
Okay.
Let's hurry up.
Otherwise,
we will be in trouble again.
No.
To complete this task,
we also need a deep and precise
and brave man to lead the team.
I heard that there is a big battle.
I will go back quickly.
Uncle.
How is the task completed?
I have already taken over the head of the underground party
with the south line.
They have now started to develop
and progress in various fields.
Prepare to cooperate with the Red Army.
I also brought a few gold Yan back.
I have already handed it to the commander.
Okay.
By the way,
I originally asked you to come back.
I asked you to go to the capital city station
to check the situation.
But there are a few tiles
that have been removed for you.
I have already cleaned up the situation inside for you.
Wang Tang Meng.
You said that the team is suspicious of Wang Ji.
Why are you still suspicious?
The team is doing this as if it were a battle.
If Wang Ji comes to attack the six-way station,
we can wait for him to take over the power
of the two-way merchant.
If Wang Ji can't be returned as soon as possible,
then we can be completely sure
that he is the murderer who killed the Lin family.
By then, we will turn around and attack the capital city station.
We will avenge our family.
Follow him.
Hurry up.
Your Granpa has arrived.
Open the door.
Follow me.
Give yourienstre company to me.
Little Granpa,
be careful.
Don't worry.
After all this,
you found his places of concern.
Cut off some extra people.
We can easily find another he is.
Question.
Go.
Commander, I'll go first.
Okay, be careful.
Whoo.
You wanna escape?
I want to run too.
But I can't.
Why do you want to run?
I can go back.
Gu Xiaozi, give me the rope.
I'll take it.
Niu Yuchun, you've earned this d Celestial
while watching給死生活.
Hemlocktin is suitable for newbies.
private
quickly
Grand Tutor
Tools
유 Fat Xu
Jaoduo, the chocolate
is spoken in foreign ancient nut shells.
Tell everyone to come up here.
Después is a high-quality material.
Put it on.
You really are a good-looking man!
Guasa, are you the one who robbed the Grandpa's memory?
Here,
pull this up
and mark it carrying.
At this time,
the doubts can be created
by this.
Everyone, just go and leave.
Go...
May I take your accumulations?
Go.
our theirs.
Go...
Take this and use letter.
I am afraid it'll hold in your eyes.
Open this pack of cheeses and lock them to pick up.
Or we will run after it.
take my life
Brothers
I'm a greedy man
Isn't it beautiful?
OK
Do you like it?
Yes
You can't like it
This is my mother
But let me tell you
As long as you look good with me
You will have a special mother
OK
Your mother is here
They are here
Brother Ji
OK
Go to the apartment
I'll go to the toilet
Go down
Wait for me
Don't wait for me
Come on
One more
Mother
We are brothers.
I can't leave you alone.
What about Zhong Defense 컸?
I want to know what they're doing.
Chai-LanLou.
Who are the的是 beginning of each expedition of course.
Fourth Uncle put his hand on the banquets.
No matter how important it is,
we must eat this well.
Don't shoot!
Hurry up!
The enemy is coming!
Let's get them!
They're coming!
Hurry up!
Don't throw the fire!
I'm the real enemy!
I'll protect you!
You're a tiger!
We're not good at pulling the ice.
Pull the tiger!
I'll kill him soon.
I'm a good guy.
We'll get you out of here.
Get out of here!
I'll be careful.
Hurry up!
The enemy is burning!
Let them go!
Run!
Hurry up!
They're coming.
Let's go.
What's the rush?
They're not open.
They're not even in the warehouse.
They're not fighting.
Open the door!
Hurry up!
Battalion commander,
get the bullet!
The enemy is coming.
I'll take care of them.
Hurry up!
Keep the enemy safe.
We're going to the open gate.
Yes, sir!
Battalion commander!
Hurry up!
It's all my fault!
I didn't know there was a secret treasure!
What's going on?
Let's go!
Open the door!
They're coming!
The enemy is coming.
They're all alive!
They're coming!
The enemy is coming.
Don't shoot!
The enemy is coming!
Let's go!
I'm going to kill them!
Don't shoot!
Be careful!
What's going on?
Let's go!
What are you doing?
You scared me!
Stop!
Don't shoot!
Don't think too much.
Take the machine gun off.
Sir!
Open the door!
Don't you want to take the machine gun?
Hurry up!
Sir,
I'm going to take the handgun.
I'm going to take the machine gun.
I know where to take it.
I'll take it.
Don't be so impulsive.
No, no, no.
I won't take it.
Let's go.
No!
Stop!
What?
What are you doing?
Sail to others first.
Take care of him.
Yes. Alright.
Go
I don't know what I need to do here and as tomorrow.
You can get there,
I will Chandengabadi you,
be care's commander
Theniin got us
Where are yourrounds?
An hour later
Let's go
Director
Hey,
this person
is the ents house
Hurry
Move
Take your ratchet
I didn't you
Take my warum