(Wall clock time signal)
♬〜
(Girl) Ah, the hat is flying off.
(Kaede) Grandpa.
♬〜
(Grandfather) Ah... Welcome back Kaede. Nice to see you here.
Yeah.
Did you meet Kanae?
I missed you.
Mom was coming.
ah….
Did I put it in the wrong place?
I agree. Hehe...
Huh? Blue tiger?
Huh?
A stately tiger
I came into the study this morning.
How did you open the shoji door?
Ah...don't you think he's handy?
I'm glad you didn't get bitten.
Yeah. Well, for that tiger...
There was something about it that made me feel relaxed.
In those eyes that just stare at me
I couldn't help but be drawn into it.
Huh~.
So... what happened to the tiger?
He smiled and walked gracefully again.
Fufufufu…. What? Did the tiger laugh?
(yawn)
He looks really happy...
(Girl) Good morning!
good morning!
good morning! Mr. Madofuki!
good morning. Oh, I can't run in the hallway.
yes!
Hey, what book are you reading now? Daisuke-kun.
<When I was a principal
That's what grandpa was called
〈At the graduation ceremony, the
Hand over a book →
He was a teacher who cared about his students.
Congratulations.
〈My grandfather was so intelligent.
Mr. Madofuki is →
memory loss now
Dementia that causes Parkinson's symptoms →
Suffering from Lewy body dementia
〈The biggest feature is →
It's a vision where you clearly see things that aren't there.
(Even if the people around you deny its existence)
It is extremely difficult to convince
〈Even if it were possible, it would be cruel.〉
(chime)
ᗕ(Iwata) Kaede Sensei.
Ah!
(Iwata) Today I made gateau chocolat.
ah~!
Jean!
Wow!
Mr. Iwata, thank you as always.
Huh!
(Iwata) News from the library...
I look forward to it every week.
Hmm….
“Dandelion Girl”?
Yeah. to meet someone you love
Risking your life to time travel →
This is a story about a girl with dandelion-colored hair.
Huh~. Is it a love that will cost you your life?
It's a wonderful love.
〈I'm sure this book has
It contains my grandfather's wishes.
Mr. Maple →
tonight
There's a national team match that I absolutely can't afford to lose.
How about together?
Watch soccer at a sports bar!
Ah... I'm sorry.
I have plans after this.
Ah... no, that's right...
Ah...
Oh, um... I really have plans!
Um... I wanted to take this to my grandfather.
Seto River….
Takeshi Setogawa.
Emperor of Logic Ellery Queen
Queen of Mysteries Agatha Christie→
A masterpiece by Dickson Carr, the master of impossible crimes.
He is a genius who directly disagrees →
I'm my grandpa's senior.
Ah... Kaede-sensei loves mysteries.
I inherited it from my grandfather.
yes! Hehe...
ᗒ(Kuki/Grandfather) Ah, hmm →
Woooooooooooooooo.
(Kuki) Yes. Well, let's have some water.
yes.
(drinking sound)
Yeah. I can drink it properly.
ᗒI’m home!
Oh...oh Kanae? Kaede?
It's Kaede.
Oh, Kaede, welcome back. Nice to see you here.
Yes, I'm home.
Ah, thank you again for today.
(Kuki) Hello.
Hello.
(Kuki) Having your grandchild here makes me feel better.
However, Mr. Himonya
You still have great hair.
Hahahaha….
Are you jealous?
(Kuki) But my daughter's hair is on par.
First, the length is different and the smoothness is different.
And above all...
The luster is different.
Great answer!
(Kuki and grandfather's laughter)
Because it's always like that
People call me ``Idiot parents.''
(Kuki and grandfather's laughter)
(Kuki) Mr. Himonya
My daughter is coming home today, so this is what I'm doing.
ah.
Ah, thank you very much. Next...
It's next Tuesday.
That's right. We hope to see you again next week.
(Kuki) Thank you very much.
thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
〈Like the storytellers of old →
Grandpa is in this place
I like the name “Himondani”
♬〜
Ah, grandpa...
Yeah….
ah~….
Okay….
Oh thank you.
Today.
There's something I want to show Grandpa.
oh! This is Setogawa Senpai's last work.
We were in a circle together, right?
ah. Waseda Mystery Club.
Wow, that's so nostalgic.
Oh...that time at Cafe Moncheri
We often had mystery discussions.
That moment
It was a time that could be considered my starting point.
Fufufu….
Yeah~. Fufufu….
You got it well.
There are online bookstores that specialize in used books.
It's a treasure trove of rare books.
this is…?
Ah, it was stuck inside the book that arrived.
Wow, that's a lot for a bookmark.
Yeah?
Grandpa, don't you feel some artificial discomfort?
I think this is what you would call an everyday mystery.
Yeah….
Who exactly and for what purpose?
Did you put these four obituary articles in between?
Yeah.
Kaede...could you please let me burn the scent?
Yeah! Hehe...!
♬〜
nostalgic.
I can now see the picture.
Look, right there→
A man with a calm face
Something is stuck inside the book.
But... unfortunately →
The man who is the former owner of the book
He's already dead.
How do you know?
he was alive
The obituary article of my favorite Takesuke Setogawa →
With condolences
It was tucked inside a book I treasured.
However, after his death, his wife
I had no idea it was such a treasure→
As part of sorting out the belongings →
with various books
I sold all of them to a used bookstore.
Why do you say the former owner is male?
Isn't there a case for women?
Hmm…→
“When your spouse dies →
Being able to act calmly while suppressing sadness
If you say, “Because I’m a woman,” →
Will you agree?
In fact, me too →
When Natsume passed away
Because I couldn't do anything.
Kaede: Look!
Yeah?
to Mon Cherie
The members of the Waseda Mystery Club are all there.
There, I was talking to Setogawa-senpai.
He is the former owner of the book.
This is this!
This time it's Queen and Christie's turn.
Oh? Hehe...
Before I knew it, Carr had joined the discussion.
Ah~ Hehehehehe….
Yeah.
Hmm….
Looks like fun.
oh…. Hey! Hey!
Hahahahahaha….
♬〜
(Iwata) Kaede-sensei!
Ah, good morning. Mr. Iwata.
good morning.
Actually, Kaede-sensei loves mysteries.
There's something I really want to ask you.
Oh, something happened?
There's an izakaya called Haruno...
Yeah, ah... I've been there a few times.
My grandfather used to go there.
Now, please calm down and listen.
yes.
Yesterday during the national team match
Apparently there was a murder in Haruno.
kill!?
(Iwata) Yes.
Moreover, my junior from high school
It was like I was there.
ah….
I'm having drinks with you tonight.
How about we join together if you like?
Ah, but if I suddenly go
I'm sure you'll be surprised...
Haha... That's okay. however….
Yeah?
On his side
There are quite a few problems, though.
After all, he's quite a weirdo.
♬〜(In-store music)
that…
Are you Mr. Iwata's junior?
(Four seasons) Yes.
Ah, good. that….
You have 4 minutes and 25 seconds until the meeting.
There's only a little bit left to read until the end.
Ah... yes.
nice to meet you. Please call me by the name below.
The four seasons in Japan are written as "shiki".
Mr. Shiki.
Well, nice to meet you too.
Um, the wind blows on wood
A maple tree with beautiful autumn leaves soon →
My name is Kaede.
Hahaha... Is it a poem?
Huh?
I was drawn to my self-introduction.
It's not hard to understand, though.
when explaining your name
Do you usually say things like ``How beautiful are the autumn leaves?''
yes?
(Staff) What's your order?
I think it's coming soon, so I'll start with three raw ones.
(Salesperson) Yes.
You can drink it, right? Suddenly to me
I just made him drink some weird poems.
Ah, the master of impossible crimes.
Are you Dickson Carr?
Oh, what? What, do you know?
It's ``Four Chests.''
Ah, it's almost the end.
It's pretty good.
Are you really reading it?
Isn't it just a fashion thing?
What about Carr's early works these days?
It's stylish all around.
What's wrong with reading cars?
Ah, no, it's not the car's fault...
Hmm…→
A classic, full-scale mystery translated into reality.
I thought it was a good read.
What do you mean?
If I listed all the reasons, it would take me all night.
I'll just give you the conclusion.
The stage setting, character setting, and translation are all outdated.
It's hard to remember the characters' names.
Rex Fortescue
Adir Fortescue →
Percival Fortescue
Jennifer Fortescue...
ah~…!
(Four seasons) of the Fortescue family
How to know the full names of all family members →
It is a very difficult task.
Even if Imhotep's daughter Lenisembu appears
It just doesn't enter my mind.
ah~….
Haha….
Shiki-kun of Japan's four seasons
Are you a bunch of prejudices?
Kaede with beautiful autumn leaves
Don't you think you've changed?
No, it's often said, but that's exactly it.
That's it.
No, you too...!
Yes, that's it for both of you!
How can I do that when we meet for the first time?
Iwata-senpai: It's late.
I'm running a drinking party and I'm late.
Isn't that impossible?
Iwata Sensei, I'm sorry, but to your junior.
May I say one more thing?
The Fortescue family has ``rye in their pocket''￫
Imhotep's daughter Lenisembu
A character from ``Death Comes Last.''
Even if it’s a name that’s hard to remember or something made up →
After all, a classic translation mystery
You're reading it!
Thank you for waiting.
Ah, thank you very much.
Three draft beers.
I'll do it. yes. yes~!
Sorry for the delay!
cheers! Yes~ Cheers. cheers!
cheers….
Excuse me, three Bolognese, please.
(Salesperson) Yes.
(Four seasons/Kaede) Huh?
No, the bolognese here is
It's so exquisite that you can't recreate it at home!
Me "Cooking Papa"
You have all the volumes, right?
This is my first time hearing it.
See you again next time about ``Cooking Papa''.
Ah... it looks like this from high school
I was building a baseball battery.
Hey!
It's about time
Can we talk about the incident?
That's right. That's the main topic.
I heard that you were present at the scene.
yes.
Maybe it was due to the national team match last night.
There hasn't been much news yet →
This is definitely... murder.
This is Haruno's simple floor plan.
Are these A to V customers?
(Four seasons) That's right.
I was sitting in H.
(Voice of the Four Seasons) Where can you watch the national team games?
It was a lively and crowded place.
(Shiki's voice) And 3 to 3→
The second half begins with the score tied →
A while later, 10 minutes before 9:00 p.m.
From here, by the Japanese representative
Three furious shots are fired.
Oh, those 10 minutes were amazing!
So?
(Shiki's voice) The onslaught is over
The enemy controlled the ball →
It was exactly 9 o'clock at night.
(Nezu) I'm going to the bathroom.
Yeah.
(voice of the four seasons)
Nezu, who was sitting in F, stands on the toilet.
Ah... Nezu is a member of my theater company.
I'm a regular customer of Haruno's...
This guy is a member of a theater company.
Hey!
This is an important point, so please listen carefully.
Nezu went to the bathroom for about 3 minutes.
I returned to my seat.
🖥️(Live) Japan is shaken.
🖥️Ahhh, I got a vertical pass!
Nezu.
(Four seasons) Nezu?
(Nezu) Huh?
Was the toilet empty?
ah….
please.
(Nezu) It's empty.
Ou.
(Sound of turning doorknob)
(knock)
(Four seasons) Wow! Huh!?
It's... Are you okay? OK!?
Did something happen!?
♬〜
I was convinced.
This person is already dead.
Were you the first to discover it?
Huh? So? What happened?
Did you call the police?
First of all, try not to make a fuss as much as possible.
I went to the kitchen.
The landlady rests her chin on →
Chicken dish with spices or something
New menu →
I was writing it down on paper...
Toilet... There's a man covered in blood in the toilet...
(Shiki's voice) As soon as you saw my unusual behavior →
I threw away the paper I had.
Sigh….
Then three police cars arrived and the scene was sealed off.
An interview was immediately conducted.
First is V, a man who can see the path to the restroom.
After halftime is over
Maybe 8:30?
After that until around 9am
I don't think anyone is doing anything.
(voice of the four seasons)
Next, the woman at the table next to us, I.
After Japan's three shots in a row
I remember that the person at the table next to me went there.
That was my friend Nezu-san.
that's right.
In addition, ``Until 9 o'clock
Everyone in the store remained seated.''￫
"Honestly, it wasn't anything like that."
Testimony follows.
So the body was discovered just after 9 p.m.
Except for Shiki-san →
The last time I went to the men's restroom was →
Just before that, I went to relieve myself.
His name would be Mr. Nezu.
And what's even more problematic...
Nezu said, "I will remain silent."
He refuses to give any testimony.
Because of that, I was taken to the police.
Did your friend take you away?
What is the identity of the victim?
Probably, but I don't think it's clear.
``I don't have a driver's license or anything,'' he said.
I heard the policeman's voice.
What about the murder weapon knife?
This too
I heard about the forensic investigation →
The male victim is →
Store the knife in your waist belt
Apparently he was wearing a leather case.
Then who is the culprit?
Did you grab the knife from the victim's waist and stab him?
That's how it will be.
It's bad for the four seasons, but for some reason →
That man named Nezu
Didn't he kill her impulsively?
Three minutes is enough time to commit a crime.
And there's the thing about keeping quiet...
It's really suspicious.
Nezu is an extremely serious person.
I guarantee that you have a good personality.
He's not really the kind of person who could kill someone.
There must be a reason to remain silent.
Can I make time tomorrow?
There is someone I want you to meet.
(Four seasons) It's big.
(Iwata) That's amazing.
♬〜
What are you doing?
No, that...
A visit to Kaede-sensei's parents' house...
What are you talking about? I'll go.
No... wait a minute...!
Entrance Okay...
Well, the kitchen and toilet are okay too.
Ah, should I wear slippers?
Ah, the cushion...!
(chime)
Ha... yes!
The above is a summary of the incident that occurred in Haruno.
The victim kept showing up in the bathroom.
At the same time, the culprit also disappeared.
(four seasons) and no one
The perpetrator and victim were not seen.
Don't you feel any artificial discomfort?
Yeah….
Haruno?
The offal stew over there is the best.
When there are fewer customers→
I want you to teach me how to study
The landlady asked me well.
What were you studying?
High school graduation certification exam.
Well, it seems like she dated a bad guy a long time ago.
Arrested for taking part in multiple burglaries.
He wasn't the main culprit, though.
I guess I was forced to drop out of high school.
It's like Bonnie and Clyde.
Hehe... The small and nimble proprietress...
It must have been the Japanese Bonnie.
The landlady's partner... shall I call him Clyde?
What about Bonnie & Clyde?
in the 1930s
This is a couple who repeatedly committed robberies in America.
Nezu-kun, who was a regular, too.
I often talked happily with the landlady...
I see. There was a murder over there...
So, what kind of story will Kaede weave?
Mr. Nezu is not the culprit.
The real culprit is Clyde, the landlady's partner.
The victim man
Find out about the landlady's past in some way →
He was threatening me.
The landlady couldn't stand it anymore
He asked his former partner Clyde for help.
(Kaede's voice)
Clyde was among the customers at the store last night.→
Kill the man and lock the door from inside →
He escaped through the top of the toilet and returned to his seat.
Yeah... Clyde's appearance isn't bad.
But there is a big contradiction.
Will the landlady ask Clyde for help?
And my castle that I worked so hard to obtain.
I don't think they would choose it as the scene of a murder.
…surely.
In short, there is another story X other than this one.
Now, Kaede, could you please let me burn the scent?
♬〜
I saw a "picture".
…Is that so?
Who is dying in the toilet →
This is Clyde, the landlady's former partner.
The victim is Clyde...?
Huh...?
Grandpa. Tell me about the world you see now.
♬〜
(grandfather's voice)
Japan's shooting offensive is in full swing...
Clyde has arrived.
The purpose is probably the landlady's money.
Was it Clyde who was threatening the landlady?
I noticed his presence
Only the landlady saw her behind the counter.
(Four seasons) Normal When a man who stands out comes in
I think you'll notice.
The customer's eyes are on the TV →
Shiki-kun over there
While thinking, “Why are you getting so hot?”→
Eating edamame.
Ah... Shiki-kun over there...?
In other words, no one was paying attention to the door.
that's right.
The landlady was most afraid of a commotion inside the store →
Call Clyde to the bathroom.
♬〜
(Clyde) If you tell me what you've done with me
A store like this won't go out of business soon.
Hey. Hey...
Hurry up and give me the money.
(Landlady) Go home.
♬〜
Hey, are you dying?
I don't have any money to give you...!
(Grandfather's voice) Clyde pulls out a knife.
And at this time...
(Grandfather's voice) Nezu-kun has arrived.
(grandfather's voice)
He grabbed the knife to save the landlady.
(stinging sound)
(Clyde) Uh...
(Nezu) Ha...!
Ha!
Too much momentum
I stabbed Clyde in the back.
In other words... Nezu is the culprit?
Please wait!
It's possible that the landlady stabbed Clyde.
There is, right?
The landlady had been strangled.
In that state, I was on Clyde's back.
It's almost impossible to stick a knife into it.
Was the landlady really strangled?
You don't understand, right?
No, I can say that.
Kaede: I thought I was the landlady.
Could you please touch my aching neck?
And when I supported his arm on the desk...
(Iwata) The landlady is
It wasn't like I was resting on my chin...
But!
There is no proof that Nezu stabbed him.
Then why the silence...
So, suppose...
Suppose Nezu stabbed Clyde →
why is that guy
Did you make me go to the men's room?
If it was a men's restroom, there shouldn't be a problem.
Shiki-kun, what was the gender ratio of the customers at Haruno last night?
There were 18 male customers and 4 female customers.
More than 80% of customers are male...
Men's restroom after the game
There is a high possibility that there will be a rush of customers.
So why Clyde?
Found it in the men's restroom?
(Iwata) That's the men's toilet.
Because it was a crime scene...
If so
Will Nezu-san say, "I'm free?"
(Iwata) What do you mean...?
(voice of the four seasons) Why is he?
Did you make me go to the men's room?
(grandfather's voice)
If it was a men's restroom, there shouldn't be a problem.
(Iwata's voice) More than 80% of the customers are male...
Clyde was supposed to be in the women's bathroom.
(Landlady) Are you okay? Are you okay?
(Kaede's voice) After Nezu stabbed me.
Clyde is still alive...
The landlady tries to avoid being seen as much as possible→
Clyde is still alive
I think they took her into the women's restroom.
(breathing heavily)
Because it's okay.
I'll do something about it then...
Go back.
(Kaede's voice) Mr. Nezu→
After seeing Clyde in the women's restroom.
I returned to my seat.
♬〜
(Grandfather's voice) But Clyde
He showed his ferocity again.
(Landlady) Wow!
(piercing sound)
(Clyde) Ah...!!
(Grandfather's voice) The landlady pushed me away
The knife in my back is stuck deep →
It completely severed Clyde's artery.
♬〜
(locking sound)
(grandfather's voice)
The landlady locks the men's toilet from the inside →
Escaped from above.
Like when she was Bonnie.
So, the landlady's legitimate defense...?
Maybe so.
But his scars
When Nezu-kun stabbed me →
It was already deadly
There is a possibility.
(Iwata) Huh? but
Did the landlady go into the toilet or come out?→
There is no such testimony, right?
she
He should have known what happened in the bathroom.
Shiki-kun
You're seeing evidence of that.
picture…?
The men's restroom where Clyde is.
When you want to prohibit use →
What would Kaede do?
There was a sign that said, ``Do not use due to malfunction.''
Pepper!
that's right.
The landlady was in a panic
The kanji for "malfunction" did not appear.
So I had no choice but to write it in hiragana.
As a landlady, at this stage →
How to read the instructions on the toilet
I didn't go.
So the landlady had no choice but to throw away the paper.
Then why?
Has no one seen the landlady?
The landlady came out of the toilet→
Contains Clyde's belongings
I was carrying a trash can.
As always.
Same as when I come out after cleaning the toilet.
A sight as usual...
Chesterton's "The Invisible Man"
I guess we haven't seen the landlady.
I just wasn't impressed.
But Nezu-san was different.
Nezu.
(Four seasons) Nezu?
(Nezu) Huh?
Was the toilet empty?
ah….
(Grandfather's voice) The landlady and Clyde are in the bathroom.
Nezu-kun must have been confused.
The landlady just came out
"Don't worry" I nod →
Nezu-kun was upset.
I just accepted it as ``It's okay now''.
please.
(grandfather's voice)
That man should be in the women's restroom.
that's why….
It's empty.
(Grandfather's voice) There shouldn't be anyone there.
If it’s a men’s restroom… I think →
I had no choice but to send Shiki-kun to the bathroom.
But Clyde's isn't the women's restroom.
It was discovered in the men's restroom.
ᗕ(Officer) The victim is a man in his 40s.
In the men's toilet
With a knife stuck in his back...
(Grandfather's voice) Nezu-kun must have thought so.
After that, the landlady
I think I may have dealt the final blow.
Sorry...
But I don't know why.
Why is Nezu silent?
The motive is temperature.
Mr. Nezu saw the landlady being attacked.
I guess I thought so.
The landlady and the store that she values ​​above all else.
I want to protect it.
Fufufufufu….
(Kaede's voice) When I realized
Maybe he stole the knife.
Mr. Nezu
Because I thought the landlady was the culprit →
I'm still keeping quiet.
Why did you go that far...?
I liked it...maybe it was.
The way he smiles when he talks to the landlady
I still remember it.
Nezu-kun, unless she shows up →
I vowed not to say anything.
Even the sound of the landlady crying
You can hear it, right?
I didn't stab her intentionally.
He's not bad.
Kaede. Give a handkerchief to the landlady.
♬〜
No... to Kaede-sensei.
I can't believe there was such a great grandfather.
Fufufufu….
There are words that I believe in.
"Everything that's happening right now is correct."
This is how I interpret this word.
“Every event is a story.
And it's a happy ending.''
Hmm.
《Everything that happens in the world is a story.》
《Words my grandfather used to say》
♬〜
《But it feels strange...》
(sound of breathing)
♬〜
(Emergency team member)
``A bloody Kaede is lying here.'' →
I have received a report.
<As far as I know, that is
It was the first vision my grandpa had.
Kaede?
Yeah. I'm home.
I wonder if there's something to talk about? You can tell by looking at that face.
Grandpa...
Grandpa…→
The truth is that I'm sick
Don't you understand?
It’s not reality…→
I'm always seeing visions →
You're really aware of it, aren't you?
But aren't you just pretending not to realize it?
Kaede is right.
I am unmistakable
He is a patient with Lewy body dementia.
One morning, when I saw this pillar,
Just like a skilled shrine carpenter
As if carved into a mikoshi →
It used to have detailed carvings on it.
But when I touch it
It doesn't feel like it's carved at all.
It's extremely smooth.
Making such elaborate carvings in one night
It's simply impossible.
That means...→
My eyesight is completely unreliable.
Well...
I'm curious about what's happening to this body.
As I flip through various books →
There are scarlet Lewy bodies in my brain
I'm convinced it's spreading.
If Poirot has gray brain cells →
I am the owner of scarlet brain cells.
Then... then why... →
always tell me about visions
Are you going out of your way to ask me?
When I'm talking about visions
Kaede cries out and gives a thumbs up.
While changing his expression
It makes me smile.
Then I
I can feel Kaede's existence with certainty.
Huh... why?
I will be forever...
I'll always be by your grandpa's side, okay?
Well...
I wonder if you'll understand if I say this.
I used to face Kaede→
Honestly it won't be that long
About my future behavior →
There was a time when I spoke my true feelings.
At that time, even myself
I'm so proud of how well I feel.
I think we talked for about an hour.
However, for some reason, Kaede remained silent →
Suddenly it disappeared.
That Kaede... was a vision.
So miserable
There's nothing sad about it, right?
♬〜
Since then I
I decided not to talk about my illness.
An elderly person with dementia who cannot hold a proper conversation.
It can't be helped even if you think so...
That's what I thought.
♬〜
《I'm sorry I didn't notice you》
《Grandpa is
It wasn't like I lost my intelligence.
《Much more than me
I accepted my illness.