(DNA Test Report)
The master's real child...
is not Tsubaki
but me.
No way.
I love you, Nao.
I can't hide my pregnancy,
but I can't let my real identity be revealed.
I have to find the truth before then.
That door is only opened on a special occasion.
The day of The Twilight Tea Ceremony.
My last will...
In case a grandchild
with Takatsuki blood appears,
I shall inherit all the property.
What is that?
Only Tsubaki shall take over Kougetsuan!
Let's get started.
Okay.
In this sweltering heat,
(Kougetsuan)
The Grand Master's tea ceremony.
(The Day of The Twilight Tea Ceremony)
It about to begin.
Osugi, sake, quickly! Slowly, quickly!
Slowly and quickly?
Carefully and quickly.
Get the cups too!
Yes.
It's quite a big event, isn't it?
In the Twilight Tea Ceremony,
the guests are seated at sunset.
And entertained from twilight...
It is a tea ceremony
to enjoy the light of the night.
Please don't be rude to our guests.
Yes.
Is this the Moonflower?
Yeah. I put yellow paste inside.
When it's getting dark,
yellow is the color which catch your eyes.
(Moonflower)
In the night,
looking at the moonflower,
I hope it'll remind you of
the full moon above the night sky.
Moonflower and the moon...
How beautiful!
This sweet characterizes you.
Nao.
The Hotaru no jouga you made before...
I think I've tasted this somewhere before...
It was made by a girl named Sakura.
Ho!
What?
Nothing. Nevermind.
Everyone, hurry up! We're running out of time.
Yes!
When the front door is opened slightly,
it means the event has begun.
And...
Today, that room will be unlocked.
(Hamabe Minami)
(Yokohama Ryusei)
=Cursed in love=
Professor, please enjoy!
Thank you.
Thank you for coming today, Takigawa-san.
It's my honour to be invited again this year.
Look, they're perfect for each other.
Nao-san... um, I...
Haseya-san's...
I'm sorry I'm so impudent coming here.
But I got Tsubaki-san's permission.
No, I'm sorry about that...
Isn't that the girl, who crashed the wedding?
Yes.
Oh, she's the one they're talking about.
She must be pretty thick-skinned, mustn't she?
I apologize but...
did you know that
the roots of the cherry tree are very thick?
Sometimes they can even lift up the concrete.
And the stronger and thicker the roots are,
the more beautiful...
the more plentiful the blossom is.
Without such that brave,
there's no way someone can continue this shop.
I see, Kougetsuan-san...
Now that you has a strong-willed bride,
it means more and more prosperity.
I hate how beautiful they are.
That's true.
Tsubaki-san is the only one
who can make lines like these.
I don't think I'll ever be as good.
I want to remember these forever.
All the sweets that Tsubaki made.
Another year, another great pastry.
Hmmm, this is brilliant.
Delicious!
That was all very beautiful!
That's right.
After the sweets,
we need to prepare the main room
Nao-san!
What's wrong? Jojima-kun.
Nao-san,
something is bothering you, isn't it?
What?
You can tell me anything.
I want to help you.
I'm not good enough?
Oh, look, I...
I still owe you for the...
For the warabi-mochi, so...
Ah... thank you.
Really... anything I can do to help, just let me know.
Then...
Promise me you will reopen Shimaya one day.
Yes.
Where? Where is it?
Where the hell is it?
What are you doing in my room?
Grand Master...
I didn't know you were there.
If you raised your voice...
Is this what you're looking for?
(Will)
You're still as sneaky as ever.
You thought you could sneak
past me during the tea ceremony.
It was a night like this.
When I first started
suspecting your character.
I was at a tea ceremony and came home late.
So I cut through the garden to go back to my room.
I saw you with another man...
When I realized that's not Itsuki,
For the first time I...
saw someone resemble a monster!
Doesn't Tsubaki look just like...
that man?
Well...
Please give me your will!
Ugh!
Why did you betray me?
When I first saw you,
I'm the one who took you in this house!
That's why I didn't kick you out.
You were from Kaga's top families,
daughter of the Ootori family,
As beautiful and intelligent as a butterfly.
I thought you'd be
a good landlady for Kougetsuan!
But you were not a butterfly at all.
You're an evil snake,
who will swallow up this shop!
But who...
made me be like this?
I married into this family 25 years ago.
I was full of hope.
I thought I'd be loved by Itsuki-san,
and spend everyday happily with him.
That I'd dedicate my whole life to this man.
I had made a vow in my heart.
And yet...
Itsuki-san
never loved me.
He won't even touch...
Not even once!
After all, Tsubaki is...
Even your father-in-law didn't look into it.
Because you don't want to find out
that Tsubaki is not your real grandson, do you?
He's your umbrella for that rainy day.
Why?
Why do you want to take everything away from me?
Stop!
It's Tsubaki who's going to take over this shop!
No matter what!!! Ahhh!
(Will)
Grand Master...
Tsubaki-san, I'll go change the candles
in the tea room before dinner.
Yes, please.
Grand Master?
Once a year, after the tea ceremony...
The Grand Master drinks
only one cup of tea in this room.
That's true, I've seen it.
Mom... we have to go get mom.
In a garden full of camellia flowers.
There was a woman.
Tsubaki-san, should we take the guests
to the main room?
You're right.
Oh, by the way,
Is Nao still not back yet?
It's a bit late, isn't it?
No one is here.
Listen, Tsubaki...
One day you're going to take over this shop.
Promise me!
Are you going to let
Tsubaki-san take over Kougetsuan?
That's what I intend to do.
That girl,
I think Tsubaki calls her Sakura.
Yes.
I think everyone thinks she's Sakura.
That's good.
I wish for her...
They've kept us waiting for a long time.
Don't you think it's about to start soon?
Yes.
Why are you here?
What are you doing?
Can I ask you the same.
What are you doing
in the middle of the tea ceremony?
Can't you tell?
I'm airing out the kimono.
You have to do it once a year.
If not, they will be ruined in no time.
This room was The Master's room, wasn't it?
I heard that he was stabbed to death here.
by the craftsmen who worked with him.
It was just some work-related jealousy.
He didn't do anything wrong.
But people think he died of an illness, right?
I heard from one of our long-standing customers.
The master and that craftsmen,
They were close.
That they were in love with each other.
I've love him... for a long time.
Please give me back my Itsuki-san!
Noisy.
Shut up! How dare you say that to me?
Love... Two people in love...
Tell me. Am I supposed to
forgive them because of that?
Although he's in a committed
marriage with his wife?
In the beginning,
I trusted him that he hired her as an artisan.
Oh my! What a lovely sweet!
Did you make this?
That's amazing!
Thank you.
But it was this woman.
The two of them shattered my heart into pieces.
They tore my beautiful wings off
and turned me into a monster!
And those two...
didn't get punished at all.
I hated them.
From the bottom of my heart.
Are you sure, Tsubaki-san?
Did you really see her in your father's room?
You saw them fight, didn't you?
You saw it, didn't you? Didn't you?
Who? Who was it?
Sakura's mother.
Excuse me!
Are you okay?
Hey, be careful.
Yes, sir.
Did you get hurt?
Does anyone... smell something?
That's why...
That's why you framed her.
Did you also stab The Master?
No, I didn't.
Tell me the truth!
You have no proof whatsoever!
I will take you to court!
I'll say that I saw you that day.
What did you just say?
I am...
Sakura.
I am that artisan's...
(To Sakura: I didn't do anything)
I am the daughter of Yuriko Okura.
Thank you, Nao-san.
You've finally said it.
Hey.
You heard that, didn't you?
That girl...
I think Tsubaki calls her Sakura.
I think everyone thinks it's Sakura.
That's good.
I wish for her...
to be free of the curse of this shop.
I hope she can be free to make her own pastries.
Tsubaki.
Sakura.
Let's hurry up!
Tell everyone!
What are they doing?
There's a fire!
What? What?
Hey, where's the fire? I don't know.
But the main house...
We have to evacuate our guests!
Yes!
Now...
Did you say you are Sakura?
You are...
Nao...
You're lying... aren't you?
15 years ago.
What happened in this room?
I wanted to know the truth...
I know my mom didn't kill The Master.
I'm....
I'm here to prove my mom's innocence.
Did you lie
in front of the hanging scroll?
All of them... All of them...
All of them!
Why?
Tsubaki.
No.
Tsubaki-san, we've got a problem! There's a fire!
The whole house is filled with smoke.
Everyone have been evacuated.
Except the Grand Master...
His room? Did you check the Grand Master's room?
I can't get close to it
because there's too much smoke.
I'll look for him. Yamaguchi-san,
you take care of the shop.
Yes!
Tsubaki!
You'd better get out of here quickly.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'll wait here, for Tsubaki!
Everyone, please calm down.
We're checking the escape routes.
The shop's fine.
All right, everybody, this way!
Over here! Where's Tsubaki-san and Nao-san?
What?
Are they still in the main house?
Tsubaki-san...?
♪Pinky promise♪
♪ If you lie to me♪
♪I'll make you swallow a thousand needles♪
♪I cut my finger♪
(Will)
♪ I've won♪
Grandfather!
Are you there, Grandfather!
Somebody... somebody, please help me.
Grandfather...
Waiting for Tsubaki.
We can't get there.
It burns my throat.
I can't breathe.
Tsubaki.
Sakura.
Right.
You've come to take everything from me.
I've always been afraid
that this day would come.
Tsubaki-san is as good as the Grand Master.
He treasures this shop!
That was just another lie to deceive me, wasn't it?
To her, I'm the enemy of her parents.
But...
No problem, we'll take care of it.
He loves sweets and he's a purist.
We've got two idiots here, so we'll be fine!
Why?
You always gave me the words I wanted...
Nao.
I'm afraid Tsubaki won't forgive me.
But...
Nao, I love you.
Everything about Tsubaki,
I just love them all.
That's all I have to tell him before I lose him.
Will you marry me?
Nao. Nao.
I've found my first...
happiness.
Nao-san! What are you doing here?
Let's go!
I'll be here.
I'm waiting for Tsubaki.
We don't know when the fire will get here.
What?
Oh no.
What's wrong with you?
Oh no... just that...
Wait... quickly...
Nao-san!
Tsubaki.
Nao-san! What's going on?
I don't know. She collapsed suddenly.
Let's get out of here now.
No.
Wait... no...
(Kougetsuan)
We're all trapped.
By the curse of the shop.
Nao.
Yuko-san.
Thank goodness.
You're awake.
Excuse me. This is Hanaoka.
Nao is awake.
Can I get a doctor here, please!
I...
I was so shocked to here you were in a fire.
But I'm glad that you're safe.
Fire...
Tsubaki... Where is Tsubaki?
As for Mr. Tsubaki...
I don't know the details.
- What...
- But with the fire...
I heard that no one died.
So I'm sure he's fine.
Thank goodness.
Is Tsubaki awake yet?
Still...
Ugh... it hurts.
Are you OK?
What about my baby?
Well.
I guess... I didn't make it.
A mom like me...
You must hate me, right?
That's not true.
Don't say that!
It was no one's fault!
It was no one's fault. It's okay.
I've had my punishment.
Nao-san shouldn't come back to Kougetsuan.
She'll just continue to suffer if she get back.
It'll be okay.
Please don't cry.
(Kanazawa Daiichi Hospital)
I don't know what I'm supposed to do from now on...
Did Tsubaki get back after that?
Or...
Two days since the fire at Kougetsuan.
The locals are mourning the partial loss
of the historic main house of the building.
I heard you managed to save the tools,
which are considered municipal cultural assets.
Here it is!
Our young master save this set.
Risking his life in the flames,
After rescuing the Grand Master,
he went back to get these tools.
The tools which belongs to the proper successor.
I wil not let anyone take over this shop.
Tsubaki protected it.
I'll be here waiting for Tsubaki!
I've been deceiving Tsubaki all along.
Of course he won't forgive me.
Mom...
I'm sorry.
I couldn't do anything.
Because of that woman...
Even though I figured out that
she was the one who frame you...
I'm sorry...
Sis, are you hungry?
Here, you can have one.
Thank you.
But now...
Go ahead!
Sweet...
Delicious.
Really?
Thank you.
Haruka!
Mommy!
Nao-chan.
Why...
the meal I just ate..
was so bland.
But these sweets...?
Nao-chan.
What do you want to do now?
Do you want to go back to Kougetsuan?
What I really want to do...
I...
I just want to make sweets.
I want to go back to that time.
Making sweets was so fun.
I'm so happy every time I finish one...
All I have...
is just the love for making sweets.
Let's forget everything.
Including Kougetsuan...
I love you.
And Tsubaki.
It's all right... I can forget.
I'm sure... I'm sure...
(Kougetsuan)
(Three months later)
And finally, take the sweet paste
place it in the centre of the flower
by chopsticks.
Now you have the autumn wildflower,
the cosmos.
Wow, it's beautiful! It's beautiful!
Next month we will be making the peony.
I'll come! Me too!
Me too...
What a silly idea, a Japanese sweets class.
As the master of the shop,
this is not your job.
What's wrong with trying something new?
And I'm not the master yet.
I'm just filling in for the Grand Master
while he's in hospital.
And Nao-san.
When are you going to stop looking for her?
I heard you're asking around
all the shop in this prefecture.
What's the point of finding out now?
The day of the fire.
You chose the inheritance
of this shop over her.
That was because...
After the fire.
I was unconscious for ten days.
When I woke up,
She's gone.
Why do I want to find Nao?
I'm not even sure myself.
I don't know whether this feeling is love or hate.
The one you should be focusing on,
Isn't there anyone else?
(Takatsuki)
Excuse me.
Thanks for holding a class just for me.
No.
Tsubaki-san!
Tsubaki-san?
Thank goodness!
I'm really sorry.
It's my fault.
Please don't apologize anymore.
I did that on my own...
Don't worry about it, really.
You picked a very bright red color.
Oh, did I do it wrong?
I'll redo it right away.
Shiori-san, do you like red?
You wear a lot of red kimono too.
Ah... yes.
Since I was a kid.
It cheers me up
and makes me stand out.
Stand out?
I have two sisters.
They're both beautiful and charming.
Compared to them, I'm so plain and boring.
So if you wear red,
I think people will notice me more.
For my father,
he said "Don't wear it, it doesn't suit you".
I'm sure everyone think so.
I don't think...
Why would you assume that?
It's my own opinion.
I like it a lot.
You can't say that, Tsubaki-san...
(Haseya) We're very excited to
become a family with you.
Thank you very much for everything.
With my daughter scarred like this,
I won't have been surprised if you said no.
Oh no... it was an accident.
For Shiori-san...
I will make sure she doesn't have to
face any guest, please don't worry.
I'm sorry, this may be old-fashioned, but
I'd like Shiori-san to a be homemaker
as much as possible.
Shiori?
Why do you assume?
I like it a lot.
Today.
I brought you some cold peonies
as they were in bloom.
Excuse me...
Excuse me, has anyone else been here today?
Oh, that wasn't there before.
I wonder who did that?
Autumnalis Cherry.
Sakura.
Nao!
Sorry.
I knew it!
I can't get married.
There's something I really want.
Shiori, come here for a minute!
I don't want to!
"You've got nothing to show for it".
"The sooner you get married, the better".
Your words,
I've always believed in it, I've never doubted it.
But I...
I want to wear a red kimono!
Set me free.
Nao.
(Will)
I'll sue you.
"I saw you that day.
You have to crush anyone who gets in your way.
(Kougetsuan)
Please...
Do you want to work for us?
Yes, I've run away from home.
Can you put it here?
But why...?
You may not remember Tsubaki-san.
Two years ago at a painting exhibition.
It was the first time I met Tsubaki-san.
What?
No one cared.
At a time when I was thinking
"I don't know who I am after all"...
This camellia,
why are there no leaves?
It's said that a fallen camellia is a bad omen.
Oh, but that's...
Because the camellias are so beautiful.
Some say it's a superstition, spread by
the greats of old to keep them to themselves.
I like it better...
Because it's beautiful.
Interesting.
I like it and I'll take it.
Please...
Please hire me at Kougetsuan.
About me...
I don't want to give up now.
Please.
If you don't think you have the right qualities
We'll get rid of you soon.
That's...
I'm sure you'll be out in a month.
I...
I'm dying to do my best.
(Autumn 3 years later)
(Kougetsuan)
(Chestnut cake)
Go ahead.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Shiori.
A little.
You have a customer who's looking for Shiori-san?
Yes.
He listens to me without hesitation.
He was so happy.
At first I could barely say "Irasshaimase".
Now it's my...
Oh, it's a shop sign.
That's encouraging.
Jojima.
What is this colouring?
No, I thought the more vivid the better.
There will be no more products.
Be careful.
Yes.
Tsubaki-san, it's almost time
for the Kouwakai tea ceremony.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yamaguchi-san,
could you please continue with the molding?
Yes...that's right.
What sweets do you want to serve
at the Mayfair Pavilion selection meeting?
I'll leave that to you too, Mr. Yamaguchi.
Yes, you can.
He doesn't make many sweets
for the shop these days, does he?
You don't have a choice.
I do everything on behalf of the Grand Master.
I'm a lot busier than I used to be.
My nails are such a mess.
No, you have to look after it properly.
Sorry.
The landlady does it herself...
It's my dream.
I'm going to do this for my daughter-in-law.
Oh no...
I'm really enjoying working here...
My words make my customers happy and responsive.
That's it...
We've been here for three years.
Nothing with Tsubaki-san?
Huh... it's no use.
The landlady...
A seductive scent that will make any man swoon.
Sometimes you have to take the initiative.
Shiori is...
It's very attractive.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
Um, Tsubaki-san...
The next holiday...
Hmm?
Excuse me.
Ah... then I'll take this.
Oh...
This is the money I owe you for this month.
You're a stubborn man.
Then.
Tomorrow, you'll start
helping with the main pastry.
Yay!
Huh, but why all of a sudden?
You've been here for four years now.
And those bright colours on Jojima.
I believe that one day it will be an advantage.
Oh... wow.
Come to think of it, Nao-san was a pale colour.
Tsubaki-san, about Nao-san...
I chose this shop over Nanazakura that day.
(Hamabe Minami)
Tsubaki!
Are you okay? Hey! You, go to the back!
Yes!
Everytime I think about her
The same scene always comes to mind.
A small Japanese sweets shop
in a quiet town.
That's where she makes pastries every day.
Forget all about this world
She is free to create.
Three years...
It's time to put it behind us.
I'm sure she's already looking forward to it.
Tsubaki-san...
You're happy, aren't you?
What do you mean?
The sweets we will be serving for the next year...
They've decided to go to another shop.
Oh no...
In a shop that makes very interesting pastries.
What kind of shop is it?
Indeed...
I think it's called "flower vase".
"Hanagasumi".
(Hanagasumi)
Male It looks delicious.
Thank you very much.
We've decided on the sweets from the May Festival.
Okay.
Do you think he'll notice your sweets?
Tsubaki-kun is.
Maybe... but no matter.
I'm going to ask Kougetsuan to disappear now.
(From the fiance to the enemy)
Why did you disappear without saying a word?
I am Sakura.
Until the dream comes true, it's still not...
(Emotional interference)
I will always be by your side.
Tsubaki, hug me! Please!
Shiori-san.
I won't forgive, if you don't take responsibility.
Get out of my way!