I want you to put Fifi in the star section.
You can go on with "The Certifieds."
As for us...
- We are--
- We are the-- The Verifieds.
- Super? Super!
- Ya see? Super!
And to all the teachers,
we have gifts for you.
There's no one in this world
that I look up to
except for you.
Time for our surprise!
- The Panty Droppin' Award!
- Yes!
Get the juice.
Poor kids. They must be so tired.
I'll take this too.
Preggies can be picky.
Who's preggy?
Huh?
Then in just one click,
the whole world will know
your dirty little secret.
What's this?
Lost and found.
Who's this?
What the hell? It stinks.
Duh, it's a fart.
Did you expect to smell perfume?
Excuse me.
Where are you going?
You stink!
As human beings,
it's normal to lose stuff.
Wait up!
But not lace panties.
Diana!
Jennifer...
Why are you Sir Dax's favorite?
Why do you care?
You have a lot to explain.
Give me that.
- Give it to me.
- No.
Wait,
is that the panty from the chat room?
Mind your own business!
You already ruined my plans earlier.
Now, you wanna ruin my night too?
Hey!
My twinnie ain't doing anything wrong.
It's you who's being a bitch here.
Wait, what's going on?
It's Diana.
Such a busybody
who keeps running her mouth.
At least I don't do it with older men.
What are you trying to say?
Whatever it is,
it's fake news.
- Give me that.
- No.
- Give it!
Give it to me!
- Jen--
- What the?!
What the hell?!
Hey!
It's also normal for people to find
the things you lost.
Move.
Except maybe for
a panty with the initials...
JD?
Jennifer?
Dimaculangan?
Yuck! That's yours?
You fucking stink!
Jennifer.
Whatever it is you're doing with him,
I'm telling you now,
- it's not gonna end well.
- Stop speaking English!
Jen...
you're still a minor.
Please, just stop it!
I just don't want you to end up
like me, okay?
I don't want you ruining your life
because of sex.
Hey, girl! How's it going?
I can't hear anything.
I know, okay?
I know this is a bit confusing.
But trust me.
I felt it once too.
I just don't want you to end up like me.
- Like what?
- Knocked up by the wrong person.
Okay?
You're pregnant?
You're not a virgin?
Hey!
This is not about me.
Okay. Don't you get it?
I'm warning you.
Maybe he's just grooming you
because that's what pedophiles do.
Jennifer, I'll help you.
We'll help you.
- We'll report Sir Dax to...
- Wait. Wait.
Jen?
And Sir Dax?
So that's why you're Sir Dax's favorite!
No.
Wait. Hold on.
- That's not--
- Yes.
Yeah.
I caught them the other night.
And sooner or later
the whole school will know.
Jen, I'm telling you.
Why didn't you tell me?
Jen...
Jen, you have to stop
this nonsense with Sir Dax.
We'll help you. Promise.
Jen...
Jennifer!
What are we doing here?
Can we stop first? I need to go to
the bathroom. I can't hold it in.
You know what,
- let's go back. Let's just go home.
- No, we're already here.
Diana, I really can't--
Shut up.
I can feel it coming.
Save your energy.
Let's do it again.
Aren't you tired?
I'm all fired up.
Let's just go.
Are you there yet, babe?
- Wait a sec.
- I'm getting all sweaty here.
Move! I really need to go poop.
Shit! Jennifer--
Shit!
Let's go.
Where is she?
Jennifer! I really have to go.
In that moment,
- The Certifieds realized two things.
- Jen?
Jennifer?
Jennifer? Are you there?
- One,
- Jennifer!
some things are better lost
than found.
Jennifer!
- Two,
- What a pity.
why are bathrooms in Pacaque too far?
- Pity your ass.
- Let's find Jennifer first.
Jen? Jennifer?
Jennifer,
you know I get scared pretty easily.
Jennifer!
Fuck, Fifi!
It's so stinky!
Can't you just--
hold it in?
Just five more minutes.
Hold it in!
How?
Fuck, it smells so fucking bad.
Hold it in. Can you just--
- ...be a few steps away.
- There. You happy?
What a brat.
DID YOU FIND HER?
This is my fault.
Jennifer's gonna come back. Don't worry.
Maybe--
maybe she just needs some time to think.
She's right.
Your daughter can be pretty mean
but she's still our friend.
Don't worry, Ma'am Jemma.
I'll ask Pops...
to help us find Jennifer.
Thank you.
Ma'am Jemma.
Yes?
I'm really sorry
but I've been holding this for too long.
Can I use your bathroom?
Sorry, girl.
What?
Sorry.
There you are.
Girl, it's okay.
Just let it all out.
No one's looking.
But girl,
when you're done
and you're feeling okay, just tell me.
I'll take you home.
I don't want to. I can't go home yet.
What?
Where do you plan to go?
I don't know.
Maybe if only--
if I can find
some place to stay.
A friend's house, perhaps?
Someone kind enough...
to take me in...
while I'm having a hard time.
Even just for a few days.
I just really don't want to go home.
A couple of days will do.
Hey.
Hey, girl.
Are you asleep?
Well, you said you didn't want to go home.
I know!
Let's ask Diana for help.
She's from Manila, right?
I'm sure she knows a lot of--
No.
And besides,
she has other things to worry about.
Plus, we aren't that close.
Where will you stay then?
At Fifi's?
Don't you get it?
It's only the two of us here.
Maybe I can stay with you.
Sorry.
At your place, if it's alright.
I don't want to force anybody.
I just really don't want to go home.
If it's just okay with you.
Sure, you can stay with us.
But tell your mom, okay?
I don't want to.
Alright, just stay at our house.
I'll tell my mom
to prepare your clothes and food.
It's okay. Cry it all out.
Don't be shy, Jenny.
Bring some food home for your mom.
Ma,
Jen is going to stay here again later.
We're going to finish a project.
Why not stay at Jennifer's so Ma'am Jemma
can help you out?
She's busy with her other man--
--mandatory seminars.
All the teachers are required to attend.
- Alright. I'll call your siblings.
- Okay, Ma.
Eat a lot, okay?
Let's just wait for them.
Engaged!
Fifi...
love...
Rafael!
You have a guest.
Who is it?
A member from your basketball team.
Right, Pops.
That's my friend.
Wait up. I'll just freshen up.
Fifi...
love...
Jeff.
Will you marry me?
Yes, I do!
Rafael!
What's taking you so long?
Your guest is waiting outside!
Jeff, I appreciate that
you're asking for permission.
Of course, sir.
It's for us anyway.
Just make sure you get home before curfew.
Yes, sir.
I'll make sure to take good care of him.
Alright.
Nice.
Thank you for letting us use
the court, Chief!
- Chief! Chief! Chief!
- What?
- Chief! It's about Vicky's kid!
- What about?
He fell through the sewer again?
No, sir.
Then what?
Have you seen him?
Dumbass.
I should be asking you!
Let's go. Let's look.
This kid always goes missing.
Ma, do you think I can
handle the responsibility?
You? Of course!
You can do it.
Take care! Bye. I love you.
- Please get home safe. Love you!
- Love you!
Ma, thank you for inspiring us.
You are my pride and joy, Ma.
- I love you, Ma.
- I love you too.
Have you tried climbing here?
Dumbass!
Don't point your fingers! They say there's
a spirit living in that tree.
Really?
Yes! Here, bite your fingers. Like this.
- All of it.
- Then?
And then you go back home.
You're so annoying.
Hey.
Sorry.
But...
Thank you, really.
No worries.
Alright, cut the drama.
As if I have a choice?
I'm kidding.
That's a joke.
Just promise...
that you'll go home once you're okay.
Hey.
One moment.
It's Anton.
TRIPLE DATE LATER WITH THE GUYS
AND THEIR GIRLS. EED SOME LOVING. CARPS?
Carps?
What does that mean?
As in the fish?
Maybe it means carpet.
Are we going to have sex on a carpet?
You're so gross.
Girl...
can you come with me?
It's my first time meeting his friends.
I'm nervous.
You're going without even knowing
what ‘carps' mean.
Are you sure
you know what you're getting into?
Or he's the one getting into me?
Watch your mouth!
You'll never know.
Have you done it?
Like I said,
I'm still waiting for the perfect moment.
When I turn eighteen.
Just be sure
you'll be responsible for it.
So girl, are you coming?
Hell no.
I still don't even know what 'carps' mean.
Besides,
I'd rather have my date here.
With the spirit in this tree.
I'll find him.
Who knows, maybe you can
find a cute guy there.
No, thanks.
- Come on, it's fun to have a love life.
- At this state I'm in? Really?
Okay.
I'll go on my own then.
Ready, babe?
Let's go.
Boys!
- Hey!
- Yo!
Meet my new girl.
- This is Nicole.
- Different girl again, I see.
No, bro.
She's the one.
Wait, let's drink to that.
Babe,
can you dance for me?
I'm shy.
Come on, babe. For us?
Okay.
- Let's dance.
- Go, babe!
Drink up!
Shot! Shot!
Shot?
Shot!
It tastes bad!
- Are you alright?
- It's bitter.
Babe.
I'm so lucky to have you.
I'm tired, babe.
Are you okay?
Just tired.
So lucky to have you.
Thank you.
C'mon, bro, drink up!
Cheers! Cheers!
- Here, babe. Have a shot.
- Okay.
Cheers! Cheers!
Cheers!
- Bottoms up.
- It's bitter.
Drink some more!
Drink up, we have a lot.
She's hot, bro.
Small tits, though.
I'm good with small tits
but nice ass.
Point taken.
But here's a legit question.
Would you still hit that after she pukes?
Of course!
A pussy is still a pussy.
Even if she's drunk.
Still good as fuck.
But I won't kiss her though.
- Fuck, bro. That's nasty as fuck.
- Fuck you, man.
You'll just jerk off?
Yup!
I can go from here, babe.
I'll just walk home.
Thank you.
Can I get one more kiss?
I feel like
this is the right time to tell you that
you're the one for me.
I want to do it with the right person.
Wait.
I thought we'll wait until my birthday?
You said
that you love me, right?
Super.
Isn't it that
if you love someone,
you want the person to be happy?
Yes.
Then make this sad boy happy.
What?
You're sad?
Not anymore if we do it now.
I really want to be with you.
Do you want to be with me too?
Yes.
Super.
Wait.
It's okay.
I don't want you to worry.
It's just that...
it's my first time.
And believe me,
you're doing it with the right person.
Don't worry about it.
This is just one of the many things
that we're going to do together.
Okay?
We got this, babe.
Okay.
Okay, let's do it.
Babe...
Babe, we're here.
Where are we?
In Sta. Lucia.
I can't let people see my car in Pacaque.
My dad will kill me.
Let's go.
Okay.
It stinks.
TV!
Shit, shit, shit!
Wait!
Now?
- Get on with it.
- No kiss?
That's it?
Is this it?
It is, right?
As they say,
you find the things you lose
when you least expect them.
In Nicole's case,
Expectation?
Lost.
Reality?
Found.
Our BFF needs help.
I imagined my first sex to be magical,
only for him to finish in five minutes.
His dick doesn't even come close
to an inch.
We have something for you.
This is extreme booze.
Are you ready to get wasted tonight?
Ready!
♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
He's just a boy with a small dick.
Let's go, girls!
Let's go!
Shit, look at this.
Please report to
the principal's office immediately.