The information you requested , Young Master
I heard that when Lin Shenling was in the military academy
That 's how overbearing he is .
But those people say
Lin Shenling is an alcoholic young man .
I also like to visit the kiln on weekdays
This is interesting
It seems that there is someone else under this skin .
Continue to check
Don 't let go of any clues
Yes
I heard that Lin Shenling is not happy without wine
I just got a bottle of foreign wine
Bring it over quickly and taste it with the participants .
I don 't know .
You also need to drink to help you play chess
Last time at the suburban warehouse
Didn 't Marshal Zheng buy me enough drinks ?
What warehouse is it ?
Why don 't I remember such a thing ?
I remember
The reference is
That time Zhou Ziyu took you away .
Don 't talk about this .
You can hear about the Jade Beauty of Condensing Fragrance Courtyard
I heard she was the top player there
A song is worth a thousand dollars
Yuyan has long been a good person
Now they 're the top player
Shen Xinyi
And this is old news three years ago .
It seems that the young marshal is not well informed .
It 's your turn
Young Marshal 's move is extreme
There must be a backup .
Does the participant think this is a dangerous move
Playing chess is the same as being human
Anyway
You can 't let the other person know your thoughts .
Isn 't it true
Nature
Once the queen is captured
The King is also in danger
I just don 't know
Can my aunt be counted as a queen ?
This Western Chess
How can we consider our situation ?
Furthermore
Even if the queen is captured
I can also translocate my car
How should I respond when I participate ?
Harsh conditions for translocation of the king car
But I 'm looking forward to that day
It 's a relief .
Hope for the next life
You can be yourself
If you 're still here
It seems that the fire
The burning is not complete enough .
Who is this ?
Father
This is evidence delivered to your door .
Isn 't this the Xu family 's housekeeper ?
You 're still alive
You are mistaken
Small
I never knew anything about the Xu family
Father
I 've interrogated him
He won 't say anything .
This kind of person
It 's more useful to be dead than to be alive
Do you mean
Father 's meaning
That 's what I mean
I 'd rather kill a thousand by mistake
Not a single one .
Didn 't I say you don 't bother me ?
Xiaofei
Do you remember who he is
It 's okay if you don 't remember
But I remember
He is the housekeeper of the Xu Clan
It 's the person with Xu Junyou
What are you trying to say
Don 't you know
Possession of the son of the traitor Xu family
What 's the end ?
Xu Junyou is dead
Don 't forget
That fire was started by your Zheng family
Is Xu Junyou really dead
Your Zheng Family attacks
There is still a living person
This world
If you are not afraid of ten thousand , you will be afraid of the event .
That 's right
How are you doing
Is there any discomfort left ?
Don 't bother the young marshal
It 's much better
Just because there is no attack doesn 't mean it 's fine
This medicine
When there is no attack , it is no different from ordinary people
But if it happens
Getting more painful every day
Except for this antidote in my hand
There is no other way to cure
Coercion and inducement have been used
Zheng Shaoshuai
What do you want to order
Very good
As expected of the woman I liked
Jong
My guys found this in a hospital
I want you to kill him yourself