Entering the Bridal Chamber
Ye Xiaofei
Did you ever lie to me ?
I 'm not
Did I tell you the answer ?
Get out of the way , get out of the way , get out of the way
Rang Rang
Performing official duties
Yield , yield
Yes , yes , yes , yes
Rang Rang
Get out of the way
People inside listen
You are surrounded
Participation
Open the door quickly
Come out and open the door
We hit the door . Did you hear that ?
Open the door
If you don 't open it , you will hit the door
Nickname outside
Ye Family Married Daughter
Young Marshal Marries Wife
A match made in heaven and congratulations on engagement
The talented woman and her beauty are enviable
Nickname outside
Tonight is the engagement party of the eldest miss
Everyone move quickly
Now clean up the house
OK
Miss , you are back
Young Lady
If you are not strong enough
It fell down with a light touch
Young Lady
Master instructs you to dress up as soon as possible
Your engagement banquet with Shaoshual Zheng in the evening
Will be held on time
Where are my clothes
The Master said
Use the set left by the former lady
He won 't even make me a new dress
This
Master says time is too short
It 's too late to prepare
Go on .
Yes
This makes you look like a bride
Los Angeles
I 'm back
Welcome to Participate
Participation
Marshal Zheng learned that you arrived in Los Angeles today
Someone has specially sent you an invitation .
I invite you to attend Shaoshual Zheng 's engagement party in the evening
All four major families will be present
You don 't know something .
These four great families control the lifeblood of the whole city
The people of Los Angeles want to make a living
All depends on the four major families
Got it
I 'll be there
This is Marshal Zheng 's thoughts .
Please accept it
Get it for me
Don 't move and be honest
What is it doing
Don 't move
Say
Who sent you ?
Why do you want to take poison ?
Take it back for examination
Don 't let him die
Yes
Walk
Stop
Who told you to pick it up
Report Acceptance
This is evidence
What is your name
Just call me A Jiang
From today
You are their captain
It 's Time
It 's time to go to dinner
Hurry up
Yes
Young Marshal 's engagement party
It really opened my eyes .
Yes
After Zhou Family
The Ye Family wants to get closer to the Zheng Family .
The Zheng Family is truly worthy of it
The head of the four great families in Los Angeles
Young Marshal 's wife
Your wine has arrived
Isn 't my father here yet
I haven 't seen Master Ye
Go on .
Yes
This Marshal Zheng is really dignified
Yeah
Let me go over first
OK
Xiaofei
You are beautiful today
Thank you
This dress was left by my mother
If she is in the sky
See how I am today
You should be happy too .
Congratulations
Congratulations Congratulations
Lin Ginseng received
This seems to be the newly appointed Shen Ling
I heard that this participant is one of the best individuals
Become the most valued person at a young age
It 's just too sharp
You said you would listen to Marshal Zheng from now on
This is Lin Shenling
It 's Lin who 's late .
It 's also Dashuai Zheng 's way of hospitality
That 's it
No , no , no
Lin Shenling
You came
Just in time
Let me introduce the participants .
This is the dog Zheng Tian
This is Ye Xiaofei , the eldest miss of the Ye family
Also Inuko 's fiancee
Lin Shenling
Nice to meet you
Shen Ling just arrived in Los Angeles
Stranger
I 'm afraid there are many uncomfortable places .
My life is free
Unrestrained
Nothing uncomfortable .
Zheng Dashuai
Actually , I 'm here today
I fell in love with someone
I don 't think the commander will stop you .
Where to participate
Since it 's the person that Shen Ling likes
That must be the best among the best .
If at my son 's engagement party
Can make a good marriage happen again
Isn 't it a much - told story ?
OK
Choosing the best among the best
That
I choose her