=A Deadly Loop=
=Episode 13=
What's the matter?
I didn't see anyone rush out.
Luo Changsheng.
Just died.
Died.
Do you know him?
He's Luo Changsheng.
He's in cahoots with Jia Bonian
and Liu Yangchu.
What's going on?
Got hit and died.
Detective Qin.
What are you doing here?
I'm assisting this gentleman.
He said something's wrong
and asked me to the scene.
I didn't expect to
bump into this guy
halfway in this alley.
At the fireworks plant,
I saw this suspicious guy
carrying a gun
and looking for someone.
I suspected
he was involved in the explosion.
I was about to go up to him,
but he ran away as soon as he saw me.
I chased after him with Yangchu.
Unexpectedly, he got hit and killed.
Hey,
who was driving the car?
Him.
How should I address you?
Fang Xuewen.
He's the one
who asked for your help?
Yes.
Yangchu.
Call the hospital.
Okay.
Mr. Fang.
You can't leave here yet.
I need to get someone to handle this.
Sorry.
I can't stay here now.
Someone died here.
No one is leaving this place.
Detective Jia,
I can prove
that Mr. Fang did not intentionally
hit him.
No one is leaving.
This is the rule.
Besides,
his identity remains unverified.
How about this?
I'll take Mr. Fang to the car
for a rest.
He's of no use here anyway.
Detective Qin,
listen to me.
Luo Changsheng was in cahoots with them.
But they had infighting.
We must figure out a way
to leave here now.
Otherwise,
we will be their next targets.
Believe me.
Mr. Fang,
please calm down first.
It's quite clear
that they don't know your identity yet.
I will find a way to help you get away.
Before that,
don't panic and mess things up.
No one answers the on-call line.
At this hour,
all doctors were at the explosion site.
The injury on your neck.
What happened?
I accidentally got hurt.
Mr. Fang,
before things are cleared up,
you cannot leave here.
Detective Jia,
we have an emergency.
No.
Mr. Fang.
Let me ask you.
Do you know the person
lying on the ground?
No.
Then why at the explosion scene,
he was aiming a gun at you?
What?
What exactly happened between you?
I don't know what you mean.
Qin Yaochuan.
Did you notice his injuries?
The marks on his neck were just made.
It's quite strange.
Detective.
Half an hour ago,
I just arrived at the scene by car.
I've been talking
with your station officer.
I have no idea
who would
point a gun at me.
As for the injury on my neck,
it has nothing to do
with this explosion.
I really can't stay here now.
I must go home to my fiancée now.
How about this.
After I've dealt with my family affairs,
I can cooperate with your investigation.
Alright?
Before that,
Detective Qin can follow me.
Okay.
I can go with you.
Yangchu,
stay here and wait for support.
No need.
Detective Qin can handle it.
What are you really afraid of?
I've told you.
Nothing.
Let me tell you.
I've been doing this for over 30 years.
When one's feeling guilty,
I can tell it with just one glance.
Detective Qin,
do you believe what I say?
Detective Qin.
I knew this is fishy.
Save me.
Jia Bonian,
put the gun down.
Qin Yaochuan,
what is this?
Do you really believe
this person's nonsense?
Yangchu,
disarm him.
what are you waiting for?
Don't you see he's pointing a gun at me?
Yangchu,
it's your show now.
I'm sorry.
I didn't
want it to end this way.
Please forgive me.
I'll repay you in the next life.
Who is it?
Look how scared you are.
Senior.
Why are you here?
You know why.
Did you put the note on the table?
So you know everything.
Well, people
all make mistakes,
right?
Did Jia Bonian teach you this?
Nothing to do with him.
It's all my fault.
He just...
He just covered it up for you.
Knowingly breaking the law
is also a capital offense.
Senior,
I'll do
whatever you want me to do.
You are too serious.
Jia Bonian and I
have long been colleagues.
His apprentice is my apprentice.
Are you saying
that you'll just keep it to yourself?
You are a smart person.
You know what to do
from now on.
Master,
I'm sorry.
To my surprise,
that Fatty Xu is the sliest one.
He hid a trick up his sleeve.
Right, senior,
can you spare Detective Jia?
After all, he is my master.
If he doesn't die,
you
and I
both have to die.
Then
how do I explain this to my superiors
when I go back?
Let me tell you
what to do.
(It is him.)
Alcohol merely compounds sorrow.
Enough is enough.
Mr. Fang.
Speaking of your skills,
I really
respect you.
So what concerns you
has something to do with me?
Do you remember that fortune stick
you interpreted for me a month ago?
Fortune stick?
Birds are nesting in the trees.
Villains plot and set fires.
With restless hearts and busy minds,
all plans go to waste.
Well,
you totally called it.
My fault. My fault.
No worries.
I don't blame you.
If anything, I blame myself
for trusting that woman too much.
Wait a moment.
My buns are ready.
Wait here.
Buns.
Alas.
Mr. Fang.
Try the buns I made myself.
Mr. Fang?
♪The wind brightens the moonlight♪
♪Yet it cannot cover the past♪
♪Meeting you stirs my thoughts♪
♪A lifetime journey awaits♪
♪While petals remain fragrant
at fingertips♪
♪I cherish our bonds in my heart♪
♪You've given my days a purpose♪
♪A grand dream, monumental and vast♪
♪Boundless world, beyond our grasp♪
♪Love and hate,
the absurd path we tread♪
♪Once you look back♪
♪It shall last forever♪