[Put Your Head On My Shoulder]
[Preview]
Do you think I'm cute?
Cute
So cute
[Episode 13]
We meet again. What a coincidence!
Yes
There's something that I'd like to ask
Do you think there's a pure friendship
between a man and a woman?
You're staying with Gu Wei Yi,
but you two are not a couple
So I'm wondering about it
Or you guys...
No
We're just friends
But when a man stays
with a woman, they might...
Absolutely no
Senior
Why did you ask? Are you into Gu Wei Yi?
Yeah
Oh yeah
He said he'll lunch with me.
Why didn't he come?
I thought he's in the old campus
We moved here long time
ago, didn't he tell you?
No
Maybe he thinks I'm not important...
He thinks it's not important,
so he doesn't need to tell me
Yeah, as you're not
doing the experiments
Gu Wei Yi
I'll go get him
You're so slow, don't eat
You...
I haven't taken my lunch yet
I'll buy you a treat
Where's Si Tu Mo?
Let's dig in
-What's wrong?
-Let's go out
-Didn't you want to go out?
-What's happened?
The food at the canteen sucks
You look like trying to run away
It's on me. Want to go?
Sure
Let's go
Wait
I need to send the meal box to Ke
-Let me call him to get it himself
-What?
My mobile phone
I left it at the canteen
As well as my meal card
I'll kill you if my phone's gone
I'll kill myself
Your phone is with you, huh?
Hello
Your friend's phone and
your meal card are with me
I'll go get them now
I'm back to the lab for something,
see you in the lab
Okay
Gu Wei Yi is keeping it
and he's back to the lab
Let's see him after lunch
I've promised Ke to go for a movie
Help me put it in the dorm
Okay, let's go for lunch
I must have something expensive
No way
I have no money
Gu...
How? Is it cute?
It's so cute
How could you let
Prof. Jiang chase it out?
Don't bring me into this
Do you think I'm cute?
I'll come to you if you don't respond
Okay
Cute
Are you Gu Wei Yi's friend?
Prof. Jiang
Looking for Gu?
-I want to get something from him
-Where's he?
-I don't know
-I'm here
What are you doing there?
Thinking
Thinking?
Alright
Take your time
-Waited for so long?
Just a while
There you go
Thank you, I'm off
Where to?
Dorm
-What time will you go home?
-I don't know
-Let's go back together
-I don't want to disturb you
It's alright
-I...
-I'm not alright
What's wrong again?
Jealous again?
I didn't do anything
Class
Let's call it a day
It's about time
Okay
Professor, I'm off
See you
Zhou Lei, wait a moment
Stay here
Clean the lab
thoroughly
Prof. Jiang
Why me?
How dare you ask?
Your kitten messed the whole lab up
Can't you see it?
-You must clean it up
-I...
Let me do it
Prof. Jiang, he wants to clean it
Aren't you ashamed?
Look at Gu Wei Yi and look at yourself
Oh, no!
Are you going to give
him an extra lesson?
Stay here for the extra lesson then
Take your time
What's your trick?
-I'm waiting for someone
-Who?
I got it
Clean it then
I'm off
Take your time
Love can make one do everything
I'm leaving, take your time!
Bye
Xiao Gu
-Why are you here?
-Waiting for someone
Waiting for someone?
Call her and ask her to come down
She didn't pick up
Whom are you looking for?
Let me bring her
It's alright
I'll wait for a while
Now you're here, don't be ashamed
Are you waiting for her?
Is she the girl you
mentioned that day?
No
You scared me
They are a lovely couple
You can't make them apart
They're a couple?
You know them?
The guy waits for her everyday
They'd bring many books along
when they went out
They study even when dating
I think they're going to make it
Stop!
What are you doing in girls' dorm?
I left something here
Call her to bring it down
That's crap!
Miss me!
Gu Wei Yi, what brings you here?
Waiting for Si Tu Mo
Sorry for that day
That day?
What did he do to you?
We went to Mo Mo's house
and cooked porridge for him
Don't be afraid
You helped him, didn't you?
He thought I helped you to get
Mo Mo and he's angry with me
You were trying to bring us together
It's all my fault, sorry
I accept your apology
Fu Pei
Let's talk
We should've gone for a fight
for what happened before
Did you tell Si Tu Mo
about you and Wang Shan?
We have made it clear
You meant...
Gu Wei Yi
I seldom see you like this
We've been living together
in the dorm for 4 years
You only look human today
Answer it
We have made it clear
She doesn't like me and
I don't like her either
We're apart
She could
fall for someone else
I could be with Wang Shan too
We can't stop each other
Really?
Of course
Who do you think I am?
I was hurt by Mo Mo and
it left a shadow in my heart
Why are you laughing?
You snatched my girlfriend
You're such a scum
Was she your girlfriend at that time?
Almost
I feel like giving you a whack
Let's fight then
Don't call her Mo Mo again if you lose
Are you crazy today?
You called me?
Why didn't you pick up?
I was taking a shower and
my phone was in the living room
Are you home?
-Why didn't you tell me?
-Why should I?
Alright, bye
She hung up on you?
Mo Mo is not easy to handle
Alright
Si Tu Mo
Si Tu Mo, I won't call her Mo Mo again
Insane
Do you think I'm cute?
Cute
So cute
"Cute my ass"
You have the keys
Can't you tell it's a song?
No
Listen
"If I had a wand"
"I can be big, small or pretty"
"I want to get a house"
"full of comics and chocolates"
"If I had a machine cat"
"I'll call it Doraemon"
"A hopter and time tunnel
can bring us to everywhere"
Stop it
Is the juice nice?
Try to drink more than 10 bottles
Drink it with a mug?
I did use a mug
Si Tu Mo
What's wrong?
Aren't you working in
an adverstising company?
Why did you only look into the flavour?
What are you looking at?
Show you something magic
No, thanks
Take a look
Come on
The orange juice under zoom 2000X
What is this? Why is it moving?
Microorganism?
Let me see
Not microorganism
It's tiny particles in Brownian motion
Your cutie suddenly appears
Do you think I'm cute?
I'll come to you
if you don't respond
Get back to your room! You are disturbing me!
For you
What's this?
Take a look
I don't want it
I thought it was sold out.
Where did he get it?
I love it
Gu Wei Yi
Finally, you bring it back
Let me try it
Let me see
Gu Wei Yi
You're living outside
So?
You are the only one
who lives outside among us
Now we have an honorable task for you
Not interested
Prof. Jiang stops me
to keep the kitten in the lab
He's extremely strict these few days
Are you willing to
see the kitten homeless?
Yes, I am
What an emotionless killer!
We received the client's message yesterday
They have changed their
spokesman to a new artist
His name is...
Lin Zhi Cun
Yes, Lin Zhi Cun
Jie Er
Find out his information and sort it out
Okay
So, we should change
our thinking as well
Don't think he's famous
like super star Zhao Xue Yu
Don't think about
the difficulty of shooting
Focus on the creativity
Li Na
Get several proposals
done in these few days
Okay
One more thing
There's graphic design competition
We have distributed the message in OA
You may have a look if you're interested
Gu Wei Yi
Why are you here?
Buying books
The perspective of advertising?
Are you sitting for advertising?
Just for fun
For fun?
I don't think so
Let me think
Who works in an advertising company?
I know
I'm off
Don't go
-I haven't finished
-Take your time, I'll go there
Why did you buy the book?
She always gets mad
without reason recently
I'm wondering if it's related to her job
What's wrong with you?
You said you stopped...
I feel happy for you
Finally, you're growing up and
know how to take your initiative
But do you think you can
find the answer from the book?
Why not?
Only several conditions
will make a girl mad
Can't eat or sleep well
and the menstruation pain
I don't think so
Well...
Tell me what happened recently
Lin Zhi Cun is quite handsome
Really?
Send me the picture
-I'll send it to the chat group
-Okay
Look! Is he good-looking?
Look at it
-Is he good-looking?
-Not bad
Look at his mouth
Do you want to kiss him?
No
You're loyal to Fu Pei
We are not...
What?
-We're not a couple
-Who is your boyfriend then?
Look at your face
Tell me!
-Go back to your seat
-No way
See ya
Are you in love?
No
Liar
Your face told me that you're in love
Or you met
a flirt?
Cute
So cute
This is what happened recently
That means Si Tu Mo was angry
because of your senior
It's easy
She gets jealous
Prof. Jiang told me the same too
But she's angry outside the lab that day
My senior wasn't there
Are you sure?
Think again
Was she there?
She was!
She's playing with
a kitten in the stairwell
She was jealous with our conversation
What a smart boy!
I know Si Tu Mo very well
Come to me if you have any problem
I'll be your counselor
So, you'll get Si Tu Mo easily
But you didn't get her, right?
You guys still chatting?
Just finished
Let's go
Let's go for a movie
Don't bother the single man
See you
Senior
Don't count on Gu Wei Yi
He refused to help
Cold-blooded
-Gu Wei Yi, can't you really...
-Senior
Don't beg him
No need
When he finds his conscience back,
he'll be in tears and regret it
-Give it to me, I'll take care of it
-No way
Cut it out! He just agreed
Give the kitten to him
He refused to take care of it before
Why should I give it to him?
I tell you
Even if the kitten and I are homeless
or starve to death,
we won't beg him
What if I put the kitten
at the animal shelter
and bring it back in 2 days?
Will they allow it?
Call and ask them
Okay
Zhou Lei
Give it to me
I really want it
No way
What do you want me to do?
Beg me
I beg you
Gu Wei Yi
You begged me readily
I don't feel satisfied at all
Put it in a bag later
Look
It's funny
Let me with chat him
That's right
The guy is handsome
Really
He's carrying a kitten
He must be a kind man
Go chat with him
-It's not appropriate
-Go!
Go ahead
Okay
Hello
The kitten is cute
I always want one
Mew...
It's not mine
Where did you buy the bag?
I don't know
Could I add you in WeChat?
Look
Where did you get it?
I'll tell you later. Let's go
All smart guys have a girlfriend
Where did you get it?
You want to raise a kitten?
Zhou Lei asked me to keep it for a while
Cute?
Not bad
My senior said, this is
the cutest stage of a kitten
Really?
It will faint if we walk too fast
Alright
I'll give you a knack
Si Tu Mo taught me
A girl can't stop a sticker
Stick on her
Follow wherever she goes
What's wrong?
I don't know what to do with it
Why did you
bring it back then?
Zhou Lei said he couldn't keep it
in the dorm
My senior lives in the dorm too
Take care of it
Why should I?
I don't like cats
Why did you bring it back then?
Because someone got it wrong
When we were in the stairwell,
I meant the kitten was cute,
not my senior
Actually...
Why suddenly want to see a movie ?
I bought the tickets long time ago
We made a deal before
We'd have a date including
dinner, shopping and movie
I've been hoping to take you to a movie
I won't let you out
I'm allergic to cats
Stop mewing
I won't fall for that
Come out yourself
What's wrong?
I have an allergy
Really?
Even mantis prawn and kitten
You're really too much
I'm serious
I'll bring it into my room
So cute
"Arrived at the destination"
Come on!
I want to kiss you
Good
I like you the most
Si Tu Ding Dang is so cute
Like your name?
Ding Dang
I'm calling you Si Tu Ding Dang, okay?
So good
Hello
Si Tu Mo is staying in the room
I can't stick on her
What?
Go to her room
-She has a cat there
-Cat?
Lure her out then
I'm watching a movie, bye!
-What's wrong?
-It's okay
Let's go out and let it stay in the room
You may go out,
we don't have to go with you
I want to play with it
Close the door when you go out
Don't let it out
Have some water
Si Tu Mo
Anything?
-Come out for a while
-I'm playing with Si Tu Ding Dang
It will go out if I open the door
Who?
Si Tu Ding Dang
I gave it the name
What is it?
Let's clean the house
It's night time now
-The house is full of cat fur
-Let Circle clean it
Circle is tired and needs a rest
I'm tired too
I need a rest
"A cat likes to bath
will have healthy skin"
"Stay away from fleas
and so much bubble"
"Si Tu Ding Dang is pretty"
Don't be afraid, I'll give you a bath
Don't be afraid of water
Good boy
Did it hurt you?
No, it's afraid of water
So it screamed when
I put it into the water
What's this?
Mosquito bite, I scratched it myself
Aren't you allergic to cats?
Sit down
Step back
Don't be angry
It didn't hurt you purposely
I'll come to you if you're angry
I'm not angry
Don't come near
Ding Dang wants to eat dried fish
I have only cat food
No, dried fish
Okay, I'll buy for you
Ding Dang wants to thank you
It wants to give you a kiss
What are you doing?
Come on
I suggest you step back
What if I don't?
What will you do? Huh?
-I'll kiss you then
-You did it before
When you're drunk...
I'm just kidding
Don't be serious
[Here comes the Easter egg]