[Put Your Head On My Shoulder]
Gu Wei Yi
Would you like to marry
this woman as your wife?
Yes
Gu Wei Yi
Don't be kidding
It's okay
If you don't want...
I just want you to know
You're really in my plan
[Episode 24 - Finale]
No wonder I couldn't find it
He secretly brought it here
But I love you
I love someone else
Please leave
I want to see your girlfriend
It's none of your business
I'm his girlfriend
You?
Yes
But I love him
-"Mao bing"
-"Mao bing" (Crazy)
Not maybe, but I'm pretty sure
She's not my girlfriend
She's my wife
I don't believe you
It's true, and I'm pregnant
I see
Explain it
Just like what you saw it
She's been annoying
and I can't get rid of her
She won't be so brave
if you didn't give her hints
I didn't
Alright, I trust you
Your turn to explain it
I just got my visa, so I came here
That's not what I'm asking
What then?
What is the meaning of pregnant
in Chinese?
I don't know
So as I, I don't understand
You just said it
What?
My English is poor and
can't remember any words
I only know "Yes" and "No"
"Come" and "Go"
That's all you know?
Yes
You have to
improve your English level
I'll bring you out to improve it
No need, as long
as you can speak English
No way, let's go
Get your changed
What's wrong?
What do you want?
Is it free to learn English here?
This is the best place for you
They have the same
level of English as you
Only "Yes" or "No"
Let's begin
My name is JC Caster
I'm honored to be here today
to celebrate the wedding
of Gu Wei Yi and Si Tu Mo
I'd like to begin
the marriage ceremony
according to our custom
What's going on?
Quiet, he's teaching English
Do you really think I'm stupid?
Can you understand that?
Gu Wei Yi
Will you take this woman
whose hand you hold
choosing her to be your wife?
To live with her
for the rest of your life
To always love her
To comfort her
To follow her at all times
And to be faithful to her
Gu Wei Yi, don't be kidding
Yes, I do
Si Tu Mo
Will you take this man
whose hand you hold
choosing him to be your husband?
To live with him
for the rest of your life
To always love him
To comfort him
To follow him at all times
And to be faithful to him
Si Tu Mo
It's okay
If you don't want...
I just want you to know
You're really in my plan
Yes, I do
Congratulations
I now pronounce you
man and wife officially
I've been here once before
The sausage platter is delicious
Still angry?
Shouldn't I be angry?
I didn't even wear a wedding gown
Gu Wei Yi
Si Tu Mo, why are you here?
To get married
Congratulation!
Thank you
I'm done, I'm leaving first
Bye
-Bye
Shan Shan
What's up?
The bank offered me a loan
Really?
Really
I didn't even wear the wedding gown
Where's the ring?
Where's my ring?
Not even a ring
Gu Wei Yi
Don't pretend sleeping
Gu Wei Yi, get up
No breathing, what should I do now?
Oh yeah, CPR
You're dead
You're finally dead
CPR requires artificial respiration
You know?
I don't know
Mo Mo
May I?
That's what I wanted to ask you
You'll know it
What's going on
with Zhi Cun's blog today?
How could he have
Si Tu Mo's resignation letter?
I'm working on it too,
I can't reach him now
I'll call you back after this
Bye
Hello
"Reason of resignation:
The leader is too ugly"
"It's an advertising firm"
"The leader stole her artwork
and put it under her name"
Si Tu Mo
Are you okay?
You're going to be a dad, huh?
Shut up!
Why did you throw up all of a sudden?
We ate the same food, right?
I don't know
I threw up several times
when you were asleep
Did you eat anything else?
-I took medicine
-What medicine?
Contraceptives
Where did you get it?
His girlfriend gave it to me
Don't mention it
Give me the medicine
It has a strong side effect
And you ate with an empty
stomach, you can't stand it
Still want to throw up?
I'm better now
That's good
Why did you take the medicine?
The baby might not
be in your plan yet
Everything about you is in my plan
I'm leaving
Wait a minute
You forgot something
What's that?
Hello
Si Tu Mo, you're really something
You're so close
with Lin Zhi Cun, huh?
What are you talking about?
Don't you surf the Internet?
Lin Zhi Cun stands up for you
regarding the artwork
What?
I'm not sure from where
he got your resignation letter
He posted it in his blog
and it's a hot topic now
Miss Sha Sha was soon found out
Now the company says
they'll look into her problem
I just saw an interview on the TV
A reporter asked her about it
Guess what she said
What did she say?
Si Tu Mo
Congratulation!
Finally, the justice served
What are you talking about?
You're so lucky
Even my idol stands up for you
I didn't expect you two
have a relationship
I envy you
You forgot me
Let's go home
Welcome home
What is going on?
I just studied it on the plane
How did you make it?
As long as I'm on a same
local area network with it,
I can control it with my phone
I called its current state
as pet mode
Have you studied other modes too?
Want me to try it all for you?
Okay
I've set up an escape mode as well
If there is a fire, it will
automatically run to the balcony
and jump down into the bushes
I've set the parabola
Did you ever think
how many pieces it will break into?
Don't worry
We're on the 17 floor
The height of each floor is about 3.5m
Altogether
is about 59.5m
So, even if it jumps down...
Gu Wei Yi
Welcome home
I cleaned it up and
found something's wrong
What's wrong?
I think we should
live in the same room
What about the empty room?
I'll change it to a lab
I'll divorce
I'll tell your mom then
My mom didn't even know
I was getting married
I haven't told my parents
about our marriage
I didn't tell my parents either
Let's call them later
Okay
No way
If my mom knew that we're
married in a church in Germany
without her knowledge...
Oh, no!
We haven't got the
marriage certificate yet
So, in a legal sense,
we're not married
That's good
I'm safe
I've booked online
for the marriage registration
When?
On the plan
Why did you do
so much things on a plane?
You want to go?
Sure
Come on, please sit down and smile
Cheers, the photoNwill be used for a life time
Ready
1, 2, 3
Why did they give us
2 copies of the certificate?
To avoid of losing it?
Since there are 2 copies,
it doesn't matter if you lose one
Let me keep it
Why?
One of the certificates is mine
Give it to me
Give me back
Cut it out! Your mom is calling
My mom
always calls you
and she seldom calls me
Hello, aunt
Xiao Gu, have you two
got your certificate?
Yes
Don't call me aunt again
Mom
Wishing you a happy marriage
I planned to have a meal together
for celebration after you got the certificate
But Mo Mo's sister
suddenly wants to study abroad
They...
Dad, please drink the tea
Okay
It's okay
So good
Thank you
Mom, please drink the tea
So sweet
You're so sweet
Mo Mo
I just talked to Xiao Yi
about the banquet
He still rejected it
Can I just tell him that
my family insisted to do so?
Okay?
Forget it, it's okay
Since he didn't want it,
I just feel hard to force him
In fact, we're here to see you two
Aunt, you may...
Mom
You and dad can stay here longer
No way
You are just married
If we stay here longer,
Xiao Yi will get mad with us
No, he won't
Xiao Yi, come on
What's up?
Look, it's amazing
The sunset is nice,
but it just near dusk
It's going to rise again tomorrow
Just the Earth's rotation
Xiao Yi
It's not scary to get married
But marriage is not that easy
I know
Are you sure?
Marriage is not like doing a scientific
research which always with traces
Just like what you said just now,
the Earth's rotation
If you say it to your mom,
she's going to be
nagging for a long time
But, Si Tu Mo won't
My son, I wish you
have a very good time in your marriage
Thank you
Why? You've never seen
anyone looking for a job?
Can't get a job?
Look at here
This company doesn't recruit
married women with no child
And this one
Must drink 500ml of liquor
Must recognize 300 stars
This is more outrageous
Must have a story in your eyes
Let me see
There's a story in your eye
No gloating please
I want to hit the person who doesn't
have to look for
a job like what you do
You really hit me, huh?
Because you're gloating
Don't look for a job first
Take a break first and think about it
Are you going to
raise me if I'm jobless?
Sure
Do you have enough money
in your bank account to raise me?
My grandma sent it to me when
she knew that we got married
How can we spend Grandma's money?
Actually, I gave all my scholarship
to her since I was small
Unexpectedly, she saved it
That means, it's not much
RMB240,000
You're so generous
I was really terrified
Forget it
No way, you can't keep the money
Or some weird machines
will appear in our house tomorrow
I'll keep it for you, I won't spend it
Don't you want to sleep?
Wait a minute
I'll sleep when
I'm done with this test
What test?
The most reliable company is the one
asking people to recognize 300 stars
So I found their test
and tried to do it
Gu Wei Yi
You know the Four Flow Men after 1985?
Flow?
I knew
You know Flow, huh?
The "flow" in Physics means
the flow through a closed pipe
or the amount of fluid
in the effective cross section
of the open channel in a unit of time
It's also known as instantaneous flow
Isn't that flow?
Forget it, I think too much
You wouldn't know it
You probably don't even
know who are the Four Kings
What is that?
Oh, my goodness
You really don't know, huh?
Isn't that common sense?
Even my dad knows that
Do I need to know it
Do you know the
Four Physical Mechanics?
The Four Kings of Hong Kong
Andy Law, Jacky Cheung,
Leon Lai and Aaron Kwok
Four Physical Mechanics
Theoretical, statistical,
quantum and electrodynamics
You're awesome! You're knowledgeable
Awesome
I'll sleep first
Take off your glasses first
Come down
No, I'm going to
sleep like this tonight
You'll regret it then
Why should I?
Your parents are in the next room
What can you do to me?
Here it comes
I'll go to the lab first
Alright
Wait a minute
Mom cooked the herbal tea
Drink it first, it will
make your body cold
Bitter?
What say you?
Come back early
Mom, I'll clean it up
Prof. Jiang and seniors will
arrive at 8 pm tonight, right?
8 pm tonight
So, the four swordsmen
of the lab finally reunite
Why must be four swordsmen?
What's the special meaning
of four?
Yeah, why they always use four?
Four Masterpieces
Four beautiful women and four kings
You know who're the Four Kings?
I know, don't you know it?
Have you finished reading
the German experiment report?
I sorted it out for you
before I came back
I'm done, wait for me
Hello, Shan Shan
Mo Mo
Where do you think I am?
Where are you?
I'm at Fu Pei's company
Why are you back? Break?
I'm here to spend the
anniversary with Fu Pei
Anniversary?
I thought Fu Pei is going to...
Si Tu Mo, shut up!
When are you going
to buy us a meal?
Why should I?
You two get married
You should invite us to the banquet
You should ask Gu Wei Yi
I'm jobless
and it has nothing to do with me
You haven't got a job yet, huh?
Do you want a part-time job?
Please design posters for me
How much you're going to pay me?
We're old friends
Don't hurt our relationship with money
I'm going to an interview
You should call Gu Wei Yi,
don't bother me
Why is it so dark?
Dad! Mom!
Fell asleep?
I don't think so
Dad! Mom! We're back
They aren't here
They already went home
Impossible
They will tell us before that
Are they taking a walk?
Mo Mo, Xiao Yi
We're going back
We didn't mention it earlier
just to avoid you to send us
And I have an urgent job,
that's why we're rushing back
We're at ease
when we saw the way
you two get along
There's pepper mantis prawn
in the pot, remember to eat it
Don't forget to post
the wedding photos to us
They already went home
And they left a lot of mantis prawn
So strange
Aren't you allergic to mantis prawn?
I can't finish it
But we'll turn them down
if we don't finish it
It's alright
Just leave it to me
Let me help on it
It smells good
So fresh
The mantis prawn is so nice
Can't you just eat one and clean one?
You don't understand
We must eat the whole plate of it
to feel a sense of accomplishment
Okay
Let's just eat this first
It is too fresh
You can have one
It doesn't matter if you eat little
It's alright
Allergies don't kill people
At worst you'll be admitted
It doesn't matter
Forget it, you'd better don't eat
If anything happens on you,
I can't carry you
If you're admitted, how should
I explain to mom and dad?
You'd better don't eat
Just one, it won't be allergic
Yes
Mom said, someone ate a lot
of mantis prawn during the New Year
Definitely not allergic
So you started to fall into me
when we're by the sea
No
No?
Why did you give me
the mantis prawn then?
I suspected the mantis
prawn was poisonous
You're poisonous
You hate it because you love it
What's wrong with you?
You've been quiet since the dinner
What are you doing?
Get up
I...
I'm proposing
We're in a long-distance love
You still have to study and
I just started my business
I have no achievement yet
But, everything will be okay
after we get married
What do you think?
Okay
Maybe you think
it's so sudden
But, I'm sincere
Wait
What did you say?
I said "Okay"
She said Okay
Did you hear that?
Calm down
Hi, the bride is changing
clothes on the second floor
Just a minute
Okay, thank you
Not ready yet?
Almost there
That's what you said an hours ago
You may leave first
Take your time
Why? Spellbound by my beauty?
No
Let's go
We're going for outdoor shooting first
I was really caught by Si Tu Mo
I got 187 in my IQ
After meeting Si Tu Mo,
it seems only 87 left
I started to do a lot of stupid things
Buy for your girlfriend?
It's really comfortable
Wait!
"Like surrounded by the warmth"
"The story was shaking the destiny"
"Bamboo Dragonfly and the Time Tunnel"
"can go anywhere"
I started to do craps
Are you writing a thesis?
"The sky of glowing starlight"
"Melt me into your eyes"
"I want to go further with you"
"It's all I miss"
And lost the calmness I've always had
I poisoned her
When will the ambulance be here?
"I want to go further with you"
"Despite the changing of world"
You got scratched by it?
Aren't you allergic to cats?
And watch her giggling at all times
"Strand the lost memories"
"Write a new romantic poem"
I haven't driven a car
since I got my driving license
Do you know where the
throttle and the brakes are?
Do you really think I'm a stupid?
The shooting theme
which was chosen by
you is kind of stupid
"I want to go further with you"
"Despite the changing of world"
Let's just forget it
But,
I found my IQ is in
the continuously declining trend
For example,
Although I knows it's dangerous,
but I still get into the car
I'm willing to
"Promise me to be
by my side every day"
Gu Wei Yi
Please tie my hair
Just fine
Gu Wei Yi, bring me a glass of juice
I'm Si Tu Mo
Gu Wei Mo