[Put Your Head On My Shoulder]
[Preview]
Surprise!
Happy birthday!
It's falling!
Let me see!
Take a selfie with someone you like
[Episode 9]
I'm coming
Who will come during mid night?
What are you doing?
Let me open it
Why do you bring the knife?
A girl shouldn't open
the door during mid night
Who is that?
I'm looking for Mo Mo
Fu Pei
Are you okay?
Shall we talk?
I have something to tell you
Okay
Let's go
Mo Mo
Fu Pei, let me go
Mo Mo, give me one more chance
Get off me
What are you doing?
Take your time
Carry on
I'll leave first
Thank you
Why did Fu Pei look for you?
You're straight to the point, huh?
So?
Why did he look for you?
Gu Wei Yi
You've never been a busybody before
Your mother asked me to look after you
Did she pay you?
Yes
The rental
What were you guys doing out there?
Don't you want to talk to me?
I want to be with you
What?
Let's get together
Forget it, we're not suitable
Why?
Are you falling into Gu...
Someone else?
No
I just stopped loving you
In your heart,
I'm nothing
and you can give up anytime, right?
Why did you stick on me and pretend
that you won't leave me forever?
Did I beg you?
No, I did not
I didn't mean
to stop loving you suddenly
When you told Xu Jie Er
that we're not a couple,
I told myself,
you're protecting me
When you let go of my hand
on the bridge in the school,
I told myself,
you're afraid
Anyone can feel afraid
Every time you promised me
but didn't turn up,
I told myself,
you're too crazy in games
and forgot it
When you smiled
and asked me to get
a girlfriend for you,
I just couldn't convince myself
When I saw you running
out from Gu Wei Yi's house,
I was upset with myself
That day, when I saw
you and Wang Shan...
I suddenly found that
I was not sad anymore
No, I should say
that I no longer feel sad because of you
I felt sad because I found
I stopped loving you finally
I didn't mean to stop it suddenly
It's because you always ran out
and left me alone at the place
Then?
I'll buy some medicine for you
-Fu Pei, let me go
-Mo Mo
-Fu Pei!
Get off me
Mo Mo, give me one more chance
Give me one more chance
Last chance
I'll never do that again
Calm down
Get off me
Let me go
I really no longer like you
He confessed to me
Then?
We had a fight
I'm tired, I'm going to bed
He hit you?
No, I hit him
I hit him
Really?
Really
Why did you hit him?
As I rejected him
but he's still mumbling
You rejected him?
I'm going to bed
As I rejected him
Fu Pei
Why not pick up the call?
I have been calling you
the whole night
Have you registered for CET 4...
What's wrong with you??
Come with me
It seemed I always apply
medicine for you recently
I confessed to Mo Mo
and she rejected me
I guessed it
She hit you?
No
My father hit me
Your father?
It's alright
He used to hit me when I was small
This is just a small hurt
Maybe I've been annoying since I was small
Now Mo Mo doesn't like me too
What if I say I like you?
Give me a chance to stay by your side
I know you still like Mo Mo
I can wait
Don't
That's my decision
Wang Shan
Even though I'm tall and strong,
but I'm actually timid
When I face something awkward,
I will run away immediately
I don't know how to say no to girls
So, everyone thought I was fickle
Now I don't even know what to do
with my relationship with Mo Mo
I don't deserve you
It's my call
Fu Pei
I didn't feel you're timid
as you saved me at the stall that day
I didn't feel you're fickle
as I knew that
you only love Mo Mo all the time
Mo Mo
doesn't like you anymore
I think...
The most important thing is...
Although I'm not as tall as you,
I'm not tiny
We're matched perfectly
Are you here to comfort me?
Well,
don't keep my words
in your heart
I will keep bugging you after this
No one can stop me
Come on
Li Na, brief the introduction
There is an insurance company
coming from their HQ in USA
They want to enter China's market
and their main request is creativeness
Let's share your views
[Done your thesis?]
The local marketing
should base on families
Most of the advertisements
are family-style
It's not creative
I saw several similar ads
on my way to the office
Agreed
Throw out the outdated
and bring up the creative
They come from the HQ in USA
They must emphasize on creativity
China's market is
approaching to family-style
Don't you have any new idea?
Mo Mo
What's your view?
You don't have to get up
So sorry
Can we just frighten the consumers?
For example,
any uncertain accident could happen
When you're enjoying
the fossil exhibition,
you might get hurt
by a bone of dinosaur
which falls suddenly
In term of parents love
When something happens on you,
your children might
be displaced out there
In term of insurance benefits,
consumers are earning no
matter there's an accident or not
You have a lot of ideas
Okay, Li Na
Try to get three proposals
by next Monday
Okay
Dismiss
Hello, Shan Shan
Why did you call me
back to the university?
The counselor got mad today
According to him,
we have the least submission of thesis
Quickly pass it up if you're free
It might affect our graduation
I have something to tell you
What is it so mysterious?
Let's talk when we meet
Okay, I'll try to apply for a leave later
Bye
Miss Li Na, your note book?
Thank you
Complete a proposal together with Jie Er
Miss Li Na
I'd like to leave in the
afternoon to submit my thesis
Okay
But, don't take leave too often
Jie Er and you are both interns
But she seldom applies leave
Okay, thank you
It's crowded
Oh yeah
What did you
want to tell me?
I'll tell you later
Alright
I think the format of my thesis
should be no problem
You should
worry about the content
Can't you stop teasing me?
You off today?
I'm here to print my thesis
What about you?
I thought you have your
experiment in the old campus
I have something here
Oh yeah
She is my senior, Xie Yu Yin
I know her, we have met before
Right?
Your girlfriend?
Girlfriend?
How did you know?
That's crap!
Your words are confusing
It will cause misunderstanding
Misunderstanding?
How should I explain it?
After you took me to the counselor,
I bluffed him as I wanted to help
Gu Wei Yi
to join Professor Jiang's experiment
So, you are not a couple?
No, we're not
Your turn
Print your thesis
Okay
Shan Shan
Thank you
How much?
Scan and pay there
50 cents per piece
Let me pay for you
Thank you
It's paid
Okay
Gu...
Did you see any error here?
Here
I have calculated it
Should be no problem
Alright
It's not working
Slowly, let me do it
We'll leave first
See you
Bye
Let's go
Okay
I thought
Zhou Lei is finalising the
experiment in the old campus
What's wrong?
It's okay
What makes you so dull?
Nothing
Alright, forget it
You said
you have something to tell me
Why did you hum and haw?
I have confessed to Fu Pei
What did he say?
He said he didn't know how to say no
and he rejected me
But I won't give up
Are you angry?
No
Your look creeps me out
Frankly,
he confessed to me the other day
It's okay
I knew
Really?
Alright
I'm innocent
Bull shit
I don't know why,
but I feel sympathy to you now
Fu Pei is such a scum
You'll know it someday
Same as you
It was just ended and
now you're setting it up
What do you mean?
-I won't tell you
-What do you mean?
Make it clear
What's wrong with you?
I'm doing my thesis
My god!
Gosh!
How long you didn't wash your hair?
Since we cane back from the beach
Mo Mo
Can you buy me lunch?
Cut it out!
I haven't received my salary yet
Even the rental was paid by my mom
Gu Wei Yi asked for the rental?
What a stingy guy!
I must lecture him
What about
you bring me for dinner at your house?
I'll give him a lesson
Why do you always
want to go to my house?
I want to run out from here
No way
You are not welcomed
I must go there one day
Hello
Are you going home?
I'm going home
So early
My mother is coming
Who?
My mother
She wanted to treat you to dinner
I'm not hungry
I'll tell her then
Dont!
Why did she want to treat me?
I have no idea
I'll ask her
Dont!
I'll go with you
I'll wait for you downstairs
Okay
What's wrong?
Gu Wei Yi's mother is coming
She wanted to treat me to dinner
Go ahead
Why do you
look so sad like meeting
your mother in law?
Perhaps, I have a phobia
to meet the elderly
[Who created the printer?]
Why are you searching this?
Let's go
Are you sure?
Why not?
When will your mother get here?
Very soon
Is she fierce?
Like your mother
Do we need to wait for her outside?
How about a red carpet?
Forget it, I just need to calm down
Here is she
Hi, aunt
I'm Si Tu Mo
You are Wen Jun's daughter?
So pretty
Just like your mom
Thank you
Mom
Why are you standing here?
Let's sit down
Hurry up
This way please
Have you ordered the food?
Not yet
Waiter
Give me a braised meat platter
Do you eat seafood?
Yes
Okay
Mantis prawn
Your favourite
I thought you're allergic
She got it wrong
What's wrong?
I'm allergic to mantis prawn
No
Yes
When you're small,
I brought you to grandma's...
You're busy when I was small
I might've got it wrong
What a bad memory!
Do you eat fish?
Yes
Okay
Let's get a fish
Thank you for the meal
How was the food?
So good
That's good
Thank you and please come again
So sorry
to ask you out for dinner suddenly
In fact, I feel scared
to stay with him alone
Xiao Yi
We had our dinner quite early
Let's have some tea in the house
I have booked a cab for you
Can't you just cancel it?
You said you'll get insomnia after tea
Actually, it's alright
I think...
The cab is here
I've sent you the plate number
Call me when you're home
Let's go
See you, aunt
Be careful
Have something to tell?
I don't mean to pry into
your family affair
But the communication
between you and your mother...
When I was small, she was busy
and have no time for me
Can you teach me?
How did you make your mother
so docile?
I want to make my mother...
You know, my mother is talkative
and
excited in front of you
Don't you feel annoyed?
Am I right?
I saw the way you treated your mother
Hello, Jie Er
Do you have any idea
about the proposal?
Are you asking me
to figure it out on a Friday night?
But we need to submit it on Monday
You do it first
Let's discuss after this
But...
Alright, bye
Well...
Ready?
Add in cart?
Yes
Grab it at 12am
Alright
Many people are trying to get it
The Internet will be slow
Let's find a hotel outside
Find a hotel?
Do we need to do that?
It's only sales
That's crap!
Do you know how long it took me
to choose, compare the
prices and grab the coupons?
Don't make the crap if you don't know
how hard I worked for it!
Alright
Don't worry, I promise I'll get it
I'll go to a cyber cafe
Oh yeah
Double 11 Carnival
I forgot it
How can you forget it?
Don't wait?
Go shopping
We don't have to buy so much
It's trouble to move it after graduation
I just remembered that
Mo Mo's birthday is coming soon
I almost forget it
It's alright
I'll pick a gift for her
Me too
Today is Saturday
I'm surprised you
got up before noon
Don't mention it
Meng Lu called me in the morning
They wanted to come here
Don't worry
I have rejected them
Dig in
I bought yours too
I know that you hate crowds
Who comes so early?
I'll open it
Surprise!
Happy birthday!
Where is Mo Mo?
We decided to celebrate
outside, right?
Let's go
Why should we go out?
Ke said
they always have hot pots
and watch soccer games here
Your room-mates are here too
No way
Gu Wei Yi hates dirty
Let's go
Come in
You don't know
their destructive power
You'll regret it
Treat it as your birthday gift
Fatty, hurry up!
Don't urge me!
I'm in the toilet
Fu Pei
You don't want to go?
It's Si Tu Mo's birthday
I'll pass
Enjoy yourselves
Fatty
Stop urging me!
Hurry up!
Let's go
[Happy birthday, sorry...]
I don't care
It will leave marks on the wall
It's hard to remove
I have bought it, don't waste it
No way
Who's gonna clean it then?
It's nice for taking photos
It's nicer on the floor
You're studying advertising
Can you be more artistic?
Don't...
I'll go and help Niu Niu and Shan Shan
I don't care, I want
to stick balloons on the wall
Don't worry
I'll protect our wall no matter what
Let me help you
Hurry up!
I'll massage your scalp then
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday to Mo Mo!
You're one year older now
Make a wish!
It's time to make a wish!
I'll make a wish now
I wish peace to the world
and I get slim without any exercise
Dream on
I wish peace to the world
I always have money and slim body
Impossible!
Wait!
Let's take a photo
Hurry up!
Take a photo
Make my face smaller
Come on
1, 2, 3
Cheese! Happy birthday!
I'm one year younger!
Happy birthday!
Cut the cake!
Alright
Fatty
For you
Thank you, Mo Mo
What are you doing? This is mine
I want to be the first
Shan Shan
Thank you
Serve yourselves
Let's toast
Come on! Cheers
Happy birthday, Mo Mo!
Happy birthday
Where is my birthday gift?
Birthday gift!
It's shaking
Shaking!
The centre of the 3rd row
You help her again
Yeah, you did it again
Let her draw
on your face with a lipstick
I'll open my eyes
Closer
Who did it?
Him!
Gu Wei Yi did it
Which one?
3rd row...
No way!
Don't help her again
That's right
Falling
It's falling down
Let me see
Please find a person who
wears the same colour
and look at each other for 20 seconds
Nobody wears the same colour with me
Gu Wei Yi is wearing a yellow top
Yellowish brown
It's the same
It's yellow too
Look at each other!
Mo Mo, you bet, you pay!
Hurry up!
That's right
The timer is ready
Mo Mo
Are you feeling shy?
What for?
Gu Wei Yi, don't be shy
I'm never scared of it
Come on
Start
-Mo Mo!
You're falling into his eyes
Alright, let's continue
Carry on
Your turn
Hurry up!
-It fell!
-Let me see
Take a selfie with someone you like
with your mobile phone
Who?
[Here comes the Easter egg]
I go out for a while
Let's go