[English subtitles are available]
[Warm on a Cold Night]
[Episode 13]
Hu.
Yes.
How many people are still outside?
Let me go and have a look.
Wang Jirong.
Lass, there are not many left.
Only about fifty to sixty people.
Fifty to sixty people left?
There are still another fifty to sixty people.
Liu.
Daren.
How are things going?
The girls at the Cuiyan Brothel all claimed that
Xu Youdao had been painting there
for several nights in a row.
Take a look.
This is what Xu Youdao
painted for them.
He spent the day in Nanfeng Studio
and the night in Cuiyan Brothel,
and he was always surrounded by people.
He does not seem to have enough time
to kill and set up the scene.
Daren, what are we supposed to do next?
Yeah, Boss.
What should we do?
Xu Youdao…
Let him go. What else can we do?
[Inspection Bureau]
Please.
Floral fabric for sale. Come and take a look.
Premium flower fabric.
How can I track him down
when the Qi people are so ferocious?
How can I follow after him?
People who are constantly on the move,
come let me tell your fortune.
Come and check it out.
Candied hawthorn!
They are sturdy and durable.
Come and have a look.
Little trinkets.
Take a look.
My floral fabric is of excellent quality.
What on earth is this guy up to?
[Zuixiang Brothel]
What kind of person is this?
So unhygienic.
What brings you here?
Do not worry.
I am uninterested in your minor
and irrelevant case.
I have my own reason to arrest him.
Then, General, may I ask
how this guy offended you?
It is not about him.
It is about that wolf's head.
That wolf's head?
What is  wrong with that wolf's head?
The three scars on the wolf's head
were not natural.
They were intentionally painted on,
and it's deliberately made to look old with exquisite skills,
almost fooling my eyes.
So, you make a guess.
Did someone instigate the person
who drew three scars on the wolf's head?
Let me interrogate this man,
if General does not mind.
I do not mind.
However, you are currently serving as an Inspection Bureau inspector,
you are not permitted to use lynching.
Really? I just said a couple words
and you really backpedaled.
Have you become foolish
as a result of spending too much time recently
with Qian people?
If us Qi people want to interrogate someone
without leaving any evidence,
aren't there many ways to do so?
You both...
What are both of you up to?
We have something to ask you.
What is it?
What exactly do you want to ask at this place?
Who painted the three scars
on the mask?
What three scars?
Hurry up, let me up.
I am the Eldest Senior of Nanfeng Studio.
He fell by himself,
it has nothing to do with me.
That's fine.
This silly girl.
How can I even follow him
when Qi people move so fast?
Someone is falling down!
What's the fuss?
He is flying so high.
So high in the sky!
Please wait. Wait, please.
Wait. Please wait.
It hurts.
I found them.
What exactly are you two doing?
Let me ask you again.
Who painted the three scars
on the wolf's head?
My specimens…
My specimens are flawless.
How can there be any scars?
So you are saying that
you are not the one who painted the three scars on the wolf's head?
You also have no idea
who drew it?
Exactly.
My studio's doors are all open,
so anyone can come and go as they want.
Then the wolf head
the three-scarred wolf's head
you drew earlier?
I dare not,  I dare not say.
I am afraid to say.
Sir.
Sir, please help me up.
Even if I tell you,
you will not believe me.
Tell me then.
How about this?
Sir.
Sir, help me up, please.
Sir, please save me.
-You deserve it.
Why did you jump off by yourself?
Not everyone
can save you.
I did not jump off.
Are you done?
Can you tell me now?
I will.
I will tell you.
In my dream.
I dreamed of him many times.
Although it was a dream,
it was very real.
I saw
the dark street.
Ghost fire-like eyes.
His scars are still bleeding.
He seems to come from hell.
He came to take revenge on everything in this world.
Walking in the dark.
That is why I drew it out.
I am really telling the truth.
Warrior, please spare my life.
Please spare me.
What do you think?
What on earth was he talking about?
He does not seem to be lying.
What if
it is really a dream,
Could it be because of that thing?
What thing?
Qi Vital Stone.
What are you doing?
Transforming on the street,
do you want to be arrested again?
How can a Qian man
obtain such a thing?
I want to know too.
Qiyuan Stone.
Can I entrust you
with this matter?
Certainly you can.
But, let me make it clear in adavance that
this clue might not have anything to do with
the case you are looking into.
It does not matter.
But, if Xu Youdao
is not the murderer,
then I was off the scent.
What are you afraid of?
Don't you still have your partner?
How about this?
I will continue
to find the murderer who
painted the three scars on the wolf's head.
Is it okay for you to be in charge of investigating Xu Youdao?
Okay.
Then I will go first.
Is it a must that
I have to give in to that girl?
Alright, stop crying.
This candy is for you.
The candy is delicious.
Really?
Yes.
It's delicious.
Here.
Thank you.
Be careful.
We had been asking around for the whole afternoon,
and the information we gathered is all about there.
Hence, I figured it out that
Xu Youdao and Wang Jirong have been brothers
since their childhood.
They never have conflict over neither women
nor money.
As for Wang Jirong,
he had been doing bad things since he was a child,
but in this studio, Xu Youdao
is the most sympathetic to him.
Jun.
Do you remember one of
Wang Jirong's disciple saying
he was still in the studio
the day before yesterday.
The following day,
nobody saw him.
That's true.
So,
it took only twelve hours
for him to be found after going missing.
On this particular day,
Xu Youdao was in the painting studio during the day
and only went out for
three hours at night.
We apprehended him the next day
when he returned.
If he is the murderer,
then only these three hours
are available.
However, during these three hours,
he also visited Cuiyan Brothel.
How did you know?
I noticed it on him
when I arrived here yesterday–
it was the scent of the Cuiyan Brothel.
I also know that he has
a special side room in the Cuiyan Brothel,
which is dedicated to painting.
So...
So?
S-so what?
Han Zheng surely cannot find a clue.
Really, all you can recall is fighting with him.
Not really.
Well, I also want to be
a good partner to him.
But...
So,
if I want to manage him,
I must first mentally
subdue him.
But...
Unfortunately,
we have not found any clues.
He does not like painting at all and is only interested in money.
He is a money lover who enjoys gambling.
I heard that Eldest Senior
lent him a sum of money to
redeemed
a painting he sold.
Got it.
What?
Wang Jiarong is greedy for money and loves gambling.
He values money as his life,
but he is willing to borrow money
to redeem his painting.
Doesn't this
sounds strange?
Yes.
Lass.
I'm back.
I'm back!
Godfather.
How?
How is it?
Stop drinking. Let us get down to business.
It is not a trial case.
Come on, tell me.
Han Zheng
[Nanfeng Studio]
What?
He hurled the man up and down
the City Gate Tower.
Hu,
did Xu Youdao get hurt?
Trauma is certain–
Trauma is certainly not there.
Did he cover his face?
He seemed to have covered his face.
That's good.
In such a case,
I do not need to be made a scapegoat.
Oh no.
In that case,
he will
come back for us soon.
We are about to be screwed.
Be careful, be careful, be careful.
Lass.
Are you looking for Senior's painting?
Can you make it?
Young Prince,
you are quite strong.
How is it, Lass?
Is it bumpy?
This is so fun.
Painter Feng,
you are amazing.
You made
such an interesting and useful thing.
My Master had gout,
which made it difficult for him to walk for a while.
As a result,
there is such a chair in the studio.
I did not expect it to be used today.
Then Master Wei does not need to use it any more?
Master's gout was treated with acupuncture all year round,
and his leg improved significantly.
When he is able to walk and run,
he travels far and wide to spend time outside.
I have no idea
where Master is right now.
It seems that Master Wei has been travelling
for half a year now.
Yes.
I did not expect anything like this to happen
after Master left.
Please.
Let us go.
This is the warehouse of Nanfeng Studio.
Some items that were not previously in use
are all here.
So what happened was
Wang Jirong redeemed the painting
and tossed it here.
A disciple discovered this painting
and assumed it had been stolen,
so he gave it to me.
But when I asked Second Senior,
he said the painting was evil and
demanded that I destroy it right away.
Evil.
What does he mean?
I have no idea,
and I have never encountered it.
Let us take a look first.
It is a normal scenery painting.
Where is the evil spirit?
Nothing wicked is apparent to me.
Yes, I cannot tell either.
Your Highness, what do you think?
There are no flaws
and there is no negative meaning,
as in his other paintings.
I cannot tell too.
Why did he redeem this painting?
[Excellent Exquisite]
Your Highness.
What is wrong?
Is this painting
redeemed
from Nameless Art Gallery?
Sir, you are extremely perceptive.
This painting
was indeed redeemed
from Nameless Art Gallery.
Nameless Art Gallery?
Your Highness.
What is wrong with Wuming Painting Club?
Nothing.
Wuming Painting Club is a decent place.
It is just that
the place is not so compatible with me.
Incompatible?
It does not matter.
I can go to that place
with her.
When did you come in?
When the three of you were
in Wang Jirong's room,
I was there.
He's been around for so long now–
Where are you taking me to?
To Wuming Painting Club.
It will be late if we do not go now.
Why are we going there?
What is this?
Bring the painting along.
You only know I'm useful now.
You're not going to bring even me?
They're not going to bring even you?
Well…
- Please come in.
[Nameless Publisher]
Invitation card please?
This is my invitation.
Please come in.
Here, Jiu'er.
Put your hands down.
Thank you.
Jiu'er.
Remember,
the owner rarely shows up,
and the shopkeeper enjoys being praised
and prefers to listen to stories.
You can definitely handle him.
Then, I...
will not go in.
I will leave it to you.
Do not worry.
Go back early.
Let us go.
Who are you? Do you have an invitation card?
Sirs,
please help me inform your shopkeeper
that Inspection Bureau inspector Su Jiu'er has stopped by to
get shopkeeper Li's opinion on some matters.
Do not think you can bribe me
with a bag of candies.
I have not settled with you about
what had happened during the day.
It is not too late to settle the matter
after we find the clues.
Please follow me.
Please.
Young Master, please.
I get to drink wine too?
What?
No, thanks.
This place is really magnificent.
I do not understand,
why is this place incompatible with
Jun'er?
Pull your chin back.
It is almost on the floor.
Please wait a moment.
Thank you.
Coming.
[Qian, Shopkeeper Li]
Inspection Bureau inspector.
What are you doing here?
I have known your name for a long time, Shopkeeper Li,
and I have heard that you have a large collection of paintings in your possession.
We came here today with a painting,
and I would like to ask you for some advice on it.
Your flattery is excessive.
There are more than 100 paintings coming in and out of
Nameless Art Gallery every day.
Nameless Art Gallery has been in operation for over ten years,
and even an immortal can't remember all of the paintings that has been here.
This painting is different.
Two days ago,
this painting was just taken back
by the painter himself.
So...
did he regret it again?
He asked you, an Inspection Bureau Inspector,
to collaborate with him to put up a show
so that he could sell it at a good price?
You got it wrong, Shopkeeper Li.
The main purpose we came today is
because
the painter
is dead.
[Fishing Alone at Han River]
What do you want to know?
Why did Wang Jirong want to
redeem this painting?
Sir,
do you know the reason?
You are the inspector.
You cannot even guess that?
Well...
how should I guess?
This painting is called Fishing Alone at Han River.
Don't you think it's strange?
Han River?
Fishing Alone at Han River.
Fishing alone?
Yes.
There is only a river in this painting.
A lonely boat.
There's no one fishing alone.
You are worth being cultivated.
Is this the reason for
him to redeem the painting?
Exactly.
Is it possible that he made a mistake in the drawing
and this is not the right painting?
How could there be a mistake
in a painting I collected?
What's wrong
with this painting?
When the painting was first brought here,
there was nothing wrong with it,
and there was nothing special about it as well.
How is it?
You are lucky.
Master is here today.
It depends on
whether Master likes it or not.
Take it slowly.
Slowly.
Zhen.
Our art gallery's collections are
divided into three categories:
Good, Excellent, and Exquisite.
The owner values
those in the Exquisite category
which are considered rare
by the rest of the world.
The category of Zhen is
determined by the owner's preferences.
The owner might play with it for a few years
or perhaps give it away,
or sell it.
No one knows.
Then why is this painting
with the marks of two categories?
Because of that strange occurence,
it upgraded this painting from the category of Zhen
to the category of Ji.
This was also the reason why Wang Jirong is determined
to redeem this painting.
That night,
the old man
who was fishing in the river originally
disappeared from the painting overnight.
The man in the painting disappeared?
Exactly.
Such a strange painting.
Your boss
has even promoted it to a higher category.
It's nothing.
Please have a seat.
Our boss prefers rare things.
The more mysterious the thing is,
the more our master likes it.
So
it is also possible that Wang Jirong painted
two paintings at the same time,
one with and
one without the old man on the boat,
and then found an opportunity to switch them.
Exactly in accordance
with your master's preferences.
There is no such thing as just looking exactly the same in paintings.
There is also the differences in the ink used and the brushwork.
I personally examined the painting and
remember every stroke
clearly.
Even if it is drawn by the same artist,
as long as there is a wrong stroke,
it will not escape my attention.
Furthermore,
if it is done for the owner's favor,
why would he pay
twice the price to redeem the painting?
It is completely illogical.
Actually,
it is not that illogical.
Shopkeeper Li, what else do you know?
You just said
he was hung with a wolf's head after his death.
Is it true?
Yes.
Do you know
this is also a painting?
Xu Youdao's Wolf-Headed Man Roaming at Night.
You have done your research.
Since we get along so well,
let me give you a piece of advice.
Do not investigate
this case any more.
Why?
Because I think
they were killed by the painting.
In the end,
all your investigation will be in vain.
Maybe
you will get killed by the painting as well.
Sir,
people were killed by the painting?
That's
too ridiculous.
Little girl,
I like what you say.
But as for your subordinate,
he is so unlikeable.
You...
Calm down. Calm down.
Sir,
I have one more thing
to ask you.
Is…
Is there any other paintings
from this Nanfeng Studio
with which
such bizarre things happened too?
You are smart.
Is that painting called The Painting Immortal?
That is right.
Sir,
can you tell us more about
what happened
in more specific detail?
So that we will also know whether
we should pursue the investigation further.
I'll reluctantly
to give you some advice.
That painting
is called the Painting of a Snow Night in Jiuxiao City
The Immortal in the Painting is just the nickname of it.
Could it be...
someone in the painting is missing too?
The opposite happened for this painting.
The Painting of a Snow Night in Jiuxiao City
is the final work drawn by Master Wei Gonglin,
the head of Nanfeng Studio,
who devoted his whole life to this painting.
Congratulations, Master.
The painting of Master Wei is fantastic.
The sky was full of vibrant colors
one evening,
and auspicious snow fell unexpectedly at night,
and the sky and the earth were vast.
Some people in Nanfeng Studio
heard fairy music
and smelled a strange fragrance.
The next day,
they discovered
an extra immortal in red had appeared
on the Painting of a Snow Night in Jiuxiao City.
Senior.
Who'd dare to draw
on Master's painting?
This stroke
must be done
by Master.
What a skillful work.
I did not.
[Qian, Wei Gonglin]
I have no idea either.
Congratulations, Master.
The achievements of Master are extraordinary.
This is the immortal in the painting.
Come in uninvited and live in the painting.
Congratulations, Master.
From that onwards,
the painting has been called The Immortal in the Painting
and became a priceless treasure.
The Painting Immortal?
“Wolf-Headed Man Roaming at Night" hasn’t been solved yet.
Fishing Alone at Han River
is also very strange.
Now comes another "Painting Immortal."
Do you believe that this case
has anything to do with the painting?
Do you truly believe that the paintings
are killing those people?
If you want to believe that,
it's better to believe
that the trees over there, the grass on the ground,
and the door outside
can jump out and kill you.
Believe me.
Maybe the key to this case
is really related to painting.
As long as the case is not solved,
there is no truth.
Then, Xu Youdao is not the murderer, right?
Shouldn't you apologize
for what happened during the day?
You're walking so fast again.
I am having difficulty walking right now,
why can't you wait for me?
Take it.
What?
♫ I want to travel mountains and lakes with you ♫
♫ The shadows the moon casts on the waters is lovely  ♫
♫ Through winds and rains, I bring you to a place where the sky is clear ♫
♫ Your smile comes into my dream with the wind ♫
♫ I'm glad to have you when I wake up from my dream ♫
♫ I realized love has its own reason after meeting ♫
Han Zheng, don't let go of me.
♫ The two hearts understand when the night is warm ♫
I'm scared.
♫ I'll hold you in my arms outside Jiuxiao City ♫
♫ Turn the past into dust ♫
Han Zheng, you scared me!
♫ Our future is more worth looking forward to ♫
You scared me.
You are so timid.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
What do you mean?
You almost killed me.
You haven't apologized
for what happened during the day.
You just threw me out.
Why are you always like this?
I...
Listen.
I have prejudice.
Whether it's Wenjun or you,
both of you have your own ways.
I shouldn't interfere.
Without you and him,
I can't say
I can't make it in this Jiuxiao City,
but it definitely wouldn't be as smooth as it is now.
Also,
I was mean to you.
That does not mean
I want to do anything to you.
I just don't want you
to ask me
about the matter of the three scars.
I'm sorry.
Alright.
If you send me home,
then I will forgive you.
Let's go.
You have to fly well this time.
My home is over there.
Slowly.
Why did you bring
here again?
I have already said sorry to you.
You should help me to investigate the case.
I thought
you sincerely apologized to me.
So you're exploiting me again.
Who said that?
I'll investigate if you don't.
Fine.
I will send you back
to where I picked you up from just now.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
After the checking the painting,
can you
send me home like how you brought me here just now?
It is just a piece of cake for me.
Really?
Why are  there so many people
in this painting?
You come and take a look,
which is the painting...
Get up.
Get up...
Hurry up.
Hurry up. Find out who is the immortal in the painting.
Could it be you want to pull the immortal out
and interrogate her?
Ridiculous!
Get up.
I'm so sleepy.
Here.
Come on. Wake up. Sober up.
Don't push me.
By the way,
did Xu Youdao
tell you
why he drew
the wolf's head with three scars?
He said he had a dream.
A dream?
The dream came true.
The painting came to life.
If this is another case,
I would not believe it.
But this case,
I don't think it's a coincidence.
Help!
Bad news!
I heard
a scream just now.
Well,
let's go.
Where are you going?
To find where the scream came from.
Let's go together.
Is it Senior?
I think so.
How did he become like this?
Come on.
Make way, please.
We're from the Inspection Bureau.
He is dead.
How is that possible?
This Qiyuan Stone.
Do you know
when painter Xu came back?
Two hours ago.
Is there anything strange?
He seemed shocked.
on the way back to his room,
he told us not to disturb him.
He said he wanted a good rest.
Before that,
has he met
with anyone?
I don't know.
Su Jiu'er.
Did he die like one of
the paintings?
So cruel.
Senior is here.
Flower of Evil.
[Be Perceptive of the Minutest Detail]
Three hours ago,
he was still at the Inspection Bureau
and now he is dead.
What's the cause of death?
Did you find out?
He's not injured.
The cause of death is very strange.
There's no sign of poisoning.
What do you mean?
Could he have
been suffocated to death by these flowers then?
Commander,
come and have a look.
I’ve been investigating for more than ten years.
I’ve never seen such a way of death.
A living person
being scared to death.
Can you believe it?
Commander,
you saw
what happened just now.
When we opened the chest,
the heart
was already exploded.
[Nanfeng Studio, Xu Youdao]
He was so terrified
at that instant.
What could've happened
for one to be scared to death?
Because I think
they were killed by the painting.
In the end,
all your investigation will be in vain.
Maybe you will
be killed by the painting as well.
Do you believe
those people were killed by the painting?
Lass,
what are you talking about?
Tell me if you have any clues.
Uncle Liu,
are you familiar with flowers and plants?
Do you know the origin of these plants?
This is a kind of vine flower from the south.
It's easy to grow.
But few people plant it.
I've checked carefully.
In Nanfeng Hall,
they are only found
in Lin Zhixing's courtyard.
Isn't this
the same way Wang Jirong died?
I got it.
Wang Jirong was turned into Xu Youdao's painting by
Xu Youdao's wolf head.
Xu Youdao was transformed into Lin Zhixing's painting
by Lin Zhixing's flowers.
I got it.
The murderer is warning us.
He's forewarning that the next person to die is
Lin Zhixing.
[Lin Zhixing]
Commander.
I have an idea.
We just need to send someone
to keep an eye on Lin Zhixing
and follow the clues.
Then we can catch the murderer.
Yes.
Prince Han,
what is your opinion?
You are really enthusiastic to
follow the murderer's idea.
What idea do you have then?
Brother Daren,
what Prince Han means is
you are going towards
wherever the murderer wants you to.
Are you the murderer's good son?
What if the murder wants us
to protect Lin Zhixing
but has another purpose?
Right?
Come here.
Time is running out.
What you should do is
split up.
Split up.
Let's not talk about the preview,
But this...
Lin Zhixing
must have something
to do with this.
So we can't
ignore it.
Right?
Yes.
Besides,
what Prince Han said
also makes sense.
We can't be always
led by the murderer.
We must find out
his purpose and motive.
Right?
You're right, Commander.
How about this?
I'll take someone to keep an eye on Lin Zhixing.
Don't Jiu'er and Prince Han
have some clues?
They can go and investigate.
Yue Daren,
are you trying to take my job?
What do you mean?
Hu Badao,
do you even know what's going on?
Go away!
I was the first one who mentioned about
keeping an eye on Lin Zhixing.
How is it not helping?
You are certainly not helping.
You are stealing the job.
This...
You...
She's already like this.
Han Zheng, Han Zheng.
Your Highness, what are you trying to do?
Forget it.
Yue Daren!
Come here.
Come over.
Go, go, go.
Forget it.
No wonder you have been always bullied
at the Inspection Bureau.
I'm not.
I don't want to be so calculative with him.
They are usually like that.
But today,
it seemed that they were really scared.
However,
without Prince Han,
no one would have stood up for me.
Right?
Stop.
There must be something behind your sweet words.
You stop.
Have you forgotten?
Forget what?
You said it yourself.
I will accompany you to check the painting,
then you will send me home.
Aren't I sending you home now?
Is this considered sending me home?
I am so sleepy and tired now.
My leg is injured as well.
I just hope
you can fly me around again.
Then I will be flown...
I am also tired and sleepy .
Take me with you too.
And I'm home...
That was so fast.
You brat!
Mother.
You still know to come back?
[He'an Hall]
Look
at the time now.
You really...
Mother, I'm back.
He'an Hall
Hurry up, come in.
I'll apply some medicine for you.
Alright.
Look at you.
You just can't stay still.
This Han Zheng
usually looks fierce.
I didn't expect that
he would apologize to me.