[English subtitles are available]
[Warm on a Cold Night]
[Episode 17]
Painter Feng is so diligent.
He never stops practicing.
But for two years,
he didn't produce anything.
That was the time
he studied abroad.
We missed
such an obvious clue.
Meng Huaiyun died
and the painting immortal appeared
on New Year's Eve of the 29th year of the Dingkun reign.
That means
he was actually
studying in the far east back then.
I see.
He escaped.
That table
was moved.
There's a secret tunnel here.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Be careful.
My master has arthritis in his legs.
For a while, he couldn't walk,
so there is a chair like this
in the studio.
The lamp is here.
Isn't this Master Wei 's fan?
So Wei Gonglin hasn't been traveling.
He has been imprisoned here.
His money was taken
to redeem Meng Huaiyun's paintings.
Look at the ground.
Those are wheelchair tracks.
That means
Feng Muyuan
has been lying to us all along.
Wei Gonglin's leg
hasn't recovered.
That's not right.
Then who was the person
who attacked him?
And why hasn't he killed
Wei Gonglin?
Isn't it more difficult
to imprison a living person?
Could it be...
the masked man is his accomplice
and has been helping him in secret the whole time?
The gas lamp just went out.
He can't have gone far.
I don't care.
Don't try to get rid of me this time.
We agreed
we would catch him together.
I won't be a burden.
Get off.
No.
Hold on tight.
A partner like me
is hard to come by.
Your Highness.
Go and get
everyone from the Inspection Bureau.
Let's go.
Where do I find you?
My disciple,
I was wrong.
I had always thought
you were the most foolish amongst your peers,
and had no talent for painting,
so I hadn't taken good care of you.
But since you've came back from the far east,
you have impressed me.
Although you've been hiding your true skill in painting,
I can see that
after you achieve a breakthrough,
it won't take long
before you surpass me.
My disciple,
why are you so persistent
about heartlessly destroying everything?
Let it go.
Where is
Huaiyun’s body?
It's not worth it
to ruin your own future
even if it's for Huaiyun's sake.
I loved Huaiyun so much.
But if I didn't keep the secret for them,
Nanfeng Studio would have been destroyed.
Do you really think
if you conceal the whereabouts of her body,
and the evidence doesn't surface,
that you would be able to live your life anew?
Master.
The world already knows
your true colors.
I didn't kill Huaiyun.
I just made a choice.
I waited until today
to make you see
it is your so-called choice
that ruins Nanfeng Studio!
Tell me.
Where did you hide her?
My disciple,
I've told you everything.
For old time's sake,
please spare my life.
I never knew
you and Yun had a relationship like this.
You've always done everything
in silence.
Why do this to yourself?
If you leave this sentiment
in painting—
Shut up!
Don't come here!
Stay away!
Otherwise,
I'll kill him right this moment!
Calm down,
Painter Feng.
Calm down.
I'll calm him down first.
You take the chance to save him.
Don't be impulsive.
I'm not good at swimming.
I'm afraid I won't be able to take care of you.
Painter Feng.
Are you waiting for someone?
Who?
That man yesterday
was your accomplice,
right?
If I say I have no accomplice,
would you believe me?
How is that possible?
In this world,
I don't have partners
nor a family.
Even if someone like me
disappeared,
no one will notice.
Just like Junior.
Painter Feng.
Why are you doing this?
She will never know
about your avenging her,
nor your love for her.
Right?
So what?
I don't deserve her.
It's all because of me...
I didn't protect her.
Back then,
I was only a junior disciple in Nanfeng Studio.
All I did were menial tasks
like serving tea and water.
I learned painting in secret,
hoping Master would take me as his disciple.
Senior, please have some tea.
And she
was just an apprentice who came to learn painting
once in a while.
She hadn't become a disciple yet.
Go.
Serve that lady tea.
What kind of beautiful painting
could such an ugly person create?
Go.
Senior.
I'm too clumsy.
I'll make some tea for you again.
Three years later,
Master finally accepted
his only female disciple.
From a distance,
I thought her eyes
looked very familiar.
She was extraordinarily gifted.
The entire Nanfeng Studio
treated her like a star,
but she kept her distance from everyone.
Junior.
Don’t go.
Where are you going?
At that time,
although I was no longer a junior disciple,
I still had to do menial tasks
for my seniors.
Junior.
Senior.
Why are you still so stupid?
Still?
We seldom talked,
but we always hid out
in the warehouse together.
We just wanted
a quiet place to paint.
Although she didn't talk much,
I knew
it wasn't because she was aloof,
but because her background was complicated.
When she first came to Nanfeng Studio,
I've already heard that
the youngest daughter
of an official from Jiuxiao City
had a birthmark on her face.
A few years later,
when Master brought her back,
I heard that
the official's property had been confiscated
and his family had been beheaded.
Only the youngest daughter with a birthmark on her face
had gone missing.
Junior's painting
was taken by the palace again.
I've also heard that
the Empress Dowager wants Junior
to paint another one on her birthday.
Junior was getting better and better at painting,
and her name spread.
Her painting was sent to the palace
and recongized by the Empress Dowager.
As for me,
I was still
a nobody in Nanfeng Studio.
Muyuan.
Monk Suoluo
likes your painting.
He thinks you should meet each other.
He invites you to go to the far east with him
to hone your painting skills.
Master,
I...
My disciple.
This is a great opportunity.
But you can decide
whether you want to go or not.
Thank you, Master.
Congratulations, Senior.
Congratulations.
I didn't think that would be
the last time we saw each other.
Two years later,
I came back to Nanfeng Studio and learned that
Junior had given up painting to go back to her hometown
with her family.
But I knew
that was impossible.
But in this vast world,
I could only forget her.
Until that day.
Painter Feng.
Are you running errands for Master Wei again?
Please have a look at these paintings.
This is so well-painted.
[Spring in Nanfeng Studio, Meng Huaiyun]
I couldn't get it out of my mind.
But Master said
Junior had painted that
before she left.
I wanted to repress myself and forget,
until a coincidence occurred.
Good wine.
Senior is drunk.
Senior.
I'm not drunk.
You
are definitely drunk.
More.
Come on.
The three of us
haven't had so much fun in a long time.
Come on.
Cheers!
Do you remember
that time we drank with Junior
here?
What are you talking about?
Junior,
have you forgotten
what we had done
to her?
My disciple.
I've let you down.
In life,
if the one soulmate you had
was treated unjustly
and disappeared off the face of the earth,
what would you do?
So,
from the very beginning,
you never wanted to get away with this?
You blew the matter up on purpose
to let everyone know
about the evil deeds
your seniors had committed,
right?
That masked man.
Do you really not know who he is?
I don't know.
He's just a mysterious helper.
I've never seen
what's behind his mask.
But it's okay.
He taught me
how to kill people with the Qi Vitality Stone.
He even gave me
such a valuable Qi Vitality Stone.
And my three despicable seniors
were controlled by their own fear.
They kept using the Qi Vitality Stone
and scared themselves to death.
Have you ever thought about
why a stranger
would take the risk
to help you
frame Wei Gonglin?
He once told me
if I did two things,
he would help me with everything.
Except murder.
He also said
he wouldn't dirty his hands
because of me.
What two things?
First
was to turn the first criminal
into the “Wolf-headed Man Roaming at Night."
Second
was to tell you about this personally.
Jiu'er.
Lass.
What else did he tell you?
We will help you.
Painter Feng.
We will report
everything you've said.
But before that,
don't do anything stupid
that you'll regret.
Inspector Su,
do you know?
What I regret the most
is the day I left five years ago,
not today.
Muyuan!
Painter Feng!
Han Zheng!
You can't die.
You haven't explained
about the masked man.
You can't die.
Oh no.
Su Jiu'er.
It's so dark here.
Can you find me?
Han Zheng.
No matter where you are,
I can find you.
She really found me.
With you around,
it's not so scary
in the water.
Jiu'er!
Prince Han!
Lass!
When did you tie it on me?
When you were on the boat.
Why?
Because
I was scared something would happen
to a certain bad swimmer.
How dare you say I'm risking my life?
You're
no better than I am.
Jiu'er!
Prince Han!
Lass!
Jiu'er!
Jun!
Hu!
Jiu’er!
We’re here!
Lass!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Didn't I say she'll be fine?
She's a good swimmer.
We found her.
Don't stand so close to the edge.
You might fall.
We're coming.
Hurry up.
If you don't come over soon,
I'll kick her off.
How dare you!
Your Highness, slow down.
Why are you so wet?
Hurry up.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
No need. Don't come over.
He doesn't need it.
I had no choice
just now.
I did it to save you.
You'd better forget it.
Do you hear me?
Who wants to remember?
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
[Deyue Restaurant]
[The Case of the Painter]
Jun.
It's just a case file.
You can read it if you want.
You don't have to treat us
to so much delicious food.
Your writing is so good.
You can praise something like this?
I'm serious!
Although it's short,
it contains the entanglements of a dozen years,
the obsession after parting,
and
the loss of five human lives.
But I just want to write about
the painting immortal.
I want people to forget about
the brutal murders,
and only remember their sincere feelings.
In comparison, I...
Go ahead.
I...
I'm still conceptualizing it.
Why are you looking at it for so long?
Jun.
If you need any materials,
just let me know.
I'll tell you everything I know
without holding back.
What materials does he lack?
He just wants to take the chance
to spend time with her.
Jiu'er.
I have a question.
Go ahead.
But
it's not about this case.
Well,
I often see
you and Brother Han
talking to each other about
health and longevity.
What's that about?
I...
You'll also hold hands.
I'm guessing
Brother Han must be
helping you recover your strength, right?
Why are you so smart?
Because I know you.
I also know
the Xueqi tribe
have much stronger powers of rejuvenation
than the others.
No wonder you
keep pestering Brother Han.
What is he confirming,
exactly?
I was right.
It's because you are her medicine,
there's nothing more to it.
What else?
Nothing.
Maybe it's fate.
The story of your Qian-Qi relationship
has spread in Jiuxiao City
because of your partnership
and this case.
[He'an Hall]
Mother.
I'm back.
From now on,
I'll be the top inspector in Jiuxiao City.
Mother.
W- What are you doing?
Su Jiu'er.
How dare you hide it from me?
W- What did I hide from you?
How dare you talk back?
Mother! Mother!
What's gotten into you?
Tell me.
I...
What should I say?
Your reward money.
You cracked your first case
and went to collect your reward money today.
What?
Aren't you going to share it with me?
Reward money?
You should have said so earlier.
It's all for you.
Take it.
That's more like it.
I find that
since you've gotten this partner,
things have been going very smooth for you.
Is our family going to produce
another senior inspector?
I wish.
By the way, Mother,
did you know
the Inspection Bureau
is going to recruit a batch of
Qi inspectors?
So what?
Mother.
Tell me.
If they assign me
a Qi as my partner...
That won't do.
You've just had a little success,
and you already want to ditch Han Zheng?
That's not what I meant.
I meant...
If he...
If he wants to find a Qi partner,
you must stop him.
Think about it.
The Qi are temperamental.
If he gets killed,
wouldn't you feel sorry for him?
Mother.
If he is...
Inspector Su.
What is it?
Our boss
has something for you.
Mr. Li?
Yes.
Thank you.
Mr. Li?
What is this?
I don't know.
Great.
This painting is so beautiful.
There's a letter here.
Mother.
I'm working on a case.
Go ahead.
I'll leave you to it.
Alright.
I'll buy you something delicious to eat.
Five days ago,
Painter Feng sent someone
to send it to the Nameless Art Gallery.
He asked me to hand it to you
in five days.
I had my guesses then,
but I didn't expect it
to happen so soon.
He jumped into the lake that same night.
Maybe he was determined to die,
and it was all planned.
He wanted to entrust these paintings to you.
Maybe he thought
you'll understand him.
[To Inspector Su]
I lost.
You beat me.
How is this a win?
I didn't save anyone.
I didn't even manage
to save him.
He didn't want anyone to save him.
He just wanted to find
Meng Huaiyun's body.
Also,
he needed someone
to remember
all that had happened between them.
You were the only one
among us
who found out about his love.
So,
you beat me.
I'm not used to
you talking like this.
Are you addicted to being bullied?
Or...
Then I'll use my privilege.
Can I?
Sure, go ahead.
What do you want?
Can I ask for anything?
Tell me first.
I want you to transform
into a puppy
and walk with me around the city.
Will you...
Han Zheng.
I was just kidding.
Why are you so serious?
I only have one request.
I have something to tell you,
but you're not allowed to get angry.
What?
Does the man with three scars
look like this?
Where did you get
this portrait?
I found it
in one of the Chief Inspector's
case files.
Why would he investigate this too?
I want to know too.
Because
the Inspection Bureau's Chief Inspector
was my father.
My father went to Shuobei before he died.
After he came back,
he contracted a strange disease
and grew black spots all over his body.
Soon after,
he died.
My mother
raised me, a sickly child,
all by herself.
She doesn't want me to take risks.
She just wants me to live well.
Every time
I work with you,
it is like there's a sword hanging over my head.
I don't know
if I should take risks
to do what I want to do,
or if I should listen to my parents
and live well.
You silly girl.
Why do you keep calling me silly?
I'm a reasonable person.
How could I let
a little girl
risk her life for me?
But from now on,
you can just order me around.
We are partners.
You
use your brain to the fullest.
As for the rest,
just count on me.
I just want to know
if the person on this portrait
is really
the man with three scars?
Is he?
I...
Look.
You don't want to
tell me anything.
Yet you say I'm your good friend
and trusted partner.
You only think of me
as a tool to solve cases.
No.
You're turning it on me.
I can only tell you
this man
is called Mu Yan.
He is related
to the Qi race's secret.
That's all I can tell you.
If I continue,
Chilan might come
to take your life.
By the way,
the disease you just mentioned
is similar to
a type of Xuanqi poison I've seen before.
Poison?
What poison?
The Xuanqi tribe is adept at medicine.
They have always been opposed to
friendly relations between the Qian and Qi.
So it's not surprising
that they would do something
to harm a Qian.
However,
what exactly happened to your father?
What if the person he met
wasn't Mu Yan?
Is he the one
in this portrait?
This portrait looks like the one
on the arrest warrant
the state of Qi once issued.
Logically speaking,
it shouldn't appear
in Jiuxiao City,
nor should it
come into your father's possession.
Thank you for trusting me
and telling me so much.
I have to tell you that
if one day,
I find out it was Mu Yan
who poisoned my father,
I won't let him off the hook.
Here.
Give me your hand.
What are you doing?
This is how the Qi
make a vow.
I swear
I will help you
find out the truth of your father's death
and give you a proper explanation.
Even if that person were Mu Yan,
I believe
he wouldn't kill a Qian
for no reason.
What?
You still don't believe me?
I...
Since Your Highness says so,
of course I believe you.
Can you
not call me "Your Highness"?
You can...
just call me Han Zheng.
Why are you suddenly
so amiable?
Did you wrong me
somehow?
Look at you.
Are you picking a fight again?
Do I have to be mean
to calm you down?
Let's go.
Actually,
I have been wanting to tell you something.
I recognise
you, Su Jiu'er, now.
You are different from
all the other Qian people.
You are qualified to be my partner.
However,
in the future,
I won't say any of these nonsense again.
I won't use them
to control you either.
But can you
not be so silly
and risk your life for me again?
Unfortunately,
it's all Yue Daren's fault.
If it weren't for him,
we might have caught that man
that night.
Tell me.
Was that person
the real Mu Yan,
or someone posing as him
to trick you?
We'll find out.
Here.
Eat more of this.
Become a sweeter talker.
Don't keep arguing with me
out of nowhere.
We are opposites.
I like to banter with you
when I'm in a good mood.
When I see you get so angry
that you have wrinkles on your face,
I'm happy.
Who has wrinkles on their face?
You.
-You’re full... -You.
You have wrinkles all over your face.
I don't have wrinkles.
I really don't have wrinkles.
Mother, I'm back.
Mother.
Do you want some candy?
You went to see His Highness secretly again?
Not His Highness.
It was Han Zheng.
He treats you so well.
Daughter, you must lock him down.
Mother, what are you talking about?
We are good partners.
We don't see gender.
Try one.
It's really sweet.
Take this red one, it's sweet.
Is it sweet?
Very.
The effects of her Qi Vitality Stone
haven't worn off.
I wonder
whose Qi Vitality Stone she used.
Will she dream of that Qi?
If she dreams of another Qi,
then...
She won't touch him, right?
Touch his face?
No way!
Pinch him like this?
Hold his hand?
She can only touch me—
Painter Feng?
Inspector Su.
Where is your partner?
Did he leave you
alone here?
Of course not.
How could he?
Yes.
He won't leave you
alone here.
So that was what he meant
when he said that
back then.
What happened?
Am I dreaming about this
because I've been thinking about it in the day?
Junior.
Stop painting.
Tell her now.
You...
You fool.
Why didn't you tell her
you liked her
while she was still around?
She likes you too.
Why are you
so dull?
He doesn't want to say it.
Why force him?
Han Zheng?
Why are you here?
A dream?
Did she use
my Qi Vitality Stone?
That was the time.
Fine.
You're not an outsider anyway.
This is a dream anyway.
Don't just stand here.
Help them.
Let them be together.
Why do you want them
to be together?
Why?
Look at how pitiful they are.
Shouldn't people who have feelings for each other
get to be together?
Why are you acting so dull too?
Weird.
Why aren't you talking back
no matter what I say to you today?
Smile.
Don't smile.
Smile again.
Are you really a fake?
Since you're a fake,
let me practice on you.
Maybe
when I lie to you in the future,
I wouldn't blush
and my heart wouldn't beat faster anymore.
How about that?
Okay, let's practice.
Why aren't your ears fluffy
in my dream?
Qi people's noses
are also very sensitive, right?
Why are your noses
so sensitive?
Let me see.
Do it yourself.
Hold it up like this.
Hold it up.
Do you know
you're very cute
when you're obedient?
Oh my goodness.
What an amazing dream.
I can't believe
Han Zheng is being so docile!
Dear Heavens,
are you making it up to me
for my suffering in the past?
Han Zheng.
Look at them.
♫ I never forgot your warm gaze ♫
♫ Under the moonlight, the laughter is searching for the answer ♫
♫ Time goes by quietly, color turns grey ♫
♫ I only want him to be safe ♫
♫ The geese's return looks like a message from you ♫
♫ The warm dusk is like your embrace ♫
♫ The night breeze sweeps through my long hair, as if you are wrapped around me ♫
♫ The future can only depend on the beauty of imagination ♫
Go do farm work.
Is this enough?
Yes.
Mrs. Zhang.
Have you heard?
I think Su Jiu'er from the Inspection Bureau
has a Qi for a partner.
Really?
Is there anyone in Jiuxiao City
who still doesn't know about them?
They solved
several strange cases together.
These two
are joined at the hip.
They're like twins.
What does that Qi
look like?
You don't know.
I heard that Qi
is 8 feet tall,
has a mouth full of fangs,
and hair so long it sweeps the ground.
Granny.
When he talks...
Granny!
It's so loud and clear,
like the ringing of temples' bells.
You can hear it from five miles away.
It's not as exaggerated
as you said.
He's just an ordinary person.
His physique
is a little bulkier than ours.
But his nature
is very rough.
-My carriage! -Every time he's on the job,
he can catch the criminal.
But he leaves a mess
at the scene!
In the end,
it's still the misfortune
of us commoners!
I heard that
he's the prince of the Qi race.
So what?
In our country,
isn't he still an assistant
to our female inspector?
I've also heard that...
What did you hear?
I know you.
I'm the most—
You're the biggest gossip!
What's so good about selling wontons?
You sissy!
You're always strutting around!
How dare you question my information network?
Do you know who I am?
Thief!
Help me catch the thief!
Wait for me!
Thief!
Don't move.
Excuse me!
The Inspection Bureau is on a case!
Excuse me.
Don't move.
Be gentle.
Sir.
He took him down so easily.
That's amazing.
-Please spare me. -Oh no.
We're going to have to pay compensation again.