[English subtitles are available]
[Warm on a Cold Night]
[Episode 10]
Although I was flogged today,
I'm happy.
The flogging has earned me
two candid friends
and friendship between the two races.
Isn't that great?
Two friends?
I think it's just
that patrolwoman, Su Jiu'er.
Who is she to you?
Why are you so protective of her?
She's a very important old friend.
Jun.
No matter how much you cherish old friendships,
you mustn't be so naive.
Your statuses are different.
It's rare enough
for you two to be friends.
If you disregard your identity,
do something unbefitting of your status,
and lose the commoners' respect for you,
it will not only
be a problem for you.
If you lose your status,
you won't even be able to protect her.
Brother,
you are always so considerate
and you always think ahead.
As your older brother,
I only wish that your life would be smooth-sailing
and have few setbacks.
Brother,
my butt hurts.
Fan it for me.
Here.
Jiu'er.
What are you doing?
Do your hands grow on your back?
Can you apply medicine on yourself?
Didn't I ask you to wait for me?
Mother.
I'm afraid you'll be tired.
I think
you'd better
quit your job.
The Emperor has already had you flogged.
I don't think you'll last long there.
Don't say that.
Mother.
I asked for the punishment myself
to protect my subordinates.
I didn't make a big mistake.
Mother.
This time,
I solved a big case.
Maybe I'll be promoted
soon.
I don't want you
doing such dangerous things.
There's no danger.
My subordinate is very formidable.
I protected him so well today.
In the future,
he will give it his all and spare no effort
in working for me.
Don't worry.
Fine. Come on.
I'll apply the medicine for you.
Be careful.
Be gentle.
Here.
This lass.
When did she
become so ambitious?
She just got a subordinate,
and she's already getting flogged for him.
[Tablet of Father Su Yao]
Su,
talk to your daughter.
If anything happens to her,
I...
Mother.
I promise you.
I will be careful in the future.
Why are you here?
I just—
W- When did you get here?
Just now.
You are here...
I'm here
to visit
an invalid.
You were flogged so many times.
I wanted to know if you would die.
I didn't expect
to hear the truth the moment I got here.
It turns out that
you took the flogging for me
because you wanted me to give my all and spare no effort
in working for you?
No, it's not like that.
It's me—
My butt hurts.
You haven't changed at all
since I last saw you.
You're still pretending to fall
as an excuse to touch me.
I didn't do it on purpose.
No.
Why are you like this?
I went there to
call and shout everyday.
I was cheering for you on the outside.
How could you say that to me?
How could you point your finger at me?
Let go.
Let go!
What if I don't?
Aren't you
mysophobic?
Aren't you afraid of being touched?
Let me tell you.
I touched a lot of things outside
just now.
There were cats, dogs,
frogs, hedgehogs,
and a whole lot of stinky things.
Smell my hands if you don't believe me.
Stinky, right?
Enough.
I haven't replenished your health
in a few days.
I'll make it up to you today.
Life and death are predestined.
Who was the one screaming and crying
in the ice cellar,
saying she didn't want to die?
Looks like I saved her for nothing.
I should have let her
freeze to death.
Aren't you still the same as well?
You don't mean what you say.
You're cold on the outside but you're actually soft-hearted.
Your mother is here.
My mother is here—
Jiu'er, I've prepared some—
Where is she?
This girl.
She ran out after applying the ointment.
Well.
Your complexion looks good.
Your health must already be sufficently replenished.
I'll... get going now.
Wait.
Well.
Tomorrow morning,
come to the Inspection Bureau a little earlier.
Are you really treating me
as a patrolman?
Do I have to start working at dawn from now on?
Idiot.
It's my fault.
I can't get Chef Zhang
to name his accomplice.
He insists that
he did it himself.
I...
I need you.
The one who thinks she is the cleverest person
in the Inspection Bureau...
What did you just say?
I said,
Your Highness, the pride of the Qi race,
I
need you
to work with me on this case.
Alright.
See you tomorrow morning at the Inspection Bureau.
Wait a minute.
I have another question.
Why do you have so many questions?
I'm thinking,
since you are the prince of the Qi race,
why didn't you issue an order
for the whole of the Qi race to come out
and look for that Qi man with three scars for you?
Because
he is an old friend
all of us are looking for.
I must
find him
before they do.
You can go now.
Put this on. I'm leaving.
Teacher.
You can't sleep either?
I was just waiting for you.
Hanzheng.
Your father asked me
to bring you back.
We're leaving tomorrow.
But Teacher,
I'm now a patrolman
newly hired by the Inspection Bureau.
If I disappear
from the Inspection Bureau
so soon after I was released,
the Qian will make a big fuss
out of it.
So what if they do?
If so soon after I was released,
I become someone
who went back on his word,
I think
it won't be easy for you all
to push for the Qian-Qi Six Treaties.
You've gotten good at manoeuvring
since you've been away.
I was always good,
I just didn't do it often.
Sit down.
No.
Preceptor.
Don’t worry.
I'll keep an eye on him.
You?
Why are you looking at me?
Chilan was going to come to Jiuxiao City
on a diplomatic mission next month.
We're just here to make preparations
in advance.
Fine.
Chilan is the main emissary,
you'll be her aide.
If the Qian-Qi Six Treaties
can be signed successfully,
you can earn your father's trust.
You must make this happen.
I understand, Teacher.
But
can you take her back
with you?
I'm used to being alone.
I'm not comfortable with assisting her.
You're not comfortable with assisting me?
Are you comfortable
working with a Qian?
You—
Enough.
Stop teasing him.
You must come clean to me
about the reason
you sneaked out of Shuobei.
Teacher.
Chilan.
Do you guys
already know about the ember?
So you do know.
Forget it.
I asked your father
not to tell you.
You and Mu Yan
grew up under my tutelage.
I know
how close you are.
Teacher,
do you also think
he took the ember away?
Whether we believe it or not,
we can't change the fact that
the Qi race is in danger.
Now that the holy ember has been lost,
deep night will descend upon us.
The Qi race
might be annihilated.
You must find him.
Don't let your emotions get the better of you.
You are the son of the King of Xueqi,
and the future of the Qi race.
Also,
your father has always thought highly of you.
He asked me
not to bring more men with me.
He only asked Chilan
to stay in Jiuxiao City with you.
You should know
what this means.
You're gravely misunderstood about His Majesty.
Really?
I think
you are more suitable than I am
to be his son.
You ignore me whenever things get serious.
When will you kick
your bad habit
of acting wilfully
and isolating yourself from others?
Standing apart from the crowd
allows one to calmly
assess the entirety of a situation.
Hanzheng.
In the whole world,
only your father, Chilan, the King of Chiqi, and I
know about the ember.
Now that you know,
you must keep it a secret.
No matter how much you trust someone,
you must not tell them.
Especially not a Qian.
Chilan, let's go.
It's time.
Well, I...
Keha!
Your Highness!
What's wrong?
Where did you put
my clothes?
They're in the cabinet.
Is Lord Chilan here?
Are we running away?
I'll pack up now.
Wait.
How confused are you?
This is the first time
I am showing up in Jiuxiao City
as the Young Master of the state of Qi,
as well as a special hire
of the Inspection Bureau.
You have one joss stick's worth of time.
Get me an outfit
befitting of my status
and help me get changed.
If you fail,
I will...
Rip out a tuft of fur from your tail
and burn it.
I'll go now.
[Inspection Bureau]
The doors are closed.
Get lost!
Yes, Sir.
Commander Yan.
I’ve
closed the doors for you.
No one will come in.
You see,
I've done my best to preserve your dignity.
Let's begin.
Let’s begin.
I spoke out of turn
and offended Brother Su
as well as his precious, eloquent, daughter.
Like father, like daughter indeed.
Su Jiu'er managed to catch the murderer
before the deadline.
She managed to prove Brother Su and herself.
I hereby
apologize!
Dismissed!
No, no, no.
That's it?
What about Brother Hu?
Let me tell you.
I'm her godfather.
I should definitely be included too.
Don't pile on here.
Commander Yan!
Hu is
my able partner.
Without him,
this case wouldn't have been solved.
If the case hadn't been solved,
you would be humiliated.
If you were humiliated,
it wouldn't simply be a matter of
an apology anymore.
Brother Hu,
I've offended you many times in the past.
Please
forgive me.
It's okay.
I forgive you.
He forgives you.
I'll watch over him in the future.
Dismissed.
Okay. Dismissed.
Coming.
You're back.
I've bought the last of the
Qi-repellent sachets.
Liu, what are you doing?
I've bought them.
This...
What's that smell?
Not bad.
Yue Daren.
Our new colleague is coming.
You're acting like an unwelcome guest is coming.
Can't you treat him
as an ordinary person?
Exactly.
Why did you prepare all these?
Our new colleague is coming,
so we must
be well prepared.
But I didn't buy your share.
Why?
Boss, give me one.
No.
No!
Don't grab it.
Stop it.
Give me one.
Stop fighting.
Stop fighting!
No.
This...
Wasn't she here just now?
How did she get there so fast?
I remember it like that too.
So fast?
You can't stand up again?
Did you get hurt
or did your illness act up again?
I almost fell down.
Then you suddenly showed up
and flew me around.
I feel a little dizzy.
You almost got hurt
because of these fools.
How stupid.
I thought
the prince of the Qi
would be a burly man with thick hair.
I didn't expect him
to be so elegant.
I thought the Qi
hate physical contact with other people.
But he was willing to rescue Jiu'er
from a crowd.
He's quite considerate.
Indeed.
He's not as the rumors described.
Let's get down to business.
Why don't you say hello to everyone
and get to know them?
It doesn't matter.
They're prejudiced.
It's not a problem if I don't get to know them.
You heard it wrong. You—
-Stop explaining. -You misunderstood them.
With my hearing,
I can hear you all whispering
from three streets away.
Qi-repellent sachets?
Hanzheng, listen to me first.
Liu, I'll return mine to you.
Mine too.
What are you doing? Wait.
Hu.
Ren.
No.
I paid for these!
Chen Li, stop there!
I thought that
after all that had happened,
the mindset at the Inspection Bureau would change.
To think that
they're still a bunch of fools.
Don't talk nonsense.
My godfather and I aren't.
I know it very well.
Your Highness
saved me first.
Even though nominally,
you're only a patrolman,
in private,
I'll follow your orders.
But your clothes...
Our clothes
are not befitting of your status.
I'll make the call.
You don't have to change out.
Alright.
And this.
[Han Zheng]
This is not bad.
Let's go.
Which cell
is the chef in?
The innermost one on the left.
The innermost one?
What's wrong?
There are no signs of life
in that cell.
Open the door.
He bit his tongue and committed suicide.
He has been dead for hours.
The door lock
isn't damaged.
He died out of the blue before the trial.
It doesn't seem like an ordinary suicide.
I suspect...
You suspect the murderer was someone else?
That's possible.
Why can't it be?
Did you examine the body?
Are there any wounds?
What about the cell?
Are there any signs of a fight in the cell?
Did anyone damage
the cell's door lock?
It's intact.
Indeed.
Everything seems to point towards
this being a suicide.
-But... -Come.
Commander.
Everything points towards
Zhang Sen knowing
he was doomed,
and committing suicide to avoid punishment.
I think
we can close the case.
That seems to be the only way.
Wait.
Your Highness, what can I do for you?
Even if it were suicide,
there's a difference between voluntary suicide
and suicide under duress.
We have investigated
everything.
Zhang Sen had no visitors.
There are no signs of a fight
in the cell.
So what?
Is it hard to find master fighters who could do this
without a trace?
What do you mean, Your Highness?
Are you not satisfied
with a petty chef as the murderer,
and want to uncover a greater conspiracy?
Not only that.
I'm not satisfied with you.
You...
He died
in your prison.
As the chief here, not only are you not reflecting on yourself,
but you're trying to close the case in a hurry.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean, "your prison"?
It's ours.
Our prison.
Ours.
Yes.
Couldn't there be anyone amongst us
who is secretly
consorting with outsiders?
That's too much.
What do you mean?
Commander Yan.
Have some tea and calm down.
Brother Han,
I don't like what you said.
You...
We are all on the same side.
Right?
I promise you.
Commander Yan.
He is just a young man, he speaks—
He looks young,
but he's actually an old monster.
He is used to being a prince.
He's a bit official.
Please understand.
Nonsense!
This is not Shuobei.
I’ve been working diligently at the Inspection Bureau
for over ten years.
My service can be considered meritorious,
can't it?
No one has dared
to criticize me!
Really?
Greetings, Your Highness.
I was flogged because of this case.
Even when I'm dreaming,
I want to find the murderer.
Now, you're telling me the case is closed.
Are you afraid that I'll hold you accountable?
I just thought that
because we are out of leads,
this case
cannot be investigated any further.
Don't you know that this case
has caused two princes to suffer?
It also involves the relationship between our two states.
Father takes it very seriously.
I finally
got the case,
but Zhang Sen committed suicide in prison.
What am I
supposed to tell Father?
Your Highness.
His Majesty
wants to hear about this case?
Of course.
Father takes it very seriously.
Patrolman Su.
Yes.
Come with me.
Where...
Where are we going?
Where?
We are going to see my older brother,
then my Father,
and finally discuss closing the case.
You have to report
the details of this case clearly to me.
If anyone has been negligent in their duty,
you have to tell me as well.
My eldest brother and Father
are extremely intelligent.
You won't be able to hide it from them
even if you wanted to protect someone.
Yes, Your Highness.
Jiu'er.
What?
Godfather.
What's wrong?
Look at my eye.
Is there something in it?
Okay.
I'll leave you to it.
Let's go.
Goodbye, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Since Prince Han is your assistant,
he must know a lot about this case.
Let's go together then.
Thank you, Your Highness.
-Let’s go. -Let’s go.
Commander, I need to go to the toilet.
[Deyue Tower]
How was it?
Did I look like
a prince just now?
What do you mean?
You are a prince.
Miss Jiu'er.
You don't know about this.
His Highness
is afraid of dealing with those officials.
Then why did you
come to the Inspection Bureau?
I wanted to observe
your investigation
as inspiration for my novella.
But I couldn't bear to see them
pick on you.
That's why—
That's why you pretended to be a spoiled brat.
Right?
How unexpected, Your Highness.
You're such a good actor.
You could probably even play the young scholars
in your novellas.
I'm not that good.
That means
the Emperor didn't say he wanted to review the case,
and nor did you claim the case.
I'll just have to
talk to my eldest brother
about the case later.
I think
it's more important to close the case first.
You want to brush off the case too?
Brother Han, calm down.
Investigating and closing the case are not mutually exclusive.
Do you remember
Miss Jiu'er getting pushed off
that tower?
Plus, Chef Zhang
isn't capable of killing Qi people.
The Inspection Bureau has already interrogated Zhang Sen
many times.
He insisted that he didn't have an accomplice.
Right?
It would be fine if he hadn't committed suicide.
Now that he has committed suicide in prison,
all the more it makes people believe
he was just a lackey.
There must be a true culprit
instructing him.
Since you want to find him,
why should we close the case?
This person
once said he wanted to kill Miss Jiu'er.
Besides,
he can send messages to Zhang Sen
in prison.
He also had Zhang killed
without a trace.
What does this mean?
It means only one thing.
Zhang Sen tried to hide the person
who is behind this.
If he finds out that Miss Jiu'er
is determined to crack the case,
what would he do?
I saved Su Jiu'er once,
I can save her a second time.
What happens
if you go back to Shuobei?
You mean to say
I can't solve the case?
I mean
it's better for us
Su Jiu'er.
What do you think?
I think it's delicious.
It's not about this.
Oh, this?
I think
since Zhang Sen is dead,
if there really is a true culprit,
we might as well let him get what he wants.
Maybe this would make him
give himself away.
You're both Qian people,
of course you're thinking the same thing.
Miss Jiu'er.
Here, on your mouth.
Where?
-Here? -No, there.
Here?
There.
Let me help you.
Here.
Your Highness.
Well...
I'm sorry.
I'm still not very good at using
Qian chopsticks.
You—
It's fine.
It's no big deal.
Don't be nervous, Your Highness.
Have some food.
Stop staring at
the oil stain on your left.
There isn't any on your right, is there?
It's fine.
Excuse me.
What's wrong with him?
I'll go check on him.
I'm here. Don't worry.
I've prepared clean clothes for you.
They're in the carriage.
He really went to get changed.
You're so cunning.
You know he's particular,
but you still made him wipe his left,
then his right,
then his left again,
and then his right again.
I'm not picking on him.
I just wanted to eat.
It's just that
Qian restaurants
are not only small,
but have nothing in them
I want to eat.
Fine.
If you say so.
But, my good partner,
we rely on our friends when we're outside.
You need friends to help you with the investigation too.
He's a prince after all.
He can make the investigation
a breeze.
It's good for you
to keep him happy.
I don't know
how to make people happy.
That's why
you should leave the coaxing
to me.
I'll keep him happy.
You can just keep quiet.
I'm not allowed to talk?
Fine.
For your sake,
I'll do it.
I promise you.
It's settled then.
Here's what.
You go eat something delicious first.
I'll go check on him.
Your Highness, you can open your eyes now.
Okay.
Let's go back.
Mu Yan.
Why is Mu Yan's scent here?
Brother Han was worried about you
so he asked me
to check on you.
I said I'm fine.
It's okay.
Hanzheng.
Where's Brother Han?
Where did he go?
Maybe
he went to the bathroom?
My flour!
Stop!
Kid.
Did you see anyone going over there?
Me?
Where did you get this?
That man said he was giving it to me.
What man?
A man
with this on his face.
Where did he go?
Did he say anything?
He said,
"Don't worry.
I'll appear again very soon."
Brother Han is indeed a Qi.
He used the toilet
until the sky got dark.
Have you found him?
Your Highness,
the waiter said he didn't see
anyone who looks like Brother Han go to the toilet.
He didn't?
He left me
without saying anything?
Tell me.
His Highness
treated him warmly.
How could Brother Han
leave just like that?
He won't.
He must have found
a new lead,
and went to investigate.
Qi people are
always hasty
like this.
By the way,
before he left, he was telling me about how
impressive Your Highness is.
You know so many people.
As our partner,
could you help us
look into something?
What is it?
The Qi man on the tower
is still the key to this case.
Hanzheng said
there were three scars on his mask.
Three scars?
Your Highness, you're well connected.
Could you help us
ask around?
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
It's a small matter.
Consider it done.
We'll wait
for your good news.
Miss Jiu'er.
How about I send you back?
No, Your Highness.
I can walk by myself.
Then...
Your Highness, let's get on the carriage.
Well...
Be careful.
His Highness went through so much trouble,
but Miss Jiu'er wouldn't even let you
send her home.
Your Highness.
Do you think Miss Jiu'er
has already forgotten about you?
It's better that way.
I embarrassed myself
in front of her when I was young.
I'd love for her to forget about it.
Now, Your Highness and Miss Jiu'er
have different statuses.
I'm afraid His Majesty and His Highness
will oppose
the two of you being together.
But I think
Jiu'er is really smart.
As long as she interacts more with my eldest brother,
he will be impressed by her.
If he is willing to help me,
do I still have to worry
about anything else?
But Your Highness—
It's rare to encounter an obsession in life.
She is my obsession.
No matter how hard it is,
I want to try.
Hanzheng is too much.
He never gives me a heads up
before he acts
and runs away.
I was left there for a whole day for nothing.
I didn't get to solve my case,
nor replenish my health.
Where
did he go?
The craftsmanship is intricate. It's not a common item.
But there are no special marks on it.
Are you sure it's the culprit's?
I can't be mistaken.
In your opinion,
was that person Mu Yan?
His physique is different.
But I can't be wrong
about Mu Yan's scent.
Even if it wasn't him,
it was someone
who can get in touch with him.
In that case,
Mu Yan is in Jiuxiao City.
Maybe
he'll come to us soon.
What's wrong?