[English subtitles are available]
[Warm on a Cold Night]
[Episode 16]
The old painter from Nanfeng Studio
who has been traveling for a long time,
Wei Gonglin.
Impossible.
Are you kidding me?
You're lying.
You can't say that without evidence.
My master
has been traveling for a long time.
How could you suspect him?
Exactly.
You are speculating without reason
and blackening his name.
Why?
Why would Grandmaster do that?
The bunch of you
killed his favorite disciple.
In order to hide the truth,
you even modified his painting.
Isn't that enough?
How is that possible?
Could it be true?
You have to have evidence.
Feng Muyuan.
If you don’t tell the truth now,
I'm afraid
you won't be able to live long either.
That's just an unreasonable speculation.
You have no evidence.
It might be blood,
but we don't know whose blood it is.
How can you be sure
this is Junior's blood?
It could be mine,
another disciple's,
or a maid's.
Master couldn't bear
to let the painting go to waste,
so he painted a few extra strokes on it.
It cannot prove
the painting immortal doesn't exist.
Maybe
that's the painting immortal's blood.
Master
has been traveling for a long time.
I'm just following his orders
to help Junior sell paintings.
My seniors used the Qi Vital Stone
to paint and do evil,
so the painting immortal punished them.
But I have a clear conscience.
I still believe
this is a painting of the immortal's arrival.
I also believe
she will bless me.
Yes.
That inspector
was just making a blind guess.
But he really made the fisherman
disappear.
What's the use?
We have a painting immortal in our studio
not just because of that one painting.
So many of us
are indebted to her.
That couldn't all be fake, could it?
You're right.
I didn't mean to ditch you.
Why did you ignore me?
Tell me.
What case do you want me to help you with now?
Don't say that.
I want to give you a point
for your performance just now.
No need.
You don't want points?
I don't have evidence,
so I haven't taken the lead yet.
I just wanted to trick him,
but I failed.
That's why
you need me.
Am I not the grandmaster
of playing tricks?
You should have done this just now.
The two of us should work together
and back each other up.
-Su Jiu'er. -Maybe then—
You always say that I need you.
But have you ever thought about
what I need from you as a partner?
Our competition is not over yet.
I hope you will
do your best.
Your Highness!
Where are you going, Your Highness?
Your Highness.
Why are you running so fast?
I haven't finished talking yet.
I have an idea!
[Nanfeng Studio]
I shouldn't have suggested
making a bet.
I wanted to prove that
I am a worthy partner,
but I scared him away.
I'm even pushing him further and further away.
Father,
have you ever
written anything about
how to tame a partner?
Where are you going?
Shouldn't you
be guarding Painter Feng right now?
You should thank
your good partner, the prince.
He has offended every single person
in Nanfeng Studio.
People mock us
everywhere we go.
We couldn't stand it, so we came out for some fresh air.
You were kicked out?
You came out
because they told you so?
Lass.
If you aren't bothered, you take the night watch instead.
Fine.
I can't
let anything go awry with
this case again.
Lass,
this is Hu's water bag.
You don't usually take the night watch.
You'll need it when you need water.
You've always been incompetent.
Today, without us around,
I'll see you'll do when you get in trouble.
What are you murmuring about?
None of your business.
Let's go.
What is this?
You made this?
It's useful.
You're always causing trouble.
Look at them.
We can't let anything happen to
Feng Muyuan.
Yes.
Looks like we need to be more vigilant.
I wonder when Han Zheng
will come back.
It's my fault.
I keep wanting to control him.
I always tell him
nonsense.
That's because
I'm too weak.
You always say
you'll abandon me if I'm useless.
If I don't play tricks on you,
what can I rely on?
I'm just a weak Qian.
If I don't do that,
how can I keep you aroud?
Painter Feng?
Inspector Su?
Didn't I tell you all to go back?
I'm still a little worried.
I wouldn't be able to sleep well even if I went back.
But don't worry.
I'll leave soon.
I won't bother you.
I've thought about it.
You're just doing your job.
You're not trying to smear Nanfeng Studio.
I was really angry,
but I didn't really mean to kick you all out.
Seeing that you are still here,
I feel much more relieved.
When you get the chance,
please thank your partner
for his diligence
in the investigation.
It's our duty.
By the way,
where's your partner?
Did he leave you
here alone?
He...
Of course not.
How could he?
Of course.
He won't leave you
here alone.
Something feels off.
I don't think he's
talking to me.
But
His Highness really left me here
alone.
The bell rang.
Someone fell into my trap.
M- Master.
Why did you come back?
The authorities have already found out
about Junior.
Soon,
they'll find out
you're connected to the case.
But they
don't have evidence yet.
There's nothing they can do to me either.
You'd better run away now.
It's you?
How was it?
All is fair in war.
You weren't vigilant enough.
Guards!
The murderer has fallen into the trap.
Great! Catch him!
Brother Han.
What happened just now?
The lass' bell
must have caught someone.
Where is she?
She ran away.
She followed that shadow.
You mean the person
who flew out just now
was Su Jiu'er?
Are you surprised?
I am, too.
Uncle Hu, keep an eye on him.
I'll go after her.
Don't worry.
Leave him to me.
Stop!
You lass.
You couldn't trick me into helping you,
so you secretly used the Qi Vital Stone.
Are you crazy?
Qi Vital Stone?
I really don't know what happened.
Since I made a mistake,
you can scold me however you want later.
But right now,
we mustn't let him escape!
Who are you?
Stop!
Over there!
This way!
Stop!
Where is he?
Up there!
Su Jiu'er!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Wei Gonglin is over 50,
but his stamina is this good.
Did he use the Qi Vital Stone too?
Or
is this person a Qi?
Han Zheng!
Let's surround him
and take him down!
Three scars.
It seems I have really become
a master of martial arts.
Stop!
You have nowhere left to run.
Who are you?
Su Jiu'er, are you crazy?
I'm finally not a good-for-nothing.
Don't worry.
I promised you I'll catch him,
so I will definitely catch him!
This...
What's going on?
What happened?
Wasn't I in the sky?
Xu Youdao.
Wang Jirong.
Lin Zhixing.
Help.
Am I seeing ghosts
or
am I dreaming?
I...
Meng Huaiyun.
Why are you here?
Are you Meng Huaiyun?
Something is wrong.
Her pulse is normal.
Why are her eyes closed?
-Jiu'er. -Be gentle.
-Jiu'er, wake up! -Be gentle.
It's working.
Mother.
I was dreaming.
Why did you pinch me?
She pinched you so hard,
but you were dreaming?
How could you?
It's so early in the morning.
What should I do
if not dream?
Why are you guys
in my room?
You little...
Seriously.
We were so worried,
but you were dreaming?
You're heartless.
His Highness and Young Master Han
worried about you for nothing!
Physician Qin.
Are you alright, Jiu'er?
I'm fine.
Mother.
What's happening?
Have you forgotten
what you did last night?
What did I do?
I...
Last night, I...
I was on night watch...
That's right!
Wasn't I at Nanfeng Studio?
How did I get home?
You don't remember anything?
Lass.
Why don't you remember anything?
Do you remember last night,
you jumped three feet into the air?
You sped around,
trying to catch the murderer all by yourself.
You don't remember anything?
Hu, don't lie to me.
I'm not that capable.
Speeding around?
I can't even stand properly.
Jiu'er.
Do you remember
why you used
the Qi Vital Stone?
What?
Qi Vital Stone?
Help!
Help me!
Come on.
Time to eat.
Two handsome men are in front of you.
Why are you looking down?
Come on.
The foods today are all medicinal.
They're good for your health.
Eat more.
Hurry up.
You guys eat first.
I have another dish.
Eat first.
We'll wait for you.
Don't wait.
It's things like chicken stew with ephedra,
braised fish with silar,
and tofu stew with forsythia again.
What?
Still not satisfied?
Suit yourself.
Your Highnesses,
I've been eating
these dishes for over ten years.
I've never gotten tired of them.
How about this?
Let's not wait to drink.
Come on.
There are no rules of superiority in the martial arts world.
From today on,
after drinking this wine
and eating this medicinal meal,
we'll be the best of friends,
nothing less.
Cheers!
Come on, Your Highnesses.
Let's drink.
He was always at Nanfeng Studio.
He never left.
He even saved me despite what happened between us.
Forget it.
Why do I
keep trying to prove I am smarter
than this lass?
Jiu'er.
Here.
Eat this.
Thank you, Your Highness.
You're so sweet.
This was a blessing in disguise.
I got to experience the effects
of the Qi Vital Stone.
Do you want to try it again?
No, I dare not.
That's not what I meant.
It's just that I finally understand
why you hate people
who use the Qi Vital Stone so much.
The Qi Vital Stone is so powerful.
The Qi must be very weak
now that you've lost it.
Forget it.
If you told me earlier,
you wouldn't have
made the bet with me.
How about
we call it off?
No.
We have to continue.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't have done your best.
I wouldn't have noticed your capabilities
because of this, either.
However,
in the future, just tell me
what you want to investigate.
Sickly girl,
you can't do anything without me.
That's right.
I can't do anything without you.
I can't get anything done.
If you had figured it out earlier,
would we have fought?
Do you mean it?
Of course.
I...
Really...
I mean it.
Forget it.
As a Qi,
how can I
keep haggling
with a delicate Qian woman like you?
You can't say that.
I want to
be useful too.
It's just that I was born weak
and helpless.
There's nothing I can do about it.
But you eat a lot.
Look at you.
You only got a little powerful,
but you were about to risk your life.
Don't do silly things like this again.
With me around,
you won't have to
charge the enemy lines personally.
So,
what should I do next?
Get up early tomorrow
and interrogate Feng Muyuan for me.
Yesterday, when you were
abusing the power of the Qi Vital Stone,
I tricked something
out of him.
It's just as we thought.
He already knew
the murderer
was probably Wei Gonglin.
He refused to tell us
because he wanted to protect him.
Wei Gonglin wants to kill him,
but he still wants to protect him?
So,
Inspector Su,
it's your turn.
Take it.
This is mine, right?
It's for you.
Bye.
Take care.
You look cute
when you're talking nicely.
Painter Feng,
we're here today
to confirm with you again
that you really do not know
who it was that wanted to kill you that day.
Young Master Han.
Didn't you already know?
Are you talking about
you stalling for time for your master
in exchange for him sparing your life?
Although
your acting was sincere,
I think
there's another
possible explanation for this matter.
All along,
you have been your master's accomplice.
You don't have to tell me,
but we can already
arrest you
for being an accomplice.
Not bad.
You've learned 30 percent
of my skills in deception.
It's 70 percent.
Painter Feng,
I saved you yesterday.
Although it was rather chaotic,
I saw it very clearly.
That mysterious man
was left-handed.
He held a knife
and could scale walls,
so my partner and I
couldn't catch him.
You mean...
Painter Feng.
You're a painter.
I've seen all your paintings.
You are
someone with ambition.
Although
your master
has never praised you,
you didn't take to
painting with the Qi Vitality Stone
like your three seniors.
What does this mean?
It means you're righteous at heart,
and you believe in justice.
Am I right?
Why are you saying this?
Your master came here
using the Qi Vitality Stone.
Otherwise,
he couldn't possibly have escaped
from my partner and me.
You want to protect him,
negotiate with him,
and you want him to be
at least a little bit reasonable.
But Painter Feng,
I want to tell you,
with all my sincerity,
that I hope
you will
protect yourself.
Don't rely on someone who
made use of the Qi Vitality Stone to commit crimes
to uphold justice for you.
He is no different
from your three seniors.
I don't know why,
but it's amazing.
You don't know anything.
Fine.
I'll tell you.
All of this started
with just a coincidence.
In Nanfeng Studio,
my seniors were
Master's favorite disciples.
When Junior showed up, however,
everything changed.
Extraordinary...
Junior was very diligent
and extraordinarily talented.
Even when she had first gotten here,
she was already
outshining everyone else.
Maybe my seniors were envious,
or maybe they were jealous.
At some point,
they found a way
to surpass Junior.
You mean
they started
painting with the Qi Vitality Stone
because of
Meng Huaiyun?
Liu Fu.
It tallies.
From the 28th year of the Dingkun reign,
Xu Youdao,
Wang Jirong, and Lin Zhixing
started to have two painting styles.
What is the coincidence
you mentioned?
At that time,
the painting immortal didn't exist.
The "Painting of a Snow Night in Jiuxiao City"
[Painting of a Snow Night in Jiuxiao City]
still hung in the guest hall.
On New Year's Eve that year,
I wanted to copy Junior's painting
to learn her painting skills.
But in the middle of the night,
my three seniors suddenly came.
I was afraid they would laugh at me,
so I hid.
That's strange
I saw
someone passing by.
Eldest Senior.
You're drunk.
It's impossible.
How can you talk to Eldest Senior like that?
No.
Could Eldest Senior be drunk?
Eldest Senior has far-seeing eyes.
Come on.
Hush.
How dare you.
Lower your voice.
What are you afraid of?
Today is New Year's Eve.
Those ungrateful people from Nanfeng Studio
have all gone home to celebrate.
Only the three of us
who have no parents
are still here.
Who else could there be?
Is anyone there?
No, no.
Come on.
Let's drink!
Pour it for me.
Junior.
You're here to paint again.
Unfortunately,
the other person in the Studio who also had no parents
was Junior.
Come here.
Just in time.
Come on.
Junior, come here.
Let me teach you how to drink.
You never talk.
Why are you so arrogant?
Drink it.
Catch her.
Come back!
You're going to drink even if you don't want to.
Aren't you arrogant?
I'll let you have a taste of the Qi Vitality Stone Wine.
Where are you going?
She's dead.
I drank the Qi Vitality Stone,
so I was too strong.
Oh no. Look.
This is Master's painting.
What should we do?
Junior.
You must have been hiding for a long time.
So this is the truth?
Seniors didn't do it on purpose.
But in order to protect themselves,
they took advantage of the fact that
there were few people around on New Year's Eve
to dispose of her body.
Then, they made up rumors about the painting immortal
in case someone asked questions
about the damage
to Master's masterpiece.
You know such a big secret.
Why didn't they kill you?
Maybe they were afraid that
another missing person would be too obvious,
so they didn't kill me.
Soon after,
I asked to study abroad in the far east.
I was there for two years.
Two years later,
they seemed to think
things had settled.
We didn't talk
about the past.
I thought the matter wasn't significant
and had long blown over.
Until one day, Second Senior found out
the person in his painting had disappeared.
All three of them panicked.
So,
Xu Youdao borrowed money
to redeem the painting for Wang Jirong.
They scrutinized it,
but couldn't tell what had happened.
Instead, they thought Junior
was trying to kill them.
They didn't tell me about this.
It was only after you all came
that I found out this had happened
to Second Senior's painting.
But once Xu Youdao died,
you and Lin Zhixing knew
someone was trying to avenge your junior.
He had a reason not to talk.
Why didn't you?
No.
I went to find Third Senior,
but he said...
Why are you panicking?
No one knows about this
except you and me.
He's taking revenge like this
because
he has no evidence.
Just keep your mouth shut.
I'll find out who he is.
When that time comes,
we'll see
who kills who.
By the way,
don't you think Master has been
traveling for far too long?
The truth
is exactly as
Brother Han deduced.
Yes.
What came after
is what you all already know.
When Senior Lin died,
I knew I'd be Master's
next target.
But I believe
Master only means to punish me.
He wouldn't kill me.
I didn't kill Junior,
and I have always regretted
my cowardice.
So you've been
kneeling in front of the painting immortal
to beg him to spare you?
Don't worry.
With your testimony,
we can now issue an arrest warrant
to take him into custody.
You're safe now.
[Arrest]
Wei Gonglin?
Isn't this the famous painter?
Why are they arresting him?
I heard it has something to do
with the horrible case at the Lantern Festival.
What?
All done?
Yes.
They have been pasted on all the streets.
Dali.
Folks!
This man is a major criminal. The whole city is to be vigilant.
Those who report to the authorities with tips
will be greatly rewarded.
Hasn't the truth come to light?
Why are you
still worried?
Jun.
Listen up.
There isn't a body.
Everything rests on
Feng Muyan's testimony alone.
We can’t believe
everything he said.
It's just that
he insists it's the truth.
We can only take his word for it.
The most important thing now
is to find Wei Gonglin
and see if there'll be a turn of events.
You don't believe him?
I'm not sure either.
But I feel
something is wrong.
I think it's a bit lamentable.
Why?
Look.
Master Wei
is a famous master.
His genius in painting is almost divine.
He went this far
for his disciple.
Do you think he cherishes talent and
loves painting,
or hates them
for ruining his work?
I know who to ask now!
Who?
Jun.
Clean these up.
Don't waste them.
Let's go!
Where are we going?
Your Highness.
What do you mean?
I can't accept it.
It's okay.
This was all my idea.
Thanks to
your help,
we solved the case successfully.
You contributed a lot.
So I prepared
some delicious food
to express
our gratitude.
Don't you think
Jiu'er is usually slow,
but at critical moments,
she's very eloquent?
Keep watching.
She's about to start
talking glibly
to make him happy.
How do you know?
Because
I've been through this before.
I think you're here
not just
to treat me to dinner.
You are wise.
You can tell at a glance
what we want to do.
No.
I'm very glad
you think highly of me.
Ask me anything.
I'll tell you everything I know.
Actually, we came here today
to ask you
which disciple
Wei Gonglin liked the most.
What?
The arrest warrant has been issued,
but you're still suspicious of his motive?
You are
very well-informed.
However,
I can
understand this.
Wei Gonglin has always been fair.
After Meng Huaiyun became his disciple,
it is true
he favored her the most.
I think it must be
because she was
a talented female disciple.
Is that true?
I have another question
to ask you.
Go ahead.
Did Wei Gonglin love Meng Huayuan
as a young disciple,
or as a woman?
Inspector Su,
why are you asking something like this?
What's wrong with this?
I just want to know
who was the person who redeemed
Meng Huaiyun's painting.
If the master murdered them
to take revenge,
why would he help her
redeem all the paintings?
Wouldn't it be better to leave them here
and let them be immortalized?
Exactly.
Which is it then?
Mr. Li.
Can't you just say it?
Inspector Su,
we get along well.
I'll only tell you
about this.
Treat it like a little puzzle.
Let me test you.
Why are you talking about me?
Jiu'er.
What did Mr. Li say?
He...
He told me
the love Wei Gonglin had for Meng Huaiyun
was only that of a master
for a disciple.
He even personally
wrote calligraphy for her
and sent it to the Nameless Art Gallery.
Then...
Why did he have to say it secretly?
You're good at making things up.
Forget it.
I'm not going to expose you.
It's not the kind between you and His Highness
nor the kind
between you and your friend.
Mr. Li
is like that.
He's addicted to investigating cases.
He likes to play tricks.
There are many characters like this
in your books.
You should know.
Right?
That's good.
Why are you curious
about this?
You were the one who reminded me.
The love a master has for his disciple
is a great love.
If he really wanted revenge,
he didn't have to redeem the paintings.
That would only give himself away.
Lin Zhixing suspected
the person
who took Meng Huaiyun's paintings.
He seemed to have some sort of
extreme protectiveness and possessiveness
towards the one who got away.
So you wanted to confirm
if Wei Gonglin had special feelings
for Meng Huaiyun?
Yes.
If this was
his motive,
the murderer
would be Wei Gonglin.
But Mr. Li just said
Wei Gonglin
loves himself the most.
He favored the junior
because he wanted the best
for Nanfeng Studio.
Maybe
we overlooked something.
Jiu'er.
What is our direction
this time?
Meng Huaiyun's painting.
Lin Zhixing died
because he found the murderer.
That means
the murderer is whoever
has those paintings.
Lass.
Maybe
the murderer has hidden
the paintings away.
Then, let's look for
the person here
who has such feelings
for the junior.
Let's split up.
Excuse me,
where did Meng Huaiyun
usually paint?
She often painted
in the storehouse.
The storehouse?
Thank you.
Su Jiu'er.
I'll help her with her work.
You like to work so much?
Then do mine too.
How did I fall asleep?
Jiu'er.
You're awake?
Let me tell you.
I've searched all the paintings here.
And?
Nothing.
This is strange.
You see, Wang Jirong,
Xu Youdao, and Lin Zhixing's paintings
from when they were children are all here.
But why aren't
Meng Huaiyun's?
Maybe
they were also taken away by the murderer.
If you say so,
the murderer
must really have special feelings
for Meng Huaiyun.
I knew that long ago.
But...
Do we have no other leads?
Don't move.
What?
Look over there.
Jun.
Can you tell
who painted this?
This lady
looks like Painter Feng's style.
But the cloud
seems to be...
Meng Huaiyun's!
So it was really him.
Painter Feng is so diligent.
He never stops practicing.
But for two years,
he didn't produce anything.
That was when
he went abroad to study.
We missed
such an obvious clue.
Meng Huaiyun died
and the painting immortal appeared
both on New Year's Eve of the 29th year of the Dingkun reign.
That means
he was actually
studying in the far east then.
I see.