Now everyone,
let's play a game of passing and guessing songs.
Okay.
Let's go.
Everyone put on your headphones.
Each person will use the melody heard by the first person
to sing different lyrics in front of them.
The final guess of the melody song will be the winner.
Come on.
Okay, come on.
I once loved a man like this
He said, "No"
He said I was the most beautiful woman
Like this
Very simple
Wait for the prelude
I once loved a man like this
Hard to catch
This melody
You get it right away, don't you?
Got it
It's still the same melody, right?
I
I have thought for a long time
Jackson, right?
I cried and told you
Fairy tales are all lies
Very good
Isn't this the song?
Can I listen to it again?
Another song
I thought for a long time, I started to panic
Did I do something wrong again?
Did you understand the previous part?
Isn't it very simple?
I am a fire in the winter
Is this the song?
Come
You should know
this will break my heart
heartbreak
Okay
You sing
What was the song he just sang
I didn't hear the tune.
I
Oh no, what song is this?
It breaks my heart.
The first few lines.
Done
You guys are just in time for this song
Just captured
I never want another man
to see your charm
You break my heart
This will break my heart
What song are you listening to
Is it this song, right
It's not this song
Give me a tune
I forgot
How could I bear to let you
It's not that song
"Overfire"
Yes
Alright, come on.
I don't want you wandering around late at night anymore.
Really?
Not at all.
Do you understand? Do you know which song it is?
Yes, I know.
Got it.
I feel like I don't deserve to sit here.
Isn't it "Over the Fire"?
No, it's not.
You know again
No need for me to sing more for you
You want to show
That's enough
Give me a chance
Hum for me again
Try the questionnaire, okay
Don't pretend you can't hear
Take it off quickly
What
You are as comfortable as being in a nest
In the nest
It's a fish making a nest
The perfume
is like a pair of irresistible red high heels
"Love Like the Tide"
Isn't this song called "Overfire"?
"Overfire"
Wasn't it just now
"Love Like Tides"
that it appeared once?
"Overfire"
Your answer
The problem lies with you
I don't know the answer
It's because I don't know the answer
Isn't it just "Overfire"?
So, what song did you sing?
I sang
What about you?
Why did it go to "Overfire"?
Sister Xiaotong
You are like that fire
This song could be misinterpreted.
I'm leaving.
Song Yaxuan, come here.
You finished the last shift.
I'm in the last leg.
What do you mean by finished?
Come on, let's start with Xiaotong.
Jingyu, you're second.
What if I can't hear it?
It'll be ruined when it gets to you.
Brother Teng
I haven't seen my sister Xiaotong for a long time.
I can see clearly this way.
Alright, stop singing.
It's too perfect.
This part of the singing
I think even the rhythm got stuck.
Maybe I actually like being wasted by you
How about I teach you
Please don't ignore me
Did you hear it?
It's almost like the original.
I haven't heard this song before.
Great.
This round is yours.
Let me teach you again.
Wait a moment.
Let me think.
I haven't heard this song before, what should I do?
You sing this.
It's over, this song is over.
Blow, blow, you can't destroy my pure garden
After the first line is sung
He should know what song it is
Blow
I'll be honest with you
I haven't heard this song
Brother Jingyu sang it to me, but I can't remember
But I know it has a high note
That's it
Alright, you two are set for this round
I won't take the blame for this
Let's leave it at that
It's this song
I'll take the blame for this round
I haven't heard this
There's really no way
Haven't heard it
I was the third one over there just now
You are the third one here
Come on
My pride
Blow, blow
Come on
Wait a moment, let me think about this song
Blow, blow
Isn't this "A Love Letter to Filmmakers"?
How did it end up being sung like this?
It always happens at the third leg
Look
Completely wrong
This is how you sang it
Blow, blow
After singing the first line
He should know what song it is
How could I not know this song
Think of a song I wouldn't know
I just heard this song
Fine, blame me
Come on
Here I come
Isn't there still
Do you think you sang really well?
There is a second plan
There is another plan
There is some
My feelings are true
My dreams are true (my love is true)
The moon represents
my heart
It actually fits quite well.
There's another version that I've already forgotten.
Then just this note
Hurry up, forget it immediately
Alright
It always starts in minutes
What song is this?
Is it that song?
I only heard this line.
Why does this song sound so familiar?
Sis, don't look at me like that.
You should look at the third leg like this.
This round was my fault.
Sis, stop guessing.
You won't guess it right.
What was that song called again?
If
It's this song
Worldly Dream
"A Love Letter to Filmmakers"
Yes, it should be this song
Sister Yan's answer
"A Love Letter to Filmmakers"
Yes, it is
There are indeed two answers
I forgot one
One of them is this
He sent me two
Then I can only remember one
Me too
"A Love Letter to Filmmakers"
Yes
It's this one
Okay, it's this one
Sister, you also said it's this one
It's just that they made a mistake in the question
It's this one
It's this one, right?
Come on, let's listen to the original song
"New Endless Love"
Yes
This is a must-sing song for me at karaoke
Really?
Actually, it kind of sounds like these two
Yes
The beginning sounds a bit similar
Xiaotong, how about we switch places?
Let's switch
I want to go to the middle
I'll go first
I'll go to the middle
Let's switch
Let's see if it works
Where do we start?
I'll switch to the middle
I'll start
Can I go first?
You go first
If I can't do it, we'll switch right away
No
Let's sit together
Okay
We'll sit together
First, second
Third
Here comes the third
As long as the fourth person doesn't create on their own
I believe it can be passed to the fifth person
The second person should sing louder
This round, we'll start from the middle
What
I'm the first one, right?
But we really like your creativity
And you like my communication skills
"Second stick" stop talking
"Second stick"
"Third stick"
Turn this way
Yes
Okay
Come
Why do sweet dreams
always end so easily?
Okay
No problem, right?
You old
Why did you add those words?
I didn't add any words.
Whatever the lyrics are, I just sing them.
Just because I glanced at you in the crowd
I could never forget your face
Dreaming that one day by chance
Since then, I began my lonely longing
I know this song
Done
Finished
I sang
I could tell
That's right
It went smoothly this time
No problem
No issues
It's fine
Nothing unexpected will happen
What song
"Your Desk Mate"
Yes
The One Sitting Next to You
Here is an old
song, getting impatient, what
Wait, let me think about how to sing the chorus
Here is an old record
I got it
You got it
Alright
This time it's steady
Steady
Never had such a wonderful start
How could there be such a wonderful start
Alright
Wait a moment
She is starting to stir up a vortex
Get ready to have a big gash cut into you
It's not a crime for men to cry
No, there's one cry missing
Right?
I'm in a pretty bad shape right now.
It's over.
She was brought back.
Yes.
Right?
Want to ask why.
Made such a big circle and came back.
Done, this line went off track again.
Your first line
Yes
Is the first line and the second line from the same song?
Really?
The first line
The first line is this
Will you remember tomorrow
"Your Desk Mate"
Okay
Yes
Will you still remember tomorrow
The one who used to cry the most