Morning
Hello everyone
There are clouds on the mountain today
There are some clouds every day
Those clouds are really beautiful
This place is really beautiful
Yunnan is on the Tropic of Cancer
the only biodiversity oasis
It is our country's biodiversity
richest province
It has the kingdom of plants
the kingdom of animals
and the reputation of the world's garden
Behind the diversity
are the clever survival strategies of plants and animals
So today in Dali
we will embark on a clever nature journey
Clever
Let's go then
Hello everyone
Actually, Yunnan is a very magical place
In such a deep mountain area
Such a place with high biodiversity
They have
completely different "superpowers" compared to us humans
The one that just flew onto you
That little bug is called an aphid
You just remembered, so you say it
Yes
When we were just taking a break
It happened to fall on my hand
I told him
I said, what's going on
Its mother will give birth to a daughter
The daughter has another daughter inside her
And that daughter has another daughter inside her
Aren't there any boys
Xiaotong asked, aren't there any boys
Why mention me
Very good
This is a child who loves to learn
Yes
Both clumsy and diligent
Actually, only in cold places
do they need
males
to lay eggs and overwinter
In our hot Yunnan region
there are no (need for) males
only females give birth
females give birth
continuously reproducing generation after generation
Let's explore
what kind of amazing strategies
these animals can evolve
Alright, thank you everyone
Thank you, Dr. Chen
Thank you, Doctor
So before we start our
clever nature journey
let's first complete a task
to divide everyone into two groups
Our next task is called
It's actually very simple
just slap hands
Oh my
Won't we see bruised hands the next day?
The first day, it's still bloody
We have just one minute
for one person to choose another
and both sides attack
to see who hits more times
The winner joins one team
The loser joins the other team
Quick, take off the ring, sis
It's still sticking out
The ring
This is a bit
Wear the ring inside out
You're seeing blood on your hand
I'm most afraid of playing "Hand Slap" with Jingyu
I'm a bit scared
It's okay, I can't react in time
You push me, you get me out
It's nothing.
Come on, An Yu.
Okay.
Song chickened out.
I want to be on Jing Yu's team.
Showdown.
Okay
I said my reaction is screwed
Your reaction is slow, right?
Xiaotong and I
Why should I answer this question?
Start
Afraid
Come
It hurts so much
Two
Three
Crisp
Really anxious
Couldn't dodge it in time
Thrilling, so thrilling.
Wait for me to put it back.
No way
I need to switch partners
This hurts too much
It hurts a little
I want to be on the same team as Jingyu
It's bruising, it's bruising
I'm telling you
It bruises immediately
No need to wait until tomorrow
So red
Can we change it?
Is it green? It's already green.
It's red.
Right on the spot
I'm completely numb
The backs of my hands
When I clench my fists now, they're numb
Let's start the timer
What
I can't react in time
this reaction
You scared me.
Hurry up, this counts as time too.
I once thought you were an expert.
Jingyu, this...
Jingyu
Come back here.
My hand is also numb
I can't even dodge anymore, later on
Jingyu, your muscles are all worked to death.
Mine is starting to settle now.
It's starting to show white spots, mine.
I'm quite dark, so the color doesn't show.
This really has spots now.
It hurts a lot from the beating.
It's showing sha marks.
It made me sweat from the beating.
Come on, Song.
Skilled in both literature and martial arts.
Don't do that, you won't hit any of them.
Xiao Song's little hands
So fast!
Can't hit
Don't miss every single one
It's electric
You two work well together
Don't even change the rhythm
Can't hit once
It's quite frustrating
Once
Twice
I'm exhausted.
It hurts so much
He dodged the most
They just had a series of six or seven hits in a row
Only I, the great general
I feel so uncomfortable
The rhythm is out
Start
I think An Yu's reaction should
He must have gotten beaten up
He got beaten up.
An Yu, you are not just a black hole in some game
you are a complete black hole yourself
My hand is already red.
Don't touch it.
Getting anxious.
General Wang is getting anxious.
A bit uncontrollably trembling.
My palm is all red.
Show it.
Very red.
Okay.
Well done, Song.
You're really ruthless.
Your palm is red, you're really ruthless.
Almost broke the record, Song.
I was even slower than him just now.
Come.
The two of us.
I'm the worst at this game.
Dodge first.
Then you hit me first.
Then hit.
Okay, fine.
Here it comes.
I'm the worst at this game.
Really?
Aren't you weak?
Hit me then.
Just a couple of times
It's still quite solid.
One hit at a time.
What's going on, Daxi?
My hands are leaving afterimages.
It doesn't mean to hide after hitting
Okay
Give it a shake
Not bad
You play this game well
I'll go first.
Let's warm up first.
Is that necessary?
Take off the ring, good person
Spread out a bunch of rings
Come
Start
One time, it lit
Two times
Three times
Four times
Five times
Six times
Seven times
Why are you pecking me?
Eight
Why don't you come inside?
It's getting farther and farther away.
It's all off track.
It needs to be released.
About to break the record
Fifteen
Sixteen
Seventeen
About to break the record
Nineteen
Twenty
Twenty-one
Twenty-two
Twenty-three
Twenty-four
Twenty-five
No
Doesn't count
Didn't make it in the end
Made it in the end
I'll apply some medicine to my sister.
I put on my ring
You find two nails
Dig me
Alright
It went numb instantly.
What kind of pose is this?
A strange shape.
Just give it a try.
Four times
Five times
I didn't
I'm too tired to dodge
I'm exhausted
Pause
I need to catch my breath too
There's still pause time
A thrilling battle
These two sports guys
There's still the second half
I'm here
The second half begins
It starts when I say it starts
Start
Still playing this game
Gave up
I give up
She gives up
Not me
She gave up
I lost
Okay
Why am I grouped with this lot?
Am I?
Why do you seem so disgusted?
No
Teng hit Xiaotong
Twenty-five times
King of bruised hands
Who would have thought
Simply
I want a rematch with Teng
Come on, it's our turn
I'm giving it my all today
I don't need this hand anymore
Alright
I'll accept your challenge
I'll stand here
Okay
Why do you have a terrain advantage?
Start
You scared me
Why are you playing with one hand?
Same
That far up
I have to run for this
All around
I'm a little scared.
Nine times, this time it hit too.
Thirteen, it's lit.
Fourteen
Fifteen
Sixteen
Seventeen
Seventeen, all lit.
Not lit.
This one isn't lit yet.
Take a break.
I can't lift it anymore.
Grant me some strength
Come on, bro
Why did you high-five him?
I don't know either
He suddenly came over
Out of politeness
Like he made some kind of decision
Are you ready?
Ready
We can start now
Come back
I can't hit him.
"Old Fox" Brother Teng
Really can't catch
So annoying
Still up for a challenge?
This big bloodthirsty guy
Bro came to "die" fighting me
Turned into Yunnan ham
I can almost see your fingerprints
It's not that I play so well
It's that my opponent is excellent
All the big brains are gathered together
Take a look
No problem
And the clever trip to Yunnan
You also have an advantage
You have the "Great General"
Don't worry, I'm here
You should be called the Big Brains Team
Big Brains Team
What are you called?
Little Confused Team
Okay, we'll be the Little Confused Team
The four of you sit together
It feels very happy
At a glance, it looks like a row of teeth
Our first task this episode
is to protect the bird eggs
Two teams will wear special bird goggles
and successfully transport the bird eggs back to their nests
to complete the protection task
But you cannot use your hands during the entire transport
You can only use your feet
Best two out of three
Bird goggles
What the heck are bird goggles?
They are just glasses
Why is everything upside down?
Why is it really this confusing?
I'm a bit dizzy.
I'm confused.
Yes, these are my glasses.
It is.
Can you look at me?
Can you look at my feet?
I don't know where you are now.
Where?
So complicated.
What is this?
This is me.
Who touched my butt?
No, I clearly grabbed your head.
Xiao Song, come here.
Here, take this.
I'll go first.
How
so hard to control
Okay
Come
Don't move
I'm not eating anymore
You don't move
Wait a moment, let me find your mouth first.
Here it is.
Are you shaving my beard?
Okay
Xiao Hu, I'll feed you something
Can you find your mouth?
You should be eating it.
Where are you, bro?
Here
I took it off, it doesn't work.
Can't feed it.
I'm gradually getting the hang of it.
An Yu, turn around.
What's up?
What's up, sis?
Looking at it this way, the eyes are too funny.
Let me see, let me see.
What? What are you looking at?
That guy
His eyes just rolled back
Let me see
Let me see.
The double eyelids are too low.
That's too much.
The outcome of this round's task is particularly important
It will affect
the final rewards and penalties of this recording
The losers
will be provided with special delicacies
will receive our Yunnan specialty
scorpion, centipede, and spider feast
Scorpion, centipede, and spider feast
No way, I really can't eat this
I can't either
Tell me first
What's the biggest bug?
Scorpion, centipede
Isn't it a locust?
There are locusts
Right?
Are locusts the same as grasshoppers?
Pretty much
Locusts are definitely not grasshoppers
How are they not?
Really?
Yes
Locusts are grasshoppers
Grasshoppers are a type of locust
Isn't that the same?
If it's a type, then it is
You are a type of human
But are you Shen Teng?
You are twisting the concept
Too many golden phrases
I need to take notes on this burden
No matter how much you memorize the jokes
It can't compare to Teng's casual remark
Dr. Chen
No, it's going to choke again
It came glowing
Are locusts the same as grasshoppers?
First of all,
locusts and grasshoppers both belong to the order Orthoptera.
This is a technical term.
Just say yes or no, don't say too much.
To be precise,
So, in reality, is it
broadly speaking, you could say
yes
you see
it doesn't represent science, right?
I represent science
Dr. Chen, you are with Wang Anyu
One of you is responsible for wisdom
and the other for science
to promote human progress and development
Are the grasshoppers in Qiqihar locusts?
There are many types of grasshoppers in Qiqihar.
Locusts are one type of grasshopper.
Locusts are really tasty.
Locusts can also be eaten raw.
Eat raw
Help
Teacher Guan Xiaotong
I'm almost fainting from listening
Can you eat it?
I can't eat even one
I can't eat even one either
Absolutely not
We have to win, we must win
Why, why us?
No, we can't lose
We still can't win
We can't lose
Ambitious
No, I really can't eat this bug
How do you win this game
Protect the bird eggs
How do you protect them
It's like soccer
Just kick the egg into your own basket
Come on
Alright, come on
Has it started? Directly
Where is it
Where
is
the
ball
Where is the ball
Why are there only feet?
I saw it
Don't pull me
It fell
It really fell
Where's the ball
Underfoot
Who poked me?
Where's the ball?
No
Mr. Huang
Can you be more respectful?
Who reached out?
Don't reach out
Destroy
I have to destroy it
Wang Anyu
It's destroyed
Xiaotong is in front of you
Xiaotong, defend
Did you get in?
Scorpions, centipedes, spiders
Not here
This is too hard to get into.
I'll go guard the door.
Beautiful
Attack
Hold on
You're fine.
It's okay.
I'll push him away.
Attack.
No.
Don't kick me.
Wait, I found it.
I found it, don't move.
Hatching.
Where's the ball?
Where's the goal?
Here.
The goal is behind me.
Jingyu, you grab me.
This way, the goal.
Behind me.
Help.
Help!
Where's the ball?
Ball
She's here again.
You are from the other side
Go away
Go
Jingyu, take these two away
Mr. Huang
There's also Xiao Song
Isn't there also Xiao Song?
It's over
Kick, kick
Scorpion, centipede, spider
We have to win, we must win
Kick
It's in
I can't help with this at all
Don't pull me
No, I don't dare to kick
Right in front of me is Xiaotong's head
Did Jingyu just carry that person away?
It sounded like it
What is that?
I carried Xiao Hu out
It sounded like
Laughing to death
I was wondering why it went so smoothly
No, he can carry you too
That teacher Huang carried the opposing player away
This behavior in the entire sports world
is very rare
Everyone, the second round of tasks is upgraded.
Each team sends one person to be the goalkeeper.
Use a blindfold to cover the eyes.
The rest of the members still use bird's eye goggles.
It's harder.
Who will guard?
I'll guard.
You guard.
If you guard, we have no one to attack.
Right.
It's okay, I'll wear the blindfold.
I won't delay clearing obstacles either.
Okay.
As long as I can touch him, it's fine.
Alright.
That's fine too.
I'll be the goalkeeper.
Good.
Here it is.
Okay.
You're so fast
You came here
I've already got Teng under control
Do I still need to waste one of your spots?
Here, come
Attack
Teng, guard the door
Why did the goalkeeper from the other side come over?
Why did the goalkeeper from the other side come here?
Did I hear the ball coming?
Is the ball coming?
The opposing goalkeeper is coming over.
Goalkeeper.
The goalkeeper left.
Quick, attack Song Yaxuan.
Hurry, grab it!
Go!
Grab it, hurry!
I'll protect you.
Help!
Hurry, go!
My shoe!
Teng, hold on!
Teng!
Where's the ball?
I've never in competitive sports
worked this hard
I just don't want to eat bugs
Hurry up
Brother Teng, hold the line
Brother Teng
Hurry up
Do we need to restrain anyone?
You come
This
You stay here and hold them all
Get them out quickly
Huang Jingyu
Are you still leaving?
Give me your hand. Come on.
It hurts.
Go
Where to go
This way
Go
There's someone here, it's Teng.
I'll get the person out of here.
Over here.
Over here
Move Brother Teng first.
Where's the door?
Move Teng first.
The door has fallen.
Where's the door?
That's amazing
You can still kick it in like that
We won
We won, no need to eat bugs
I really worked hard
No need to eat bugs
No need to eat bugs anymore
It's fine as long as we don't have to eat bugs
Just to avoid eating bugs
We really gave it our all
So much effort
I have never in such a sports competition
worked so hard
So much effort
That is to say
Your structure is very similar to birds
Scorpions, centipedes, spiders
Can eat
Silkworm pupae are okay
I'm fine
We have to pretend we can't eat
It's called punishment
No way
Scared
I'm the most scared
Most scared of bugs
Looks uncomfortable
Don't scare me
Take a break.
Let me share something delicious with you.
This is my travel treasure food.
Xizhilang Konjac Jelly
Smooth and bouncy.
Zero fat, no burden.
Great joy eating Xizhilang
Double the joy
Happiness doubled
In a while, together with everyone
Share this happiness
Let's go
Okay
Please welcome the "Great General"
Come, our task for this round
is called "Race Against Time"
The two teams need to take turns guessing
The guessing team needs to choose one person
to sit in front of the frame and guess
The other three team members are inside the frame
and act out the topic they see
The other team
sits on either side of the guesser with their backs turned
and uses mirrors to observe and guess
The team that guesses the most topics correctly wins
The losing team has to eat scorpions
What
We worked so hard to avoid eating scorpions
We worked so hard
They also worked hard
Move the scorpions to your mouths
Did you hear that, Wang Anyu?
We need to give it our all this time too.
Got it.
Come on.
So, our team of big brains and little fools
Which team goes first?
We'll guess first, bro.
Whatever.
You guys act first.
Okay.
This little mirror is really small.
Why is it this kind of mirror?
Can you see clearly?
A mirror that can't show clearly.
It turned out that An Yu was looking in the mirror the whole time.
Not even looking.
Looking.
It's possible.
The smartest brother.
Then you look.
Lift it
A few words
The truth will come out.
What
How are you so smart?
By the way
This is Xiaotong
The determination not to eat scorpions
Well done, Xiaotong
I'm done here
That was too fast
Brother Teng is resting here
Come up and perform
The paper Daxi drew looks too much like a TV
This is so hard
As soon as you say seven words, they know
Alright then
I hold it like this
Got it
Come on
Here it comes
If you get closer, you can see everything
Really?
Come on
What are you doing here?
Drinking.
Carrying.
Beer foam
Sprinkle beer foam
How many characters was it?
I don't know
Seven characters
The intention of the drunkard is not in the wine.
No
The little girl picking tea leaves
Swaying wine glass
Wine glass under the armpit
Grape wine in a luminous cup
You can
You are really amazing
I really didn't notice this armpit
Grapes
Your Chinese exam score is very high
That's incredible
I can see it too
Your determination not to eat scorpions
Brother Teng fell asleep
Why is there no sound
I think I don't need to take the mirror
It's useless to look at it this way
It seems to be a very abstract question.
Flower
Haha Chicken
Beggar's chicken
Just a little bit more
Great
How did you come up with this?
Guessed
Really impressive
Beggar's chicken
Is there any beggar's chicken?
Then why are you yawning?
Yawning non-stop
Like this
You have to do it this way
Look how accurately they act
No, I don't call it like this
Come
I always think you consider yourself very smart
You sit there and guess
Xiao Hu, come
If we lose, it's your fault.
Start
Shucking corn
Peeling bamboo shoots
Double-sided tape
Okay
How did they all guess it?
Xiaotong, you're really smart, Xiaotong
You're pretty smart too
So determined
You absolutely can't eat that plate of scorpions
This is quite difficult too.
Then this one of mine
Come on
A few words
What? What are they doing?
Caught in class
Indirectly criticizing
Indecisive
Quick
Tattletale
Okay, Anyu
Okay
I give up
This is my determination not to eat scorpions
Four words can actually be tattling
Tattling
They said four words
Tattletale
Quick, change the person.
The pressure is too much for me.
I'll perform.
You go.
It's okay, you embarrass yourself a bit more. Quick.
This seat is too hot for me.
This seat of mine
What's this?
What is it?
Lyrics
This is too difficult.
A few words
Eleven words
What shy roses quietly bloom
Xiaotong
You are amazing
What
He hasn't performed yet
I'm a little scared.
I almost feel like I'm so smart
as if I "stole" the answers.
Great job.
This Xiaotong really has the ability.
Bro
How did you guess that?
Were you struck by lightning somewhere?
That's terrifying.
Let's switch people.
The pressure is too much for me.
I'll perform.
I can't guess it.
Go, Xiao Song!
With Xiao Song sitting there, let's play abstract.
It's steady.
No one can out-abstract him.
Can you give me fewer hints?
Just give me fewer hints.
Very confident, Xiao Song.
No, I just don't want you to see it.
I'd rather not guess myself.
And not let us guess, right?
A few words
Three
Sun Wukong
Monkey catching the moon
Beautiful
Who said that?
So fast
I didn't see how many words he said
Yes
Couldn't see how many words
Really didn't see it just now
I thought it was three words
Just like that
Very, very good
That entered Xiao Song's comfort zone
It's okay
Wang Anyu, go for it!
Go for it!
Washing machine
Front-loading washing machine
Fully automatic washing machine
Okay
Impressive
Xiaotong
Fully automatic washing machine
Impressive
These six words
Didn't you see me throw it in and leave, Xiao Song?
I didn't think about the washing machine
She is my wife.
Separated
I can't tell that I'm acting in there
I can't even see it
This is the only way.
How do I act this?
How many characters
How many words
Didn't see it, really didn't see it this time
Looks like eight characters
Four or five
Think carefully
It suits you, Xiao Song
What
A more abstract expression
I know
Yes, it's exactly the direction you're thinking.
Xiao Song
Think boldly.
Be a bit bolder.
Have I seen it?
Do I know it?
This thing
You can't possibly not know.
Let's see what this person is doing
Eating
Eating steak
Eating Western food
This is crucial for us
Come
Tomahawk steak here
Couple cutting steak
Husband and wife cutting steak
Chewy steak
Synthetic steak
Fresh steak
Sirloin steak
Wellington steak
What does Wellington have to do with their performance
What is that?
The Cowherd and the Weaver Girl
Seven
Give them the answer.
This is my wife
I really don't understand this
medium-well steak
This is a medium-well steak.
What is this?
There's also a clever pun
"Divorce" steak
So shocking
A thoroughly enjoyable performance
So explosive
So abstract
No
Medium-well is too hard to portray
Hu, you guess
I'll go
Good luck
You guys act a bit more abstractly too
Just like that was fine
They don't even know a few characters
We still have one more chance
Too difficult
Puppet
Beating up the puppet
Pouting, why are you still pouting?
Hit anyone you see
What is this thing?
Going out to hit the "fool"
The bird that sticks out gets shot
Five words
Do you want to do it again?
No need to act it out
I can just go over it in my head now
I have noted it down
So should we wait for you here?
We want to rehearse it again
No need for anyone to hit
Just like that, getting hit
Acting like getting hit without anything
Zombie
Zombie over there
Is it a zombie, Wang Anyu
That
So abstract
Is there anything about fighting "ghosts"?
What movies are there about fighting "ghosts"?
Russian nesting dolls
Is there anything to fight the "ghost"?
I got it, Song
I got it
But I really couldn't make the connection
So what do you know?
Three Battles with the White Bone Demon
Yes
Awesome
Alright
Nothing more to say
Awesome
Is it that strong?
Bro
Journey to the West
Three Battles with the White Bone Demon
One to eight
The Smart Team defeated the Confused Team
Our team members are amazing
Didn't we also score a point?
No shutout
That's a victory
Three Battles with the White Bone Demon
Let me use your mirror.
Look how solid An Yu's elementary education is.
This is my true level of intelligence.
Then you sit here.
Come on.
Say a few words first.
Uncared for.
What
Just now
Goubuli
Goubuli is amazing
Hitting the bull through the mountain
No
Hitting the tiger through the mountain
Turtle Style Energy Wave
For you
I turned into a werewolf
I became crazy
One is willing to hit, the other is willing to take it
Chain reaction
True Samadhi Fire
Adding fuel to the fire
Monsters and demons
Evil spirits
Possessed by demons
Great joy
Great joy from the start of this show until now
Guessed right for the first time
What was that expression just now
Stranger
I can brag for three years
No matter who you are
Please stay with Sister Daxi a little longer
Don't come down yet
Don't leave yet
I'm really happy
No matter who you are
Startle the snake by hitting the grass
It proves we acted quite well this time
Look at Teng's expression
I really am
I said "General"
Okay
Alright
Let's compete
I see the three words myself
I know it's a warning
The desire to win is rising
I've never been this serious before
Galloping on horseback
The horse stumbled
Who is this?
You acted this so well.
It hurts, I hit myself.
Strange
It's strange, bro
It's strange
Stay with Teng a bit longer
I'll be over to him soon
The person who came this way
The slow bird flies first
A bit slow
You guys are fast
Yes
The pressure is starting to build up.
Journey to the West
Curtain
Curtain "General"
Curtain General
Sha Wujing
Yes, Curtain General
Yes
"General"
Sha Wujing
Why mention yourself
"General"
Isn't it this one
Curtain General is enough
"General"
Change person, let someone else guess
Song, it really came to you
I'll be right over to you
Seven characters
Disgusting
The King and the Beggar
A well-fed person doesn't know the hunger of a starving person.
Sis, repeat that.
That's right.
Right.
A well-fed man doesn't know the hunger of a starving man.
Doesn't know hunger.
You insist on adding a word.
What more can I say?
Well-fed man.
Well-fed man, I added a word, right?
It's too uncomfortable.
A well-fed person doesn't know the hunger of the starving.
Is the hunger of a man the same as the hunger of a person?
But it seems he came to me.
Sis, this position suits you.
Hamburger
Sandwich
Turkish kebab
Is this three words?
Chinese hamburger
Yes
What is this?
What?
Thank you
Really impressive
Sis, just sit there
Great performance
Great (performance)
Right to the point
Yes
Done
Amazing
I want to taste what centipede is like
What's the score
Five to four
The moment to decide fate has arrived
Who will take this match point
Mr. Huang
No
This pressure is too much
Jingyu, prove yourself
I better not prove myself
Are you afraid, Jingyu?
Provocation
Jingyu
Xiao Song is asking if you are afraid
Yes
He doesn't fall for that
You
Then I'm afraid I can't guess it either
I usually can't guess it from the front
It's okay
How about I take a mirror to the back
Okay
It's okay, come on
Alright
What should we do?
How should dad act?
I don't know if Xiaotong has seen this movie.
Then we can only act out the wrestling and dad parts.
Am I acting like a daughter?
How should dad act?
I'm under a lot of pressure.
Ultimate showdown.
Come on.
Did she understand a few words?
Yes, she did.
What is this?
Wrestle, Dad
Impressive
What does it have to do with you, Wang Anyu?
I am
You came here just to make that face
A superb performance
Isn't it worth showing off once?
So, we call it a tie?
No
We won by a large margin, this round
The one where we were one to eight
The one to eight round
You play in the Olympics
No matter if you get a clean sweep
Or whatever
You always count the big scores
Right
Okay, the last question
One question to decide the winner
Mr. Huang
This is no problem
The pressure is on me now
I can't do it
The last question
One person sits on each side here
One person sits on each side.
Then one team sends two people to act, okay?
Okay.
Four people act.
Then these people guess.
Everyone turns around to guess, alright?
Alright.
Like this.
We designate which two of you will act.
We also have to designate you.
Okay.
Alright.
Choose the smart ones.
Brother Teng
Sit down
He even got a "critical hit" on him
General Teng
Xiao Song's performance
recognizing me so much
great joy
Xiao Tong's performance, An Yu's performance
Go, Song
Go, Daxi
Go
Just the two of us cheering is enough
They don't need cheering
Why would they need cheering
Go, bro
Go
This
Everyone can play a role
Yes
Then let's collaborate
You play Che Shui
Che Shui
The two of us will play Ma Long
Right
You need to relax
I realize you need to relax
This can't
You can't be nervous
Once you get nervous, it won't work
Come
Street Fighter
Ping Pong
A few words
Four words
Start drinking
Drink master
Driver
Competition
Ping Pong
Champion
Four words
Pegasus
Drunk driving
This is also crucial for us
Heavy traffic
Mr. Huang
They are playing the same character, right?
Heavy traffic
How did this happen?
How did Ma Long perform?
Tell me
They played ping pong
He won the ping pong game
He is Ma Long
He always wins
I am Ma Long
Then who are you?
I am his opponent.
She is.
Tomokazu Harimoto.
No, Ma Long should pull up his pants before playing.
Really?
He has this habit.
Admit it, you are convinced.
Really impressive.
Proved himself at match point.
Good.
So strong.
Whoever figures out Ma Long first.
Will win.
Everyone.
Today.
The Smart Team won two rounds in a row.
They are really smart.
Got it.
Where is it? Two consecutive wins.
The last round was a tie.
The Smart Team also won the bird egg protection.
Big.
Confused again, huh?
Little confused one.
Really impressive.
The next task
is also related to eating scorpions
Here it comes
So big
Do you think the other person is a
senior or a peer
That's not certain
Do you like her
Jingyu, did you ever love her?
I think the word "love" is too strong.
It's not enough to
express it with love.
What about Anyu?
I did love.
Wait a minute,
are we using the same words?
This thing is making it
too confusing.
Are you guys in a romance show?
It's stumping me.
Actually,
I originally thought Jingyu was very much like
that feeling of loving more deeply.
But there's nothing wrong with what was said, right?
Nothing wrong, right?
Transferring someone's warmth to
What was the song he just sang?
"The Moon Represents My Heart."
Makes my every day wonderful.
"Love Like Tides."
You don't need to feel ashamed in front of me
Quickly exchanging time for
Never had such a wonderful start
Jackson, right?
Why live so miserably?
But why do you smile bitterly and say
I understand everything.
Your first and second lines
are they from a song?
No need for me to sing more for you.
You want to show
This is a sure thing.