So beautiful
Feels like it's coming at us
No, that's not right
The winner of each round
can get a spot to choose a horse
Let's see whose horse
can win the horse race
Next, Teng
Being young is great.
This move is too tiring.
These two "gorillas"
are all crap.
It's all crap.
This crap is fresh.
My horse is versatile.
It can compete in races.
Show off its bones.
They say my horse is
last year's 40-kilometer champion.
The coach always says this.
Choose the white horse.
Choose this one.
Number two.
Number five.
Then choose number six.
The mountains are truly beautiful.
The scenery in Xinjiang is really stunning.
Beautiful.
Vast.
Grasslands.
So comfortable.
These clouds are really beautiful.
It's really nice here, really nice.
This view is truly unbeatable.
Is this wheat?
These snow-capped mountains are so magnificent.
So beautiful.
It looks quite spectacular.
Imagine how beautiful the background would be with those mountains.
Indeed.
Great joy.
Your hearing is really bad.
I called you, and you looked over there.
Maybe you didn't pass it to the right place.
I have a sharp tongue.
Hello everyone.
Hello, Teacher Chen.
Good.
Before we start the last task,
let's think about a question first.
Has anyone noticed
the color of the horse's body, which is its coat?
Clearly on the green grassland,
it turned into a black, white, and yellow horse.
Why are there no green horses?
Natural competition.
Because they eat grass.
They can't be green.
If they were green,
wouldn't they be better at camouflaging themselves?
They might get bitten by their kind while eating grass.
I never thought of this approach before.
This is the mindset of a scientist.
Let me tell you all
a very important reason
because mammals
are mostly red-green colorblind
and most of their predators
also cannot see red and green clearly
so in their world
only yellow is needed
to hide in the grasslands
Alright, so the next question is
why do horses have such long faces
because it's too cold
their
noses
need to have longer passages
to eat grass without bending too much
This is rare
Convenient to eat
What Mr. Shen Teng just said is very correct
I guessed part of it right
Actually, horses are very timid
They need to see all their predators
Their faces are very long
This way, their field of vision is wider
Horses' ears have a "superpower"
Horses' ears can move
They can rotate 180 degrees
They have the largest eyes with peripheral enhancement
Plus, their ears can hear distant sounds
This forms their ability to use all five senses
To sense any danger
Amazing, all five senses are activated
So, this is the "superpower" of horses
Thank you
Come on, everyone
We are about to go through a
sensitive ears
to train everyone's ability to locate sounds
Everyone will be divided into two groups, attackers and defenders
for a competition
The attackers will hit the defenders five times in a row
to win
Best of five rounds
The winner will get the last two horse slots
The winner of the last round
will automatically become the two team captains
Xiao Song, An Yu
You were the winners of the last round.
They both can't believe it
You guys, come forward
Those willing to be their teammates
Please stand behind them
We choose
Everyone's chosen, I'll cover the rear
Come
The three of us go this way
The two of them go that way, and it's done
Alright
Keep it simple
Please take a look at your teammates
I knew it was you all along.
A hint of disdain mixed with surprise.
Xiao Song
Satisfied
Alright
Brother Bai
We, the post-90s generation
Our post-90s group
Yes
Okay
What's wrong?
Got it.
Let's start.
Come on.
Who goes first?
Hitting and getting hit are different.
You're good at taking hits.
Be nimble.
They're better at hitting.
I'll do it.
Okay.
Do it.
It bounced back
We chose the right person
I'll go
Brother Bing, you choose the opponent
I'll choose
You choose
Da Xi, come here
Come on, Anyu, come on.
Come on.
Pink little hammer
Come on, rock-paper-scissors
The attacking side directs the blindfolded teammate
The defending side opens the watermelon blind box
The speed at which the defending side eats the watermelon
Determines the duration of the attack
Once all the watermelon is eaten, the roles switch
So the attacking side
Teammates don't need to eat
Yes, we attack
Just tell me where to hit
Then they eat the watermelon
Once they finish eating, we switch
Once finished, Bing will hit me
You guys need to help me eat some
Okay, eat
Otherwise, I'll get hit
Eat a lot, I'm just thirsty
Are you eating, Allen?
Okay, I'll do it
You eat
Then we'll both eat
I'll direct
Bro
Feel the weight
Smart
This one is light, mine is light
Come on
Go for it
Not much
Three
Two
One
Start
Brother Bing, dodge
Charge forward
You can move again
Keep dodging
Move again
Dodge to the right
Move
Brother Bing, go left
Right side
Run
To the right
Turn right
He's in front of you
Three steps to the right
Move forward again
He's in front
Run quickly
Three steps to the right
He's up ahead
Keep going forward
Hurry up
Left, right
Quick
Left
Hurry up
Right, go right
Run to the right
Run quickly
Behind, back
Right
Behind, behind
Further back, back
Back, directly behind
Hurry up
Right
Brother Bing, run quickly, okay
Chandlerpan, run quickly!
Run forward!
Okay, got it.
Hurry up
Chandlerpan, run quickly
Quick
Right
Yes
Hurry up
Go
Run straight ahead
Right
Go right again
Run forward
Underground
Yes
Go straight, yes
Move forward, get up
Chandlerpan, run quickly
Go right again, right
Three steps to the right
Run straight ahead in front of you
Run forward
Yes
Underground
Hurry up
They are reporting positions
Okay, five more times.
Is it delicious, you two?
Meat.
The teammates aren't very helpful, Bing.
You have to eat the watermelon quickly.
Is this the reason?
Who will come?
Do you want to eat or fight?
Then I'll fight.
Rock-paper-scissors is important.
Okay.
How about I fight, brother?
Go.
Did you forget?
I rely on speed to win.
Go.
I'll do it, Bing.
Don't let Lun.
You have to participate in the next few rounds.
Last time
we
the time we splashed each other's faces
Come on
I won't go easy on you
Rock, paper, scissors
Okay
I'll just get hit
It's fine
We'll finish eating soon
Watch out
I will run very fast
I will end your pain quickly
Come on
Alright, get ready
Three
Two
One
Start
Alan, twelve o'clock direction
Easy
Alan, charge forward, quickly!
I rely on speed to win.
Ten o'clock direction.
Ten o'clock.
Smart thinking.
Right, two
Two twenty
Right
Go
Right, reach forward
Quick, grab it
Forward, left
Left
Go up, Daxi
Go straight
Go straight, right
Turn left, right
Forward
Okay, right here
Once
Twice
Thrice
No, what's wrong
What's wrong, what's going on
Below, below
Changed
Daxi ran
Smart
What are you digging for?
Alright, let's switch offense and defense.
Daxi is running.
Right
Hit her
Right front
Smart
Move forward
Why
did you hit the ground
Move forward
Da Xi, charge
Go straight, right
Forward
Go straight
Move forward
Switch
Left side
Switch offense and defense
Switched again
Right
Hit it
Continuous beating
Alright, print out all the ones for next season.
So tired, this
How did the hammer get switched over?
Good job, Daxi
So fast?
Actually, we could go even faster
Because just now I blew the whistle
A watermelon seed got blown in
Brother, didn't you just call for a minute?
How did I end up talking for so long?
Because they eat quickly over there
Come
Here I come
You go ahead
Go for it
Yes, it's underground
Yes, fight
Okay
This is an enormous disgrace
This is forcing me to go again
Ice, it's recovering
Yes
Go
Come
Let's go
But brother
Who eats watermelon
Can you hold a stick in your right hand and a melon in your left hand
and fight while eating
Do both tasks for me
Come
The stakes are high.
Okay.
Brother Bing
I'll beat you a second time.
I'll teach you a lesson.
Come on.
Go.
Charge forward
Move to the right, a little to the left
Yes
Move forward
To the left, left
Right
Turn right
Back again
One
Behind you
A few more steps forward
Left hand
Swing to the left
Hit
got beaten up
A good beating
Switching offense and defense
So big
He's on the ground
Ahead
Run straight ahead
Left side, left
Left
Arrived
Okay
Switching between offense and defense
Run quickly
Okay
Did we win?
What?
We won, right?
I'm going
I'll do it
I'll do it.
We can't all go together.
Can I go too?
You...
Xiao Song is coming too.
Who's going?
I'll go.
Come on.
Okay.
Go, Brother Bai!
Xiao Bai
Rock, paper, scissors.
Xiaobai, I will call you later.
It's okay, bro.
It will be over soon.
Xiaobai hasn't reached you yet.
I've finished my snack here.
Wait, why are the audience members also talking tough?
Let's start.
Charge straight ahead
Sorry
Sorry, bro
Come on, I'll take this
Brother Teng
Hit
How come this
Brother Teng
Move forward
Move forward, get up
Get up and move forward
Keep moving forward
Left side, a heavy stick on the left
Left side
Behind
Move back, fall back
Move back again
Move back
Behind
Move back again
In front
Right, right side
Right
Right, walk ten meters
Move forward ten meters
Is it ten meters?
Bro, step back.
Let's block him, bro.
Step back.
Walk forward ten meters.
Okay, hit him.
Just one
Brother Bai, move forward
A little closer
Sorry, bro
Sorry
It's not over yet
Brother Teng
Hit
Xiaobai, I'll beat you black and blue
I can't do it anymore.
Brother Teng
Who's calling?
Teng is attacking.
No movement.
Grazing.
I'll go.
Xiao Song went.
I'll do it myself
Give it to me.
Defeated but still ashamed
Defeated but still honorable
End your pain quickly
It's on fire
I'll be there soon
This is too big
Just two pieces
Charge
Yes, good
Go diagonally
Straight ahead
Front left
Stand straight and walk to the left
Underground
Hit him
Right side
Right
I'll beat you to "death" with five consecutive hits
Where did you go?
Yaxuan, take a break first.
Going home.
What are you laughing at?
Where did you go?
Left
Far from you, left
Have those two not finished eating yet?
Right away
Swing it backward
Where are you?
So tired.
Move forward.
Forward
Right
Hard right
Yes, straight ahead
He went out
To the left
Xiao Song
I can't do it anymore
We won
The fruit I hate the most is watermelon.
Really?
What's your favorite fruit?
Watermelon.
Really?
No.
There are people who don't like watermelon?
On the first day, you said your favorite fruit was watermelon.
This episode is over.
I'm almost "sick" of it.
You won unfairly.
You three.
We three.
Our Anyu team defeated the Xiaosong team
to secure the last two spots for the horses
one horse per person
Set up a step for me at that gap.
Let me see if I can ride up.
Bro, after you ride it,
I finally understand what it means for a pig to ride a rabbit.
Brother, what are you going to do?
Brother
What?
Next is the Meituan group-buying extra meal competition
by horseback archery
hitting balloons of different sizes
can make the Meituan magic coupons
expand to different amounts
5 yuan magic coupon
can expand up to 50 yuan
the saved money can all be used for extra meals
who will try
young people
This young man
Being young is great
Come on
Song
Not a bit flustered
Come on, ready.
Go for it.
Cool
Gone
Come on
Beautiful
It's not your fault, blame the arrow.
Come.
Okay
What's wrong? Who pushed you?
Alright, let's leave it at that.
I'll shoot another arrow for Daxi.
That's it.
Who's coming up?
Alan
I'm coming up.
It's all yours.
I'll give it a try.
Okay.
One hand in the pocket
Alright, brother, this works
Shift up
Shift up quickly
No problem
Not yet
Even the stop has stopped you
You still have no problem
Swing your leg up
Yes
Why did I hear a bang?
Please give me the crossbow
Crossbow it
Let me crossbow it
Wonderful
Did I shoot the arrow just now?
You just got beaten up by a horse, right?
Let me try
First, get the style right.
This thing
is really deadly
Do you think we should move together?
Come on, bro
You'll run out of energy soon
Chandlerpan, do you need a crossbow?
Yes, a crossbow
Why would I come up here if I didn't need a crossbow?
It's quite smooth.
Just follow the force of the "gun".
Let me tell you
The people who didn't come up
This is completely different from what you imagined
Did it explode?
It even "misfired."
Really scary.
Just these two and a half "bullets"
And kicked it once more
Almost
You must look back
You must keep your head
There is still one "bullet"
Who turned it around for me?
Come on, drink up.
Come
This is way too slippery
I exceeded my exercise limit today.
Let's go eat.
Okay.
Alright.
Let's go.
Tianma Special Barbecue
This name is pretty good
Our first stop is Xinjiang, without a moment's rest
We set off as a group
None of us are going solo
Bro, you just took the lead
You hit the jackpot
You need to eat well to perform at the horse racing event
Show your skills
That was smooth
What else is there
I am now
Quickly ordering food for everyone
This four-person meal for the director's team
It's only half price on Meituan group buying
This set meal is really worth it
Group buying saves 200
Using the coupon saves another 50
Saved enough for an extra serving of roast lamb
All the main dishes are served
Travel group food
Just use Meituan group buying
The coupon saves even more
We are not lacking
Not bad
Xiaobai and Daxi
Only two horses were chosen
Then maybe the champion is among them
Then Xiaosong
There are two horses
I can
spare one
From today, I'm a fan of Xiao Song.
Which brother did you offend?
This is too difficult.
It's better not to even it out.
You should ride yours.
No need, don't be afraid.
Come on, let's pick a horse outside.
Okay.
You choose first.
Then I'll choose.
Which number is this?
Which one?
Number three.
Little three.
Then I'll choose little three.
Then I'll choose little four.
Little three, little four.
It's okay, don't be afraid.
This is just a sense of ritual.
Its face is too long.
Run well tonight
You are the most obedient.
You are the most beautiful.
Ladies and gentlemen,
viewers at home,
welcome to the first
"Start Now" horse racing event.
Let's give a warm round of applause to welcome
the six horse contestants
and their owners.
Let's go, amateur.
Giddy up.
High heels.
Chelsea.
Don't step on my Chelsea.
Who can this shoe kick to "death"?
Appearance
Passed
Go, number three!
Go, my number five!
I feel like my number one horse is sure to win.
Number twenty-six seems very confident.
My number five looks eager to move.
It's drooling.
It's hungry.
And a telescope
High-end
Is it my eyesight?
Or what?
I saw it wrong.
Saw it wrong.
Horse number one.
Gave me a scare.
Come on!
Horse number three.
The one with goggles must be fast.
Why does the rider of my horse
not even wear glasses?
Some have small eyes, not easily distracted.
How much does the rider contribute?
How much does the horse contribute?
Seventy-thirty, eighty-twenty.
I guess.
Do you mean seventy for the horse or the rider?
Horse, seventy.
Number one is kicking.
Welcome everyone to
the "Let's Go Now" horse racing event.
This is a 2000-meter speed race.
The start and finish of this race
are right in front of you.
Two and six
Then your chances are high
This horse racing event is about to start
So nervous
Counting down five seconds
Five
Four
Look, my horse is getting restless
Yes
Three
Two
One
False start
It was a false start
Go, number three
Far ahead, friends
Alright, we now see number one
On the outer lane
Currently in first place
The white horse is so fast
Next, we see
Song Yaxuan's horse
Two-year-old horse group, 2000 meters
For our speed race
It's a short-distance race
It's also one of the most classic
Such a race course
The white horse is still first
The white horse is so fast
Look at it
A horse is catching up to my white horse
Alright, we see
our number one and number six
are vying for the first place position
number six horse
we see our number six horse
and number one horse are neck and neck
can the number one horse hold
the first place position
Alright, we see our horses
are already on the opposite track
having covered a distance of 800 meters
About to overtake.
Unleash your inner power, Number Six.
I'm running out of steam here.
I...
It's okay.
There's still the second half, Ma Ge.
No, Ma Ge went.
Ma Ge
Halfway through the journey
My horse is falling quite behind
Go number five, go number five
Go number three
Number six
They're starting to speed up, folks
Alright, what we see now is
Number one, number six
Less than half a horse's length apart
Quite intense
Tied for first, it's a bit tense
Go number six
Go number one
Overtaking on the curve
Go number one!
Go number six!
Has overtaken
Number six
Overtaken again
Alright, we see
Our number six, Song Yaxuan's horse
has become the new lead horse
Now there's only the final turn left
Other riders have started to accelerate
Let's cheer for them together
Come on, there's still a chance
Stop holding back, Number Four.
Run
A straight sprint shows true strength.
Go number five!
Go number six!
Keep going!
Go number one!
Go number six! Go number two!
Go number six!
Go number five!
Number six is so fierce.
Not bad
Congratulations to our number six
for crossing the finish line first with an absolute advantage
and becoming our top horse today
Does anyone choose this number six?
No
It's the smallest
Then I'll choose number six
You chose a small horse
Go number six
A horse is catching up to my white horse
Number six
Number six is so fierce
Is number six the one that jumped the start?
Who is this?
My horse
Is this part of the competition?
Alright, we see our number four horse
also crossing our finish line
There are also those in Mali who are not strong
This time, the horse racing event
The 2000-meter speed race has come to an end
Congratulations to our number six horse
for becoming today's top horse
Other riders are also encouraged to keep up the good work
in the next race
and achieve a better result
Number six, unexpected
Number six
It is the smallest
Watching them ride makes me want to cry
Next, we will broadcast the award ceremony
Welcome to the horse racing awards ceremony
Now approaching us is
the second place winner of this race
horse number one
Let's welcome our award presenters
Wang Anyu and Teng Ge
to present the award to today's champion horse and its rider Xiao Song
to present the award
Under what title are we
allowed to present the award to the champion
We are the second and third place winners
Alright
Congratulations to the champion of this horse race
Let's invite the etiquette lady to present the trophy
I can be the etiquette lady
Go
I'll present the award to them
Big carrot
These are all the exciting moments of today's horse riding
Congratulations, young man
Are we taking pictures now
Pretend to take pictures
Okay
So, having won this horse race
I believe our horse
must have a lot to say at this moment
Let's invite our champion horse
to give a speech
Okay
Then please
Then please, our Yaxuan
translate for us
It says
I think the older brothers and sisters' taste
is not very good
No, excuse me
Excuse me
You picked your nose and wiped it on me
I didn't pick
Chandlerpan, translate for Anyu
Regarding the horses that narrowly lost to Xiao Song today
What exactly are their feelings
Actually, after the game
it told me
it mainly blames itself for today
Because it really did
perform excellently in previous performances
and always showed outstanding performance
but it falls apart as soon as it gets on stage
this is very similar to its partner, myself
who also tends to fall apart at critical moments
Yes
That's all for its speech, thank you
My number one Xiaobai
After the race
I consoled it alone for half an hour
Tears were still streaming down
Before coming in just now
I was still wiping its tears
Complaining
Complaining about horse number five jumping the start
Six, four, three, two
Also jumped the start
Number one Xiaobai was on the outermost lane
All the unfavorable conditions
Were present
Many factors
But that's how competitions are
There are both chances and inevitabilities
Hope next year we can
Perform normally
Achieve a fair and just
Fair and just
Competition environment
Thank you everyone
Thanks to both of you
Come, let's invite Jin Chen and Xiaobai
They also have the right to speak
Yes, we
Xiao Huang
It has a bit of an upset stomach
Plus, it lacks experience
That's not its fault
Due to physical reasons
So I hope next time
It can achieve a good result
I believe in it
Sixth place
Told me a lot
It was indeed very last minute
Because I heard it was today
First time participating in such a big competition
The number five horse that has been running quite fast
See, I told you it would be the champion
Mine is quite stable, right
I feel like these
shouldn't be participating
a bit
this is for it
the first official race of its life
I see
Competing with these seniors feels a bit unfamiliar
But it's not its fault
So let's try harder next time
Alright, thank you everyone
We have reporters
and some simple questions
I would like to interview Mr. Allen first
May I ask, regarding not having a horse partner today
do you have anything to say?
As long as they have fun
Our goal is to make them happy
Although I didn't get to choose a horse
but I have something delicious
Pure Zhen 0 Additive Yogurt
has always been with me
With us as partners, we will surely succeed next time
Okay
The next interview is with Mr. Teng
Mr. Teng
I am a reporter from "Pure Zhen Times"
Thank you for your hard work at the horse racing event
Delicious
This sip tastes purely delicious
You really understand me
I heard that a secret weapon was prepared for this competition
To be a cut above
you must use the ultimate weapon
When Pure Zhen 0 Additive Yogurt appears
it makes other contestants so envious they give up
Can this be said?
It says yes
Okay
Let's once again congratulate today's
champion horse partner, Xiao Song
Okay
I just want to thank everyone
Now we
enjoy our celebration banquet for today's horse racing event
okay?
okay
Fragrant
So aromatic
Extremely fragrant
Delicious
This is really kidney
Come on, kidney
I'll have one, bro
The kidney is very delicious.
Delicious
Does it taste much different on a big branch?
This branch has flavor
Yes
Red willow branches have flavor
They have flavor
Then this iron skewer also has flavor
Rust flavor
When I was a kid, the lamb skewers I ate also had
a bicycle flavor
They were all skewered with bike spokes
What is this?
Grilled salmon
The salmon here
Is it salmon from Xinjiang?
Xinjiang salmon
Now Xinjiang salmon
is very famous now
sold worldwide
Isn't this the farthest place from the sea?
Xinjiang's arid climate and unique environment
have caused soil salinization
But humans discovered
that in these saline-alkali lands
the salt content is similar to seawater
After improvement
they turned the saline-alkali land here
into a marine environment
So we can enjoy
in this inland area farthest from the sea
such delicious and pollution-free seafood
Wisdom
This
Come on, have a bite
It's quite tasty.
It's still a bit tough.
Have another skewer to press it down.
Let me taste this rice first to see if it's good.
It's just a bit cold.
Cold? That's not okay.
Fry a bowl.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
Here.
Bring the rice up, come on.
Master, do you need my help?
Get me ten.
Ten, twenty lamb skewers.
That's perfect.
Alright.
Is that okay, Master?
Yes.
Here.
As soon as I pick up the rice spoon,
you call me Master, right?
Using that much?
You do it, bro.
You'll feel great after eating.
It's time to eat.
I'll take a bite first to taste it.
It's also delicious
Take a bite
Master's heartfelt recommendation
It smells so good
This fried rice is so tasty
Egg
It's fried rice
Fried rice
How do they fry the eggs like this?
Who knows?
The green onions are the finishing touch
Absolutely
I'll make you a dessert
There's also dessert
This season, thanks to this Pure Zhen
Accompanying everyone on the journey
Today I'll use our
Pure Zhen 0 additive yogurt
To make an authentic Xinjiang dessert for everyone
Pure Zhen yogurt rice dumplings
Yogurt rice dumplings
Are they tasty?
Tasty
Since we have nothing to do
Let's play something
Dance
Xiaobai
Can you use your brain when playing games?
Intuition isn't our strong suit as men
Can you use your brain?
Song chickened out
I can only say
The wolves have banded together
You're guessing again
You guessed like that last season too
You're not suited for this game
Wang An, my brother
It's all
psychological blows
Today, we will experience as a family
a day in the authentic life of the locals.
We are a family living on the grasslands.
You guys, try not to let the youngest do anything.
Come on, little brother.
Here I come, "big brother."
"Big brother" is so amazing.
The second child loves to imitate people.
The third child loves reading books.
All the knowledge is flowing into my brain.
The fourth child loves singing and dancing.
We feel so fulfilled on the grasslands.
Teng, why aren't you talking?
What's wrong with Teng?
Is Teng done for the day?
I think it's Teng.
If I were a wolf,
I would fight to the "death."
I would spit this thing out at the same time.
Shen Teng
Select the three most handsome people internally
I see you guys
how handsome
made me nervous all of a sudden
Isn't this simple
Bullfighting
Who is the one with the covered face?
This is a dimensionality reduction strike.
Now all of us
point to who you think
is the most handsome person.
Come on.
One, two, three, point.
In the very center of us
is what we prepared for the champion.
It's perfect for you, Xiao Song.
This is fun.