This time
we are heading to nature's
various slices
Feel it within
the hidden energy
The entire cast of season two promises
to never be careless
or picky
to never say "you guys play"
I'm tired, I'll take a break
to never say "you guys eat"
I'm on a diet, I'll eat less
to never complain about being tired before dark
to live each day with full enthusiasm
to not spoil the fun or complain
to fully enjoy the good times
to never let words fall to the ground
to never strain a thigh
to never secretly work out
to never eat alone
to never break a promise
to never think I'm very beautiful
to never let everyone go hungry
to set off happily
and return home joyfully
Come on
A few words
Okay
Carrying an Italian cannon
Galloping on horseback
Plan
Hi
What is this?
Hot air balloon
What is this
The sun is shining
What are you doing
Hi
Hi again
Going to sleep
Is this a song?
Four characters
So busy
What's going on?
It feels like there's a dance battle going on back there.
What are they doing?
Stop fighting!
They're both fighting now.
I...
You can't intervene now.
I'll do it later.
Hurry!
What is this?
Cannon
"Gangnam Style"
Okay
Who's next?
Xiao Song, you choose.
Brother An Yu
Come
Come on
Four characters
Carrying a cannon
The second character
Hit
It's over, the second sentence
The third sentence
Not the third sentence, it's a character
The third character
You are doing it character by character
I can't hear
The third character is "up".
The fourth character
Okay
It's fine
Just four characters, right? This song
Are you describing the song title or what?
I don't know either.
This is already a graduate-level question.
I feel
Three words
The second character
is "Niu"
The third character
Morning glory
What
What is that?
Picking up cow dung, you say.
Where did the morning glory come from?
The main thing is
it keeps leading me
and then it's the cow again.
Not because
of my "morning glory"
I read everyone's comments online every day
I think netizens are even funnier than me
I didn't think that much
I thought of it
but I feel like there's no problem
I really think so
Alright
If I hadn't thought of it
I should have been
very confident when I said it
I hesitated a bit
which means I might have had some concerns
It's too hot in this room
Director
Should Xiao Song and Xiao Hu
poke each other's dimples
they started fighting
Okay
Makes sense, let's do it
What are you doing
They're fighting here
Why are you hitting me
You dare poke my dimple
This is the only place on my body
that you can't poke
I'll poke you
How did you know
my dimple is my weak spot
You are such a bully.
You keep poking, you poke continuously.
I'll poke you to death.
Come on, poke and slap in circles.
Bro, I think I made you look great.
Everyone sit side by side.
We male actors are very particular about scratching here.
How about I do it like this?
Okay.
How old are you?
And you still make us scratch here.
Alright, and so on.
During the process,
whoever loses drinks a sip of water.
Okay.
I like drinking water.
How many monkeys are in the desert?
One monkey.
Two monkeys.
Five monkeys.
Six monkeys.
How many monkeys are in the desert?
Three monkeys.
Four monkeys.
It feels very sneaky
From that monkey to the next
Okay
Still don't understand, Daxi
Every time after playing
This round, the non-monkey person shouts
Okay
Come on
I'll drink
How many monkeys are in the desert?
Six monkeys.
Three monkeys.
Four monkeys.
Let's choose another one.
It's a bit of a waste on the monkey.
Think carefully
It suits you, Xiao Song
What
A rather abstract expression
I know
Yes, it's exactly the direction you're thinking.
Xiao Song
Think boldly.
Be a bit bolder.
Have I seen it?
Do I know it?
This thing
You can't possibly not know.
Give them the answer.
This is my wife
I really can't understand this.
Medium-well steak.
This is a medium-well steak.
What is this?
Monsters and demons
Evil spirits
Possessed
Great joy
Great joy since the start of this show
Guessed right for the first time
What was that expression just now
Strange
I can brag for three years, I
No matter who you are
Please stay with Sister Daxi a little longer
don't come down yet
don't leave yet
I'm really happy
Startling the snake by hitting the grass
It proves that we acted quite well this time
Look at Teng's expression
I really am
I said "General"
Okay
Alright
Let's compete
When I see those three words
I know it's a warning
A slip-up
Who is this?
You acted this so well.
It hurts, I hit myself.
Stay with Teng a little longer
I'll be over to him soon
The person who came over like this
Come
Street Fighter
Ping Pong
A few words
Four words
This is also crucial for us
Heavy traffic
Mr. Huang
They are playing the same character, right?
Sir Huang
He is Marlon
He always wins
I am Marlon
Then who are you?
I am his opponent
She is
Zhang Ben Zhihe
The Little Confused Team will perform
Little Mustache, Little Mustache Team
Among the four of us
only one person has a mustache
Sometimes I have one too
Da Xi also stays up late sometimes
sometimes
then he shaves first
when he thinks hard, it grows
so I don't dare to move
the first one is always late
I give Daxi a perfect score
The name of this task is
The theme of this round is animals
"Animal World"
Spring has arrived
The small animals are actively running around.
Next, we see
come
he is stepping
he is coming with a steady pace
What kind of animal is he?
What is this animal?
He walks on two legs.
You have to
figure it out yourself.
What is the second one?
I couldn't guess this one.
What other features does he have?
I'll show you.
He walked past like this.
All the features
expressionless
walking on two legs
wild model
I think Song should be that little monkey.
Song is that wild model.
Are you "sick"?
We're on the same team, why make it so hard?
You walk over there.
Of course.
Really.
No one understood what that was.
Humans are also animals.
You are too abstract.
This is only when you harm your teammates
that you do this
Alright, let's begin.
This is the word count.
Nine.
Put your hand here
Nine characters
Stick out your butt
Stick out your butt and lift your head
Smile
Do you know who it is?
That one
Got kicked
Still smiling
She is a person
A character
She is a character
What is she doing
Like this
Who is this
Then the foot
rides a bicycle
Person
Who is this?
Here they come.
Cover your crotch with both hands.
Both hands.
Cover your crotch.
Stick out your butt.
Laugh.
Clench your fists.
Turn your head.
Clench your fists with both hands.
Clench your fists.
Right.
Straighten.
Then your feet.
Move back and forth.
Twist back and forth.
Kick back and forth.
Kick your feet back and forth.
Right.
Good, legs.
Time's up