This round of tasks
Each round involves four participants
Each person has a name on their forehead
Members need to take turns asking questions
Through others' answers
To guess the name on their own forehead
Each person can only ask one question at a time
Among the four people guessing the words
There is one undercover
Who needs to complete a special task
Everyone votes to find the undercover
Anyway, it's all very abstract
The four of us (on the left) will try first
Everyone close your eyes
The person who drew the number (undercover)
Open your eyes
Those of us not playing will just guess who the undercover is.
If you guess correctly, you get points.
Xiao Hu, are you peeking?
How did you find my shoulder so quickly?
Isn't it right here? Where else could it be?
Everyone can open their eyes now.
Is she an anime cartoon character?
Yes
Then it's my turn
It's your turn
Is mine an ancient person?
No, it's not
No
Next
Then I'll ask one too
Is mine a cartoon character?
Cartoon character
Kind of
Is she a real person?
Yours
Is a real person
Real person
Okay
Is mine a
Who
What do they do
A scavenger
A main character
What do they do
Yes, she is a main character
A main character
Plays the main character
A scavenger
Passed
Is she in the entertainment or music industry
A celebrity or something
Quite famous anyway
This counts as a sports star
So obvious
You put it right on your face
Just
He said, what did you just say?
I asked if he was a celebrity in the entertainment industry
Yes
I said he is very famous
Not necessarily, it could be the one in the tree
It could be the one in the tree
The one in the tree
No problem
Also
Kind of
What in the tree? Then what is mine?
No one acknowledges this thing
The one in the tree
No, is he in the entertainment industry?
Yes, he is in the entertainment industry
He is definitely considered a celebrity in the entertainment industry now
He has acted, but he is not in the entertainment industry
Got it
Okay, I roughly understand
I'm being reasonable, right?
And you?
Come on
I just said it was the animation I asked about
Yes
Is it foreign?
Yeah
Is this it?
Yes
Then it must be
It's foreign
China has it too
There is also a Henan dialect version
If you put it that way
There is also a Tianjin version
I watched "Tom and Jerry" when I was a kid
It was always the Tianjin version
Really?
Coming to Tianjin
I didn't learn anything
Let's put it this way
Chinese audiences quite like him
Is it okay?
I am.
I am a real person, right?
What is my profession?
That's a good question.
I don't dare to answer that recklessly.
Actor.
Yes, didn't he say he wanted to do abstract?
How do you do abstract?
Abstract is also an actor.
That's a professional actor.
Doing abstract is also acting.
Just an actor.
Actor.
That's it, just one.
No more.
Okay.
Cartoon character, a scavenger.
Am I a cartoon adult?
Yes.
It's also hard to define.
Daxi is an undercover agent.
What did I do?
What's wrong?
Intuition.
Did I guess right?
Really not.
Her questions are too precise.
Really?
That's because there are only a few questions.
Not really an adult. Is she considered an adult?
Yes and no.
She has a growth arc.
They didn't specify her exact age, right?
They didn't specify her age.
Is she dating someone?
Dating abroad, they start early.
Dating abroad.
Then she is considered an adult.
Considered an adult.
Considered an adult abroad.
She's from abroad.
Why are you so quick to speak?
Okay
Adults abroad who pick up trash
Anime
Anime about picking up trash
Who is this?
A scavenger from abroad.
If you know, just say it.
I really don't know.
Shrek.
Little Sloppy.
That's from China.
It's a scavenger cartoon character.
Really.
I can't think of any subconsciously, actually.
Except for the Sloppy King.
Sloppy King.
Still being called
a scavenger.
I
am a sports star.
He acted, but he's not in the entertainment industry.
Is he a foreigner?
Yes.
Okay.
I am...
There are so many dialect versions.
Yes.
It's Haier Brothers.
Your mouth...
Just eliminate the wrong options for him.
Is it an animal?
This thing, it seems like it is, but it isn't.
He is not an animal.
No, he is and he isn't.
How do you define what that thing is?
He is definitely not an animal.
It's an animal.
He is not an animal.
Humans are also animals.
You can't count it like that.
Why can't you count it like that?
Let's just say it like this.
He walks upright.
He is a moving object.
Right, you can say it like that.
Upright walking.
Not quite like an animal.
Close to human
No
No problem
Can only say him
Like a
Not fully evolved animal
Is a lifeform
Just go ahead
Lifeform is absolutely accurate
Just walking upright
You know he walks on two legs
Does he speak human language?
Speaks human language
Is it okay? Is it too much?
Who is she most familiar with among us?
That should be
Because I don't know about you guys
I'm quite familiar
Yes
Then it's Teng
Yes, it should be Teng
It's Teng
Great joy
I am
Have I always been picking up trash?
Behind her
Undercover, definitely undercover
What? I didn't say anything
I am a
She has always been guiding in that direction
Yes
One hundred percent
Has she always been picking up trash?
Or will there be something behind her
Ascended to immortality
Really?
Almost
Definitely leveled up
It's a story of a comeback
Definitely climbed a step
Brief
Had a brief moment of glory, I can only say
Then fell into decline again
Right? There's nothing wrong with that
There are actually several versions of her character
Had a brief moment of glory, right?
Had a brief moment of glory
I'm talking about the popular version
Popular version
Then it passed
Passed
I won't say for now
Summarize it in a few words
Acted in movies
Athlete
Is quite brutal
That kind of passionate sport?
Yes
Okay, I'm done asking
Whose turn is it?
It's Xiaobai's turn
Who here has seen this cartoon?
I haven't seen it
I've seen it
I've seen it too
Do you want to see which era it's from?
Right?
Watch it every day
Watch every day
I was watching it in bed yesterday
You found out again
It's over
How did you get to know Teng?
Become familiar
Why don't you just ask him?
You have to ask Teng
Many times we
met
because we were doing similar things
making movies
You can understand it that way
But I can't tell you
Did you make a movie together?
That's another question
Wait another round
Am I Ultraman?
Ultraman is
Did Ultraman ever pick up trash?
I don't know his past
What did he do when he was a kid
Which foreign anime character picked up trash
I'm going to talk about people
Is this the boxer Tyson?
What? An undercover?
Why didn't you say he was an undercover?
Then what am I?
Peppa Pig?
No.
Have you been on our show before?
No
Am I a
Disney character?
Yes
It's my turn
Is it SpongeBob?
No
It's my turn
Describe her appearance
As beautiful as a flower
Good looking
Her eyes are quite big
Chengcheng, describe her appearance
Who told you she is as beautiful as a flower?
Brother Teng
Quite pretty
Big eyes
Am I Cinderella?
Yes
Really impressive
Am I a Teletubby?
Yes
Then I lost, I admit defeat
I want to question
Xiaobai is the undercover
This round's undercover mission failed
Sorry, Teacher Cai Ming
Who does everyone think the undercover is?
I think it's Brother Gengxin
No, the undercover mission failed
He didn't
He might be the second one to answer correctly
What about the third one to answer correctly?
I have a "condition"
Then I have a "condition", the first to answer
Have you ever considered this premise?
Then I am "sick"
Or he is "sick"
Or you are "sick"
I am "sick" I
Then I still think it's Daxi
I still think it's Daxi
Daxi
You guys have to guess well this time
No, I still think it's Xiaobai
Xiaobai
But he said, he said the mission was not accomplished
He didn't expect Sister Daxi to guess it
He originally wanted to be the second
He was originally the second
It was supposed to be his turn, but he didn't make it
How crucial
Then you were exposed
And you didn't grab it again, you see
Why can't I guess quickly?
This round (the undercover) is Xiaobai
No
Do you know?
I was supposed to get it, I was very confident.
But you were afraid of being questioned.
No, I said it wrong.
I confused Teletubbies with SpongeBob.
I said SpongeBob.
Then you said no.
No
I panicked.
I was just thinking.
Then I guessed it, right?
Yes
I remembered it wrong.
Both are "babies."
I
Then it was that round.
In the next round, Daxi guessed it.
You said Cinderella, she wasn't a scavenger.
Yes, she was a cleaner.
Cleaning
Her job is just a
Seems like she's just a daughter
A daughter from a poor family
She doesn't have a job
Right
Being an undercover is really urgent
It's really urgent right behind
Feels like I need to ask again
Ask accurately but not accurately
Come on, everyone please close your eyes now
Undercover, please open your eyes.
Everyone, please open your eyes.
Describe her appearance
Pretty
Beautiful
Like a flower
Also beautiful
Beautiful like a flower
Pretty
You also have to answer
Weak
Alright, I'm almost done
Next
Does this person look like me?
A little
Not really
There are some similarities
Does he look like me?
The face shape is not quite the same
I don't know
Does he look like me?
Sometimes, sometimes he does
I just summarized in my mind
Some things about this person
are very similar to you
Is this a real person?
No
Is this a person or an actor?
Or something else?
That's several questions
It's not about asking yes or no
It is a
Anyway, it's
an animal
It's quite impressive
An animal, right?
It is close to humans, superior to humans
Close to humans, superior to humans
Come on, next question
Is she a real person?
Probably not
Not really
No
Of course not
Fictional
Alright
What is his most notable feature?
Happiness
Happiness is his most notable feature
That's all I can tell you
I believe no one would disagree
who has seen this
Indeed
You're right
Next
If I'm not a real person
Is it male or female?
Male.
This is a bit more precise, male.
This is a bit too precise.
Has there never been a female?
Okay.
Next.
Can someone help me explain who this is?
Bro, I'll just tell you the answer.
Alright.
It is a
creature superior to humans, right?
Yes.
But this creature
Let me give you a very precise explanation.
has developed its own intelligence.
It has even formed a certain society and civilization.
You really have just two questions
It's him
Undercover
Undercover within undercover, you
If not
He might really not be
I'm taking it off
In what genre does she appear
Literary genre
Right, isn't it, bro
I don't know
Can I say that
I guess so
Literature, right
Literature
So am I a real person or a cartoon
Cartoon
Male, not human
How do I guess this? What genre is this?
Literary genre
Next one
Is it from one of the Four Great Classical Novels?
Yes
Alright
Wang Anyu is the undercover
This is still
Wang Anyu
Still thinking about the literary genre
Wang Anyu must be the undercover
Alright
The literary genre can reach the Four Great Classical Novels
I don't believe this
No, that's not the most important thing
The most important thing is the beginning
Jin Chen told him about that weakness
I think that information is the most sufficient
I am the weakness from the Four Great Classical Novels
Stop acting and guessing
Just say the answer
Still act and guess a bit
It's really unnecessary, Anyu
Pretending to think, see that?
No, it should be the third one to say it.
Yes, with me.
We still need to take a small detour.
Right, he has to wait up ahead.
Maybe he has to wait for the ones in front.
He's setting it up.
Is it Lin Daiyu?
Yes
He just loves music.
He's in a cartoon again.
And he looks a bit like me.
No one said he looks like you.
He doesn't.
Which cartoon has that guy who never talks?
Just laughs.
Talks.
Is it domestic or foreign?
Foreign.
Cartoon, love to laugh
Foreign
Mr. Bean
Anime
Cartoon
Didn't you just mention cartoons?
Anime, cartoon
Just love to laugh, isn't Mr. Bean funny?
He just laughs
Mr. Bean
Isn't he just laughing?
He really looks like it.
Is this from one of the Four Great Classical Novels?
Yes
Zhu Bajie
Right
Failed
The undercover mission failed
Wang Anyu, it must be Wang Anyu
I guess Teng Ge
If it's not Xiao Hu, then it's Wang Anyu
Could it be me?
Definitely not you
Absolutely not you
I vote for Teng.
I vote for An Yu.
Teng.
I just vote for Teng.
I vote for An Yu.
I think Xiao Hu is also possible.
Anyway, it's An Yu and Xiao Hu.
I vote for Teng.
It's really Teng, trust me.
I think it's between An Yu and Teng.
Teng's is a bit too mysterious.
Teng is possible.
It really was a sudden inspiration.
Although
Although in this game
scores have never been important
but if you vote for An Yu with me
you will definitely get points.
It must be Teng.
Who votes for Teng, raise your hand.
Raise your hand if you think it's Xiao Hu
Forget it then
I'll change my vote, I vote for Xiao Hu
Raise your hand if you think it's An Yu
Announce it.
You guessed it too accurately.
I'm not saying
Wang Anyu's brain
can think of the Four Great Classical Novels from literary themes
is just pure nonsense
I'm telling you
because of his thinking
is too wild
he can't be that specific
you talk to him about literary themes
he would even guess Harry Potter
because I was an undercover
putting myself in that mindset makes it very clear
it's very uncomfortable, right?
problem
it seems like someone in front is about to answer
because I think
then I should also guess closer
because I think, what I want to say
when I get to the Four Great Classical Novels
he even guessed my number
he said it must be touching three
then he just stared at me
no, it should be the third one to say it
It fell apart, right?
It kind of fell apart.
Acting thoughtful
Acting for a long time
Describe her appearance
Beautiful
Delicate
Is it from one of the Four Great Classical Novels?
An Yu, were you just thinking hard
In the Four Great Classical Novels
Who is the delicate person
Besides Lin Daiyu
Who else is delicate
An Yu suddenly mentioned Lu Zhishen
I think he is a bit delicate
Going to eat