♪Flower petals have fallen,
piling as high as mortal mercilessness♪
♪Gone with the wind,
as if it has never existed♪
♪I ask for more time♪
♪To rewrite our stories♪
♪We travel together in joys and woes♪
♪Blood bathes this entangled destiny♪
♪For the next reunion
in the troubled times♪
♪We tread a treacherous path♪
♪To find each other♪
♪Wars and bleakness,
the bright moon shines upon the city♪
♪I will offer my bravery♪
♪Fighting relentlessly♪
♪All for no regrets♪
♪In this life-and-death battle,
I will not back down♪
♪Withstand enduring time♪
♪Someone at the end of the world
never leaves♪
♪I brave the grim haze
to be with you once again♪
=Love of Nirvana=
(Based on Xiao Lou's novel of the same name)
=Episode 17=
You're all right now.
You're all right.
Poor Miss Ayan.
Send someone
to stand guard around this place
and don't let anyone get close.
Yes.
Are you going to stay here all night?
I just haven't seen you for two hours,
and you've become more shameless.
It's because
I've spent too much time with you
that I've become self-taught.
Look.
Your kind just went over.
I think you're more like it.
My master said the same thing about me.
Don't cats rest early during winter?
Go to bed.
Where are you going?
I'm going back to my room to rest.
Don't worry.
I'll look into
Ayan's case.
Are you planning
to become a night owl in advance?
Without a night owl like me,
I'm afraid
all your blood is about to be drained.
Stretch out your hand.
All done.
I'll come back tomorrow
to change the dressing.
Since you can't sleep,
why don't we talk?
Are you trying to comfort me?
Don't worry. I'm not that fragile.
I just feel sorry for Ayan.
Pei Yan came to Nanling this time
to regain His Majesty's trust in him.
He intends
to weaken his clan's influence.
The military equipment case
can only be concluded with corruption.
There can be no other truth.
You understand him quite well.
He and I are opponents only
because we have different stances.
If I were him,
I'm afraid
I wouldn't be as thorough as he is.
I think if it were you,
you would find out the real culprit.
You won't care about the pros and cons.
You will just eat him alive.
You seem to understand.
You Shameless Cat.
How can you be so stubborn?
You make me so mad.
I'm Guangming Bureau's commander.
Lord Cat.
You're a kitten
I can crush easily.
It's your choice
to live or die.
♪Let it fly with the wind.
Into sweet dreams♪
♪The beautiful moments we shared♪
♪Last through time.
We never leave each other♪
♪My love sees♪
♪The sun rising and the moon setting♪
♪Your face stays vivid in my mind♪
♪Two hearts♪
♪Bound to each other♪
♪Like flowing water,
love and hate continue♪
Lord Cat.
Is there anything you'd like
to say to your friend?
For example,
giving back her clay cat friend.
♪Time cannot separate us♪
Dream on.
I don't want to play anymore.
How did you learn to do this?
I get bored when I'm alone.
I learned to do it
just by gesturing randomly.
You said
you were the only one in your clan.
Where are your parents?
My master picked me up by the river.
She also named me.
She raised me
and protected me.
What's next?
What's your plan?
Do you remember when He Yonglin said
Ayan wasn't the first woman he harassed
and she wouldn't be the last?
That means
there must be a lot of other
women in the city he had harassed.
I don't believe he can control everyone.
Even if you find them,
they may not do what you want,
nor will they step forward to help you.
I'll have to give it a try anyway.
Do you really not understand
what "Mind your own business" means?
Aren't you the same?
Lin.
Father.
Lin!
Be careful.
Father.
I'm doomed.
I'm so doomed.
Lin.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here for you.
Your Lordship.
Look at the state Lin is in.
You must get justice for him.
You and I
both know the truth.
Your son
committed many crimes in Nanling.
Everyone makes mistakes.
Forgive them when possible.
Forgive them when possible?
Lord Pei.
Wei Zhao shot me in the hand first
and ruined the rest of my life.
Calm down.
Lin.
You should rest.
Rest well.
I know
Miss Jiang was your maid,
so you can't bear to do it.
You treated her so well.
Didn't she run away
with someone else anyway?
Li Ayan is crucial.
She was not only Zheng Sheng's wife
but also
the root of Foundry Bureau's troubles.
Every word she says
is evidence
against Your Lordship and Madam.
If you don't settle this case,
Nanling Provincial Governor's office
won't be the only one that's at risk.
Official He, what do you mean by that?
I beg you to save Lin.
I will feel at ease
only when Lin is safe.
And Madam's foundation
in Nanling will be solid.
As long as you can do that,
I'll make sure
that the Foundry Bureau case
is closed in a way
that satisfies both you and His Majesty.
(Changfeng Estate)
(Biwu Hut)
Your Lordship.
What happened today?
Can I share your worries?
Ziming, you're overthinking.
Maybe I caught a cold last night,
so I suddenly feel unwell today.
I can prepare a few more tonics for you,
but I'm just afraid that your illness
can't be cured by medicine.
Your Lordship.
He Yonglin's case is not unsolvable.
There must be something fishy
about what happened today.
From my observation
of He Zhenwen and He Yonglin's behavior,
there must be other victims.
If we can investigate it,
we'll solve this case.
I'll
investigate in this direction tomorrow.
It's late now.
Go to rest, Ziming.
You said before
that you wanted to get justice
for Zheng Sheng and yourself,
but now
you're scared.
I just never expected
my father
to be the He family's servant.
Do you really believe
that your father
is so devoted to being a slave
that he would send his own daughter
to He's Residence to become a maid?
Ci.
Commander Wei.
Ziming, why are you here?
Miss Ayan was frightened today,
so I brought her some medicine.
Thank you, Ziming.
Tianma,
Ginseng,
dried orange peel,
Tuckahoe with pine,
and licorice.
And crow-dipper,
Nanxing,
Baifuzi and Szechuan Lovage.
Ci.
I can't help but notice
how fast you improve.
Speaking of which,
I thought
you and Commander Wei
might be running low on medication,
so I brought some over today.
Thank you, Ziming.
Today's case is full of mystery.
I think Miss Ayan
isn't the only one who suffered.
I'm afraid the results
may not be as good as we expected.
Ziming and I have the same idea.
There must be other women
who had been victimized in this city.
Do you want to convince them
to come forward
and testify against He Yonglin together?
But this process won't be simple.
I need to give it a try.
Then I wish you
success in clearing up
this turbid Nanling.
Thank you, Ziming.
Ci.
Commander Wei.
I'll leave first.
It's rare to have someone provide help
in times of need.
Ziming's a gentleman.
No.
I'm a maid in He's Residence.
How can I testify
against Official He and Young Master?
You're human,
not something for them to bully at will.
Miss.
I know you mean well.
I'll keep today's meeting
a secret for you,
but please spare me.
I
can't afford to offend them.
Go.
Stop coming here.
It would cost my life
to report it to the officials.
Go.
A lady's reputation
is more important than anything else.
How can I show my face?
Leave.
Don't get me involved.
Go.
My husband is coming back.
Don't
mention this again.
Go.
Don't come to me again.
♪Bond people together♪
♪The rain heading north and
the wild geese returning from the south♪
♪Who can meet again?♪
♪Looking at the mountains far away
and seeing everything red♪
♪Immersed in the passing years♪
♪Back then, the road seemed ordinary♪
♪Looking back, it seems like a dream♪
♪Don't forget each other
even if we're far apart♪
♪Don't waste time♪
♪Back then, the road seemed ordinary♪
♪Taste all the vicissitudes of life
in a flash♪
♪Though nothing is permanent♪
♪I wish you well♪
Wipe it yourself.
Here.
Thank you.
I met a lot of people today.
They're the victims,
but everyone considers herself a sinner.
Justice and the law of nature
seem simple,
but how likely can they be realized?
Should they live in the shadows
for the rest of their lives?
If this doesn't work,
find another way.
Are there other ways?
That day,
Pei Yan
deliberately delayed for two hours.
It was the time
when He Zhenwen hurriedly got ready.
Two hours.
How did they change the situation?
Is the slave contract fake?
I felt something was wrong
when I saw it that day.
I even smelled a fragrance.
We'll know if it's real
once we examine it.
But He Zhenwen has it now.
How do we get it?
You called it.
Commander Wei
headed for Provincial Governor's office.
Sanlang's clever.
How could he not guess
that there was something wrong
with the slave contract?
That's why you set up a trap
in Provincial Governor's office.
Are you trying to take this chance
to delay Commander Wei
and go to Zheng Sheng's house
to persuade Miss Ayan to come back?
If Sanlang can't get the slave contract,
no one will be willing to come forward
to testify that they were harassed.
If this matter becomes a big deal,
both sides will suffer.
Let's persuade Ayan back
and see how to resolve the situation
and compensate her.
Well...
What about Miss Jiang?
Bring her back.
Yes.
Miss Jiang.
It's windy at night.
Why are you out here?
I'm fine.
I figured out
what Commander Wei asked me that day.
What did he ask you?
(Do you really believe)
that your father
is so devoted to being a slave
(that he would send his own daughter)
(to He's Residence to become a maid?)
He won't do that.
He Zhenwen is lying to me.
That slave contract
must be fake.
Don't worry.
He has already gone to
get the slave contract.
We'll find out if it's real
by examining it.
Are you
waiting for Commander Wei here?
I wonder what happened.
He's been gone for so long
and there's still no news.
You're back.
Why are you here?
Enough.
Go back with me.
Go back where?
Changfeng Estate?
That's your house,
not mine.
Do you think
this will help Miss Ayan?
Your Lordship.
Can I have a word with you?
Why did you allow
He Zhenwen and He Yonglin
to bully the weak
and harass women?
The slave contract is proof.
Ayan is He Clan's slave.
Since He Clan
is willing to give her a title,
it's already the best outcome.
If you think it's not enough,
I can ask His Majesty for a decree
to give her a title.
This is just your idea,
not what Ayan wants.
Aren't you confident
because you guessed the outcome
for Ayan with what you want?
Do you know
that your willful behavior
will put her on the spot and let others
criticize her until she dies?
You'd think this way
because you never cared
about these people's lives.
If I didn't care about your safety,
why would I
risk bringing you to Nanling?
I know you've taken great care of me.
And I will always
remember your kindness.
I don't want you to remember these!
Go back to Changfeng Estate with me.
I promise
I won't let Miss Ayan get hurt,
let alone hurt you.
What's your real purpose
in taking Ayan away?
Keep everyone safe.
Is it to protect Pei Clan?
If Ayan's existence gets in your way,
you'll kill her, won't you?
I told you I won't hurt her!
Please spare Ayan then.
Let...
Let me go!
When did you get here?
Why are you also here?
Shaojun.
The case will go to trial tomorrow.
Miss Ayan is an important witness
and must be well protected.
You shouldn't disturb the witness.
Jiang Ci belongs
to Lord of Jianding's Residence.
I'm taking her.
But I remember
that you don't have
Miss Jiang's indenture.
Even if you do,
slaves are also human beings.
No one can bully them.
They really left.
With a monster like Commander here,
no one will act rashly.
You're getting better and better
at taking advantage
of other people's power.
Did you get it?
(Nanling Provincial Governor's office)
(Fairness and Justice)
Today,
the case is reopened.
If there's no evidence,
the case should be closed
as required by law.
Your Lordship.
I have evidence.
What evidence do you have?
Can you please present
Li Song's indenture?
Official He, may I ask
is this contract
really printed more than 20 years ago?
As real as it gets.
With Dangtu County's seal as evidence,
the evidence is conclusive.
Since the seal
was from more than 20 years ago,
so would the ink.
Bring it up.
The year
before the signing of the contract
is the Year of Wu Xu.
It coincided with natural disasters.
Musk's production dropped significantly.
I wonder if you elders still remember.
Indeed.
Yes.
Musk is the material used to make ink.
There wasn't enough musk,
so the workshop used sea bamboo shoots,
which are similar to musk.
There's nothing wrong
with sea bamboo shoots,
except one part.
Once mixed with green tea,
it will change color.
Please look.
This is the ink used by
Nanling Provincial Governor's office.
If this contract
had been really printed 20 years ago,
it would have changed color
after adding green tea.
If not,
it proves
that this contract
is fake,
whether it's ink or seal.
Stop talking nonsense.
How can you be sure
that the ink
is from Provincial Governor's Office?
Everything the government uses
is made by the government.
The ink from
Nanling Provincial Governor's
office is naturally marked.
How can it
be passed off as real if it's fake?
Examine it!
Yes.
Please look.
The color of the two bowls
of wine didn't change.
It proves
that the ink
wasn't produced in that year.
Why is the ink of a contract
from more than 20 years ago
not from that year?
There's only one possibility.
The contract is forged.
Li Song isn't the He family's servant,
and neither is Ayan.
Please handle this impartially
and give Ayan justice.
Your Lordship.
The evidence of the indenture
is conclusive.
It can't be fake.
Justice
has long arms.
Since the truth has been revealed,
what are you waiting for?
Young Master.
Don't be scared.
He can't hurt you anymore.
I promised to marry you
to protect your reputation.
Why would you
still cause so much trouble?
Lin.
- Yifei.
- Lin.
Do you think she won't
hold her head up high
after you assaulted her?
Your crime can't destroy her innocence.
You're filthy
and wrong.
You...
Yes.
Even if I'm the only one doing this,
I'll fight you to the end
and expose your sins to the public
so that you'll receive
the karma you deserve.
I'm Tao,
a maid at He's Residence.
I'm willing to sue He Yonglin
for committing crimes
and bullying me.
How dare you betray me too?
Although I'm a slave,
I'm also human.
Why should I endure your
beatings and humiliation?
Today,
I want justice for myself.
I'm suing He Yonglin
for violence and bullying me!
It's you.
We share lots of commons
and should go through
thick and thin together.
I'm already a victim.
How can we let this brute
get away with it?
I want to hold my head high
and be innocent.
I'm suing He Yonglin!
I'm also suing He Yonglin!
You...
Please get us justice, Your Lordship.
- Please get us justice, Your Lordship.
Both witnesses and physical evidence
are present.
Imprison
He Zhenwen
and He Yonglin
and hand them to Ministry of Justice.
- Yes.
I don't want to die.
Father.
Father, save me.
Lin.
Don't be afraid.
Your Lordship!
Please
save Lin.
It's you.
I'm going to kill you.
I'm going to kill you!
Lin!
What's wrong?
Lin...
No.
Lin.
Lin!
You killed my son.
I want you to die with him!
Thank you all.
- Thank you, Miss Jiang.
(Nanling Provincial Governor's office)
Let's go home. Here.
Darling.
Let's go.
(Zheng Sheng and Ayan's Old Residence)
Miss Jiang.
Commander Wei.
I got justice
all thanks to you.
Here's a toast to you.
That's all I can do.
I can't get Zheng Sheng justice yet.
Now that He Zhenwen is in prison,
I've gotten justice
for Sheng.
Commander Wei.
That day, you asked me
why I had such a habit of cooking.
Actually,
it's because of Sheng.
Sheng's mother was a slave.
When she was in the slave camp,
what she ate every day
was worse than kitchen slop.
Life got better later on,
but
she couldn't eat food
that was mixed together.
What about his father?
He died long ago.
His mother rarely mentioned his father
in front of him either.
Sheng only knew
that his father
worked in the palace.
He would
send some money back every few years.
After his father passed away,
their life
became difficult.
Have they always lived in Nanling?
After his father passed away,
his mother brought him to Nanling.
And life became a little better.
They seem to
have someone
secretly helping them from time to time.
How did you know?
After Sheng passed away,
I came here to clean up occasionally.
One night...
Have you ever seen
the person who sent the money?
It was too dark.
But judging from the person's figure,
it should be a woman.
This is a cloth bag that the person
uses to contain the money.
I kept it because
it's not Nanling's craftsmanship.
Is there something wrong?
We're just chatting.
Miss Jiang.
Commander Wei.
I plan to leave Nanling
and go to Sheng's hometown.
I wish you
all the best in the future.
Have no worries
for the rest of your life.
Miss Jiang.
Knowing you is the best thing
that has ever happened to me.
Knowing Zheng Sheng
is the best thing for you.
Knowing me
can be considered second best.
So what are your plans for the future?
Are you going back to Lord?
My master and I have agreed
to meet at Yuzhou Island in late autumn.
Yuzhou Island
is very close to Nanling.
Yes.
But I still have something
in Commander's hands.
He refuses to give me back.
How troublesome.
If he refuses
to give it to you before,
maybe he will now.
Why?
You're confused because you're involved.
When this part hurts,
you'll understand.
Why didn't you ask Miss Ayan
more questions?
Are you just going to let her leave?
Where did you get this?
Miss Ayan.
I have a favor to ask.
If the people
who helped Zheng Sheng over the years
were the Yans,
this bag
is very likely
the only clue to find her.
Look into it.
Yes.
♪Pluck a red bean, cherish you♪
♪Deep within♪
♪A flower of affection blooms
without fading♪
♪Forever in love♪
♪Fold a kite, let it fly with the wind♪
♪Into sweet dreams♪
♪The beautiful moments we shared
last through time♪
♪We never leave each other♪
♪My love sees
the sun rising and the moon setting♪
♪Your face stays vivid in my mind♪
♪Two hearts bound to each other♪
♪Like flowing water,
love and hate continue♪
♪I only wish for your unwavering heart♪
♪You are still there when I turn back♪
♪As passionate as we first met,
I hold your hands through eternity♪
♪Time cannot separate us♪
♪Our longings go on♪
♪My love sees
the sun rising and the moon setting♪
♪Your face stays vivid in my mind♪
♪Two hearts bound to each other♪
♪Like flowing water,
love and hate continue♪
♪I only wish for your unwavering heart♪
♪You are still there when I turn back♪
♪As passionate as we first met,
I hold your hands through eternity♪
♪Time cannot separate us♪
♪Our longings go on♪