♪Flower petals have fallen,
piling as high as mortal mercilessness♪
♪Gone with the wind,
as if it has never existed♪
♪I ask for more time♪
♪To rewrite our stories♪
♪We travel together in joys and woes♪
♪Blood bathes this entangled destiny♪
♪For the next reunion
in the troubled times♪
♪We tread a treacherous path♪
♪To find each other♪
♪Wars and bleakness,
the bright moon shines upon the city♪
♪I will offer my bravery♪
♪Fighting relentlessly♪
♪All for no regrets♪
♪In this life-and-death battle,
I will not back down♪
♪Withstand enduring time♪
♪Someone at the end of the world
never leaves♪
♪I brave the grim haze
to be with you once again♪
=Love of Nirvana=
(Based on Xiao Lou's novel of the same name)
=Episode 39=
Today,
we
fight together,
and we die together
in honor and disgrace.
Destroy the enemy invaders,
and secure the country.
Fight together, and die together
in honor and disgrace.
Destroy the enemy invaders,
and secure the country.
Jiang Ci.
Be careful on the battlefield.
I'll wait for your return.
I'm sorry.
I can't let him find you.
I'll be back.
Mr. Ping,
take her away.
Young Master...
Sure.
Attack!
Attack...
Left wing, right wing,
support the front line.
Charge!
Attack!
Wei Zhao is indeed no ordinary man.
The difference in military strength
is so vast,
yet he is still holding on.
Increase our forces.
Surround them.
Our army is about to be encircled.
Should we proceed as planned?
Attack!
Attack...
(The enemy will surely use their
superior numbers to encircle us.)
(Once their wings break formation,)
(I'll lead the troops to break through.)
(But the remaining allied
forces will be surrounded.)
(Since we are allies,)
(we have no choice
but to trust each other,)
(to be each other's vanguard)
(and shield.)
Recall the front line,
and support the center troops.
Quickly!
Protect me and retreat.
Hurry, go!
Allied forces, hear my command.
Attack with all your strength!
Attack...
Attack!
Are you still fighting?
♪Looking back♪
♪Is my homeland still standing strong?♪
♪Traveling across rivers♪
Listen.
Gao Xiu, Emperor of Wei,
invaded our homeland.
Today, you have been defeated.
Out of goodwill,
Liang will accept your surrender,
provided you order a retreat
and vow
not to set foot on our lands
for the next ten years.
Let the soldiers comply.
♪I will offer my bravery♪
♪Fighting relentlessly♪
♪All for no regrets♪
Huzzah, Commander Wei!
♪I brave the grim haze
to be with you once again♪
♪Even with just a heart full of passion♪
♪I hold my resolve, blood running hot♪
♪Just for that one answer♪
♪In this life-and-death battle,
I will not back down♪
♪Golden armor reflects
the warmth of the setting sun♪
♪A jug of wine to toast
what joy remains♪
♪May we be together in the next life♪
Commander Wei truly lives up
to his name.
Return to the palace.
Father, are you going
to the battlefield?
The battle has been won.
Why bother going?
Return to the palace.
Commander Wei.
The intense battle
has triggered the poison.
I'll administer the acupuncture
right away.
Jiang Ci must not know.
I have already sent her away
to fetch the medicine box.
Rest assured, Commander Wei.
(Secret Residence, Yueluo)
When did you wake up?
I thought I sent you away.
Why did you come back?
Mr. Ping,
where are you taking me?
I can't leave him alone.
Miss Jiang,
please don't
go against the Young Master's
good intentions.
(Since I met him,)
(I've never abandoned him.)
(That's how it's been,)
(that's how it is,)
(and that's how it will always be.)
Miss Jiang.
I know you sent me away for my own good,
but I don't want to go anywhere.
I just want to stay here.
I won't be a burden.
Congratulations.
Nine lives,
and not one was lost.
Are you hungry?
Wait here.
It looks terrible.
It's not like you have never
eaten it before.
♪Cherish you deep within♪
♪A flower of affection♪
♪Blooms without fading, forever in love♪
♪Fold a kite♪
♪Let it fly with the wind
into sweet dreams♪
♪The beautiful moments we shared♪
♪Last through time,
we never leave each other♪
♪My love sees♪
♪The sun rising and the moon setting♪
♪Your face stays vivid in my mind♪
♪Two hearts♪
♪Bound to each other♪
♪Like flowing water,
love and hate continue♪
Is it sweet?
Yes.
Gosh,
even after a long rest,
you're still not thinking straight.
It just feels as though
I've been together with you
for a long time.
From now on, you'll stay with me.
Whatever I eat, you'll eat too.
♪Two hearts♪
♪Bound to each other♪
♪Like flowing water,
love and hate continue♪
♪I only wish♪
♪For your unwavering heart♪
♪You are still there when I turn back♪
♪As passionate as we first met♪
♪I hold your hands through eternity♪
♪Time cannot separate us♪
♪Our longings go on♪
He's arrived.
Yes.
Rest assured.
I will never let him hurt you again.
What about you?
I will end this.
Sanlang.
Ci.
Shaojun.
How are your injuries, Sanlang?
Nothing too serious.
You two have a chat.
I'll go prepare some food.
Do you know
His Majesty is coming?
Yes.
You captured Gao Xiu,
forced a peace treaty
and won the respect of the three armies.
His Majesty has always been wary of you.
Now, I fear
it will only get worse.
The tree desires calm,
but the wind won't stop.
He's long had the intent to kill me.
Whatever I do,
there's no turning back now.
Rather than live in fear,
I will face him head-on.
That's my only hope of survival.
What is your plan, Sanlang?
I intend to reveal the truth
about Prince Qi's case
in front of the three armies,
to redress justice for my father
and Yueluo.
This is a death wish.
At this point,
it's the only thing I can do
for my father and Yueluo.
What crime has Yueluo committed?
Who else but me can bear this burden?
Just pretend you know nothing
lest you get implicated.
What crime has Yueluo committed?
I will respond to your call
on behalf of the world.
What harm is there in that?
I have been taught since childhood
to fight for my family's interests.
In the end,
family ties were severed,
close friends were harmed
and I was estranged from my loved ones.
Apart from fighting,
I know nothing else.
Are you going to keep fighting?
Of course.
In this world,
whether good or bad,
nothing comes without a price.
To punish evil, we must fight.
To uphold justice, we must
fight even more.
This time,
it's a fight for the people,
for justice and righteousness.
I am willing to stand by your side
and fight
to restore justice for Yueluo.
Shaojun, I am grateful
for your righteousness.
Sanlang,
only today have I realized
that you and I are not opponents.
We are confidants
and friends.
Why are the streets of Yueluo
filled only with
the elderly and children?
Every year, Yueluo offers
slaves as tribute.
The young men and women
are sent to Liang.
Look at their faces.
They didn't want to be slaves,
so they scarred their own faces
and covered them with tattoos.
It is to encourage themselves
to face life with courage.
Back in Liang,
we were used to slavery
as a form of tribute.
But Yueluo
has seen 20 years of broken families
and unbearable pain.
I never knew these things.
Your Highness,
Yueluo is a territory
of the Liang state,
and its people are also your subjects.
All they want is to live
like ordinary citizens,
to live in peace
and safety.
I know that you are
kind-hearted and benevolent,
but forgive me for speaking bluntly,
if you wish to become a wise ruler,
benevolence alone is not enough.
You must also
have the boldness
to surpass the Emperor.
Shaojun,
don't speak recklessly.
Do you truly not understand
what Princess Yong'an's trial
was all about?
If you only follow the Emperor's orders,
when will you ever become
a ruler who can stand on your own?
I'm torn between filial piety
and righteousness.
But he is my father.
What choice do I have?
What is it that you truly
want to uphold?
Loyalty to your father,
or righteousness for the people?
(Palace, Yueluo)
Father.
What is it?
If I may be so bold,
Father,
please restore justice for Yueluo.
Justice?
Back then,
the former lord of Yueluo, Xiao Haitian,
was accused of plotting
against my uncle, Prince Qi.
But there were no witnesses or evidence,
and many details were questionable.
If the people of Yueluo are
implicated again,
it would be an affront to humanity
and a travesty of justice.
Are you saying
that I wronged them?
You have always been a diligent
and kind ruler,
but I believe
that you may have been deceived
and passed a wrong judgment.
You are the ruler of the nation
and Yueluo's sovereign.
You should restore justice
to the people of Yueluo.
Who has been filling
your head with gossip?
You've taught me benevolence,
righteousness, propriety, and wisdom.
I know what is right and wrong.
I know we should rule the world
with benevolence,
govern the world with virtue,
secure the world with propriety,
and put the people first.
My beliefs
and my actions
are not influenced by anyone else.
It all comes from my own heart.
I will not
waver.
So, in your view,
what should I do?
I would like to organize a ceremony
to reward the three armies
on your behalf,
and to reward the soldiers of Yueluo,
thus restoring justice to Yueluo.
The three armies and all the people
will surely remember you
as a great and kind ruler.
If you say so,
you may proceed.
Father,
thank you.
Greetings,
Your Majesty.
You are indeed
a pillar of the nation, Sanlang.
Your reputation now echoes
throughout the three armies.
I
am unsure
how to reward you.
The defeat of the Wei army
was not my doing.
If anyone is to be rewarded,
it's the soldiers and people of Yueluo.
I have already ordered
the Crown Prince to organize
a grand ceremony in three days
to reward the three armies.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Besides the soldiers who fought bravely,
I've also heard about a physician
with miraculous healing skills.
I should reward her as well.
The army's physicians
are all skilled and kind.
I thank you on their behalf.
You seem to be hiding someone.
There's no one in the army
that would be of interest to you.
I have nothing to hide.
If that's the case,
then we will decide the rewards
and punishments
on the day of the grand ceremony.
Your Majesty.
Everything is ready.
Sanlang is no longer the boy
he once was.
It all began with Yueluo,
so it shall end with Yueluo.
You're back.
Why aren't you asleep yet?
All thanks to you
for coming back so late.
Come.
Sit here,
I'll help you dry the clothes.
There, it's done.
Now it's your turn to push me.
Last time, I let you off easy.
When all this is over,
I'll build a small house,
and move this swing there.
That way, no matter how far we go,
we'll always have a place to call home.
This swing is clearly mine,
and you think you can just move it?
Who said this swing is yours?
(Ci, Xia)
Sit down.
You're always mooching food and drinks,
why don't you stay here?
Now that I'm no longer
a commander,
I'm afraid
I don't even have money
to pay rent anymore.
Then work
for me.
If you do your chores well enough,
I might just take you in.
You're giving me all the work,
what about you?
Me?
I'll sit here on the swing
and supervise.
Fine.
If you say so.
Tomorrow is the reward ceremony.
I've asked Yifei to guard this place.
As long as you stay hidden,
you'll be fine.
What about you?
Me?
Of course, I'll go receive
my rewards and honors.
Once the ceremony is over tomorrow,
you'd better come straight home.
Your pinching skill is improving
day by day.
Whoever ends up marrying you
would be one unlucky man.
But compared to how you
hurt me back then,
it's nothing.
Wouldn't you agree?
If only this night
could last a little longer.
I've already given you the swing,
why are you still unhappy?
I don't want the swing.
I want you.
Come back soon.
Wait for my return.
(Happiness)
(I've never feared death.)
(But since I met you,)
(I realized that this world)
(isn't all darkness and pain.)
(There are many things
worth cherishing.)
(So I began)
(to long for more.)
(In order to save me,)
(you pretended to be my wife.)
(To you, it was a temporary measure,)
(but to me, it was a lifelong promise.)
(You're the only one for me, Jiang Ci.)
(The future is uncertain.)
(So I'm sealing)
(our marriage right now.)
(First bow to the heavens.)
♪Fortunate to walk together,
even for a moment♪
(Second bow to the earth.)
♪Who could have known
how we'd arrive at today♪
♪A wilted heart with no one
to depend on♪
♪Is the reason I cannot bear to part♪
♪Our last burning memory in my heart♪
(Third bow to my wife.)
♪No more memories of you♪
♪A wilted heart with no one
to depend on♪
♪Is the reason I cannot bear to part♪
♪Our last burning memory in my heart♪
♪From then on, no more pain or regret♪
♪No more memories of you♪
Yifei,
guard this place with your life.
I will.
As for Jiang Ci,
I'll leave her in your care, Ziming.
His Majesty will definitely move in
on Jiang Ci during the ceremony.
She must not be discovered.
Rest assured,
I will protect Ci with my life.
Today's ceremony
could be a trap.
Besides, you have no evidence.
At this point,
there is no other way.
Since I've taken this route,
I won't turn back.
What's this?
Are you planning to leave me behind?
Without you,
no plan would be complete.
Shaojun,
let's go.
Take your men
and find Princess Yong'an.
Today's a grand occasion.
It'd be a shame if they missed it.
Yes.
We welcome Your Majesty.
Everyone, rise.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
You, the soldiers of the three armies,
have defended our great state
and repelled the foreign invaders.
You deserve praise and merit.
I
have brought fine liquor and meat
to reward you all.
When you return to Liang,
I will personally
grant you titles and rewards.
- Thank you for your grace, Your Majesty.
Father,
the soldiers of Yueluo fought valiantly
against the Wei.
Please grant them the same rewards
so that they may be consoled.
Anyone who has contributed
to our nation,
regardless of any past crimes,
will be
treated equally
and rewarded accordingly.
People of Yueluo,
do you have anything to say?
We, the people of Yueluo,
humbly accept the decree.
Your Majesty,
I have something to say.
Wei Zhao,
what do you wish to say?
I wish to speak about
Prince Qi's case from 20 years ago.
Prince Qi's old case?
What is there to say?
The injustice in Yueluo
must be addressed today.
- The injustice in Yueluo
- must be addressed today.
The former lord of Yueluo, Xiao Haitian,
was a man of honor.
He was not the actual murderer
of Prince Qi.
If it wasn't Xiao Haitian,
then who was it?
The true murderer of Prince Qi...
Mother, why are you here?
Didn't you ask us to come celebrate?
Yes.
Today's reward ceremony
is meant for the people of Yueluo
to share in the victory.
Wei Zhao,
step forward.
you just said Xiao Haitian was wronged,
and that Yueluo was wronged.
Why don't you explain it
in front of the people of Yueluo?
Your Lordship,
what's happening?
His Majesty is using the people
of Yueluo to intimidate Sanlang,
making it hard for him to speak.
Order the Changfeng Guards
to be vigilant.
Make sure
the people are protected.
(Mount Mingyue, Yueluo)
What do you see?
Our home.
Do you know what I see?
Mr. Ji's home,
Madam Ping's home,
and the homes of all
the people of Yueluo.
I'm not a hero,
nor do I want to be one.
I just want to protect this land,
this home.
That's why I practice
the art of the blade.
One day, you will understand
its true significance.
Then you will understand
the words I'm telling you today.
Why aren't you speaking?
I spoke recklessly.
I do not know who
actually murdered Prince Qi.
Prince Qi
died in Yueluo
during a peace talk.
The Xiao family
should bear all the blame.
But the injustice of Yueluo
cannot go unaddressed.
For speaking falsely,
I could sentence you
and your entire family to death.
The crimes of the Xiao family
should be borne by them alone.
But the mistakes of the
former lord of Yueluo
should not continue to implicate
the people of Yueluo.
The people of Yueluo have
already suffered for 20 years.
They have endured the pain
of broken homes
and torn families.
In the battle between Liang and Wei,
the people of Yueluo
fought bravely
to protect their land
and the nation's fate.
Yueluo
is part of the Liang state.
The people of Yueluo
are also Your Majesty's subjects.
All they desire is to live in peace,
to reunite with their loved ones,
and to be with the people
they care about.
I earnestly request Your Majesty
to abolish all harsh policies
against Yueluo
and pardon Yueluo.
Please, Your Majesty, pardon Yueluo.
Wei Zhao,
in what identity are you speaking to me?
I
am Wei Zhao, commander of the
Guangming Bureau of Liang.
In this lifetime,
my allegiance
is to you, Your Majesty.
Having fought
alongside the soldiers
and civilians of Yueluo,
I was moved by their courage.
I hereby
plead on their behalf.
Even if it means giving up everything,
I will have no regrets.
I humbly request Your Majesty
to pardon Yueluo.
I too fought alongside the soldiers
and civilians of Yueluo.
I wish to plead for Yueluo.
Your Majesty, please pardon Yueluo.
I
also wish to plead for Yueluo.
Father, please pardon Yueluo.
As I have said,
anyone who has contributed
to the Liang state
will be rewarded.
I
hereby pardon Yueluo.
Long live
the Emperor.
- Long live the Emperor...
Wei Zhao,
since I have granted your request
and pardoned Yueluo,
you will accompany me
to Zhaixing Pavilion
to pay homage to Prince Qi.
I
accept your command.
(Yueluo)
♪The slanting sunray refuses to leave♪
♪The moon is fading off♪
♪Frost on the sword, string of the bow♪
♪Bond people together♪
♪The wind heading north and
the wild geese returning from the south♪
♪Who can meet again?♪
♪Looking at the mountains far away
and seeing everything red♪
♪Immersed in the passing years♪
♪Back then, the road seemed ordinary♪
♪Yet now I am left wandering
in this life♪
♪Faint memories of the past♪
♪All tell of parting sorrows♪
♪Back then, the road seemed ordinary♪
♪Amidst the wind, I suddenly look back♪
♪The face that feels so dear to me♪
♪Where are you now?♪
♪Back then, the road seemed ordinary♪
♪Looking back, it seems like a dream♪
♪Don't forget each other
even if we're far apart♪
♪Don't waste time♪
♪Back then, the road seemed ordinary♪
♪Taste all the vicissitudes of life
in a flash♪
♪Though nothing is permanent♪
♪I wish you well♪