The End
Episode 1
If you really think Lin Qian Jin is innocent,
then get the evidence.
Tell everyone, understand?
Please.
I will do my best to find out the truth.
I will give everyone an explanation.
And I will give Lin Qian Jin a light.
Come.
The criminal who killed Princess Liu Yun in the Golden Silk Forest,
is Lin Qian Jin.
The City Leader has ordered to kill Lin Qian Jin.
It's not me!
No!
You're fine.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
You...
You should be well-well.
You shouldn't be late.
I have something urgent.
What is it?
I really can't without you.
If you can't, then you can't continue to investigate.
So I need you.
I'm fine.
All the evidence is pointing to Cheng Le.
When she was in the 18th-degree pool,
she was suspicious.
Later, on the lamp,
her reaction was strange.
Especially when I asked her about the night pool,
she said she didn't want to talk.
And she was very reactionary.
Tell me.
Did she intentionally avoid our investigation?
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
I...
Did you have any symptoms of faintness?
No. Just two times.
Then...
Did you use any other food recently?
Or did you get a cold because of the weather?
No. I didn't have any.
Look. It's not hot at all.
I...
I'm fine.
What happened to you?
I...
You're wearing too thick爷 and thin.
It's sorta cold out there.
Here's a sweater.
LIFE
You're occupied with me?
If you're occupied with me,
then do me a favor.
What?
I have to go to theầy
You're going to the place where you live?
Chaiye Beach?
I have no other way.
Last time you were in the hospital.
But it's not like this every time.
I won't let you go.
You care about me?
No matter what,
I won't let you go.
If you care about me,
you should help me to clear my name.
I want to take away my power.
Ah Xiang,
I have to clear this matter up.
Otherwise,
the City Leader will misunderstand me.
I...
I'll help you to take care of half an hour.
That's great!
I knew you wouldn't be so stubborn today.
Good boy.
I'm leaving.
Wait.
You can go.
Ah Xiang,
help me to think about it.
How can I make up for you?
I think
why don't you let the City Leader make a request?
Can you still resist the order?
What do you know?
I want you to fall in love with me
instead of giving me orders.
To be honest,
it's all because of the lantern meeting
and Lin Qianjin's half-way corner.
If she didn't seduce me,
Brother Li Yan might have been
already mad at me.
Brother Li Yan,
I know you're kind to me.
Brother Li Yan.
Your Highness.
The fresh grape I just made
is very sweet and juicy.
It's very delicious.
Have a try.
Be careful.
Let me try.
Your Highness.
The City Leader entered the bus channel
and ordered me to drive the entrance door
Let's make a
Christmas Eve present for the winner.
Let me prepare the others.
είναι kamicka is hiding there.
The End
Brother Li Yan, do you think it's nice?
Brother Li Yan
This is beautiful
It reminds me of many beautiful things
I bought a lot of fresh spices today
I want to go to see it with Brother Li Yan
Princess, this
This garden is more natural
I will accompany you
OK
Then we will enjoy the natural scenery together
Who is inside?
Brother Li Yan, can you accompany me to enjoy the flowers often?
Look at that lotus flower
Stop
Princess Linggao
Princess, this assassin is good at your bedroom
Take the assassin with you
Yes
Brother Li Yan
Are you OK?
You are bleeding
I'm OK
The thief is bold
He dares to break into Princess' bedroom
Princess
I have to take him to the police station now
Xing'er, take care of Princess
Brother Li Yan, be careful
Princess
Come with me
Are you OK?
I'm OK
What about Yan'ai Tao?
It's important to protect her now
Go
Wait
Lin Qianjie
Why are you here?
You are so bold
How dare you break into my bedroom
You are the master of the city
Little girl, don't be angry
Then it's my home
Now it's my home
Sister-in-law doesn't treat you as a family
You are so shameless
I have never seen you before
How dare you call yourself sister-in-law
Come, take her down
Master of the city is here
Greetings, Master
Master
What are you doing here?
Brother, Lin Qianjie
She didn't just break into the city's master's house
She even stole my bedroom
No one can tell
Lin Qianjie
It's you again
Master
Well
It's like this
I'm the most famous in the city
And I heard that
Princess Chang'e
has a very special sauce
I'm curious to see
I can prove it
Miss Lin is still very good at it
So I let you
to be honest
I should do it
Brother
Don't you want to punish Lin Qianjie?
How can you blame Li Yan?
Lin Qianjie
You can't do anything
You should do it yourself
100 times
You can't go home without doing anything
You can't do anything
Why am I so unlucky?
I was so lucky
that I got into the trap
Now I'm here
to find some tricks
I'm so hungry
I want to go home
and eat the chicken leg made by my mom
Are you hungry?
It's delicious
You said that
two brothers and sisters in Murong family
are really over
They must know
I hate these
funny things
So they asked me
to make some tricks
and make so many jokes
Give me your hand
I...
I mean
give me your hand
You...
You want to eat my hand?
I'm so hungry
I want to go home
and eat the chicken leg made by my mom
Are you hungry?
I'm so hungry
I want to go home
and eat the chicken leg made by my mom
Are you hungry?
I'm so hungry
I want to go home
and eat the chicken leg made by my mom
Are you hungry?
I'm so hungry
I want to go home
and eat the chicken leg made by my mom
Are you hungry?
I'm so hungry
I want to go home
and eat the chicken leg made by my mom
Are you hungry?
I'm so hungry
I want to go home
and eat the chicken leg made by my mom
Are you hungry?
I want to go home
and eat the chicken leg made by my mom
Are you hungry?
I want to go home