The Long Ballad
Episode 17
Your Highness, I have kept the treasure
for Miss Lin in the past 70 days.
I won't stay here.
Your Highness.
I'm so angry.
Why am I dizzy again?
Let me down.
Don't talk. I'll send you back.
Actually, the clue is broken.
I really can't find the real murderer.
I have no time to take the blame for three days.
But you can tell the City Leader
that I will obey the agreement.
Even if I take the blame, I'll still be dead.
Actually, after these days' investigation,
I don't think you're a murderer.
I know.
But I can't take the blame.
Besides, the City Leader hates me so much.
He won't let me go.
How do you know that City Leader hates you?
Why did he let you watch me all day?
He must not want me to be the City Leader's wife.
Maybe I'm the one who's guilty of the punishment.
That's what he's looking forward to.
Don't think too much.
Take care of yourself.
Don't worry.
I'll help you find a way.
It's okay. You can't help me.
It's a pity.
I haven't seen this thing well.
Li Si Jun.
What's the matter?
Yes.
City Leader, please.
Li Si Jun.
Thank you for helping me.
I'm not dizzy anymore.
Put it down.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'll go to see City Leader now.
Miss Lin is unwell.
Send her back.
Yes, Li Si Jun.
Wait.
I can't keep watch on you.
I'm quite worried about you.
This token is for you.
It's as good as a sword token.
If you want to bully me,
show her this token.
If anything really happens to you,
I'll turn the whole city around
and find you.
Thank you.
You said that.
Although Lin Qian Jin didn't take the risk,
her performance was not bad.
If Lin Qian Jin
is really a murderer,
she won't be so cruel.
Besides,
she won't say
that even if she can't find a murderer,
she'll still obey the promise.
If she's really a murderer,
it's not her.
It's not her.
Who is it again?
The clue is broken.
I can't be sure.
Li,
I don't want to make you feel bad.
It's been too long
since the incident.
Princess Liu Yun hasn't woken up yet.
Every day,
every hour in the city,
she's putting pressure on me.
Their 100,000 soldiers
are on the border.
If Princess Liu Yun
has any three-way Liang Duan,
I'm afraid that
they'll be in the military.
Li San,
you should share the burden for me.
I know
you're under a lot of pressure.
So,
I've made a plan for you.
This method
might have made Princess Liu Yun wake up,
but it can still catch the real murderer.
By then,
you can have an answer to it.
Good brother,
I knew you'd think of me.
But,
I hope you and I
can cooperate on this method.
Of course.
Let's do it again.
Come on.
Li Si Jun,
your clothes are ready.
What are you doing?
I think you look happy
when you wear this.
So, we want to try it.
Stop laughing.
You can't be so considerate
in the City Leader's Mansion.
This standard
can only be brought by myself.
You can all take it.
Let's go.
I've seen this sign.
It's like a sign.
If anyone dares to bully you,
just show him this sign.
If something really happens,
I'll turn the whole Nanling City
and find you.
In fact, after these days of investigation,
I don't think you're a murderer anymore.
You said you believed me.
Of course, I'm very happy.
But
the suspect in Chang Le's case
was fired.
The suspect's head
pointed at me without hesitation.
He found the real murderer's clue
and was interrupted.
I'm afraid
he'll find the real murderer.
How can I prove
my innocence?
I still have three days to go.
Unless God helps me.
Otherwise, I'll be in danger
at any time.
Who's that?
Qian Jin.
It's me.
Why did you come to my house
so late?
What for?
Put on your clothes.
I'll take you to a place.
So beautiful.
Didn't you say
you haven't seen the world
before yesterday?
Then you
brought me here
to get the soul of the night.
Don't you like it?
I do.
I didn't expect
you to be so beautiful.
you to be so good at killing the birds.
You did such a romantic thing.
I...
You two
are in love
to trust each other.
Moreover,
you'll do
many romantic things together.
Look.
The food is all out.
Situ,
do you know
that
you'll be with someone
who likes each other.
So,
is this Simutong
confessing to me?
Simutong,
where are you going?
Why are you still smiling?
You...
Why are you back?
I'm afraid you can't smile.
Xie, take me to see the sunrise.
I'm much better now.
I think you're so good at changing.
You're just
loving the position of the City Leader.
If you let the position of the City Leader
go,
it won't affect you.
You won't be
so nervous.
You're right.
I didn't mean to
be the City Leader.
I did all this
to get something.
So,
I mean,
my father is a great politician.
If
the real brother is me,
I won't be punished.
After all,
Princess Liuying is not dead.
Right?
So,
if you don't want
the position of the lady,
what do you want to do?
If I'm lucky,
I'll be with the person
who likes me.
But,
if this Mo Rong is a man,
she'll bite me
and I'll be the murderer.
She'll have to kill me.
What else can I do?
Have you thought of
another way?
For example,
cure Princess Liuying.
After she wakes up,
we'll ask her
about the situation.
Maybe we'll know
who the real brother is.
This is a good way.
Move.
What's going on?
Come here.
It's a yellow horse.
Come.
Princess Liuying has become
kg-matured for a month.
Older people searched
for the best doctor to cure her.
Old lady Liuying
found the best doctor
who can cure her.
Young lady Liuying took her
in because of shiny face.
So großes
many people have been rewarded.
You're responsible for the rest of the city.
Can you do it?
I can.
I'm a fire-fighter.
I have no other choice.
Right.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm excited.
This is not fair.
Boss.
You're back.
Didn't Lin Zheng come?
He's sick.
You're here to catch him, right?
What's wrong with him?
He's been very strange lately.
He's in a bad mood.
He's always talking to himself.
He's always jealous.
I know.
He's been like this every month.
Every month?
Is he a bad guy?
No, no.
It's a small problem.
But
he's in a bad mood.
He's sensitive.
You should take good care of him.
I understand.
Let me see.
Here.
Take it.
It's a cure.
It's a cure?
It's a good medicine.
Boss.
Have you prepared the medicine for Mr. Lu?
Yes.
Here.
Take it.
Take it on my son.
Okay.
Thank you, boss.
No need.
Right, boss.
What medicine did the man just now?
He's got a thousand gold coins.
A thousand gold coins?
Why does it have my name on it?
You're not a good student.
It's a poison cure.
It has nothing to do with you.
Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu, here's your medicine.
Let me ask you.
Thank you for this.
I didn't expect
you have a taste.
It's because you like it.
That's why I'm studying it.
I'm not good at it.
I have a bag on me.
Okay.
Here.
We should go.
Qianqin.
Li Yan.
Why are you here?
I'm here to see how your injury is.
I brought you some medicine.
The wind blows through the mountains and the leaves.
The mountains and the trees are bitter.
Who still misses him?
Who has ever loved him?