(All places, characters, firms and events
depicted in this show are fictitious.)
Senior Yoon!
Are you alright?
What's wrong?
It's too cramped.
What about you?
Are you here with your friends?
No, I followed you here.
How did you know I'm here?
I saw you while I was passing by.
You stood out.
Great eyesight.
You can go now. I'm here with my friend.
Why? Since we've met, let's hang out.
Hey.
Do you need to leave now?
No.
Let's hang out then!
Great!
Let's go!
-Let's go!
Come on.
So you two have been friends
since middle school?
(Episode 5)
So you two have been friends
since middle school?
Yes. And we live together too.
It'll bring us trouble
if people find out that
the HQ employee and
store employee are friends,
so I told her not to tell anyone.
I swear upon my life I won't tell anyone.
You're overreacting.
Then upon all my assets?
By the way, why are you here?
If you have any plans, you can go now.
It's okay.
Plans? Oh, my friends?
They are already gone.
I was on my way home
before I followed you inside.
Why?
I know, right?
I would like to know why.
Were you worried if she might meet a guy?
Hey, Kim Ga-young!
Yes.
You!
No, I mean, she
causes trouble quite often.
When I'm not around, she wreaks havoc.
I followed her inside
because I was worried.
I was worried that she
might cause trouble again.
I'm your senior.
I know.
If you were my junior,
I'd knuckle you on the head.
She gives me so much headache.
So this is who you are.
You're better than I thought.
If you get to know me more,
you'll find me even better.
Should we get to know
each other more tonight then?
Sounds good.
Cheers.
Cheers?
Unbelievable.
We need to get to know each other more.
What a party pooper.
Why don't you two go drink some more?
Shall we?
I'll have to take a rain check.
I can't fall out of favor
with Senior Yoon.
Seriously.
Let's meet up early next time.
We should start drinking
in the morning. Up for it?
Sure!
Awesome!
Stop talking and get in.
Alright. Call us!
Okay, bye.
Get home safely.
Okay.
Senior Yoon.
Have a great weekend.
You, too.
Get home safely.
Bye.
Alright!
Fight on!
Ji-Seung, you're watching this, right?
Go easy.
Alright!
Wait!
Seriously.
Is it good?
The shrimp is good.
Try the sweet and sour pork.
Thank you.
Hey.
You're seeing someone, right?
You're being too giddy.
Of course, I am.
It'd be weird if I'm not.
Who is she? What's she like?
Why do you think it's a woman?
It's a man?
Seriously!
What about you?
What about me?
You're not seeing anyone, are you?
Of course, you aren't.
You never know.
Remember the chef
of the restaurant we went to?
My hubby's friend?
Yes, what about him?
Do you want to set her up with him?
Huh?
Just one date. He seems perfect for you.
I'm not interested!
That's why you need to see him.
If I wait for you to get interested,
I'll never see you get married.
You need to make an effort.
That's the only way
to improve this situation.
Why do you keep running away?
I'm not running away...
Then what? Huh?
Why do you keep your distance
from everyone?
Since we're on the subject,
I'll ask you upfront.
Is the canceled engagement
still troubling you?
Yeon-seung.
It was your choice.
You weren't dumped, you quit.
So why are you afraid?
Do you regret it after all these years?
I don't regret it.
I'd do the same if I went back in time.
Then what's the reason?
You're breaking my heart.
You should love, and be loved by someone.
That's the way to live.
Yeon-seung, stop it.
The noodles are getting cold.
So this time, do as I say.
If you don't like him,
I won't bring it up again.
Okay.
People might think
you're the older sister.
Show me some respect then.
Alright, Big Sister.
Here's your receipt.
Do you, by any chance, have a dog in here?
Sorry?
I keep hearing the sound
of a dog whimpering.
Is she sick?
She's not well for sure.
Stop that and call her.
This has gone too long.
Do you think I don't want to call?
I'm scared.
What if she says she'll
never see me again?
She's so heartless.
She hung up the phone.
It'd be nice for her to call me first.
I told her to go to the college here,
but she abandoned me and went to Seoul.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Are you really her biological mother?
Huh?
You're breaking my prejudice
that all the mothers would sacrifice
themselves for the children.
In your case,
your daughter sacrificed herself.
How can a real mother
not let the child date or go to college?
I feel so sorry for her.
You...
Customers are waiting. Go make beverages.
Go work!
Okay, I will.
So stop pouting and tend the counter.
If you keep loafing around,
I'm going to quit.
Sheesh.
Boo!
Yikes!
Seriously!
Good morning.
Did you rest well yesterday?
Yes, and you?
Me too.
By the way, do you go to clubs often?
You danced really well.
What were your moves?
When did I dance like that?
Or is it like this?
I danced way better than that.
Way better than this?
Show me then.
How dare you!
You must be crazy.
BM Lee, you must be slacking off.
How can you come in
later than the director?
Are you wearing makeup?
Oh, uh...
We're launching a new product.
You're so thorough, as always.
How was the wedding shoot? Exhausting?
I guess.
It's not far off now.
Let's talk about your promotion soon.
Become a director before the wedding
and go to Europe after that.
It's perfect, right?
Stop what? Me?
Stop goofing around.
I didn't.
Get in, Senior Yoon.
Right,
the lipstick is coming out
next week, is it?
ABM Yoon.
Yes, the shipment will be on Thursday.
I'll keep checking.
So you're in charge of it.
You'll send LMS, right?
(LMS (Long Message Service):
Group messaging service for long texts)
You'll send LMS, right?
(LMS (Long Message Service):
Group messaging service for long texts)
To the customers who already bought it.
(LMS (Long Message Service):
Group messaging service for long texts)
Please pay extra attention.
It's very important to me.
Of course, sir.
Wait, I should give more than
lip service to you.
What do you think about lunch?
You are free, right?
Yes.
Will you be okay?
There's no reason not to be. I'll be fine.
If that customer comes,
please let me know.
Please call me. This is really good.
Japanese food is okay, right?
Perhaps I should've asked.
Yes, it's alright.
How long have you been working here?
Is it your third year?
Yes.
How's the marketing business? Is it fun?
I'm enjoying it.
I've been looking forward
to dining with you.
BM Lee complimented you once in a while.
He doesn't usually do that.
That's why I've been
keeping an eye on you.
I think you're great.
You're diligent and tactful.
Thank you.
Are there any difficulties at work?
For example, something like
wanting another BM?
What? Are you saying yes to that?
You should step up your game.
Your competent team member might run away.
Yes, sir.
Come in.
Your meal is ready.
Chef Oh is here, right?
I'm here with important guests,
so pay extra attention.
I wonder what Song-ah's eating.
It'll be really expensive and good, right?
Of course.
I hope I can sit with the director too.
-Manager Ahn.
-Yes?
Should I give you some money?
Really?
Of course. You think I'm lying?
I'm opening my wallet.
Am I being too generous?
Here, buy and eat anything you want.
You want a designer bag, right?
Buy that too.
And bring me back the change.
Why do you still have so much left?
No appetite?
Oh, right. I guess I don't.
Why? At your age,
even a stone tastes good.
Is it because of your crush?
Oh, no. Not at all.
Who is your crush anyway?
Just tell me. I won't tell anyone.
I was so curious that I couldn't sleep.
Look. Can you see the bags under my eyes?
Manger Ahn, you've always
had bags under your eyes.
At first, I thought you were a panda.
Hyun-seung.
Yes?
If you tell Ahn,
the whole company will know.
Just tell me.
You know I'm good with secrets, right?
I rarely speak.
I told you. It's Manager Yoo.
Seriously!
Don't say that.
She might really think you like her.
He learned bad stuff at the office.
Song-ah should have taught him better.
Hyun-seung!
Hello.
Huh?
Are you having lunch?
Yes.
-You too?
-Yes.
Have you had lunch?
-I see.
You're with them?
Yes.
I see.
You know about the Europe Project, right?
The Europe Project?
Huh?
You haven't told her yet?
I think it's too soon to make it public.
Geez, you're too cautious.
I can tell her now, right?
She'll be going with you anyway.
Are you interested in working overseas?
Yes, I guess...
We'll begin a major push
into the European market.
We'll open independent stores
starting with Paris.
So we need to set up a TF team.
I hope you'll join the team.
Me?
We need competent people more than ever.
-If you agree, then...
-Director.
I'll discuss it with ABM Yoon later.
It hasn't been made public yet.
I don't think it's fair to others.
I guess you're more cautious
because she's your team member.
People might think you're favoring her.
BM Lee is in charge of the project.
You can learn the details
from BM Lee later.
That'll do, right, BM Lee?
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
(Kim Ga-young: Knock knock)
(Sir, she's here!)
(Wink)
Now?
I'm sorry, but I need to go now.
It's urgent.
You two finish up.
Think about it, ABM Yoon.
Sorry.
You were planning to take me to Europe?
It's a good opportunity.
It'll be a great asset to you.
So you really were going to take me.
You never planned to tell me about
your marriage, is it?
If I never found out,
you would've taken me to Europe.
How could you?
Are you really the same person I know?
How much worse are you going to get?
How much lower can you go?
I'm not that stupid
to fall for the garbage
that is disguised as a good opportunity.
Tell the director that I'm not going.
What happened to you last weekend?
You just left.
Was it because of the call
you were waiting for?
Something important came up.
Is that so? Still, you should've told us.
You didn't even pick up your phone.
Actually, I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Not long ago,
I saw Seo-yeon on my way home from work.
It seems like she works
somewhere around here.
She must've found a job too.
Are you okay?
About Seo-yeon?
Of course, I am.
I don't even remember her number.
Really?
Since you turned every girl down,
I thought you were still into her.
Then, by any chance, this weekend...
Sorry,
something important came up.
Thanks.
Senior Yoon!
Did you enjoy your lunch?
I guess.
Are you back from lunch?
Yes, I am.
Go ahead to the office.
I'm going to take a walk.
Can I walk with you?
I ate too fast. I feel bloated.
Okay then.
Do you have something important
to do in the afternoon?
No, not really.
Good.
Huh?
(Right.)
Hara is already well known,
but if you open a pop-up store
in our department store,
it will help to further promote your shop.
And thanks to Hara, it'll improve
the image of our store too.
Okay, I'll think about it
in a positive light.
We're planning to make some changes too.
I look forward to your response.
See you again.
Goodbye.
Bye.
We meet again.
You must be wondering why I'm here.
Who are you?
No way.
You don't remember me?
I'm not that easily forgettable.
Lipstick.
I'll get it for you.
Even if I have to make it myself.
You remember me, right?
What brings you here?
Oh, that.
There's something I want to ask you.
Which is...
Do you need to go through a lawsuit?
For me to meet you?
For example,
a divorce suit
or something like that?
(Is she saying no?)
(She's saying no, right?)
Do you need it or not?
No.
There's no need for a divorce suit.
Yes!
Okay!
That's great.
As I promised, I'll let you go now.
We'll meet again, so don't be sad.
I'll rack my brains
to find ways to see you.
Bye.
I broke off my engagement.
If that's an issue...
Should I break off an engagement too?
Tell me your answer next time.
And also your name.
You said you want to bunk off.
That's why we're here.
There's nothing else to do,
so why don't we look at the products?
What are you talking about?
We can eat something nice, watch a movie
or just take a walk.
It's not a date.
I asked you to bunk off.
But still...
We need to develop a new product.
We have to do this soon anyway,
so let's do it now.
It's a lip tint, right?
Do you like your work that much?
When people don't want to work,
they don't even go near it.
Yes,
I like my work that much.
I'm going to do it for a very long time.
So I just need to work hard
to win your favor, right?
Teach me quickly,
so that I can develop a good product
and win your favor.
Please explain to me.
Hurry up.
The shape of an applicator
is important in lip products.
We make the shape based on the texture.
It's a bit bent. Like this.
It goes on well.
Right?
The color is really deep.
What's the color?
You know the colors by number, right?
No. 1 is pink, no. 2 is
orange, no. 3 is beige, no. 4 is red
and no. 5 is purple.
You can name them whatever you like.
But just to be sure,
you need to check
with the legal team first.
Another company might have patented it.
When I come up with a new name,
I should patent it too.
That's right.
What could they be?
For example, avoid names like these.
Oh, because they are already taken.
Come in!
Take a seat.
Sorry about earlier.
It was really important.
Was the lunch good?
Yes.
About the TF team...
You should've told me
before you spoke about it.
I thought you already told her.
We decided to take
ABM Yoon a long time ago.
I don't think I said anything
I shouldn't have.
I think I should sleep on it.
Why all of a sudden?
Is there a problem with her?
It's hard to find someone like her.
Does she have a problem with you?
No,
I just want to be careful.
You should be,
but this is unexpected.
Okay, I know you'll do the right thing.
Let me know when you make a decision.
I'm changing the job assignments.
Manager Kang.
Yes, sir.
You'll be the new trainer for ABM Chae.
He'll be working closely with you
for products and channels.
Why so suddenly?
I've been watching him closely
and I think he's having
a hard time with his task.
Color cosmetics development
is harder than skincare.
I think it was too much
for a first-year newbie.
Teach him well, Manager Kang.
Yes, sir.
Who will come to color cosmetics then?
And who will handle his channels?
I'll let you know after I think about it.
Manager Yoo and ABM Yoon
will have to work on it for now.
Yes, sir.
Just transfer ABM Chae
when you have the decision then.
We can't afford to spare anyone
in our section right now.
We don't know how long it'll take
for you to make the decision.
We can just swap the members when there's
someone available for our section,
so that there's no gap.
Was ABM Chae doing that much work for you
to worry about a gap in the workload?
As I see it, he's more like an assistant.
He does quite a lot for a newbie.
He's doing great.
ABM Yoon,
I understand what you're saying.
But this is my decision as a BM
to operate the team better.
I think it'll be better for his career
to learn the basic knowledge.
I'll decide quickly
so that there won't be a gap.
Start the takeover immediately.
ABM Chae, learn from
Manager Kang after this.
Yes, sir.
Senior Yoon...
Song-ah!
Is there a lot to hand over?
No, not much. Why?
Can it be done
before we get off work?
You can just give me the material.
I'll have to check first.
Okay.
Why?
What were you going to say?
We'll talk later.
Do what you have to do first.
Okay.
(Canceled?)
I didn't cancel it.
Why did you cancel my dress?
It was because of internal affairs.
I'm getting married in a month.
I'm sorry.
What is the internal affair?
Are you closing the shop?
We will compensate...
What else do I need other than a dress?
Are you really telling me I'm on my own?
Is this how you handle things?
I don't believe it!
Find a new dress shop for me.
Where they can meet the deadline.
I'm going home.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
Senior Yoon!
Are you done?
Yes.
After the meeting, it was so hectic.
We didn't have a chance to talk.
I'm sorry.
You're suffering because of me.
I knew you would say that.
I was going to say I'm alright.
I'm really okay.
Since he thinks we're dating,
he'll surely split us up.
You're better than me.
You'll learn a lot of new things
at skincare and door-to-door.
Do your best.
Okay.
I'll work twice as hard,
so don't worry.
By the way,
the weather is so nice.
Are you not going to
throw me a farewell party?
I will,
but I'm a bit tired today.
Let's set a date soon.
Okay.
Get home safely.
You too, bye.
Bye.
You're home.
Thank you.
You should've let yourself in.
I have manners.
I don't barge into other people's houses,
even if you're my boyfriend.
Can you take a day off this week?
Why?
There's a problem with my wedding dress.
I'm going to change the shop.
I'll check my schedule.
Are you not going to ask
what problem it is?
You must have a good reason for it.
I guess I'm getting married alone.
It's my wedding dress anyway.
It's not someone else's problem.
I'll be careful from now on.
I'll get the earliest possible day off.
A lot happened today. I'm tired.
I'll get going now.
Hyo-joo.
You know, Jae-shin.
You can't walk all over me.
I do love you more,
but it's not my weakness.
This is really good for the complexion...
It goes like this, right?
Huh? What?
Song-ah.
Changes are hard, right?
Yes, a little.
It's been only two days,
so it must be awkward.
Still, how can you know just by his voice?
Lucky you, Hyun-seung.
Your trainer is so affectionate.
Oh, she's your ex-trainer now.
Get ready to go, Hyun-seung.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll introduce Hyun-seung
to the sales team.
To celebrate his transfer,
talk to Chief Kim
and ask for an increase in sales.
Hyun-seung.
Yes, sir.
Hang in there.
I will.
We'll be back.
Yes, this is Yoon Song-ah from KLAR.
Yes, Director Lee.
Director Lee asked to see me.
Tell him it's ABM Yoon Song-ah.
Please wait for a moment.
Sure.
Sir, ABM Yoon Song-ah is here.
Yes, sir.
You're here.
Hello, sir.
I've brought the product you asked for.
Good.
Okay, thanks.
Have you thought about it?
What I said at lunch the other time?
Well...
You're still thinking about it.
While you're at it, give it some thought.
It's the chance of a lifetime.
If you say you want to go,
I'll send you there for sure, okay?
You may go now.
What? I'm busy.
Jae-shin is at work, right?
Why would you ask me about him?
Of course, he's at work.
Two of these, please.
All right.
Lastly, two of these.
Pack them with the drinks
I ordered earlier.
Okay.
He decorated this place so well.
Did he pick these out himself?
Is omija tea okay?
Try it, I made the ingredients myself.
What a lovely color.
Thank you.
Am I bothering you at break time
when you should get some rest?
I'm okay if it's you, Yeon-seung.
What brings you here anyway?
Since you're always nice to us,
I want to thank you.
This is men's skincare.
My brother's company makes it.
My husband said it's good.
I'm using this too.
Oh, really?
That's great!
Everyone has a different taste
for their skincare,
so I was a bit worried.
Thank you.
Did you choose the decorations yourself?
Or a girlfriend choose them for you?
They are so pretty.
I chose them myself.
I don't have a girlfriend.
Oh, why though?
You seem like a great guy.
Are you not interested in dating?
I am, but...
The reality is harder than you think.
Why?
Where there's a will, there's a way.
Perhaps you haven't met
the right person yet.
If you don't mind my asking,
what's your type?
There might be someone
I know who fits your type.
I don't know what type I like.
But there's a type I'm curious about.
Which type is that?
Ow, hot.
It's hot.
Yes, it's hot.
(But there's a type I'm curious about.)
He's talking about me, right?
He has an eye for beauty.
Who?
Oh, just someone I know.
Did someone say you're pretty?
Why do you ask?
That person might be conning you.
What?
You're not pretty, Mom.
What about Aunt Ji-seung?
She's pretty.
And Uncle Hyun-seung?
He's pretty.
And you?
I'm pretty.
Why aren't I pretty then?
Ask Grandma, not me.
A daughter is supposed
to support her mother.
But I can't lie.
Green light.
Go, Mom.
Hello.
Long time no see.
He's a newcomer.
Hello, I'm Chae Hyun-seung from KLAR.
Let's talk later when we have time.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Hello.
Go introduce yourself.
Yes.
Hello, I'm Chae Hyun-seung from KLAR.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
He's the new ABM.
Oh.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Hello, I'm Chae Hyun-seung from KLAR.
Hi.
I look forward to working with you.
I'll get going now.
(Gangnam)
Chief Kim,
I want to introduce the new ABM.
Oh! He's new?
No, but he was assigned
to door-to-door this week.
Hyun-seung.
Right, I'm Chae Hyun-seung.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, I'm Kim Do-gyun.
Hello.
How long have you worked here?
I've never seen you before.
It's my first year.
So you have zero background
about door-to-door.
Have you been to the branch office?
I went once when I was an intern.
Then you haven't.
Are you free today?
Today?
It's up to you. Check your schedule.
I don't have anything important today.
It's settled then.
Hey, Manager Jin!
You're going to the branch office, right?
Yes.
Take the new ABM with you.
Teach him well.
Put the samples in the trunk.
Yes, sir.
Marketers should know
the situation on the field.
You all just sit at your desks.
That's not how you develop
a proper sales policy.
Fasten your seatbelt.
Yes, sir.
Three boxes.
Okay.
Here's your receipt.
Here.
Okay, thank you.
Goodbye.
Bye.
It looks heavy. I'll do it.
No, it's okay.
Do you really want to end it like this?
Is it that easy for you to move on?
Even if we break up, this isn't the way.
Just tell the director that
I won't join the TF team.
That's all I want to hear from you.
Is it because of Chae Hyun-seung?
Did he tell you not to go?
Let's go.
I'm here!
Come on in.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Put the box here.
Yes, sir.
Coffee?
Perfect.
Hello.
Who is he? A newbie?
An ABM from KLAR.
He's doing door-to-door now, but
he's only done department stores before.
Coffee?
No, I'm okay. Thanks.
If an elder gives you
something, you take it.
You're such a geezer.
I'm glad that I don't have to make more.
I have something
to say to KLAR's marketing.
Good, pour it all out
so that they'll work properly.
Sit down.
Yes, sir.
Please tell me everything.
About the policy...
It's always a sample or 5:1 or 4:1.
What are you doing? Take notes.
Oh, right...
Can I use that pen and paper?
The policy is always 5:1 or 4:1...
Yes, but the policies should be...
We're back!
Did you sell a lot?
Oh! Manager Jin is here.
Did you bring something good?
I'm the good thing,
what more can you want?
Who is this?
An ABM from KLAR.
Oh! ABM!
So handsome! How old are you?
I sold a lot of KLAR products today.
Why didn't you give him a cup of coffee?
Do you want some coffee?
No, thanks. I don't like caffeine.
How about iced tea?
No, it's alright.
Over here! He's an ABM from KLAR!
Oh, hello.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
We have a gathering later.
A gathering?
You should come!
It'll be fun.
(Yes, ma'am, I just got in.)
(Yes.)
I'll get my stuff and go home.
Yes.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Goodbye.
Okay.
Chae Hyun-seung.
Okay. Rock, paper, scissors!
I'm going first.
I did it!
Did you really have dinner?
Your cheeks have sunken in.
It's because I worked outside today.
You should go home then. Why come here?
I said I'd be at Ha-eun's recital
but I couldn't make it.
So I'm keeping my promise today.
Because my pretty little niece
wants to see me!
Right, Ha-eun?
If you're tired, it's okay
to break one promise.
You can just tell me next time.
You're exhausting yourself
trying to make a living.
You understand it?
Is she really seven years old?
The kids these days don't act their age.
She's more like a 17-year-old girl.
Are you sure you're alright?
You don't look too good.
Honey, feel Hyun-seung's pulse!
No, it's okay.
I'm healthy. I'm really fine.
Still, I'll check your pulse later.
See me before you go.
You should.
Okay, thank you.
He's busy.
Checking your pulse won't help though.
What?
You got dumped, right?
I can tell.
Don't cry even though it hurts.
Love is supposed to hurt.
Who is she going to be when she grows up?
Is it really about a girl?
No, not at all.
How could you listen to a kid?
I want some cold water.
Sit. I'll get it for you.
Is it my turn?
Thank you.
Senior Yoon!
What are you doing here?
The Gangnam sales team wants to see me.
I see.
Are you alone?
Manager Kang said she's busy.
Is that so?
You're doing well, right?
Aren't you getting on?
Yes, just a moment!
Go on then.
Okay.
Keep it up.
You too.
(Chae Hyun-seung)
(Don't worry, Senior Yoon!)
(Whoosh whoosh)
(Boom boom)
(Don't forget about my farewell party!)
Don't even think of
going home before midnight.
Okay, sir.
What song did you prepare?
I prepared "Ground Bee".
Good choice.
What about you?
I prepared "Unconditionally".
Oh! "Unconditionally"?
Write down your home address
and emergency contact number.
Why do you need this though?
Okay, let's go!
Yes, sir!
Oh, okay!
I'm going to head home.
Manager Kang,
how come Hyun-seung is not back yet?
He's probably at the gathering.
Why?
It's obvious.
They're trying to break him in.
You should've stopped them.
How could you let him go?
He should take care of himself.
Bye, guys.
Okay, bye.
Wow, she's so cold.
I'm so glad that she's not my trainer.
Let's go, Manager Ahn.
Take it easy, Song-ah.
Take care.
Bye.
Awesome!
Attention, please!
Let's propose a toast to all the ladies!
Chant, ready!
Chant, begin!
Flip the board!
Increase sales!
Meet the goal!
We are the kings of sales!
Bottoms up!
Have one more glass.
Yes, of course.
-Whoa.
-Oh, dear.
One more shot!
Bottoms up!
(Are you still at the gathering?)
(Chae Hyun-seung)
(Senior Yoon Song-ah:
Hyun-seung, where are you?)
Manager Jin!
I love you all!
We love you!
It's a beautiful night.
Be happy.
(We'll form a TF team.)
The team will stay in Europe
for about three years.
Song-ah is one of the candidates.
I guess she hasn't told you yet.
So what?
Do whatever you can to make her go.
She thought I recommended her
and so she refused to go.
But she's competent enough for the job.
She can decide on her own.
That's why you don't know her.
If she's stuck on something,
she can't see anything else.
So if you really care for her,
make a sensible choice.
I assume you know that much.
There's nothing much to life.
Just enjoy it!
Why isn't he picking up?
Where did he go?
Okay, who is no. 1 next year?
KLAR!
Good!
Let's go for round three!
Are you serious, sir?
I'll go if our ABM goes.
That's enough. Stop.
Hey, Marketing!
At your service!
How about round three?
Yes, sir!
He's going?
Round three! Let's go!
Huh?
Go away.
Manager Jin!
Manager Jin.
What is he doing?
Why did you come so late?
What?
Seriously.
Hey.
I missed you.