[English subtitles are available]
It's a dead-end lane ahead.
Confront him.
I know.
What the heck?
You should apologize for bumping into me.
I don't want this in my room.
Won't your eyes feel dry?
Rest in peace.
Pu Yiyong, you bastard.
Strange.
That's weird.
[Performance Clothes]
Yiyong asked me
if I had any photos of you from that time.
I didn't give them to him.
I didn't allow him to ask or find them either.
Normal people
wouldn't feel like seeing it, right?
Yiyong is always
different from the others.
You know your son.
He's got a simple brain.
He thinks
he can know
whether you left the world without suffering
after seeing it.
This fool.
Who would know
this kind of thing
but the person involved?
Right?
Tell him yourself when you have time.
Don't let him spend his life guessing.
[Bullying Determinator]
[Episode 3]
He's not under the bridge either?
I've looked at it.
Where else would he go?
I thought he said he would never leave you.
Of course, people are just saying that, no matter who it is.
He's such a troublemaker.
I couldn't get rid of him before.
I can't leave.
Why?
The power of the human heart
is much stronger than skin and flesh.
That's why I can't leave.
The human heart.
Zheng Lisong.
What's wrong?
Why did you come here?
I didn't want to come.
This body did.
Lisong?
Get up and take a look.
Is it Lisong?
Look, is it?
It's Lisong.
It's our Lisong.
Lisong.
Are you hurt?
It's okay. Let's see.
You fell down on a bike?
It's okay.
We won't blame you.
Just don't ride it in the future.
Lisong! Lisong!
Where should you go now?
Back under the bridge.
I'm not leaving you.
You...
What are those?
The strength that grabbed me
is gone.
Human heart?
The one who died.
Zheng Lisong?
What does it mean? What's he talking about?
Can't you see?
He's falling apart.
Then you can leave, can't you?
You go back to your own body.
No big deal.
I can help you get your body out of the river.
Even if I'm not available,
she's a cop. She can do anything.
I don't want to.
You don't want to?
I'm not going back.
The flood broke out.
The water destroyed our village.
I wish to erect this statue
to bring good fortune…
I grew out of their painful hearts.
And to keep the water away and report the disaster.
They want me to be there forever to protect them.
After a long time,
those people are no longer there.
But I remain where I am.
I remembered
why I came to see you.
It was an incomplete word.
But it had the same power as the heart,
just like the hearts of those villagers.
After another long time…
I want to leave.
Don't let them find my body.
Help me.
what?
Give me this power.
I don't want to go back to my old body.
I want to get out of there.
The power of the human heart you were talking about.
I don't understand it.
I am indeed a human being.
I have a heart too.
But where is the power?
What does it look like?
I don't even know if I have it.
How should I give it to you?
What word will have the power of the heart?
Charm?
Words that have the power of the heart.
The work your grandfather did
is not mass production.
You can see his heart
through every word he wrote.
He didn't just mourn the dead.
He also comforted the living.
Thank you, Mr. Pu.
They are so pitiful.
This is at least a little more dignified.
Don't say that.
Come on, say thank you to Mr. Pu.
Don't force him.
I'm really sorry.
He's been like this
not long after his brother…
He won't cry or talk.
Don't force him.
Our class has the lowest grade point average in the whole school year.
It's my fault.
During the essay test,
I just copied the topic and fell asleep at the desk.
So I couldn't
write anything decent for you.
You can draw from it.
I'll write whatever you get.
Does that help?
Look at all the stuff floating out.
He's finished.
I'm just taking my chance.
Thank you.
Hum.
I didn't
leave you
because
I really liked you.
Just go.
Are there many more like you?
You're really good.
I feel like
I've done something great.
You?
I think it's me.
I've done something great.
I saved you.
When did you ever save me?
You tried to strangle me to death before.
Don't think I've forgotten.
You were on that bus, right?
Almost two years ago?
When I found you,
there was no sign of life.
I tried my best to resuscitate you.
CPR?
It was my duty.
You're welcome.
I hadn't even kissed anyone yet.
It should take a while for the grass to grow.
Why didn't the body decompose?
How did you find it last time?
It's really something.
Hey.
Let me see the record book.
I am.
But can you please stop calling me “police”?
You can call me Chuying.
I want to ask you something.
Did you see my father
the day you saved my life?
He was wearing a cotton jacket.
It was grey.
He carried a backpack,
on which
there was probably his company name tag
with his name Pu Renxiu on it.
[Dandelion Show]
No.
I didn't see it.
Then have you found
his body?
It remains in the same place.
It looks pretty bad, doesn't it?
I think so.
I want to ask you something.
It's so troublesome. Go ahead.
You're going to get his parents to come and identify the body, right?
Is it now or...
The identity is basically intact.
Maybe we'll organize the body
After the autopsy.
Stop it.
Don't what?
Let his parents come and see it.
Do you mean don't let them see it?
Leave it as it is.
Let them see it.
They can't stand it. They'll remember it for the rest of their lives.
That's why Zheng Lisong
didn't want to be found.
Don't stop them from seeing it just because you feel sorry for them.
Even if they can't see,
they will also guess and imagine.
He must have left without suffering.
He must have died on the spot
without feeling scared.
Whether they see it or not,
they won't forget it.
At least don't let them guess and imagine.
They have the right to know.
Senior,
when to invite the family to identify the body?
This doesn't look good.
After all, his parents are older…
We'll ask them to come
after the autopsy and body organizing.
This is what I thought.
I will try to ask them to do so.
Let's ask the parents about their will first.
That's fine.
How come I have to be here
while you can sit over there?
If you get washed away,
I can use the walkie-talkie to call for help.
I'm your insurance.
You're wearing civilian clothes today.
Where's the walkie-talkie?
Call for help.
Police.
Did I get you again?
Sorry.
I found it.
I'll count to three. Let's move together.
One, two, three.
We can't move it even if you count to 80.
Then what should we do?
Let's leave it here.
It's already an empty shell.
[Taipei City Police Station Shangcheng Police Station]
A year ago, a serious CP pointed out
something wrong with Dr. Muzi's prescription in the Urology Department
and thus offended Muzi.
After the CP changed to a pharmacist.
Muzi urged other pharmacists to gang up on him.
The young pharmacist
didn't know how the world works and was too responsible.
So he got bullied
in the hospital
where speed was valued the most.
I once saw him taking high blood pressure medication.
I asked him why he didn't quit.
In a word,
the salary in the big hospital was good.
Money can be lethal sometimes.
Don't ask me who Muzi is.
I'm also afraid.
[Chongge University Affiliated Hospital Zhou Ping] [Student]
Muzi.
His last name is Li?
[It's caught.]
[But what should I do?]
[If you report about being bullied,] It'll lead to suicide.
[Don't lie to the living.]
[Chongge University Hospital, Li Zhenghei] [Urology]
I don't know him well.
I barely talked with him.
About a year ago,
Zheng Lisong came to work
as a clinical pharmacist at your hospital.
You worked together for a while, right?
Maybe.
It's been so long that it's a bit vague.
And after all,
our departments were far apart.
It was less than a year ago.
And he corrected you on your prescriptions.
He made you look bad.
That's impressive for you, isn't it?
Excuse me.
Do you know me
have to do with
whether I know him well
or something in my workplace?
You said you didn't know him well because your departments were far apart.
Then I'd like to ask you.
Why did Dr. Li
often have dinner with other pharmacists?
Dr. Li.
You're from the urology department.
May I ask
what diuretics
usually treat or do?
It's not a special drug.
You can find it on the internet.
It's just a joke.
What joke?
I just wanted to make him
to suffer from diarrhea.
It was a joke.
You're a doctor.
You knew what would happen when blood pressure medication
and diuretic were taken at the time, didn't you?
I didn't know.
I didn't know he was taking blood pressure medication.
Less than an hour after that,
he crashed into a guardrail at high speed.
He didn't even brake.
Either he killed himself,
or his blood pressure was too low and he was in a coma.
You said it was just a joke?
Yiyong.
Pu Yiyong.
Come on.
Where are you going?
Someone sent you a present.
Who? What is it?
It's an auspicious gift. I love it.
You can't return it.
I've already signed for it.
It's from Chen Ying or something.
It's too poor to be left in the river.
And if you look closely,
don't you think he looks pretty cute?
So cute.
Then why didn't you ship it to your house?
How to put it?
I still think it's a little scary.
I'm asking you.
That night,
you looked at him and said he was finished.
Was there something on him?
That's rude.
Are you reading comics on duty?
It's not comics.
What else would it be?
It's...
Comics.
Okay.
You did well
this time.
Thank you, Yipa.
Look at this.
When you said “thank you”, I got goosebumps.
Stop it.
It's a good thing he wasn't framed as a suicide.
The body was also found.
Do you want to go help Detection 2?
They seem to be dealing with something weird lately
and can't close the case.
It seems to be an unsolved case.
It's already the fifth time.
From now on, don't sign for anything
that comes from Chen Ying or something.
You got it almost two years ago.
Who gave it to you?
He was very old.
Much older than me.
Two years ago.
Very old.
Was that the old woman?
Who's the old woman?
This is mine.
It's going to be cold tonight.
I don't know why.
I think this dress suits him so well.
I don't think you should
give my clothes to it anyway.
Show some respect to him.
It's cold. Let's go eat something hot.
Sure, sure.
I'd love some soup.
Oden.
I'll have the pig's blood cake.
I'll take the call.
I'll see you later.
We'll wait for you then.
It's okay. You guys go ahead.
Let's go.
I'll wait for him. You can go first.
I'm so annoyed.
They have to eat, go to the bathroom and do everything together.
Dad.
I'm sorry I didn't get it because of the noise.
It's okay now, you can say it.
Unemployment?
Saying you're not worried,
do you really mean it?
Five years of tuition.
[Tuition fee, maintenance fee, life, scholarship] All
Tuition fees and living expenses.
And then the scholarship.
Senior.
Guang.
It's the same for you.
Be sure to check out if there is anyone before you leave.
Good.
I'm sorry.
I knew you couldn't come in as a second-year.
But thank you for your kindness.
I'm so grateful.
I'll go first.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
You have to live with the landlord.
It's not easy.
Isn't the rent much lower than before?
That's not a problem anymore.
Guangyan.
Didn't I tell you to live in the big room?
Why did you move to the smaller room?
If you want to work at home afterward,
you'll need space to work.
No need.
I'll find a publisher then.
That's impossible.
They won't want you
with your seniority and experience.
The publishing industry is having a hard time on its own.
They can't afford to hire senior people like you.
So it's most likely for you to do outsourced work at home.
I'll take you to the next door to say hello to the neighbors.
That's okay.
We have to unpack first.
I'll never be able to see her again.
What about her?
What? What about her whole life?
Come on.
Come here.
You’re going to her house before you finish.
Come on.
You can start a small business for free
in this empty lot.
No rent?
It's unused anyway.
That's good.
This is a good place to set up…
You can start a small business
in this empty lot.
Yes, you just told us. I know.
Thank you.
20% of the turnover.
Didn't you say it was free?
Yes, I just heard her say it's free.
Why is she taking 20% now?
Mrs. Pu.
They are the first tenants in my life.
How are you?
We just moved in.
Why are there still people with the surname Pu nowadays?
This is...
No.
[I'm awarded for solving the case.]
[Don't send messages at this hour.]
[Has anyone come to see you recently?]
[Who?]
[A living corpse?]
[I'm going to sleep.]
[Don't call the police if you do, call me.]
[Understand, Hua Sheng?]
[What Hua Sheng?]
[You are my Huasheng.]
[Hua Sheng]
[John Huasheng]
[Detective and Assistant]
[A golden relationship]
[Screw you, Huasheng. I'll call the police if you send any more messages.]
Remember to talk to grandpa
in the hospital.
Okay.
And apologize to the nursing staff.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Mr. Cao.
Your noodle stall
is
very...
Dad, I'm going to class.
Guangyan.
Hello, auntie.
Hello.
What are you looking at, son?
Is it so attractive?
What are you looking at?
Tell me.
Let's go.
What's to look at?
He's still staring.
He's sick.
[Cao Noodle Shop]
There's a sign?
And a menu.
[Menu]
Did you write this?
No, Yiyong wrote it.
Pu Yiyong?
That's right.
Look at his handwriting.
He's the same age as you and his writing is so beautiful.
And it was done in five minutes.
Is that so?
The most important thing is that he charged a reasonable fee.
He charged a fee?
That's right.
The market is 300 yuan.
He's our neighbor
and your schoolmate.
He only charged me 150 yuan.
All of it?
That would be
taking advantage of him.
Of course, each word.
10,000 yuan for less than five minutes?
Where are you going?
To confront him.
What? Why?
Wait.
Where are you going now?
I can't beat him.
Good morning, Mr. Cao.
Good morning.
He's sick.
Guangyan.
Give me a hand.
Take this to school and send it out
for advertising.
I think this is a photocopy.
No, it's not.
It's written.
It's all written.
150 yuan per word.
No, this time it counted by a sheet.
It counted by a sheet.
One is only mine.
Don't count it.
I don't want to know.
All right.
You've been unconscious for so long.
Why didn't you let me know when you woke up?
Yong, let me see.
Let me see.
Yong.
Are you all right?
My mother said you visited me often.
Don't come anymore.
You come twice a week.
Don't you have to prepare for the college entrance exam?
Yes.
His time is suspended.
But yours are not.
After the exam,
If he is still unconscious,
none of you should come anymore.
I don't want to.
I don't want to either.
Seeing Yiyong like that,
how can you feel good?
This would be like a big stone.
Don't put this
in your hearts.
Think about your own life.
That's why we visited you
before the exam for the last time.
Yong, are you still painting?
Thank you.
You've been paying for the subscription, right?
My comics.
Ah.
Actually, you don't have to both subscribe to it.
No.
We should pay for it.
We should.
What are you doing these days?
You haven't resumed school?
Besides taking care of my grandfather,
I have to find a job.
I've applied for some jobs recently.
None of those bastards informed me.
He's making money from YouTube.
I did it.
It's not good.
I'm doing an internship.
Yong.
We pay well there.
I can recommend you to our boss.
Thanks, Dongjun.
What kind of creator are you on YouTube, Li Can?
Beauty.
Do you have another subscription
to the comics?
No.
We put 35 yuan together.
I didn't expect
other people
to be willing to pay for Yong's comics.
I want to see what that person looks like.
It's good that Yong is awake.
[Hikaru, Autopsy Room, please.]
I'm sorry.
Is this mine?
Why is there no sauce?
Do you know what this is?
Why are you asking me here?
Where else should I ask?
It's a bit sudden.
So, is today our first day together?
I'm asking you what this is.
A loving heart.
Help me see what this is.
Don't do this to us.
We'll
flutter.
Guangyan, I can't stand it.
Idiot.
Guangyan, take me home.
Shut up.
Guangyan.
Can you help me see what this is?
The floor?
No, it's this.
Your foot?
Wow.
Great!
Thank you, Mr. Cao.
You're welcome.
Mom.
Do the guests and the owner's family
have to sit at the same table?
Dad.
As the boss, can't we choose our guests?
I'm sorry.
I think Guangyan is still confused
from the class today.
No.
I'm sorry.
Don't mind this guy.
You have no manners.
Why are you in such a hurry to leave?
Should I help you with the dishes then?
You saw it.
I didn't see it.
If you answered so quickly, then you did.
I told you I didn't.
You did.
I really didn't.
I didn't.
I found you.
[In the next episode]
Help me.
Here comes another one.
I want to help the girl.
You should come along.
Are you messing with me?
Please help me find the name of that man.
He didn't even say his name?
For people who live in the street,
who doesn't have a story?
Can't you see?
Help me.