[English subtitles are available]
Help me.
[To preserve one's own purity and integrity]
Help me!
You're selfish!
I won't let you go.
[Some can see, some can't.]
[Monsters are born from obsession.]
[Oh No! Here Comes Trouble]
[School report card of January 2020]
[Rynn High School of Taipei]
[Episode 1]
I was just being mad at you.
[Class 3 of Grade 3, Student ID: 70331, Name: Pu Yiyoung]
I don't care that
you were the reason
why our class average grade was ranked last this semester in the school.
I'm worried about your future.
Your hands.
The thing is
you can get into college even if you roll the dice.
But you don't even prepare yourself with the dice.
Thank you.
Did I say it was for you?
Give it back to Chen Dongjun.
Tell him to stop rolling the dice for filling answers.
Did you talk with your parents?
About your future?
About my future, I was...
You were embarrassed to talk about it, weren't you?
I was like you.
But there was this one time
when my dad got me a drink
and we talked about it over a drink.
That's what made me here today.
So you hate your dad?
Yes.
I wanted to be a professional basketball player.
Get out.
There's one more thing.
Stay away from that student in Class 1.
Here.
How was it?
What did Fu say?
He said I was the reason why our class average grade was ranked last this semester.
See?
I told you it was him.
We both passed.
Shut up!
It's okay. It doesn't hurt.
Raise your foot.
He got hurt so often.
Is he an outcast, or what?
An outcast?
He is a people person,
every human being likes him.
[Class 3 of Grade 3, Student ID: 70318, Name: Cao Guangyan]
[School report card of January 2020]
[Rynn High School of Taipei]
Thank you.
No, I said it wrong.
He's adored not just by humans.
Who did this to him?
There's only one person who doesn't like him.
Who is it?
It's the guy who's running and who looks like a criminal.
He's in a different class.
Why is he taking things personally against Cao Guangyan?
Yong.
Guangyan.
Pu Yiyong, it's a basketball game, why did you smash it?
Are you okay, Guangyan?
Pu Yiyong, it's a football game, why did you smash it?
Guangyan.
Pu Yiyong, it's a volleyball game, why did you...
Oh, you could smash it.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Guangyan.
This won't scare him.
Let me fight him one-on-one.
Principal, I suggest not.
It wouldn't look good if you hurt him.
Here, put it on.
Ah.
Principal, I've got an idea.
Pu Yiyong.
Here's the Heart Sutra.
Read it while transcribing it.
Read it again after transcribing it.
One stroke after another.
Don't scribble it.
Okay.
Yiyong,
put your heart into this.
We'll be there outside.
We won't leave
before you finish.
Pu Yiyong,
here's your last chance.
Tell me the truth.
Why did you bully Cao Guangyan?
Tell me so you don't have to do this.
I've gotta deal with something else later.
Please just tell me.
-I... -You went to the washing room 20 minutes ago.
Do you want to pee again?
You are not the Principal.
I finished it.
[The Heart Sutra]
Next month,
there's a high school calligraphy contest.
-I wonder if you... -How much is the bonus?
There will be...
There will be certificates and honors that you can't buy with money.
No.
But...
Okay. Okay. I hear you.
I don't understand.
You suck at exams,
but why are you so good with calligraphy, Yong?
It's hereditary.
I'm the reincarnation of the demon. I got it from my grandpa.
I'd believe it if you say so.
Of course.
I just don't know why my grandpa was upset.
What's wrong with him?
He said I...
You took the free ride.
[Pu Yiyong, 10,000 Yuan]
You've been copying the shape of the characters of the famous calligraphers.
You didn't put your heart into this.
You've conned people with those characters.
What did you say?
Thank you, grandpa.
Ah.
I thought he gave me a compliment that I was a fast learner.
Now I know why you suck at exams.
[One-person class starts immediately]
[Doctor of calligraphy wanted]
It is said that
my ancestors taught people how to write.
And they had a good reputation for it.
The business went well when it was passed to my grandpa.
[Pu Zhankui's Research Institute]
My mom met my dad
when she was attending the class.
[The authority of being parents]
But nowadays,
people can't take it if the Wifi
or the phone is slow.
No one would spend his time practicing the calligraphy strokes.
Yiyong,
come help me, give these to the students.
I told you not to leave.
Old Pu, no...
Mr. Pu's grandson is handing us the homework today.
It's my turn.
Are you trying to get a lucky draw？
Ah.
It dropped.
Yiyoung.
Stop playing with him.
Just pick one so I won't kill you.
My homework.
What did I buy?
Give it back to Grandpa Yang.
Whose money is this?
You can leave after you finish writing.
For this stroke on the top,
use your strength when you write it.
Yes, sir.
Good.
You want his hairstyle?
I don't want to cut my hair. It's not long.
Yes, you do.
You have to cut it before the Chinese New Year.
Give me the money and I'll go to the barber's.
I'll wait upstairs.
Yiyoung.
What?
I heard about what happened at school.
-Did you... -I didn't push him.
He fell because he was scared.
Who did?
What were you about to say?
The mentor said
the Principal forced him to persuade you to join the contest.
Anything else?
And he told us about the class average grade.
Oh.
I didn't ask you to be a top student.
But every time I saw your report card,
it hurt here.
The lowest grade in school?
Got it.
Thank you, Mr. Yao.
Goodbye.
Yiyong's grades are worse than mine when I was in school.
Yes.
You told him you didn't care about his grades.
You are his dad and you don't care.
So don't worry.
I won't teach him a lesson.
That's good.
Although I don't care about your grades,
I didn't expect
you to care less than I do.
The teacher is right.
If you have better grades,
you'll have more options in the future.
Speaking of which,
you haven't told me
what you want to do in the future.
When you were little,
besides calligraphy,
you started everything later than kids of the same age did.
Now, you think about it a little later than they do too.
As an adult, can you say things irresponsibly like that?
Why are you hiding from your mom?
Her way of cutting my hair always made me look like a hooligan.
Why are you hiding?
Now,
I don't even know what my boss and colleagues will think of me.
At least, this hairstyle makes you look like you are five...
Three centimeters taller.
Three centimeters taller?
Seriously, you don't have any?
Things like dreams
or life goals.
The Principal gave it to me.
It's not a beer?
I'm only 17.
[Geography]
[Back to the main page]
[Send]
[Uploaded successfully]
Let me die.
Will you help me or not?
It's still the same answer.
[Original Comic Camp: Your have received 70 yuan in your account]
Let me ask you one last time.
Will you help me or not?
[To preserve one's own purity and integrity]
It's still the answer even if you are dying.
[Shangcheng Police Station]
[Taipei Police Station]
[Investigation Team 1]
What are you doing during the meeting?
Giving out leaflets.
Hurry up.
Take a look at the files in your hands.
There are wounds on the victims' heads, hands, and feet.
Did you get the CCTV footage?
Yang went to get it.
Tell him to hurry up.
We're going to be late again.
I envy him.
Why that dumb?
I should be the one who joins the investigation team.
One-per.
Chen Chuying.
Sir.
She didn't listen to me.
I was testifying.
Get prepared and
go support those seniors.
Yes, sir. What's the case?
It was handed over by the director.
Excuse me.
Higher.
[Sincerely, Shangcheng Police Station of Taipei]
[United we are one. The police and the people write the Spring Festival Couplets to celebrate Celebrate the Spring Festival.]
Senior,
I can't go higher anymore.
Senior, where should I place the table?
In front of the spring couplets.
How about the chair?
Put it behind the table.
Sorry,
I mean where I can get a chair?
I'll get it.
[Calligrapher Professor Pu Zhankui]
Yiyong.
There's a seat in the back. Go sit down.
You'll be standing for the whole afternoon.
It's tiring.
Go sit down.
Hurry up.
Hurry!
Chen Chuying.
Take your juniors
to Kanding 2nd Rd. Hurry.
Put them down. Go get your gear.
1011 copy.
Pu Yiyong.
Sorry.
[Pu Yiyong's desk. Move it and you'll be dead.]
I'll wait and see
if you are the same as your grandpa.
Baby.
Yiyong!
Yi Yong!
Yi Yong.
You can do that.
Dad.
Grandpa is here.
Grandpa is over there.
Dad!
Dad.
[Medical Chart]
[Being unconscious for 717 days]
Are you done?
It's time to leave.
Are you still sleeping?
You answered me half an hour ago.
I didn't.
Did you stay up last night?
Do you remember what you are going to do today?
And what's going on?
Don't think I'll just let you go,
and won't ask you why.
Explain to me when you come back.
Why did you lock the door?
Grandpa says to bring more paper just in case.
Red and white?
Grab them all.
He's keeping us waiting.
Coming.
Okay.
Let's go.
You stayed up late again?
No.
This incident has caused public anxiety.
The board of Visa Airlines
hereby apologizes.
Who is she?
Could it be the victim's family?
Who is the boss?
This is the chairman.
Why did you hit him?
Mr. Zhang, be careful.
Did you get it?
Mr. Chen.
Mr. Chen, aren't you waiting for Mr. Zhang?
Mr. Zhang?
No need to introduce anyone.
Don't shoot me.
That's all for the press conference today.
Thank you.
Chairman.
Where are you going?
Your car is downstairs.
Say something, Chairman.
[Breaking news: 39 passengers died, 13 seriously injured from the bus crash.]
Here.
I'll play back a bit.
When I went to the hospital
to visit the victim and his family,
I found that the grandpa was unconscious
because the intracranial aneurysm ruptured.
Of course.
If it was the accident
that caused the trauma,
it would be easy and clear to define the responsibilities.
But what caused his unconsciousness first,
the accident or his illness itself,
the real reason means totally different results to our company.
Same with your company, right?
Actually, you could have asked for leave.
I took too many days off.
I need some income.
They are still denying it?
About your father-in-law's case?
They may feel embarrassed.
Okay.
By the way,
well,
I want to talk about the commission.
I'm still angry with the airlines.
Another time.
That's too much.
None of your business.
Grandpa is so much stronger than you are.
You can wake up.
He can too.
What about the calligraphy training center?
I forgot to tell you.
We moved.
We moved?
Is that something you can forget about?
Your daughter is getting married.
That's why you are taking the house back?
Yes.
I'm sorry for the last-minute request.
I remember you told me
that you didn't have any kids.
That's why you're buying houses everywhere
to plan
for your life when you are old.
Did I?
When did I tell you that?
1:30 p.m. on March 1st, 2014.
How could you remember it so accurately?
You asked me if I could pay
for half a year's rent,
because you needed the revenue stream.
And because it was my birthday that day,
I paid a lot for it.
So I remember it clearly.
Happy birthday.
Can you tell me the real reason?
Your son and your father-in-law
will not stay in the hospital forever, won't they?
If they were moved back...
You're worried that they may die in the house?
No landlord accepts this?
Or how about you buy one?
So you spent all the compensation?
Now we die if we want to
and we'll die in our own home.
No one would dare to badger us.
Excuse me.
Can you not say that word here?
Or you can lower your voice.
Sorry.
Please live a long life.
Besides, if grandpa
wants to continue teaching calligraphy,
there will be a place he can start anytime.
You're right.
You don't have to care about others anymore.
She's right.
Can I go outside now?
It's been almost two years.
It's hard to say if your situation will maintain stability or not.
Don't forget your crutches.
You really don't need your mother to accompany you?
Doctor.
Be brave.
You can do this.
Lend me 500 yuan.
700.
Okay.
Is this the right place?
Can you pull over here?
Okay.
It's okay. I'll stop the meter.
Take your time.
Pull over here. Thank you.
How much is this?
Okay.
Over there.
What do you think?
It's a little complicated.
It's either good
or bad.
What is so complicated?
It's too different from what I expected just now.
Don't ask for trouble.
Mum.
Someone's over there.
Who? Where?
There. That one.
The one next door.
It seems she's looking at me.
No one's there.
There she is.
Don't be silly.
Go inside.
You didn't see her?
No, I didn't.
Oh no.
You bought a house
where an old woman died next door and couldn't rest in peace.
And it cost you so much money.
Who couldn't rest in peace?
I'm sorry.
I was just kidding with my son.
Greet her.
How?
Granny Zeng Jiang.
She's our neighbor.
This is my son, Yiyong.
My son Yiyong.
Granny Zeng Jiang can't hear well.
Speak louder.
She can hear it through the wall just now.
Sometimes she can, sometimes she can't.
Greet her.
Hello, Granny Zeng Jiang.
I was just joking.
How can you say she couldn't rest in peace?
That's what everyone would think in that situation.
Isn't that normal?
[Welcome home]
What is this?
Impressed?
I learned it too.
What did you write it with?
With an ink brush, of course.
What else can I use?
It's used.
I washed it.
When grandpa comes back,
I'll write one for him too.
No.
He'll get poisoned.
Eat up.
It's very auspicious. Hurry up.
By the way,
I don't know
how to deal with your belongings,
so I didn't throw away anything.
I put them in the box
and brought them here.
Clean it up when you have time.
Oh.
How could you meddle with my room?
You didn't check my belongings, did you?
No, I didn't.
I kept my eyes closed.
I saw nothing.
Happy?
When will you go back to school?
No, I won't.
What do you mean?
Go back and finish high school.
It doesn't matter if I don't.
It's just a graduation certificate.
Do you think I just want you
to get your graduation certificate?
I don't want you
to lose any life experience because of that.
No.
I've had plans.
I have no plans at all.
But how could I go back
and hide in high school to be a student?
What if they won't pay
for grandpa's medical expenses？
Besides, mum has to pay for the mortgage
because she bought this damn house.
Plans?
[My life, my say. Live my life.]
[Planning Chart of School]
This form
can help you clarify
your life plans which you don't quite know yet.
Write down the true answers you've been thinking about.
Be honest.
In 10 minutes,
I'll teach you how to make your life road map.
based on this form.
Humph.
Did you say anything?
[Cao Guangyan]
Cao Guang...
Jian.
[Calligraphy classroom, Grandpa's items]
Please bless my grandpa to come back home to use you.
The owner is a man.
34 years old, called Zheng Lisong.
The bus crashed
and fell off the bridge.
I'm a cop.
I want to report a case.
I think I saw a dead person.
If you die,
and your body doesn't want to be seen,
why?
Mum.