[English subtitles are available]
Sir.
Don't do this, sir.
That kid is not the first.
I don't know which bastard built that road.
The drivers who made a turn there were like blind.
[Please slow down on the road prone to accidents]
[Six people have been killed and eleven injured in car accidents so far this month]
[Dangerous intersections. Watch out for blind area]
The victims are all children.
Sir, you can't do that.
You can't put it here. Turn off the engine.
-Sir -Wait.
Please protect the children walking on this road.
Be careful. Be safe.
Then they reorganized that shitty road.
I was supposed to be taken by those bastards,
dumped somewhere,
put in the asphalt and return to the road.
I didn't expect the seemingly incapable cop
to be a righteous man.
He thought of a way to keep me where I was.
You're actually a roadblock.
I will now start the investigation statement.
For the next question,
please try to think back carefully and answer in detail.
Is this your missing child?
Yes.
How old is the child?
Eight years old.
What's the child's sex?
Let's skip this first.
Do you know the circumstances under which the child disappeared?
When asphalting.
Don't do this. I was wrong.
I have to pay the mortgage.
Please, my mother would kill me.
Please continue.
It's like those bastards have a grudge against the land.
It was just paved.
And then they dug it again.
And then again.
Two days ago, they did it again.
They dug and paved.
And it was only half done.
That's when
I didn't keep an eye on my child and he disappeared.
I couldn't feel anything.
What couldn't you feel?
The smell of my child.
I didn't want to rely on you retarded people.
Excuse me.
No matter what,
I passed the written exam and the physical exam.
Retarded people
can't graduate and become police officers.
Can the police see the smell?
Generally speaking, we smell.
We can't see it through.
He
can see what ordinary people can't see,
something like you.
That's why I came to see you.
I've become more worried
now that I see you.
I thought you were fierce.
You look like this.
But it's different
when I see you in person.
Where did you get this?
I don't know who gave it to my child.
If you want to know, help me find my child.
Find out where he's hidden.
[Oh No! Here Comes Trouble]
[Episode 6]
[Yu Zhenyuan]
Forget it, Chief. I'll get it for you.
No need.
You just need to stay there.
Chief.
Sign for me.
When is the deadline?
The day before yesterday.
I'm sorry, I forgot.
Please, now. I'll get scolded.
It's good.
The girls in the General Affairs Department
can teach you a lesson for me.
This will save me time and effort.
Have you noticed
a piece of paper in your hands?
Yes.
Good, here are your stickers.
So today we are going to make
exclusive bubble stickers.
Are you happy about that?
Yes.
Give me that.
Find my child first.
I'm already doing it.
You're not.
I am.
You're sitting here staring at me,
and shamelessly asking me for something.
So you're not.
You've been a roadblock.
So there are many things you may not understand.
I can't just go to
the place where the police go.
Just shut up and wait here.
You're waiting anyway.
Just show me the paper.
You seem to make sense.
But I refuse.
Why?
Find my child first.
I'm already doing it.
You're not.
I am.
You are not.
-How is that possible?
-Tell me how that's possible. -Why not?
Dad, I'm back.
[Huxiaoli Office]
I think…
I think this guy is suspicious.
I've played it back for the second time.
You just said he was suspicious too.
Did I?
See?
There went my car next.
And then this guy
kept staring at my window and wouldn't let go.
And then...
It's the suspect.
Which suspect?
I told you not to come.
I don't want to wait at home.
I don't have a report card.
I'll be in trouble if it's found out.
I can't take it anymore.
Where is he?
Is he coming along?
I entrusted him to someone else.
Hello.
I heard from Pu Yiyong
that you're the patron saint of all our roads on earth.
How's it going?
Did you arrest him?
What exactly did he do to you?
Here.
Did you see anything?
You haven't signed the transfer form yet.
Give me a minute.
Why is the prisoner in the front seat?
Mr. Chief.
It's a shame you didn't become a cop.
I regret it too.
Is it too late?
Yes, it is.
[Utility Vehicle Monitor]
You found it.
Why did you lie to me?
I've told you before.
Don't feel sorry for others with your thoughts.
Just ask others to bring it in the future.
You don't have to
go back and forth.
Thank you, manager.
Then I'll go back to work.
You can ask Liu to run errands for you today.
He needs to be taught a lesson.
Just ask him to do it.
I appreciate it.
Don't worry.
I'm fine now.
Are you happy about that?
Yes.
Let me ask you a question.
Raise your hand if you like blue.
Me.
Raise your hand if you like yellow.
How about those who like red?
Me.
Manager.
Chief Yu.
Chief, please calm down.
I miss you so much.
He won't hurt him. Trust me.
He really won't hurt him.
Calm down, sir.
He's not Shang Wu.
Calm down, sir.!
I think you should take a year off.
Blue, red.
Promise me.
You must be fully prepared
before you watch it.
I promise.
You promise?
You swear?
I swear.
Are you sure the kid is missing?
I think he ran away from home.
You have such poor judgment.
I guess you'll be a quack too.
I don't think a patron saint
shouldn't at like this.
Who cares about you?
I'm only responsible for protecting children.
How old are you?
Would you please stop it?
Pu Yiyong…
I remembered that I saw your child
on my way back.
Really?
Where?
Across from the school.
Does he look like this?
He said it. Why is it my house that's being destroyed?
His house is next door.
Although it's rented,
you can break it down and make him homeless.
Isn't this better for all of us?
Let's go next door, okay?
Look what you've done.
Pu Yiyoung is broken.
This quack may be right.
He ran away from home.
The child is too young.
He couldn't move by himself.
But the abductor provided him with something.
So he grabbed it and left,
and was turned into a different person.
No wonder I couldn't find him.
What is it?
Bring me some water.
I'll do it.
This is the abductor.
This is the thing.
This is my child.
Oh, I see.
I don't know what the abductor
has taught my child.
It's been a while.
It is.
This is his daily route to and from work.
I'll have an almond tofu cactus.
What are you doing?
I think we've done our part.
He passes over your head every day.
You can just block him
and bring your child back home, that's all.
Do you want to order together?
I've been wanting to say it.
You order nothing and keep sitting in our seats.
Officer Chen, do you want the same?
Let me see.
Though humans may be stupid and slow,
I have to admit,
the power of the human heart is very strong.
As invincible as I am,
I'm made from the human heart.
Does the human heart refer to obsession?
Such as
longing, sorrows, and regrets.
I was right about you.
You are the smartest of all of you.
That guy held him with obsession.
If he won't let him go, my child can't come back.
You have to find a way to make that guy let go.
Shang Wu.
Are you bored at home alone?
Dad bought something I've been wanting for a long time.
Guess what's wrapped in here?
It's not just a pudding.
It's ice cream inside.
How about this?
We don't cut it up piece by piece
after dinner.
-We'll just scoop it up with a spoon and eat it. -I'll have three quarters
and you'll take a quarter.
How is that?
Why is it not good?
Right, I forgot.
I agreed to
use a spoon.
We'll see who has the bigger spoon.
Whoever holds the bigger spoon can eat more.
What does that mean?
Their lunch is on us.
That'll give you a favor.
No need.
Guys, your lunch is on me and one-per.
I'll give it out.
I'll do it.
How could this happen?
I said one-per should join our group.
When?
When you were not here.
Everyone, come and get it.
One-per.
And me.
Zhao Wan.
One-per.
One…
It's from my friend's father's store.
It's extra-large.
This is lunch.
There are red beans in it.
There is a cold snap today.
Should we close the window?
I want to order hot noodles in soup.
Does anyone want to join me?
Don't order.
Let's go eat hot pot.
Let's go.
You're not going?
Don't you need to see me?
What if a child
was abducted by a stranger
and wouldn't leave
even if his parents found him,
so the parents couldn't force the child to leave
unless the stranger was willing to return him?
You're talking about that movie, right?
Which one?
The one where you cried so hard that you choked and coughed,
making people stare at you?
I didn't cry.
Did you get a kidnapping case?
If so, you should hand it over.
No kidnapping cases.
I'm just curious.
Do you have any way
to make the stranger
willing to
let the child go?
We abide by the law.
That is, to punish him by law.
Do you want to hypnotize him?
Otherwise, why do you wear the uniform?
Punish him by law.
Wait a minute.
This is not your job description.
I think most of your duties are
about traffic.
That's right.
It's traffic related.
I have to go.
Eat it while it's hot.
One-per.
I'm warning you.
Don't hide the case just to get credit.
The pharmacist and the unidentified body are serious.
It's not like the kidnapping case.
Don't mess around.
I swear, senior.
There's no such thing as human kidnapping.
Okay, I'll go by myself. Don't see me off.
Go back and eat.
It's not good if it gets cold.
There's no human kidnapping case?
Then if I beat him up,
will he
be willing to let the kid go?
No.
Then scare him.
Make him feel scared.
He'll be willing too, right?
No.
It seems I can do nothing to him then.
Let me tell you.
I didn't graduate from high school.
And I'm not an expert negotiator.
I can't make him willing to
give you back your child.
You may look like an imbecile.
But your smell and the shredded paper
are very much alike.
You have to have faith.
Don't always think of yourself as an idiot.
I don't think I ever said that.
I thought the guy passed here at this time every day.
Are you hungry?
Come on.
Where are you going?
To kill Pu Yiyong.
Hello, Grandma Zeng Jiang.
He wasn't like this before.
At least not before we moved here.
That's why I said we have good feng shui here.
This is the Shangcheng Police Station.
Yes.
And the address is?
I see.
Chief, I'm going out on duty.
With whom?
With myself.
You're unbelievable.
Do you take me as a delivery boy?
None of my business.
I ordered it.
What did you get?
Burgers and coffee.
Burgers are easier to eat.
Coffee is for your potential staying up.
And you should be very tired after staying here all day.
They look familiar.
I didn't buy your share.
It's okay, I've already eaten.
Some people have reported
suspicious men
loitering here for several days.
You're suspected of being burglars.
Some people also report that you may be here to take pictures.
So please
come back to the bureau with us.
Did you take pictures?
I…
I didn't.
Ask him if you don't believe me.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I told you not to do stupid things.
I will persuade Pu Yiyong to change.
We'll save some effort
if we have more people like you in society.
Thank you, Fang.
Can I go to that table now?
One-per.
Yes.
How's it going?
No problem.
Come on, please.
Yes, thank you.
Why don't you check his phone?
He's your friend?
I'm sorry.
I'll talk to him again.
Is his kid dead?
I was just taking a chance
to see if he had any criminal record.
He had no criminal record.
But a year ago there was a report of a crime.
Yu Zhenyuan's child
died in an accidental fall.
Even if that's the case,
he can't just take away other people's child.
Theoretically.
Can we call it “a child”?
Do you have to take it back?
I'm sorry.
So what do we do now?
Punish him by law.
This is all I can do.
This is what my uniform is for.
I'm going to do the horribly boring patrol check-in.
And I'll be kind enough to take you back.
Go over there and distract her or stall for a while.
What do you want?
Are you aware
that you sound like a criminal already?
Come on.
What are you doing?
It's airier this way.
How do you want me to drive
if you don't close the door?
You can't drive if I close the door
because of the carbon dioxide.
I study medicine.
Believe me.
I noticed that the cop's computer was still on.
Go and memorize Yu Zhenyuan's address.
Are you ordering me around?
I'm sorry, please.
Watch out for your head.
-Sir, please sit down. -Thank you.
When I took the special exam,
I filled my Question 2 answer sheet with Question 1's answer,
and Question 3 answer sheet with Question 2's answer,
-and Question 4 answer sheet… -With Question 3's answer.
What do you want to say?
With Question 5's answer.
Did you have an eye problem?
Shut up.
What I mean is
sometimes we just miss the test.
Don't blame yourself so much.
You'll get so stressed out that you'll go crazy.
Am I right?
I didn't.
Did I ask you?
Am I right, Guangyan?
I didn't either.
He did.
Lane 37, Sec. 2, Wanji Road, Taipei City.
[Inquiry record]
Lane 37, Sec. 2, Wanji Road,
Seventh Floor, No.4-1, Lane 37.
You've been promoted.
I thought you were incapable.
Please.
No. 1, Lane 37, Lane 4, Wanan Street, Taipei City.
Wanan Street?
May I ask what you want from
Chief Yu, please?
I made it very clear yesterday.
It was a misunderstanding on our part.
And we've canceled the report.
Report?
What happened yesterday that you want to report?
It's okay.
I can check it out when I go back to the bureau.
Maybe you can't just cancel it.
unilaterally.
Are you really going to be a criminal?
You made me count wrong again.
And you're a low-IQ criminal.
Forget it.
Sidewalk Kid!
What are you doing?
What are you afraid of?
The guy's at work and he's not home.
Did he quit?
I haven't agreed yet.
He's on leave without pay.
I'm thinking about
how to explain it to the leaders.
The chief said
he worked in a factory.
Every year, he received so many off-campus teachings.
But Shang Wu
never had the chance to visit it.
This is our tour line.
I shouldn't have let him see those kids.
Actually, it took less than 30 minutes.
The guards noticed something strange later.
He called the police and also contacted me.
I told the police that it was a misunderstanding.
Nothing was stolen or damaged.
Then it was not a public charge.
Since the people involved were not pursuing the case,
they left.
Officer Chen.
I hope that's enough.
Chief Yu,
experienced an accident at home one year ago.
I know this.
I can understand…
No way.
You can't understand
what the parents feel like
when something happens to their children.
No one can understand.
Other people can just try to imagine.
Empathy is just
the magnification of sympathy.
I've told you before.
Don't feel sorry for others with your thoughts.
An acquaintance of mine
said something similar to you.
It seems we don't need to get involved.
Say it again.
What's that green sidewalk called?
Marked crosswalk.
Please stop shouting.
Marked crosswalk. Your father is looking for you!
Why is he home?
With your thinking logic,
You're going to sneak up there now, aren't you?
You must have brought tools to break into their house too.
If I get caught,
I'll confess that you forced me to do this.
Let's go now.
Why?
Aren't we going?
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
You can't get me.
The kid is next to him, right?
What does he look like?
Draw it and let me see.
I'll grind some ink when the light turns red.
The light is about to turn red.
Catch the one behind.
Is there a blue one?
Okay, go down.
You got it.
Good for Shang Wu.
Look.
Do you like it?
Here you go.
Let's go to the machine.
I hate this place. It's a waste of time
and money.
I can't believe I can't get it.
Why are you taking my money?
It won't work.
This is a scam.
Thank you.
This is for 200 yuan.
What can I get you?
I'm not hungry.
You can order it.
The minimum charge is one drink, sir.
I have this.
Thank you.
What kind of fruits are in
fruit yogurt salad?
Please enjoy the children's meal.
Thank you.
Gentleman,
your Paris Express has arrived.
Please enjoy it.
You can order it too.
I'm not hungry.
Four full tickets?
Yes.
Here. Four full tickets here.
Thank you.
Hello, one adult and one child.
Okay.
Let's get the tickets.
To go to this place with you?
What's wrong with that?
Hurry up, I don't have my wallet.
I hate these places that waste time.
But we all received off-campus teachings in elementary school.
I always took time off.
What's the value of teaching here?
Let me check your ticket.
One full ticket, one ticket.
Are there any children here?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Do you have any stickers
for children?
Yes.
Here, help me choose one.
Which one do you like?
This one is good. Thank you.
Let's go.
Sir.
You can have both of them.
Thank you.
Please come in.
We came together.
Okay, you can go in now.
Do you have a sticker?
No, it's just for kids.
But I just bought the ticket.
-I can't go against the company rules. -Are you going or not?
Please come in.
I've got the ticket. I should have been able to take it.
Why do you need those stickers?
I bought the tickets.
Shut up.
Come on.
I still don't understand
what's so fun about the wiggly thing.
It's so much fun!
It's not fun. It's a waste of time.
Turn back.
Where is he?
Over there.
Turn back.
Excuse me.
Did you see the Ferris wheel?
The Ferris wheel.
Here we are.
The river we just passed
is right there.
We've ridden bikes there before.
Give me back my phone.
I have to delete them.
Have you seen Yu Zhenyuan?
Why is that cup faster than us?
You want it to be faster, don't you?
Faster!
I thought you wanted it to be faster.
No way.
Did you forget?
You used to throw up on
this coffee cup.
Do you want to throw up again?
Thank you.
Don't worry, I'll get it for you.
Go on.
Let's go find a seat.
Hello. What can I get you?
I've just thrown up and had no appetite.
Then you don't have to buy anything.
I'll have vanilla.
Chocolate.
Or mango?
Or grilled squid?
Two iced coffees.
Okay.
Look at all the food on your hands.
This one too.
Come on, I'll wipe it for you.
Can you draw now?
Where did you get this?
I bought it at the gift store.
You went to the gift store?
Just draw it.
Wipe your mouth here.
Here.
No.
Why?
Don't you always draw for us?
The child is a fake.
There's no point in drawing him.
You're back.
Yiyong.
Last time you asked me
if I might have written a book with your father.
I asked my former colleagues.
I did.
This is the book.
What book?
This one.
“The way to open a successful business even at the age of five”.
Why did you come back together?
Did you meet after class?
We didn't go to class.
We went to the amusement park.
With Yiyong?
I'm going to take a shower first.
Good.
I can't believe Guangyan skipped school
and went to the amusement park with Yiyong.
You've grown up.
Thank you.
Cheers.
I heard from Guangyan's father
that he skipped school
and went to the amusement park with you today.
It's not good to skip school, right?
That's great.
-Even if it's someone else's son, how can you... -No, no.
I didn't say that.
His father did.
He said he was relieved.
Because Guangyan has never seemed to lose control or make mistakes like this
since he was a child.
So he should thank you.
What's wrong with him?
He's strange
like my father.
What are you doing?
Are you going to throw up after a little drink?
If you want to throw up, go to the toilet.
Don't throw up here.
I finally know why
I've been so upset lately.
I thought it was because Cao Guangyan was bothering me too much.
Dad is so tired.
I can't walk anymore.
Why don't you carry me?
Or you can be my crutch like before.
Are you happy?
You can press the code today,
like playing video games.
Didn't you always argue to press the code?
You said it was the past.
Return the child.
Get in.
Don't come any closer, I'll call the police.
See what the kid looks like.
Yu Jinyuan.
If I died
and my dad found someone to replace me,
I'd be super upset.
Open the door!
Return the child!
The fever's gone.
I've taken
Shang Wu home.
Wait a minute.
Shang Wu, mommy wants to talk to you on the phone.
Shang Wu.
Although you've already taken a bath,
do you want to go to your favorite place
you used to go?
I used to take you to the department store,
to the amusement park,
to ride a bicycle
and play games.
At the end of the day, you'd always say
you wanted to come here.
You thought it was the most fun.
Your mom and I were angry
because we thought we could have saved
all the money
with which we took you to those places.
Shang Wu.
You're eight years old too, right?
Thank you.
Thank you for going to so many places with me
and eating so much food.
It made me feel like
I was spending more time
with Shang Wu.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were Shang Wu.
That young man was right.
I should let you go.
If only Shang Wu
wasn't a fragile flesh and blood body like you're.
Let's go.
Please do one thing for me.
What did you see?
[Next Episode Preview]
It's like a dream, but it's not.
You and Yiyong are becoming more and more alike.
I'll plan your career.
Did you do this to me?
I can't forgive myself.
Do you want to be like him?
Or will you choose differently?
I won't let him go.