I've finished
all overseas business.
But the money left by my brother
overseas
can only be used by the company
after a new heir
is selected.
I'm back
to urge the board of directors
to select a new chairman as soon as possible.
Let my brother
be the chairman.
The position is originally his.
Chengjing,
your mother has a lot of shares
in the group.
She probably won't agree with your decision.
Uncle,
I'll talk to her
when she comes back.
Who is it?
Mr. Gu.
I need you
to do me a favor.
I haven't changed the sheets and duvet covers for half a month.
Could you go and change them for me?
Okay.
Let's go.
Mr. Gu, I've finished.
Young Master Yan, you're still up this late?
What were you doing?
I just went to
change the sheets for Mr. Gu.
Young Master Yan,
do you need anything?
Do you also need to change the sheets?
Close the door.
Then go to bed early.
As for the heir,
I don't have any opinion.
Chengyan is doing well in the company.
The acquisition of Su's Art Gallery
was very well done.
And Chengjing,
although you are new to the company,
you are young and promising,
with a bright future.
We are all family.
No matter who takes over the company,
you must continue to run
the business left by your father.
That's the most important thing.
All right.
Let's eat.
Xiaoxue.
Pour me a glass of red wine too.
Okay.
Uncle.
I'm not feeling well today.
Xiaoxue needs to take care of me.
Excuse me.
Uncle.
Xiaoxue is the personal care I found for Chengyan.
If you don't want the servant to do it,
I can find one for you.
No need.
Young Master Yan,
you don't have to be mad at them.
Mr. Gu asked me to do it,
so it's my duty.
You're my personal care.
How can you take care of others?
Xiaoxue,
stop massaging.
I have a question for you.
What's that?
It's a birthmark.
Because it looks like a snowflake,
my mom named me Xiaoxue.
What about your mom?
My mom died long ago.
I grew up in an orphanage.
Sorry.
Pour me another glass of wine.
It's empty, Young Master Yan.
Should I get you another bottle?
No need.
I'll go pick one from the cellar later.
Okay.
Look into
Ji Xiaoxue's background.
I need all the information.
Make it quick.
Do you always come here?
I've been running around
for the Su Group acquisition,
I've been visiting art galleries across the country,
looking for a way to deal with it.
Of course,
I also really enjoy art.
I often came here after returning.
But I think there are issues with these galleries.
Not only are the exhibits incomplete,
but the design is also problematic.
Look,
this gravel path.
Some ladies are wearing high heels.
Isn't that just...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It doesn't hurt.
It's okay, let me.
When drinking red wine,
you should first smell it,
to smell its fruity aroma,
and then taste it,
to taste its lingering sweetness.
Have a try.
How is it?
I'm a bit dizzy.
This time, just smell it, don't drink it.
How is it?
This is the taste of wine?
You're not smelling it right.
It has a strong fruity aroma.
Let me smell it again.
Chengjing,
you haven't tried this wine yet.
I bring it here for you.
Okay.
Why is it gone?
Did your brother take it away?
Why don't you call Chengyan?
Young Master Yan, he's calling you.
What should I do?
I don't have my phone.
He didn't answer.
Okay.
Let's see if there's any inside.
Chengjing,
this bottle of liquor is also very good.
Take a look.
Let's drink this one.
That's fine.
Let's go.
Go.