Time: 8:30-11:00
Day
Hello.
Who are you looking for?
Teacher Zhao.
Teacher Zhao has stepped out,
please wait over there.
Hello.
I have an appointment with Teacher Zhao.
Teacher Zhao is busy today,
would you mind waiting in the office?
The third mock exam is about to begin,
all students please
return to the examination room immediately.
Alright,
start working on your papers.
Everyone, please keep track of the time.
You have 30 minutes left.
Teacher,
I'd like to turn in my paper.
Are you sure?
According to the exam rules,
we can turn in our papers early.
Where were you earlier?
This third mock exam was way too difficult.
I don't think I performed well at all.
The college entrance exam definitely won't be this hard.
Really?
I hope so.
What about you?
How do you think you did?
Not bad.
So modest.
Did you notice?
The class monitor turned in his paper half an hour early.
Could he have finished everything?
I saw that.
But he's always been a good student.
But I really think he's been
acting strange lately.
He's barely attending evening study sessions anymore.
Don't worry about that.
We just need to focus on our own exams.
I'm hungry.
Let me treat you to a meal.
Really?
Look at this,
83rd place.
I improved by over 80 places.
I need to call my sister later.
That's a huge improvement!
It's alright.
You must be cheating.
No,
I guess I've been
putting in a bit more effort lately.
So you actually studied?
You better do well on the college entrance exam,
or I'll lose face.
My abilities speak for themselves.
Unlike some people,
who aren't very good
and should talk less
and practice more,
right?
Are you talking about me?
I don't know.
Say that again.
Stop fighting.
Congratulations,
you actually scored higher than me this time.
Just luck.
It really was luck.
I didn't perform well this time,
I'll definitely score higher than you on the college entrance exam.
Good luck with that.
Did you see?
Shuo has improved
by so many places this time.
But the class monitor
is only ranked 57th with 40 points.
He used to be in the top five of our grade,
and he turned in his exam half an hour early this time.
It's so strange.
Maybe it's
too much pressure.
Perhaps.
If I had known, I would have asked Old Jiang
to leak some questions,
tell me what's on the college entrance exam.
This time...
Who's daydreaming in broad daylight?
If I told you the questions, they'd just change them.
Well...
I could ask him for multiple sets
wouldn't that work?
Just in case.
If I could score almost
perfect on the exam...
Gu Ming,
your performance on
this test was unusually poor.
You should know that
the school is counting on you to win rankings.
During my recent proctoring,
I noticed you've been turning in your papers early.
Can you tell me
what's going on?
Teacher Liu...
Turning in early
is to put pressure on myself.
It also helps me
tackle more difficult questions.
But this third mock exam
is basically simulating the college entrance exam,
so why are you doing this?
This is my strategy.
Teacher, trust me,
I won't do anything reckless.
I hope so.
Zhizhi,
Zhenzhen, come quickly.
Gu Ming,
don't think your teacher is nagging.
You're the most outstanding
student in our class.
I really don't want
you to let me down at this critical time.
But with your current situation,
I'm really worried.
Gu Ming, can you hear me?
Can you hear what I'm saying?
Teacher Liu,
don't worry,
I'll definitely work hard for the college entrance exam.
On the highest clock tower in this city,
that night,
she left me forever.
White feathers flying past,
clocks turning backward,
the final scene in my memory.
But the future is no different from the past.
Perhaps tomorrow,
she will walk back from the light,
only to leave again.
I need to find that ancient key
to unlock the door of memories.
There are billions of clocks there,
functioning like perpetual machines,
turning backward endlessly.
I want to make all the clocks stop.
This way she
will never be taken away by time.
I'm not fully awake.
Writing has
really made me
confused.
This isn't my home, is it?
Is this my room?
This is completely wrong.
No.
Impossible.
It can't be.
Xing.
I'm sorry,
I just woke up
and overslept,
sorry.
I'll
come right over to deliver it.
Who are you?
It's me,
Jiang Ling.
Which Jiang Ling?
I don't know you.
This is a financial company.
Are you looking for a loan?
Need a loan? I can tell you about our services.
We offer
small loans, non-quota loans, medium-sized loans, and more...
Are you listening?
Did I write this book?
It's mine.
No.
Where have they brought me?
This isn't me.
Not me.
James Joyce.
Time has reversed.
You're still alive,
aren't you?
Otherwise you couldn't have written to me.
My phone.
Where's
my phone?
I remember now.
Zhenzhen, I remember now.
I remember.
We wrote this.
An Zhenzhen.
I remember you now.
Where are you?
Where's my phone?
So where's my phone?
I'll call myself.
Hello.
The number you have dialed is not in service,
please check and try again.
please check the number.
Hello.
Who are you looking for?
Is the owner home?
The owner hasn't been home lately.
Where did they go?
I think they went abroad.
Abroad?
When will they be back?
I don't know.
Thank you.
Hello,
the number you've dialed.
The number you're trying to reach is currently unavailable,
please try again later.
Hello.
I'd like to ask
if you've seen Qiu Qian?
Qiu Qian?
Don't know her.
Would you like something to drink?
What?
I just wanted to ask
how your novel manuscript
is coming along?
I'm stuck,
no inspiration,
can't write anything.
Wonder what's up with our class monitor lately,
always missing evening study sessions,
it's really strange.
Maybe
our discussion today
could give you some fresh inspiration.
How would that help?
I remember I gave the class monitor a book
that might have it written inside.
I'm sorry,
excuse me.
He's finished filling this out
but it's been crossed out.
Registration.
Hello.
Thank you.
You're here.
Teacher Liu.
Yes.
Come in.
A friend brought me a box of mate tea from Argentina.
Try some.
I came here
in such a hurry because...
I knew you would come back to see me,
but I didn't expect it to be so soon.
It is a bit sudden, I...
Mainly because...
You haven't been sleeping well lately, have you?
I haven't been sleeping well
lately,
I keep having dreams.
Are you dreaming about An Zhenzhen?
Yes,
how did you know?
Have some tea first.
Professor Liu,
I don't know what's
happening to me lately.
When I think about An Zhenzhen,
I feel completely
confused.
I know she's dead,
but
I feel like
all my memories of her
have suddenly been awakened,
yet they don't exist anymore.
I've tried asking
people who knew she existed,
people who knew her,
I've tried to find them
but they're nowhere to be found.
There have been
too many strange things happening lately.
And
I feel like An Zhenzhen
isn't dead,
that she's still alive.
Your feelings are correct.
But she's already dead.
Have you ever considered
that all of this is related to you?
I don't know.
I'm not just talking about An Zhenzhen,
but everything around her.
And of course,
her life and death in your world.
If you put it that way,
I'm
even more confused.
The tea is getting cold.
Are you sure you don't want a sip?
Professor Liu,
I just want you to tell me
everything
you know.
Perhaps when you've done what you need to do,
she will appear.
What should I do?
What you promised.
Why is
the protagonist always alone?
You could give her
a complete family.
The framework of this novel
has already been
established by me.
So for each character's
family background and personality,
everything is built around this framework.
Can't you write a comedy instead?
Comedies are good too.
In literature.
Most comedies
are a mixture of laughter and tears.
Indeed,
in this world,
how could everything be perfect?
I've grown up.
I always thought
everything in this world was wonderful.
My life,
I thought it was perfect.
Now I realize
it's far from perfect.
All beings suffer,
only we can save ourselves.
What does that mean?
For us,
perhaps our entire life
is meant to experience hardships.
Only after experiencing pain
can we truly understand
what real happiness is.
Happiness
exists relative to suffering,
not from external influences.
Only your own heart
can affect your judgment.
Alright.
I need to head back early today.
My aunt's store just got new inventory,
I need to go help out,
I'll head out first.
Jiangling!
Thank you.
Daughter.
At home,
your mom doesn't let you drink this,
but dad will buy it for you.
Thank you, Dad.
Cheers.
Taro milk tea.
It's delicious.
Really tasty.
I have more good news for you.
Didn't you want to visit the aquarium?
Dad already bought the tickets.
We'll go together this weekend.
But
if it's on the weekend,
doesn't Mom have a meeting?
Well.
I'll talk to her about it.
She can take time off.
She should be able to make it.
This is really good.
You and Mom
are actually divorced, right?
So you know.
I was planning
to tell you after your exams.
Aren't you tired of pretending?
You could have told me, you know.
I'm grown up now.
I can handle it.
I think...
Is this too harsh for you?
During this time,
I've really learned a lot.
I'm starting to understand
that the world
isn't
as perfect as I imagined.
So wonderful.
It's cruel
and realistic,
but I accept it.
After all,
all beings suffer.
One must save oneself, right?
Is what you're saying
from a book?
During this time,
I've been
trying to reconcile with your mom.
I want to give you back a complete family.
Mom won't agree to that.
My wish has always been
for our family
to stay together forever.
To live happily
ever after.
But
now my wish is
that I hope
you and Mom
can both find your own happiness.
That would make me happy too.
Just give me a little more time.
After all,
Dad has made
a lot of mistakes lately.
I need to make amends.
I've realized
you don't understand Mom at all.
She
has never been content
with just being a housewife.
She has her own dreams
and her own career.
She looks incredibly
cool when she's working.
So
she won't agree.
Well, I still have to try.
Good luck then.
Let's go home.
How about pork ribs for dinner tonight?
Sounds good.
Auntie.
What's wrong?
Come on, let me help you rest for a while.
Let's go.
I'm fine.
By the way,
how did you do on your third mock exam?
You haven't told me about it.
It's over.
Not bad.
I improved by over 20 points.
What?
Take it easy.
Over 20 points?
Why didn't you tell me?
I bet
half the credit for your score
belongs to An Zhenzhen.
At least she didn't hold me back,
that's good enough.
I've noticed
she's been coming over to tutor you quite often.
I really like that girl.
She's so lively and cheerful,
unlike you.
I'm the one tutoring her, actually.
That's enough,
stop working now.
I'll take you to the hospital tomorrow
to get some medicine.
Careful.
I told you not to do heavy work
but you insisted.
Come on, take it slow.
Make yourself comfortable, Auntie.
I'll leave this here,
I'm going to pay the bill first,
wait for me.
Hello, I'm here to make a payment.
How much is it?
18,000 in total.
Please take this.