Time: 8:30
Day
That's strange,
I've never seen these photos before.
Where did they come from?
Coming.
Thanks.
Please come in.
Have a seat.
And you are?
I'm
from class of 2012,
Jiang Ling.
I transferred here during the last semester.
I remember you.
After all these years,
you still remember me, Teacher Liu.
I remember
every single one of my students.
I was
passing by the school today
and thought I'd stop by.
Thank you.
I've taught so many students,
but very few come back to visit me
like you do.
Every time I finish with a class,
it feels like one chapter of life ends
and another begins.
Perhaps as teachers,
we don't expect
all our students to remember us,
we just hope they grow up happy.
I'm really happy for you,
I should now call you
Principal Liu.
We don't have as many students now,
so we don't need as many homeroom teachers.
I just thought
I could still contribute something,
so I took on some administrative work.
By the way,
what are you doing now?
I guess
I'm just experiencing life.
I always thought
you were quite a special kid.
I also wanted
to ask about
what happened back then.
What is it?
Do you remember
a female classmate in our class named
An Zhenzhen?
An Zhenzhen.
I remember her.
It's been twelve years.
Time really flies.
Yes.
Ms. Liu.
Her story
can't be explained in just a few words.
I understand.
Today I
just wanted to learn a bit more.
Leave me your number,
I'll contact you later.
Well, I'm
going to leave now,
I'll leave this here.
Goodbye.
This time we'll talk about
the stars falling
in the autumn wind
at Wuzhang Plains.
Auntie
is back.
Zhenzhen is here,
Auntie.
You two go have a seat.
I've brought you all something to eat.
Thank you, auntie.
I'm starving!
Just wait a bit.
Thank you, auntie.
Eat while it's hot.
Let me take this lid.
Thank you, auntie.
Be careful, it's hot.
Try some.
Then I won't hold back.
How is it?
This is incredibly delicious!
This is...
Do you know how much preparation
goes into making this dish?
What? You're an expert on this too?
You can cook as well?
I know a thing or two.
Keep eating,
I'll go find my aunt.
Just a thing or two...
Here it is.
Hot!
I'll get a bowl.
Try it.
Then I won't hold back.
How is it?
Not bad at all.
It's so delicious!
I didn't know you had this skill.
When did you learn it?
When the store gets busy,
I help my aunt with small tasks,
and after a while,
I picked it up.
Actually, cooking is like
writing novels -
they're similar.
You need to learn
to control the heat and timing,
and you need patience too.
That's so you -
even when cooking
you sound so literary.
But
it's really good though.
If you like it, have some more.
Don't worry,
I'll definitely finish it all,
won't let your hard work go to waste.
Have you been reading any interesting novels lately?
You could share them with me.
The novel
In Search of Lost Time.
What's it about?
What's it specifically about?
It can be summarized as
time,
memory,
and love.
That's as good as saying nothing at all.
Well, I haven't finished reading it yet,
I'll tell you when I'm done.
Is this writer famous?
Proust
was quite famous back then.
But by
today's standards,
he would be considered
a complete failure.
Why?
Throughout his life,
he devoted all
his time to writing novels.
Publishers frequently
rejected his work,
and he often had to self-publish.
This book
is considered
his masterpiece,
as well as his final work.
How sad.
Then you must never become such a person.
I'm still
many years away from being that kind of writer.
Actually, I really want to become that kind of writer.
Don't worry,
you have me.
In the future,
I'll definitely
promote your masterpiece well
and make you
both famous and rich.
Really?
Don't underestimate me.
My dad is so successful in business,
which proves that I
must have inherited
some business talent.
I envy you
for having a father like that.
Unlike me,
I've barely seen my father.
What's there to envy?
You saw it last time,
he and my mom have been putting on an act for me.
You mean because...
let's not talk about this.
As for matters between parents,
we have no say in them.
The main issue
isn't really about you.
Actually,
my only wish
has always been
for them to stay together forever.
Just like before,
happy and content.
Do you have any other wishes?
If I tell you, will you make it come true?
Within my capabilities,
I'll try my best.
Then I'll make my wish now.
I wish
all my good friends
would come back to me.
I hope our Three Bouncy group
will never break up.
But
I said such nasty things to them,
they probably won't forgive me anymore.
Your friendship
has been developing
for several years now,
it's quite strong
and not so fragile.
Have something delicious
to cheer yourself up.
Then I'll eat more.
I'll finish all of this.
Delicious.
There's meat underneath?
Of course there is.
Did you stew this?
I stir-fried it.
It's quite tidy here today.
Remembrance of Things Past.
Recently,
I've been
thinking about something.
But I've made up my mind,
I'm going to stick with it.
I'm going to finish my novel.
It might
take a few years,
or even a decade or more.
A decade?
That's way too long.
How about this.
You could teach me,
and once I learn, we can write together.
It would be faster.
That book you're holding
took 17 years to write.
17 years?
Yes, that's too long indeed.
We will.
Because of a smile,
a glance,
or a bare shoulder,
we fall in love.
These subtle moments
are quite enough.
And then.
During my long periods of hope
or melancholy,
we begin to weave a person.
Imagining
a character.
That's beautifully written.
The time we have
each day.
It's like a
flexible band.
Stretched out, it seems endless.
And we
make this time
past.
suddenly contract.
years.
Ordinary habits
fill the remaining gaps.
We ultimately cannot
change things as we wish.
As time passes,
our desires
quietly change.
It seems
the time spent.
You can still tell from
the writing style.
This is literature,
it requires
long-term accumulation
and refinement.
Seeing how familiar you are
with all this,
you must have read these volumes
many, many times, right?
Not really,
most of the time
I have to study too.
I just can't
sit quietly and read properly.
Going to sleep,
good night.
What is cell apoptosis?
What does cell apoptosis mean?
Is it when the cell,
That's the concept.
like, dies or something?
I think it starts from the nucleus.
Most of the water in cells
exists in a free form
Free form.
and can flow freely.
It's called bound water
and cell fluid.
Bound water.
Right?
What water?
What?
Next one.
Most inorganic salts in cells.
I'm leaving first.
Go ahead.
If only he were mute.
What do you mean?
I bet you won't make it next year either.
Stop.
I think...
There's no time like the present,
let's leave right now.
How about it?
Let's go now.
Let's go.
Why don't we each share our wishes?
Sure.
Wishes don't come true if you tell them.
What kind of shameful wish do you have?
I bet yours is the truly shameful one.
How about this,
I'll go first.
My wish is...
I hope
the Maya prophecy fails
and 2012 isn't the end of the world.
All living creatures
can
thrive and multiply.
World peace.
Qianqian.
Where are you going?
No entry.
Sister.
Where are you going?
I can't get through here.
Don't touch me.
Where are you going?
If I remember correctly,
don't we have some unfinished business?
Qianqian.
I'll pay you back.
I almost forgot about that.
But don't worry,
as long as you're with me,
money doesn't matter.
Let's go.
Let me go!
Move it!
What are you doing?
Let me go!
Let go!
Who's there?
Take it easy, please.
Get in the car.
Hurry up and get in.
It's good that you tried to help,
but if you go too far,
you could be breaking the law.
Alright,
young man,
next time just call the police if something happens,
understand?
Yes, I understand.
At your age,
you might not know your own limits,
and if you seriously hurt someone,
you could be committing a crime yourself.
If you encounter this kind of situation again,
please call the police first, okay?
Okay.
It's all over now.
It's all over.
It's fine.
Qiuqiu.
Hey.
Are you asleep?
Not yet.
Zhenzhen.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Thank you for helping me today.
What are you talking about?
Aren't you my princess?
As your knight,
I must protect you.
Right?
I'm really sorry too.
Qiuqiu,
about our fight before,
I said some terrible things to you.
I don't know
if you hate me now.
Of course not,
silly.
How could I ever hate you?
Actually,
I've been wanting to tell you
that we should make up.
I don't even like Jiang Ling.
It's just that when he appeared,
I was afraid of losing you,
losing my best friend.
You'll never lose me.
You forgot.
You forgot about me.
The three of us made a promise.
No matter which one of us
makes a big mistake,
as long as someone speaks up first,
we must forgive each other unconditionally.
Do you remember?
I remember.
So let's never fight again,
okay?
I won't
lose my temper with you anymore.
I used to
take out my bad mood on you all the time.
It's okay, Qiuqiu,
I understand you.
I know that's not what you really meant,
you were just scared.
Actually,
I can feel that
your emotions
are because you care.
Maybe I
didn't give you
enough security.
I've been
neglecting you lately,
so you got scared.
I understand you,
how could I be angry with you?
During this time,
when you weren't by my side,
I really
missed you.
Qiuqiu,
whether you believe it or not,
I want to tell you.
Lately I've
suddenly realized something.
Life actually
gives us more than just one chance.
Heaven
has given me a second chance.
I must seize this opportunity.
I will live my life well.
And cherish everyone around me.
We all need to live our lives well.
Qiuqiu.
Trust me.
I'm here for you.
Your future will definitely
be wonderful.
I believe it.
We all will.
Our future will be bright.
Yes.
Our future
will be absolutely wonderful.