I've come to realize...
I'm living in the world of manga.
But it's not just an ordinary manga.
I'm in a "Boys Love" manga.
Maybe you should work out a little bit?
However...
I'm a guy that doesn't want to love boys, at all.
I'm just a side character.
I've avoided all the traps.
However...
Hey.
Kikuchi...
really has a cute smile.
Sorry for making you wait!
What did you want to talk about?
It's okay. I won't give in to this...
Boys Love world!
Well...
What's wrong?
I'll never give in!
Never!
I...
What is it?
I can't...
I can't!
I can't say it!
No!
I like you!
Hey! What am I saying?
But...
I guess it's fine.
Yeah, it's fine.
I'm graduating from side-character status today.
I'm going to live with the main character of this world!
And who is that?
Isn't it obvious?
That's right.
- The man standing in front of me—
- Kikuchi!
Igarashi?
What? Roses?
And those are white roses that symbolize chastity, at that?!
I...
finally realized when you left me.
You're the only one for me!
What?
I can't have anyone but you.
What?!
This proves it!
Even when I try to open the biggest chapter of my life,
my side-character status is impenetrable!
I'm the king of all side characters!
I'll never give in!
I'm the only one...
who will never yield to this world!
And so, in this world of Boys Love,
I'm a guy who does not want to love boys.
I'm a side character.
And my relentless, daily battle of defiance
begins once again!
[A Man Who Defies The World of BL Season 2]
♫ I'm a side character ♫
♫ We're in this world of Boys Love again today  ♫
♫ That's right ♫
♫ Just a side character... ♫
♫ Never to be the main character! ♫
♫ Hiro, Miki, Minami ♫
♫ Natsuki and Nanase ♫
♫ It's always Boys Love! ♫
♫ Steer clear of the main character ♫
♫ Don't trip any story traps ♫
♫ Don't do it! (Boys Love) ♫
♫ I'm a side character ♫
♫ But sometimes... ♫
♫ I wouldn't mind some company ♫
♫ I'm just a side character ♫
♫ And I might accidentally... ♫
♫ Lower my guard! ♫
♫ You can't, you can't! ♫
♫ You're a side character! ♫
♫ Wait! (Boys Love) ♫
♫ I'm a side, side, just a side character! ♫
- Lovely weather today.
- Yeah?
- Really sunny.
- Yeah.
I'll have double helpings of miso.
Okay, Dear.
I'm so glad. Thank you.
- More rice, please.
- All right.
Coming up.
What's up, Ayato? You're not eating.
Yeah...
I don't have an appetite.
Oh, Dear...
Then you have to drink some milk, at least.
She's right, Aya.
Here, Aya.
Ayaya?
Aya? Drink it.
- Ayaya?
- Aya!
- Ayaya.
- Yaya!
- Ayaya! Ayaya!
- Aya! Ayaya!
- Ayayaya!
- Enough!
His name is Ayato! Don't shorten it, say it properly!
What's wrong?
You're probably low on calcium.
Drink some milk.
Right.
Here.
Well...
That was the first time I realized
that, for as long I could remember, the guys around me mostly had gender-neutral names.
Aya...
[Episode 1]
[VS Names]
[Micchan]
Hey, Haruka!
Aoi!
- You slowpoke!
- Sorry about that.
Hey, what happened to Mizuki?
Oh, that! I heard that Nagisa...
It didn't really bother me,
but it seemed to be one of the quirks of this world.
Yuki, what are you eating?
What?
What about you, Azusa?
You first, Yuki!
Mao!
Wait for me!
Go away.
Why are you so upset?
You're so annoying!
Mao!
If you looked at the school register, you'd think it was a girls' school.
Hey!
Chiaki!
Were you waiting long?
I was.
You're so late, Nanase.
Sorry, I was held up in class.
Really? You should've texted.
Natsuki...
Miyu...
Natsuki!
Miyu!
Na-tsu-ki!
Mi-yu!
Natsuki!
But that wasn't the end of it.
See you next week.
Class is over.
Thank you.
Hey, Rin!
We go to the same school! I was able to see you again!
Why did you call me Rin? My name's Suzuno.
Well, because...
A bell (Suzu) rings (Rin)!
Oh, I see...
Okay, then.
Suzuno is Suzuno. There's no "I see" about it.
Then...
If you're name's Yukawa...
can I start calling you "Yuka"?
- You can't.
- Huh?
Of course, you can...
Rin.
Don't tease me like that...
Yuka.
That means...
giving out nicknames was the start of a happy relationship.
- What are you talking about?
- Rika?
Rika, Rika, Rika!
That guy's name is Morikawa.
From "Morikawa" to "Rika"...
Isn't that a little too forced?
Oh! For the party tomorrow,
can I invite my friend Misaki?
What's he like?
Kind of an airhead, really cute.
He's like a therapy dog!
- That's perfect!
- Nice!
I can't wait!
And this is Misaki.
You might think it's a girl's name
but there are tons of examples of it being a man's surname.
Sorry! Were you waiting long?
Izumi?
And his last name is Izumi.
Not at all.
Yellow!
They're not sunflowers...
It's not lavender...
That's it! They're marigolds!
So?
Where are we going today?
Why don't we go to the park in the next town over?
I hear they have really pretty flowers.
You really do love flowers, don't you?
I guess so.
Then...
let's go.
It's so cold today!
And so, the couple that loves flowers above all else,
enjoys the flowers of this world to their heart's content.
Just then...
Hey!
That guy is Mayumi.
His last name is Mayumi.
What the heck is going on in this world?
Can I give you a nickname?
What?
If we have nicknames for each other,
we'll feel more like friends. Right?
Let's see...
Oh! You have big eyes!
What about Ai-Ai (Eye-Eye)?
This is bad.
This development is very bad!
Or maybe... Ai?
No... AIko, maybe?
What about Tomi?
Hey, how about Miki?
- Nice one!
- That's so cute!
- Himari's pretty cute too, huh?
- Super cute!
The second I get a girly nickname...
I will absolutely...
start loving one of these guys!
This is bad!
What about... Jeans?
That's it!
Or...
I also love this. What about Macaroni?
Oh, that's it!
Hoodie! Starting today...
I'm Hoodie! Call me Hoodie, guys!
Well...
That's good.
That's perfect for you.
Let's go back.
Let's go.
Wait...
Isn't it good? Come on.
I'm Hoodie.
And so, I was never...
called "Hoodie" by anyone.
Well, all's well when ends well.
A Man Who Defies
The World of BL
Season 2.
I'm home.
Oh, welcome back.
What?
That smell...
Hey.
Welcome home. Sorry for intruding.
This rose guy!
I can't just see them, I can even smell them.
Hello.
Nice to meet you. I'm Minami.
This is my friend, Minami.
You don't sparkle, huh?
Oh, I mean, nice to meet you.
Want to play a game?
- Come on!
- Oh!
And so...
I joined my brother's video game tournament with his boyfriend.
Hey, come on!
- I'm gonna get first!
- Go, go, go!
- You can do it!
- He's so fast!
Nice going!
- It's not over yet!
- Go for it!
I give up!
Wait a minute... this guy's in love with Ayato, too?!
Your rival is Mr. Roses!
His name is Toujou!
But then, this is the fancy of youth.
Good luck, kid!
- The red shell!
- Oh, your brother!
[FINISH]
- Come on!
- You suck at this, huh?
Hey, why don't we eat the cake now?
Good idea!
Let's go.
There's one for you, too.
Really?
Gosh, what's up with this guy?
He's totally perfect.
He's handsome, kind, considerate...
He has no weaknesses!
Pop quiz! What is Toujou's weakness?
Pardon?
And the person who gets it can choose their favorite cake!
Sounds fun.
Yay!
Mr. Roses's weakness?
[Episode 2]
[VS Weaknesses]
Quiz time! What is Toujou's weakness?
Yay!
Toujou's weakness is...
clowns?
Nope!
Then... small spaces?
I'm totally fine with them.
- Caterpillars?
- Nope.
What about... high places?
I'm fine with them.
For real? This quiz isn't fun for anyone outside of the couple.
- Tomatoes?
- Nope.
Sharp objects?
I'm fine with them.
My brother is constantly being teased,
so I bet he wanted to try and find out Mr. Roses's weakness.
Oh, I got it!
Horror!
On our junior high trip, you said you'd tell scary stores in our room...
but you didn't come!
I'm fine with horror.
You're not thinking, Brother.
The weaknesses for these
seemingly flawless, perfect, super-human types...
is something unexpected or cunning.
Excuse me.
You have an advantage after dating for so long.
So could I ask one question?
Go for it.
No fair!
In one week,
how often are you confronted with that weakness?
Every day.
Hm...
The fact that he answered without even thinking about it means...
What?
That's amazing! How did you know?
Yippie! I'll take this one, then.
Aw, I wanted that one too! What's the right answer, then?
Figure it out yourself.
Toujou, tell me!
I'll tell you, eventually.
But...
let me preserve my coolness in your eyes for now.
Toujou...
Hey, you can take a piece now.
Right...
Deep down, I was relieved.
Ayato still doesn't know Toujou's weakness.
Which means...
Toujou, it's morning.
Why won't you wake up?
Is your weakness morning time?
So, that's it!
You little...!
It means they haven't woken up together yet.
Come on!
If you don't stop that...
you'll get punished.
What the hell?!
I-It's nothing...
This is really good!
The cake you get from winning a quiz sure is yummy!
Right...
I'll have some, too.
Mine is good, too.
So tasty.
So they haven't gotten that far yet.
That means...
you still have a chance.
Good luck, kid!
What? Did I say something out loud?
Big bro...
What?
Big bro, I want to feed you some of this!
- No.
- Just one bite?
- No!
- Please?
No, no, no!
- Just a bite!
- Feed someone else!
- I've fallen for you.
- What?
Well, weaknesses can be quite unexpected, huh?
Wait, it's not like that!
A Man Who Defies
The World of BL
Season 2.
♫ Just like "Bubble Love" ♫
♫ It's an ordinary situation ♫
♫ An imitation hiding the thorns ♫
♫ Beckoning to breathe ♫
♫ A heart rattled by flirtations ♫
♫ Don't take me, why? ♫
♫ Help yourself ♫
♫ Don't leave me, I knew you would ♫
♫ Teach me how to resist you ♫
♫ Just like "Bubble Love" ♫
♫ Is this time finally true? ♫
♫ This is our famous scene ♫
♫ If you're so kind to me ♫
♫ Why don't we be happy together? ♫
♫ Just like "Bubble Love" ♫
♫ My doubt's like a bubble ♫
♫ It pops into thin air ♫
♫ What's left in my hand that should have held on ♫
♫ Are droplets of you ♫
♫ Just like "Bubble Love" ♫
[This story is fiction.]