Chief producer.
As a man,
the happiness I imagined
is to ride my love horse
and win the first place.
can create more
of China.
Seeing the orphanage they donated
and raised them happily.
But now,
I need to do something important.
Find this woman.
She's my junior.
She runs a flower shop.
She's a florist.
Her name is Ruan Qingtian.
Half a year ago,
I saw Ruan Qingtian
with a vase.
I didn't want to get involved in their business.
I didn't expect my cousin
the next day.
So,
I have to bring Ruan Qingtian
to my cousin's bed.
When I was going to find her,
At the horse farming auction,
I met her by accident.
Is this you?
He's the guy I had a crush on.
I kept confessing my love to him during college.
but he never responded.
No, I can't let him misunderstand me.
I'm going to the toilet.
Haoming.
Haoming, where are you going?
Younian.
Seon-woo.
Senpai.
It's been seven or eight hundred days.
You really impressed me.
You've learned how to
on others' shoulders.
You didn't talk that much before.
Yes, that was in the past.
Ruan Qingtian, I didn't expect to see you again.
You are...
You're with that old man?
You misunderstood me, Senpai.
Listen to me.
Actually, I... Listen to me. I...
Senior.
Let me explain.
Listen to me.
Stay here.
Don't go anywhere.
When I'm done,
I have plenty of time for you to explain.
It's not you.
If you keep mumbling,
I'll throw you away in the car.
I don't have time or patience now.
You have the freedom to choose.
Senpai.
Wait for me here.
The next horse
is the most expensive horse in the auction.
This horse is the most popular.
It's the iron hoof Beauty.
Its maternal system
It's Ruth, who won the 15th champion of Elland.
My father's family has a long history of winning the championship.
Thomas family.
The starting price is 3 million.
The price is 200,000 per time.
You must win this horse.
With our God of Land Wind,
the best horse will grow.
Wonderful.
That's why we must win this iron hoof Beauty.
Any bidding?
3.2 million.
OK, the lady here offers 3.2 million.
3.5 million. 3.5 million.
4 million.
Four million
Anyone else?
4.5 million
4.5 million.
It's 4.5 million now.
Any more guests?
So much
This is a big sum.
How dare you!
Where did you go?
I thought you escaped.
Yes, I wanted to leave, but...
But what?
But I gave you money.
4.5 million.
Now we have 4.5 million.
Is there any guest bidding?
4.5 million going once.
4.5 million going twice.
I offer 4.8 million.
4.8 million once.
4.8 million going twice.
5.5 million.
This lady has
It's already 5.5 million.
More?
Six million.
Ten million.
This gentleman has increased 10 million.
Is there any more bid for 10 million?
It's already 10 million
Anything else?
10 million once.
Everyone.
Sorry, auctioner, I have something to say.
Today
is my wife's birthday.
I want to take a photo of this horse
to my wife.
as her birthday gift.
I hope you'll accept it.
How can I do that?
I can't afford it.
It's your birthday.
Why should we?
No.
Forget it, Miss Xiaoxiao.
Mr. Qian’s wife
has been dead for many years.
I finally found a beautiful new wife.
I gave in anyway.
Me too.
Mr. Qian must be newlywed.
to have such a beautiful wife.
Today is Mrs. Qian’s birthday.
You just showed your ID card.
Let's wish them happiness.
Let's give way.
Make way
What are you thinking?
Miss Ruan.
Think about your mother's gambler.
10,2 million.
This lady offers 10,2 million.
Is there another guest?
102 million going once.
10,200,000 going twice.
It's a deal.
Ruan Qingtian, you're really something.
This is my flower shop.
Why are you kicking me out?
I invested a lot of money.
Let me tell you.
your mom gave us
to us.
Before your mom pays us back,
we'll take this shop.
Get lost.
Get lost!
Hey, Mom! Hey, hey!
I promised you
to pretend to be his wife
to take a horse for him.
I even did such a ridiculous thing.
Because he can pay your gambling debt?
Did you gamble again?
I just want to make a fortune.
Tian Tian.
Listen.
Don't go home these days.
I'll go out and hide.
Okay, I'll hang up now.
Don't go home.
Remember, don't go home.
I spent a lot of money to buy these.
They're all on the street now.
Did I see it right?
I won.
The prize is a farm. Gosh.
It's going to rain.
My mom won't let me go home either.
Where can I go?
Call my dad.
I don't know where my dad is.
Forget about that.
Pack your things.
Go back quickly.
Take your things.
Check it.
I've arranged a place to stay.
Really?
I parked my car
I parked my car in your husband's parking space.
My phone number
in the car too.
Are you sure?
Yes.
When he comes back, he will call me
he'll call me.
Okay.
What should I do?
You park your car in my parking space.
Yes.
I'll move the car right away.
Wait for me.
What should I do?
Forget about that.
Let's clean up.
Right.
Right
When you go out,
you take another elevator.
Wait for me at B3.
I'll go to B2 to move the car.
After that,
I'll go to B3 to find you.
Let's meet at B3.
Got it?
Can you do it? No problem.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Honey.
Calm down.
It's not what you think.
Let me explain.
Why isn't mom picking up?
Dad, pick up the phone.
Actor table.
Ji Chunhua, Chen Fuyu.
Brother Ma, Li Xixi.
Family doctor, Li Yong.
Pervert B Su Peng
No. 1 blind date man, Hou Yuhang.
Auction Room B
to perform.
Zhou Jianjun, Miao Yulan, Su Yahan. Zeng Fanrong, Qiao Jianqiang, Jia Jianxi Zhang Yijuan.
Li Xiao Jun, Zhu, Lin, Mo Mei Ling, Wang Yu Guo Li Lili, Wang Shu Mei, An, Ni, Liang Xiu Xiu. Zheng Gui Li.
Confucius, Lin Pansi, Zhao, Rong, Liu Lu Man. Wei Lele Fu Weiwei Shen Li Zheng Tong Yuntan Pei Huixia
Xia Hongwei. Liu Xiaoxian. Liu Xiaoxian. Liu Xiaoxian. Marshal Zhang, Liu Beihua, Wang Jiaming, Wang Jiaming, Wang Jiaming, Wang Jiaming, and Wang Jiaming Zhang Jiaqiao: Look at this. Look at this.
Directed rouge
Wang Xu.
Script: Ale Lee, Ren Dali
Photography team.
Props, Li Jintao, Zhang Lilun.
Lighting team.
The recording team.
The combing assistant, Du Xing.
The marathon team.
Faith.
Lyrics: Jiang Mengdan
Composed by Zhang Jiaqing
Singer Zhang Jiaqing
Lock Love.
Singing Cai Xiang.
"Ungrateful".
[Lyrics: Jiang Meng Dan]
Lyrics: Jiang Mengdan
composed by Jiang Meng Dan.
Editing by Zhao Weiqiang
Audio Producer
Recorder Lin Li Yang
Visual effect production.
Transportation Team.
Product Company.
Wuhan Lexiao Media Co., Ltd.
of Wuhan Lexiao Media Co., Ltd.
The production company