Your balance is almost depleted.
Your next payment is due on the 12th.
Call me when the drip is done.
The patient is on an IV right now.
If you have questions, ask them quickly.
Sorry to bother you.
We brought you some fruit.
Have a seat.
We'll just ask a few questions and go.
Do you know if your brother A Xin
ever delivered medical supplies
for this nursing home?
Has your brother Xin Qili
been using some other means
to pay for your medical bills?
We aren't asking this without proof.
We checked your medication records,
and your payment details.
They don't match your actual condition
or your health status at all.
And this nursing home
is giving you unauthorized drugs.
And they're not cheap.
Based on the leads we have,
your brother Xin Qili
is suspected of illegal transactions.
About all of this,
do you know anything?
My brother...
My brother
has been doing some shady things.
Because of my illness,
he really had no other choice.
People like us,
with no money,
no connections,
we can only wait to die when we get sick.
I know that money
definitely wasn't earned legally.
But I want to live.
I want to stay alive.
Is that against the law?
He never told me
what he was doing,
or where the money came from.
And I never asked.
Because I was afraid if I asked,
I wouldn't be able
to live with myself anymore.
Are you done asking?
The patient needs to rest now.
Let's stop here for today.
If you remember anything new,
let us know anytime.
Officer Zhang.
Chen Yongjiang is dead.
What about his company?
The second shareholder took it over.
What is it?
After all, he killed my brother.
Did your brother ever tell you anything
about the Fengmao Company?
Is that so?
Zhang Heng.
Excuse me.
It really is you.
What case are you working on?
I keep running into you here lately.
How's Paopao doing these days?
Thanks to you, brother-in-law.
Since you're back at the law firm,
the hospital bills are more manageable.
That's great.
Same as before,
let me know anytime if you need anything.
Come home for dinner when you have time.
Did you hear?
That girl next door,
her brother died.
She's the only one left in her family.
Poor thing.
The past couple of days,
people have been keeping watch downstairs.
I bet she owes someone money.
Where do you hear this stuff all day?
She's got a caregiver here every day.
That doesn't come cheap.
Come in.
Sorry to bother you.
I'm a family member from the next room.
My family said
you're staying here all by yourself.
These are freshly made.
Eat them while they're hot. Don't be shy.
Those people outside,
what's really going on?
Those people outside...
Luo Xiao.
You think you're an exception?
Do... do we know each other?
You didn't just take Brother Mao's place,
you took on his risks too, didn't you?
What are you trying to say?
I'm guessing you've already met Ruan Chen.
Those people outside,
he sent them to watch me.
Because of the evidence A Xin left me.
A Xin paid for this life of mine.
So I have to stay alive.
You have to help me.
Because I can help you too.
Otherwise, look at those men outside.
When are they coming tomorrow?
I don't know.
Whether they're coming for me,
or coming for you,
or going after your daughter,
I have no idea.
You don't believe me?
Then what about Zhang Heng?
Do you even know?
He's already found out
that the nursing home's bills are shady.
He found out my medical records are fake.
If he keeps digging like this,
how sure are you you'll get out clean?
What do you mean?
I'm getting blisters on my lips.
These transactions are way too scattered.
It's just like Yi Zhan.
They're all straw-man accounts.
After bouncing around a few times,
it goes back to Fengmao.
It's all stuff we already know.
Besides this,
Fengmao runs many businesses,
but Ruientai Pharma shows up a lot.
It's also in the nursing home's books.
Ruientai Pharma repeatedly
wired money to Fengmao.
Each transfer was hundreds of thousands.
All marked "project promotion payments."
Look.
Just as I thought.
No project approval process.
No reconciliation documents.
I just checked too.
Zero project partnership with Fengmao.
Ruientai isn't a shell company,
but it has fake projects with Fengmao.
The nursing home's books are dirty.
Xin Youna's medical records were faked.
This Xin Qili
is the middleman for the bank and Fengmao.
Then what links Ruientai and Fengmao?
Looks like you don't know yet.
Could you be a bit clearer?
This nursing home
can treat your daughter's illness,
but it requires some illegal drugs.
Banned substances.
Foreign drugs.
Looks like you just moved in recently.
The director hasn't consulted you yet.
Otherwise, why would you think
a county-level nursing home like this
could grow to such a scale,
with patients coming from out of town
in an endless stream every day?
This nursing home
has an underground drug supply chain.
A Xin convinced Brother Mao
to add this to the laundering pipeline.
They put the money in,
under the guise of buying drugs,
clean it, then move it out.
Of course, part of that money
was to buy medicine for me.
Then Brother Mao saw profits dropping.
He wanted to shut it down.
A Xin refused.
That's why the "accident" happened.
So you mean this nursing home
is also a downstream link for Ruan Chen.
It's not just this nursing home.
Pharma company, Ruan Chen, Brother Mao,
they each have their own interests.
They cooperate, but they also clash.
A Xin just sweet-talked Brother Mao
into running the money through here.
Zhang Heng has dug this far.
That means he already has
evidence of Fengmao's money laundering.
He's also tracked down A Xin.
He might have caught Ruan Chen's tail.
If that's the case,
why not give the evidence to the cops?
If the police go after the bank next,
by working with me,
what would you gain?
I'm not after any benefit.
I want to stay alive.
Zhang Heng can't give me that.
The drugs, yes.
I can give you leverage on the bank,
but you have to guarantee my safety
and the drug supply.
Your leverage,
how much weight does it carry?
Only two hundred moved this week.
A Xin's side collected as planned.
Keep the reserve at one hundred.
Check the books one more time.
The heat is on lately.
The cash flow
must strictly follow the chain.
I need some time to think about it.
Those guys outside are just scaring you.
There are cameras everywhere here.
They wouldn't dare touch you.
If there's any issue, call security,
or call me anytime.
I'll leave you to it.
The first transfer was exactly three days
before Xin Youna checked in.
The last transfer
was a week before A Xin died.
The timing's too much of a coincidence.
Excluding the Ruientai payments,
Fengmao's other accounts ran normally.
No external promotional projects,
no obvious funding gaps either.
In other words,
the transactions between the two of them
weren't for actual goods,
nor were they money laundering.
But they're strongly tied to the nursing home
and to that brother and sister.
We've got our breakthrough.
These past two years,
we must find a way to shut Fengmao down.
Otherwise,
it's too dangerous.
Alright.
Lawyer Luo.
After you, Mr. Ruan.
A Xin's sister,
Xin Youna has something important.
You go
and get it for me.
What is it?
It can't be dumplings, can it?
I'm not trying to put you in a tough spot,
but you need to realize
who you're in the same boat with now.
Do you have any idea?
What she's holding
is a ticking time bomb.
Once it goes off,
not only you, Luo Xiao,
or me, Ruan Chen,
the whole chain behind us gets exposed.
You only see the money,
if you knew where it came from,
whose hands it passed through,
and where it ended up,
you'd be at her room right this second.
Do whatever it takes,
and bring that thing to me.
I'm not capable of that.
Your guys can only stake out outside,
let alone me.
Zhang Heng has already contacted her.
At the slightest move,
she'll call the cops immediately.
I won't let you do this for nothing.
Money laundering is one thing,
getting that item is another.
They're two different matters.
The guy your wife cheated with,
you know him, right?
Just say the word,
and he disappears, just like that.
I can help you get the item,
but hold off on Feng Zhan for now.
He's still useful to me.