[Love You 3000 Times]
[Episode 4]
Ms. Jiang,
it's done.
I knew
you'd come to save me.
He Yuchuan?
What's wrong?
Ms. Jiang,
He Yuchuan
is trapped by a man in a small alley.
Don't take any action.
Don't act rashly and alert that guy.
Let me see the situation at the scene.
Okay.
Ms. Jiang, look!
He Yuchuan is being beaten.
I don't know what they said.
Ms. Jiang,
should I take action?
Wait.
Take action now!
Bai Long,
where is He Yuchuan?
Ms. Jiang,
I've already sent Fang Zeyuan to the police station.
♫I try to overcome the darkness♫
But my dress got dirty.
♫And change my bad habits♫
Okay. I'll buy you a new one.
♫Just to fill♫
♫My meager sense of security♫
♫That's left♫
How did he get injured so badly?
♫At a quiet restaurant♫
Why didn't you protect him?
♫I'm afraid of the darkness in the corner♫
It was you who told me not to do anything.
♫The cold tea longs to be warmed up by hands♫
But now you are blaming me?
Forget it.
♫Your departing figure♫
You can go back first.
Okay.
♫I gazed at it until my eyes ached♫
Good night.
♫Ripples spreading in my lake♫
♫At the lakeshore where you can't touch♫
♫I turned disappointment♫
♫Into skyscrapers♫
♫Moonlight was my dancing partner♫
♫In the dim lights, you and I got separated♫
♫In a wedding dress, walking down the aisle♫
♫Friends and family toast and cheer♫
♫They wait for me to get married♫
♫But who am I waiting for?♫
Why didn't you fight back?
Xingchen,
if it were you,
you would have fought back.
I wish it were you who came back.
Can I have a chance to atone?
♫In the dim lights, you and I got separated♫
♫In a wedding dress, walking down the aisle♫
♫Friends and family toast and cheer♫
♫They wait for me to get married♫
♫But who am I waiting for?♫
How long are you going to keep up this act?
That night three years ago,
what exactly happened?
[Backup]
[Jinjie Psychological Counseling Center]
[Medical Record]
[Chief Complaint]
He Yuchuan.
He Yuchuan?
[AirDrop]
[Decline] [Accept]
[AirDrop] [He Yuchuan] [Sending]
He Yuchuan?
[AirDrop]
[AirDrop] [He Yuchuan] [Sending]
He Yuchuan?
I'm here.
You're at home.
Why didn't you respond to me when I called?
I was in the bathroom.
I didn't hear you.
Check the operation records of my computer.
Okay.
By the way, Ms. Jiang,
He Yuchuan just went out.
I found out that he is
volunteering at a nursing home,
the one where Auntie Shen is staying.
Let's follow him and take a look now.
Okay.
My son!
Mom.