Since you're working here now, let's have a competition.
Are you challenging me?
(I challenged him to see who's better at doing their jobs,)
(but he decided to challenge me at every turn instead.)
Don't you have anything else to do?
I'm praying for your downfall.
Waiting for somebody to be fired.
(You've got skills. So, why don't you work to pay off your debt?)
Why did you get married to pay it off?
I think if we try to accept each other,
it'll be better.
I don't know her at all.
You should get to know her once again then.
(If Mueang knows that I've dug up a lot of information on him,)
(will he be scared of me?)
(Detective Piti, he's good.)
(Personal History)
Okay. I'll check the place out while I wait.
You can tell me when you're ready.
I have to go now, Mr. Phudin.
Get him some rest.
Be a good stepmother.
Let's go.
Have you been busy, Young Master? You haven't seen Kaykay in a while.
I've been quite busy.
You can go now.
Yes, sir.
Mueang.
What are you doing here?
I won't tell you.
On a date with Tin?
How did you know?
You like to hang out with him.
Don't act like you know me.
See? You're doing that again.
Doing what?
You rubbed your eyebrow.
Don't you realize you often do that?
It was itching.
No, I think it means something.
I'm trying to figure it out.
Why would you?
I'm trying to get to know you.
Don't you want to try to get to know me?
No. You're too complicated.
I can't deny that.
Look, rather than spending the time to get to know me,
you should get to know my dad instead.
Or you might make another mistake.
What do you mean I made a mistake?
Well, it's nothing specific.
I'm just worried my dad would trick you.
My dad is not the good man he appears to be.
Are you saying your dad is not a good "fiancé?"
I'll let you know something.
Nobody in this world is worse than my ex.
This is bad, guys.
Mrs. Sita!
- What is it?   - My zodiac sign,
your zodiac sign,
Din's zodiac sign, and also Mueang's
would encounter a big disaster.
Here.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
They're cursing nearly all the zodiac signs.
Do you believe this?
I do.
This one has been spot on!
What do you think
we're going to encounter?
A meteor crashing down on Earth?
Be serious, please, Mrs. Sita.
Maybe chaos is upon us here.
What chaos now?
It's bad enough that Apo came in.
Perhaps
another secret character will show up.
A secret character?
Who is it?
Spoil me.
I don't know.
Mrs. Sita, a spoiler, please.
- No.   - Please.
No.
Good morning.
We're here to see Mr. Phudin.
It's you, Ing.
I almost didn't recognize you.
(Who the heck is this old hag?)
(Why does she know me?)
I get it. I have trouble remembering faces too.
Please tell your parents I said hi.
Okay.
So
who is that?
Your boyfriend?
No.
He's my employee.
I'm a gemologist.
Gemologist?
We're here on time. Can we go straight in?
Not yet. Mr. Phudin is in a meeting. He'll be ready in half an hour.
Half an hour?
We apologize for your inconvenience.
Should we check out the place while we wait?
I think you should look around outside.
Take some photos with cute animals and flowers.
Okay.
When Din is ready,
Mrs. Sita will call you, okay?
Okay. Thanks.
She's still arrogant, like she was as a kid.
Right?
No comment.
Mrs. Sita.
Come on, Ms. Ing.
- Don't get upset.   - He knows I don't like to wait.
Don't think of it as waiting.
Think of it as our date.
Is it far away?
The entrance is probably that way.
Let's go.
- I'm not going.   - Why not?
It's hot. Just get me an iced lemon tea. Be quick.
What was her childhood like?
She's so hard to please.
Why does it keep twitching?
- Here.   - Thank you.
Hey, I think I'm seeing things.
When I parked, I saw
that trash-talking woman
at your dad's office.
How can that be?
Is our world that small?
You weren't listening.
Sorry.
When you talk,
I always listen.
Come on. I said sorry.
What's on your mind?
I'm just thinking that the world makes no sense.
Some people only get good things.
Others only get bad things.
That's just how it is.
There's nothing we can control.
There!
God up there is controlling everything.
(Sometimes, I wonder)
(if we're in a reality show)
(or a video game where someone is controlling us.)
Wait and see
what God has in store for you.
(Personal History)
(Game used to date Apo.)
(They used to show their relationship on Facebook three years ago.)
(Game has just shown his profile as "single" recently.)
(According to those close to Game,)
(he has other women throughout his three years with Apo.)
(He also has a rich widow sugar mommy.)
(Her name is Lady Keerati,)
(a prominent person in jewelry.)
(Lady Keerati has always been supporting Game financially.)
(Apo never knew about any of this.)
(Personal History)
(That's right.)
(Sometimes, God brings those we hate)
(back into our lives.)
I'll let you know something.
Nobody in this world is worse than my ex.
Is your ex that bad?
What do you think is one of the reasons I ran away to the beach?
Since we've opened up a bit,
I'll tell you in short.
I saw him in bed with another woman.
(That's why I left his life that day.)
(If possible, I don't want to see him ever again.)
(I didn't know what made me walk up to her.)
(I just felt that if I could change the world,)
(it would be great.)
Whoa! Watch where you're going!
Sorry.
It's crowded here. Let's talk somewhere else.
What are you doing?
(I did it.)
(I can't believe I've changed this!)
(I really can turn this around.)
What the heck are you doing?
What the heck did you do?
- Do you want to fight?   - Let's do one-on-one!
- Are you high?   - Game!
Game!
Where have you been?
Sorry, Ms. Ing.
This guy picked a fight with me.
Where is my drink?
I spilled it.
This is for your drink. Don't ever step foot here again.
No! It's not worth it.
Yes, ma'am.
Game?
Apo?
(At that moment,)
(I realized I couldn't change anything at all.)
It's you?
(If God really exists,)
(I'd like to ask)
(what more you have in store for me.)
Are you here for a trip?
What a coincidence.
Yeah. What a coincidence.
Sorry.
Happy anni...
So, are you dating that woman?
I'm not asking because I felt anything.
I just wanted to make sure I was right to break up with you.
I'm happy you can move on.
Me too.
I thought it would be harder.
Maybe because you got someone else, I got over you so easily.
You're over me. That's good.
I think you look well.
I've been well. Really well.
So we parted on good terms, right?
Wait. Who said that? Who parted on good terms? Have you lost your mind?
If you hate me that much, the next time you see me,
don't even say hi. Pretend I don't exist.
- Just walk past by.   - Okay. Fine. I will do that. Like we never met.
Good. That's it.
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry for making you feel bad.
I have to go now.
The owner of this place is expecting me.
Wait.
The owner of this place? Who are you talking about?
Is she not picking up?
No. Ms. Ing won't pick up.
I think she's busy taking photos.
That's what you would do.
I wasn't talking about myself.
You know what? Take her to the lounge when she gets here.
Yes, sir.
I think she's taking photos for her Instagram.
I really think so.
I told her to do that.
So, where have we met?
The parking lot.
You tripped and bumped into me.
I don't remember.
Don't play dumb.
I'm not. I meet a lot of people. Do you expect me to recognize them all?
You really don't remember my face?
- I don't.   - I don't believe you.
I'm not asking you to believe me.
Who are you? Why do I need to recognize you?
I'm telling you right now. I'm your victim.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Ms. Ing.
Do you recognize this man?
I don't.
Is my face that forgettable?
He said he met me at a parking lot.
Where?
So it's you.
That's better.
The guy who made your high heels dirty.
It's you!
Wait.
You got it all wrong. You bumped into me. That's what you should remember,
not that I ruined your shoes.
What a waste of time. Let's go.
Hey! Are you really going to just leave?
Seriously?
Is he following us?
He's not.
My mom said the world gets smaller as you get older.
Am I really getting old?
How can you be old? You're too gorgeous.
Don't flatter me.
You are gorgeous.
It's good you don't recognize that guy.
It's a waste of your memory.
Who said I don't recognize him?
How could I forget him? He pointed at my face and called me names.
How have you survived?
So that was...
Yes. I was acting.
I don't want to deal with him. He's annoying.
You sure can act.
You deserve an Oscar.
Can we please move on from this?
Okay, ma'am.
How was it with your ex?
Well, it was nothing.
It's just a coincidence. I don't think I'd see her again.
Okay.
(Mr. Phudin)
The owner? Do you mean Mr. Phudin?
That's him.
Do you know him?
I read his interview somewhere.
I have to go. I have some work to do.
(Mr. Phudin)
(Where are you? Why are you not picking up?)
(The people I'd like you to meet are here waiting for us.)
Hi.
Are you done talking to him?
Who's that man?
Why did you ask? You already knew.
Why would I know?
Well, you warned me.
Look, rather than spending the time to get to know me,
you should get to know my dad instead.
Or you might make another mistake.
What do you mean I made a mistake?
Well, it's nothing specific.
I'm just worried my dad would trick you.
My dad is not the good man he appears to be.
I figured you had
dug up about my ex.
Are you mad? Who would have time to spy on you?
You would!
You were stalking me just now.
I saw you.
I saw him looking suspicious, so I followed him.
I didn't know who he was.
Anyway, that's him,
the ex I told you about.
Oh! So it's this guy?
He shows up right when you talk about him.
Do you think this is the afterlife?
What?
Where are you coming from?
Maybe I'm dead,
and this is hell.
Yeah. This is hell.
If not, how would Game and his new girl
meet Mr. Phudin?
Wait.
What does this have to do with my dad?
You know what?
Mr. Phudin wants me to meet his friend's daughter.
She's taking over her family's jewelry business.
It seems his friend's daughter
is Game's new girlfriend.
What? Are you serious?
I am.
Does my old man know about your ex?
Mr. Phudin wants me to meet Game and his new girlfriend now.
I don't want to go.
Mueang, what should I do?
What should you do?
Wait a sec. Let me think.
We have to figure out if you go and if you don't,
what's going to happen, both good and bad.
If we figured that out, we'd know what to do.
Mueang.
Sorry. I shouldn't ask for your advice about this.
I'll figure this out myself.
Hey, wait.
(Bike For Rent)
Get on.
- Where are you going?   - Come on. Just get on.
Okay.
- Ready?   - Never.
Let's go.
Mueang, where are you taking me?
I won't tell you.
Where are you taking me?
To my old man.
No, I'm not going. Stop!
I won't!
I don't want to go, Mueang.
Why? Are you embarrassed your new boyfriend is old?
You said it was your life choice. Why would you be embarrassed?
The one who should be embarrassed is your ex.
Let's show him
how much your life is better than when you were with him!
Look, although my dad is not as nice and handsome as I am,
I'm confident he is at least richer than that guy.
Show him who's boss!
Now, let's go!
It's odd.
It's really odd.
How is it odd?
She texted me at 2.13 pm.
I replied at 2.14 pm, but she hadn't read it.
She won't pick up my calls.
It looks like
she just died right there while texting you.
Are you saying my girlfriend was in an accident?
No, Uncle. I think she just doesn't want to meet me.
Why would you say that?
I just sense it.
I don't think so. I think she has something to do.
Let's talk about our business at hand.
Why do you want to see me, Ing?
I need you to mine Siamese ruby for me, Uncle.
I have to refuse.
Why not? Did someone take my deal?
No. You're still the priority deal.
It's just that our mines
only contain small pieces of Siamese ruby.
We haven't seen a big piece in a long time.
Just because you haven't seen one doesn't mean it's not there.
Maybe you haven't been mining in the right places.
Your name is Game, right?
Yes, sir.
A few months ago, a foreigner sat here.
He said the same thing you said.
Let me give you the very same answer.
I have been in the mining business for over 30 years.
Nobody knows these mines as well as I do.
I'm not saying I know better than you do, sir.
I'm just commenting based on my experience.
I'm sorry if I offended you.
It's fine. You can share your opinions.
But it's up to you if you would listen, right?
That's right. You do know me well, Ing.
You really won't mine for me, Uncle?
Ing, I'm sorry.
Okay. If you change your mind, just call me.
I won't.
Who knows? I might be able to change your mind.
It's fine. I'll just leave for now.
- Goodbye.   - Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Sorry, I'm late.
Why is your hair messed up?
I rushed here on a bike. I had no time.
I forgot to introduce her.
This is Apo, my soon-to-be bride.
Good afternoon.
Yes!
This is Ing, my friend's daughter.
This is Game. He works for Ing.
Good afternoon.
I'm sorry I wasn't here to welcome you guys.
I got caught up in something.
I ran into someone I knew in the park.
Really? Who was it?
My old enemy.
Old enemy?
I'll tell you later.
I really have to go now.
Hey, wait, ma'am.
Where are you going? Are you in a rush?
I have a lot of things to talk to you guys.
It's fine. We have a reservation.
What a shame!
Rain check, then?
See you, Ms. Ing.
And you, Mr. Game.
(Are you messing with me?)
(I'm dreaming. I'm surely dreaming.)
I'll walk you to your car. This way, please.
- No need.   - No need.
Excuse me.
We'll see you when we hand out the invitation.
Of course. I have to go now. Goodbye.
- Goodbye.   - Bye-bye!
Bye!
- Ms. Ing, wait.   - Let's talk in the car!
I really didn't know about this!
I'm sorry.
You said I should act like your lover.
You don't have to try that hard.
You can touch me. I'm not a monk.
Your old enemy.
What's your story?
I'll be back and tell you later.
Why? Where are you going?
I'll be back in a minute.
- I need to hurry!   - Apo.
Mueang.
How did it go?
Those two couldn't wait to leave.
See? I thought it would work.
Guys like your ex have a fragile ego.
Serves him right.
Mueang.
What? Why do you keep saying my name?
Why did you help me?
What help?
Everything you did,
from the moment you called me onto your bike,
you gave me a pep talk, you took me here.
Who took you here? You rode that bike yourself.
Don't deny it.
You were obviously helping me.
I just can't stand seeing you playing the victim.
You need to show him you're fine without him.
That's the best revenge.
Mueang.
You're actually kinder than I thought.
What now?
Well...
Although you don't like me,
you still feel bad for me.
You're really kind.
Thank you, Mueang.
Stop!
I said stop!
Stop what?
Stop giving me that look.
What look?
The teary, almost crying look that you don't give to just anyone.
What's that?
- What?   - Listen.
Stay like this. Don't turn around.
- Don't turn around.   - Oh?
- Mueang...   - Hey!
Like this. Don't! No!
If you turn around,
I'll...
You'll...
Oh, hey! Mueang!
What's wrong with him?
You're really kind.
Thank you, Mueang.
(You're really kind. Thank you, Mueang.)
Stop!
Stop what?
Stop giving me that look.
What look?
Look at you!
You have to stop being kind to Apo,
understand?
Understand?
Do you understand?
Young Master! Please take a look at Tin.
- What's wrong?   - Tin's in a bad shape.
Quick, Young Master!
Tin, calm down!
Is he possessed?
Hey.
Who are you?
Did you eat my friend?
Come on. Spit him out! Spit him out now!
It's me!
Did you just yell at me?
Why are you so fierce, Tin?
Hey, Tin.
You can't be fierce like this.
That's my character.
We can't play the same role, okay?
Tin?
Please turn away from the dark side early.
I beg you.
Dealing with Young Master is hard enough.
I can't deal with you too.
Yeah, I agree.
I don't want to feel this way. I'm mad at myself too.
Just don't let that woman control you!
I'm trying, but just seeing her face
makes me so frustrated!
Hey! You know what? Wait a sec.
Young Master? Where are you going, Young Master?
Here you are.
Look at this.
Look at Lisa's MV. Keep watching it.
Look at her cute face and forget that woman's face, okay?
I'll show you how to dance.
Hey!
If I can't escape her in this life,
please put Lisa's album in my coffin.
- Tin!   - Help him!
Revive him!
- For god sake!   - Tin, wake up!
Tin, please be okay.
- Do it properly!   - How, Young Master?
How? Take a deep breath.
Tin, wake up!
Yeah. Call me if you feel bad.
Stop thinking about it.
Just sleep.
Read these.
In the future, you will have to help in my gemstone business.
Okay. I'll start reading these tonight.
Don't rush it. It's late. Just get some rest.
I'm not tired yet.
Go to bed.
Okay, sir.
- Good night.   - Good night.
Sleep. Stop reading Twitter.
I need to set my alarm.
Close your eyes.
Good. You're all here.
- Why did you summon us here?   - Why did you summon us here?
What now?
And what's this?
(Meet me at the office at 11 pm.)
(From PD.)
Don't pull this again, Din. I got spooked.
I opened my door and saw this with no one. It was scary.
I thought I got haunted.
Well, you guys sure get scared easily.
Stop! No! Don't!
All of you get scared easily.
Well, let's get to business. It's almost midnight.
Tomorrow, we have an important mission.
It's gone.
This mission can't fail, Aum.
- Make it perfect, okay?   - Yes, sir.
Everything is step-by-step. Don't make a mistake.
Boss.
What's wrong?
Are you having a seizure?
Thanks, Aum. You can go now.
Apo, what's wrong? Why the long face?
I lost something.
You did? What did you lose? Maybe I've seen it.
My MP3 player.
I always carry it with me.
Have you seen it?
No. Do people still use one of those?
I think I left it in my office.
- I have to go now.   - Okay.
Sis said this place will be expanded so that we can see better views.
- Sis, good morning.   - Good morning.
- Num, May.   - Yes?
Have you seen my MP3 player?
MP3?
It's small. There are white earbuds attached.
We've only seen this. It's a measuring tape.
What tape? She's looking for a pair of earbuds.
Where is it?
What are you doing?
Mueang.
Have you seen my MP3 player?
It looks like this.
Why would I have?
Are you still using one of those?
I think I dropped it when you took me here yesterday.
I told you I didn't take you here.
What do I do?
Is it really gone?
Have you asked the Lost and Found booth at the park?
I have. It's not there.
Just buy a new one.
Some things have a sentimental value.
Nothing can replace them.
If you remember anything, tell me.
Hey!
Are you using me again?
Don't play dumb. I'm not helping you this time.
Did someone do something to annoy you today, Young Master?
Number one, Boss. Or number two, Ms. Step...
Ms. Apo.
Do you have a number three?
- As you wish, sir.   - Yeah, it's number three.
Both of them.
You can talk to me. I won't tell anyone.
Are they crazy?
They are having a huge event in this economy.
Boss probably wants a small party before the wedding.
- You know about it?   - Of course I do.
I've been helping Boss.
You've been helping him?
I've been getting free meals too.
Why did you sell yourself so easily?
I said I would reward you,
but no one gave me a good report on Apo.
I haven't seen anything wrong from Ms. Apo, Young Master.
Go away! Get your butt out of here!
Wait, Young Master.
Are you coming to the party this evening?
Look at my face.
Do I look like I'm in the mood for a party?
I'm not going!
Yes, sir.
You're not going. I get it. Just say it nicely.
- I'm leaving.   - Yeah.
(If someone sees an MP3 player,)
(please let me know.)
(Okay!)
Ms. Apo.
What's this?
Mr. Phudin sends your outfit for the party.
Party?
What party?
Don't you know we're having a party?
I don't.
Judging by how serious this is,
I bet someone just gave birth or came back from abroad.
You will find out at the party. I'll send you the location.
Please check it out.
This... Whoa! This is...
What kind of party is this for?
I almost forgot.
You need this to complete your get-up.
Welcome to the survival game.
If you don't want to die,
prepare your weapons.
From this moment on, it's about your own survival.
Ready!
Go!
Phing?
Om?
Hey, everyone looks so cool!
Well done!
- You like it. We're happy!   - You like it. We're happy!
Phing, I missed you.
I missed you more.
I missed you too.
Why didn't you tell me before you came back?
Mr. Phudin wanted to surprise you. We couldn't tell.
How was it?
Did you like it?
Phing said you liked survival movies, so I did this.
See? How was it?
I like it.
What are we celebrating anyway?
You don't know what this party is about?
It's your birthday, Apo!
- Yeah!   - Whoa!
How did you forget?
Really? Is it my birthday today?
Yeah! What day else could it be?
Can you forget your own birthday?
You can, I guess.
Why did you?
It's just who she is. It's normal. She forgets everything.
I've been so busy I haven't looked at the dates.
It's not the first time my sister forgets her own birthday.
It's not important. It's just a birthday.
Ever since I lost my parents, I have never celebrated my birthday.
I really didn't expect this party to be for me.
Don't tell me I was the first one to throw you a birthday party.
Really?
If I had known, I would have made it even bigger!
- Awesome!   - More!
This is already huge.
I'm so touched. Thank you so much, Mr. Phudin.
- Thank all of you too.   - Welcome.
Do you like it?
If you do, I'll dance ten more rounds. I love it! When I dance...
Boem, you liar!
Ms. Stepmother, he misses every rehearsal.
I only missed one!
We didn't miss a single rehearsal.
Guys! It turned out awesome because I choreographed the entire thing.
You're taking the credit again!
Let me shine for once.
Here comes the Queen!
Hello.
Wi? Why are you dressed as Nakhee?
- No! She's Dae Jang Geum.   - No! She's Dae Jang Geum.
No!
We've got a new show now.
I'm the Zombified Queen.
Scary!
Araji?
Jee, my butt!
Din! I spent a long time getting dressed.
I was the last to make my entrance.
You shouldn't have come.
I'm sorry. Wi is family, so I invited her.
It's good you invited Ms. Wi and Mrs. Sita.
This is going to be so much fun.
Is everyone here?
No! More people are coming.
- More?   - Yeah.
Happy birthday, Ms. Apo.
Ing and Game said they were still in town,
so I invited them.
We're really sorry. We had one day to get costumes. We weren't prepared.
Game, you fiend!
Sorry!
My friend is too drunk. She's going to vomit.
I'll sober her up!
That way, ma'am.
- When did she get drunk?   - I don't know.
What did she drink?
Why didn't you let me smack him in the face?
- Calm down.   - Yeah, Apo. Let me give it to him!
Calm down, both of you.
Mr. Phudin doesn't know about us.
So how did they come to your party?
Game's new girlfriend knows Mr. Phudin.
What?
The woman with him is his new girlfriend?
- This just gets good.   - Hey!
Calm down!
Phing, listen to me.
I know you don't want to do as I'm about to ask,
but please act like you don't know Game.
- Are you mad?   - Om, you too. Please?
- What's wrong?   - Please?
I don't want to ruin the mood.
The mood was ruined the moment Game stepped foot in here, dude.
That's right!
It's my fault.
I should have told Mr. Phudin about Game.
I was just afraid it would affect his business.
So, you let it affect your life instead?
Why are you always like this?
You care about others,
and it ruins you every time.
I promise.
After this party, I'll tell Mr. Phudin about Game.
Do you promise you'd tell him?
Fine.
Because if you don't,
I'll tell him myself.
Deal.
I want to smack his face so badly.
Who was that woman?
She's Apo's best friend.
She probably knows about us.
What the heck is this?
Did we make a mistake coming here?
We didn't. Don't forget our objective.
Repeat it.
Find out how Apo got together with Mr. Phudin.
That's right.
But Ms. Ing, this is not the place and time to do it.
Apo might have told Mr. Phudin about us.
No! I think she hasn't told him yet.
He wouldn't have invited us if she had.
He might have invited us to make a fool of us.
Uncle Phudin and I have always been on good terms.
It's you that might have been the reason he refused to mine Siamese ruby.
You must figure it out with Apo. Is that clear?
Who is that?
Do you think I'm scared of you?
Zombie Mueang.
What kind of person likes to watch zombie movies?
What did you say?
My kind, that is.
Scary.
It's not scary.
It's fun. It's like watching my own life.
Why?
Hey, you can talk normally.
No, I need to stay in character.
Thank you for coming to my birthday party.
I think this look suits you better than your usual look.
Really?
For your sore throat.
Thanks again.
Wait.
Apo!
What are you doing here?
Everyone is looking for you. Come on!
It's time. Come on!
- Come on!   - Wait.
Wait for what? Nothing's there. People are waiting.
Come on!
Slow down. You will trip.
- Happy birthday to Apo!   - Happy birthday to Apo!
Thank you, Mr. Phudin.
Thank you everyone.
You've finally found happiness, Apo.
Thanks, buddy.
This is a present from me.
Take it.
I don't know if it can make up for your lost MP3 player,
but you can listen to music on that one.
Thank you.
I know it can't replace that one.
You're attached to something because of your memory.
Even if we have lost the item,
the memory is still there.
At first, I was sad that it was lost,
but
it's probably for the best.
It will help me let go of old things
and have a fresh start.
Awesome. Fresh start.
Let's give a round of applause for Apo's fresh start.
- Fresh start!   - Fresh start!
Everyone here knows who this necklace belonged to!
This necklace is mine!
I can give it to whomever I want!
- Go on.   - I'm here to buy your Siamese ruby necklace.
If I could give you this necklace, I would,
but I can't because your dad told me to treasure it.
I can't let this go.
This is a must-have.
If I have something important to you to trade with it,
would you go against my dad's wish?
What's that something important?
Meet me at my house at four. Bring the necklace.
Since you're cruel to me,
I don't have to be kind to you!
Mueang!
- Apo!   - Apo!