Are you traveling alone?
- Let's travel together, shall we?   - Sure.
(I thought it was a good night for both of us.)
(However, I was wrong.)
I want you to meet my soon-to-be new wife.
Who is she?
You can ask her yourself. There she is.
I said, do you love my dad?
I don't love him.
- If you don't, why are you getting married?   - Mueang.
Don't pull this stunt again.
My sense tells me she's up to no good.
You need to keep an eye on her. Tell me what you know.
I found out how she came to marry Uncle Din.
- (How is it?)   - It's pretty smooth, Aunt Da.
There's no problem at all.
Is the house big? Let me see it.
(They must be so rich.)
(Can I visit you?)
(Get back here, Ri.)
- Get back. Po.   - Hey, Om.
Run away, Po. Just run.
Where can I run to, Om?
(America, Canada, or Australia. Just move to another country.)
- Take this.   - Ouch.
No matter where you run to, I can take you back anyway.
(And don't forget this. Don't disappear on me again.)
(And don't try to live happily by yourself.)
You have to pay back for what your parents did.
(Aunt Da)
(Aunt Da - 20 missed calls, Ri - 15 missed calls, Om - 10 missed calls)
(Where are you? You didn't answer my call.)
I'm sorry, Aunt Da.
I muted my phone.
Come back home right now.
What happened, Aunt Da?
What?
I'll get back as soon as I can.
I might be there by 3 pm.
Aunt Da, has Mr. Phudin arrived?
Don't be stupid. You would have seen him by now.
Why did he suddenly decide to demand money from us again?
We pay him every month.
I don't know. Isn't it strange?
You're back?
Ri.
What have you been doing all day long? You're so useless.
Ri, were you sleeping here again?
Well, you weren't here.
No one took me upstairs, so I slept here.
- Are you alright?   - Yes. It's just a hangover.
- Mom.   - What?
I'm hungry. Do we have any food?
I have nothing for you.
You only sleep and eat all day long.
Here.
I'm so glad that my servant is back here again.
Hey.
Po isn't your servant, Ri.
That's disgusting.
Om, you play games all day long. You've never made money to help Mom.
This is my way of making money.
When I'm famous, don't talk to me anymore.
There aren't many people who watch your livestream.
- You suck.   -  No, you suck.
You're looking down on my dream. Look at Po.
Although she isn't my real sister, she's taken care of me better than you.
- Om, you... Come here.   - What are you doing? What?
- Stop.   - Come here. Come back here.
- Let me go.   - Wait.
Stop!
Mr. Phudin is here.
Mom, did you tell Po the truth?
What truth?
The money you made...
Mom used it all for gambling.
Is that true, Aunt Da?
I haven't paid Mr. Phudin back for half a year now.
Rita, go open the gate. Quick. Yes, you.
Go right now. Now.
Half a year, Aunt Da? How could you do this?
You have no right to say that to me.
I've sacrificed myself for your family for long enough. If your parents
didn't take a loan and used me as a guarantor,
I would never be in this much trouble.
Do you understand?
Welcome.
Hello, Mr. Phudin.
I miss you so much. We haven't seen each other for a long time.
I'm here to talk to you.
Please come into our house, Mr. Phudin.
Do we have any space to talk together? Just two of us.
Yes.
I'm sorry
for not paying you back for half a year.
We'll try to find money to pay you back again.
Where can you find it?
Aren't you unemployed?
I know that you're the only one who's trying to make money,
not Darin.
For today,
I have an offer for you
in exchange for canceling your debt.
I'm not sure if you'll be interested.
What offer?
You'll marry me.
- Marry you?   - Yes.
- The condition is that you...   - No.
No.
I won't marry you to pay off our debt.
Don't you want to listen to it first?
No.
No matter how good it is, I won't do it.
Well, I can't force you.
I promise I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
Please give me around three or four months.
If you change your mind, contact me.
Yes.
Goodbye.
Po, what did Mr. Phudin say?
Two million baht by next month?
Why is it that quick? Did you make him upset?
You're the cause of this, Mom. Stop blaming this on Po.
I asked you if you made him upset.
I rejected Mr. Phudin's offer.
What offer?
He...
He asked me to marry him.
Ew, marry him to pay off our debt?
Po, it's good that you refused him.
No one will make you marry him.
You must marry Mr. Phudin.
Mom.
Mom, are you crazy?
Yes, you can call me crazy.
You should do what Mr. Phudin tells you to do.
- Mom, this is too much.   - What?
It's not too much, is it?
Think about it.
How many times
have both of you lost your opportunities because of this debt?
Rita and Om didn't get to study abroad because of you.
That's true.
Mom, can you stop talking about this?
Isn't it true? If I didn't have to use my money for this debt,
you'd be comfortable by now.
Anyway, Po isn't at fault for that.
She didn't even know that her parents took a loan.
They took a loan for her education.
I'll tell Mr. Phudin that you change your mind.
Mom.
I beg you, Mom.
Think about it. If she died in a car accident one day,
wouldn't we be in debt for all our lives?
Even if you have to get married,
even if you have to do anything for him,
you have to handle it yourself.
Stop dragging everyone else down with you.
Understand?
Mom, we have to talk about this.
It's true.
(Stop dragging everyone else down with you.)
Ri, what's wrong?
It's fine, Ri. I'm here now.
Don't talk to me.
I don't get to learn ballet now because of you.
Mom wouldn't let me anymore.
(Rita and Om didn't get to study abroad because of you.)
Mom, can I go to summer school in England?
Do we have money?
What did you use to buy your handbag?
Handbags are more expensive every year. It's a worthwhile investment.
Can you invest in my future, then?
My friend's parents all sent them there.
I'm sorry
that I'm not as good as your friend's parents.
Can you pay for it first? I'll try to return the money to you later.
If you can do that,
you should just pay off our debt first.
I'm sorry, Om.
For what?
You didn't get to study in England.
You worried too much.
It's not your fault.
I'll try to save money for you.
No. It's not a big deal.
I'll just apply for a scholarship.
I'm pretty good, you know?
Trust me.
You should smile.
Smile.
(If I didn't have to use my money for this, you'd be comfortable by now.)
Yes. I'll transfer it to you at the end of the month.
For sure. Trust me.
Yes.
Hello, Aunt Da.
You're back?
Aunt Da.
I'll transfer the money from tutoring this month to you.
It's not enough.
Do you know
that every time I see your face,
what do I think of?
"Unfortunate."
The only thing I can see from your face is that word.
It's on there.
I'm so unfortunate...
Po, don't cause trouble for others when you grow up.
Yes, Mom.
The trouble that came from us
has to be handled by us.
Don't let others take the fall for it.
Understand?
Yes.
Did you change your mind?
I'll gladly do anything
that you want me to do, except marriage.
We're in the digital age. Do we still have people marry to pay off debt?
What do you say? Aren't you here to pay off your debt?
So, what then?
Pathetic.
Yeah. My life is pathetic like that.
Why are you like this?
You don't look like that kind of person.
The woman you used to know
and the woman I am right now is different.
Which one is the real you?
Hey.
This one.
I know it looks crazy,
but don't judge anyone's decision before you know them well enough.
It's not that I don't know you well enough.
I just don't know you at all.
You...
You're just greedy.
And what's wrong with that?
I thought you'd love yourself more than this.
- Didn't your parents teach you to value yourself...   - Hey.
You can rebuke me however you want but don't talk about my parents.
Then, stop doing this.
There are millions of other ways to pay off debt.
I chose this way.
You don't know everything, Mueang.
Your world and mine are different.
You can marry me instead.
If my dad owns your debt, it means I also own your debt.
I won't marry you.
- Why?   - It's...
It's...
It can't be you, that's why.
I already agreed to marry your dad. Understand?
Stop talking about useless stuff. Can we talk about the main matters now?
Can you forget about that night?
Think of it as...
As something fun that we did in the heat of the moment.
Like...
A one-night stand.
- Can you?   - No. No way!
Stop talking about that night. I don't want to hear it anymore.
Okay.
Then...
We can make it like nothing happened.
We've never known each other before. Alright?
Who do you think you are? Trying to argue with me.
Mueang.
Don't make it harder than this.
Do you want an easy way out?
I'm sorry that I don't want to do that.
Don't ever think you can come, stay, and leave easily.
Nothing will be as easy as you think.
Sita, tell Wi and Apo to meet me in the living room.
Okay.
Stop.
Open the door.
Just say what you want.
Ten million baht for a new wife. Is it worth it?
Our opinions on what's worth it are different.
You might run out of money easily, you know?
- Thank you for your concern.   - I'm not concerned.
So, are you jealous?
I'm possessive of my mom's legacy.
What do I need to do to stop this wedding?
You're even worse than I thought.
Tell me.
Do you have ten million, then?
So, you want ten million?
You really don't want me to get married that much?
Yes.
Why?
It's not like that.
You can get married, but you can't get married to her.
I'm sorry. Apo...
She's just my type.
Even if you have 100 million baht, I won't change my mind.
Then, why did you say that?
It's fun for me to see you furious. I like it.
What did you do to Apo?
No.
I didn't do anything.
I saw everything. You took away Apo's food.
Am I a dog or what?
This.
Did you set up cameras inside the house?
You aren't the only one here who can buy stuff online.
Apologize to Apo now.
Quick.
I'm sorry.
Your punishment is
that from now on, you have to receive your packages by yourself.
Din...
I can't wake up in time for that.
Then, don't buy anything anymore. Our house is full of stuff now.
If I find out that you
do something to Apo again,
I'll cut you off from every streaming service.
Don't cry. Take this.
Let's go, Apo.
Please stop.
If not, you won't get to watch the Korean series.
Darn it.
I have to apologize to you again.
My house is full of weirdos.
Are you sure you're alright? You looked stressed earlier.
I'm okay.
Look.
I'm the only one who can help you in this house.
If you aren't honest with me,
I won't know how to help you.
I want time.
Everything happened too fast.
I'm still a little confused.
Sure.
You can think about it again.
I won't change my mind.
I have already decided on something. I won't turn back to it.
Why is he
acting like a heartbroken man?
Just go to bed. I'll handle it.
Good night.
Don't be too dramatic.
I'm not, though.
Do you think you can trick me?
When we were in grade two,
you stole an eraser from your crush.
I still caught you.
I know what you feel.
You already told me everything
about how good you felt at the sea.
Why don't you just tell Uncle Din about you and Apo?
So that it'll be over.
I'll watch her for now.
You still haven't stopped.
- Stop what?   - You haven't stopped sulking.
I'm not sulking.
Look.
I'll tell you something.
You didn't like her. You were just charmed.
If she didn't come here for a week,
you'd already forget about her.
(It's something fun that we did in the heat of the moment.)
(Like a one-night stand.)
(You said you didn't have your phone.)
(You're addicted to social networks. Delete it. Did you delete it?)
(If I could turn back the time...)
Someone is drowning.
I'll help you.
Thank you so much.
(It'd be better if we didn't meet each other.)
Human hearts
are really difficult to understand.
That's why I don't want to get involved with people.
Do you agree with me?
What do you say, Pinkie?
Jenny.
Peter.
Alexandra.
You agree with me, right?
Everyone, Boss' new wife is here.
This is serious. She's really beautiful.
Boss brings his new wife here. I repeat, Boss brings his new wife here.
Oh my god. Our boss is pretty good, isn't he?
We have to get back here. He'll introduce her to us when they're done.
- Roger that.   - Roger that.
Roger that.
She's Apo, my soon-to-be wife.
Hello.
- Hello.   - Hello.
I'll be in your care.
Yes.
From today onwards, Apo will work here.
I'd like all of you to get to know her.
- Of course.   - Of course.
Good. Everyone, you can go back to work now except Son.
Me?
What's wrong, Boss?
Has Mueang gone to Bo Phloi today?
He hasn't gone there.
Then, when you're done with work, please take Apo there.
- Let's go.   - Let's go.
That place.
Of course, Boss.
Oh my god.
He's here.
What's wrong? Hey...
- Ouch. What's wrong with you?   - Come here. Come here now.
Son, what did Boss tell you?
Boss told me to bring Ms. Stepmother to Bo Phloi.
- Stepmother?   - Yes. What's wrong?
Soon, Ms. Apo will become our young master's stepmother.
Of course, we have to call her that.
Well, I understand that.
But why did Boss want you to take her to Bo Phloi?
Yeah. Won't she get killed by Young Master?
Poe, are you sadistic or what?
My young master is a nice guy with a nice face.
He's not cruel or sadistic like you thought.
Hey, you're just taking your superior's side.
Your young master
is really scary, you know?
Since I worked here,
I haven't seen him smile ever.
But I have.
I've seen his cold smile.
- How?   - He was smirking like this.
He looked down like this.
He also said...
What are you talking about?
- I really saw that.   - It's you who's scary.
Let me say something.
As a so-called annoyed person,
I'm not annoyed. I'm just hot.
You're annoyed right now.
Your eyes are scary.
If you want to protect him that much, you should just be his girlfriend.
Then, should we break up now, Poe?
Ging, you can't say that to me.
- You challenged me yourself.   - It hurts, you know?
You're always trying to make yourself look tough.
- Ging.   - You...
- Hey, stop that. You're like dogs.   - Please stop.
Stop, you Pomeranian. Stop, you Shih Tzu.
You two just can't break up every day like this.
I always have a headache from being with you.
All of you, get to work. The park is almost open now.
If there's anything, I'll tell you all about it.
Ging, let's go. Come with me.
Go.
You have to make up with me later.
Look at her.
You also have to go to work, Poe. Gosh.
Young Master.
What's this sign? Why is it here again?
Right, Young Master.
Bad news.
Boss is going on an offensive.
He's taking Ms. Stepmother...
He's taking Ms. Apo to the park.
Hello? Young Master?
Is he sleeping?
Is this another hibernation?
You told me to tell you if anything happened.
Here you are. The car is here for you, Ms. Stepmother.
You don't have to call me that. Just call me Po.
I can't do that.
Boss told me to do that.
If not, we'll get scolded by him again.
Ms. Stepmother.
We can go now.
Are you sure you'll go there?
Yes.
Why? What's wrong?
It's nothing.
There's nothing at all.
Shall we go?
This is it.
This is the place where Boss wants me to take you to.
Young Master's Bo Phloi.
You can take a look at it.
Yes.
- This way?   - Yes, that way.
This is it, Ms. Stepmother.
Follow this path, and you'll see Bo Phloi.
- Thank you.   - Please wait a second.
Are you sure you'll go there?
Yes. I have to go there anyway.
Well, you can go there first.
I'll come back with cold water for you.
- Thank you.   - You're welcome.
You can go inside.
Good luck.
(The way to Bo Phloi)
Have you asked the owner before coming in?
What you're doing is a crime.
Do you think you can come here easily?
I'll let you know that Son is my people.
(I heard Apo was at the park.)
(Do you have anything to tell me?)
(You read my message but didn't answer it. Suspicious.)
Oh no...
(I'm sorry.)
(So what?)
(Boss asked me to take Ms. Stepmother to Bo Phloi.)
Why are you here?
I'm here for work.
What work?
I have to change this place to become a new spot for Phudin Park.
I'm the landscape architect for this project. Let me go.
I don't allow it. Get out of here right now.
If you don't get out, I'll throw you in a hole.
You're good at threatening someone.
It's not a threat.
I'm serious.
Fine. I'll leave.
I'm leaving
not because I'm scared
but because my work is done.
We can talk later when your mood is better.
I won't talk to you.
Get out.
Get out and don't come back.
Leave.
Young Master.
Where have you been?
Do you know what he wants her to do at Bo Phloi?
I know even more than that.
What?
Tell me what you know.
Boss appointed Ms. Apo as an executive.
They said she had a 200,000 baht salary.
- A salary of 200,000 baht?   - Yes.
I think she isn't here to pay off her debt.
She's here to rob us.
Fine.
If you want to be a thief that much,
we'll see.
Whom did he talk to?
Apo!
Where are you?
Come out here.
Apo!
I'm here.
You're the one who summoned me here.
Summoned you here?
I was summoned here because of your desire.
It's because of your strong desire to make money.
That's why I have to come here.
I'll move in and live here.
So that I can watch over you.
- Watch over me for what?   - I'm not sure now
if you're here to pay off your debt
or you're here to rob my dad.
It's not wrong for you to want a rich husband.
But most of everything here is my mom's legacy.
I won't allow you to take it away.
I didn't come here to take anything.
I'll keep myself close to you.
- Are you crazy?   - If you behave suspiciously,
I'll throw you out of the house.
From this moment on,
you will be under my watch 24/7.
What?
Mueang.
What's this?
What's going on?
He's crazy.
(From this moment on,)
(you will be under my watch 24/7.)
What should I do?
Why does my stomach always act up
whenever I'm stressed?
I'm getting goosebumps now.
I can't stand it anymore.
There's another one coming.
What's that sound?
What's this again?
I haven't finished my business yet.
It's a sin to stop someone from finishing their business.
Get back. Get back in. Get in.
What are you doing?
Installing a peephole to watch you.
Do you have to do this much?
Yes.
Be nice.
I'm always watching you.
You're playing with the wrong person.
It's too obvious.
He's acting like he's doing some push-ups.
Coffee or me?
Did he just warp? He's too quick.
He can't follow me here.
Come out. I need to pee.
Darn it. I'm getting crazy.
Come out.
Go use another toilet. You have a lot of them.
No. I want to use this one.
Come out.
I'll break into it.
You can come. I left a big pile of poop in the toilet.
Go in.
(For someone like me,)
(whenever I'm curious,)
(nothing can stop me.)
(No matter how deep you try to hide it,)
(I'll still dig it up.)
(I have to know if you get close to my dad for...)
(Social network users share posts about "poop relieving medicine.")
Poop relieving medicine?
How could you look at my laptop's screen? That's so rude.
I thought you were doing something suspicious.
You're being secretive.
So, you're just trying to find a way to stop taking poop?
I understand why this place stinks now.
You should learn your manners. I can't stand it anymore.
You asked your subordinate to follow me all day the other day.
You're always using the same trick. You're uncreative.
Well, Aum isn't as quick-witted as me.
That's why I have to be close to you.
Why don't you just possess me?
Let your spirit possess my spirit.
So that you'll know what I have on my mind.
Interesting.
And how do I do that?
Possessing you.
Don't you know I was being sarcastic?
Let's begin the ritual.
Mueang? Wait. Hey...
What are you doing? You'll get dizzy for sure.
Mueang.
I'll possess you.
- Ouch. You...   - This is crazy.
- Stop. Come here.   - Don't come closer.
Mueang.
- Let go of my legs.   - No.
Are you scared that my dad will see you?
I'm scared that all the people here will see us.
It's good, then. They'll realize how close we are.
- Ouch.   - Who's close to you?
- You?   - You're crazy.
Mueang is here?
- Mueang, let me go. You won't let me go?   - No way.
You won't let me go? Fine.
- Stop.   - No.
- Mueang, stop. Let me go.   - No.
Darn it.
- I won't let you go.   - Why are you this sticky?
Were you a gecko in your last life?
No. But I won't let you go.
- You won't let me go?   - No.
If you don't let me go...
Wait. What?
Stop there.
Where? Where is he?
Old man, you're back?
What are you doing?
Oh, wow. What a warm welcome for me.
Everyone is here to welcome me.
I'm so touched.
Why did you come back?
What? Do I need any reasons?
Stop blabbering.
I'm moving back to live in this house again.
- Live in this house again?   - Live in this house again?
Yes.
Do you know the word "homesick?" I miss my home.
Who would be stupid enough to believe you? I'll let you answer it again.
No. You're the one who doesn't understand my answer.
(You come back to get rid of Apo, right?)
Din,
Mueang already decided he wanted to move back into the house.
Please don't ruin the atmosphere.
Wait.
Since when have you and Mueang been close?
You've never wanted him to be back.
Well, didn't he say he missed his home?
I also know that you miss your son.
Isn't that right, Sita?
I'll let the family handle this.
I don't have any opinion.
Well, you should have talked to her first.
Din, it's like this.
I know that you also want Mueang to live here again.
Right?
You don't mind, right?
A dad and son want to spend their time together.
How could I say anything?
This is Mueang's house.
Don't you see?
Everyone's okay with it.
You're the only one who's concerned.
I'm concerned because I know you're back to cause trouble.
What? Please look at my face.
Do I look like a bad guy to you?
- Yes.   - Yes.
Are you crazy? But I'm handsome, right?
A handsome man can be a bad guy.
If I'm a bad guy, you're also a bad guy.
Your face didn't even get any of the actor genes from me.
Which era of actors, anyway?
You can use Google to look it up.
Stop.
Can we get back to the main topic? We don't have much time.
What do you say?
Are you letting me live here again?
You can stay here.
See? It's that easy.
Wait. If you ever cause me trouble,
I promise I'll throw you out of this house immediately. Understand?
Yes.
What did you understand?
- I understand what you said.   - What did I say?
- Everything...   - Stop.
Please.
Please lock the door.
Look.
Did anything happen before I came in?
So, you won't let me go? Ouch.
- Hey.   - I won't let you go.
Did you set up cameras inside the house?
Why aren't you answering me?
Mueang has been trying to find fault with me.
Find fault with you?
I've never thought that
you would cause him to be this restless.
Good job.
Mr. Phudin, I have something to ask you.
What is it?
What's wrong between you and Mueang?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have asked.
It's your usual problem between a dad and son.
Why do you want to know that?
If you want me to be his stepmother,
I think I should know about it.
That's unnecessary.
Listen.
Sometimes,
it's not good to know too much of something.
Do you understand what I said?
- Yes.   - Good.
If there's anything I think you need to know,
I'll tell you.
Why didn't you agree with me earlier, Sita?
How could you say you didn't want to offer any opinion?
I don't want to say anything that I'm unsure about.
There's already an example right here.
If we get challenged,
people will say we're stupid.
Please stop with your acting.
I know that you hate her.
Instead of helping me chase her away,
you chose to stay silent.
People have different ways to express themselves.
When will you stop being silent?
Do you want to wait for you to be involved first?
Sita.
You've been taking care of us since we were children. I know
how much you love my big sister.
You're still here
because you want to look after what Nudi has built.
Can you really stand
watching that woman
take everything away from Nudi?
I...
I'll let the family handle it.
You...
Gosh.
I'm so done. Just do whatever you want.
I don't care anymore.
I'll just count on Mueang to handle it for me.
It's 8 pm.
She hasn't come up yet?
Did she just fart?
Do you think I'm scared?
You can't escape my watchful eyes.
Am I in hell right now?
I'll just borrow this for now.
Just you come in.
I'll stab you. Stab you. Stab you like this.
Phing? Phing.
Phing.
Are you in America or hell? You haven't answered my call at all.
Po, calm down.
(You don't have to use the knife to scare me.)
I'm sorry. I forgot I had it.
Are you an assassin or what?
My fever is pretty bad.
I haven't answered any calls for two days. I was sick.
Really? Are you sick?
It's so frustrating. I've had a fever since I arrived at the airport.
I see. It's a shame. I wish you a speedy recovery.
I'm getting better. What about you? How are you?
Have you moved on?
(But you already have a man from the sea to heal you, right?)
Heal what?
It's bad. It's so bad now.
(Why is it bad?)
Tell me about it.
It's like this.
It's over. That's the recap from me. Isn't this bad?
Phing.
Don't tell me you're disconnected.
Hello? Phing?
(It's not that.)
(I was shocked.)
Po, did you choose the hard difficulty when you were born?
- Right?   - (Your life is like a drama.)
It's like a drama plot. A female lead
was forced to marry
a man who was as old as your dad because of necessity.
But in a twist of fate,
that man's son is the man you truly love.
Hold on.
Who loves him?
Po, I think
you'll learn that you have an incurable disease in three or four months.
If not, you might learn that
you're the daughter of a wealthy family.
Phing...
I know the ending of this.
Tell me.
You will end up with Mueang.
Wait. Hold on.
How could it end like that?
It's a happy ending for a romantic drama.
I think you're misunderstanding something.
This drama is a drama about murders.
I'm a corpse that's involved in the story.
It's not that bad. Do you know why?
Because you have a friend like me
who'll save your life, Po.
I think you should stop being a YouTuber and become a scriptwriter instead.
Fine. I'll stop joking. I don't want you to be stressed.
When will you come back?
Around next month. I have to record my trip to America for my vlog.
(I'll immediately visit my best friend as soon as I'm done.)
Don't be sick. Don't die. Understand?
Please come back soon.
(I love you.)
I love you too.
You'll survive, alright?
It's 11 pm.
- Who is it?   - It's me.
Wait, old man?
Why is he here?
Please wait a second.
Let's start with this.
You should just go back, old man.
He's so stubborn.
I'm sorry for being late.
It's fine. Can I go inside?
So, you really won't talk to me?
- I'm still furious.   - Was it fun last night?
- Should I tell you about it?   - No.
Last night, Mr. Phudin brought me a key...
- I said don't tell me.   - After that...
No...
I was looking at my phone, so I bumped into you.
How much is it? I'll buy a new one for you.
I don't want you to misunderstand that I intend to come here to hurt you.
Even if it's unintentional,
I'm already hurt. I already felt it.
(Did I overdo it?)
Cancel this project.
I don't think I can do as you wish.
Don't think that you can easily close down Bo Phloi.