- Why are you here?   - Mr. Phudin sent me to learn about work in Bo Phloi.
Do you have only this much strength?
(Ms. Stepmother, if you actually know him,)
(you'll realize there's nothing wrong with him at all.)
(He's just not good at communicating.)
(He only has goodwill.)
(He never has ill will for anyone.)
You're going in the wrong way.
The relationship between you two will only get worse.
(I know Mueang better than you.)
(How would you know)
(that you know Mueang the best?)
(There might be other things that you didn't know about.)
(From now on, I'll be the one to protect your dreams.)
Tomorrow morning, please come to the house.
I promise I won't waste your time.
I thought I was the only one meeting you here.
Why did you tell him to come here?
Calm down.
I want both of you guys
to talk nicely, please.
- I'm leaving.   - I'm leaving.
All I need is five minutes.
Please, Mueang.
Make it quick.
What do you want?
I think you two actually want to reconcile.
Who? Who would want to reconcile with the old man next door?
Who are you calling the old man next door?
I didn't mention any names.
Are you really my son?
Why are you nothing like me? Darn it!
You're the exact same!
- You're a bootleg version of me!   - You're a bootleg version of me!
Again, exactly the same.
Hey, please stop!
You scratched your butts with the exact same movement.
- Are we different now?   - Are we?
You are!
I think if you both try a little bit harder,
you would...
They don't even listen to me!
Listen, Apo. It's hard for me to talk to Mueang.
It's harder than making a monkey give birth to an egg.
Do you know why I'm sick of people?
It started with my dad.
I'm sure I've been a good dad.
A good dad? The dad who forgot his kid at the mall? How is that a good dad?
Yeah? So you've been a good son who never understands his parents?
Stop! Stop trying.
Apo.
I think you should find another way.
This is hard.
Boem, Poe, please help me.
Ms. Stepmother, if you need our help, just let us know.
We're always on your team.
We're ready to support you.
- Let me go!   - We're here!
- Come on!   - Let me go! Help!
- Did you pick him up just like that?   - We did! And we can't let go!
Ms. Stepmother, ask him if you want to know something. He knows everything.
Okay. Aum, since you've opened up to me about your young master,
please help me one more time.
I want Mr. Phudin and Mueang to do something,
but I don't know how to get both of them on board.
- Die!   - There's one way, ma'am.
Both Boss and Young Master don't like to lose.
Challenging them will probably work.
- Let me go!   - Stay still!
- Mr. Phudin.   - Yeah?
I heard you kidnapped Aum.
Mueang.
It's good you're here.
Now that you're both here,
I have a challenge for both of you.
I'd like to challenge you two to swap your life with another for a month.
Mr. Phudin will live Mueang's life.
Mueang will live Mr. Phudin's life.
This is the best way to make you guys understand each other.
That's playing like a child.
Who would want to switch with you?
Are you afraid to lose?
Living as the old man? How would that be difficult?
Living as Mueang? That's a piece of cake.
Then there's no reason to refuse
if you're not a coward.
- Challenge accepted! Bring it on!   - Challenge accepted! Bring it on!
Young Master, stop! Don't hurt yourself.
Aum! Do you know what's bigger than a titan?
I don't.
My ego!
That's really big.
I shouldn't have accepted her challenge!
Din, I need to talk to you about my store.
Get out if you don't want to get hurt!
Get out of here!
Young Master?
I can't fail. I can't lose.
I won't lose my face.
What?
Do you want to fight?
Bring it on!
To prevent confusion about your switching,
I've informed Mr. Phudin's employees
and Mueang's workers.
Both of you can get to work.
Okay. I'll be on my way.
So will I.
I can't believe it.
You actually got Din and Mueang to switch.
That's creative.
I binge-watched a lot of shows and never came up with that idea.
I'm just trying to find a way for Mr. Phudin and Mueang
to open up to each other.
I think it won't work.
Mr. Phudin and Mr. Mueang will run out of patience before that happens.
That's right.
- Prepare to accept failure.   - Prepare to accept failure.
Let's go.
Keep going, me! I'll do my best!
- What the...   - Beep!
You're censored. Don't swear. Please respect the place.
These are all the documents that Mr. Phudin has to sign.
You don't need to sign it. Just read through everything.
You will find out what Mr. Phudin does.
He has to sign documents all day long.
Doesn't he do anything else?
It's hot!
Do your best, Boss! Don't be afraid!
This is not the world of humans.
This is hell.
This is fricking hell!
- Do your best, Boss!   - Do your best, Boss!
It's so boring!
It's a waste of my time.
Mining crypto will make me richer than mining this!
What the heck is he doing here?
What are you doing?
Whoa!
Stop!
No, stop!
Mueang, we have to stay at least one meter apart.
- Stop that!   - Hey!
It's over.
Did you have fun pranking us?
This is not a prank.
What I did, I mean well.
You mean well?
I'm getting bored to death! I've got a huge pile of files!
You have to calm down and adapt.
You can talk. You're not the one doing it.
Are you giving up?
Mr. Phudin hasn't complained yet.
I didn't say I gave up.
Then do your best.
Do your best.
Hi! Hi, Ms. Apo.
Ms. Ing, are you here to see me?
No.
The only way you can get that necklace
is to have Mueang sell it to you.
I'm here to see Mueang.
Hey, give me your hand.
What?
Have lunch with me.
Are you trying to poison me?
Whoa! Come on!
I just thought we'd be working together for a while,
so it's better to get ourselves acquainted.
No!
Come on, Mueang.
Don't play hard to get.
What do you want? You're being weird.
Do you have a crush on me?
What if I do? Will you date me?
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting for Mrs. Sita.
I'm here to see Mueang.
He's up there, isn't he?
He is.
I won't.
You're not my type.
Wait! Hey, Mueang!
I said no! Why would you follow me? What's wrong with you?
- Where are you going?   - Tin!
You're late. I'm starving.
- Let's go.   - Why are you so hungry?
- What should we have today?   - What would you like?
Ms. Apo, why is Mueang working in Uncle Din's office?
What? Ms. Ing has a crush on you?
Yeah! She likes me, not Apo.
Your courage is a five,
but your confidence is a ten, bro. Nice!
Hey, I'm serious.
Why else would she ask me out?
I believe you, bro. Just pretend you don't understand.
She will stop when she's bored.
Just don't be too mean to her.
Hey, wait.
Why are you so nice to her?
You said you hated her.
When did I say that?
Whoa, man!
Let's forget about her.
We should talk about you switching with Uncle Din.
What's got into you?
Tell me.
Mueang switched with Uncle Din?
Yeah.
Is it okay to tell me, though?
It's okay. It's not a secret.
So, can I join in?
Join in?
Yeah.
I want to see Mueang and Uncle Din reconcile too.
I'll do my best to help.
You want to get involved.
I'm ready.
How was your first day?
Old man.
Let me ask you this. You have projects all over the place.
Don't you want to have an inch of nature?
Why would I?
It's better to make money.
You should start thinking like I do.
If I leave everything as it is, when will we get rich?
How much money do you need to be rich?
A hundred million? A billion?
All we need is enough to pay our employees and make a living for ourselves.
That's it. Employees?
Why don't you use machines to save on labor?
Look at my mine.
I have only a few workers.
Your machines destroy the environment.
Which do you think is better?
- What?   - My way or Mueang's way.
Answer me honestly.
Both of your ways have pros and cons.
Whoa! That's a Miss Universe's answer.
It's true.
You know what? I'll give you time to think.
I'll ask you again later.
Think carefully. Me or Mueang.
Take this card. It's got an unlimited balance.
You're not trying to pay me to say you win, are you?
No, I don't have to bribe with this little challenge.
This! This is obviously a bribe!
I just thought you might want some new clothes.
Maybe you want a new pair of designer shoes,
a bag, or an acc...
Thank you,
but please don't think for me.
I think you should head to Bo Phloi.
Oh! Don't forget to water Mueang's plants.
The target
cannot be bought.
This way, please, Boss.
Our next task is to water the plants.
- Water the plants?   - Yes.
Din!
I'll be helping you.
No need. Give it to me. I'll do it myself.
Come on.
Please talk with the plants, Boss.
Are you mad? Why would I talk to them?
Young Master always talks to them.
Talks to the plants?
He does. When he was young
and felt lonely,
Young Master turned to plants
and made them his friends.
Guys.
What does Mueang talk to you about?
Do the plants talk?
- I didn't hear a thing.   - Oh!
How does he talk to them?
Talking is my expertise. Talking to myself is my specialty.
Move it, Din.
(Speaking gibberish)
This one looks like it's well-fed.
You have good photosynthesis. You're nice and green.
We understand each other
because we communicate with our hearts.
I haven't talked to Mueang so much that he has to talk to plants?
While The Maze project is on hold,
I'll pitch another project to Mr. Phudin. I'll give you a brief.
Okay, sis.
- There's a space that's way out...   - Knock-knock!
Are these foods for us?
You bought a lot!
Yeah. I saw how you guys always work overtime.
- Thank you, Brother Mueang.   - Thank you, Brother Mueang.
What? Wait!
Since when do you consider him your bro?
Since now, right?
Yeah.
- That's right.  - We'll leave these here, for now, sis. Let's eat later.
Don't eat without us!
Hey.
Are you trying to bribe the judges?
Do you want to make sure I pick you as the winner?
No!
I just thought they were probably hungry.
Don't do that!
Aren't you taking this challenge too seriously?
Also, both the dad and the son know how to bribe.
I'm not like him. Don't think I'm the same as my old man.
Look. You have to oversee the construction for Mr. Phudin today.
Why are you still here?
Do you
want to lose?
Do you? You're losing.
Get going.
Mr. Mueang, Mr. Phudin's employees are here to see you.
- Fine, bring them in.   - Okay.
Please come in.
- Young Master?   - Yes?
Has Boss contacted Master Bee?
Who's Master Bee?
The fortune teller who's been accurate.
A fortune teller?
My old man doesn't believe in this stuff, does he?
He didn't in the past,
but he has become so concerned for you.
What does it have to do with me?
Boss is afraid he'll die, so he wants to see the future.
He's concerned that when he's gone, will you be okay?
This guy is too much!
Tell him I'll be fine. Don't worry.
- Okay!   - Leave. This is nonsense.
I'm not seeing any fortune tellers.
- Will this be okay?   - I don't know.
You know what? I'll give you time to think.
I'll ask you again later.
(Think carefully.)
(Me or Mueang.)
You're clumsy.
Next time, use this
so you won't waste paper.
Not going home yet?
I need to read some more things.
I'll be in this room with you.
We need to save on electricity.
Am I handsome?
What are you asking?
You've been staring at me.
Am I your type?
Where did that confidence come from?
Are you my type? No.
Never ever!
Ms. Apo, do you have a type?
My type?
- Aum, show me how.   - Bend down, Young Master.
- A bit harder. It's not easy, Young Master.   - Harder?
- Yeah. That's good.   - Harder, Young Master. Keep it tight.
- Yeah! Use your waist!  - Is this it?
- Young Master, you got it!   - Is this right?
Are you ready, Young Master?
(A funny)
(and sexy guy.)
So, do you have a type?
I don't.
Not at all?
I really don't.
Once I grew up, I didn't really have a type. Just someone who understands.
Why did you ask?
I didn't mean your type for a boyfriend.
I meant the type of plants you like.
You want some plants for your desk, don't you?
I do.
Why did you say type? It's confusing.
Choosing plants is like choosing a partner.
It's totally different.
Okay. It's different.
I'm sorry for using the wrong word.
What you said
triggered my curiosity.
What kind of guys do you like?
That's more like it.
You spooked me!
I'm sorry.
I don't forgive you. I'm two million percent sure.
You needed to talk to me. What is it?
Please sit down.
Last night, I checked last year's revenue.
Since when have we been suffering losses?
Let me ask you this first.
What are your boundaries for this switch?
We're just learning each other's lives.
The power and decision remain the same in each of our own jobs.
Okay.
Then I can tell you this.
Phudin Park might be closing down.
(I know Phudin Park is not as important as Bo Phloi to you,)
(but this place is your dad's life work.)
(He's trying to hold on to it.)
(He's barely hanging on, though.)
Mueang, if you want to ride an elephant, ride me first.
- Let's go!   - Come on. Turn around.
Are you ready? One, two, three!
- Are you okay, Din? Be careful!   - Whoa!
Don't fall off!
- Be careful!   - Left and right!
Forward and back.
Be careful, son!
(Even if it's closed down,)
(you wouldn't feel a thing, would you?)
Go and help out.
- Son.   - Yes?
Although Bo Phloi is closing down,
I'm not leaving you guys behind. You know that, right?
We know, Boss.
What are you afraid of then?
I'll still get to work at Phudin Park,
but for those other guys,
the jobs you offer
are out of reach for some of them.
Those who didn't graduate will have to leave and work low-paying jobs.
All of us right now
are making a good living with Young Master.
He even gives us sick days off.
It doesn't mean I won't take care of you guys.
Well, Boss.
It's unfair if you're the only one taking care of us.
We all want to make ourselves useful.
We all want to take care of both of you together.
But
if you really have to close it down,
we all understand, Boss.
- Let's go.   - Sorry!
It's fine.
These are all must-read for you, Mr. Mueang.
All of this?
This is not all. You have two more batches coming tomorrow.
- There's more?   - Yes. You'll get it tomorrow.
Whoa. This...
I'll just take this for now.
Okay, Mr. Mueang.
(Ms. Apo, do you have a type?)
Hold the file.
Look at it after I walk away.
Hi, Ms. Apo. Go get dressed up!
Ms. Ing, how did you know we're doing an exercise?
Aunt Wi told me.
She said from now on, everyone has to gather in the afternoon.
It's to improve the relationship between Uncle Din and Mueang, right?
Yeah.
Can I join you, please? Pretty please.
Okay. You're welcome to join, Ms. Ing.
Yay! Come on, Ms. Apo. Let's rehearse.
Come on.
Why are you here? Who called you?
I invited him.
Oh, okay.
If we want Mueang and Uncle Din to reconcile quickly,
we need to bring back the old atmosphere from when they were happy. Agree?
I agree. We can bring back the good memories.
I remember. I came over to his house as a child.
They did group activities. They were very cute.
For a healthy relationship in the family.
Healthy relationship!
- Fight!   - Fight!
Pathetic.
Look at you. You're a woman in her 20s.
You're bold to lead.
Okay, everyone.
Let's get ourselves warmed up.
Let's start with our heads. Move your head around.
Okay. Next is the shoulders.
Swing your arms.
Shake your waist. Yeah, shake it! Now, legs!
Thank you so much for coming today, everybody.
I think it's really nice that we meet every afternoon.
Maybe we can talk more.
It's good for your health.
Ms. Apo, you're awesome.
So
let's get started.
- Hi. This is Bebe's Fit Routine...   - Bebe?
Are you ready, guys?
Let's go!
Let's go, guys!
Jump up! Jump and bounce!
- Are you alright?   - Give me a break.
Punch!
The world is not fair!
Bebe still looks fine after this workout.
Ms. Apo.
I think this is too brutal to invoke nostalgia.
Right now, I'm thinking of my next life.
Next life,
I wish it didn't exist. I'm tired.
The equipment you need is here.
Don't forget what we talked about.
When Mueang and Uncle Din reconcile,
tell them they have me to thank too.
The next activity
is the hula hoop. Guys, shake it!
Let's go!
Okay.
Can you do it, sweetie?
- Come on, Mueang.   - One, two, three.
Shake it, Din.
- Shake as hard as you can. Are you ready?   - Bring it.
Stop!
I know what you're trying to do.
Don't do this again.
Young Master?
Din?
I told you it won't work.
Wait, Mueang.
You still blame me, don't you?
I told you. Before your mom passed away,
your mom and I
had already cleared everything up.
We agreed to divorce.
If we had tried to drag it on,
it wouldn't have been good for you.
I'm sorry for everything.
I'm sorry too.
Have a safe travel.
Thanks.
So
when I come back, we'll file the divorce.
I have to go.
Okay.
Be back soon, Mom.
I'll miss you.
I'll be back soon.
Do you still don't understand?
I've never blamed you for Mom's death.
However, after she passed away,
have you ever been a good father to me?
When I needed you,
where were you?
(I've never blamed you for Mom's death.)
(However, after she passed away,)
(have you ever been a good father to me?)
(You still blame me, don't you?)
(I told you. Before your mom passed away,)
(your mom and I had already cleared everything up.)
(When I needed you,)
(where were you?)
(We agreed to divorce.)
(If we had tried to drag it on,)
(it wouldn't have been good for you.)
You didn't sleep, did you?
Thank you.
I didn't come last night.
I thought you needed some time alone.
I got to think about a lot of things.
I said I knew Mueang well.
It was all in my head.
The movies he liked,
the music he liked,
the girl he had a crush on,
I never knew any of that.
Then, you can use this time
to get to know all about Mueang.
Yeah.
- Nut. Check the packages and send some photos to the buyers.   - Yes?
- Okay.   - Handle them with care when you ship them.
- I'm counting on you.   - Okay.
- Surprise!   - Surprise!
Dad, Mom, why are you here?
Do you like her?
If you do, swipe right. If you don't, swipe left.
Whoa. What are you doing?
This is not a dating app.
What about this one?
Stop. That's enough.
You guys said you wouldn't force me again in this life.
You're too slow.
Did I give you too much freedom, TinTin?
I'm good.
TinTin, your dad and I are worried you'll be alone when you're old.
Dad, Mom, don't worry.
I talked to Mueang about this.
If we don't have anyone when we're old, we'll get a nursing home.
My gosh!
Stop and leave. Go home. I need to pack my shipment.
What about this one?
How is she on the list?
Ever since you were a kid,
this style of women has been your favorite, right?
Right.
Don't know me too much.
Honey, that means this one has a chance.
Is that right?
- Admit it.   - Whoa!
I'm going out.
Young Master.
Are you all right?
Young Master?
Young Master!
Young Master won't see anyone today.
Wait.
He called in sick, so I came to check him out.
Well, he's in a bad shape.
Aum!
Is it done?
I've been waiting.
What's so funny? You're a bully.
Sorry.
I'm ugly, right?
You're not. You're kind of cute.
That's so fake.
Go back to where you come from.
Before you go,
please look for Aum.
Aum headed out to buy your medicine. It has run out.
You need to get up and eat. When Aum gets back, you'll take your pills.
Get up.
Go back already.
It's not serious. I'll be fine tomorrow.
I will.
Did Aum buy this?
No, I ordered it.
Why didn't you get the beansprouts?
You don't eat it, do you?
How did you know?
I remember.
I said no beansprouts.
Eat up.
I bought two, just in case.
There's also Lod Chong
and muskmelon with lots of coconut milk, your favorite.
Look.
About yesterday,
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean for it to turn out that way.
Forget it.
What's done is done.
From now on,
I won't do anything without making sure I know what I'm doing.
I promise.
Don't look.
Is it good?
Let me eat with you.
I'm hungry.
Thanks.
Don't look.
You're looking at me.
I'm not.
Don't scratch!
Don't scratch.
Hey! I said don't scratch! Stop right now.
It's too itchy. What am I supposed to do?
Stop! Enough already.
Stop! That's enough.
Stop!
You're almost bleeding all over.
Look.
Look. See?
You scratched all over your neck, the back of your neck.
It's spread to your forehead.
Don't scratch. Stop.
Why are you taking care of me?
Are you free?
I'm not.
So why are you doing it?
Do you
care about me?
I care.
Aum's here. Make sure you take your pills.
(I don't know when it started)
(but when I noticed...)
(You said you're not using your phone.)
(You're a social media addict. Delete it.)
(Did you delete it?)
(You said you're not using your phone.)
(You're a social media addict.)
(Delete it. Did you delete it?)
(Delete - Restore)
(Restore)
(I found myself often watching my story of him.)
(And)
(I keep thinking about the nice things he did for me.)
I don't want to go, Mueang.
Why? Are you embarrassed your new boyfriend is old?
You said it was your life choice. Why would you be embarrassed?
The one who should be embarrassed is your ex.
Let's show him
how much your life is better than when you were with him!
Leave my house now!
Let go.
How did it come to this?
- Son.   - Yes?
Has Mueang ever brought a girl over?
No, sir.
Really?
Yeah.
Young Master never introduced us to any of his girlfriends.
Why don't you try asking Aum?
He knows a lot more than I do.
Aum won't talk. Mueang must have told him to say nothing.
As his father,
I want to know what kind of girls he likes.
Do you know about that?
I know a little bit about that.
This is the one. She's his type.
Whoa! Did he attend a net idol's Meet and Greet?
I heard Young Master talk to Tin.
Young Master goes to every event of hers.
Mueang likes a halfling?
He does.
Every time he meets a girl like this,
he always loses control.
Every time.
Stop scratching! Will you stop or not?
Stop scratching. You're going to ruin your face.
- Okay. I'll stop.   - Are you tapping out?
I'm tapping out.
You're going to ruin your face.
Tin, did Aum tell you?
Have you eaten?
I have.
Apo brought me a meal.
Ms. Apo did?
Come to think of it,
Uncle Din and Ms. Apo are indeed strange, as you said.
I told you they're strange.
You told me they sleep in separate rooms.
Right!
They probably still think they had me fooled,
but I know that Apo's room is connected to the other room.
I ran all over that house as a kid.
I saw my old man come out of that room early in the morning.
It's true that I don't believe in their fake marriage,
but Apo is still my dad's fiancée.
What do you think Ms. Apo and Uncle Din are planning?
I don't think it's just a marriage to pay off her debt.
I'm trying to figure it out.
At first, I thought my old man brought her in to get me to work for him.
But she's trying to get you and Uncle Din to reconcile.
I think there's more to it.
There must be some important reasons. That's why Apo can't say the truth.
But what are they?
What are those reasons? Why is it so confusing?
I don't like this!
Please don't get things more complicated.
- My head hurts so much already.   - Mueang!
I'm going to start.
What?
(Just when I thought things couldn't get more complicated,)
(things get even more complicated!)
It's Apo.
Sorry. I...
I'm here to get my purse.
- Apo! Let me go!   - Mueang!
What the heck are you doing?
I'm here to let you know.
- Let me know what?   - I'm going to hit on you.
I didn't mean to spy on you. I'm leaving.
Don't go anywhere.
She says it out loud. She wants all of us to hear it.
That's right. I've got nothing to hide.
I already rejected you.
I don't like you. Leave me alone.
All men say that at first.
Mueang, what's wrong with your face?
Ew! Does it spread?
Ew! I touched you a lot.
Clean it up!
- Does that spread?   - Are you trying to kill me?
I'll be back, okay?
I'm surely hitting on you, okay?
Do you have anything to tell me?
I don't.
Why don't you ask Mr. Mueang and Ms. Apo themselves?
If it's that simple, they wouldn't have kept quiet until now.
If you insist that I do this,
I'll have to find another way to pay off my debt.
Are you asking me to change the deal?
Is that Mueang's girlfriend?
Who are you talking about?
The cute girl who owns a jewelry brand.
Apparently, she's having lunch with Mueang in the cafeteria.
I just want to let you know I'm not dating Ing.
(All I know is from this moment on, my heartbeat)
(will never be the same.)