How's your case going?
Don't even ask.
I'm completely free of official duties now.
I've been suspended.
Right after I lost track of He Mingxu
shortly after Fengshen was killed.
So,
I'm becoming more and more suspicious
that this refined young master of the He family
has some serious issues.
He Mingxu.
So I've been thinking,
I must perform in opera,
perform what I want to perform,
become who I truly want to be.
Only when I'm on stage
am I truly myself.
I
am really scared.
Forget it.
It's not a big deal if I don't perform.
I can still live without it.
But you need to think clearly.
Is that really what you want?
Deep down, senior brother
I really want to see you on stage.
Maybe then
I'll have to respectfully
call you Boss Chen.
Young lady,
these fallen leaves
don't necessarily need to return to their roots.
As long as they're buried in soil
and nourish new life,
they will be reborn.
Come back!
Where are you going?
You all drove senior sister away.
She finally came back.
I need to go talk to her.
Come back!
She just returned.
You can't upset her again.
I'm stewing chicken right now.
Let's bring her a bowl first before talking.
No, I can't wait.
I'm going to apologize to junior sister now.
Come back!
Senior brother.
Zhiyi, senior sister.
Your third senior brother bought you a chicken.
He said it's to satisfy your cravings.
So,
we'll have meat to eat soon.
Junior sister, let me tell you.
Senior brother, I think... just say it.
Yes, second senior brother is right.
Senior brothers,
I want to tell you something.
Go ahead.
The other day,
I ran off without telling you and didn't come back.
I made you worry.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's good that you're back.
Don't worry,
I won't be so impulsive anymore.
These past few days,
I met a friend.
She's also an opera performer.
She took me to their small theater.
I found it very interesting.
Watching her perform
is like
seeing myself on stage.
Really?
Zhiyi,
don't overthink it.
We were wrong that day.
We won't force you to be the lead anymore.
Yes,
we were wrong.
We should be supporting the Mule Opera Troupe.
Don't worry, little sister.
If you want to perform, then perform.
If you don't,
I'll take care of you for life.
About performing or not,
I haven't decided yet.
But
I've been thinking carefully
about what you all said to Ruan Suiqing.
I understand everything.
You're looking out for me
and for the troupe.
So...
If
you're still willing to trust me,
I'd like
to try again.
That's wonderful!
When Master Ruan hears about this,
he'll be delighted too.
Has Ruan Suiqing been here recently?
I did see Master Ruan once.
A few days ago,
he came to tell us
that the Young Marshal will be coming to town.
The streets won't be safe,
so we should be careful.
Then he left.
Well,
did he say anything else?
Zhiyi,
Master Ruan might be tied up with something.
Perhaps
he'll be here in a few days,
right?
Yes, yes.
The chicken is almost ready.
Come on, let's eat. Hurry.
Let's go, sister.
I won't eat now.
I have something to do.
I need to go out for a while.
Why is she leaving again?
Okay.
If I remember correctly,
the Young Marshal also enjoys opera.
I've already looked into it.
The Young Marshal particularly loves Beijing Opera.
Here's what I'm thinking.
After the Young Marshal arrives and settles in,
I'll take the lead
to organize a small competition
to welcome him.
That's thoughtful of you,
Mr. He.
It's the least I can do.
About that matter I asked you to handle recently,
how's it going?
It's all arranged,
but we need to wait two more days.
We don't have much time left.
You need to hurry it up.
I know, I know.
Is this the place you mentioned?
That's right.
This is where I lost track of He Mingxu last time.
I feel there's something mysterious about this temple,
but I couldn't figure out what it is.
Are you sure
that Fengsun's death and the old beggar incident
are both connected to the He family?
Young Master Ruan,
where do you usually get your inspiration for writing?
Inspiration is something
unpredictable.
Sometimes it just comes suddenly
and can't be stopped.
So, great writer,
please respect a professional police officer's instincts.
I'm always accurate.
Yes,
so accurate that you found nothing last time.
Why are you talking so much nonsense?
Weren't you the one insisting I bring you here?
If you don't want to investigate, then leave.
I was just thinking
I could learn how to investigate cases from you, Officer,
right?
We do have some clues.
Look.
What's this?
Moss.
This stuff
is quite rare in the north.
So?
It's unusual.
When we investigate cases,
we always pay attention to
abnormal things in everyday life.
If this old temple is connected to our case,
there must be clues left behind.
So according to what you're saying,
this stone is also quite unusual.
I didn't notice it last time I was here.
Often the things we can't see on the surface
might be hidden inside.
I suspect
there's a secret door in this temple.
But I've been here twice and couldn't find any mechanism.
What are you doing?
Paying my respects.
When you come to someone's territory, you should light incense and pay respects.
How else would you ask for help?
Perhaps after you worship,
the secret door
will reveal itself.
Joke.
Secret door.
A secret door!
Why is there only a candlestick but no candle?
That's so stingy.
Wait.
What did you just say?
I said this candlestick
doesn't even come with a candle.
How strange.
There were candles last time.
Why isn't there any wax left?
It's stuck.
Why can't I get it off?
Be careful!
Dalin!
Who are you?
Run!
Suiqing!
Get out of here!
Dalin,
are you okay?
I'm used to getting hurt.
It's nothing.
If it weren't for
this guy being so vicious
and attacking from behind,
would I have been bitten by this dog?
Indeed.
Every strike was lethal.
Seems like they came prepared.
But it also indirectly proves
that our investigation is on the right track.
Yes,
looks like I was right.
This temple
must have secrets.
If only I hadn't been suspended and had my gun.
I...
Being incompetent has nothing to do with having a gun.
How can you say that?
You insisted on coming along.
Without you, I'd have less to worry about.
Is your wound okay?
I'm actually fine.
I must have burned incense and prayed to Buddha.
Buddha is watching over me.
By the way.
I have plans tonight.
Let me take you home first.
Don't die on the way.
Wish me better luck than that.
It's nothing. Just a minor injury.
Let's go.
Take it slow.
Stop right there.
Come here.
What do you want from me?
Sit down.
Take a seat.
Having a meal with your father.
Is that too much to ask?
Take it easy.
I've taught you to be well-mannered since you were little.
Look at yourself now.
I was wrong that day.
I shouldn't have hit you.
I had hoped
to raise you to be someone with dreams and ambitions.
But after your mother passed away,
I suddenly realized
none of that matters to me anymore.
In times like these,
I'm just glad if you can live well.
That day...
I have plans with someone.
If you want to apologize,
we can talk when I get back tonight.
It's Miss Chen, isn't it?
I put a check in your coat pocket.
When you're on a date with a girl,
don't be stingy.
I don't need your advice on this.
You take after me.
Take her away.
Miss,
the show is over.
Aren't you leaving?
Mingxu, why are you here?
Sister,
it's getting cold.
Let's go home.
Senior, senior!
Senior, something terrible happened!
Come quickly!
Bastard!
They're nothing but a bunch of robbers!
The He family is hosting some exchange competition
What right do they have to use our 'Old Dreams' as a prize?
And nobody even asked if we agreed to this!
This whole thing
was planned by He Zhen all along.
Under the pretext of welcoming the Young Marshal to town,
he organized this competition
just to force us to hand over 'Old Dreams'.
But why?
Why?
He knows we don't have the power to fight against him.
If he wins,
'Old Dreams' will naturally fall into his hands.
If we don't participate,
it would be disrespectful to the Young Marshal
and an insult to the military.
How could a small theater troupe like us
possibly stand against the military?
So what do we do?
Do we just
swallow this bitter pill?
Let's just
go all the way.
We can move away,
find another place.
We can perform anywhere, can't we?
Sister,
what do you think?
Is Manager Chen here?
What can I do for you?
This is unexpected.
The legendary Mule Society
is actually in such a remote little courtyard.
When my master was alive,
Mule Society was one of the
most prestigious opera troupes.
Please mind your words, sir.