Uncle Zhang.
Good thing you're all here.
Here.
I'm pouring this drink for you myself.
You've worked hard.
I'll definitely keep working hard
to protect the Young Commander.
Here.
This drink is for Boss He.
I can see that
our officers and soldiers
have been troubling you quite a bit here.
From now on,
we'll definitely keep in touch.
Yes.
Since I've been ordered to take over Haicheng,
naturally,
I want to live in harmony with the local people.
In the future,
we'll need your help, Mr. He.
You're too kind, Commander.
Commander,
if there's anything I can do,
just let me know.
I'll serve you in any way
without hesitation.
Whatever it takes.
Let me in!
I need to see the Commander and Young Master Ruan.
I've been wronged! You can't go in.
What's going on?
Damn it!
The Commander is here,
you can speak plainly.
Speak.
Sir,
Young Master Ruan insisted on barging in.
He says.
Says what?
He says he's been wronged
and he's here to turn himself in.
If you have grievances, go to the police station!
What kind of place do you think this is,
letting him shout and make a scene?
Go.
Find some people to get rid of him.
Wait.
I understand your situation.
You want to clear your father's name.
My father was truly wronged.
He went to prison in my place.
I had no other choice.
I rushed in only because I knew you were here.
You're such a spoiled brat.
And you're supposed to be educated.
Newspaper young master.
When officials handle cases,
do you think they wrongfully accuse people?
They must have caught him red-handed.
What now?
Should we just take your word for it?
Is there no justice anymore?
My father was truly innocent.
He copied my article.
Young Marshal.
I also have the Ruan family seal.
How can you be so certain
that my father wrote that article?
Besides, the writing,
I remember every single word.
That article,
what did it say?
I heard some rumors
and wrote some unfounded words.
Young Marshal, you don't need to read it.
The writing is good.
Shows some backbone.
But,
just from this article,
do you really understand what kind of person I am?
From this alone,
the one being judgmental
is you.
Young Marshal.
He's just a foolish young man.
Please be magnanimous.
Since his father has already been arrested,
please don't hold it against him.
That's not right.
If we just let him go,
where does that leave our military's reputation?
If a mere boy can easily change a verdict,
then in Haicheng,
who's really in charge?
So you're suggesting
since he insists on confessing,
we should arrest him too,
investigate thoroughly,
and make an example of him.
Mr. Zhang.
That's not necessary.
You just said
we should live in harmony with the people.
Now you're starting a literary inquisition.
That's not right.
Young Master Ruan,
what do you think?
I already said.
One must take responsibility for one's actions.
I did it.
As long as you release my father,
whatever punishment you choose,
I'll accept it.
Well.
So you'll accept any punishment.
Young Master Ruan,
I've heard
you write plays
and are a theater enthusiast.
How about this?
Perform a piece for me.
If I enjoy it,
we'll consider this matter settled,
and it will count as your admission of guilt
and punishment.
As for your father's case,
I'll look into it later.
Will you really reconsider my father's case?
After I hear your performance,
I'll consider it.
Young Marshal,
which play would you like to hear?
Whatever you want.
Since you're a military man,
I'll perform
The Battle of Changsha.
Wait.
A performance needs proper presentation.
Performing without makeup
doesn't seem right.
What do you want?
The cream on this Western cake has some color.
Put it on.
Since the Young Marshal said you must be punished,
you should show a proper attitude of acceptance.
Come here on your knees.
Do you really understand
the situation in Haicheng?
Do you know who holds power,
who has the upper hand?
Do you?
All you see is
innocent students being arrested.
But do you know
who will take the blame if I don't write this article?
If we also take a stance against it,
how many intellectuals in Haicheng will suffer?
How many newspapers
will fall into the hands of those villains?
Do you know all this?
I originally wanted
you to be a person with ideals and ambitions.
But after your mother passed away,
I suddenly realized
none of that matters to me anymore.
In these times,
it's enough if you can just live well.
That day.
I have an appointment.
If you want to apologize,
we'll talk when I get back tonight.
Who told you to stand up?
Kneel back down.
Sing while kneeling.
Ruan Suiqing, stand up now!
Get up!
What a lively evening tonight.
Mr. He.
This is quite a nice place you have here.
And who is this young lady?
Get up.
Young Commander.
What a coincidence.
She's the one from Mule Opera
Troupe, the Young Marshal.
I am the manager of Mule Opera Troupe,
Chen Zhiyi.
Madam Manager.
May I ask
why you've come here, Ms. Chen?
I heard that
my friend has disturbed your enjoyment.
Unfortunately,
he is an investor in our troupe.
Ruan Suiqing is a good-for-nothing playboy,
as everyone in Haicheng knows.
So,
if the Young Marshal wishes to enjoy opera,
I'd be honored to perform for you.
Good.
What a fine show of 'Beauty Saves the Hero.'
They say opera performers are the most heartless.
Yet I see in you, Ms. Chen,
something of
a heroine.
You flatter me, Young Marshal.
As the old saying goes, convince with reason.
Though I am just an opera performer,
even for a private performance,
this is not how it should be done.
Interesting.
Then, Ms. Chen,
how would you like to perform?
Young Marshal.
This Ms. Chen
is like my apprentice-niece.
Her master and I trained under the same teacher.
The 'Old Dreams' I mentioned earlier
is in Ms. Chen's possession.
For this competition,
Ms. Chen's Mule Troupe was also invited.
However,
she hasn't accepted the invitation yet.
How about this, Ms. Chen?
Today we sign the invitation,
and in a few days,
you can perform for the Young Marshal on stage.
Wouldn't that be better?
Well, I'm truly looking forward to
your performance, Ms. Chen.
Let's do this.
Since you came here for your friend,
I'll make my position clear.
If you win the competition,
Master Ruan's father,
I can guarantee his safety.
Mr. Chen,
what do you think?
Good.
Agreed.
You shouldn't have come.
Hurry up.
Second Brother said
we're having dumplings tonight.
If we don't leave now,
I said you shouldn't have come.
they'll eat them all.
My problems have nothing to do with you.
Just focus on managing your Mule Society.
Isn't being a class teacher enough?
Why must you get involved?
When I was sad, you were by my side.
You helped me sneak onto the stage.
When Fengshen scolded me,
you stood in front of me.
And also,
you were the one who lifted my wedding veil.
I haven't even settled that score with you yet.
How can you say it has nothing to do with me?
But I don't want to drag you down. I'm not afraid.
Ruan Suiqing.
You know,
I was once an orphan.
I finally found a family.
I'm afraid of losing it.
But the more afraid I am, the more I lose.
I lost my loving master
and my doting senior brother.
I lost the entire Mule Society.
So I don't want to be afraid anymore.
Because
I'm afraid of losing you.
Chen Zhiyi.
Do you even understand what I'm saying?
Didn't you see it?
Today I was crawling on the ground
like a dog.
I have no dignity left.
As long as I can save my father,
I'll do anything.
When my father was around,
I never thought about
what would happen next.
What could happen?
I always thought
I could live peacefully as a young master.
But when I saw our family's possessions
being taken away piece by piece,
when I watched my father go to prison,
I couldn't do anything.
I'm just useless.
Useless.
Do you remember
what you once told me?
You said,
The past,
right or wrong,
is all behind us.
Courage
means not looking back.
Those words of yours
were like fireflies.
Although
the light was faint,
it was the only light I had
when I couldn't see the way forward.
Zhizhi.
I have nothing left.
So,
let me be the one to protect you from now on,
okay?
Get up.
Come home with me.