Listen up, all of you!
About recent events,
I'm sure everyone already knows.
I don't want to say more about it.
Mule Society
has reached such a desperate state
it's like a dying wild horse.
Nanfeng is probably beyond saving.
Even if he recovers,
with his current reputation,
he can't sustain this theater troupe anymore.
Today,
on behalf of the old master,
I officially announce to you all:
Mule Society
is disbanded.
Impossible!
Master would never say that.
This is exactly what the master meant.
Don't tell me
you think I stole these indenture contracts?
Everything I'm doing today
is for Mule Society
and for you ungrateful bastards too.
Do you all want to starve to death?
Those who want to starve,
those who want to perform on the streets,
I won't stop you.
Those who want food to eat,
those who want a place to perform,
come with me.
Fine!
So you're all loyal to the bone, huh?
It seems
today
someone needs to set an example for you all.
This villain
will be me.
Flowers bloom and wither, as is the way of all things.
Gatherings and partings all have their time.
Go and find your own way.
Disperse.
Leave now.
Senior Brother.
Junior Sister.
Get out of my way.
I was wrong, Senior Brother.
I was wrong.
I am a harbinger of death.
I bring nothing but misfortune.
Junior sister,
don't be like this.
Get out of my way.
At a time like this,
why are you still playing the victim?
Uncle Feng,
I was wrong.
You can hit me or scold me, I'll accept it all.
I'll never sneak onto the stage again.
I'll listen to you from now on.
I'll listen to Master.
As long as you don't leave,
I'll do whatever you ask.
I'm begging you all.
Please don't leave.
The Mule Club cannot disband.
It can't disband. Get out of my way!
Nobody is allowed to leave.
Junior sister.
Junior sister, please get up.
Don't be like this.
You heard it.
Junior sister.
Master said
Mule Society
is disbanded.
Brother.
Everyone just wants to make a living.
Please clear
the path for your brothers.
Take care, little sister.
Brother.
Chen Zhiyi.
I want you to remember
how Mule Society ended up like this.
It's all because of you.
Get up.
The floor is cold.
I still remember
the day you first came here.
Mr. Wan
brought you to Mule Opera Troupe.
Snow was falling heavily.
You were like a little bird
standing in the courtyard.
Mr. Wan asked me
if I wanted to take you in.
At that time,
Your little face was red from the cold.
Your big watery eyes
were staring at me.
Do you remember
what I said to you then?
You said opera is exhausting,
and if I couldn't perform on stage,
would I still want to stay.
Perhaps this
is the fate between us.
Father,
I was wrong.
I won't perform on stage anymore.
I won't sing opera either.
Can you forgive me?
It's them
who stick to the rules
and don't allow women on stage.
Clinging to so-called equal social status.
Separating lovers.
It's not your fault.
They are the ones to blame.
About your senior apprentice,
That was his own choice.
He and Miss Xie
are in love.
I know.
It's my fault
for not going earlier
to propose marriage,
which led to today's outcome.
Your performance
was also to
save the reputation of Mule Opera Troupe.
None of this is your fault.
Now,
whether he lives or dies,
it's his fate.
Then why are you disbanding the troupe?
Why are you sending my senior brothers away?
I'll listen to you carefully from now on.
I'll stay properly by your side.
Please don't send me away,
will you?
You're my precious daughter.
Father.
How could I bear to send you away?
Really?
I want to see you
get married,
have children,
and live peacefully.
I won't get married.
I want to stay by your side,
for my whole life.
That's fine too.
As long as you live
happily
and healthily.
Then we'll keep singing together.
I'll take care of you.
Alright,
stop crying.
These days,
you've been running around
and lost weight.
Father, it's been so long.
No more opera for you.
Go make me a cup of tea.
I haven't had your tea for days.
Go ahead.
Mr. He.
Theater manager,
I'm here about Mr. Lu's matter.
I've been negotiating with the police and the Xie family for a long time.
His case
has been mitigated.
Mr. Xie has agreed not to press charges further.
Although he's escaped the death penalty,
he still faces exile and forced labor as punishment.
Don't overthink it.
There's hope as long as he's alive, isn't there?
He'll be leaving tomorrow.
I've made all the arrangements.
You can go see him off.
Go quickly and pack
some of his everyday clothes.
Come with me.
Go on.
What a disgrace.
You've completely humiliated the Xie family.
Look at yourself.
Look at what you've written.
Having an affair with an actor.
What are you doing?
Nanfeng and I are in love.
It's not as filthy as Father describes.
Shameless!
You are a lady from a respectable family.
How could you
get involved with an actor?
I feel
embarrassed just hearing about it.
In love, you say?
I'll beat that love out of you!
Do you understand your mistake?
Being with someone I love -
I don't see what's wrong with that.
You
dare to talk back?
Still claiming you're in love?
Still saying you're a perfect match?
I'll show you what love is!
I'll teach you about perfect matches!
Your affair with that actor
is already spreading around town.
If I hadn't found a way
to suppress this scandal,
who knows what people would be saying about our Xie family.
Your mother and I
have no face to show in public anymore.
Since the rumors are already spreading,
why don't you grant my wish, Father,
and just let me be with him?
Fulfill my heart's desire.
You!
You
are absolutely hopeless!
Fine.
Guards!
Bring the family rod.
Master!
No!
Don't use the rod!
I know I was wrong.
Yan'er,
just look at her attitude!
She doesn't regret anything!
If she doesn't wake up today,
I might as well beat her to death.
Let's just pretend
the Xie family never had this daughter.
No!
Do you truly understand your daughter?
Since childhood,
You taught me to be well-educated
and literate.
You kept me confined in this vast Xie mansion.
I only learned rules
and etiquette,
but never understood the human heart.
Until I met Nanfeng,
he showed me the world beyond these walls.
Listening to him perform,
I finally saw the world
and understood the heart.
If you truly care for your daughter,
withdraw the charges
and release Nanfeng.
You gave me life,
I dare not throw it away carelessly.
But if you insist on executing Nanfeng,
then execute me as well.
Since I know he's been wrongly accused,
I cannot let him die for me
and for my reputation.
Yan'er.
Go.
You're letting her go?
To find her lover?
And then allow
everyone to gossip about the Xie family
and criticize your parents?
You see this place as a prison,
but isn't this your home?
You were born here,
you are a Xie.
Whether you acknowledge it or not,
you cannot sever these ties
with just a few words.
I have done so much as your father,
was it all just for myself?
When you were involved with Lu Nanfeng,
did you think about your parents
and the reputation of the Xie family?
If you truly care about Lu Nanfeng,
Fine.
I will no longer seek his life.
But you must promise me.
To settle things with him.
Make him sign this confession letter.
I'll arrange for someone
to exile him to the south.
Yan'er.
You both have your own responsibilities
and things to protect besides each other.
I'm sparing his life.
And that's the biggest concession I can make.