This unworthy person
has disrupted Master Xie's birthday banquet.
How should I make amends?
I have nothing to say in my defense.
However,
regarding the matter with your daughter,
this issue
is of great importance.
There might be some misunderstanding.
I humbly request Master Xie
to give us a chance to clarify the situation,
so the two young people can prove their innocence.
Innocence.
In broad daylight,
an actor
was lying half-naked in my daughter's chamber.
If this gets out,
Mr. Lu,
tell me,
how can anyone remain innocent?
Nanfeng has
grown up by my side since childhood.
I can vouch
for his character.
Miss Xie's reputation
cannot be compromised.
But I've heard
that these two young people
are actually in love with each other.
Old Master,
I respect you because you performed
for the Emperor and Empress Dowager,
which is why I'm showing you some courtesy.
I didn't call you here today
to listen to your explanations.
If even a word about Yan'er's situation
gets out,
your Mule Theater Company
will be shut down.
As for Lu Nanfeng,
attempted misconduct.
Please, officer,
just take him away.
No, you can't!
Master, please save my senior!
Senior, say something!
Isn't there some misunderstanding?
Senior!
How could there be any misunderstanding?
I saw him enter the young lady's chamber with my own eyes.
He must have seduced the young lady.
Mr. Xie,
this matter
can still be negotiated.
There's nothing to discuss.
Guards!
Show them out.
No way.
I wondered what the big deal was.
So it's about Miss Xie
being defiled by an actor.
Ruan Suiqing!
Mind your words.
Your father runs
the most prestigious newspaper in Haicheng.
He's known for his fairness.
Don't let the words of a wastrel like you
ruin both our families' reputations.
I certainly wouldn't slander Miss Xie.
Our newspaper doesn't publish falsehoods.
It's just that if this news
reaches the tabloid reporters,
they might write something even worse than what I've said.
Even if you kill Nanfeng then,
it won't restore Miss Xie's reputation.
You!
You spoiled brat!
Everyone knows
you've always been good friends with Lu Nanfeng.
A newspaper owner's son
who spends all his time at theaters,
throwing money around to support actors,
and now you dare threaten me like this.
I swear
I'll have you, you lawless scoundrel,
sent to the authorities too.
You're the lawless one.
Based solely on your word,
you've already concluded this case.
That's a complete disregard for human life.
How dare you!
I witnessed this with my own eyes.
Lu Nanfeng offered no defense.
My household maid can testify.
How am I disregarding human life?
Everyone present during the incident was from your Xie household.
You can say whatever you want.
Furthermore,
why doesn't Nanfeng say anything?
It's to protect
that precious daughter of yours
and your Xie family's lofty reputation.
You condemn him without any due process.
It's complete nonsense.
You!
But Uncle Xie,
I was just joking with you,
please don't take it personally.
Anyway,
I do have a solution
to restore Miss Xie's reputation.
As you mentioned earlier,
my family's newspaper
is the most influential in all of Haicheng.
If I ask my father to write an article
clearing Miss Xie's name,
then this matter
would be easily resolved.
Easy for you to say.
I'm afraid
your father doesn't even want to see you.
I know you don't believe me,
but right now
you have no choice but to trust me.
Two options:
Either Nanfeng stays here
and I return with the newspaper that solves the problem.
Or you take Nanfeng away,
and tomorrow all of Haicheng
will be talking about your family's scandal.
You're absolutely shameless.
How do I know this isn't just a delaying tactic?
Three days.
I only need three days.
In three days,
I'll return with the newspaper that solves the problem,
and you'll withdraw the case at the police station.
If I don't come back,
you can do whatever you want.
How about it?
Mr. Xie,
this deal
is a win-win, isn't it?
Mr. Xie,
don't waste time talking to him.
We've seen plenty of people like him.
We police officers don't just sit around doing nothing.
The facts are clear.
Officer Li, please wait.
Uncle Xie,
I hope you don't mind me
speaking as an outsider.
I actually think what Mr. Ruan said
makes a lot of sense.
If Mr. Ruan fails to fulfill his promise,
you can still deal with Lu Nanfeng.
If he succeeds,
it would benefit the Xie family
and Miss Xie,
which would be good for everyone.
Either way, you won't lose.
Officer Li,
I believe
you certainly uphold the law fairly.
But even under the law, there's room for compassion.
After all, this matter
concerns the reputation of the Xie family.
If anything goes wrong,
I'm afraid Miss Xie's reputation
will still be compromised.
If you're concerned,
you can take Lu Nanfeng away first,
but don't convict him.
In three days,
we'll see the outcome at the police station.
Is that acceptable?
All right.
Today,
for the sake of the He family,
I'll trust you this once.
Three days.
You only have three days.
If you don't come,
no one can save Lu Nanfeng's life.
Show them out.
Get up.
Senior Brother.
I told you she was trouble.
But you wouldn't listen.
You insisted on taking her in.
Spoiling her.
Letting her perform on stage.
Letting her sing in the opera.
And now letting her get Nanfeng killed.
What's next?
Master Feng.
Mind your words.
Don't jump to conclusions before we know the facts.
Besides.
What kind of person she is
is not for you to judge.
Fine.
I don't have time to discuss her.
Tell me.
What should we do now?
Are we going to save Lu Nanfeng or not?
What will happen to Mule Society?
Master.
Someone from the He family is here.
Zhiyi,
don't listen to their nonsense.
Nanfeng must have been framed by someone.
Today I used the newspaper issue
to threaten Mr. Xie,
and also to warn them
not to act rashly.
Don't overthink it.
I'll definitely come back with the newspaper to save Nanfeng.
You're always trying to score points.
Master is still angry.
She hasn't spoken to her all day.
Why are you going over there now?
Looking to get scolded?
Senior Sister has been kneeling all morning.
If she keeps kneeling,
her legs will be ruined.
That's why I say you're silly.
Master is truly angry this time.
Doing this
will also teach her a lesson.
Besides,
if you let Junior Sister play the victim a bit,
once Master's heart softens,
she might forgive her.
I really don't understand you anymore.
Now
the situation is clear.
Either Nanfeng admits his wrongdoing,
the Xie family stops pursuing Mule Society,
and we still have a chance to make a comeback.
Or
I go humble myself to the He family
and ask them to mediate for us.
But look at you,
you refuse both options
and insist on choosing a dead end.
Master.
Mr. Lu.
I know what you're thinking.
Even though Nanfeng's
innocence is important,
he's already in his twilight years.
Between Nanfeng and Mule Society,
you need to be clear about what matters more.
Let me be frank.
If you can't let go of Lu Nanfeng,
you can't save Mule Society.
When the birds are gone,
the bow is put away.
When the cunning hare is dead,
the hunting dog is cooked.
Brother Feng, are you teaching me
how to cut losses to save myself?
Nanfeng
is not Mule Society's cash cow.
I nurtured him from a seedling
into a thousand-year timber.
Decades of care
cannot at this moment
bend his backbone.
Fine.
I'm heartless.
But you must consider
those dozen or so mouths waiting to be fed.
You weren't willing before
to join the theater guild, that's fine.
Now Mule Society is in trouble,
and the He family is willing to help us.
If you go humble yourself and apologize,
perhaps we could...
All these years,
I understand
your contributions to Mule Society.
That's why most decisions you've made,
I've followed.
The rules you've set,
I've never questioned.
But what kind of place is Fuchun Hall?
He Zhen's character,
I know best.
Enough.
For performers,
there's always a beginning and an end.
Some things
are destined.
As the troupe master,
I will be responsible for Mule Society
and every decision
I make.
Fine.
Master Lu.
If you can kneel until this stone slab wears through,
perhaps a miracle might still happen.
Now you realize your mistake.
It's too late.
Harbinger of doom.
Senior.
Come.
Senior,
where are you going?
Let her in.
So
you're that little girl who wanted to perform on stage.
It's you.
I didn't expect
that Mule Society was hiding
such a brave young lady.
I
just want to ask you, Mr. He,
to put in a good word for my senior apprentice brother
and see if he can be released first.
After all, Ruan Suiqing has already promised
he'll bring back the newspaper in three days.
Waiting at home is better than being in prison.
I also came from a theater troupe.
I know very well how actors
are viewed in society.
Your senior apprentice brother
won't be easy to save.
But I've seen the Xie family
and how those police officers treat young Master He.
You're the head of the He family,
the owner of Fuchun Hall,
and the manager of the Theater Guild.
If you step forward,
there must be a way.
Such a silver tongue.
Well then,
considering you're from the theater community,
young lady,
I'll point you in the right direction.
Are you
willing to help now?
Don't you know that Ruan boy?
You can ask his father
to publish an article
on the front page of Haicheng Daily.
Just say that Lu Nanfeng
is of poor character
and attempted
to harass a respectable woman.
Then it would have nothing to do with your Mule Society.
As long as you distance yourself from him,
sacrifice Lu Nanfeng,
and you can
save your Mule Society.
No,
that's impossible.
I can't abandon my senior apprentice brother.
M-Master wouldn't agree to that either.
What is Lu Shun to you?
He is my master.
I lost both my parents when I was young.
Master raised me
as his own child.
Why didn't you say so earlier!
So you're
my grand-niece who's come to visit.
Well,
originally,
your master refused to sign
to acknowledge
the Theater Guild I established.
So when the Mule Society got into trouble,
it wasn't convenient for me to intervene, you see.
But since
you've come to me for help,
I can't just ignore it.
Are you really willing to help
and speak up for my senior apprentice brother?