♬〜
♬~(BGM in the store)
(Customer) Hiromi-chan, please give me another meal.
(Watari Hiromi) Yes.
thank you very much~.
Also!
♬〜
Shogo: The shop is over now.
(Chikaishi Shogo) Yes...
Hey
If I put it somewhere like this, it's wet.
Wake up.
Yeah….
Hey... it's already shining.
Hey.
♬〜
Hehe, it's so messy...
Ah, here...
what? That's fine. Yes Yes.
this is….
This... walk around this. Hehe.
I'll do it.
Yes Yes Yes.
That's good. Ah, huh.
I'm really drunk today...
wait a minute….
yeah? I'm not drunk.
I'm drunk.
Huh?
Hehehe...
what? what?
Why are you laughing?
A little...
Ugh...
Stop it! Hehe.
It hurts.
yes.
Stay still for a moment.
Ahaha, it's no good anymore.
Yes Yes Yes. Ah.
Good luck.
Hehehe.
Ahaha!
Ahahaha.
Hehehe.
Haha, ahhh... Yes.
Hehe.
Hehehe, that's weird.
Hahaha.
My heart is...
♬〜
Hey Shogo, if you're bored, come to the store.
📱 If you feel like it.
📱 Two-two…
(The sound of the phone being cut off)
He was sleeping.
(Yashiko) Huh? Are you coming?
Even if you feel like it.
Yeah.
(Yashiko) The two of them are...
It's changed isn't it?
yeah? Where?
Huh? Because...➡
If it were me, I might come
Cake for people who don't know➡
I won't make it.
ah~….
Hehehe.
Hehe.
yes. happy birthday.
Hey.
(Fukumoto) Huh?
Let Hiromi sing this.
(Fukumoto) What?
That's fine.
(Fukumoto) Hiromi-chan! ➡
One song please.
Ahhh ➡
Wait a second, wait a second.
Oolong Hai?
Yeah.
Today, I'm treating the store.
🔊 ♬~ ("For a long time")
(Fukumoto) Yes, I put it in.
What? "for a long time"? Yeah~.
Wait, wait... why am I?
yes. Yeah~….
🔊 ♬ Sorry for keeping me waiting for a long time
🔊 ♬ I suddenly got work again
Hehehe.
🔊 ♬ Always
I can't be together
🔊 ♬ It made me feel lonely
♬〜
(Recollection)⦅Wait Shogo!
wait a minute! ⦆
⦅Par! (Cracktion)⦆
⦅Kiki! (Brake sound)⦆
♬〜
(Goddess) Let's welcome you.
(Goddess) Just go on and go on.
♬〜
(Goddess) Why are you hesitant?
There...
Can I meet Shogo again?
(Goddess) That person will not come.
Huh?
(Goddess) That person
Repeat death in a world where life is present. ➡
You are
Just go on and on. ➡
There's no hesitation.
♬〜
I want to be with Shogo.
If it's a goddess, then the memory of that person
Leave it there. ➡
There's no way they'll be tied up.
That's fine.
♬〜
And someday ➡
Maybe we can overcome that fate.
Hehehe...
(Goddess) Leave! A foolish person.
(Goddess) Awaken!
♬〜
sigma.
Shogo?
Is it Shogo?
It's Shogo.
Finally...➡
We met.
Hehe...
♬〜
let's go.
Yeah.
Bishun! (gunshot)
Huh?
Ahh... ha ha ha ha...
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha... Ha ha ha...
Ha ha ha... Shogo...
Ha ha ha ha ha ha...
Your Majesty, are you injured?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha...
Please leave immediately.
He is human.
Ah!
Bang! (gunshot)
Squish! (The sound of falling)
Uh... ha ha ha...
Ha ha ha ha... uh...
Shogo... Uuuuuu...
immediately
I'll create a new body.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha...
Are you okay….
♬〜
I want to die as a human...
What...
Ugh...
I don't want any more...
Ha ha ha ha ha... Uuh...
You... Ugh...
I liked it...
♬〜
Me too.
i love you.
Hehehe...
♬〜
Ugh... I don't like it... I don't like it...
Shogo... Ugh...
Ugh... Shogo Ugh...
Uuuh... ah...
Shogo... Ugh... Shogo...
Uuuh ah...
ah~! Ah... ahhh!!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha...
♬〜
I'll go soon too.
Swing (start sound)
♬〜
Catan (sound of a statue)
On a somewhat high sky ➡
You and my atoms intersect.
♬〜
One day we can become one.
Hmm...
♬〜
Me...
How many times should I die?
(Goddess) Trials will last forever.
permanent?
(Goddess) Being tested for love forever➡
Forever
They experience the pain of love.
already….
It's been painful enough.
(Goddess) thousands of years, tens of thousands of years ➡
Humans are
I've been repeating that pain. ➡
Until humans die
That continues. ➡
Repeat until that day.
(goddess)
Now, the next destiny awaits.
♬〜
Zaza... Zaza...(Wave Sound)
Was there an accident here?
(Shimoda) Ah... but a while ago.
Ah, um...
Maybe...➡
Is it Hiromi?
Huh?
It was my teacher who passed away.
He was someone who helped me so much.
Well then.
♬〜
(Shimoda) Maybe the teacher
It could be the person who helped me. ➡
Hiromi... Was it?
What...
The teacher is here
A woman who was nearly hit by a car ➡
I was trying to help. ➡
Excuse me.
♬〜
Hiromi...
Who is it?
♬〜
Maybe
Have you met before?
Um... after I got into an accident ➡
What happened before that was absolutely...
♬〜
Please let me know if you like.
Me and you ➡
What kind of relationship is it?
♬〜
It looks like it's going to be a little longer.
Will you still listen?
♬〜
yes.
Hmm...
♬〜