Lee Joon Gi
Lee Kyung Young
Kim Ji Eun
Again My Life
- Sir!
- Just a comment, please!
I brought the powerful Jo Tae Seop here
to show that you're nothing but a piece of garbage.
I am looking forward to seeing what card you will use.
I have done the job.
I will take care of it as instructed.
If you have another life, will you use it to catch Jo Tae Seop again?
Promise me.
Can you show him hell?
My life began again to catch that person.
Hey!
Always the same tactics...
It's old now. It's boring.
Who are you?
Is that important right now?
I asked who you are.
Someone who knows you too well.
Have we met before?
Yes.
And...
I died at your hands.
You have the wrong person.
I have never failed before.
You're right. You didn't fail.
I just resurrected like a miracle.
I was so angry at how unfair it was
that I even managed to avoid death.
Sounds interesting.
Then try to avoid it this time, too.
Are you stupid?
I wouldn't have interfered then, you bastard!
♫  Hey, you're so cold. That evil leer  ♫
♫  You clearly intend something nasty  ♫
♫  Lie lie lie gradually it will come out  ♫
♫  Standing up, Standing up, Standing up  ♫
♫  What kind of gang came at me?  ♫
I can't lose twice.
♫  wait just for me  ♫
♫  Even if you fool everyone else  ♫
I can see it now.
Got it.
I think I can do this.
As expected, he is strong.
Do you work out?
A little.
To be honest, I'm shocked. This is the first time I've been so flustered.
Right?
I feel like I have fought with you hundreds of times.
You will soon be more shocked.
A fight is different from a competition.
You talk too much.
Come on then.
You cowardly bastard. That's cheating.
I already told you that a fight is different from a competition.
Fine.
I will give you a proper lesson today.
You lucked out.
Hyeong Hui Wu. Hyeong Hui Wu! Are you all right?
That black-suited scumbag!
What about Seung Hyeok?
Prosecutor Gu?
Seung Hyeok!
Prosecutor Gu!
- Are you alright?
- Yeah, I am.
Sang Man, we should rush to the hospital.
Okay, Hyeong. I'll go bring the car.
Okay.
- Hey, can you stand up?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Try some of this.
Episode 13
Are you hurting anywhere else?
No, I am alright.
Punk...
Hey, Gu Seung Hyeok.
Seonbae.
Are you alright?
Thank God. Look at his face. It's a mess.
A mess?
It's just a figure of speech.
But, only one rib is fractured. Everything else is fine.
I might not be able to fight well, but I'm resilient.
What kind of bastard did this to a prosecutor?
You were lucky today.
That's right. He wasn't a petty gangster.
While I was getting beaten by him, I really thought I could die.
I'll ask the police to cooperate.
Let's check out the CCTV immediately and identify the—
Wait.
Could the two of you step out for a moment?
Sure.
What do you want to say?
Are you asking us to back down?
Yes.
Gyu Ri, you go to the District Prosecutor's Office and release Kim Yeong Il immediately.
From this moment on, you both stay away from the JQ Construction case.
- Hey, Kim Hui Wu!
- What are you saying?
You want us to stop because of a thug?
Yeah. It would be even better to say you stopped because you were scared.
- Hey!
Kim Gyu Ri. Gu Seung Hyeok.
You guys trust me and back off.
I promise I will finish off this case.
Do me the favor.
Please?
Again My Life
I am looking forward to the prosecution you will build.
I will never forget this favor.
But sir,
I am really sorry,
but I want to ask you something.
The one who told you about the Bando Bank investigation,
was it Kim Hui Wu?
Kim Hui Wu ...
He is a capable prosecutor. He is quick-witted and skilled.
Unlike others of his age, he has good judgment skills.
I guess that's why you got it wrong.
Did you think I wouldn't be able to see through him?
I must have looked lax.
If you are in my position, you see a lot. You also might hear a lot.
Your thoughts and actions are no exception.
I am sorry.
That's alright.
- Do well from now on.
- Yes, sir.
Sir.
Yes.
- Then I will get going now.
- All right.
What's the matter?
- He failed.
- Failed?
Someone intervened, and the police showed up.
We are checking all the CCTV from around that area.
Sir, Prosecutor Kim Hui Wu wants to meet with you right now.
- Kim Hui Wu?
-  Yes.
- Prosecutor Kim Hui Wu is here.
- Come in.
I am sorry for coming so late at night.
- Is there a problem?
- Yes.
What is it?
I had a fight.
- Fight?
- Yes.
The Prosecutor who arrested JQ Construction's Managing Director Kim Yeong Il is my colleague.
When I went to convince him to drop the case, I met an unidentified assailant.
- Assailant?
-  Yes.
So you fought that assailant?
Yes, sir.
Did you manage to convince your colleague?
Yes. I'll have Kim Yeong Il released by the end of the night.
Both prosecutors have decided to stay out of this case too.
Is that why you came to see me?
No.
I came to hear your opinion.
My opinion?
Yes. I was taught that a prosecutor should always question everything.
And?
It's an assault case involving a prosecutor.
Obviously, I'm going to go after that assailant from this point on.
But, all of a sudden a thought crossed my mind.
That perhaps the assailant
could be one of your people.
What?
I apologize if I'm mistaken.
But, I wanted to make sure
and receive instructions before taking action.
Whether I can go after that assailant,
or if I should just cover it up.
I'll do as you say.
Don't go after him.
Can I take this to mean that he is one of your people?
You're still young.
It just means that I'll take care of him myself. Understand?
I understand. I will follow your instructions.
You seem very tired. Go home and rest.
Yes, sir.
Kim Seok Hun will be the next prosecutor general.
Will you be okay? The person you're trying to take down will be the next prosecutor general.
If you made that decision, I will trust your judgment.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
Your faith in me and your hard work so far,
I would like to repay you this time. Tell me what you would like.
- I'm okay.
- You're okay?
I understand. You can leave.
- Hi Gyu Ri.
- I let Kim Yeong Il go.
Thank you for believing in me.
Make sure your plan works.
I will.
I understand.
Kim Yeong Il has been released.
Really?
What do you think of Kim Hui Wu?
He seems to have a tendency to succeed in whatever goals he sets.
I like him.
The people who seek me out tend to make a lot of noise.
Whining and asking me to solve their problems.
But Kim Hui Wu isn't like that.
He brings me solutions. But something is bothering me.
He doesn't want anything.
He is a young prosecutor. He's not old enough to be able to discriminate between good and bad.
At his age, one should have ambition and aspiration.
He came out on top from the training center, and by looking at all the cases he's been involved in so far,
he's unusual.
That's not all. He figured out my relationship with Park Dae Ho and Bando Bank.
He also figured out that I sent the assailant.
Sometimes, he catches me off guard. He's remarkable.
He also knows he is great.
But, he doesn't want anything?
- Secretary Kim.
- Yes, sir.
Pick someone who can keep Kim Hui Wu in check.
- Someone skilled and unique from inside the prosecution.
- Yes, sir.
Those at the Eastern District Prosecutors' Office who backed off, leave them alone.
Yes, sir.
Daily Newspaper.
'Principles and Integrity' Kim Seok Hun, Candidate for Prosecutor General.
Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office Chief Kim Seok Hun
Don't worry about your son's problem. I will take care of it.
Get rid of Yun Jong Gi, who is blocking your path.
Come in.
Did you call for me?
- The Bando Bank Investigation. Shut it down.
- What?
The opponent has figured it out. It's meaningless now.
Yes, sir.
I will give you a new target. Your planning skills will be more than enough.
Get him. Eastern District Chief Prosecutor Yun Jong Gi.
- Got it?
- Yes.
- Get started.
- Yes, sir.
Chief Director of Prosecutors' Office
Chief Director Kim Seok Hun.
It's me.
You want to bring down Kim Seok Hun?
Yes.
How?
Loan Agreement
- This is...
-  Yes.
It's the illegal loan file of Kim Seok Hun's son, JQ Construction's Executive Director Kim Yeong Il and the Bando Bank.
It's a card I can't use at the Prosecutors' Office, but I think it's different in political circles.
- Do you want to expose it?
- No.
Please persuade CEO Kim Jeong Taek.
Persuade him...
Will CEO Kim Jeong Taek use this to hold Kim Seok Hun back?
The general election is around the corner.
Nobody knows what kind of variables will come up.
Although he is the leader of the weak opposition party, Kim Jeong Taek already got a taste for power.
He might aim for something more.
For now, just persuade him.
Please do me that favor, sir.
Okay.
I am sorry.
I cannot tell you everything yet.
That Kim Seok Hun is the bait and the target is Kim Jeong Taek.
In my prior life, Kim Jeong Taek was eliminated brutally by Jo Tae Seop.
After his arrest on a charge of defamation, Great Korea Party head Kim Jeong Taek,
who accused JQ Construction's Executive Director Kim Yeong Il
and Assemblyman Jo Tae Seop as being behind  Bando Bank's illegal loan case,
resigned from politics.
For causing concern among the public by spreading incorrect information,
I humbly apologize.
I, Kim Jeong Taek, will go back to being a citizen from now on.
Thank you so much for sending so much support and love till now.
Kim Jeong Taek, former head of Great Korea Party.
A bridgehead to eliminate Kim Jeong Taek was made.
Bando Bank's Loan to JQ Construction, Related Documents
Daehan Party
A Better Korea
Is this all true?
Everything is factual.
If you find it suspicious, check it with the Eastern District Prosecutors' Office.
But... why are you giving this to me?
How long are you going to act as Jo Tae Seop's puppet?
How long are you going to be a puppet for the ruling party?
How much has our Daehan Party faced because of Jo Tae Seop, till now?
During the sexual favors scandal, all the assemblymen in the Democratic Party went unscathed
but in our party, two assemblymen lost their positions.
Jo Tae Seop has already decided unofficially on Chief Prosecutor Kim Seok Hun as Prosecutor General.
Of course, he's already finished talking with the members of the legislative judiciary committee.
Besides the Assembly, he's trying to gain command of even the Prosecution Service.
We must stop him.
Before the general elections, through Kim Seok Hun, we will reveal flaws in the ruling party.
Using that momentum, if we show that the ruling party is a corrupt group,
we can even claim the majority.
Assemblyman Hwang, please stop digging up dirt on other people and instead take care of the public welfare.
If you don't, during this party nomination, you cannot be assured of your district.
Assemblyman Jo Tae Seop
Great Korea Party
A Better Korea
Could you excuse me? It's an important call.
Yes, sir.
Ah, I understand.
Assemblyman Hwang Jin Yong
- Yes, sir.
- I've conveyed it to Minority Leader Kim Jeong Taek.
But I don't think he's convinced.
I understand. Thank you for your efforts.
The wind will start picking up now.
Have you been well, Minority Leader Kim? You look good.
It's been a while since I last saw you.
Why did you want to see me?
The approaching general election. I mean the Daehan Party nominations.
Let you and I discuss who will make that list.
- Sir.
- Minority Leader Kim.
Do you believe Korea is normal right now? Let me ask again.
Do you think it will become normal if it continues this way?
Until when must each party fight like enemies?
As a result of useless fights over pride, the country's competitiveness is falling behind.
Other countries are growing daily. What are we doing?
Postponing marriages, not having babies, giving up on jobs.
Why?
Because the country's assemblymen are only fighting and not doing the work they should be doing.
Now is the time for both parties to combine their strengths.
I mean that it's time for cooperation.
You and I will be opening the door to that era.
Toward one goal,
I'd like to run instead of fighting.
Still,
Daehan Party's nominations aren't something I can discuss with an assemblyman of the Democratic Party.
If there wasn't a problem in the first place, would I have set up a meeting like this?
- Manager Han.
- Yes,  sir.
Investigation Results for Kim Jeong Taek, the Leader of Daehan Party
Wasn't this matter already over with?
On the condition of not holding me accountable, I also
gave you the list of names of corrupt assemblymen in the People's Party that Assemblyman Hwang Jin Young obtained.
It was an equal trade.
I took action on behalf of the party,
and you took action in order to hide your guilt. Look at the following page.
You again accepted a request to select a business for government property.
You received 1 billion won from two local construction companies.
I also heard that you're making deals these days using Daehan Party's nomination rights.
Sir!
Minority Leader Kim, I, too, am someone who was a prosecutor.
I can't keep my eyes shut after seeing violations of the law.
Register the names for the party nominations after discussing them with me.
Daehan Party
Material regarding Bando Bank's Loan to JQ Construction
How are you? It's me, Kim Jeong Taek.
Could I see you for a moment?
Material regarding Bando Bank's Loan to JQ Construction
How did you...?
Let me get straight to the point, Chief Prosecutor.
Let's join hands.
Won't the risk be too big? You must know already.
It could also mean that we can gain a lot if we succeed.
For you, the Prosecutor General position, and for me, it'll solidify my position.
It's a matter that's already been upended.
But it's never been made an issue of in political circles.
Do you mean that you will stoke the fire?
Yes.
We will bring up the truth at the start,
so please bring it to justice and take care of the end.
Then the name on the next prosecutor general's desk plate
will be your name, Yun Jong Gi.
Is that so?
The prosecution office doesn't always have to be the one to search for the truth.
If you work hard, I shall also do my best.
Thank you.
I understand.
Modify the ones I've checked.
Yes, sir. I just received a call from Chairman Park Dae Ho.
Kim Yeong Il is holding, as a hostage, the stake in Cheonha Holdings.
He said he wants a business loan.
Tell him to deny it. Kim Seok Hun will take care of it.
All right.
- Manager Han.
- Yes, sir.
It seems the three Cheonha siblings are being quiet.
Shall I summon Vice Chairman Kim Yong Jun?
Just relay my greetings to him.
Yes, I will.
Director.
The National Tax Service's special tax investigation team went to Cheonha Electronics.
What?
Only Cheonha Electronics?  Not the other affiliates?
Just Cheonha Electronics.
They're targeting Oppa, and Jo Tae Seop is behind this.
It's such a sudden investigation that even people in related departments weren't aware of it.
So what's Oppa doing?
Vice Chairman Kim Yong Jun is meeting with the finance team to come up with a plan.
- That's not going to do it.
- Excuse me?
It's a signal from Jo Tae Seop to go see him.
It means he is slowly going to tighten the leash.
I need to send a signal to Jo Tae Seop, too.
It's not going to be easy to hold onto our leashes.
I will do exactly what Jo Tae Seop did.
So I was so surprised when I saw her wearing that.
Anyway, what's the amount you urgently need?
Two hundred billion won.
- Two hundred billion?
- Yes.
I can't.  The amount is too large.
It would be too difficult because the Financial Supervisory Service (FSS) is scrutinizing corporate loans.
Chairman Park, that's not what we agreed on.
The stake in Cheonha Holdings is in my hands.
What do you want me to do when the FSS is watching with a spotlight on?
Don't even think about trying to convince me.
Why don't you ask your mom for some allowance?
Or go to those wealthy shareholders and beg on your knees.
It's up to you. It's your company, not mine.
JQ Construction Executives:  Kim Yeong Il, Executive Director
JQ Construction Trend Briefing No. 13
How many shares of JQ do we own?
About 3.4%.
Approach Kim Yeong Il.
For the amount of shares you own, he will cater to you on his knees with just one call.
Yes.
But, Hyeong, there's something you should know.
A few days ago, a big private investor appeared at JQ Construction.
He wiped up the shares after stock market hours, and there was nothing I could do.
Did you find out who it is?
I barely managed to get the name. Park Jong Hyeok?
Park Jong Hyeok...
Okay. He may show up tomorrow, so be on alert.
Yes.
And Yeon Seok, you're Sang Man's secretary and driver.
I'll be his security, too.
I saw on the news that sometimes fights break out.
All right. Make sure to look after him well.
JQ Construction
JQ Construction Co., Ltd. Invitational Business Briefing for Shareholders
Have you come for the business briefing?
- Yes, that's right.
- May I have your name?
It is Park Sang Man.
Chairman Park Sang Man.
I am Sin Dae Wung, Managing Director of JQ Construction.
Our Executive Director is waiting for you. Follow me.
Yes.
Oh, welcome.
Say hello. This is Executive Director Kim Yeong Il.
Hello. Nice to meet you, Chairman Park.
Yes. What is it?
I guess they are in a rush
He says his father is going to become prosecutor general and he's encouraging investment.
So I promised investment using the shares as collateral.
Good.  Hang around a little before you go home.
Yes, Hyeong. I'll come back early. In the morning.
Aren't you going to work out?
I'm leaving right now.
What is this?
I eat it before I work out.
The color is intense.
Two at a time.
Here.
Thanks.
What for?  Have a nice chat.
But, I noticed you were pensive since earlier.
Kim Seok Hun has been nominated to be prosecutor general. It's an affront to the Prosecution Service.
- Are you sure?
- I heard it from a colleague at the Supreme Prosecutor's Office.
We've collected so much evidence, yet, we couldn't use any of it.
The path that Kim Seok Hun travels is a bed of roses.
We need to make it a thorny path.
How?
I'd like to borrow some external help.
External help?
Kim Jeong Taek, the leader of Daehan Party.
Kim Jeong Taek?
Yes.
Politicians are good at biting into and hanging on to other people's corruption.
I... don't trust politicians.
And would that alone be enough?
There is a surefire solution.
Sir, the JQ Construction Corruption documents have reached Daehan Party Chairman Kim Jeong Taek.
How was it leaked?
I'm looking into it right now.
First, we checked the chief prosecutor of the Eastern District Prosecutors' Office and Prosecutor Kim Hui Wu.
It has been confirmed that they have not contacted Kim Jeong Taek or his close associates.
I suspect it was Yun Jong Gi, the chief prosecutor of the Eastern District Prosecutors' Office.
It could also be an expression of dissatisfaction with the prosecutor general's internal affairs.
- Make sure to investigate fully.
- Yes, sir.
Sir, Chief Prosecutor Kim Seok Hun is here.
Come in.
Ah, yes.
Congratulations on being nominated Prosecutor General.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
There will be a hearing soon, so prepare well.
I've put in a good word to the Judiciary Committee of the National Assembly.
If you prepare your answers well, you will pass easily.
Yes, I understand.
I will prepare well so as not to be a hindrance.
And be careful not to become fodder for gossip until the hearing.
Yes, sir.
And... Kim Jeong Taek.
Excuse me?
It's Kim Jeong Taek's nomination scandal. It would be  better if there's another charge.
Just investigate, don't prosecute.
I'll decide when to file the charges, so just keep that in mind.
Yes, I understand.
Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office
Come in.
You called for me?
Yes.
I am going to be the next prosecutor general.
Oh, congratulations.
I didn't call you to congratulate me.
We're nearly there.
The prosecution I've always wanted, beyond everyone's expectations. I'll be able to achieve it soon.
So, I have something I would like you to do.
Give Yun Jong Gi's case to Choi Kang Jin.
Improper Nomination by Daehan Party Chairman Kim Jeong Taek
It's the details of the nomination scandal of Kim Jeong Taek, the leader of the Daehan Party.
Check the facts and find every detail on Chairman Kim Jeong Taek.
That is your job.
Yes, sir.
You may leave.
Okay, it's Assemblyman Hwang Jin Yong's turn.
You want me to become the party leader?
Yes, sir.
I would like you to become the leader of Daehan Party.
I don't like the sound of pushing out Kim Jeong Taek when he's done nothing wrong.
Please take a look at this.
Daehan Party Chairman Kim Jeong Taek Improper Nomination
request  for money and valuables, sexual favors
We can't beat Jo Tae Seop because someone like him is leading the minority party.
How did you get...
I've received orders from the chief prosecutor
to look into what Kim Jeong Taek has been doing
all these years.
I'm sure the chief prosecutor got his orders from Jo Tae Seop.
Kim Jeong Taek has started on the Bando Bank's illegal loans incident.
The wind that you helped create has finally started to blow.
Did you plan all this to make me the party leader?
Is that why you told me to give the file to Kim Jeong Taek?
Yes, sir.
I apologize for not telling you everything in advance.
I'm sorry.
Fine.
Then what are you going to do now?
I'm going to help Jo Tae Seop and bring down Kim Jeong Taek.
I will offer him help and cut out his right hand man, Kim Seok Hun.
Then, I will get Hwang Jin Yong appointed as the leader of the opposition party to rival Jo Tae Seop.
Please become the leader of the party.
You...
have crossed the line.
Do you like fishing?
The sun has to set and dew has to settle for fish to come out at this reservoir.
Until then, you have to keep throwing bait
and wait.
Just wait a little bit.
It'll be night soon and it will be covered in dew.
I apologize.
The trigger has already been pulled.
Wow! It's a big fish before the night dew.
You'll also be able to catch big fish at the National Assembly!
Oh, Sang Man. What's up?
Yes, Hyeong. I discovered something a little weird.
- What is it?
- You know the big JQ Construction investor Park Jong Hyeok that we talked about last time?
I hacked into the system and did some investigating.
That person's IP address...
Are you sure?
Okay.
Prosecutor Kim is here.
Welcome, I was surprised by your sudden contact.
What brings you all the way here?
I needed to check something.
- Confirm?
- Yeah.
I will step outside.
Hold on.
I would like to speak to you.
Management and Strategy Chief Office
I was going to tell you at the right opportunity. You beat me to it.
I simply returned to Jo Tae Seop, Park Dae Ho, and Kim Yeong Il what they gave to me.
My name is too well known so I asked Mr. Park.
He was a former special agent, so he's been using the alias Park Jin Hyeok.
instead of his real name, Park Jong Hyeok. He was perfect for this plan.
I see.
I had no idea it was the Office Manager Park I knew. I thought another major shareholder had surfaced.
I'm sorry for confusing you.
It's fine. This happened because I didn't know your real name.
On the other hand, I'm impressed by your intel source.
You should be impressed.
But if I noticed, I'm sure Jo Tae Seop did too.
He'll figure it out soon too.
This could be dangerous for you.
The only reason Jo Tae Seop left you alone is because you didn't get involved in this game.
But you already got yourself involved.
So?
We have the upper hand now. That's all we should focus on.
Do you think I didn't expect this when I started? My dad told me something.
"When the fight starts, only focus on winning."
"Don't deviate even if you bleed."
"Just think about crushing the opponent."
I've already stepped into the boxing ring. I can't pull out now.
It's now how risky it is.  I am focused only on winning.
How large a stake in JQ Constructions' shares did you gather up through Sang Man?
About 3.4 percent. You?
I have two percent.
That means together we have over five percent.
If we buy a little more we should be able to earn management rights.
Sang Man invested around 20 billion won with JQ Constructions' shares as collateral.
But it seems Kim Yeong Il wants to borrow more than that.
Borrow more?
He must not be afraid of debt.
If we are successful in acquiring more shares, we might be able to take over JQ Construction.
Relay this to Sang Man.
A big player nuna who wants to invest in JQ Constructions is looking forward to his call.
Okay.
That'll make that kid happy.
Contact me if you ever need me.
Thank you.
- I'll be on my way now.
- Bye.
Here's the investment contract.
Kim Yeong Il is asking to borrow an even bigger sum.
Lend it to him, since there's already collateral.
Because the amount is so big, it's a bit burdensome.
Should I decrease the burden a bit?
How?
That big private investor. It was one of Hui Ah's people.
Yes! I knew it.
Hui Ah says she wants to invest in JQ Construction with you.
Nuna Hui Ah said that?
Happy?
-  Meet up with her and discuss it.
- She wants to... to meet me?
Hyeong, what has happened to me?
Does she like me?
Yes, sir.
I'm on the way to meet Kim Jeong Taek.
If this time things go again as you expect, I will make a bid.
Leader of the party.
I fact-checked the material you gave me.
JQ Construction and Bando Bank's illegal loan.
It was true after all.
You asked before how long I was going to live as Jo Tae Seop's puppet.
I won't.
So I have a request to make.
For the moment, I'm going to bow before Jo Tae Seop.
Seizing the opportunity while my opponent is off guard...
Material Concerning Bando Bank's Loan to JQ Construction
please expose this.
Exactly like the last time.
The outcome will be different
since we also have the prosecution.
List of Daehan Party Assemblyman Nominees
I will follow your wishes.
It's our party's list of nominations.
Get ready. It'll come out shortly.
Yes.
Material concerning Bando Bank's Loan to JQ Construction
Jo Tae Seop.
You underestimated me.
He knows my weakness, yet he pretends to act innocent?
Should I contact Chief Prosecutor Kim Seok Hun?
That's alright. Not yet.
Making a move now will only be venting my anger.
There's nothing to gain.
Rat-like bastards.
Thank you for coming again. I guess the taste suits you well.
Because it's been a while since you've come,
Hui Wu's mother put out the entire kitchen.
- Here.
- You always pack up food whenever we come here.
We are the ones who are thankful.
It's me you should say thanks to.
It was hard to bring out the entire kitchen. Since I'm the king in the kitchen.
Madam, when it comes to food, mine is tastier, no?
What are you saying?
Hui Wu, tell me honestly.
Between mine and your dad's, whose is tastier?
- Excuse me?
- Prosecutor, tell us the truth.
That is...
That's it. It's exactly that!
- When you get married, don't take anyone's side.
- Right.
You're right. I didn't think of it. When we got married,
I said my mom's food was tasty and suffered at lot at your mom's hands.
However, I'm on your side.
Indeed, Prosecutor Ji has sense.
Fake prosecutor, please leave. Get out immediately.
Get out. Get out.
Welcome.
I wasn't saying that to you.
Please sit here.
It's tomorrow.
Kim Seok Hun's confirmation hearing.
Right. How sweet. It's been a while since we got together.
- Here, let's drink!
- Yes.
Chief Prosecutor is coming.
- Goodbye, sir.
Why are you all out here when it's not even anything special?
Let's proceed, Prosecutor General.
- Goodbye, sir.
Goodbye, sir.
We will now begin the confirmation hearing of the Prosecutor General nominee.
"I swear to tell the truth in accordance
with my conscience without evasion and aid.
You may now question the nominee.
Making false resident registrations, falsifying contracts, or committing property speculation.
Indeed, it's befitting a candidate for the next prosecutor general.
Thank you.
As a prosecutor, I did not do anything that ran counter to my position.
As you're a member of JQ Group, people are concerned
that you may go easy on the wealthy.
What do you think in regard to this?
I can understand where it's coming from.
While living as a prosecutor for over twenty years,
I have never been shaken by improper requests or bribes.
Also, my in-laws' and my work are completely separate.
If you become the prosecutor general, what would you like to change first?
Our agency comes across as rigid and unapproachable.
I want people to see it as a flexible and friendly agency, so the people can freely communicate with us.
Hello.
I'm Prosecutor Jeon Seok Gyu of the Central District Office.
I will now begin the briefing about Nominee Kim Seok Hun's son,
Managing Director Kim Yeong Il of JQ Constructions. During this briefing, I'll disclose the corruption behind the bidding
for the construction site as well as the embezzlement of the deposits for apartment units.
Hold on. Did you run this by the public relations officer?
He's in the confirmation hearing to be the Prosecutor General and you're going after his son?
What does that matter?
Isn't telling the truth a journalist's spirit?
If you're not going to write the article, please leave. I will tell the truth by myself.
I guess I'll get an exclusive.
Please continue, Manager Jeon Seok Gyu.
Criminal Investigation Division Five noticed a sign of collusion between public and private sectors
and the unlawful involvement of civil servants during the bidding process of development areas in Gusan and launched an investigation.
JQ Construction colluded with its competitor to win the bidding with the lowest price,
and they offered bribes to civil servants to look away from this corruption (turn a blind eye).
On top of that, they also embezzled the deposits for apartment units.
Therefore, they should be severely punished.
Assemblymen, do you have any other questions?
I know it will be hard, but please stay until the end.
A news flash has surfaced.
Please check.
- What?
- What is it?
Sir, please take a look.
Arrest Warrant Issued for Managing Director Kim Yeong Il
Nominee Kim Seok Hun.
It's been confirmed that your son, Managing Director Kim Yeong Il, indeed committed corruption.
What's your opinion?
Please tell us.
You didn't know about this, okay?
But sir...
You are my last stronghold.
It's preparation for when things go bad for us.
Enough. Don't look at me that way.
My wife asked how long I was going to work at the prosecutor's office.
You know. Promotions have gone down the drain but it's midnight by the time you leave work.
Even the kids say the neighbor is better than you.
I don't have any regrets now.
You kids. Don't make that kind of face.
I put in my years for my pension.
Drink up!
What do you plan to do?
The citizens are full of distrust.
Do you perhaps intend to see it to the end?
What should I do?
Resign voluntarily.
Assemblyman.
Are you asking me to save you?
Is that possible now?
I will turn over the Cheonha Holdings shares my son has to you.
Why?
I am hoping you will spend it in the national interest.
In the national interest, you say.
- Look here, Manager Han.
- Yes.
Release Kim Jeong Taek's corruption incident.
Yes, sir.
As for you, go and arrest Kim Jeong Taek.
Cover your name with Kim Jeong Taek's name.
Thank you, Assemblyman.
But that won't be enough.
It won't even make a dent.
JQ Construction shareholders and victims won't forget this incident.
There's only one way.
It's to eliminate the cause when there's a problem.
You have a great precedent.
Choi Kang Jin does.
He himself informed the authorities about his own father.
Arrest your son with your hands.
Sir...
Your son broke the law, so you must punish him.
Before others arrest him, you arrest him.
Think about everything else after you become the prosecutor general.
Whether you get him out on probation or keep him in prison,
take care of that as you see fit.
Become a righteous prosecutor.
I will turn the public opinion.
And Jeon Seok Gyu.
Don't provoke him.
For now, embrace Jeon Seok Gyu.
And when it quiets down, kick him out then.
Yes, sir.
Prosecution Service
Come in.
Chief Prosecutor Kim Seok Hun
You called for me.
Arrest Kim Yeong Il.
Immediately.
Yes, sir.
You were supposed to expose him!
Why did you not touch Bando Bank's illegal loan?
Kim, I'm not a dog you've raised.
Did you think I wouldn't know what you were thinking?
By ordering me to do the divulging,
what were you going to do?
You probably thought
you could make me do the dangerous work and, if things went wrong, you'd get out.
Did you think I wouldn't see right through your wickedness?
Assemblyman!
A person like you isn't suited to be a party representative.
Step down now.
Hwang Jin Yong!
Sir.
Kim Jung Taek Soon to Be Summoned On Corruption Charges
Prosecutor Yun Jong Gi
Daehan Party Leader Kim Jeong Taek
There's no way I can drown with you.
Hwang Jin Yong too. Jeon Seok Gyu, the tiger too.
To find a way to live,
they did not provoke Bando Bank.
- A comment, sir!
- Any comments?
- Please answer our questions!
- Tell us the truth!
Please one comment!
Are the allegations true?
Did you know about this?
Do you admit to the charges?
- Sir! A comment!
- Please answer our questions.
Please answer our questions.
For corrupt loans,
Executive Director Kim Yeong Il of JQ Construction
was detained by the Central District Prosecutor's Office today.
Today's detention resulted from Executive Director Kim Yong Il's father and
Central District Prosecution's Chief Prosecutor Kim Seok Hun's special order.
Through a briefing by the prosecution service, Chief Prosecutor Kim
revealed that he tried to be faithful to a prosecutor's duties.
Assemblyman, he's arrived.
Did you come together?
Escort him in.
Please come in.
Welcome.
You're riding in a nice car.
What is it?
Why don't you ride in the crap car today?
I came to escort you, as a prosecutor.
Prosecutor Lee Min Su, isn't it about time now to give up?
But I obtained a warrant again.
Arrest Warrant
I won't give up.
Until I catch you. Until the end.
Mirae Electronics' CEO Jeon Il Bo stood trial for bribery and a violation
of the Act on the Aggravated Punishment of Specific Crimes and was released on probation in his first trial.
He has been detained again by the prosecutors on yet another charge.
Go first.
Did you come here to say hello?
So you could order a fancy meal for him again? Too bad.
But it won't work.
Jeon Il Bo is mine.
I'll give him food and I'll also give him the punishment.
So don't provoke me.
If you provoke me, know that your life will also end in a prison.
This time, I won't let you off.
Prosecution Service
Jeon Il Bo was arrested.
Did Kim Seok Hun allow this?
I apologize. Prosecutor Lee Min Su is someone difficult to control.
President Jeon Il Bo will soon—
Carry it out according to the law.
That bastard Jeon Il Bo has committed too many crimes.
And bringing down Jeon Il Bo will look great in your resume for your future title.
Yes, I understand.
Kim Hui Wu.
Yes.
If you didn't exist, I would have chosen to live having fun.
But not now.
Because I found something more fun.
Fighting with you.
I am going to work for Assemblyman Jo Tae Seop.
I know.
That the person who framed my father is Jo Tae Seop.
But at that time, Assemblyman Jo Tae Seop was a prosecutor
and was only doing his job.
Seonbae.
Don't worry.
I will keep my mouth shut and help with bringing down Kim Seok Hun.
That way, there's the right balance to the game.
Right, Bro?
You'll keep quiet and help Kim Seok Hun's fall.
Our last partnership?
Then, you will fight me?
Yup.
Yes, fine.
Let's do it.
♫  Dear, All your things you've done  ♫
♫  We are here to wreck it up  ♫
♫  Who knows, how will it go?  ♫
♫  Hiding in black and white  ♫
♫  We are here to find the truth  ♫
♫  Give up, I warn you so  ♫
♫  Who would ever find out who you really are? Hm  ♫
Again My Life
Let's kick Kim Seok Hun out fast.
Don't kneel!
Are you going to use him as an excuse?
He saw my weakness. So I need to know at least one of his.
If you want a deal, bring me something worthy,
not your threat.
Our partnership ends today.
Sit. If you leave now, it won't end with you going home.
Next, I must get rid of Park Dae Ho, Jo Tae Seop's source of funds.
♫  Let them get what they want  ♫
Again My Life