[English subtitles are available]
[Third Semester, Major Field Mission]
Idol specialty.
[Vocal, Rap, Dance]
Vocal, rap, dance.
[To get the position you want]
To get this position,
[1v1 battle for positions]
you will engage in 1v1 battle.
1v1.
[So cruel]
So cruel.
-Stay back.
-Hello.
[The trainees begin battling for the positions they want]
I'm so disappointed.
[I'm so disappointed]
Juwnon, please.
[Please]
Junwon, listen to me.
[16th in Second Semester,
Kang Minseo: So cruel.]
So cruel.
[20th in Second Semester
Keum Jinho:
I feel like I got stabbed in the back.]
I feel like I got stabbed in the back.
Hanbin, I'm sorry. Come out.
[Sighing]
This won't do.
[The third semester is about to begin]
[Special MC Minho]
[I have "I will die if Gyurae doesn't debut" disease]
[Gyurae]
[I want to survive today]
I want to survive today.
For the third semester's Major Field Mission,
[Major Field Mission]
[The trainees choose either the vocal, rap, or dance position in the song of their choice to form a team]
the trainee who ranks 1st during the live voting
[Major Field Mission]
[This mission is a group battle.
For each field, the trainee that ranks 1st across the five teams
will receive a benefit]
will not only receive an individual benefit.
Please.
[Special MC Minho: Everyone in a group who has a 1st ranked trainee]
Everyone in a group who has a 1st ranked trainee
[Special MC Minho: will receive the benefit.]
-will receive the benefit.
-So good.
It doesn't matter who gets it.
[26th in Second Semester, Vocal, Ha Seokhee:
It doesn't matter who gets it.]
Please let one of us get it.
[The 1st for each field must come from our team]
The first performance,
[Special MC Minho: The first performance]
a mega hit by one of the producers, is highly anticipated.
[Special MC Minho: a mega hit by one of the producers, is highly anticipated.]
Let's watch it now.
[Special MC Minho: Let's watch it now]
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
In the second semester, "Deja Vu" and "Thunderous" won first place.]
Didn't our teams place 1st in the Second Semester?
[Hyping themselves up
Will we win again?]
We're going to place 1st again.
-What?
-1st in my group.
[(Beomjun, you never placed 1st before, right)]
I was 1st in my group too.
1st in his group, 1st in his group, 1st in his group.
["Crown" 1st place: Hikaru]
["90s' Love" 1st place: Oh Hyeontae]
["Deja Vu" 1st place: Hong Sungmin]
Our team members did a great job.
[Our team members did a great job.]
[10th in Second Semester, Dance, Oh Hyeontae:
To be honest, I think our team is very balanced.]
To be honest, I think our team is very balanced.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
I ranked 33rd in the Second Semester.]
I ranked 33rd in the Second Semester.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
It felt like a diagnosis of a terminal illness.]
It felt like a diagnosis of a terminal illness.
I think this is an opportunity for me.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
I think this is an opportunity for me.]
Have you decided which song to choose?
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
Have you decided which song to choose?]
Yes.
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal Lee Hanbin:
Yes!]
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
I chose "Really Really"]
I chose "Really Really"
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
to create a legendary stage.]
to create a legendary stage.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
Strategizing to get the benefit]
Strategizing to get the benefit
will help someone like me survive.
[I must survive!]
Sungmin.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
Sungmin was 1st]
Sungmin was 1st
so in many ways, he can make up for my shortcomings.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
[3rd in Second Semester, Hikaru]
I can improve my ranking by a lot.]
I can improve my ranking by a lot.
[10th in Second Semester, Oh Hyeontae]
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
This is a rare chance.]
This is a rare chance.
[13th in Second Semester, Kim Gyurae]
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
This is a rare chance.]
[13th in Second Semester, Kim Gyurae]
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
I think we can get the benefit.]
I think we can get the benefit.
[21st in Second Semester, Hikaru
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
I think we can get the benefit.]
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
Beomjun (33rd in Second Semester) must survive.
Beomjun must survive.
[Stay alive!]
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
We'll do our best]
We'll do our best
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
to keep Beomjun alive.]
to keep Beomjun alive.
[1st in Second Semester, Dance, Hong Sungmin:
"Operation Save Beomjun (33rd in Second Semester)" involves]
"Operation Save Beomjun" involves
[Getting 1st place at least twice to earn at least two benefits]
earning at least two benefits
so Beomjun can survive.
[So Beomjun (33rd in second semester) can survive!!]
["Really Really" Vocal position:
16th in Second Semester, Lee Hanbin
3rd in Second Semester, Hikaru]
♫ I'm in front of your house ♫
♫ I like you ♫
["Really Really" Rap position:
33rd in Second Semester, Kim Beomjun
13th in Second Semester, Kim Gyurae
3rd in Second Semester, Hikari]
♫  Honey or baby or darling ♫
♫ The criminal who stole my heart ♫
["Really Really" Dance position:
1st in Second Semester, Hong Sungmin
10th in Second Semester, Oh Hyeontae]
[No position
All parts that any member can choose]
♫ I like you ♫
♫ Really Really Really Really ♫
♫ Please accept my heart ♫
Let's divide the parts.
[1st in Second Semester, Dance, Hong Sungmin:
Let's divide the parts.]
[Distributing All parts]
(Prelude) [All]
(Hey) Really Really Really Really
(Oh Wah) Really Really Really Really Hey
The first part.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun is first to raise a suggestion]
(Prelude) [All]
(Hey) Really Really Really Really
(Oh Wah) Really Really Really Really Hey
This part, "Hey."
I like WINNER,
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
I like WINNER, so I watched their performance.
(Prelude) [All]
(Hey) Really Really Really Really
(Oh Wah) Really Really Really Really Hey
so I watched their performance.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
One member shouts "Hey" into his microphone]
One member shouts "Hey" into his microphone
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
and walks out like this.]
(Prelude) [All]
(Hey) Really Really Really Really
(Oh Wah) Really Really Really Really Hey
and walks out like this.
[Hey!]
♫ Hey ♫
So I want to do the "Hey" part.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
So I want to do the "Hey" part.]
Hyping the crowd up is your strong suit.
[1st in Second Semester, Dance, Hong Sungmin:
Hyping the crowd up is your strong suit.]
Yes, that's right.
[Can I do this part? >.<]
Can I do this part?
"Hey," and then start singing. Okay.
[Okay I'll do it]
I'll do this.
Hold the microphone and say "Hey."
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun
will hold the microphone and say "Hey."
Okay.
[Everyone agrees 33rd in Second Semester, Kim Beomjun
will be in charge of the beginning of the rap]
Beomjun will open for us.
I really think so.
[21st in Second Semester, Vocal, Hikaru:
Only in this way can we be more confident on stage]
Only in this way can we be more confident on stage
[Low ranking
Team members accept Beomjun's opinion]
"Operation Save Beomjun."
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun
continues to offer suggestions]
This is a rap. The part before this
[Because of the pressure of elimination, he asks for more and more parts]
is like an exposition. I want this part.
[33rd in Second Semester, Kim Beomjun
wants to sing the first chorus of the All part]
[(Um...)]
[Looking]
Is this the part?
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun
has his eyes on the first chorus for the sake of the impact of his Rap part]
Yes.
But the first part is...
[1st in Second Semester, Hong Sungmin:
But the first part is...]
I think Hyeontae 10th in Second Semester) should come out here.]
I think Hyeontae should come out here.
The second and third parts are followed directly by the dance.
[If we take out the dance break,
(10th in Second Semester) Oh Hyeontae won't have a chance to stand in the center]
-Okay.
-If Hyeontae comes out,
it can only be in the first part.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
The first chorus is an impactful part.]
The first chorus is an impactful part.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
I want to survive too.]
I want to survive too.
[I'm very greedy now]
I'm very greedy now.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
That's why I'm taking initiative.]
That's why I'm taking initiative.
Actually,
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
Oh... Actually]
I was happy at first,
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
I was happy at first]
but (33rd in Second Semester) Kim Beomjun's greediness for parts was a bit unpleasant.]
but it was a bit unpleasant.
[On the day of the interim evaluation]
WINNER's "Really Really."
Please come forward.
Okay.
♫ Really Really Really Really ♫
[Hey!
"Really Really" Team starts with a cheerful word.]
♫ Oh Wah ♫
♫ Really Really Really Really ♫
♫ Where are you ♫
♫ Are you home ♫
[16th in Second Semester, Lee Hanbin and
21st in Second Semester, Hikaru are performing well in their vocals]
♫ Are you busy ♫
♫ Come out ♫
♫ If my feelings for you were money ♫
♫ I’m a billionaire ♫
[He did the high note successfully]
[I like you.]
♫ I like you ♫
[Satisfied]
[Vocal trainer, Jeon Woongmin: They're doing well.]
They're doing well.
♫ I like you ♫
[Perfect chemistry of the Vocal position:
16th in Second Semester, Lee Hanbin and
21st in Second Semester, Hikaru]
♫ Really Really Really Really ♫
[First chorus
33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun
took on the All part by himself]
♫ Trust Me Oh Woah ♫
♫ Really Really Really Really ♫
♫ I like you ♫
♫ What do you think of me ♫
[33rd in Second Semester, Kim Beomjun's rap part follows immediately after]
♫ My goal is to score (Shoot) ♫
♫ Even if there's a goalkeeper, I'll aim for you ♫
♫ I'll tell you how I feel ♫
♫ (Boom boom) Who will stop this feeling ♫
[The other members have relatively fewer parts]
♫ (Oh) Look at me ♫
♫ Really Really Really Really ♫
♫ What do you think of me ♫
[Mid song Dance part by
1st in Second Semester, Hong Sungmin
and 10th in Second Semester, Oh Hyeontae]
[Dance Break that highlights the Dance position member, 10th in Second Semester, Oh Hyeontae]
[Vocal trainer, Park Soomin: I like your part, Hikaru]
I like your part, Hikaru.
[Eardrums, Happiness]
♫ I like you ♫
You've worked hard.
[You've worked hard.]
-Thank you.
[What's Main Producer JINYOUNG's evaluation?]
Let me give you some advice.
[Producer JINYOUNG: Um... Let me give you some advice.]
Actually your group is doing well.
[Producer JINYOUNG: Actually, your group is doing well.]
Beomjun not only raps
[Producer JINYOUNG: Beomjun not only raps]
but also sings the melody with Hanbin.
[Producer JINYOUNG: but also sings the melody with Hanbin.]
But Hyeontae doesn't have an individual singing part, right?
[Producer JINYOUNG: But Hyeontae doesn't have an individual singing part, right?]
Right?
He's a great vocal.
[Main Producer JINYOUNG: He's a great vocal.]
He's one of your team's strongest members.
[Main Producer JINYOUNG: Hyeontae is one of your team's]
[Main Producer JINYOUNG: strongest members.]
You must use him.
[You must use Hyeontae]
After all, it will help your team perform better, right?
[Main Producer JINYOUNG: After all, it will help your team perform better, right?]
So think about this
[Main Producer JINYOUNG: So think about this]
before distributing the parts.
[His evaluation is that the part distribution needs to be more strategic]
That way, you will have a better fighting chance.
[Main Producer JINYOUNG: That way, you will have a better fighting chance.]
[Vocal trainer Jang Jinyoung:
If you want the team to stand out... Aren't there highly-ranked members?]
If you want the team to stand out...
Aren't there highly-ranked members?
[Vocal trainer Jang Jinyoung:
You need to show their faces to make the fans happy.]
You need to show their faces to make the fans happy.
[Feedback that 1st in Second Semester, Hong Sungmin
and 10th in Second Semester, Oh Hyeontae could not be seen]
It's not obvious now.
I'm confident I won't lose to the more highly ranked members.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
I'm confident I won't lose to the more highly ranked members.]
It's not clear yet.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
It's not clear yet.]
After singing, I realized
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
After singing, I realized]
(1st in Second Semester) Hong Sungmin
and (10th in Second Semester) Oh Hyeontae really couldn't be seen]
they really couldn't be seen.
[After the interim evaluation, "Really Really" Team is redistributing parts]
How about this?
The part Hyeontae sings, the third part...
[16th in Second Semester, Lee Hanbin:
speaks up first as the oldest member]
Why not we give this part to Beomjun
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
Give (10th in Second Semester) Oh Hyeontae's part
to (33rd in Second Semester) Kim Beomjun]
and let Hyeontae handle this himself?
[Suggestion to give the All part in the first chorus to
10th in Second Semester, Oh Hyeontae]
You have two parts and Hikaru has one.
I think it's better to choose this.
[Objection!]
The first chorus is the first complete chorus.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
The first chorus is the first complete chorus.]
The rap part after it is my part.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
The rap part after it is my part.]
If I hype it up before the rap part,]
If I hype it up before the rap part,
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
it will be more impressive.]
it will be more impressive.
"Really Really"'s choreography
[1st in Second Semester, Dance, Hong Sungmin:
"Really Really"'s choreography]
during the climax is very famous.
[1st in Second Semester, Dance, Hong Sungmin:
during the climax is very famous.]
I think
[1st in Second Semester, Dance, Hong Sungmin:
I think]
it'll be good to give this part to Hyeontae.
[To highlight the choreography, we should give this part to Dance position, Hyeontae]
Hyeontae's ranking is high too.
[10th in Second Semester, Oh Hyeontae's ranking is high]
I know what you mean.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun
is the only one who disagrees]
But as a rapper...
I was very proactive in the part distribution from the beginning.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
I was very proactive in the part distribution from the beginning.]
-I feel apologetic towards Hyeontae (10th in Second Semester) too (because he doesn't have a part).
-I feel apologetic towards Hyeontae too.
-Yes.
My ranking is too low.
[My ranking is too low.]
-Actually.
Amongst the highly-ranked trainees,
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
Amongst the highly-ranked trainees,]
I'm ranked relatively low.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
I'm ranked relatively low.]
I don't want to give in easily.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
I don't want to give in easily.]
[Silence caused by disagreement]
I think it's better to leave it to someone suitable.
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
I think it's better to leave it to someone suitable.]
But there's one thing.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
But, but]
Don't ask for the part if you think you won't do it well. Are you confident?
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
Don't ask for the part if you think you won't do it well.]
[I'm confident I can do it]
I'm confident I can do it well.
Are you confident?
I think it is most important to highlight your position.
[The most important thing in the Third Semester is to highlight your position.]
So I think doing your best at your own part
[21st in Second Semester, Vocal, Hikaru:
So I think doing your best at your own part is the right thing to do.]
is the right thing to do.
What I want to say is I have absolute confidence in my part.
I can do it better than anyone else.
[Of course I'm confident about my part.]
I could tell everyone was getting flustered.
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
As the discussion went on, I could tell everyone was getting flustered.]
So I thought I had to say it firmly.
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
So I thought I had to say it firmly.]
It was for Beomjun's sake,
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
It was for Beomjun's sake,]
as well as the whole team's.
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
as well as the whole team's.]
To be frank,
[Let me say something harsh]
you want to change the rap lyrics, right?
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
you want to change the rap lyrics, right?]
You haven't changed them, have you?
[You haven't changed them, have you? Aren't you in charge of rap?]
Aren't you in charge of rap?
Right?
We have three rappers on our team.
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
We have three rappers on our team.]
But Gyurae and Hikaru's rap parts are half the length of yours.
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
But Gyurae and Hikaru's rap parts are half the length of yours.]
You show up again in the bridge.
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin:
You show up again in the bridge.]
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
has more parts than the other members]
Considering all this,
[Hanbin hopes Beomjun should be less greedy and focus on his Rap part]
you must perform well in this part. We are all thinking this.
Not only me.
I also...
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
I also...]
You may not understand how I feel.
[You may not understand how I feel.]
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
I'm dying.]
I'm dying.
You want to survive, right? Then we must get the benefit.
[1st in Second Semester, Dance, Hong Sungmin:
You want to survive, right? Then we must get the benefit.]
In that case...
[(Giving the part to Hyeontae is the right move)
To be honest, on one hand, I felt very sorry for him.
[1st in Second Semester, Dance, Hong Sungmin:
To be honest, on one hand, I felt very sorry for him.]
But on the other hand,]
But on the other hand,
is it necessary to be so attached to that part?
[Is it necessary to be so attached to that part?]
They don't know how it feels to be in the 30th place.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
They don't know how it feels to be lower than the 30th place.]
[No way.]
No way.
I'm always nervous and afraid of being eliminated.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
I'm always nervous and afraid of being eliminated.]
I didn't come here to be eliminated so early.]
I didn't come here to be eliminated so early.
It'll be over. That's what I think.
[It'll be over. That's what I think.]
It's complicated.
[21st in Second Semester, Vocal, Hikaru:
Everyone's interests are very complicated. It's complicated.]
It's complicated.
[Complicated]
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
Don't touch the ground with the hand holding the microphone.]
[D-3 to Third Semester Competition
Don't touch the ground with the hand holding the microphone.
You can do it. When you do this...
[Another argument after assigning parts]
Like this.
[Handheld microphone VS headset microphone]
It looks cool because
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun
wants to use handheld microphones on stage]
people think you look good even when you're dancing with a microphone.
The handheld microphone is like a prop.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
The handheld microphone is like a prop.]
Visually, when you're singing or rapping,
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
Visually, when you're singing or rapping,]
holding a microphone makes you look cooler.
[Holding a microphone makes you look cooler.]
You can touch the ground with this hand.
[10th in Second Semester, Dance, Oh Hyeontae:
Okay. Then show me something that looks better.]
Okay. Then show me something that looks better.
[10th in Second Semester, Dance, Oh Hyeontae:
Show me. Don't be all talk.]
-Like this.
-Let me see. Don't be all talk.
[Using a bottle in place of a microphone and trying to practice the Dance Break]
[It's hard to do the Dance Break choreograhy while holding a microphone]
[21st in Second Semester, Hikaru
watching from the side]
Okay.
It's a bit awkward.
Do you have time to talk?
[21st in Second Semester, Vocal, Hikaru:
Do you have time to talk?]
[All members are gathered.]
-Me too?
-Yes.
It's quite...
[21st in Second Semester, Vocal, Hikaru:
It's quite...]
Didn't we talk about holding a microphone?
[21st in Second Semester, Vocal, Hikaru:
Didn't we talk about holding a microphone?]
We agreed on it.
[21st in Second Semester, Vocal, Hikaru:
We agreed on it.]
If we use handheld microphones,
[21st in Second Semester, Vocal, Hikaru:
If we use handheld microphones,]
we'll have to change the choreography for dance break.
[21st in Second Semester, Vocal, Hikaru:
we'll have to change the choreography for the Dance Break?]
No, not yet.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
No, not yet.]
I'm not sure if we'll change the choreography.
[10th in Second Semester, Dance, Oh Hyeontae:
I'm not sure if we'll change the choreography.]
We're not sure so everyone is lost.
[21st in Second Semester, Vocal, Hikaru:
We're not sure if we will change the choreography]
so everyone is lost.]
Beomjun, a rapper, wanted to hold a microphone.
[21st in Second Semester, Vocal, Hikaru:
Beomjun, a rapper, wanted to hold a microphone.]
He was very insistent.]
He was very insistent.
We didn't know how to deal with it.
[We didn't know how to deal with it.]
It may not matter,
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
It may not matter,]
but it's a lethal weapon for me.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun:
but it's a lethal weapon for me.]
One, two, three.
["Ready Ready" Team's Third Semester stage
whose members had the most conflict]
[Overcome their disagreement
Will they finish the performance successfully?]
[Kim Gyurae] [Gyurae]
[Focused gaze]
[(Hoping it can be completed successfully)]
[Vibe] "Really Really" Realz
Original song: WINNER
[Kim Gyurae] [Hong Sungmin]
[Oh Hyeontae] [Hong Sungmin] [Taeseon] [Ahh]
[All]
♫ Really Really ♫
♫Oh Wah♫
[Hikaru]
♫ Where are you ♫
[Vocal]
[Lee Hanbin]
♫ Are you home ♫
[Hikaru]
♫ Are you busy ♫
[Lee Hanbin]
♫ Come out ♫
[Hikaru]
♫ I'm in front of your house ♫
♫ Wanna tell you something ♫
[Hikaru]
♫  Don’t know how to say it but ♫
♫ I don’t know ♫
[Oh Hyeontae] [Hikaru]
[Vocal]
[Kim Gyurae]
[Hikaru]
♫ It’s nothing weird ♫
♫ No pressure ♫
[Lee Hanbin]
♫ In my eyes ♫
♫ The most beautiful thing ♫
[Lee Hanbin]
♫ Is you, Lady ♫
-Good job.
-Hanbin, what?
[Taeseon is incapacitated]
[Vocal]
It's so similar.
[Producer SOYEON: It's so similar to SEUNGYOON's voice.]
[Lee Hanbin]
♫ In my eyes ♫
[Vocal]
[Lee Hanbin]
♫ The most beautiful thing ♫
♫ Is you, Lady ♫
[Lee Hanbin]
♫ If my feelings for you ♫
♫ If you measure it with money ♫
[Lee Hanbin]
♫ I may be a billionaire ♫
[Surprised]
[Vocal]
What?
[Good job!!]
[Vocal]
Good job.
[Hikaru]
♫ I like you ♫
[Ahh]
[All]
♫ Really Really ♫
[Oh Hyeontae]
♫ Trust me ♫
[All]
♫ Really Really ♫
[Oh Hyeontae]
♫ I like you ♫
[All]
♫ Really Really ♫
[Hikaru]
♫ Accept my heart ♫
[All]
♫ Really Really ♫
[Nervous] [All]
[Hikaru]
♫ What do you think about me ♫
[Kim Beomjun]
♫ My goal is to score ♫
[Rap]
[Kim Beomjun]
♫ Even if there's a goalkeeper ♫
♫ I'll still aim for you ♫
[Kim Beomjun]
♫ I'm going without hesitation, men don't worry ♫
♫ I'm only shouting "Hello" ♫
[Kim Beomjun]
♫ My gaze is too direct ♫
I can't hear him clearly.
[9th in Second Semester, Vocal, Taeseon:
I can't hear [his rap] clearly.]
[Kim Beomjun]
♫ Your haughty expression makes me nervous ♫
[Rap]
[Kim Beomjun]
♫ When will I get your green light ♫
♫ I can't stand it anymore, walking along the streets ♫
[Kim Gyurae]
♫ I am lost for you ♫
[Gyurae] [I'm also trapped in Gyurae's charm] [Rap]
[Kim Gyurae]
♫ I'll show you my heart ♫
[Rap]
[Kim Gyurae]
♫ Who will stop this feeling ♫
[The rap has him incapacitated] [Rap]
[Kim Gyurae]
♫ Look at me ♫
[Rap]
[Hikari]
♫ Shoot out towards your wavering heart ♫
♫ From now on, you'll be sold out to me ♫
[Huh? Shoot out?]
Why are they targeting our group?
[18th in Second Semester, Jin Myungjae:
Why are they targeting our group?]
[Hikari]
♫ Shoot out towards your wavering heart ♫
[Rap]
[Hikari]
♫ From now on, you'll be sold out to me ♫
♫ Building up my confidence, I love you ♫
[Hikari]
♫ I really really ♫
♫ I like you, I will call you ♫
[Dance]
Let's go!
Dance!
[What is this?]
[Restriction]
Scorpion.
[All]
[Lee Hanbin]
♫ I like you ♫
[What? My heart flutters.]
[All]
♫ Really Really♫
[Hong Sungmin]
♫ Trust me ♫
[All]
♫ Really Really ♫
[Nodding] [All]
[All]
[Hong Sungmin]
♫ I like you ♫
[(Me too)!] [Sungmin is sexy] [I'm Sungmin's bride] [All]
[All]
♫ Really Really ♫
[Lee Hanbin]
♫ Accept my heart ♫
♫ Really Really ♫
-Hanbin.
[I got goosebumps. Hanbin's voice is amazing.] [All]
[All]
[Lee Hanbin]
♫ What do you think about me ♫
[Kim Beomjun]
♫ If you feel ♫
[Rap]
[Hikari]
♫ I made you uncomfortable, let me know ♫
[Kim Beomjun]
♫ I’ll take a step back ♫
[Hikari]
♫ Just be a guy you know ♫
♫ I can wait ♫
[Vocal]
[Lee Hanbin]
♫ Tell me you think you like me too ♫
[Hikaru]
♫ Let’s meet right now ♫
[Lee Hanbin]
♫  I have something to tell you ♫
[Hikaru]
♫ I like you ♫
[All]
♫ Really Really♫
They're so good at expressing themselves.
[Kim Beomjun]
♫ Trust me ♫
[So good] [Sungmin] [All]
[So good] [I Really Really like you, Hikari] [All]
[All]
♫ Really Really♫
[Kim Beomjun]
♫ I like you ♫
[All]
♫ Really Really♫
[Gyurae, debut] [Kim Gyurae, if only I gave birth to you] [All]
[Focused] [All]
[Hikaru]
♫ Accept my heart ♫
[All]
♫ Really Really♫
[Hikaru]
♫ What do you think about me ♫
[Dance]
[Hikari] [Dance]
[Oh Hyeontae]
[Dance]
♫ I like you ♫
[I like you~]
[Moon Hyunbin] [Like]
[21st in Second Semester, Hikaru]
[1st in Second Semester, Hong Sungmin]
[13th in Second Semester, Kim Gyurae]
[33rd in Second Semester, Kim Beomjun]
[10th in Second Semester, Oh Hyeontae]
[3rd in Second Semester, Hikari]
[16th in Second Semester, Lee Hanbin] [I like you]
[Encore!] [Encore!] [I can see the heart]
One, two, three.
[Heart launch!]
[(Heart Get+1)]
[(Heart Get+2)]
-There's fan service too.
-The fan service is good.
[Not bad]
[Producer WOOYOUNG: There's fan service too.]
The Third Semester's Major Field Mission,
[Special MC Minho: The Third Semester's Major Field Mission]
the first Team's performance is over.
[Special MC Minho: the first Team's performance is over.]
Who will be Fantasy Makers'
[Special MC Minho: Who will be Fantasy Makers']
favorite trainee be?
[Special MC Minho: favorite trainee be?]
[Special MC Minho: Voting for "Really Really" begins now.]
Voting for "Really Really" begins now.
[Lee Hanbin is handsome]
Let's start with the members in Vocal position.
[Special MC Minho: Let's start with the members in Vocal position.]
[Special MC Minho: Let's vote]
Let's vote.
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal, Lee Hanbin]
[21st in Second Semester, Vocal, Hikaru]
[You can do it!]
Hanbin is really stressful to be up against.
[7th in Second Semester, Kang Daehyeon:
Hanbin is really stressful to be up against.]
Good job, Hanbin.
[31st in Second Semester, Vocal, Kim Seungjun:
Good job, Hanbin.]
Hikaru is great, but Hanbin is more outstanding.
[8th in Second Semester, Vocal, Moon Hyunbin:
Hikaru is great, but Hanbin is more outstanding.]
Right?
[4th in Second Semester, Rap, K-Soul:
The performance on stage and on camera is different.]
The performance on stage and on camera is different.
It's really different.
Hanbin picked right.
[8th in Second Semester, Vocal, Moon Hyunbin:
"Really Really" was the right choice for Hanbin .]
Let's begin voting for the rap position members.
[Special MC Minho: Let's begin voting for the rap position members.]
[Extremely nervous]
[Hikari]
[13th in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Gyurae]
[3rd in Second Semester, Rap, Hikari]
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun]
It's so pressurizing for Beomjun.
[7th in Second Semester, Dance, Kang Daehyeon:
Live voting is so pressurizing for Beomjun.]
[26th in Second Semester, Vocal, Ha Seokhee
I totally understand how Beomjun is feeling.]
I totally understand how Beomjun is feeling.
[9th in Second Semester, Vocal, Taeseon:
Gyurae? Hikari? Beomjun? (Who will get 1st?)]
Gyurae? Hikari? Beomjun?
Beomjun.
[Beomjun! Beomjun!]
[Will Fantasy Makers think the same way?]
Lastly, we will be voting on
[Special MC Minho: Lastly, we will be voting on]
the Dance position members.
[Special MC Minho: the Dance position members.]
[The rankings are higher, and the screams are louder]
[Hong Sungmin]
[Oh Hyeontae] [Ahh]
Please press the number of the trainee that makes your heart beat faster.
[1st in Second Semester, Dance, Hong Sungmin]
[10th in Second Semester, Dance, Oh Hyeontae]
Both Sungmin and Hyeontae did well. If they all vote,
[8th in Second Semester, Moon Hyunbin:
Both Sungmin and Hyeontae did well. If they all vote (for both of them)]
the votes will be...
[8th in Second Semester, Moon Hyunbin:
the votes will be very concentrated.]
[Secretly showing off]
OK. The voting is about to end.
[Special MC Minho: The voting is about to end.]
Voting is over.
["Really Really" Team's voting is over]
Voting has ended for all positions.
[Special MC Minho: Voting has ended for all positions.]
First of all, what will Producer SEUNGYOON, who composed the song and lyrics,
[Special MC Minho: First of all, what will Producer SEUNGYOON, who composed the song and lyrics,]
[Special MC Minho: have to say about the stage?]
have to say about the stage?
First, Hanbin sang the high note
[Producer SEUNGYOON: First, Hanbin sang the high note]
[Producer SEUNGYOON: with much more ease than I expected. This is great.]
with much more ease than I expected. This is great.
But on the whole, I think
[Producer SEUNGYOON: But on the whole, I think]
I have to say something harsh.
[I have to say something harsh.]
You only focused on your own parts, right?
[Producer SEUNGYOON: You only focused on your own parts, right?]
[Producer SEUNGYOON: It even makes other people notice it.]
It even makes other people notice it.
[Producer SEUNGYOON: You were offbeat during the chorus.]
You were offbeat during the chorus.
[Producer SEUNGYOON: You didn't work well with each other.]
You didn't work well with each other.
Those parts were a shame.
The boy I really want to evaluate now is
[Producer SOYEON: The boy I really want to evaluate now is Beomjun.]
Beomjun.
If it's the Rap position,
[Producer SOYEON: If it's the Rap position, you should do better.]
you should do better.
You should do better.
Yes.
[Accepts]
In idol songs,
[Producer SOYEON: In idol songs,]
it's hard to get so many rap parts.
[Producer SOYEON: it's hard to get so many rap parts.]
So you really have to show it
[Producer SOYEON: So you really have to show it in all four or eight sentences.]
in all four or eight sentences.
[Producer SOYEON: I hope you practice more. Still, you've worked hard.]
I hope you practice more.
Still, you've worked hard.
Thank you.
[Emergency] [Hong Sungmin suddenly cries.]
Don't cry.
-Why are you crying? -Sungmin.
[Why are you crying?]
-Don't cry. -Don't cry.
[(My heart aches)]
-It's okay. It's okay.
-Sungmin. -Don't cry.
[29th in Second Semester, Rap Position, Kang Irang: Sungmin, don't cry. T T]
We've finished counting the votes for the "Really Really" team.
[Voting is over]
So, how did the Fantasy Makers
[MC CHANGMIN: So, how did the Fantasy Makers]
evaluate everyone?
[MC CHANGMIN: evaluate everyone?]
Now, let's announce the voting result.
[MC CHANGMIN: Now, let's announce the voting result.]
Don't cry.
[But, 1st in Second Semester, Hong Sungmin can't stop crying]
[The more I try, the more I cry...]
[Surprised Heartache]
Sungmin, you did well!
[The Fantasy makers trying to console the sad boys]
Good job.
Our Sungmin!
[MC CHANGMIN: Sungmin.]
[MC CHANGMIN: I think it's because it's a pity. He's likely shedding tears of regret.]
I think it's because it's a pity.
He's likely shedding tears of regret.
[Oh Hyeontae is the best] [MC CHANGMIN: I want to tell you that you did great.]
I want to tell you that you did great.
[My heart is broken.]
[Good job, Sungmin!]
Good job, Sungmin.
[Also crying]
First, I'll announce the ranking for the Vocal position members
[MC CHANGMIN: First, I'll announce the ranking for the Vocal position members]
[MC CHANGMIN: of the "Really Really" team.]
of the "Really Really" team.
[REALY REALY] [Vocal Position Battle]
[21st in Second Semester, Hikaru VS 16th in Second Semester, Lee Hanbin]
The ranking for the Vocal position members of "Really Really" team is...
[MC CHANGMIN: The ranking for the Vocal position members of "Really Really" team is...]
[Producer KANGSEUNGYOON: Will Hanbin rank higher?]
Will Hanbin rank higher?
[I'm not sure]
Please reveal the result.
[Please reveal the result.]
[Nervous]
[Lee Hanbin]
[1st place: Lee Hanbin] [2nd place: Hikaru]
[Hanbin (Congratulations)]
Hikaru is in 2nd place.
[Vocal Position 2nd place: Hikaru]
In the 1st place...
Lee Hanbin.
[Vocal Position 1st place: Lee Hanbin]
[15th in Second Semester, Dance Position, Kang Minseo: Don't cry from the start.]
Don't cry from the start.
[(Good job, brother!)]
[Sorry, guys]
I'm sorry, guys.
["Really Really" Team Vocal Ranking]
[Current Position 1st: Vocal Lee Hanbin] [Current Position 2nd: Vocal Hikaru]
Now, I'll announce the ranking for the Rap position members of the "Really Really" team.
[MC CHANGMIN: Now, I'll announce the ranking for the Rap position members of the "Really Really" team.]
[Nervous x100]
[33rd in Second Semester, Kim Beomjun VS
13th in Second Semester, Kim Gyurae VS
3rd in Second Semester, Hikari]
Beomjun you did great.
Please reveal the ranking for the Rap position members.
[MC CHANGMIN: Please reveal the ranking for the Rap position members.]
I still hope Beomjun can get it.
[Producer WOOYOUNG: I still hope Beomjun can get it.]
[Producer SOYEON: Me too.]
-Me too -Yeah, I hope it's him.
[Producer WOOYOUNG: At least I hope it's Beomjun now.]
At least I hope it's Beomjun now.
It would be a shock of reality if it's not Beomjun.
[Producer SOYEON: It would be a shock of reality if it's not Beomjun.]
[What's the result of the Rap position ranking?]
[Oh my]
[Rap position 1st: Kim Gyurae]
[The boys are surprised by the unexpected result]
Kim Gyurae.
Gyurae, the 1st place.
[11th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Kim Wooseok: Gyurae in 1st place?]
[Doubting his eyes]
This isn't right.
[29th in Second Semester, Rap position, Kang lrang: This isn't right.]
[Unbelievable]
Guys, this is live voting.
[4th in Second Semester, Rap position, K-soul: Guys, this is live voting.]
-It's live voting. -Yes, it's a popularity voting.
It's a vote from the fans. It's not what we thought.
[4th in Second Semester, Rap position, K-soul: It's a vote from the fans. It's not what we thought.
[Nervous. The last place of the Second Semester.]
I really want to cry.
[It really hurts]
How is that possible?
[29th in Second Semester, Rap position, Kang lrang: How is that possible?]
I told you.
[26th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Ha Seokhee: I told you.]
There are obstacles that you can't overcome even if you work hard.
[26th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Ha Seokhee:
There are obstacles that you can't overcome even if you work hard.]
["Really Really" team, Rap Ranking]
The Fantasy Makers have voted for
the ranking for the Rap position members of the "Really Really" team.
[Beomjun=Eminem]
In the 3rd place, Kim Beomjun.
[Current position, 3rd in Rap, Kim Beomjun]
In the 2nd place, Hikari.
[Current position, 2nd in Rap, Hikari]
In the 1st place, Kim Gyurae.
[Current position, 1st in Rap, Kim Gyurae]
Congratulations.
It seems to be an unexpected result.
[MC CHANGMIN: It seems to be an unexpected result.]
Let's hear how Gyurae feels.
[MC CHANGMIN: Let's hear how Gyurae feels.]
Gyurae.
-Thank you very much. -Well done.
[13th in Second Semester, Rap Position, Kim Gyurae:
Thank you very much.]
This is my first time creating a rap.
[13th in Second Semester, Rap Position, Kim Gyurae:
This is my first time creating a rap.]
Beomjun, who has a lot of rap experience, helped me a lot.
[13th in Second Semester, Rap Position, Kim Gyurae:
Beomjun, who has a lot of rap experience, helped me a lot.]
Because Beomjun
[13th in Second Semester, Rap Position, Kim Gyurae:
Because Beomjun...]
is the last in our group,]
is the last in our group,
I can't feel just happiness.
[13th in Second Semester, Rap Position, Kim Gyurae:
I can't feel just happiness.]
[Gyurae, what should we do...]
Lastly, we will announce the ranking for the "Really Really" team's
[MC CHANGMIN: Lastly, we will announce the ranking for the "Really Really" team's]
[MC CHANGMIN: Dance position members.]
Dance position members.
-Good job. -Good job.
["Really Really" Team Dance position battle]
They both did well.
[The two boys showing off their matching popularity]
Hyeontae, good job.
Hyeontae gets 1st place!
[Hyeontae gets 1st place! Oh Hyeontae] [Sungmin Number one!]
Hyeontae, you're number one.
[Hong Sungmin] [Hong Sungmin on his way to real debut!]
Sungmin, you're number one.
[Please reveal the result!]
Please reveal the result.
[10th in Second Semester, Oh Hyeontae VS 1st in Second Semester, Hong Sungmin]
[Who will receive 1st in "Really Really" team's Dance position?]
[1st in Dance position: Hong Sungmin]
[I knew you'd make it!]
[Hyeontae ! You're the best!]
I'm sorry.
[I'm sorry]
[After seeing the result, 1st in Second Semester, Hong Sungmin cries again]
The Fantasy Makers have voted for
the ranking for the Dance position members of the "Really Really" team.
In 2nd place, Oh Hyeontae.
[Current position, 2nd in Dance, Oh Hyeontae]
In 1st place, Hong Sungmin.
[Current position, 1st in Dance, Hong Sungmin]
Congratulations.
[Don't cry] [Hong Sungmin]
[Don't cry T T]
[Hong Sungmin] [You're handsome when you're crying too]
First of all, I'm very sorry to our team.
[1st in Second Semester and Dance position, Hong Sungmin: First of all, I'm very sorry to our team.]
[1st in Second Semester and Dance position, Hong Sungmin: I was in charge of the Dance position,]
I was in charge of the Dance position,
[1st in Second Semester and Dance position, Hong Sungmin: and I'm also the leader.]
and I'm also the leader.
I was badly injured and couldn't dance.
[1st in Second Semester and Dance position, Hong Sungmin: I was badly injured and couldn't dance.]
[No way]
[Oh Hyeontae]
I should be more cooperative as a leader.
[1st in Second Semester and Dance position, Hong Sungmin: I should be more cooperative as a leader.]
[1st in Second Semester and Dance position, Hong Sungmin: But I was unable to do that.]
But I was unable to do that.
I was unable to create a better stage.
[1st in Second Semester and Dance position, Hong Sungmin: I was unable to create a better stage.]
I'm so sorry about that, it's a big pity.
[1st in Second Semester and Dance position, Hong Sungmin: I'm so sorry about that, it's a big pity.]
Well done.
[That's enough! Sungmin! You're the best leader! You did well!]
[Hong Sungmin]
-Sungmin. -You're the best Sungmin.
[You're the best Sungmin]
[Emergency] [He pulled the ligament of his left leg during practice]
[Told not to move. The worst situation.]
It's not a solo performance I prepared.
[1st in Second Semester and Dance position, Hong Sungmin: It's not a solo performance I prepared.]
[1st in Second Semester and Dance position, Hong Sungmin: I had teammates.]
I had teammates.
[Compared to the pain from his injury, 1st in Second Semester, Hong Sungmin, felt that he had let his team down instead.]
The most I felt was that I have let them down.
If you think it's difficult, from the Vocal part...
[Hong Sungmin came back with a cast]
-What's going on? -You're here when we're almost done.
-We're almost done... -What's going on? Are you alright?
[13th in Second Semester, Rap position, Gyurae: What's going on? Are you alright?]
[Startled]
What's going on?
Wait, what should we do with this?
[Faced with an unexpected situation, the "Really Really" team is flustered]
It's a bit difficult.
[10th in Second Semester, Dance position, Oh Hyeontae: It's a bit difficult.]
He's in the Dance position.
[13th in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Gyurae: He's in the Dance position.]
-You... -Will you be alright?
[Unable to reply]
[13th in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Gyurae: Is it fine? Is it a fracture?]
-Is it a fracture? -My bones are fine.
[Worried]
But it's not that serious.
[Don't want to worry everyone]
So I'll do what I can.
[1st in Second Semester, Hong Sungmin is doing his best to talk calmly]
I'll get treatment after this performance.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Beomjun: What should we do?]
What should we do?
I was scared.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Beomjun: I was scared.]
I feel sorry for my teammates.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Beomjun: I was only minding myself, so I feel guilty towards everyone]
The second stage for the third semester's Major Field Mission features a song
[MC CHANGMIN: The second stage for the third semester's Major Field Mission features a song]
from the group that inherited the Wild Idols title from 2PM,
[MC CHANGMIN: from the group that inherited the Wild Idols title from 2PM,]
[Inherited Wild Idols 2PM]
[MC CHANGMIN: the third generation Wild Idol group,]
the third generation Wild Idol group,
[MC CHANGMIN: MONSTA X.]
MONSTA X.
[Monsters, come forth]
Here to showcase the song, "Shoot out"!
[MC CHANGMIN: Here to showcase the song, "Shoot out"!]
Please come to the stage, everyone.
[29th in Second Semester, Rap Position, Kang Irang: Looking forward to the "Shoot Out" team.]
Looking forward to it.
[Myungjae are you a cat?] [Jin Myungjae I love you]
[Jin Myungjae]
[Shoot Out Dance Position
18th in Second Semester, Jin Myungjae
20th in Second Semester, Keum Jinho]
[Shoot Out Rap Position
32nd in Second Semester, Seo Sangwoo
36th in Second Semester, Song Duhyun]
[Producer KANGSEUNGYOON: What kind of figures are those?]
What kind of figures are those?
[Vocal Position
22nd in Second Semester, Nam Seunghyun
30th in Second Semester, Daniel
34th in Second Semester, Kim Daehui]
They are so handsome.
Is Daniel the Terminator?
[26th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Ha Seokhee: Is Daniel the terminator?]
Yes.
[I'm Terminator Daniel]
It's like he's going to war.
He's not the same person.
Myungjae. Myungjae has become healthy.
[Producer SOYEON: Myungjae has become healthy.]
[Producer WOOYOUNG: He looks healthier? Haha.]
-He looks healthier. -Yes.
[The sudden sound of siren at the Fantasy Boys Live stage?]
[14th in Second Semester, Yuma, who is startled by the siren]
I thought it was real.
[15th in Second Semester, Dance position, Kang Minseo: I thought it was real.]
[Personal specialty. Amazing.]
There's only one stage left.
[One stage left]
[Hello, we are]
Hello, we are
the team with a fatal shot.
[the team with a fatal shot]
Dry bread!
[Dry bread]
So cute.
Our leader Jinho.
[MC CHANGMIN: Our leader Jinho!]
I heard your team was the most crowded team
[MC CHANGMIN: I heard your team was the most crowded team]
[MC CHANGMIN: during the song selection process.]
during the song selection process.
[20th in Second Semester, Keum Jinho: Because our average ranking is lower than other teams]
Because our average ranking is lower than other teams,
so we've assigned the best parts
[36th in Second Semester, Song Duhyun]
to the best candidates for the highest effectiveness.
[30th in Second Semester, Daniel]
[34th in Second Semester, Kim Daehui]
[32nd in Second Semester. Seo Sangwoo]
[The boys who are in crisis of elimination. How was the preparation process?]
["Shoot Out" team practice room]
[32nd in Second Semester, Seo Sangwoo: The reason we're here together is because]
The reason we're here together is because
more than half of us had our spots taken away.
[32nd in Second Semester, Seo Sangwoo:
more than half of us had our spots taken away. We're here because of our own circumstances.]
We're here because of our own circumstances.
That's right, I was also...
Junwon, you just warmed up, right?
[On the day of song selection]
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: After "Yu Junwon" was called, Junwon stood up.]
After "Yu Junwon" was called, Junwon stood up.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: Then he (looked at me and) walked over slowly.]
Then he walked over slowly.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: I kept praying at the front.]
I kept praying at the front.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: No, I really want to do "Monster".]
No, I really want to do "Monster".
Junwon still chose me.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: Junwon still chose me.]
One, two, three.
[20th in Second Semester, Keum Jinho,
defeated by 2nd in Second Semester, Yu Junwon.]
Sorry.
Three.
[34th in Second Semester, Kim Daehui, defeated by
21st in Second Semester, Hikaru]
Three.
[22nd in Second Semester, Nam Seunghyun, defeated by
7th in Second Semester, Kang Daehyeon]
Three.
[Even 36th in Second Semester, Song Duhyun, was defeated by the other boys]
[36th in Second Semester, Rap position, Song Duhyun: I really wanted to cry.]
I really wanted to cry.
[36th in Second Semester, Rap position, Song Duhyun: How could this happen?]
How could this happen?
[36th in Second Semester, Rap position, Song Duhyun:
In my case, I have a very low ranking.]
In my case, I have a very low ranking.
If I don't get the benefit, I'll be eliminated.
[Ranking 36th out of 37. In order to enter the Fourth Semester, he desperately needs the benefit.]
I think I might be eliminated.
[36th in Second Semester, Rap position, Song Duhyun: I think I might be eliminated.]
[34th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Kim Daehui: Because my ranking is low,]
Because my ranking is low,
I feel very uneasy.
[34th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Kim Daehui: I feel very uneasy.]
[Ranking 34th out of 37, Kim Daehui also urgently needs the benefit.]
[30th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Daniel: I've always been in the lower ranks.]
I've always been in the lower ranks.
[I must get the benefit to survive]
I have to survive.
[32nd in Second Semester, Rap position, Seo Sangwoo: I have to survive. I hope I can survive.]
I hope I can survive.
All team members have low rankings.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: All team members have low rankings.]
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: We might be eliminated this time.]
We might be eliminated this time.
They also got a song they don't like.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: They also got a song they don't like.]
Just looking at these conditions makes me feel the despair.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: Just looking at these conditions makes me feel the despair.]
So how do we divide the parts?
[They divide the parts in a grim situation]
[22nd in Second Semester, Vocal part, Nam Seunghyun: I think we can share it fairly.]
I think we can share it fairly.
There's no part I want to fight for.
[Giving up. There's no part I want to fight for.]
Let's split the parts first.
[The boys of "Shoot Out" Team have lost the will to fight]
Hurry up.
Come on. Come on.
[This won't do]
What about the center position?
[22nd in Second Semester, Vocal position, Nam Seunghyun: I think the dance trainer will decide that.]
I think the dance trainer will decide that.
[18th in Second Semester, Dance position, Jin Myungjae: The trainers will decide, right?]
The trainers will decide, right?
[During the Mid-checkup]
MONSTA X's "Shoot Out".
You didn't come here because you wanted to perform this song, right?
[Producer JINYOUNG: You didn't come here because you wanted to perform this song, right?]
[Producer JINYOUNG: You had no choice.]
You had no choice.
[Producer JINYOUNG: That's why everyone must be outraged.]
That's why everyone must be outraged.
Yes.
[Yes, yes...]
Show us.
[Will the "Shoot Out" team be able to meet their expectations?]
["Shoot Out" Team's Dance position
20th in Second Semester, Keum Jinho
18th in Second Semester, Jin Myungjae]
[Perfect chemistry] [Dance evaluation is over]
You danced well.
[Satisfied]
[Next, the mid-training evaluation for Rap and Vocal positions]
[The rap starts with the patented back stretch]
[Stretching]
Stretching his back.
Love pierces through my heart.
[32nd in Second Semester, Seo Sangwoo, who immediately forgot his lines]
Grrr, bang bang, pierce through my heart now.
Trrembling lips. Look at me.
Grrr, bang bang.
[36th in Second Semester, Song Duhyun, who was unable to deliver the rap properly]
A painful betrayal.
Anxiousness coming closer.
♫After losing myself♫
[Vocal position, 30th in Second Semester, Daniel's part has started]
[Oh~]
[Oh!]
♫nana nanana nana♫
[nana nanana nana(?)]
[I thought it was good at first but he forgot the lyrics immediately]
What's going on?
[What's going on?]
♫Twilight to dawn without you♫
[Vocal position, 22nd in Second Semester, Nam Seunghyun's part]
[In the same Vocal position, 22nd in Second Semester, Nam Seunghyun also made many mistakes]
♫For me, shoot out♫
♫Shoot out, shoot out♫
♫Shoot out, shoot out, shoot out♫
[34th in Second Semester, Kim Daehui, concludes the mid-training evaluation]
If today was the competition, it's over.
[If it was the competition, it's over!]
[A cruel comment from the Third Semester's Main Producer, Producer JINYOUNG]
It's over if today was the competition.
The performance was bad.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance Position, Keum Jinho: The performance was bad.]
[20th in Second Semester, Dance Position, Keum Jinho: The members had the mindset that]
The members had the mindset that
we can't do it anyway.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance Position, Keum Jinho: we can't do it anyway.]
Even though there were many good singers.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance Position, Keum Jinho: Even though there were many good singers.]
[The highly approved Vocals,
16th in Second Semester, Lee Hanbin,
and 25th in Second Semester, Hwang Jaemin]
♫You're the prettiest, Lady♫
♫Hold on tight, or I'll leap for you♫
♫Before my heart leaves you♫
[36th in Second Semester, Rap position, Song Duhyun: Currently, in Fantasy Boys, Beomjun is the top rapper.]
Currently, in Fantasy Boys, Beomjun is the top rapper.
[33rd in Second Semester, Kim Beomjun, with highly approved rapping skills since the entrance evaluation]
My fame uh.
It's all same.
I bet everything on this game uh.
[36th in Second Semester, Rap position, Song Duhyun: It'll be hard to get the benefit.]
It'll be hard to get the benefit.
[After the Interim Reevaluation]
[Deep sigh]
[Depressed]
[30th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Daniel: Unfortunately, everyone made a mistake in the lyrics.]
Unfortunately, everyone made a mistake in the lyrics.
[36th in Second Semester, Rap position, Song Duhyun: Mistakes made me even more nervous.]
Mistakes made me even more nervous.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho:
It's not time to be discouraged yet! Actually, we haven't done anything yet.]
Actually, we haven't done anything yet.
Because this is just the beginning.
[It starts now!]
Okay.
[OK]
[The mood's getting better! Leader Keum Jinho improved the atmosphere and morale.]
Okay.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: It's not a good situation.]
It's not a good situation.
My rank is not far from you guys.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: My rank is not far from you guys.]
I turned my crisis into an opportunity. So my ranking got a little higher.
[Even though he only ranked 31st in the First Semester, he rose to 20th in the Second Semester thanks to the benefit.]
[I did it. You can do it too!]
I did it. You can do it too.
Five, six, seven, eight.
[20th in Second Semester, Keum Jinho, who managed to improved the mood and get everyone moving again]
One more time. That was not in sync.
Focus.
[Jinho, who hopes to get the benefit and help his team members rank up]
Yes.
We don't have time.
Let's start now.
[Practice separately according to the position. Maximize efficiency.]
We'll practice separately according to our positions.
♫If it's over♫
[The teammates help each other and start practicing.]
♫And your heart is gone♫
[30th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Daniel: Your pitch reduction is not handled accurately.]
Your pitch reduction is not handled accurately.
[They're receiving feedback.]
♫Discard all the hope♫
[You can do it. It was much better.]
Don't be too anxious in the future.
Rap doesn't write like a normal passage.
[The Rap position is not losing in passion too!]
[32nd in Second Semester, Rap position, Seo Sangwoo: Rap doesn't write like a normal passage.]
It means it won't follow the grammar rules.
[32nd in Second Semester, Rap position, Seo Sangwoo: It won't follow the grammar rules.]
It's not 'I'm already tired, look at me'.
[Sharing his experience with 36th in Second Semester, Song Duhyun, who is challenging Rap for the first time]
It's 'Look at me, the me who is tired'.
[Ah~]
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: The team atmosphere itself follows the leader.]
The team atmosphere itself follows the leader.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: So, if the leader cheers up, everyone will begin to cheer up.]
So, if the leader cheers up, everyone will begin to cheer up.
[A crisis is an opportunity. We can do it!]
A crisis is an opportunity. We can do it.
[VIBE Shoot Out
Dry bread Original song: Monsta X]
[Seo Sangwoo] ♫Excuse me♫
[Rap]
[Seo Sangwoo] ♫I'm walking like zombie♫
[Seo Sangwoo] ♫The more I miss♫
[Seo Sangwoo] ♫The more I suffocate, not my body♫
[Seo Sangwoo] ♫I can't control the gun to my chest♫
[Jin Myungjae] ♫Blokka♫
[Seo Sangwoo] ♫I can't dodge the bullet flying towards me♫
[Seo Sangwoo] ♫Now I'll also pull the trigger♫
[Song Duhyun] ♫Blakk. Can't block♫
[Song Duhyun] ♫You're blah stop talking♫
[Song Duhyun] ♫When I'm down, I'm like a monster♫
[Song Duhyun] ♫If you confuse me, nonstop♫
[Song Duhyun] ♫I'm hurt and beyond repair♫
[Song Duhyun] ♫Even crazier, Boom♫
[Song Duhyun][Rap]
[Song Duhyun] ♫You eat me and tear me apart♫
[Rap]
[Song Duhyun] ♫Love is fire, burn it all up♫
[Daniel] ♫After losing myself♫
[Vocal]
[Daniel] ♫I drag my heavy legs to move♫
He improved a lot.
Wow, Daniel. Great job.
[Daniel is good.] [Vocal]
Daniel is good.
[Vocal]
[Daniel] ♫After losing myself♫
[Daniel] ♫I drag my heavy legs to move♫
[Kim Daehui] ♫Wandering somewhere♫
[Kim Daehui] ♫I'm looking for someone♫
[Nam Seunghyun] ♫Twilight to dawn without you♫
[Nam Seunghyun] ♫What grabs me tight is farewell♫
[Nam Seunghyun] ♫I'm tottering dangerously♫
[Nam Seunghyun] ♫In the dark♫
[Kim Daehui] ♫For me, shoot out, shoot out, shoot out♫
[Kim Daehui] ♫Spitefully shoot out, shoot out, shoot out♫
[Daniel] ♫If everything is over♫
[Daniel] ♫And your heart is gone♫
[Daniel] ♫Discard all the hope♫
[Nam Seunghyun] ♫For me, shoot out, shoot out, shoot out♫
[Nam Seunghyun] ♫Spitefully shoot out, shoot out, shoot out♫
[Kim Daehui] ♫Saying you'll return one day♫
[Kim Daehui] ♫That sounds crueler♫
[Daniel] ♫Hurry up and get cold♫
[Jin Myungjae] ♫Walker, walker, walker♫
[Seo Sangwoo] ♫Love pierces the heart♫
[Rap]
[Seo Sangwoo] ♫Ignoring all the bad words♫
[Seo Sangwoo] ♫You cruelly toy with me before tossing me away♫
[Seo Sangwoo] ♫You're one step away from me again. Walker walker♫
[Song Duhyun] ♫Grr bang bang my heart is hurt♫
[Song Duhyun] ♫Trembling lips, look at me♫
[Song Duhyun] ♫The piercing pain of betrayal, the closing anxiousness♫
[Song Duhyun] ♫Right now, I straighten my falling body♫
[Oh!] [Rap]
It feels like Duhyun is rapping next to me.
[26th in Second Semester, Vocal Position, Ha Seokhee:
It feels like Duhyun is rapping next to me.] [Rap]
[Rap]
Yes.
My ears.
[Song Duhyun] ♫The piercing pain of betrayal, the closing anxiousness♫
[Song Duhyun] ♫Right now, I straighten my falling body♫
[Kim Daehui] ♫Ever since I wanted you♫
[Vocal]
[Kim Daehui] ♫I've been heartbroken♫
[Daniel] ♫Even though I'm covered in injuries♫
[Daniel] ♫I still love you♫
[Nam Seunghyun] ♫Twilight to dawn without you♫
[Nam Seunghyun] ♫What grabs me tight is farewell♫
[Kim Daehui] ♫I'm tottering dangerously♫
[Kim Daehui] ♫In the dark♫
[Keum Jinho] ♫For me♫
[All]
[Kim Daehui+Nam Seunghyun+Daniel] ♫Shoot out, shoot out, shoot out♫
[Keum Jinho] ♫Spitefully♫
[Song Duhyun] ♫If everything is over♫
[Song Duhyun]  ♫And your heart is gone♫
[Song Duhyun] [All]
[Song Duhyun] ♫Discard all the hope♫
[All]
[Jin Myungjae] ♫For me♫
[Kim Daehui+Nam Seunghyun+Daniel] ♫Shoot out, shoot out, shoot out♫
[Jin Myungjae] ♫Spitefully♫
[Kim Daehui+Nam Seunghyun+Daniel] ♫Shoot out, shoot out♫
[Kim Daehui] ♫Shoot out♫
[Jin Myungjae] [All]
[Nam Seunghyun] ♫Saying you'll return one day♫
[All]
[Keum Jinho] ♫That sounds crueler♫
[Jin Myungjae] ♫Hurry up and get cold♫
[Jin Myungjae] ♫Fire♫
[Daniel] ♫Now, personally shoot the words of the end♫
[Vocal]
[Daniel] ♫straight at my heart♫
[Jin Myungjae] ♫Fire♫
[All]
[Vocal]
[Nam Seunghyun] ♫Let's end this hellish hope♫
[Dance]
This level of performance.
Jin Myungjae.
That's amazing.
Myungjae.
[Jin Myungjae] [Dance]
[Dance]
[Cool!]
[Jin Myungjae is so cool!]
[30th in Second Semester, Daniel]
[34th in Second Semester, Kim Daehui]
[22nd in Second Semester, Nam Seunghyun]
[36th in Second Semester, Song Duhyun]
[32nd in Second Semester: Seo Sangwoo]
[18th in Second Semester, Jin Myungjae]
[20th in Second Semester, Keum Jinho]
[Shoot on, nice one!]
[Good ending]
Good ending.
Amazing.
Not bad.
Very strong.
[Very strong]
[Exclaiming]
Very good.
What happened to Daniel? How did he improve so much?
[Producer SOYEON: What happened to Daniel? How did he improve so much?]
Daniel improved a lot, didn't he?
[Producer JINYOUNG: Daniel improved a lot, didn't he?]
Yes.
Daniel is crazy. He sings well.
[Producer KANGSEUNGYOON: Daniel is crazy. He sings well.]
What do you think, Producers?
[MC CHANGMIN: What do you think, Producers?]
Personally,
[Producer KANGSEUNGYOON: Personally,]
I got goose bumps from this stage.
[I got goose bumps from this stage!]
Really.
It doesn't matter which part.
[Producer KANGSEUNGYOON: It doesn't matter which part.]
Every part did it.
[Producer KANGSEUNGYOON: Every part did it.]
Vocal, Rap, Dance. In every part,
[Producer KANGSEUNGYOON: Vocal, Rap, Dance. In every part,]
I got goose bumps.
[Producer KANGSEUNGYOON: I got goose bumps.]
[Producer KANGSEUNGYOON: I don't feel like it's a pity]
I don't feel like it's a pity
for any of the boys.
[I don't feel like it's a pity for any of the boys]
Personally, my happy Daniel.
[Producer KANGSEUNGYOON: Personally, my happy Daniel.]
[Producer KANGSEUNGYOON: Daniel is really outstanding.]
Daniel is really outstanding.
Thank you for your hard work.
[(Agrees)]
Thank you.
[Thank you!]
[The mission is completed, Terminator Daniel]
There's only praises.
[12th in Second Semester, Rap Position, Kang Hyunwoo: There's only praises.]
Now, let's announce the voting results.
[MC CHANGMIN: Now, let's announce the voting results.]
Let's start with the rankings for Shoot Out's vocal position.
[Vocal position result announcement]
[Current position 1st place
Vocal Lee Hanbin]
Please.
I want to give the benefit to our team.
[16th in Second Semester
Lee Hanbin: I want to give the benefit (to our team).]
[Vocal
1st place Lee Hanbin
2nd place Hikaru
Team members of the 1st place will all get 5000 points]
It may change now.
[Producer JINYOUNG: (The rankings) may change.]
It might.
[Producer KANGSEUNGYOON: It might.]
So cruel.
[The voting that is nothing but cruel]
It's a cruel voting.
[Vocal
1st place Lee Hanbin
2nd place Nam Seunghyun, 3rd place Hikaru]
[Smiling]
[Current position 2nd place
Vocal Nam Seunghyun]
2nd place, Nam Seunghyun.
4th place, Kim Daehwi.
[Vocal
1st place Lee Hanbin
2nd place Nam Seunghyun, 3rd place Hikaru,
4th place Kim Daehwi, 5th place Daniel Hyunoo Lachapelle]
[Current position 4th place, Vocal Kim Daehwi
Current position 5th place, Vocal Daniel Hyunoo Lachapelle]
5th place, Daniel Hyunoo Lachapelle.
Hanbin secured it.
[26th in Second Semester, Vocal position
Ha Seokhee: Hanbin secured (1st place).]
[(Thankfully)]
Next, let's reveal the rankings for Shoot Out's rap position.
[Rap
1st place Kim Gyurae
2nd place Hikari, 3rd place Kim Beomjun
Rap position result announcement]
[Current position 1st place
Kim Gyurae]
[Will he be able to bring his team the 5000-point benefit?]
[Rap
1st place Kim Gyurae
2nd place Song Duhyun, 3rd place Hikari, 4th place Kim Beomjun]
[(Gyurae!!!)]
2nd place, Song Duhyun.
[Current position 2nd place
Rap Kim Duhyun]
2nd place, Song Duhyun.
[Current position 4th place
Rap Seo Sangwoo]
4th place is Seo Sangwoo.
Congratulations.
[Rap
1st place Kim Gyurae
2nd place Song Duhyun, 3rd place Hikari, 4th place Seo Sangwoo, 5th place Kim Beomjun]
Kim Gyurae ranks 1st.
[Current position 1st place
Rap Kim Gyurae]
[Really Really team which managed to secure 1st place for vocal & rap position]
Awesome.
The last one is dance position.
[Special MC
Minho: The last one is dance position.]
Please show us the result for dance position.
[Among the two of them, who will be able to surpass Hong Sungmin as dance position's 1st place?]
Please, please.
[16th in Second Semester
Dance Jin Myungjae]
Please, please.
[20th place in Second Semester
Dance Keum Jinho]
Jinho really did a good job.
[Producer SOYEON: Jinho really did a good job.]
[Breathes]
But the two of them are really strong, Sungmin and Hyeontae.
[Mentor SOYEON: But the two of them are really strong, Sungmin and Hyeontae.]
[Current position 1st place
Dance Hong Sungmin]
[1st place in Second Semester, dance position
Hong Sungmin: Hyeontae, since we are already in this situation, let's just keep taking the 1st and 2nd place.]
Hyeontae, since we are already in this situation, let's just keep taking the 1st and 2nd place.
[Unconfident
I'm sorry]
I'm sorry.
Let's keep taking the 1st and 2nd place, please.
[33rd place in Second Semester
Kim Beomjun]
Please reveal the result.
[Dance position result announcement]
[Dance
1st place Hong Sungmin
2nd place Oh Hyeontae, 3rd place Jin Myungjae]
It's below?
[(Myungjae) is below?]
[Myungjae, you did well]
[Dance
1st place Hong Sungmin
2nd place Oh Hyeontae, 3rd place Jin Myungjae]
3rd place, Jin Myungjae.
[Current position 3rd place
Dance Jin Myungjae]
[Dance
1st place Hong Sungmin
2nd place Oh Hyeontae, 3rd place Jin Myungjae, 4th place Keum Jinho]
4th, Keum Jinho.
[Current position 4th place
Dance Keumjinho]
Nothing has changed.
[Producer SOYEON: Nothing has changed.]
[Though the producers were full of praises,
they took 3rd and 4th place]
I heard that Keum Jinho was the most hardworking
[Special MC
Minho: I heard that Keum Jinho was the most hardworking]
Minho: and is always encouraging his teammates.]
and is always encouraging his teammates.
Jinho, how do you feel now?
[Special MC
Minho: Jinho, how do you feel now?]
[Shoot Out team which didn't get any benefit]
Benefit...
[Choking up]
I promised my team members we will get the benefit...
[I promised my team members we will get the benefit]
[Without the benefit
this might be the last stage for some of the members]
[As the team leader too
knows very well 20th in Second Semester Keum Jinho's feelings right now]
Jinho must be really sad.
He must have had a hard time that's why he cried.
[(I understand)]
[Producers KANGSEUNGYOON & SOYEON understand very well the responsibilities and pressure of a leader]
He must've really done his best.
[He must've really done his best (for his members)]
[20th place in Second Semester, dance position Keum Jinho
who has done his best for his members]
For his members.
I hope all of us can survive.
[I hope all of us (our team can) survive]
[With the pressure of being eliminated
they did their best to prepare for the stage]
We'll vote for you.
Don't cry. Don't cry.
[Cheers for Shoot Out team who are in tears]
[(Shoot Out did well)]
Thank you.
[20th in Second Semester, dance position
Keum Jinho: I thought we could get at least one (benefit).]
I thought we could get at least one.
But you really did well.
You really did well.
[Will everyone in Shoot Out team survive?]
In the Third Semester's major field mission,
[Major field mission
Third stage to be performed]
the third stage is
I Need U by BTS.
[BTS's I Need U]
[Kim Wooseok is awesome]
[(It’s BTS's song!)]
[The reactions are already explosive]
[Kim Wooseok
Crazy for Kim Wooseok]
[Expectant
Looking forward]
Wooseok.
[Kang Irang]
[Expectant
Looking forward]
[I Need U
Vocal
Kim Seungjun, Kim Wooseok, Kang Daehyeon]
[Vocal position
31st in Second Semester, Kim Seungjun
11th in Second Semester, Kim Wooseok
7th in Second Semester, Kang Daehyeon]
Good luck, Kang Daehyeon!
[I Need U
Rap
Kim Kyuhyun, Kang Irang]
[Vocal position
27th in Second Semester, Kim Kyuhyun
29th in Second Semester, Kang Irang]
Go for it, Irang!
[I Need U
Rap
Shiryu, Hayato, Jeong Deunhaesol]
Go for it, Shiryu!
[Dance position
24th in Second Semester, Shiryu
23rd in Second Semester, Hayato
35th in Second Semester, Jeong Deunhaesol]
Shiryu, you're the best!
To be honest, their dance is...
[The team they are keeping in check the most
Many dance members]
After all it's Shiryu, Hayato, and Haesol, the three of them.
I heard they made the choreography by themselves too.
[12th in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Hyunwoo: I heard they made the choreography by themselves too.]
That's right.
[(Choreographed by themselves?)]
Looks like they put everything on dance.
[Dance positions who are super nervous]
[I need it! I need it!]
I need it.
[Acting suddenly]
[Oh my]
What's wrong, Irang? What do you need?
[What does Irang need now?]
I need you girl.
[That is
I need you girl]
[Kim Wooseok]
[Crazy]
[Cute]
[So cute it makes breathing difficult]
Cute.
[The studio is filled with cuteness]
Hello.
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: We are what Fantasy Makers need]
We are what Fantasy Makers need,
U Need Us.
[I Need U team
says their greetings!]
[You're the best, Daehyeon]
[Hayato]
[Hayato, your future is brighter than me]
[Prince Kim Wooseok]
[Kim Wooseok]
[You need us
U Need Us is quite good though?]
U Need Us. U Need Us...
[(Isn't our group name perfect?)]
They came on with such a cute greeting.
[(We did it!)]
I heard that during the interim evaluation,
[Special MC
Minho: I heard that during the interim evaluation,]
this team was criticized for poor teamwork.
[Special MC
Minho: this team was criticized for poor teamwork.]
[On the day of the song selection]
[We became a team first]
We became a team first.
Yeah.
So let's decide on the leader first.
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: So let's decide on the leader first.]
Does anyone wants to be the leader?
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: Does anyone wants to be the leader?]
No one?
I want to be the leader.
[I want to be the leader!]
I'll volunteer first.
Okay.
[I Need U team
Leader Kang Daehyeon confirmed]
I think it's great.
[(Please take care of me)]
I agree.
First of all,
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: First of all,]
teamwork is the most important.
[Teamwork is the most important!]
I think teamwork is the most important. So we'll focus on teamwork.
[The most important to the leader: teamwork]
And I think for this song,
stage performance is very important.
[The second most important to the leader: performance]
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: Let's work hard in the performance.]
Let's work hard in the performance.
[The best!]
Let's get it!
[Let's get along well!]
Come on! Come on!
[(Come on, leader!)]
Our efforts are important.
[Harmonious]
- Let's watch it from the beginning. - Play the video.
[Start to assign the parts]
Here we go.
[(No prelude)
[All] Fall (Everything) Fall (Everything)
Fall (Everything) It's falling
Fall (Everything) Fall (Everything)
The part that's sung together]
All part.
Yes, all part.
[Rap part]
[[Rap]
Because of you I'm ruined (I'm ruined)
That's enough, I'm not going to ask you to stay (ask you to stay)
I can't do this? What is this?
Please stop these excuses (excuses)]
One of you.
[27th place in Second Semester, rap Kim Kyuhyun
29th place in Second Semester, rap Kang Irang]
[[Vocal part]
[Vocal] I need you girl, you're so beautiful
I need you girl, you're so cold
I need you girl
I need you girl, I need you girl]
Are these all vocal parts?
[7th in Second Semester
Vocal Kang Daehyeon]
[[Vocal] I need you girl, you're so beautiful
I need you girl, you're so cold
I need you girl
I need you girl, I need you girl]
[11th in Second Semester
Vocal Kim Wooseok]
[[Vocal] I need you girl, you're so beautiful
I need you girl, you're so cold
I need you girl
I need you girl, I need you girl]
[31st in Second Semester
Vocal Kim Seungjun]
[[Vocal] I need you girl, you're so beautiful
I need you girl, you're so cold
I need you girl
I need you girl, I need you girl]
Okay. Next, Dance for the boys. Break.
We all dance, but the dance break emphasises on the dance part
[35th in Second Semester
Dance Jeong Deunhaesol]
[24th in Second Semester
Dance Shiryu]
and will be by those who have the dance part.
[23rd in Second Semester
Dance Hayato]
Let's start from the beginning...
[Shall we try dividing the parts?]
Let's start choosing from the all part.
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: Let's start choosing from the all part.]
Okay.
[(No prelude)
[All] Fall (Everything) Fall (Everything)
Fall (Everything) It's falling
Fall (Everything) Fall (Everything)
Fall (Everything) It's falling]
Fall, fall... This part.
This vibe is like this, and this is an all part,
[7th in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: This vibe is like this, and this is an all part...]
I personally think Shiryu might fit...
[Leader 7th in Second Semester vocal position Kang Daehyeon recommends the intro part
to 24th in Second Semester dance position Shiryu]
[Fall fall fall]
Fall, fall, fall.
I think it'd be great if Shiryu sings the "fall,"
[35th in Second Semester dance position
Jeong Deunhaesol: I think it'd be great if Shiryu sings the "fall,"]
and Kyuhyun sings the "everything" part.
[35th in Second Semester dance position
Jeong Deunhaesol: and Kyuhyun sings the "everything" part.]
Everything.
[(No prelude)
[All] Fall (Everything) Fall (Everything)
Fall (Everything) It's falling
Fall (Everything) Fall (Everything)
Fall (Everything) It's falling]
[Everything]
[That's perfect]
Everything.
That's right.
Kyuhyun will sing all the "everything,"
and the remaining ones will be by Shiryu and Seungjun.
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Under the guidance of leader Kang Daehyeon, the part was successfully divided]
- Okay. - Okay.
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: I am confident. We'll do well anyway.]
I am confident. We'll do well anyway.
If we practice like this,
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: If we practice like this,]
Kang Daehyeon: I'm sure we will do well. That's what makes me more expectant.]
I'm sure we will do well. That's what makes me more expectant.
Let's do it.
[The vocal lesson
that starts with the leader's anticipation]
Let me listen.
♫ I need you girl ♫
[Showing their strengths according to their practice]
♫ Why do you decide to love by yourself ♫
♫ And leave by yourself? ♫
♫ I need you girl ♫
♫ Why do I still need you ♫
♫ Even though I know I will get hurt ♫
♫ I need you girl ♫
[But...]
♫ You're so cold ♫
♫ I need you girl ♫
[The expression on the vocal trainer's face that can't be read]
[The song is coming to an end]
♫ I need you girl ♫
[Worried]
[What would the vocal trainer's feedback be?]
First of all... You have to understand it yourself.
[Vocal trainer Jang Jinyoung: First of all... You have to understand it yourself.]
This song I Need U...
[Vocal trainer Jang Jinyoung: This song I Need U... Will you listen to it?]
Will you listen to it?
[He's cold about the result of their hard practice]
The problem is with the vocal. Daehyeon's tone is not high enough.
[Vocal trainer Jang Jinyoung: The problem is with the vocal. Daehyeon's tone is not high enough.]
Wooseok's range isn't high either.
[Vocal trainer Jang Jinyoung: Wooseok's range isn't high either.]
[This group's vocal is having a hard time]
It's tiring.
It's hard.
[I Need U's crisis that came quickly]
[Vocal trainer Jang Jinyoung: Let's sing it all again.]
Let's sing it all again.
With the pitch lowered.
[Lowering the key now?]
We're lowering the key now.
We will lower the key by half a note.
[How will it be this time?]
♫ I need you girl ♫
♫ Why do you decide to love by yourself ♫
♫ And leave by yourself? ♫
♫ I need you girl ♫
[Paying attention]
♫ Why do I still need you ♫
♫ Even though I know I will get hurt ♫
I think this is better.
[Vocal trainer Jang Jinyoung: I think this is better (with half a key lowered)]
[Vocal trainer Jang Jinyoung: Like this, everyone can do it and it won't be too tiring.]
Like this, everyone can do it and it won't be too tiring.
I was sad.
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: I was sad after the lesson.]
It's still a long time before the performance.
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: It's still a long time before the performance.]
But the trainer just dropped our key by half a note.
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: But the trainer just dropped our key by half a note.]
I think we just need to practice.
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: I think we just need to practice.]
Kang Daehyeon: To be honest, I think I can do it now too.]
To be honest, I think I can do it now too.
♫ Fall, fall, fall ♫
[23rd in Second Semester
Hayato]
9Because of the vocal position
The members of the other positions are practicing again according to the new key]
♫ Fall, fall, fall ♫
[Because of the vocal position
The key was lowered
and the song sounds dull]
♫ Fall, fall, fall ♫
Now that the key is lower, I can't sing it.
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: Now that the key is lower, I can't sing it.]
Now that the key is lower, I can't sing it.
[If you're a vocal, you should work hard]
If you're a vocal, you should work hard.
I couldn't say anything because I went to the hospital.
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: I couldn't say anything because I went to the hospital.]
When I came back, the key was already lowered.
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: When I came back, the key was already lowered.]
[Interim evaluation day]
Next team, BTS's I Need U.
[Amazing]
[Starting with the dance part's evaluation]
[I'm Shiryu]
[(Dance benefit is ours)]
[Satisfied]
[(The dance break is amazing)]
[Not bad]
[Following with the vocal evaluation]
♫ I need you girl ♫
[Start singing as they practiced with a key lowered]
♫ Why do you decide to love by yourself ♫
[Focused]
♫ And leave by yourself? ♫
[The vocal position
that presented it easily]
♫ I need you girl ♫
♫ Why do I still need you ♫
♫ Even though I know I will get hurt ♫
[Focus]
♫ I need you girl ♫
♫ You are so beautiful ♫
♫ You're so cold ♫
♫ I need you girl ♫
[Working hard]
[What will the interim evaluation be like?]
[Nervous]
The key has been lowered by one key.
[The key has been lowered by one key]
But with this as the beginning
[Producer JINYOUNG: But with this as the beginning]
[Producer JINYOUNG: is already not going to be good against the other teams.]
is already not going to be good against the other teams.
So you need to think about that.
[We must find something to make up for our shortcoming!]
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: If we lower the key, the training becomes different.]
If we lower the key, the training becomes different.
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: And the vibe of the song becomes different too.]
And the vibe of the song becomes different too.
I want to go back to the original key.
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: I want to go back to the original key.]
But the vocal members couldn't do it
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: But the vocal members couldn't do it]
that's why we had to lower the key.
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: that's why we had to lower the key.]
I think we should practice.
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: I think we should practice.]
Shiryu might be the one who gets the dance benefit.
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: Shiryu might be the one who gets the dance benefit.]
To make Shiryu stand out,
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: To make Shiryu stand out,]
Kang Daehyeon: if everyone helps, we can save a lot of people.]
if everyone helps, we can save a lot of people.
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: That's why I want Shiryu to be the center.]
That's why I want Shiryu to be the center.
- I think so too. - Yeah.
[Unanimous agreement]
I want to show that this is what we can do.
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: I want to show that this is what we can do.]
Kang Daehyeon: With a clearer direction]
With a clearer direction,
[Real strategy
Using dance to cover the shortcomings of the vocals]
we can show them our charms as a team that's good at dance.
[Show them our charms as a team that's good at dance
with Shiryu in it]
[I Need U team who puts all their focus on dance
to get the team benefit]
Shiryu and Hayato, stand here.
[Dance trainer Yoo Intae:
Shiryu come to the center.]
Shiryu come to the center.
[The dance break that shines a limelight on 24th in Second Semester dance position Shiryu as the center]
It's a benefit system, so we need to highlight Shiryu.
[24th in Second Semester dance position Shiryu
who's targeting the Third Semester's strategy to get I Need U team their benefit]
[The boys are focused on practice]
[(Shiryu)
With 24th in Second Semester dance position Shiryu as the center
the dance practice continues]
Five and six and seven, eight.
[(Shiryu)
(Hayato)]
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
[(Shiryu)\(Hayato)
23rd in Second Semester Hayato who has been moved to the side]
Move to the center.
Haesol.
[23rd place in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: Haesol.]
[(Let's talk)]
What do you think about the part distribution?
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: What do you think about the part distribution?]
[35th in Second Semester, dance position
Jeong Deunhaesol: My part?]
My part?
[35th in Second Semester, dance position
Jeong Deunhaesol: But I can't do anything about it. Cause I'm a dance position.]
But I can't do anything about it. Cause I'm a dance position.
If I knew,
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: If I knew (this was how my part would go),]
I'd have gone to vocal or rap part.
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: I'd have gone to vocal or rap part.]
Choosing dance part... I regret it a little.
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: Choosing dance part... I regret it a little.]
I only have a sense of crisis.
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: I only have a sense of crisis.]
I don't sing on this stage
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: I don't sing on this stage]
nor do I dance the main part.
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: nor do I dance the main part.]
I'll be ignored on the stage.
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: I'll be ignored on the stage.]
[After the dance benefit strategy has been set for
24th in Second Semester dance position Shiryu
23rd in Second Semester dance position Hayato that starts to not fit in]
There's no need for me.
[There's no need for me!]
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: What do you think?]
[27th in Second Semester, rap position
Kim Kyuhyun: Why do you think so?]
What do you think?
Why do you think so?
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: I just go on to dance the dance break and it's over.]
I just go on to dance the dance break and it's over.
I don't have a dance or singing part.
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: I don't have a dance or singing part.]
Hayato: Among the 8 people
(even without me) this stage can be done with just seven members.]
This stage can be done with just seven members.
No.
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: There's no Hayato on the stage.]
There's no Hayato on the stage.
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: No, no, there Hayato on the stage.]
No, no, there Hayato on the stage.
[11th in Second Semester, vocal position
Kim Wooseok: Now, though Hayato has his own part...]
Now, though Hayato has his own part...
[23rd in Second Semester, dance position
Hayato: It's fine without me anyway]
I'm fine without any.
Let's practice first.
[23rd in Second Semester dance position Hayato
who ended up leaving in the middle of practice]
I'll talk to him later.
He went out.
[Panic]
- We all understand him. - Yes.
[35th in Second Semester, dance position
Jeong Deunhaesol: We all understand him.]
This mission itself this time is,
[11th in Second Semester, vocal position
Kim Wooseok: We are looking to get the benefit]
with someone who can get 1st place in dance, we can get 1st place in dance overall.
[Division of opinions
Crumbling teamwork]
And the team can survive.
[Teamwork is the most important to the leader]
Then should we listen to...
what Hayato... has to say?
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: Should we listen to what he has to say?]
Kang Daehyeon: I've been thinking a lot for the team.]
I've been thinking a lot for the team.
[7th place in Second Semester, vocal position
Kang Daehyeon: We must show what we've prepared.]
We must show what we've prepared.
Go for it, Shiryu!
I like you the most, Shiryu!
[I Need U
U Need Us
Original song BTS]
[All] ♫ Fall, fall, fall ♫
[All]
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ Because of you, I am all ruined ♫
[Rap]
[Kim Kyu-hyun]
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ That's enough, I don't want to bring you back anymore ♫
[Rap]
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ We can't do this anymore, what is this ♫
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ Please stop with all these excuses ♫
[Kang Irang] ♫ You can't do this to me ♫
[Kang Irang] ♫ All your words are like an eye mask ♫
[Kang Irang] ♫ Covering the truth ♫
[Kang Irang] ♫ Tear me apart and knock on me ♫
[Kang Irang] ♫ I going crazy, I hate it ♫
[Goose bumps]
[Kang Irang] ♫ Take everything ♫
[Rap]
[Kang Irang] ♫ I hate you so much ♫
[Hayato] ♫ But you're my everything ♫
[All]
[Hayato] ♫ Everything ♫
[Rap]
[Kim Kyuhyun + Kang Irang] ♫ Please get lost ♫
[Jeong Deunhaesol] ♫ I'm sorry ♫
[All]
[Jeong Deunhaesol] ♫ I love you ♫
[Jeong Deunhaesol] ♫ Please forgive me ♫
[Kang Daehyeon] ♫ I need you girl ♫
[Vocal]
[Kang Daehyeon] ♫ Why do you decide to love by yourself ♫
[Kang Daehyeon] ♫ And leave by yourself? ♫
[Kim Seungjun] ♫ I need you girl ♫
[Kim Seungjun] ♫ Why do I still need you ♫
[Kim Seungjun] ♫ Even though I know I will get hurt ♫
[Kim Wooseok] ♫ I need you girl ♫
[Kim Seungjun] ♫ You are so beautiful ♫
[Kim Seungjun] ♫ You're so cold ♫
[Kang Daehyeon] ♫ I need you girl ♫
[Kim Kyuhyun + Kang Irang] ♫ I need you girl ♫
[Rap]
[Kang Daehyeon] ♫ I need you girl ♫
[Vocal]
[Dance]
[The audience is responding immediately]
[Amazing]
[(Of course we have to recognize Shiryu's dance)]
Shiryu.
[Dance]
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ It goes round and round ♫
[Rap]
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ Why do I keep going back to the same place ♫
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ I go down and down ♫
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ Doing this, I'm just an idiot, right? ♫
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ No matter what I do ♫
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ There's no helping ♫
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ It is my heart ♫
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ My feelings and my emotions ♫
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ That doesn't listen to me ♫
[Kang Irang] ♫ Talking to myself again ♫
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ Talking to myself again ♫
[Kang Irang] ♫ You're not saying anything ♫
[Kang Irang] ♫ Please, I will be good to you ♫
[Kang Irang] ♫ The sky's blue again ♫
[Kim Kyuhyun] ♫ The sky's blue again ♫
[Kim Wooseok] ♫ The sky's so blue, the sunlight so blinding ♫
[Vocal]
[Kim Wooseok] ♫ My tears must be clearer ♫
[Kim Wooseok] ♫ Why is it you? ♫
[Kim Wooseok] ♫ Why does it have to be you? ♫
[Kim Wooseok] ♫ Why can't I leave you? ♫
The expression just now gave me goosebumps.
[8th in Second Semester, vocal position
Moon Hyunbin: (Wooseok's) expression just now gave me goosebumps.]
[Kim Seungjun] ♫ Girl ♫
[Vocal]
[Kim Seungjun] ♫ Just, just break up with me ♫
[Kim Seungjun] ♫ Girl ♫
[Kim Seungjun] ♫ Just tell me, just tell me this isn't love ♫
[Kang Daehyeon] ♫ I don't have such courage ♫
[Kang Daehyeon] ♫ Give me my final present ♫
[Kim Seungjun] ♫ Make me not turn my head again ♫
[Vocal]
[Hayato] ♫ I need you girl ♫
[All]
[Hayato] ♫ Why do you decide to love by yourself ♫
[Hayato] ♫ And leave by yourself? ♫
[Kang Daehyeon] ♫ I need you girl ♫
[Kang Daehyeon] ♫ Why do I still need you ♫
[Kang Daehyeon] ♫ Even though I know I will get hurt ♫
[Kim Wooseok+ Kang Irang] ♫ I need you girl ♫
[Kang Daehyeon... go out with me]
[All]
[Shiryu] ♫ You are so beautiful ♫
[Kim Wooseok+ Kang Irang] ♫ I need you girl ♫
[Shiryu] ♫ You're so cold ♫
[Kang Daehyeon] ♫ I need you girl ♫
[All] ♫ I need you girl ♫
[Dance]
Shiryu.
Their dance break is amazing.
[Kim Wooseok]
[11th place in Second Semester
Kim Wooseok]
[7th place in Second Semester
Kang Daehyeon]
[31st place in Second Semester
Kim Seungjun]
[27th place in Second Semester
Kim Kyuhyun]
[29th place in Second Semester
Kang Irang]
I'll buy you cheese burger.
[24th place in Second Semester
Shiryu]
- Shiryu, you did well! - Shiryu!
[35th place in Second Semester
Jeong Deunhaesol]
Oh no, Irang is so cute.
[23rd place in Second Semester
Hayato]
[Good job]
Well done.
[Well done! x3]
- Good job. - Good job.
[Nodding]
Well done.
[8th in Second Semester, vocal position
Moon Hyunbin: As expected, the moment Shiryu came out, it was amazing.]
- As expected, the moment Shiryu came out, it was amazing. - Exactly.
- I need you. - I need you.
[Nervous]
That's more than what I expected.
[Producer JINYOUNG: That's more than what I expected.]
But there's always something unfortunate.
[But]
[Producer JINYOUNG: But there's always something unfortunate.]
Vocal. Because the vocal of this song is really important.
[Producer JINYOUNG: Vocal. Because the vocal of this song is really important.]
I don't think you've expressed this song's meaning.
[Producer JINYOUNG: I don't think you've expressed this song's meaning.]
[A disappointing feedback received for
I Need U's vocal team]
[Third Semester Major Field Mission]
In the Third Semester's major field mission,
[There is fantasy makers' feedback that is left!]
how will the fantasy makers evaluate them?
[Kim Wooseok]
[Shiryu]
[Daehyeon]
Shiryu, you did well!
[Kim Wooseok]
[Hayato]
Irang, you did well!
[Tear the stage apart]
- Shiryu, you did well! - You did well!
[(Thank you)]
You did well!
Firstly, let's reveal the rankings for I Need U team's
[Special MC Minho: Firstly, let's reveal the rankings for I Need U team's]
[Special MC Minho: vocal position.]
vocal position.
[Will he rank 1st for the Vocal position?]
[Current 1st rank for Vocal position: Lee Hanbin]
[26th in Second Semester, Vocal
Ha Seokhee: I think Hanbin will be able to secure his ranking as 1st in Vocal position.]
I think Hanbin will be able to secure it.
Please reveal the result.
[1st place: Lee Hanbin, "Really Really"]
[2nd place: Nam Seunghyun, "Shoot out"]
[3rd place: Kang Daehyeon, "I Need U"]
[4th place: Hikaru, "Really Really"]
[4th place: Kim Wooseok, "I Need U"]
[6th place: Kim Seungjun, "I Need U"]
[7th place: Kim Daehui, "Shoot Out"]
[8th place: Daniel Hyunoo Lachapelle, "Shoot out"]
[1st: Lee Hanbin, "Really Really"]
[The results didn't change!]
["Really Really" Team is celebrating for him]
-We secured it. -Thank god.
[(Thankfully...)]
The vocal position rankings
[Special MC Minho: The vocal position rankings]
voted by Fantasy Makers for "I Need U."
[Special MC Minho: voted by Fantasy Makers for "I Need U"]
3rd place, Kang Daehyeon.
[Current ranking
3rd place, Vocal, Kang Daehyeon]
4th place, Vocal, Kim Wooseok]
4th place, Kim Wooseok.
6th place, Kim Seungjun.
[Current ranking
6th place, Vocal, Kim Seungjun.]
Congratulations.
[Kim Wooseok, Mother-in-law is waiting for you.]
[Kang Irang]
- You did well! - You did well!
[(Thank you)]
[Special MC Minho: Next, let's reveal the rankings for I Need U team's]
Next, let's reveal the rankings for I Need U team's
[Next are rankings for the rap position]
rap position.
Irang, you did well.
[Irang, you did well!]
[(We did well!)]
You got this, Irang!
- Irang is number one to me! - Go for it, Irang!
[Nervous]
[Current ranking
1st place, Rap, Kim Gyurae]
[What will the result be?]
[Kim Kyuhyun is so cool today, I cannot resist. I'll protect you forever.]
[Shocked! Kim Kyuhyun is so cute.]
[Kyuhyun, you're so cool]
[2nd place: Kim Kyuhyun]
[Too bad]
[Successfully defended 1st place for Rap position]
This is breaking news.
[Special MC Minho: This is breaking news.]
Kyuhyun
[Rap position
Kyuhyun and]
Gyurae, who's ranked first, have a score difference
[Special MC Minho: Gyurae, who's ranked first, have a score difference]
[What??]
[How many points difference?]
[Kim Kyuhyun]
[The difference between the 1st and the 2nd place is only three points.]
of only three points.
Of only three points.
[Too bad]
That's such a pity.
[What a pity.]
[A minuscule difference leads to different fates.]
[The rap position battle was really intense.]
They'd probably rather not know the difference, no?
[12th in Second Semester, Rap, Kang Hyunwoo:
They'd probably rather not know the difference, no?]
Don't tell us that!
[15th in Second Semester, Dance, Kim Minseo:
Don't tell us that!]
[Missed 1st place for Rap position by three points]
Kyuhyun you're so cool!
[2nd place: Kim Kyuhyun]
[6th place: Kang Irang]
He ranked 2nd with a small margin.
[Pity] [Special MC Minho: He ranked 2nd with a small margin.]
[Special MC Minho: Kyuhyun, isn't it a pity?]
Kyuhyun, do you think it's a pity?
[27th in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Kyuhyun:
First of all, it's a pity that I'm only three points behind.]
First of all, it's a pity that I'm only three points behind.
But this score is something that I can catch up to with hard work in the future,
[27th in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Kyuhyun:
But with hard work in the future,]
this score is something that I can catch up to]
[27th in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Kyuhyun:
so that made me confident.]
so that made me confident.
Thank you for voting for me.
[27th in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Kyuhyun:
Thank you for voting for me.]
[Producer SEUNGYOON: What a pity. Kyuhyun did a good job.]
What a pity. Kyuhyun did a good job.
Lastly, I will reveal the rankings for I Need U team's
[Special MC Minho: Lastly, I will reveal the rankings for I Need U team's]
dance position.
[Special MC Minho: dance position.]
[Finally, we will announce the Dance position ranking.]
- You did well! - You did well!
[24th in Second Semester, Dance, Shiryu
is the main beneficiary of "I Need U" Team's benefit ]
Go for it, Shiryu!
[Shiryu! I can only see you.]
- Shiryu! - All the best, Shiryu!
[Shiryu]
All we care about is the dance ranking.
[7th in Second Semester, Vocal, Kang Daehyeon:
All we care about is the dance ranking.]
We bet everything on dance.]
We bet everything on dance.
We had a fight because of this,
[7th in Second Semester, Vocal, Kang Daehyeon:
We had a fight because of this,]
but the response was good.
Let's get the benefit for the 1st place.
[7th in Second Semester, Vocal, Kang Daehyeon:
Let's get the benefit for the 1st place.]
[Revealing Dance position results]
Please show us the results for the dance position.
I'm curious. I'm looking forward to it.
[Producer SOYEON: I'm curious. I'm looking forward to it.]
The Dance ranking may change.
[Dance X3]
[Producer SEUNGYOON: The Dance ranking may change.]
- I think dance will change. - Dance.
- Dance might change. - Dance.
[Vocal trainer, Jeon Woongmin: Will Shiryu defeat Sungmin?]
Will Shiryu defeat Sungmin?
[24th in Second Semester, Shiryu's dance abilities put him in danger]
Wait. This is really...
This is really...
Let's win Shiryu. That's our dance mission.
[The mission of the Dance members is to defeat Shiryu]
I'm praying. Please.
As everyone knows,
[1st in Second Semester, Dance, Hong Sungmin:
As everyone knows,]
no one is better than Shiryu when it comes to dance.
[1st in Second Semester, Dance, Hong Sungmin:
no one is better than Shiryu when it comes to dance.]
Not only is he good at dancing, even his facial expressions are amazing.
[1st in Second Semester, Dance, Hong Sungmin:
Not only is he good at dancing, even his facial expressions are amazing.]
I thought I couldn't win.]
I thought I couldn't win.
Will the ranking change this time?
[Will the Dance ranking change?]
[Nervous]
[Shocked]
[Shiryu! After the result is revealed,]
[The studio plunges in chaos.]
Seriously?
[What will the Dance ranking be?]
[1st place: Hong Sungmin, "Really Really"]
[2nd place: Oh Hyuntae, "Really Really"]
[3rd place: Jin Myungjae, "Shoot Out"]
[4th place: Keum Jinho, "Shoot Out"]
[5th place: Shiryu,"I Need U"]
[1st place: Hong Sungmin, "Really Really"]
[2nd place: Oh Hyuntae, "Really Really"]
[3rd place: Jin Myungjae, "Shoot Out"]
[4th place: Keum Jinho, "Shoot Out"]
[5th place: Shiryu,"I Need U"]
[6th place: Hayato, "I need You"]
[7th place: Jeong Deunhaesol, "I Need U"]
The I Need U dance position rankings
[The I Need U dance position rankings are disappointing]
that was voted in by Fantasy Makers.
5th place: Shiryu.
[Current rankings]
[5th place in Dance: Shiryu]
6th place, Hayato.
[Current rankings]
[6th place in Dance, Hayato.]
7th place, Jeong Deunhaesol.
[Current rankings]
[7th place, Dance, Jeong Deunhaesol.]
[Shiryu ranked 5th?]
This is popularity vote, right?
[This is popularity vote, right?]
[Fantasy Zone is speechless]
- I'm speechless. - I froze.
- I'm speechless. - I don't know what to say.
How many votes did Hyeontae and Sungmin get, for real?
[20th in Second Semester, Dance, Keum Jinho:
How many votes did Hyeontae and Sungmin get, for real?]
[I'm leaving. I'm speechless.]
I'm leaving.
[Producer WOOYOUNG: I think Shiryu is shocked too.]
I think Shiryu is quite shocked.
Shiryu, you did well!
[Producer SEUNGYOON: Of course he'd be shocked.]
Of course he'd be shocked.
[Producer SEUNGYOON: This is a major field evaluation.]
This is a major field evaluation.
[Sad]
Shiryu is so cool!
[Fantasy Makers are shocked too]
- Well done! - Shiryu, you did well!
Irang, you did well!
Yes, I got this result.
[24th in Second Semester,  Dance, Shiryu:
Yes, I got this result.]
I got 5th place,
[24th in Second Semester, Dance, Shiryu:
I got 5th place,]
I think my only weapon, dance,
[24th in Second Semester,  Dance, Shiryu:
I think my only weapon, dance,]
is only at this level.
[I think my only weapon, dance, is only at this level.]
[Shiryu, what should we do?]
See? That's how it is.
Because he will feel like his skill was invalidated.
[Producer SEUNGYOON: Because he will feel like his skill was invalidated.]
[24th in Second Semester, Dance, Shiryu:
But I still want to say something to my fans who cheered me up.]
But I still want to say something to my fans who cheered me up.
Thank you for cheering for me.
[Thank you for cheering for me.]
Thank you.
Shiryu, you did well!
[Shiryu, you did well!]
[Shiryu has already shown off his charisma on stage
but the results were disappointing]
What to do?
[After the performance.]
- It's okay. Hayato, come here too. - Okay.
[7th in Second Semester, Vocal, Kang Daehyeon
comforts his teammates as the team leader]
[24th in Second Semester, Dance, Shiryu:
I feel I have let you all down]
I feel very sorry.
[24th in Second Semester, Dance, Shiryu:
Everyone had a lot of expectations for me.]
Everyone had a lot of expectations for me.
[35th in Second Semester, Jeong Deunhaesol]
[31st in Second Semester, Kim Seungjun]
[24th in Second Semester, Dance, Shiryu: I also know that there are members who are at dangerous rankings]
I also know that there are members who are at dangerous rankings
who weren't able to get the benefit, so I felt really sorry.
[24th in Second Semester, Dance, Shiryu:
who weren't able to get the 1st place benefit, so I felt really sorry.
Shiryu was held back.
[Producer SOYEON: Shiryu was held back.]
- That's why those fans... - Those fans didn't vote.
[Producer SEUNGYOON: That's why those fans]
[Producer JINYOUNG: Those fans didn't vote...]
Yes, they didn't.
[Producer SEUNGYOON: Yes, they didn't.]
[The next group on standby is trying to raise their spirits]
Cheer up. Cheer up.
Gyurae, Kyuhyun, Hikari.
[Current 1st place in Rap:
13th in Second Semester, Kim Gyurae]
[Gulping]
[9th in Second Semester, Vocal, Taeseon:
Please get 1st place...]
[37th in Second Semester, Rap, Park Hyeonggeun
is looking very nervous]
I'm sweating.
We have to get 1st place, please.
[Third Semester Major Field Mission, Fourth Stage]
The fourth stage of the Third Semester's Major Field Mission
is a cheerful song with synchronized dance
[Special MC Minho: is a cheerful song with synchronized dance that will leave a lasting impression.]
[Kaedan]
that will leave a lasting impression.
[Expecting]
Now, let's take a look.
Please come to the stage.
[Please come to the stage!]
["Miroh" Team is welcomed onto stage with applause]
[Santa] [Taeseon] [Nice to meet you]
[Producer JINYOUNG: Aside from two members, every one else has a different nationality.]
Aside from two members, every one else has a different nationality.
[The mentors also feel the group made up of many nationalities is interesting]
This is full of different nationalities.
[9th in Second Semester, Taeseon]
[Vocal position]
[14th in Second Semester, Yuma]
[37th in Second Semester, Rap, Park Hyeonggeun]
[19th in Second Semester, Kaedan]
[Rap position]
[Dance position]
[17th in Second Semester, TK]
[7th in Second Semester, Santa]
[28th in Second Semester, Ivan]
["Miroh" Team is an alliance between five nations]
[10th in Second Semester, Dance, Oh Hyeontae:
All the popular members are in here.]
All the popular members are in here.
[Gulping]
-Two, three. -Hello.
[Hello everyone~]
We are X-Dream who have funky swag.
[We the "Miroh" Team, X-Dream, who have funky swag!]
X-Dream.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
[Kaedan] [Taeseon] [Taeseon]
[Producer WOOYOUNG: They have a lot of fans too.]
They have a lot of fans too.
[Nodding in agreement]
[9th in Second Semester, Taeseon]
[6th in Second Semester, Santa]
[Highly ranked
[Rescue Coupon]
Hyeonggeun, during the preparation of this stage,
[Special MC Minho: Hyeonggeun, during the preparation of this stage,]
[Special MC Minho: I heard you were under a lot of pressure because of your ranking.]
I heard you were under a lot of pressure because of your ranking.
I got a low ranking at the rankings announcement ceremony.
[37th in Second Semester, Park Hyeonggeun:
I got a low ranking at the rankings announcement ceremony.]
I came with the idea that this might be
[37th in Second Semester, Park Hyeonggeun:
I came with the idea that
my final semester's stage.
[37th in Second Semester, Park Hyeonggeun:
this might be my final semester's stage.
[Laughing]
Welcome.
[Welcome to "MIROH" Team.]
[A friendly atmosphere.]
Welcome.
[Welcome]
Welcome, everyone.
[Laughing]
Yes.
The translator is not here, right?
[Is the translator not here?]
Come on out, Papago.
[Come on out, Papago (?)]
[No translation app, no conversation.]
We need Papago.
Please, Papago.
[Ah... What should we do?]
What should we do?
[Worried]
Let's decide on the part first.
[Calm down. Let's decide the part first!]
Let's decide the part first.
♫ In the next city ♫
[Vocal position: Taeseon and Yuma]
♫ Looking down on the building ♫
♫ Fly all day ♫
♫ It's my first time, so I can't help it ♫
[Rap position: Park Hyeonggeun and Kaedan]
♫ Now my dream is blooming like flowers ♫
[Dance position: TK, Santa, Ivan]
♫ X-Dream ♫
No English at all.
[Checking the parts they were assigned]
- No English. - Really no English.
[Despair... There's really no English...]
Guys.
[Worried]
[Have you written... lyrics... before? No...!]
Have you written lyrics?
No.
[Despondence]
- Never. - Never.
[The reason Kaedan chose rap!]
[Although he tried for "I Need U" Dance position]
[He lost to Hayato]
Thank you.
I did well though.
[In the end, Kaedan is in Rap position for "Miroh"]
You can do it.
[37th in Second Semester, Rap, Park Hyeonggeun:
I think we should write our stories]
I think we should write our stories
based on the theme of the song.
[37th in Second Semester, Rap, Park Hyeonggeun:
based on the theme of the song.]
This way, it will be more...
[Ah... "sincerity" is...]
"sincerity" is...
Sincerity... Convey...
[Loading]
More like this.
[Charades for "sincerity"]
[He understands it completely.]
Okay, sure.
It's his first time doing rap,
[19th in Second Semester, Rap, Kaedan
is a seedling at rapping]
So I thought what should I do? And I was quite lost.
[So I thought what should I do? And I was quite lost.]
[The dorm that night]
- Let's decide the theme first. Topic? - Topic?
[Gathering for rap writing]
[(Korean)During the entrance evaluation...
(English)How about feeling(?)]
How did you feel during the entrance evaluation?
[(Call for Translation software)]
I don't know.
[Not confident. I don't know.]
- A flower. - Like a flower that's blooming.
[Translation: Felt like a flower that was growing]
[Thumbs up]
Is it okay?
It's really good.
[Surprised] [Thank you]
Thank you.
Then, your dream will bloom into flowers.
[Writing rap lyrics quickly]
So smart.
[Hyeonggeun is so smart!]
Good.
[They focus on writing rap lyrics into the night.]
[It's rap training rhe next day.]
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
[Depressed.] [Kaedan... is doing Rap?]
Kaedan is doing rap?
Yes.
[Smiling with difficulty]
[Hahahahaha]
Actually, Stray Kids' "MIROH"
[Rap trainer Kebee: Actually, Stray Kids' "MIROH"]
[Rap coach Keebe Is it a good rap song?]
Is it a good rap song?
So how was the rap making?
[Rap positioning mission So how was the rap making?]
[37th place in the 2nd semester Rap positioning Park Hyung-geun  19th place in the 2nd semester
Rap positioning
I finished the first verse's lyrics with Kaedan yesterday.
[Rap coach Keebe Let's listen to the first verse's rap?]
Let's listen to the first verse's rap.
[Nervous]
♫ It's my first time, so I can't help it ♫
[Hyung-geun R ♫ It's my first time, so I can't help it ♫ I'm a boat floating on the sea ♫
♫ I'm a boat floating on the sea ♫
[Nodding Hyung Geun R ♫ It's my first time, so I can't help it ♫ I'm a boat floating on the sea ♫]
[(Why not continue?) Kaedan R At first, I was just a seed ♫ Now my dream is blooming into flowers ♫]
♫ At first, I was just a seed ♫
[Stuttering ♫ Now my dream is blooming into flowers ♫ Kaedan R ♫ At first, I was just a seed ♫ Now my dream is blooming into flowers ♫]
♫ Now my dream is blooming into flowers ♫
Kaedan. You need to match Hyeonggeun's rap speed.
[Rap coach Keebe Kaedan! You need to match Hyung-geun's rap speed.]
Right now?
[The 19th place of the 2nd semester Rap positioning Kaedan Right now?]
One more time, Hyeonggeun and Kaedan.
[They keep making mistakes. Focus on the part of rap positioning]
♫ It's my first time, so I can't help it ♫
♫ I'm a boat floating on the sea ♫
♫ At first, I was just a seed ♫
[Stuttering]
[Rap coach Keebe] The 19th place in the second semester, rap positioning.
Kaedan, use more strength.]
Kaedan, use more strength.
♫ At first, I was just a seed, now ♫
[Practice time with different positioning.]
[Focusing on the rap beginners. The 19th place of the second semester. Rap positioning. Kaedan's...
The 37th place of the second semester, rap positioning Park Hyung Geun]
♫ At first, I was just a seed ♫
[At first it was just a seed]
♫ Now my dream is blooming into flowers ♫
[♫ Now my dream is blooming into flowers ♫]
Imagine JEON SOYEON in front of you.
[Imagine JEON SOYEON in front of you.]
[Their eyes meet. Imagination training.]
Look at her.
♫ It's my first time, so I can't help it ♫
♫ I'm a boat floating on the sea ♫
♫ At first, I was just a seed ♫
♫ Now my dream is blooming into flowers ♫
[Through the 37th place of the second semester,] Rap positioning Park Hyung-geun's help In the second semester,
The 19th place. Rap positioning. [Kaedan's rap skills gradually grow.]
Thank you.
[The 19th place of the 2nd semester, rap positioning] Kaedan. Hyeonggeun is really good.
Hyeonggeun is really good. Cause he is very good at also making lyrics, not just rapping.
[The 19th place of the 2nd semester, rap positioning. Cause he is very good at also making lyrics, not just rapping.]
[Mid-checkup Day]
Let's take a look if you're ready.
- Okay. - Okay.
[Nervous]
- Okay. - Go for it.
Go for it.
- Go for it. - Go for it!
♫ It's my first time, so I can't help it ♫
[The 37th place of the second semester, rap. Park Hyung-geun]
♫ I'm a boat floating on the sea ♫
♫ At first, I was just a seed ♫
[The 19th place of the 2nd semester Rap Kaedan]
♫ Now my dream is blooming into flowers ♫
Oh Kaedan.
[Oh Kaedan]
[Oh]
♫ Kill'em in a venom ♫
♫ Pour some oil to my limits and walk out of the labyrinth, keep that in mind ♫
[Man of the world] Yes
♫ Man of the year ♫
Kaedan did well.
[Kaedan: Great.]
Personally, I think, among all the members,
[Rap coach Keebe] I think
Hyeonggeun's lyrics are the best.
[37th place in the second semester, rap positioning.] Hyung-geun's lyrics are the best.
[Bowing]
But...
[But]
The rap was not that good.
[Rap is not good.]
Hyeonggeun's rap was too fast.
[Rap coach Keebe Hyeonggeun's rap was too fast.]
So I can't hear the tone Hyeongguen has.
[Worried Worried]
I can't hear any of that.
[Rap positioning in the 2nd semester I can't hear any of that.]
It just went past quickly.
You need to practice that part repeatedly.
[Yes. The 37th place of the 2nd semester Rap positioning, Park Hyung-geun]
I'm actually under a lot of pressure this time.
[37th place in the second semester, rap positioning. Park Hyung-geun: I'm actually under a lot of pressure this time.]
42nd place, Park Hyeonggeun.
[No.42 The last place in the first semester Park Hyung-geun]
[He was almost eliminated in the second semester.]
The last survivor is...
[Mentor Woo-young uses a coupon! The 37th place of the 2nd semester. Rap positioning, Park Hyung-geun]
Park Hyeonggeun.
[The last place in the 1st and 2nd semester. The third semester mission is more desperate than anyone else.]
[The 37th place of the 2nd semester, rap positioning. Park Hyeonggeun. During the mid-checkup,]
During the interim evaluation,
["your strengths were not obvious,"]
"your strengths were not obvious,"
[The 37th place of the second semester, rap positioning Park Hyung-geun what should I do]
what should I do
facing these feedback?
[facing these feedback?]
I had a mental breakdown.
[37th place of the second semester, rap positioning. Park Hyung-geun: I broke down.]
["MIROH" is practicing the next day Team.]
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
[Park Hyung-geun can't focus on class.]
[Stuttering]
One, two, three, four.
[Cut.]
[Holding her hair]
[After the dance class, The team members keep practicing.]
[The 37th place of the second semester, rap positioning. Park Hyung-geun is alone in the corner?!]
[Focusing on changing the rap. They can't focus even when they practice.]
[9th place in the second semester. Vocal positioning
Captain Tae Sun has to care about The rap positioning in 2nd semester.
Park Hyung-geun's state.]
One more time. Let's go.
We don't have much time until we perform.
[They stop practicing and try to communicate.]
[37th place in the second semester, rap positioning. Park Hyung-geun. Time was limited until the performance.]
This semester is really important to me.
[37th place in the 2nd semester Rap positioning Park Hyung-geun.
This semester is really important to me.]
And I didn't do well.
[No.37 in the second semester Rap positioning Park Hyung-geun: And I didn't do well.]
And I have to take care of Kaedan too.
[37th place in the second semester Rap positioning Park Hyung-geun.
(All rap positioning) And I have to take care of Kaedan too.]
[37th place in the second semester Rap positioning Park Hyung Geun As I told him about my current situation,
As I told him about my current situation,
I cried because I was emotional.
[The 37th place of the second semester, rap positioning Park Hyung-geun I cried because I was emotional.]
[Will he be able to overcome the crisis and show a good aspect?]
[- You can do it, right? - I can.]
- You can do it, right? - I can.
To leave no regrets, I'll show everything.
[37th place of the second semester, rap positioning. Park Hyung-geun.
I have to be nervous I'll show you everything.]
You have to be nervous.
[13th place in the second semester Rap positioning] Kim Kyu Rae, you have to be nervous.
[Current positioning No.1 Rap Kim Kyu Rae]
[13th place in the 2nd semester. Rap positioning Kim Kyu Rae.
We won't be defeated here, right?
Current positioning No.1, Dance. Hong Sung-min]
[Current positioning No.1 Vocal Lee Hanbin]
This song is strong. This song is strong.
[VIBE MIROH X] ["Dream" by Stray] Kids
[Santa] ♫ Cross the mountain, the mountain ♫
[Santa] ♫ Cross the river, the river ♫
[Santa] ♫ Cross the mountain and another mountain ♫
[Santa] ♫ Over the river and the ocean ♫
[Santa] ♫ Over it all, and everything after ♫
Santa!
[Taeseon SANTA]
[Wow]
[Vocal]
[Yuma] ♫ Without any fear ♫
[Yuma] ♫ In this jungle ♫
[Yuma] ♫ I volunteered to jump in ♫
[Yuma] ♫ I'm okay ♫
You are okay, princess!
[Yuma] ♫ We going higher ♫
[Yuma] ♫ In the next city ♫
[Yuma] ♫ Looking down on the building ♫
[Yuma] ♫ Fly all day ♫
[Focused]
[All] ♫ Whoa, whoa, oh, higher ♫
[Ivan] ♫ To the top ♫
[Ivan] ♫ Fly even higher ♫
[All] ♫ Whoa, whoa, oh, higher ♫
[TK + Kaedan] ♫ To the top ♫
[TK + Kaedan] ♫ Fly even higher ♫
[Rap]
[Park Hyeonggeun] ♫ It's my first time, so I can't help it ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun] ♫ I'm a boat floating on the sea ♫
[Kaedan] ♫ At first, I was just a seed ♫
[Kaedan] ♫ Now my dream is blooming into flowers ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun] ♫ I'm back on the mirror game ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun] ♫ Flowing with hurricane, I don't back down ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun] ♫ Because I'm not afraid ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun] ♫ Kill'em in a venom ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun] ♫ Pour some oil to my limits ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun] ♫ Walk out of the labyrinth, keep that in mind ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun] ♫ Man of the year ♫
[Shocked, alert, reaction explosion]
[Rap positioning No 1 The 13th place of the second semester, Kim Kyu Rae. I'm very nervous]
Hyeonggeun is so cool. What to do?
[Park Hyeonggeun] ♫ Man of the year ♫
[Startled]
[Taeseon] ♫ Without any fear ♫
[Vocal]
[Taeseon] ♫ In this jungle ♫
[Taeseon] ♫ I volunteered to jump in ♫
[Taeseon] ♫ I'm okay ♫
[Taeseon]
[Yuma] ♫ We going higher ♫
[Vocal]
[Yuma] ♫ In the next city ♫
[Yuma] ♫ Looking down on the building ♫
[Yuma] ♫ Fly all day ♫
[All] ♫ Whoa, whoa, oh, higher ♫
[Santa] ♫ To the top ♫
[Santa] ♫ Fly even higher ♫
[All] ♫ Whoa, whoa, oh, higher ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun + TK] ♫ To the top ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun + TK] ♫ Fly even higher ♫
[Taeseon] ♫ Without any fear ♫
[Vocal]
[Taeseon] ♫ In this jungle ♫
[Taeseon] ♫ I volunteered to jump in ♫
[Taeseon] ♫ I'm okay ♫
[Taeseon] ♫ We going higher ♫
[Taeseon] ♫ In the next city ♫
[Taeseon] ♫ Looking down on the building ♫
[Taeseon] ♫ Fly all day ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun] ♫ Okay, we are ready ♫
[Rap]
[Park Hyeonggeun] ♫ Free on the highway ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun] ♫ I've been writing all night in my notebook, the bright starlight ♫
[Kaedan] ♫ Your way ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun] ♫ And my way ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun + Kaedan] ♫ There's a new path yeah ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun + Kaedan] ♫ Not maze runner ♫
[Park Hyeonggeun + Kaedan] ♫ We're chasers chasing dreams ♫
[He flipped it]
Hyeonggeun is crazy.
[What did I see just now?]
Chaser.
[Yuma Yuma Kaedan]
[Ivan] ♫ Without any fear ♫
[Ivan] ♫ In this jungle ♫
[Ivan] ♫ I volunteered to jump in ♫
[Ivan] ♫ I'm okay ♫
[TK] ♫ We going higher ♫
[TK] ♫ In the next city ♫
[TK] ♫ Looking down on the building ♫
[TK] ♫ Fly all day ♫
Let's go, let's go!
[Vocal]
[Taeseon] ♫ Without any fear ♫
[Taeseon] ♫ In this jungle ♫
[Taeseon] ♫ I volunteered to jump in ♫
[Taeseon] ♫ I'm okay ♫
[Yuma] ♫ We going higher ♫
[Yuma] ♫ In the next city ♫
[Yuma] ♫ Looking down on the building ♫
[Yuma] ♫ Fly all day ♫
[Dance]
Let's go!
[Choi Minho Yuma Yuma Yuma One TOP Kaedan]
[37th place in the 2nd semester, Park Hyung-geun]
Well done!
[The 19th place in the second semester Kaedan]
[28th place in the second semester Chae Hong-yup]
[6th place in the second semester SANTA]
- Kaedan - Kaedan
[17th place in the second semester, TK]
[14th place in the 2nd semester, Yuma]
Kaedan
[9th place in the second semester, Taeseon]
So cool!
Amazing!
[(Ending restaurant~)]
OK
[Not even to say Ending Hyeonggeun flipped it. He just flipped it over!!]
Hyeonggeun flipped it. He just flipped it over.
[He just flipped it over!]
Hyeonggeun is so good. He's at this level?
[33rd place in the second semester Rap positioning Kim Beom-joon
Hyung-geun is so good]
It shocked me.
He's always good.
[25th place in the second semester Vocal positioning: Hwang Jaemin He's always good~]
Goodness.
Is something wrong with my ears?
[But... Is something wrong with my ears?]
Why is the rhythm so...
[Why is the rhythm so?!]
They were all too quick.
[Agreed Mentor Jinyoung They were all too quick]
Okay. Before the voting result of the MIROH group comes out,
[Special MC Minho  Before the voting result of the MIROH group comes out,]
let's listen to the evaluation.
[Special MC Minho let's listen to the evaluation.]
Firstly...
[Hesitating]
[Firstly...]
[Mentor: SOYEON Hyeonggeun rapped really well]
Hyeonggeun rapped really well.
[Relax]
[She just made up her mind.] I'll protect Hyunggeun forever. Park Hyunggeun is so cool. You're the best.]
Gyurae is in danger.
[Nervous
The 10th place in the second semester. Dance positioning Oh Hyeontae
Gyurae is in danger.]
In general,
[Mentor: SOYEON In general,]
[Well...]
I actually don't have much to...
[Mentor: SOYEON, I actually don't have much to...]
[Nervous]
To say.
[In fact she has nothing to say.]
The stage was a mess.
[The stage was a mess.]
[Lower your head. The stage was a mess....!!]
You didn't keep up with the rhythm and made mistakes in the choreography.
[She made a mistake.]
[Mentor: SOYEON And this is the third semester]
And this is the third semester.
[Mentor: SOYEON You need to make people think you've really changed. If you don't work hard,]
You need to make people think you've really changed. If you don't work hard,
I hope you can reconsider your path as a singer.
[I hope you can reconsider your path as a singer.]
[ The team received the cruelest evaluation.]
That's a bit harsh.
[Trembling That's a bit harsh.]
[It's so spicy.]
- Thank you. - Thank you.
[The evaluation from the boys is unfortunate.]
[Taeseon is the best.]
- Taeseon, you worked hard. - You worked hard.
[Yang Tae Sun: Taeseon is great.]
First, I'll announce the rankings for MIROH team's dance position.
Okay. I'll announce the result.
[Nervous. current positioning. No.1 Dance Hong Sungmin]
So nervous.
The rankings voted by Fantasy Makers for MIROH's
[Fantasty] "MIROH" by Mike. The rankings voted by Fantasy Makers for MIROH's]
dance position.
[No 1: Hong Sung-min, Really] Ready.
No 2: Oh Hyun-tae. Really.
No 3: Jin Myung-jae. Out.
No 4: Geum Jin-ho. Out.
No 5: Ji Ryuu. I'd better U.
No 6: Hayato from the village. U.
No 7: Chae Hong-yup, MIROH.
No 8: Jeong Dog Hae-sol "U".
No 9: SANTA MIROH.
No 10: TK MIROH]
[No 1: Hong Sung-min, Really] Ready.
No 2: Oh Hyun-tae. Really.
No 3: Jin Myung-jae. Out.
No 4: Geum Jin-ho. Out.
No 5: Ji Ryuu. I'd better U.
No 6: Hayato from the village. U.
No 7: Chae Hong-yup, MIROH.
No 8: Jeong Dog Hae-sol "U".
No 9: SANTA MIROH.
No 10: TK MIROH]
[Relaxed]
[6th place in the second semester.] Dance positioning SANTA. Anyway, I'm not sad.
Anyway, I'm not very sad.
Because I tried my best.
[9th place SANTA] MIROH No.10 TK MIROH
The 6th place of the 2nd semester. Dance positioning. SANTA. I tried my best.
[6th in the 2nd semester] Dance positioning SANTA. I want to tell my members
I also want to say to my members,
[No.6 in the 2nd semester] Dance positioning SANTA. thank you for working hard together.
thank you for working hard together.
[SANTA You're great.]
Next, I'll announce the rankings for MIROH team's vocal team.
[Next is "MIROH".] [Vocal rank]
[1st place: Lee Han-bin and real] The 2nd place, Nam Seung-hyun. Shoot out.
Number 3, Kang Dae-hyun. I got it. Urashimi Hikaru. Yes, really.
The fourth place is Kim Woo-seok. [6th place, Kim Seung-jun] ["Red U"]
7th place, Kim Daehwi. Out.
8th place, Daniel Bu Shoot. Out.
[The first place is always in danger.]
My heart hurts. Please.
[10th place of the second semester] Dance positioning, Oh Hyun-tae.
Please, Han Bin. [Vocal Location Number 1] You must survive.
Please, Hanbin please survive.
[No1: Lee Han-bin, real] Ready.
No2, Nam Seung-hyun. Shoot. Out.
No3: Kang Dae-hyun] U.
The fourth place is Hikaru Urashimi. Really?
No 4: Kim Woo-seok. I got it. U.
No 6: Kim Seung-jun. U.
No 7: Kim Daehwi. Out.
No 8: Daniel Bu Shot. [Out]
[No1: Lee Han-bin, real] Ready.
No2, Nam Seung-hyun. Shoot. Out.
No3: Kang Dae-hyun] U.
The fourth place is Hikaru Urashimi. Really?
No 4: Kim Woo-seok. I got it. U.
No 6: Kim Seung-jun. U.
No 7: Kim Daehwi. Out.
No 8: Daniel Bu Shot. [Out]
[The 1st place of vocal] [Lee Han-bin]
- I knew it. - Hanbin.
3rd place.
[1st place: Lee Han-bin, real] Really.
The second place is Nam Seung-hyun. Out.
[3rd place: Tae Sun, Miramoh]
[4th place: Kang Dae-hyun] U, 5th, Hikaru Urashimi. Really.
The 5th place is Kim Woo-seok. I got it. U.
[7th place: Yujin Endo, Miramoh]
The 8th place is Kim Seung-jun. I got it. U.
9th place, Kim Daehwi. Out.
10th place, Daniel. [Shoot out]
3rd place, Taeseon.
7th place, Yujin.
[Vocal] Yujin Endo.
Vocal. Tae Sun.
Taeseon, you did well.
Thank you.
[Too bad, Tae-sun.]
First of all, I'm not satisfied with the performance.
[9th place in the second semester.] Vocal positioning: Tae Sun.
I'm not very satisfied with the performance.
[9th place of the 2nd semester] Vocal positioning, Tae Sun. The third place...
I think 3rd place is actually
too high.
[9th place of the second semester] Vocal location, Tae Sun. I think it's too high.
[Tae Sun, Yang Tae Sun]
I'll work harder. Thank you.
[9th place in the second semester] [Vocal positioning: Tae-sun] I'll work harder. Thank you.
- You did well! - You did well.
[The stage is full of regret.]
You did well.
[Special MC Min-ho] Unfortunately, The first place of the part hasn't changed.
Unfortunately, there are no changes to the 1st place for vocal part.
Finally, I'll announce the rankings for MIROH's rap position.
[I'll announce the last ranking.] Rap positioning.
[Dance & Vocal both received harsh comments
It makes the rap positions, Park Hyeonggeu and Kaedan, more nervous]
[1st place, Kim Gyurae, Really Really
2nd place, Kim Kyuhyun, I Need U
3rd place, Song Duhyun, Shoot Out
4th place, Hikari, Really Really
5th place, Seo Sangwoo, Shoot Out
6th place, Kang Irang, I Need U
7th place, Kim Beomjun, Really Really]
I'm really looking forward to it.
[Vocal Trainer, Park Soomin: I'm really looking forward to it.]
Gyurae. Can you defeat Gyurae?
[Vocal Trainer, Jeon Woongmin: Can you defeat Gyurae?]
Gyurae is so nervous.
[20th place in Second Semester, dance position, Keum Jinho:
Gyurae is so nervous.]
Kim Gyurae, keep your head up.
[He dares not to look at the results of rankings defensive battle]
Gyurae, keep your head up.
[Gyurae, keep your head up!]
-Kim Gyurae. -Check it out.
[Check it out X2]
I hope Hyeonggeun ranks higher.
[Rap Trainer, Hanhae: I hope Hyeonggeun ranks higher.]
[Rap Trainer, Kebee: It's hard to tell. It depends on the fans' voting.]
It's hard to tell. It depends on the fans' voting.
[Nervous
25th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Hwang Jaemin
is holding his breath and cheering for them backstage]
[Special MC, Minho: Please announce the result.]
Please announce the result.
[Shocked]
[I just made up my mind
I'll protect Hyeonggeun
forever
Park Hyeonggeun
is so handsome
You're the best]
[Covers her mouth
Why is everyone so surprised?]
[1st place, Park Hyeonggeun, MIROH
2nd place, Kim Gyurae, Really Really
3rd place, Kim Kyuhyun, I Need U
4th place, Song Duhyun, Shoot Out
5th place, Hikari, Really Really
6th place, Seo Sangwoo, Shoot Out
7th place, Kang Irang, I Need U
8th place, Kim Beomjun, Really Really]
You won.
[The current 1st place of positions, rap, Park Hyeonggeun]
[1st place, Park Hyeonggeun, MIROH
2nd place, Kim Gyurae, Really Really
3rd place, Kim Kyuhyun, I Need U
4th place, Song Duhyun, Shoot Out
5th place, Hikari, Really Really
6th place, Seo Sangwoo, Shoot Out
7th place, Kang Irang, I Need U
8th place, Kim Beomjun, Really Really
9th, Kaedan, MIROH
Everyone knows that Hyeonggeun worked very hard, so they all congratulate Hyeonggeun sincerely]
[1st place, Park Hyeonggeun, MIROH
2nd place, Kim Gyurae, Really Really
3rd place, Kim Kyuhyun, I Need U
4th place, Song Duhyun, Shoot Out
5th place, Hikari, Really Really
6th place, Seo Sangwoo, Shoot Out
7th place, Kang Irang, I Need U
8th place, Kim Beomjun, Really Really
9th, Kaedan, MIROH]
[Good job, everyone!]
Awesome.
[Big event]
[That's how it should be]
-That's good. -Awesome.
[Having used the wildcard in the Second Semester, Producer WOOYOUNG proved Park Hyeonggeun's worth]
-That's good. -That's good.
-I got goosebumps. -That's good.
[Being revived by the wildcard in the Second Semester
37th place in Second Semester, rap position, Park Hyeonggeun, has been acknowledged by the fans]
[The boys in Fantasy Zone are also happy for him]
-It's amazing. -Hyeonggeun is really something.
-Hyeonggeun is so cool. -He's truly awesome.
-He won with his own strength. -He's indeed cool.
[(Frozen) The benefit points are disappearing...]
Decided by Fantasy Maker,
[Decided by Fantasy Maker, the current 1st place of rap position
37th place in Second Semester, rap position, Park Hyeonggeun]
the 1st-place rap position of the "MIROH" Team is
Park Hyeonggeun.
[Geun
Of course
Congratulations]
-Well done. -You all have done a very good job.
This time, I did my best as I regarded this as my last performance.
[37th place in Second Semester, rap position, Park Hyeonggeun:
This time, I did my best as I regarded this as my last performance.]
[Choking together]
I'm so lucky to stay here.
[37th place in Second Semester, rap position, Park Hyeonggeun:
I'm so lucky to stay here.]
I want to thank our team.]
I want to thank our team.
It's okay.
[Don't cry~]
-Don't cry. -I'm not crying.
[It's our turn soon
Hwang Jaemin is not allowed to cry along with them...]
I'm gratified and proud of you.
[Producer WOOYOUNG: I'm gratified and proud of you.]
Thank you for presenting us
[Thank you for presenting us with a charming drama.]
with a charming drama.
Thank you, everyone.
[Thank you, everyone.]
[Keep it up~!
Hyeonggeun, I love you]
-Thank you, everyone. -Thank you, everyone.
Hyeonggeun, keep the 1st place. Keep it up.
[9th place in Second Semester, rap position, Taeseon:
Hyeonggeun! Keep the 1st place~]
Don't be like that. I got it.
[The whole team survives together
It's a taboo to be careless]
[We must stay together this time.]
-We must stay together this time. -Promise.
[Special MC, Minho: The last performance]
As the last performance
of the Third Semester's Major Field Mission,
[The last performance of the Third Semester's Major Field Mission,]
[Special MC, Minho: with a characteristic of having unique voices and a fresh vocal template,]
with a characteristic of having unique voices and a fresh vocal template,
is Monster by EXO.
[EXO ]
[K-soul
Everyone is looking forward to it]
♫ You can call me monster ♫
[You can call me monster~]
Monster.
[Expectation MAX]
[Current 1st places of vocal and dance positions, from the REALLY REALLY Team]
-♫ You can call me monster ♫ -Monster.
Let's look forward to it.
[Current 1st place of rap position, from the MIROH Team]
[Can the Monster Team overturn the voting result?]
[(Sorry to keep you waiting~)]
Kang Hyunwoo.
[As soon as they appeared, the crowd started cheering]
[Junwon
As soon as they appeared, the crowd started cheering]
[And a boy who stands out]
-K-soul. -K-soul.
[Oh~ K-soul's hairstyle suits him well!]
Oh, the hairstyle suits him well.
[Vocal position: 26th place in Second Semester, Ha Seokhee
25th place in Second Semester, Hwang Jaemin
8th place in Second Semester, Moon Hyunbin]
K-soul.
[Monster, Vocal: Ha Seokhee, Hwang Jaemin, Moon Hyunbin]
[Rap position: 4th place in Second Semester, K-soul
12th in Second Semester, Kang Hyunwoo]
[Monster, Rap: K-soul, Kang Hyunwoo]
[Dance position: 5th place in Second Semester, Ling Qi
2nd place in Second Semester, Yu Junwon
15th place in Second Semester, Kang Minseo]
[Monster, Dance: Ling Qi, Yu Junwon, Kang Minseo]
[The  Team starts introducing!]
-Greetings. 1, 2, 3. -Hello, everyone.
We're the Eight-square Monster's.
[We're the Eight-square Monster's!]
[(Vote for K-soul~)]
[Please]
[Yu Junwon
Will the cheers of the crowd bring the desired outcome?]
Junwon.
[The best Junwon in the universe, Yu Junwon
Will the cheers of the crowd bring the desired outcome? The voting results are good too]
[Special MC, Minho: The vocal, rap and dance positions will keep their eyes on you.]
The vocal, rap and dance positions
will keep their eyes on you.
[Current 1st place of dance position, Hong Sungmin
Special MC, Minho: I wonder if you have the confidence to take the 1st place.]
I wonder if you have the confidence to take the 1st place.
[Current 1st place of vocal position, Lee Hanbin
Special MC, Minho: I wonder if you have the confidence to take the 1st place.]
[Current 1st place of rap position, Park Hyeonggeun]
Whether it's for myself or our team,
[4th place in Second Semester, rap position, K-soul:
Whether it's for myself or our team,]
I'll definitely get 1st place.
[I want the 1st, of course!]
[(Look at his confidence)]
For the team.
We can take the dance position's, right?
[8th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Moon Hyunbin:
We can take the 1st place!]
I'm not confident enough.
[15th place in Second Semester, dance position, Kang Minseo:
I'm not confident enough.]
I'm not confident enough.
[Huh?
15th place in Second Semester, dance position, Kang Minseo:
I'm not confident enough.]
I'm not confident enough to lose.
[Has no confidence to lose]
[(Wow~)]
[Gulping]
[Satisfied
What happened to the Monster Team, which is full of confidence?!]
Punchline.
[The day of grouping
8th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Moon Hyunbin:
I'm about to cry.]
I'm about to cry.
I was really worried.
[Team Satisfaction]
I really love it. I mean it.
[10th place in Second Semester, dance position, Oh Hyeontae:
(Powerful) Everyone is so excellent in this team.]
This is amazing. Everyone is so excellent in this team.
Not bad.
[15th place in Second Semester, dance position, Kang Minseo:
Our team is not bad.]
How does it look like?
[This team is perfect! This is exactly the Monster]
Perfect.
[(Look at him showing off)]
Watch your back.
[While other boys are monkeying around]
You're so adorable.
♫ You're so beautiful. You're my Goddess ♫
Do you know how lonely I am here?
[4th place in Second Semester, K-soul can't get used to it alone]
[Meaningful glance
26th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Ha Seokhee: In the Second Semester,]
In the Second Semester,
[26th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Ha Seokhee:
In the Second Semester,]
when K-soul was in the Thunderous Team,
[26th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Ha Seokhee:
when K-soul was in the Thunderous Team,]
we had some disputes.
[26th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Ha Seokhee:
we had some disputes.]
I want to rap.
[I want to rap x1]
I want to rap this time.
[I want to rap x2]
I want to sing another part too.
[I want to sing rap x3]
[When in the Thunderous Team in Second Semester, K-soul had some issues with the team members]
Another part?
[26th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Ha Seokhee:
So when we were in the same group, I wondered if it would go smoothly.]
So when we were in the same group, I wondered if it would go smoothly.
To be honest, I was worried.
[26th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Ha Seokhee:
What if something goes wrong, like how it was in the Second Semester?
What if something goes wrong?
First of all, we...
[We have to say hello...]
[Everyone
Eye contact]
We...
Right?
-Team... -Welcome, everyone.
[Hurrily welcome all with greetings]
[Temporary excitement]
-Welcome, everyone.
-Welcome. -That's right.
I hope we don't fight this time.
[I hope we don't fight this time.]
-That won't happen to us. -Generally.
[(Let's get along well)]
Let's sort out the parts.
[First of all, let's start with sorting out the parts]
Although the vocal, rap,
[8th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Moon Hyunbin:
Although the vocal, dance, and break are sorted out,]
dance, and break are sorted out,
[8th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Moon Hyunbin:
Vocal seems to have too many verses.
[Vocal] She got me gone crazy. Why did my heart skip a beat?
You're so beautiful. You're my Goddess. Closed tightly
Yeah yeah
I'll knock it open Can you let me in? I'll give you the hidden thrill
The curiosity in your eyes. You're already obsessed
Don’t be afraid. Love is a way Shawty
I got it.You can call me monster
[Vocal] Feel the tremble
Turn your life all the way around. I'm sorry. You make me so crazy
You know you do (ooh)
[Vocal] Creeping creeping creeping
Creeping creeping creeping
You (ooh oh) creeping]
I'm thinking about whether vocal has too many verses.
I think we can sing it together.
[Eyes-rolling
So?]
[8th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Moon Hyunbin:
Shall we share some parts]
Can we share some to rap or dance?
[8th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Moon Hyunbin:
with rap and dance positions?]
Can we share some?
[(Share some parts?)]
Of course, we're grateful.
[12th in Second Semester, rap position, Kang Hyunwoo:
Of course, we're grateful.]
But is it okay to give us the main part?
[12th in Second Semester, rap position, Kang Hyunwoo:
But is it okay to give us the main part?]
[8th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Moon Hyunbin:
There are about three parts here.
[All] I'm creeping in your heart baby
Overturn and swallow it. I indulge in stealing you. I want to destroy you
Brand your heart and live forever after death
Come here girl. You call me monster
(You call me monster)
I will live in your heart]
There are about two or three parts here. Three.
There are two like this. We can split them evenly.
[Since the vocal part has more verses than enough, the members are splitting the part bit by bit]
All at once.
[Rap\Confused]
-Let's split them at one time. -Let's split them at one time.
Or it won't be enough for one or two people.
[Dance
Confused]
Why are you all so kind?
[12th in Second Semester, rap position, Kang Hyunwoo:
Why are you all so kind?]
[In Fantasy Boys After School Excitement Season 2, it's rare to have such a scene showing modesty]
-Why are you so less competitive? -It's a team battle.
Compared to an individual battle,
[Moon Hyunbin, the team leader's idea: It's not only an individual battle, but also a team battle.]
-It feels like a team battle. -it's more like a team battle.
We have to decide the 1st place for vocal, rap,
[8th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Moon Hyunbin:
We have to decide the 1st place for each position.]
and dance. It's a show after all.
[8th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Moon Hyunbin:
Only perfection can show our strength.]
-Everyone needs to do well so that they can stand out. -Right.
-Then... -Then...
[(If vocal position's okay with that...)]
-That's it. -That's it?
[We are happy]
-I can do it. -I can do it.
OK.
[I'm also happy]
-Are we done so easily? -Really.
[Fantastic Boys After School Excitement Season 2
This is the first time I've seen such a part distribution]
I've never seen such a relaxing part distribution.
Very harmonious.
[4th place in Second Semester, rap position, K-soul:
It is very harmonious and the atmosphere is great.]
And the atmosphere is great.
To be honest, I couldn't imagine it before.
[Unimaginable harmony]
The atmosphere in our team is great.
[K-soul is satisfied~]
[Feeling good]
K-soul, well...
[The unprecedented tacit understanding of the Monster Team No. 1]
[12th in Second Semester, rap position, Kang Hyunwoo:
If you compose the flow,]
If you compose the flow,
I'll help you write Korean lyrics.
[12th in Second Semester, rap position, Kang Hyunwoo:
I'll help you write Korean lyrics.]
[Why are you so kind?]
I can write some English lyrics.
[The unprecedented tacit understanding of the Monster Team No. 2]
I'm fine with both the front and the back. K-soul, sing what you want to sing first.
[12th in Second Semester, rap position, Kang Hyunwoo:
K-soul, sing what you want to sing first. I'll sing the rest.]
I'll sing the rest.
[Even the consideration is perfect...]
Hold on. Junwon doesn't have a part, does he?
[No negligence to anyone
The boys take good care of everyone]
I think he doesn't.
Oh, so this is what a team looks like.
[Oh, so this is what a team looks like.]
-I got it. -Five, six.
[The Monster Team's practice time]
[They laugh even if they make mistakes]
Again.
[Cheerful]
If you've memorized all of them, work on the details.
[12th in Second Semester, rap position, Kang Hyunwoo:
Let's work on the details.]
Okay.
-Okay. -It'll be better if we work on the details.
[Okay.]
[(It's the first time Junwon looks like this)]
-Okay. -Okay.
[Do you know why they're doing this?]
-Okay.
[That night, in the group dormitory]
[K-soul is doing something]
[Among the resting boys, he's writing lyrics for the rap alone]
[25th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Hwang Jaemin:
Who wants to take a shower?]
Who wants to take a shower? Do you?
[25th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Hwang Jaemin:
Do you?]
Jaemin, I need to write the lyrics.
[4th place in Second Semester, rap position, K-soul:
Jaemin, I need to write the lyrics.]
I can't even take a shower because I have to write the lyrics.
[4th place in Second Semester, rap position, K-soul:
I can't even take a shower because I have to write the lyrics. (Fighting!)]
[Asking for advice from other teams]
♫ Open my heart with your key ♫
[4th place in Second Semester, rap position, K-soul
Wrote the lyrics till dawn]
♫ Open my heart with your key ♫
[4th place in Second Semester, rap position, K-soul:
Everyone in the team is so nice.]
Everyone in the team is so nice.
I wish I could do better than before.
[4th place in Second Semester, rap position, K-soul:
I wish I could do better than before.]
[On the day of the Interim Reevaluation]
Monster by EXO.
Personally, I'm curious about
[Rap Trainer, Hanhae: Personally, I'm curious about K-soul in the Second Semester,]
-when K-soul was on the last mission. -Yes.
You didn't get to sing rap
[Rap Trainer, Hanhae: You didn't get to sing rap because defeated by Beomjun.]
-because defeated by Beomjun. -Yes.
This time, you have a chance to rap, how do you feel?
[Rap Trainer, Hanhae: This time, you have a chance to rap, how do you feel?]
[How does 4th place in Second Semester, rap position, K-soul, feel?]
I feel...
Good, because
[4th place in Second Semester, rap position, K-soul:
Good, because]
our show was aired last week.
[our show was aired last week.]
I want to try rapping once.
[Everyone knows about his ambition for rapping]
You even did a retrospective.
-I want to show you all... -The handsome styles.
[4th place in Second Semester, rap position, K-soul:
I want to show you all the handsome styles when I rap.]
the handsome style when I rap.
[1st place in Second Semester, dance position, Hong Sungmin:
I really hope they can sing it well.]
But I hope they're a little bit worse than us.
[But I hope they're a little bit worse than us.]
♫ The curiosity in your eyes ♫
[The Interim Reevaluation of the Monster Team begins]
[High notes in the beginning]
♫ You're already obsessed ♫
♫ I'm creeping in your heart baby ♫
[Vocal confidence Full]
♫ Overturn and swallow it ♫
♫ I indulge in stealing you ♫
[Vocal Pass]
[1st place in Second Semester, dance position, Hong Sungmin:
What's wrong with this team?]
♫ Woo, roar, I'm a monster ♫
[A clear rap part sung by 12th in Second Semester, rap position, Kang Hyunwoo]
♫ You've been numb, poisoned by me ♫
[(They sing well?)]
♫ My gravity is pulling you towards me ♫
-♫ The beat of my heart is ♫ -♫ ddududdudu ♫
♫ From zero to one. Then, back to zero again ♫
[Rap position, K-soul, shows up]
[K-soul] ♫ The heart is broken ♫
[K-soul] ♫ Now it's true ♫
[K-soul] ♫ Looks gorgeous from the outside ♫
[K-soul] ♫ Jewellery is like an enchantment to me ♫
[K-soul] ♫ Open my heart with your key ♫
[K-soul] ♫ But re-lock it after opening♫
[(He practiced a lot~)]
[Well done~]
[What about Dance Break?]
They dance really well.
[Nodding]
[33rd place in Second Semester, rap position, Kim Beomjun:
Did they practice super hard? They're really awesome.]
Did they practice super hard? They're really awesome.
[16th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Lee Hanbin:
The eight people from the Monster Team are so scary.]
These eight are so scary.
They are really great.
[A round of unprecedented applause in the Interim Reevaluation]
[(They're really good)]
[All the producers and trainers are satisfied]
Their performance was consistent enough during the Interim Reevaluation.
[Rap coach Hanhae] They were so stable during the interim evaluation.
Rappers have good rhymes.
[Perfect vocal without any flaws]
[Producer JINYOUNG: It's true that this team]
It's true that this team
[Producer JINYOUNG: It's true that this team showed their fierceness.]
showed their fierceness.
They're cheering up the team together.
[Starting with the praise of the Main Producer, JINYOUNG]
I felt their prepared state.
[Keep praising]
I was really surprised after watching K-soul's performance.
[Rap Trainer, Keebe: I was really surprised after watching K-soul's performance.]
[Praise+++]
-Thank you. -First of all,
it was a unique expression.
[Rap Trainer, Keebe: It was a unique expression.]
Because the lyrics contain your thoughts.
[Rap Trainer, Keebe: Because the lyrics contain your thoughts.]
-It sounds great. -Thank you.
[t sounds great.]
-Thank you. -Thank you.
I think the Monster Team is the most threatening one.
[29th place in Second Semester, rap position, Kang Irang:
I think the Monster Team is the most threatening one.]
As expected from Monster. That's the Monster style.
[11th place in Second Semester, Kim Wooseok:
As we expected from Monster. That's the Monster style.]
[33rd place in Second Semester, rap position, Kim Beomjun:
They performed better than I thought.]
They performed better than I thought.
I think it's hard for our team to get 1st place.
[33rd place in Second Semester, rap position, Kim Beomjun:
I think it's hard for our team to get 1st place.]
[After the Interim Reevaluation, the Monster Team has become threatening to the others]
[On the day of the Third Semester's Performance]
Vote for the boys.
[Suddenly, 25th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Hwang Jaemin
looks uncomfortable]
[(Oh, this is strange...)]
[25th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Hwang Jaemin,
walks hurriedly towards the crew during the shooting break]
-I can't hear you. -Increase the microphone's volume.
-What's wrong? -Scenarist-director.
[25th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Hwang Jaemin:
Scenarist-director x2]
Why are you calling me that? What's wrong?
Are you hoarse?
[25th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Hwang Jaemin:
I can't speak up.]
Are you hoarse?
[There's a problem with his throat before the performance]
[Ahhhh]
-Why can't you speak all of a sudden? -Do you want to go to the bathroom?
[Program crew: Why can't you speak up?]
[One hour before the competition
The incident is like a bolt in the blue]
I'm going to the bathroom.
[25th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Hwang Jaemin:
My voice suddenly became weird at the Fantasy Zone.]
In the lounge,
my voice suddenly became weird.
I think I might hold up the team. What should I do?
[I think I might hold up the team.]
Don't worry, Jaemin.
[Hyunbin thought he was nervous
8th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Moon Hyunbin:
Don't worry! Jaemin.]
[25th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Hwang Jaemin:
Listen to my voice. I can't make any more sounds.]
Listen to my voice. Got it. I can't make any more sounds.
[8th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Moon Hyunbin, is now aware of the seriousness]
This is bad.
[13th place in Second Semester, rap position, Kim Gyurae:
This is bad.]
[There's not much time left until the performance]
[8th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Moon Hyunbin:
Just present once well on the stage will do.]
Just present once well on the stage will do.
[25th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Hwang Jaemin:
Yeah, just present once well...]
Yeah, just present once well.
[8th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Moon Hyunbin:
I was at a loss after I knew about Jaemin's throat condition.]
I was really at a loss.
He might blame himself for that.
[8th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Moon Hyunbin:
I was afraid that he would blame himself for that.]
Not to mention that was the day of the performance.
[25th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Hwang Jaemin, fails to carry a tune]
I want to exert force, but I can't.
[25th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Hwang Jaemin:
I want to exert force, but I can't.]
[So far, the Monster Team has been perfect
What will the effects of Jaemin's throat be?]
He seems to have lost his voice while practising.
[Producer KANGSEUNGYOON: He seems to have lost his voice while practising?]
[Producer JINYOUNG: Ah... I'm worried about Jaemin.]
I'm worried about Jaemin.
Wish him all the best.
[1st place in Second Semester, dance position, Hong Sungmin:
Wish him all the best.]
Really.
Do your best and get 2nd place.
[Do your best and get 2nd place.]
The 2nd place is good enough.
[Nervous
Current 1st place of rap position, Park Hyeonggeun]
Get 2nd place after having a blast.
[9th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Hyeonggeun
Let's pray for the Monster Team to get 1st place of vocal and dance positions.]
Hyeonggeun. Let's pray for the Monster Team to get 1st place of vocal and dance positions.
[Staring]
Please.
[Current 1st place of vocal position, Lee Hanbin]
No way.
Either vocal or dance.
[Current 1st place of dance position, Hong Sungmin]
So cool.
Come on.
Ling Qi, come on!
Fighting!
["Monster" by Eight-square Monster's
Original Singer: EXO]
[Dance]
What's going on?
Beomjun, I'm sorry.
[1st place in Second Semester, dance position, Hong Sungmin:
Beomjun, I'm sorry... [Dance]]
[I have a bad feeling [Dance]]
Beomjun, I'm sorry.
[Moon Hyunbin]♫ She got me gone crazy ♫
[Vocal]
[Moon Hyunbin]♫ Why did my heart skip a beat ♫
[Ha Seokhee]♫ You're so beautiful. You're my Goddess ♫
[Hwang Jaemin]♫ Goddess ♫
[Ha Seokhee]♫ Closed tightly ♫
Jaemin is good.
[Hwang Jaemin]♫ I'll knock it open. Can you let me in? ♫
[Moon Hyunbin]♫ I'll give you the hidden thrill ♫
[Hwang Jaemin]♫ The curiosity in your eyes ♫
This team is crazy.
[Hwang Jaemin]♫ You're already obsessed ♫
[Ha Seokhee]♫ Don’t be afraid ♫
[Ha Seokhee]♫ Love is a way ♫
[Ha Seokhee]♫ Shawty I got it ♫
[Ha Seokhee]♫ You can call me monster ♫
[All] ♫ I'm creeping in your heart baby ♫
[All]
[All] ♫ Overturn and swallow it ♫
[(I'm falling for it) [All]]
[They sing so well~! [All]]
They sing so well.
[Serious [All]]
I got goosebumps.
[All]
[All] ♫ I'm creeping in your heart baby ♫
[All] ♫ Overturn and swallow it ♫
[All] ♫ I indulge in stealing you ♫
[Yu Junwon]♫ I want to destroy you ♫
[Junwon is so sexy [All]]
[Kang Hyunwoo]♫ Brand your heart ♫
[All]
[Kang Hyunwoo]♫ Live forever after death ♫
[Yu Junwon]♫ Come here girl ♫
[Ling Qi]♫ You call me monster ♫
[Kang Minseo]♫ I will live in your heart ♫
[Vocal]
[Ha Seokhee]♫ Feel the tremble ♫
[Ha Seokhee]♫ Turn your life ♫
[Ha Seokhee]♫ All the way around ♫
[Ha Seokhee]♫ I'm sorry ♫
[Hwang Jaemin]♫ You make me so crazy ♫
He's here.
[Jaemin, go!]
Jaemin.
-Come on. -Go.
[Vocal]
[Hwang Jaemin]♫ You make me so crazy ♫
[Hwang Jaemin]♫ You know you do ♫
[Kang Hyunwoo]♫ Woo, roar, I'm a monster ♫
[Rap]
[Kang Hyunwoo]♫ You've been numb, poisoned by me ♫
[Kang Hyunwoo]♫ My gravity is pulling you towards me ♫
[Kang Hyunwoo]♫ The beat of my heart is ddududdudu ♫
[Kang Hyunwoo]♫ Yeah I'm a diamond, I make you shine but ♫
[Kang Hyunwoo]♫ I hold you tight, this is fate ♫
[Kang Hyunwoo]♫ I can only call you ♫
[Kang Hyunwoo]♫ The tension has reached the climax huh ♫
[K-soul] ♫ From zero to one. Then, back to zero again ♫
[K-soul] ♫ The heart is broken. Now it's true ♫
[K-soul] ♫ Looks gorgeous from the outside ♫
[K-soul] ♫ Jewellery is like an enchantment to me ♫
[K-soul] ♫ Open my heart with your key ♫
[K-soul] ♫ But re-lock it after opening ♫
[K-soul] ♫ Roses make me bleed ♫
[K-soul] ♫ Beautiful monster I'm crazy ♫
[Hwang Jaemin] ♫ You can call me monster ♫
[Dance]
It's the last dance. It's really the last dance.
[Moon Hyunbin] ♫ You call me monster ♫
[All]
[All] ♫ I'm creeping in your heart baby ♫
[All] ♫ Overturn and swallow it ♫
[All] ♫ I indulge in stealing you ♫
[Junwon [All]
[All]
[K-soul] ♫ I'm going to destroy you ♫
[Ling Qi] ♫ Brand your heart ♫
[Ling Qi+Hwang Jae Min] ♫ Live forever after death ♫
[Ling Qi [All]
[Kang Minseo] ♫ Come here girl ♫
[Hwang Jaemin [All]
[Moon Han-bin + Hwang Jae-min] ♫ You can call me monster ♫
[All]
[Moon Hyunbin] ♫ I will live in your heart ♫
[Yu Junwon] ♫ Creeping Creeping Creeping ♫
[Ha Seok-hee] ♫ You(ooh oh) creeping ♫
[4th place in Second Semester, K-soul]
[2nd place in Second Semester, Yu Junwon]
[[12th in Second Semester, Kang Hyunwoo]
[25th place in Second Semester, Hwang Jaemin]
[8th place in Second Semester, Moon Hyunbin]
So cool.
[5th place in Second Semester, Ling Qi]
[26th place in Second Semester, Ha Seokhee]
[15th place in Second Semester, Kang Minseo]
[Kang Minseo
That's awesome!]
[Yu Junwon, please debut! You are so cool!]
[Moon Hyunbin
Third Semester's Major Field Mission
The show is over]
[Kang Minseo
Jaemin
Third Semester's Major Field Mission
The show is over]
It was really a performance that lived up to our expectations.
[Producer KANGSEUNGYOON: It was really a performance that lived up to our expectations.]
[Along with the praises of KANGSEUNGYOON, the Fantasy Zone is filled with tension]
It's not easy to get such a rating.
[ Producer WOOYOUNG: I think if the current members]
I think if the current members
[ Producer WOOYOUNG: had a good hit,]
had a good hit,
they could have debuted already.
[Could have debuted already?]
[The highest praise]
Come here.
Let's debut.
[K-soul
Moon Hyunbin]
Hyunwoo, please debut.
[K-soul x3]
[K-soul
Fantasy Boys
Kang Minseo, marry me]
I have no objections.
[Same idea]
-I agree. -Yes.
[Current 1st place of vocal position, Lee Hanbin]
Judging from all aspects, I have to become your fan.
[They can't even smile in this situation]
[The current 1st place holders are so nervous]
Thank you.
[Producer JINYOUNG: The more eye-catching one is]
The more eye-catching one is
[The two eye-catching dance positions]
Junwon and Ling Qi.
[5th place in Second Semester, Ling Qi
2nd place in Second Semester, Yu Junwon]
Junwon.
[Junwon is acknowledged]
Junwon is good at everything.
[Yu Junwon is good at everything.]
When he was at the center,
[Producer JINYOUNG: When he was at the center,]
his stage control
[Producer JINYOUNG: his stage control was amazing.]
was amazing.
It was really something.
[2nd place in Second Semester, Yu Junwon, has shown amazing stage control
& 5th place in Second Semester, Ling Qi]
That was very important.
And I saw these.
Good job, everyone.
[Good job, everyone.]
I appreciate your hard work.
Thank you.
[Thank you.]
[The 1st place is threatened]
-But... -They're too strong.
I'm afraid that the three of them are too scary.
[Yu Junwon, Ling Qi, and Kang Minseo
I'm afraid of three of them]
I really...
[10th place in Second Semester, dance position, Oh Hyeontae:
All of them dance well.]
All of them dance well.
[Worried]
Junwon is good at this.
[Producer SOYEON: But there could be a big difference in the number of votes.]
But there could be a big difference in the number of votes.
-The votes. -Yes, I think so too.
[Special MC Minho: Our Yu Junwon.]
Our Yu Junwon.
[Special MC Minho:
Current 1st place of dance position
1st place in Second Semester, dance position, Hong Sungmin, from the REALLY REALLY Team]
is Hong Sungmin, from the REALLY REALLY Team.
[Special MC Minho: is Hong Sungmin.  Can you override Sungmin]
Can you override Sungmin and get 1st place?
[Special MC Minho: and get 1st place? How is it? Are you confident?]
How is it? Are you confident?
Say "I am."
[25th place in Second Semester, vocal position, Hwang Jaemin:
Say "I am."]
[Shy
I am...]
Yes.
Of course.
[I'm watching you
Current 1st place of dance position, Hong Sungmin]
Say it with confidence.
[Say it with confidence!]
You can do it.
[Junwon (can do it!)]
Junwon, you have to be confident.
[Kang Minseo
Junwon, Long live
Ling Qi]
[It's not easy, but...]
It's not easy, but...
[I want to take the 1st place..(?)]
I want to take the 1st place.
[(Nervous mode) I want to take the 1st place..(?)]
Take over?
Do you want it?
[Saves him from embarrassment
Do you want to get 1st place?]
Okay.
[2nd place in Second Semester, dance position, Yu Junwon, hopes for a good result]
We're going to reveal the number of votes for eight Monster Team members.
[The voting count is over.]
The voting count is over.
[The final stage
According to the result of the Monster Team,
the 1st place will be finalized for each position.]
the 1st place will be finalized for each position.
The current 1st place of vocal position
is Lee Hanbin from the REALLY REALLY Team.
[Please, please
Current 1st place of vocal position, Lee Hanbin]
Park Hyeonggeun, rap position from the MIROH Team.
[Current 1st place of rap position, Park Hyeonggeun]
It's a battle between blue-hair Hyeonggeun and red-hair K-soul.
[Rap position: K-soul from Monster VS Park Hyeonggeun from MIROH]
Hyeonggeun is more shocking.
[11th place in Second Semester, Kim Wooseok:
Hyeonggeun is more shocking.]
-Dance position. -Please.
Hong Sungmin from the REALLY REALLY Team.
These three boys are currently the 1st place in each position.
[Current 1st place of dance position, Hong Sungmin]
The voting result of the Monster Team is...
[The voting result of the Monster Team!]
I think the performance was perfect.
[2nd place in Second Semester, dance position, Yu Junwon:
I think the performance was perfect.]
Will I win?
[Will I win?]
I must keep my 1st place of vocal position
to help the team.
Will K-soul win the 1st place in rap?
Please.
[Please...]
Later.
[(Ouch... My heart)]
Tell me.
That's too much.
[K-soul]
[Fantasy Boys, please vote for your Fantasy Boys at Naver NOW.]
It's time to announce the final ranking
[Announcing the final ranking of the Third Semester's Major Field Mission]
of the Third Semester's Major Field Mission.
Before that,
[Before announcing the final ranking,]
-let's announce the benefit points first. -Benefit points.
[Special MC Minho: let's announce the benefit points first.]
Benefit points.
Was it 2,000 last semester?
[(Yes) (Nodding)]
[8th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Moon Hyunbin: Was it 2,000 last semester?]
The 1st place for each position
[Special MC Minho: The 1st place for each position
-will get 10,000 points. -10,000 points.
[The 1st place for Vocal, Rap and Dance position will get 1,000 points]
10,000 points?
[The benefit points for the 1st place are higher than expected]
That's too much.
And each team that the 1st place is in
[Special MC Minho:  Each team that the 1st place is in]
will get 5,000 points.
[All the boys in the team that the 1st place is in will get 5,000 points]
That's so much.
The benefit points for teams are also much.
Winning benefit points becomes more important this time.
[1st in Second Semester, Dance position, Hong Sungmin: Winning benefit points becomes more important this time]
Then we only have to announce the result of Team Monster.
[Then we only have to announce the result of Team Monster]
Which boys will finally get the 1st place for each position?
[Which boys will finally get the 1st place for each position?]
First, I'll announce all the rankings of vocal position.
[Special MC Minho: First, I'll announce all the rankings of vocal position]
[Special MC Minho: all the rankings of vocal position]
[VOCAL] [1st, Lee Hanbin] [2nd, Nam Seunghyun] [3rd, Taeseon] [4th, Kang Daehyeon] [5th, Hikaru] [5th, Kim Wooseok] [7th, Yuma]
[8th, Kim Seungjun] [9th, Kim Daehui] [10th, Daniel Hyunoo Lachapelle] [Vocal position results are revealed]
Vocal.
[Current 1st place for position, Vocal, Lee Hanbin]
Please, Hyunbin.
Please.
[Really Really shows a clean and crisp high note]
[The current 1st place for the vocal position]
♫If I were to measure my feelings with money♫
♫I could be a billionaire♫
I promised to bring my teammates the benefit.
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Lee Hanbin:
To get the first place. I promised to bring my teammates the benefit]
Hyunbin.
[Please] [33rd in Second Semester, Rap, Kim Beomjun. 16th in Second Semester
Vocal position, Kim Hanbin: Especially for now we have to save Beomjun]
Please.
Especially for now we have to save Beomjun.
[Team Monster keeps a close eye on the first place]
Let's hold hands.
I've been anxious.
[25th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Hwang Jaemin: I've been anxious]
We should be able to get the 1st, 2nd and 3rd place at the same time.
[8th in Second Semester, Vocal position: Moon Hyunbin: Team Monster should be able to get the 1st, 2nd and 3rd place at the same time]
[4th in Second Semester, Rap position, K-soul: The camera keeps filming us]
The camera keeps filming us.
Could it be...
[Expecting]
[Special MC Minho: The 1st place vocal position that the Fantasy Makers chose...
The 1st place vocal position that the Fantasy Makers chose...
[VOCAL] [1st, Lee Hanbin, Really Really] [2nd, Nam Seunghyun, Shoot Out] [3rd, Taeseon, MIROH] [4th, Kang Daehyeon] [5th, Hikaru] [5th, Kim Wooseok] [7th, Yuma]
[8th, Kim Seungjun] [9th, Kim Daehui] [10th, Daniel Hyunoo Lachapelle]
[The best Fantasy Boys chosen by Fantasy Makers]
My heart is beating so fast.
Please, it's our team.
[Monster versus Really Really]
[Which team will get the first place for vocal position?]
-It has to be us. -Please.
I'm scared.
[VOCAL] [1st, Lee Hanbin] [2nd, Moon Hyunbin] [3rd, Ha Seokhee] [4th, Hwang Jaemin] [5th, Nam Seunghyun] [6th, Taeseon] [7th, Kang Daehyeon]
[8th, Hikaru] [8th, Kim Wooseok] [10th, Yuma]
Hyunbin.
[The final 1st place for the vocal position, Team REALLY REALLY
16th in Second Semester: Lee Hanbin]
We won.
Well done.
[Final 1st place, Vocal, Lee Hanbin]
Good job, Hanbin.
Hanbin held on to it!
[Producer SEUNGYOON: Hanbin held on to it]
We did it!
[Team Really Really got the first place and was celebrating]
33rd in Second Semester, Rap position,Kim Beomjun: Sungmin. As long as you X3]
Good job, Hanbin.
That's a relief.
-Good job. -Sungmin. As long as you...
Sungmin. As long as you... Sungmin. As long as you...
Sungmin. As long as you...
[Too bad]
[Team Monster missed the final 1st place but got the 2nd, 3rd and 4th place for vocal position at the same time]
No, it's great.
Good job.
[It's okay]
[VOCAL] [1st, Lee Hanbin] [2nd, Moon Hyunbin] [3rd, Ha Seokhee] [4th, Hwang Jaemin] [5th, Nam Seunghyun] [6th, Taeseon] [7th, Kang Daehyeon]
[8th, Hikaru] [8th, Kim Wooseok] [10th, Yuma] [11th, Kim Seungjun] [12th, Kim Daehui] [13th, Daniel Hyunoo Lachapelle]
Sungmin, good job.
Good job.
[4th in Second Semester, Rap position, K-soul: The 2nd, 3rd and 4th place are all in our team?!]
The 2nd, 3rd and 4th place...
The 2nd, 3rd and 4th place are all in our team.
It's nice. It feels better than I got the 1st place.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Beomjun: It feels better than I got the 1st place]
You survived.
[4th in Second Semester, Rap position, K-soul: You survived!]
I survived!
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Beomjun: I survived!]
[(Congratulations)]
[Oh? I thought about it.]
Is it because of the ranking of this song?
[The original singer is satisfied] [The secret to the first place is the ranking of the song Really Really (?)]
[Producer SEUNGYOON: Can't get off from the 1st place?]
Can't get off from the 1st place?
Hanbin is amazing.
[Producer SOYEON: Hanbin is amazing]
Let's announce the rankings of the rap position.
[Special MC Minho: Let's announce the rankings of the rap position]
[RAP] [1st, Park Hyeonggeun] [2nd, Kim Gyurae] [3rd, Kim Kyuhyun] [4th, Song Duhyun] [5th, Hikari] [6th, Seo Sangwoo] [7th, Kang Irang]
[8th, Kim Beomjun] [9th, Kaedan] [Rap position results are revealed]
I hope Hyeonggeun can hold on to it.
[Producer SEUNGYOON: I hope Hyeonggeun can hold on to it (the 1st place for the rap position)]
If Hyeonggeun can...
[Current 1st place for the position, Rap, Park Hyeonggeun, 27th in Second Semester, Rap position.
Park Hyeonggeun: I'm the 1st for the rap position.
I'm the 1st for the rap position.
[Current 1st place for position, Rap, Park Hyeonggeun, 27th in Second Semester, Rap position.
Park Hyeonggeun: I'm confident I'll get the 1st place]
I'm confident I'll get the 1st place.
Hyeonggeun.
-Please. -Please.
[Nervous]
Please.
[Team Miroh desperately wants the benefit]
Hyeonggeun, please.
Please.
[Team Monster is also desperate]
I hope our team can get it.
I think for the rap position,
[4th in Second Semester, Rap position, K-soul: I'm expecting that I'll be the first place for the rap position]
I wrote rap in Korean.
[4th in Second Semester, Rap positioning, K-soul: I wrote rap in Korean]
[4th in Second Semester, Rap position, K-soul: I think I can get the 1st place]
I think I can get the 1st place.
Who will get the 1st place for the rap position?
[Who will get the 1st place?]
Please.
[Special MC Minho: The 1st place rap position that the Fantasy Makers chose is...]
The 1st place rap position that the Fantasy Makers
chose is...
[RAP] [1st, Park Hyeonggeun] [2nd, Kim Gyurae] [3rd, Kim Kyuhyun] [4th, Song Duhyun] [5th, Hikari] [6th, Seo Sangwoo] [7th, Kang Irang]
[8th, Kim Beomjun] [9th, Kaedan]
[RAP] [1st, Park Hyeonggeun] [2nd, K-soul] [3rd, Kim Gyurae] [4th, Kim Kyuhyun] [5th, Song Duhyun] [6th, Hikari] [7th, Seo Sangwoo]
[8th, Kang Irang] [9th, Kim Beomjun] [10th, Kaedan]
[Final 2nd place, Rap, K-soul]
[Yes!]
[Final 1st place, Rap, Park Hyeonggeun]
[The boys of Team Miroh are giving congratulations with their whole body hahaha]
Hyeonggeun.
Let's go!
[RAP] [1st, Park Hyeonggeun] [2nd, K-soul] [3rd, Kim Gyurae] [4th, Kim Kyuhyun] [5th, Song Duhyun] [6th, Hikari] [7th, Seo Sangwoo]
[8th, Kang Irang] [9th, Kim Beomjun] [10th, Kaedan]
[RAP] [1st, Park Hyeonggeun] [2nd, K-soul] [3rd, Kim Gyurae] [4th, Kim Kyuhyun] [5th, Song Duhyun] [6th, Hikari] [7th, Kang Hyunwoo]
[8th, Seo Sangwoo] [9th, Kang Irang]
[Producer SOYEON: But he held on to it (1st place for the rap position) ]
He held on to it.
Hyeonggeun. Really. Hyeonggeun really is...
[Applaud for Hyeonggeun's hard work]
[The result created by the 37th in Second Semester, Park Hyeonggeun, who survived with the wildcard]
You did it.
-Yes! -Great!
You all did a good job.
[Congratulations, Hyeonggeun)]
Thank you.
[25th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Hwang Jaemin: Thank you]
It's a pity for K-soul.
[Also applaud for K-soul who has worked hard]
Park Hyeonggeun who got the 1st place for the rap position
[Special MC Minho: Park Hyeonggeun who got the 1rt place for the rap position
[Special MC Minho: and all the members of Team Miroh]
and all the members of Team Miroh
[Will get 5,000 points]
will get 5,000 points.
-I love you. -I love you.
[14th in Second Semester, Yuma, 9th in Second Semester, Taeseon, 17th in Second Semester, TK, and 19th in Second Semester, Kaedan will get 5,000 benefit points]
Good job.
Hyeonggeun.
[6th in Second Semester, Santa and 28th in Second Semester, Ivan will get 5,000 benefit points]
This scene is really dramatic.
[Producer SEUNGYOON: This scene is really dramatic]
It's really a drama.
[Producer SOYEON: It's really a drama]
He who used to be the last and survived with a wildcard
[Producer SEUNGYOON: He who used to be the last and survived with a wildcard]
got the 1st place for the position.
[Producer SEUNGYOON: got the 1st place for the position]
[Producer SEUNGYOON: He made up a story]
He made up a story
and showed it to everyone.
[Producer SEUNGYOON: and showed it to everyone]
[8th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Moon Hyunbin: Dance position is the only one left so soon]
Dance position is the only one left so soon.
Our Sungmin is also...
[3rd in Second Semester, Rap position, Hikari: Our Sungmin is also amazing]
We have to get dance positions too.
[Both teams are looking forward to the final 1st place for the Dance position, and are fighting an invisible psychological war]
Sungmin, you can do it.
I did it too.
No, we can get the dance positions.
[8th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Moon Hyunbin: We can get the dance positions]
I thought all of you could get it.
[2nd in Second Semester, Dance position, Yu Junwon: I thought all of you could get it (1st place for other positions)]
No, no.
[Team Monster which only got 2nd places for the vocal and the rap positions]
Trust me.
-Trust my feelings. -We can get dance positions. We can get dance positions.
We can do it.
[The competition between 2nd in Second Semester, Yu Junwon and 1st in Second Semester, Hong Sungmin broke out again]
Sungmin!
Sungmin.
But Junwon is amazing too. Dance Junwon.
[Producer SEUNGYOON: But Junwon is amazing for the dance position]
Junwon is amazing.
[Producer SOYEON: Junwon is amazing]
Junwon and Sungmin used to be rivals.
[Producer SEUNGYOON: Junwon and Sungmin used to be rivals]
[Producer SEUNGYOON: But Junwon dances better]
But Junwon dances better.
Dance position.
[1st in Second Semester, Hong Sungmin, who couldn't play all due to left leg injury]
The 1st place for the dance position that the Fantasy Makers
chose is...
You must get it.
[4th in Second Semester, Rap position, K-soul: You must get it (the benefit)]
We have to get a dance position.
Minseo, we have to get a dance postition.
[2nd in Second Semester, Yu Junwon, the youngest and the parent in Team Monster?]
Let's see the result.
[Special MC Minho: Please show the result]
[Who will be the winner of the dance position?]
My hands...
Who will get it?
Junwon, come out.
It has to be Sungmin.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Beomjun: (The 1st place) It has to be Sungmin]
[1st in Second Semester, Dance, Hong Sungmin]
No one can beat him.
[2nd in Second Semester, Dance, Yu Junwon]
It's obvious.
You're already great.
You're all great.
[2nd in Second Semester, Dance position, Yu Junwon: I can't panic, but I think]
I can't panic, but I think
our performance was perfect.
[2nd in Second Semester, Dance position, Yu Junwon: our performance was perfect]
So I was wondering if we could get the 1st place.
[2nd in Second Semester, Dance position, Yu Junwon: So I was wondering if we could get the 1st place]
[Hong Sungmin VS Yu Junwon] [Who is the winner for the dance position?]
Here it comes.
It's joint.
Joint 1st place.
[The joint 1st place statement that emerged amidst the breathtaking tension hahaha]
Minseo, come on.
There should be a 1st place in Team Monster.
[Producer SOYEON: There should be a 1st place in Team Monster]
[Producer SEUNGYOON: In that case... In that case...]
In that case...
[DANCE] [1st, Hong Sungmin] [2nd, Oh Hyeontae] [3rd, Jin Myungjae] [4th, Keum Jinho] [5th, Shiryu] [6th, Hayato] [7th, Ivan]
[8th, Jeong Deunhaesol] [9th, Santa] [10th, TK]
[DANCE] [1st, Hong Sungmin] [2nd, Ling Qi] [3rd, Oh Hyeontae] [4th, Jin Myungjae] [5th, Keum Jinho] [6th, Shiryu] [7th, Hayato]
[8th, Ivan] [9th, Jeong Deunhaesol] [10th, Santa] [11th, TK]
What?
[Current 2nd place for the position, Dance, Ling Qi]
Sungmin.
[DANCE] [1st, Hong Sungmin] [2nd, Ling Qi] [3rd, Oh Hyeontae] [4th, Kang Minseo] [5th, Jin Myungjae] [6th, Keum Jinho] [7th, Shiryu] [8th, Hayato]
[9th, Ivan] [10th, Jeong Deunhaesol] [11th, Santa] [12th, TK] [To be continued]
-Sungmin! -Let's go!
[What's the ranking for 2nd in Second Semester, Yu Junwon?
Junwon.
Then he must be the 1st place.
[What's the ranking for 2nd in Second Semester, Yu Junwon?
Junwon.
[Producer SOYEON: Then Junwon must be the 1st place]
Then he must be the 1st place.
[Who will be the final winner?]
[DANCE] [1st, Hong Sungmin] [2nd, Ling Qi] [3rd, Oh Hyeontae] [4th, Kang Minseo] [5th, Yu Junwon] [6h, Jin Myungjae] [7th, Keum Jinho] [8th, Shiryu] [9th, Hayato]
[10th, Ivan] [11th, Jeong Deunhaesol] [12th, Santa] [13th, TK]
Sungmin.
[Sad and happy]
[Finally, 1st place, Dance, Hong Sungmin]
-I told you. -Sungmin.
What?
[2nd in Second Semester, Hong Sungmin. Although he got the first place, he wasn't happy about it]
I told you.
[Covering her mouth]
[Finally, 5th place, Dance, Yu Jungwon]
-What? -What should I do?
-I told you. -Good job.
No one can defeat Sungmin.
[Producer SEUNGYOON: No one can defeat Sungmin?]
No one can beat Sungmin. And it seems impossible to do so in the future.
[Producer SOYEON: No one can beat Sungmin. And it seems impossible to do so in the future]
[The 2nd in Second Semester, Yu Junwon who lost again in the duel. Unfortunately]
Good job.
What a pity.
I really appreciate the opportunity
[1st in Second Semester, Dance position, Hong Sungmin: I really appreciate the opportunity]
[1st in Second Semester, Dance position, Hong Sungmin: to help our team]
to help our team.
The 1st place for the dance position, Hong Sungmin,
[Special MC Minho: The 1st place for the dance position, Hong Sungmin]
and all members of Team Really Really
[Special MC Minho: and all members of Team Really Really]
[will get 5,000 points]
will get 5,000 points.
Congratulations.
[12th in Second Semester, Rap position, Kang Hyunwoo: How many points will they get?]
How many points will they get?
15,000 points?
Congratulations.
Members of Team Really Really
[Producer SEUNGYOON: Members of Team Really Really got 10,000 points just for the benefit]
-Got 10,000 points just for the benefit. -10,000 points.
[The final benefit for Team Miroh is 10,000 points]
Now only the final ranking of Third Semester is left.
[Special MC Minho: Now only the final ranking of Third Semester is left]
[Special MC Minho: The final ranking of Fantasy Boys in Third Semester]
The final ranking of Fantasy Boys in Third Semester
is determined by the total number of the performance scores of the major field missions,
[Composition of points for the 3rd semester ranking ① Live competition voting points (number of votes X 500) ② Online global voting points ③ Benefit points of the 1st place winner for each position 10,000 points ④ The whole team of the 1st place winner for each position receives 5,000 points. Totaling the results of the above 4 items]
online global votes,
and benefit points.
So, the final ranking ceremony of Fantasy Boys
[Special MC Minho: So,]
[Special MC Minho: the final ranking ceremony of Fantasy Boys]
Third Semester
[Special MC Minho: will now begin]
will now begin.
Oh my god.
[The stage opens]
It's open!
[It's open]
Again. Again.
[All the boys are curious]
It open again.
I don't like that place.
[How many boys passed in Third Semester?]
I'm scared.
Why is it so scaring?
That's right.
I hope I'm not after the 30th place.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Beomjun:
I hope I'm not after the 30th place]
How many seats? How many?
How many?
It's coming down.
[32 boys can enter the Fourth Semester]
32 boys.
Five.
[Producer SEUNGYOON: Five will be eliminated]
Five will be eliminated.
Five.
[5 boys will be eliminated in Third Semester!]
Five. Five.
Five.
[Who will be eliminated this semester?]
-Five. -Five.
There're 37 Fantasy Boys sitting here.
[Special MC Minho: There're 37 Fantasy Boys sitting here]
Five Fantasties Boys
[Special MC Minho: Five Fantasties Boys]
will be eliminated.
[Special MC Minho: will be eliminated]
Just like the last ranking announcement,
[Special MC Minho: Just like the last ranking announcement]
The wildcard of the main producer JINYOUNG in Third Semester
[Special MC Minho: The wildcard of the main producer JINYOUNG in Third Semester]
can save one of them.
[Special MC Minho: can save one of them]
Then will there be 33 places?
[There are 33 boys who can enter Fourth Semester]
Yes. Yes.
[23rd in Second Semester, Dance position, Hayato: It's starting]
It's starting.
[Full of worries. 8th in Second Semester, Moon Hyunbin]
[Special MC Minho: Let's start with the 31st Fantasy Boy]
Let's start with the 31st Fantasy Boy.
[31st place]
[12th in Second Semester, Rap position, Kang Hyunwoo:
Start with the 31th? Leave the 32nd empty?]
Start with the 31th? Leave the 32nd empty?
The first qualifier...
[Special MC Minho: The first qualifier]
[So nervous]
It's coming.
Goodness.
My heart hurts.
[14th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Yuma: My heart hurts]
Please.
[37th in Second Semester, Rap position, Park Hyeonggeun: please]
Although I got the benefit points,
[37th in Second Semester, Rap position, Park Hyeonggeun:
Although I got the benefit points, my ranking is low]
my ranking is low.
[37th in Second Semester, Rap position, Park Hyeonggeun: So I'm a little nervous]
So I'm a little nervous.
It'll be hard if I don't rank above the 31st.
[34th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Kim Daehui: If I don't get called for the 31st]
If I don't get called for the 31st,
I might really go home.
[34th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Kim Daehui: I might really go home]
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Beomjun:
(Because of the benefit points,) I don't think I'll be eliminated]
I don't think I'll be eliminated.
But what if it goes wrong?
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Beomjun:
But what if it goes wrong?]
I'm nervous because of this concern.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Beomjun:
I'm nervous because of this concern]
The 31st place is a boy who didn't get the benefit points.
[Special MC Minho: The 31st place is a boy who didn't get the benefit points]
[37th in Second Semester, Park Hyeonggeun]
[Special MC Minho: He passed]
He passed with flying colors.
[33rd in Second semester Kim Beomjun]
[Special MC Minho: with flying colors]
[Who is the 31st place, the first qualifier?]
[It's a bit dangerous today.]
-It's a bit dangerous today -Yeah.
Please call our names.
[Please call our names]
We're in danger. We have to be called now.
[We're in danger. We have to be called now]
From Team Shoot Out,
[The 31st place is from Team Shoot Out]
[Team Shoot Out that was highly appreciated for their amazing teamwork]
Kim Daehui.
Kim Daehui, please move to your place.
[31st in Third Semester, Kim Daehui]
[31st in Third Semester, Kim Daehui had 3 places up]
Daehui.
No, Daehui.
Daehui, what's going on?
Good job.
[Congratulations]
[Special MC Minho: Kim Daehui, please move to your place]
Kim Daehui, please move to your place.
[27th in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Kyuhyun: Daehui worked really hard]
Daehui worked really hard.
Daehui is really worried.
[10th in Second Semester, Dance position, Oh Hyeontae: Daehui is really worried]
[31st in Third Semester, Kim Daehui: It is more comforting to survive than to be satisfied]
It is more comforting to survive than to be satisfied
with the ranking. First of all, I'm happy,
[31st in Third Semester, Kim Daehui: with the ranking. First of all, I'm happy]
but my ranking has always been very low,
[31st in Third Semester, Kim Daehui: but my ranking has always been very low]
so I have to prepare for each performance with the mentality that it's my last.
[31st in Third Semester, Kim Daehui: so I have to prepare for each performance with the mentality that it's my last]
I'm a little sad about this.
[31st in Third Semester, Kim Daehui: I'm a little sad about this]
I'm glad.
[30th in Second Semester: Vocal position, Daniel Hyunoo Lachapelle: I'm glad]
Okay, next one should be Daniel Hyunoo Lachapelle.
[18th in Second Semester, Dance position, Jin Myungjae:
Okay, next one should be Daniel Hyunoo Lachapelle]
Next, I'll announce the 30th place Fantasy Boy.
[Special MC Minho: Next, I'll announce the 30th place Fantasy Boy]
This qualifier is in rap position.
[The 30th place boy is in rap position]
Rap position?
[6th in Second Semester, Dance position, Santa: Rap position?]
[(Ah...)]
I don't want to be ranked in the thirties.
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Beomjun:I don't want to be ranked in the thirties]
It's okay. Your ranking will be higher.
[21st in Second Semester, Hikaru: It's okay. Your ranking will be higher]
[33rd in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Beomjun: I want to be ranked in the teens]
I want to be ranked in the teens.
Irang?
[Irang? Duhyun? Duhyun! Duhyun!]
Duhyun?
-Duhyun? -Duhyun?
But I'm always the last.
[36th in Second Semester Rap position, Song Duhyun: But I'm always the last]
-Because I'm always the last. -It could be Duhyun.
[9th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Taeseon: It could be Do-hyun]
I'm always the last.
[36th in Second Semester Rap position, Song Duhyun: I'm always the last.
You might go up this time.
[9th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Taeseon: You might go up this time]
[36th in Second Semester Rap position, Song Duhyun: How could I go up for 7 places?]
How could I go up for 7 places?
[36th in Second Semester Rap position, Song Duhyun]
-Irang? -Irang?
[The other candidate for the 30th place, 29th in Second Semester, Kang Irang]
I want to go up.
[29th in Second Semester, Rap position, Kang Irang: I want to go up]
Not me.
[29th in Second Semester, Kang Irang]
Sangwoo?
[27th in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Kyuhyun: Sang-woo?
Sangwoo is in danger too.
[27th in Second Semester, Rap position, Kim Kyuhyun: Sangwoo is in danger too]
[32nd in Second Semester, Seo Sangwoo]
The 30th place.
[Special MC Minho: The 30th place]
Kaedan.
[The 30th place, Kaedan]
[30th in Third Semester, Kaedan]
-What? -Kaedan?
-Is Kaedan the 30th?
[16th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Lee Hanbin: Is Kaedan the 30th?]
-Kaedan. -Kaedan.
[Confused]
Really?
He was ranked 19th.
[9th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Taeseon:
He was ranked 19th in Second Semester]
[30th in Third Semester, Kaedan: Is that right? (Is it really me?)]
Really?
-Kaedan? -Is Kaedan in the 30th place?
[Kaedan drops 11 places to 30th in Third Semester]
-The 30th? -He was ranked high.
-Wan't he in 16th place? -Yes.
Kaedan.
[Although he got the benefit points, his ranking has dropped too]
Didn't he get the benefit points?
He got the benefit.
He got the benefit points.
Kaedan got the benefit points. If he's just in the 30th place,
[36th in Second Semester Rap position, Song Duhyun: Kaedan got the benefit points. If he's just in the 30th place]
He ranked higher than me.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: He ranked higher than me in Second Semester]
Kaedan ranked higher than me.
I'm out.
[18th in Second Semester, Dance position, Jin Myungjae: I'm out]
He even got the benefit points.
What's going on?
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: What's going on?]
[30th, Kaedan]
Hello.
[30th in Third Semester, Kaedan drops 11 places]
What should I do?
[9th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Taeseon:
He would have been eliminated if he doesn't get the benefit points.
Did he get his benefit points added?
I don't know. I don't know, either.
[30th in Third Semester, Kaedan: I don't know (why my ranking dropped). I don't know, either]
Did you have your benefit points added?
[31st in Third Semester, Kim Daehui: Did you have your benefit points added?
Yes, I did.
[30th in Third Semester, Kaedan: Yes, I did]
[30th in Third Semester, Kaedan: I thought I was like hallucinating kind of]
I thought I was like hallucinating kind of
cuz I was thinking is there a way that I could've dropped ten times down?
[30th in Third Semester, Kaedan: cuz I was thinking is there a way that I could've dropped ten times down?]
Wow, really.
[(My hands are trembling)]
Who is the 29th place Fantasy Boy?
[Special MC Minho: Who is the 29th place Fantasy Boy?]
[29th place]
[36th in Second Semester Rap position, Song Duhyun: What should I do?]
What should I do?
-Call my name sooner. -Call my name sooner.
[22nd in Second Semester, Vocal position, Nam Seunghyun: Call my name sooner]
The higher you go, the less certain it is.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: The higher you go, the less certain it is]
[Special MC Minho: For this qualifier]
For this qualifier,
[Special MC Minho: compared to the previous semesters]
compared to the previous semesters,
[Special MC Minho: tthe ranking has dropped a lot]
the ranking has dropped a lot.
Dropped.
[Lower ranking compared to the previous semester]
-Dropped a lot? -Dropped a lot?
The ranking dropped?
[Mentor: Woo-young: The ranking dropped?]
[9th in Second Semester, Taeseon] [21st in Second Semester, Hikaru]
Me? Me?
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: Me? Me?]
If it's me, I would've dropped by 9.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: If it's me, I would've dropped by 9]
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: I didn't get the benefit points]
I didn't get the benefit points,
so my ranking should be lower than last time.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: so my ranking should be lower than last time]
I think my ranking will be lower than the last time.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho:
Lower... Lower... I think my ranking will be lower than the last time]
[8th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Moon Hyunbin: Why do I feel uneasy?]
Why do I feel uneasy?
I feel so uneasy.
[25th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Hwang Jaemin: I feel so uneasy]
Why do you feel uneasy?
[8th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Moon Hyunbin: Why do you feel uneasy?]
I thought I could get the benefit points.
[8th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Moon Hyunbin: I thought I could get the benefit points]
I didn't get any benefit points.
[8th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Moon Hyunbin: I didn't get any benefit points]
I think my ranking will drop a lot.
[8th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Moon Hyunbin: I think my ranking will drop a lot]
The 29th place is
[Special MC Minho: The 29th place is]
Santa.
[Special MC Minho: Santa]
What?
Santa?
Who?
[Santa dropped 23 places in the ranking]
What?
Santa?
Who?
[A big anomaly that shocked everyone]
Santa?
What's going on?
What?
[29th in Third Semester, Santa, dropped 23 places]
Didn't he get the benefit points?
Santa?
What? Santa?
[30th in Third Semester, Kaedan: Santa?
No way.
[Impossible]
[31st in Third Semester, Kim Daehui: That (ranking) has changed too much.
-That has changed too much. -This isn't right.
[The producers are also surprised]
[JINYOUNG is startled]
What's going on?
[36th in Second Semester Rap position, Song Duhyun: What's going on?]
-What? -Didn't he get the benefit points?
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: Is Santa who got the benefit points in 29th place?]
Is Santa who got the benefit points in 29th place?
The 1st in First Semester is now 29th.
[All confused]
Santa who got the benefit points?
Does that make sense?
[23rd in Second Semester, Dance position, Hayato: Is that (the result) right?]
Is that right?
I can't forget the shock that Santa's ranking brought.
[8th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Moon Hyunbin: I can't forget the shock that Santa's ranking brought]
Ah, they must have gotten the name wrong.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho: Ah, they must have gotten the name wrong]
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho:
I thought they called the wrong name]
I thought they called the wrong name.
Could Santa's results be wrong?
[4th in Second Semester, Rap position, K-soul: Could Santa's results be wrong?]
[29th in Third Semester, Santa: It's okay. Thank you]
It's okay.
Thank you.
-Santa is in the 29th place. -It's going down a lot!
It doesn't make sense.
Hello. She's the 29th place of the third semester. [SANTA]
Hello.
[29th in Third Semester, Santa: Hello]
What's wrong?
Hello.
Isn't it good?
How do you drop down 23 places?
[30th in Third Semester, Kaedan: How do you drop down 23 places?]
And we got the benefit too.
[30th in Third Semester, Kaedan: And we got the benefit too]
[29th in Third Semester, Santa: It's okay]
It's okay.
[(I'm not okay. Crying)]
I didn't expect that.
[29th in Third Semester, Santa: I didn't expect it (dropping 23 places)]
My mind went blank.
[29th in Third Semester, Santa: My mind went blank]
I wasn't sad or happy.
[29th in Third Semester, Santa: I wasn't sad or happy]
[Started Fantasy Boys #After School Excitement Season 2 with 1st place in First Semester release ceremony]
[Then he dropped to 6th place in Second Semester release ceremony]
[29th in Third Semester, Santa: I only thought about how much effort I have to put in the future
I only thought about how much effort I have to put in the future
and to show good results.
[29th in Third Semester, Santa: and to show good results]
In this case, it is not surprising who will be called next.
[8th in Second Semester, Vocal position, Moon Hyunbin: In this case, it is not surprising who will be called next]
[15th in Second Semester, Kang Minseo: The atmosphere suddenly becomes dull]
-What's going on? -I think I'll go down too.
[3rd in Second Semester, Rap position, Hikari: I think I'll go down too]
You won't.
[You won't]
[Confused by the drop in the ranking of the upstream boys]
All of us should be eliminated.
That's normal.
-If this situation continues, no one in our team will survive. -No one can survive.
[20th in Second Semester, Dance position, Keum Jinho:
If this situation continues, no one in our team will survive]
Our team will be wiped out.
[Team Shoot Out will be wiped out]
What should I do?
How did this happen?
[The boys who couldn't calm down due to the shocking results]
Is this right? Is this right?
The 1st place of First Semester will face elimination crisis in the next semester.
[The 1st place of First Semester will face elimination crisis in the next semester]
[1st in Second Semester, Hong Sungmin: Let's continue later]
Didn't he get the benefit points?
[In chaos] [Who will make it to Fourth Semester?]
Fantasy Boys After School Excitement Season 2.
I'm telling you how to vote for Fantasy Boys.
[The voting method for Fantasy Boys is revealed]
[The voting method for Fantasy Boys After School Excitement Season 2:
Step 1. open the official app on your smartphone]
Open the official app on your smart phone.
Choose Fantasy Boys After School Excitement Season 2
[The voting method for Fantasy Boys After School Excitement Season 2: Step 2. Choose Fantasy Boys on the homepage. Click the "Voting" button on on the right.
on the homepage.
Click the "Voting" button.
[The voting method for Fantasy Boys After School Excitement Season 2: Step 3. Choose from 12 Fantasy Boys, click the voting button.
You can only vote once a day.]
Choose from the 12 Fantasy Boys and vote.
You can only vote once a day.
Votes from Korea accounts for 60% of the total result,
[Votes from Korea accounts for 60% of the total result] [while votes from the rest of the world accounts for 40% of the total result] [Votes from Korea accounts for 60% of the total result] [Votes from the rest of the world accounts for 40% of the total result]
while votes from the rest of the world accounts for 40% of the total result.
All votes counted will be converted to points.
[All votes counted will be converted to points]
Fantasty Makers,
[Fantasy Makers!]
The debut of Fantasy Boys will be decided by you.
[The debut of Fantasy Boys will be decided by you]
[Global voting] [Please refer to the official page or SNS for additional voting and global voting participation methods]
Please vote now.
[Fantasty Boys After School Excitement Season 2
Please vote for your Fantasy Boys on Naver Now]
Next is the 28th.
[The announcement ceremony continues]
His ranking has dropped a lot.
[The beginning of the dramatic change of ranking]
[Debut team drops in ranking]
What?
[Who is the boy who brings shock and terror?]
This is unprecedented in the history of survival cometition, right?
[This is unprecedented in the history of survival cometition, right?]
-The best for the Third Semester's Major Field Mission... -So cool. You passed.
[Who is the new boy in the debut team?]
Finally, the 1st place is...
[(Me?)]
Wow, awesome!
[Awesome]
[Come on]
Come on.
-It's really a drama -Really.
[What will be the fate of the boys at the announcement ceremony?]
The subject of the Fourth Semester is teamwork.
[The subject of the Fourth Semester is teamwork]
Just form your own team according to what you want.
[Team up with the boy who wants to be in the same group!]
Without red hair, everything will go smoothly.
[Psychological battle to form a team]
No. No.
Beomjun is a little...
[Compete for members to form the best team]
Remove him.
What about Minseo?
[Give up Daehui. Give up Daehui.]
Give up Daehui. Give up Daehui.
Aren't we going to win 1st place?
[Aren't we going to win 1st place?]
[Run for the song selection]
Run! Run!
No, we have to win 1st place.
[We have to win 1st place]
[Which team will be the first to pick songs?]
Now the team formation is not yet over.
[It's not over yet]
The team with bad grades...
[Nervous. In progress evaluation. The team with bad grades]
Please stop.
Should give up one team member.
[Give up one team member]
[Shocked]
This is so cruel.
♫Make me feel so high♫
[The teamwork mission begins]
♫I'm waking myself up♫
[To show everything with the replaced group members]
♫What should I do? I'm dancing♫
[Fight for the benefit points]
[Who will win Fourth Semester mission?]
That's amazing.
They sang very well live.
♫We going Ko Ko Bop♫