[Lee Dong Won as Seung Jun]
[Seong Tae as Jae Hyeon]
[Shin Myeong Seong as Ho Yeon]
[Kim Gyu Jong as Ju Won]
[Happy Merry Ending]
Focus.
A beautiful melody fills the hall.
And you meet my eyes
before you start singing.
And...
You close your eyes
Imagine that there's only you and me there.
What is that supposed to mean?
You never know.
You might sing better when I'm the only one you can see.
Now try it.
No.
Try it.
I just cast a spell on you.
I said no.
Just this once!
Forget it.
Now is the perfect time to...
Hey, Ho Yeon!
[Episode 5: Skinship With Him]
Who is this?
This is Song Jae Hyeon, who will be taking classes from me starting today.
I mean... he's Jae Hyeon Hyeong.
- Hi, I'm Song Jae Hyeon.
- Okay.
And this is my friend, Im Ho Yeon. He lives upstairs.
I see.
I didn't realize it was so late.
Seung Jun, I should get going.
See you again, Ho Yeon.
Yeah, hurry home safely.
You finished early.
I'm relieved to see that you look happier than you did a while ago.
- Good night.
- Are you going home?
Let's eat together!
I already ate.
[You must be busy. When can we meet?]
Why was he looking for me?
Seung Jun!
I've been calling you for a while.
Sorry, I didn't hear you.
Let's go in.
Next up is a song to celebrate the bright future of the bride and groom!
Please give them a round of applause.
♪ Your smiling face keeps appearing in my mind ♪
♪ One day, suddenly, you became a part of my daily life ♪
♪ I imagine the things I want to do when I meet you ♪
♪ And by doing so, even a typical boring day ♪
♪ Becomes special ♪
♪ Ever since I met you, ♪
♪ All the moments in my ordinary, daily life have become ♪
Did you like my sunglasses?
I almost made a mistake... Please don't do that again.
It's nice to see you smile.
I shouldn't have said that.
There's that startled expression again.
It's just that it's really nice to see you smile!
You don't have classes today, right?
I'll drive you home.
Seung Jun.
- Seung Jun!
- What?
Why are you staring at your phone? Are you waiting for a call?
No.
But there is someone I hope never calls.
I have to stop by some place.
Where is he?
What the...
Are you up?
Why did you come here?
Something is troubling you, isn't it?
But you wouldn't tell me even if I asked.
So I'm just going to stay with you.
I'll keep this with me for a while.
Should we take a walk?
♫ By the time the sun sets and the skies fade to red ♫
How is it?
This is nice.
No more complicated thoughts.
I like it, too.
Do you come here often?
Yes. When I'm frustrated...
When I want to listen...
When I wonder what you're doing.
When I miss you.
That is why I come to see you.
Why are you being like this...
to someone like me?
I've never done anything like this before, either.
But I just want to stay by your side...
and protect you.
I can't resist anymore.
Can I kiss you?
♫ Because I grew it just for you ♫
Where the hell is he, and what is he up to?
This guy has been calling for a while.
Are you sure you don't have to pick up?
Yes, it's fine.
Who is it?
The man who made me like this.
It's been so long since I felt this peaceful.
I couldn't stop thinking about you.
- See, I told you it doesn't work!
- Wait. Move, move.
- Is it okay?
- Yeah.
How is this?
Wow! It suits you!
Two, one!
♫ One day, suddenly, you became a part of my daily life ♫
♫ I imagine the things I want to do when I meet you ♫
- Ducks!
- Where?
There! Ducks!
That's cute.
♫ Becomes special ♫
Wow. What is this?
I made it.
- You made it yourself?
- Of course! Try it.
- I want to try it.
- Go ahead.
How is it? It's good, right?
Really good.
I can make it for you every day.
- Really?
- Of course.
Chew before you swallow.
And remember to relax your lips when you practice.
Yes!
Hm... But why isn't this coming off...
Thank you very much!
Yes, good job today.
Chan Wu.
Why don't you try taking another teacher's class?
What?
Why?
I don't want to. I like you.
The CEO told me he likes you, too.
Dance songs aren't really my area of expertise.
And I was planning on getting some time off from the academy.
Oh, I see.
That's a shame.
I'll see you out.
Get back safely.
Teacher, does that mean we won't be seeing each other?
It's not like we will never see each other again if we don't meet here anymore.
You can call me if something happens.
Oh! Thank you, Teacher.
Can I call you often?
Not too often.
Okay.
Oh! It's the CEO! CEO!
Chan Wu, can you wait for me in the car for a little while?
Yes.
How have you been?
What are you doing?
What does it look like?
I'm just picking up my trainee.
Did you send him here on purpose?
Isn't Chan Wu nice?
I thought you two would get along.
He is a lot like you.
You must be having a hard time. Your face looks rough.
My little Seung Jun, you used to be so nice when you were younger.
If you don't have anything to say, I will leave now.
What's the rush?
I have a proposal for you.
♫ By the time the sun sets and the skies fade to red ♫
♫ And I watch our shadows grow longer ♫
♫ Even if there are no expressions or words left to say ♫