♪In these hazy days♪
♪My head's in a daze♪
♪Each day's pain, like a fiery blaze♪
♪But hope flickers,
in this darkest haze♪
♪I'm used to it all,
in these darkened ways♪
♪My hand, we hold it down♪
♪We hold it, hold it down♪
♪Hold it down♪
♪My hand, we hold it down♪
♪We hold it, hold it down, it down♪
♪Before the dawn's new round♪
♪We hold it down♪
♪Hold it down♪
♪Before the stars are crowned♪
♪We hold it down♪
♪Hold it down♪
♪Lovers won't eject me♪
♪Fortune will protect me♪
♪Past will connect me♪
♪You're ducking, you're a glitch, see?♪
=See Her Again=
=Episode 15=
Hello?
He's asleep. What's the matter?
Keep a close eye on him.
Call me immediately
if he leaves the house.
What happened?
Has Sundess arrived in Hong Kong, China?
Just follow my instructions.
Keep in touch.
Your men are tailing us so closely.
They'll find out easily.
Inspector Liu,
please tell our brothers
to scatter.
Don't tail us too closely.
Understood.
Vehicle No. 1 and 2, spread out.
I'll tail their car.
Please hand over your phone.
Miss Zhuang.
It's rare for you to bring a friend.
How should I address you?
I'm Zhang Tianming.
Luckily, Inspector Zhang
rescued me in the nick of time.
If not, who knows if I'll live to tell the tale?
Welcome, Inspector Zhang.
Boss.
Let me introduce him.
This is Zhang Tianming.
Senior inspector of
Kowloon West Crime Unit.
He's highly regarded.
He's in charge of many cases.
Nice to meet you, Boss.
I'm responsible for
some of the major cases.
I hope I can be of use to you.
Inspector Zhang,
I think one of your friends
is outside.
Why don't you invite him here?
What is it?
Your friend is inviting you inside.
Who is this?
Inspector Zhang, why don't you introduce him?
Will Inspector Liu be in danger?
Give him some time.
I'm sure he can deal with it.
He's my superior.
I don't know why he tailed me.
Let me explain myself.
After the previous auction,
we've already gotten hold
of all the evidence.
We cracked your PC as well.
But for some reason,
the PC was showing garbled texts.
Miss Zhuang was released
without any charges.
After that, I started suspecting him.
That's why I tailed him.
But I never expected this.
I realized
that I could get to know
all these major figures
before my retirement.
Do you know how excited I am?
When it comes to ranking,
I'm the Chief Inspector of Police.
He's nothing.
When it comes to experience
and connections,
do you think you can one-up me?
How can he replace Chief Ye?
He's just a minor figure.
He can't achieve anything.
Do you guys want to consider me instead?
So, you were advertising yourself, huh?
So, sir,
how should we address you?
I'm Liu Weitao.
Inspector Liu,
what about this?
Why don't we have a drink first?
(No signal)
Why did we lose signal?
Is it our issue?
Let me check.
I'm done checking.
It isn't our issue.
I'll go and check it out. You stay here.
Okay.
Do another check.
Everyone, take note.
We found Coroner Chen's car in Section 2.
Dr. Zhou is found unconscious
at the backseat.
Coroner Chen is missing.
Roger that.
Please keep an eye out.
Okay.
Mustang, let's go.
All these years,
I was diagnosed with a hidden condition.
I have decision paralysis.
Making decisions terrifies me.
Both of you are elite personnel.
But I only require one of you.
How can I make a decision
between you two?
- Hui!
- Dr. Zhou.
What happened?
There's a needle mark
on Dr. Zhou's neck.
Mommy!
What is Dr. Zhou doing here?
Where's Coroner Chen?
I think we were duped.
What about this?
You two can decide for me.
Let's see who can convince me.
What's with the sudden fire?
(Level 5 Fire at King Shun Building,
39 Dead 80 Injured)
Help!
Even after all these years,
I still have nightmares of it.
I'm surrounded by fire.
The smoke is too thick!
King Shun Building Fire
that occurred in 1990
(Preliminary List of Deceased)
had claimed countless lives
(An Accident)
and homes.
It's on fire!
Where can we go?
- Leave!
- Don't go there!
Just go!
What should we do?
Boss, watch out!
Run!
Just go!
Help!
Is anyone out there?
Watch out!
Don't go there!
It's dangerous!
Help!
Don't go there!
It's dangerous!
Seek shelter in the room! Hurry!
Get inside!
Let's seek shelter!
Hurry!
Open the door!
Boss!
Boss, open the door!
Why did you shut them out?
This is a sacred Feng Shui room.
I can't allow anyone
to enter and exit the room at will.
Let us in!
Boss!
Hurry and think of something!
Put your back into it!
I don't care about that!
They'll die if we don't open the door!
You see,
just pretend
that this incident never happened.
In the future, you should serve me.
You'll enjoy endless wealth
and prosperity.
Inspector Liu!
I obtained the hard drive.
I've managed to acquire
evidence of Sundess's crime.
Great job.
Inspector Liu!
Jiajie,
where are you?
Inspector Liu is in trouble.
Doctor, how is he?
I'm sorry.
Jiajie!
Even if you kill him now,
there's no way to revive Inspector Liu!
Sundess isn't dead!
He was supposed to be imprisoned
for the rest of his life.
You set fire to the building
and implicated my brothers!
You killed him!
Officer, take him outside!
Get out!
Let's go!
Does he intend to bind his wife and daughter
with these shackles?
Just do your work.
Don't spout nonsense.
Mommy.
Where's Jiao?
He's inside Inspector Liu's office.
My mother saw the news.
She found out
that Inspector Liu was killed.
She wanted me to resign immediately.
You're the sole son of the family.
I can understand her feelings.
Indeed.
There's nothing more important than family.
What do you plan to do, then?
Inspector Liu once said
that the most important trait
of a member of the Crime Unit
is determination.
We should never give up.
Now, Inspector Liu has left the unit.
We're responsible for
keeping the unit intact.
All the more I cannot leave!
Sorry for the trouble.
What else can I do for you?
He wasn't willing to say a word
upon learning
that Sundess is still alive.
Let me give it a try.
But Mommy...
I'll be fine. Don't worry.
Let's go.
Someone wishes to see you.
I'm sorry.
I'm not here today
as a police consultant.
I'm here as your wife.
We've been together for so long.
It turns out that you were hiding
so many things from me.
I couldn't help you out
even after such a major incident.
I think I'm partly responsible
for your downfall.
Dear,
can you promise me this?
From now on,
stop hiding any secrets from me.
Be honest with me, okay?
We can face the hardships together.
I wish to know
if he was Mai Zhihong's tutor,
how they got to know each other,
and why they planned
the murder together.
Are you Mai Zhihong's tutor?
How did you two get to know each other?
And, why did you two
plan the murder together?
Fate is truly a magical thing.
I got to know Mai Zhihong
on the day he wanted to commit suicide.
(Back then, I was passing by a garden.)
(I saw Mai Zhihong
writing his last will.)
(I told him)
(that if he had the courage
to commit suicide,)
(he should do
something meaningful instead.)
(I did more than just save his life.)
(I also knew
he was constantly bullied at school.)
(It's because he had
cognitive impairment.)
(He couldn't catch up
to his classmates.)
(He was living in despair.)
(Chi Tak Secondary School Math Exercise)
(That's why I provided him with free lessons.)
For this question,
it's asking you about AC.
It is known that ABN
is larger than DIA...
(I even took him)
(around my university.)
(To him,)
(I was the only person)
(who cared about him.)
Can I truly
study here?
What was his goal for treating
Mai Zhihong that nicely?
Did he intend to use him long ago?
I truly helped him
out of kind intentions.
Maybe it's because he led
a similar life to mine.
Both of us were forgotten
by the world.
When he was born,
he was detested by his mother
because she thought
he caused her husband's death.
When I was born,
my father abandoned the family.
I had to bear the entire family
on my shoulders.
I had to rob someone
to pay for my mother's
medical bill.
Since you hate your father so much,
I'm sure you didn't do it to avenge him.
Why did you kill
all those innocent people, then?
You poured his ash
into the toilet bowl.
You hate your father that much.
All these years,
I kept reminding myself
that nothing is more important
than family.
But today, you betrayed me.
You're no different from He Zhaoyong.
Back then, I went to King Shun Building.
I begged my father
to visit my mother one last time.
However, he
and that woman chased me away.
Back then, I truly wanted him to die.
I'm begging you.
Mom doesn't have much time left.
Can you please spare some time
and visit her one last time?
You're so annoying.
Stop bothering me.
I'm begging you here.
Okay?
I'm begging you.
Please see her one last time.
Enough already.
I'll visit her, okay?
I'll visit her.
When will you visit her?
I'll visit her...
As if!
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
(It turns out that my mother
was the one who cheated on him.)
(She even made my father angry)
(by saying
that I wasn't his biological son.)
(My father left the family,)
(gambled, and fooled around)
(with other women out of spite.)
(He finally forgave my mother)
(before she passed away.)
(He even)
(apologized to me)
(for thinking)
(that I wasn't his biological son.)
(Finally, my father
had reconciled with me.)
(But that night,)
(he was burned to death)
(in King Shun Building)
(for no apparent reason.)
(My mother couldn't take the blow.)
(She passed away not long after that.)
That night,
I thought I finally had a family.
On the same night,
that fire
had shattered many families.
Since when did you plan
to murder them?
Why did Mai Zhihong help you out?
Rest early.
You too.
That night, I sent my father back
to King Shun Building
after we visited my mother
in the hospital.
When I was leaving,
I saw several suspicious men
pushing barrels
of kerosene.
Tian.
Tell our men to hurry up.
That man
exchanged a glance
with the security guard.
After that, the security guard
unlocked the gate
and allowed him upstairs.
Back then, I didn't pay attention
to the potential scenarios.
I never expected a fire to break out.
39 innocent lives were claimed,
including my father.
(11. He Zhaoyong)
(An Accident)
(However,)
(Nothing Suspicious About It)
(the investigation report stated)
(that it was merely an accident.)
(There was no human involvement.)
(Kowloon Yau Ma Tei Temple Street,)
(I thought something was off.)
(Kowloon West Crime Unit)
(Therefore, I wrote an anonymous letter)
(to the Crime Unit)
(and reported my findings to them.)
(I reminded them)
(that it might be a case of arson)
(and that they should
continue the investigation.)
(However,)
(the cops did nothing at all.)
(The issue was left unresolved.)
(I couldn't just let those murderers)
(get away scot-free.)
(Since the law couldn't deal with them,)
(I had to deal with them personally.)
Back then,
we didn't receive any anonymous letter.
I think Chief Ye intercepted the letter.
After that, I found someone named
Black Guy Tian
after my investigation.
I still wish to know
who else was involved in the case.
Therefore, I tailed Black Guy Tian.
Come.
Cheers.
We wouldn't need
to go through all that trouble
if those poor folks were willing
to sell their units in the first place.
I never expected the fire
to be that huge.
They're just unlucky.
Fire brings prosperity
to the land it blazes.
Thank you, Boss.
Thank you, Fa.
(I never expected the case)
(to be related)
(to such a huge group.)
(All of them deserved to die.)
Come. Eat up.
I wanted to kill these scums
using different methods.
But it was hard to achieve that alone.
Since Mai Zhihong idolized me,
he would never betray me.
He was the best assistant I could find.
Who's there?
Show yourself!
(I thought)
(that I could put
my medical knowledge to use.)
(First, I knocked them out
with anesthetics.)
(After that, I arranged
different methods of death for them)
(to misdirect the cops.)
Actually, Mai Zhihong
was a poor soul.
He was persecuted
and bullied by society.
He had nowhere
to express his frustrations.
That's why he helped you to murder them.
Not only did he do me a favor,
but he also did himself a favor.
He murdered the person
he wanted to murder.
Who was it?
Hold it.
Find its neck.
It's around here.
Inject the anesthetics.
This much is enough.
Slit the throat quickly.
Do not delay your strike.
Do you know
what's the best way
to deal with people who bully you?
That is to take the preemptive strike.
What about Zhang Qiang, then?
Mai Zhihong had an alibi
on the night of Zhang Qiang's murder.
Who murdered him, then?
My initial plan was merely
to murder the group of people
who planned for the arson.
But when I watched the news that night,
Zhang Qiang said
he rescued over ten people
during the cargo ship fire.
The government even awarded him
with a medal.
I remember that he said
the fire was merely an accident
during the Commission
of Inquiry's press interview.
As the leader of the fire department,
he should know the truth
better than anyone else.
But he lied to the people.
I was angry.
I started tailing him.
Wait here.
Dad, I want...
I know.
Mommy wants black sesame
glutinous rice dumplings.
You want mango pudding, right?
I'll be back in a second.
(I saw that he was
entering an alley alone.)
(Even the heavens were helping me out.)
(I couldn't notify Mai Zhihong in time.)
(I could only do it myself.)
My father was innocent!
He was forced to do so!
Why did you kill him?
Inspector Zhang!
Why did you murder him?
He told a blatant lie.
Anyway,
those who were involved in the tragedy
must pay the price.
Inspector Zhang!
Let's head outside for now!
You guys should leave.
I'll do the interrogation.
Let me go!
Get out!
You scum!
In 1993,
you ceased your operation
after murdering several people.
You murdered Deng Hongfa
a few years after that.
After that, you waited for over 20 years
before you murdered
Ma Furong and Shi Dazhi.
Why?
Because of you.
Back then,
Mai Zhihong and I were supposed
to meet up in the sewers
and discuss how to murder Deng Hongfa.
But you appeared out of the blue.
HKPD!
If so,
how did Mai Zhihong
get the knife scar on his right waist?
He said the cops
always suspected him
of being the culprit.
If they found out
that he didn't have a scar on the waist,
they'd know that the culprit
was someone else.
Therefore, he created that scar
to cover up for me.
The cops
are keeping a close eye on us.
If they find out
that there's no scar on your waist,
all of our previous efforts
will go down the drain.
(It's a shame)
(Mai Zhihong was sent)
(to Siu Lam Psychiatric Centre)
(after attempting to murder his sister.)
(I lost my trusty assistant.)
(And, Deng Hongfa)
(had also tightened
the security around him.)
(His bodyguards were guarding him 24/7.)
(Since there was no chance
for me to strike,)
(I used the opportunity
to lay low abroad.)
(I went to Canada,
using study as my excuse.)
(After that, I thought of)
(getting over the past)
(and leading a simple life.)
(But some events
are predestined to happen.)
(Maybe the ending would've been different)
(had I not returned
to Hong Kong, China, in 1996.)
Dear,
we've tried all the ways
that are available.
Maybe the heavens
don't want us to have children.
If so, we can adopt foster children.
It doesn't matter.
(Mr. Deng Hongfa Donated 10 Million HKD,
Sparing No Effort for Charity)
(Initially, I thought I could)
(get over the past.)
(But that scum, Deng Hongfa,)
(he committed all kinds of evil deeds,)
(yet he was leading a glorious life.)
(And, everyone was praising him)
(for being a renowned philanthropist.)
(There was no way I could let him off.)
(Deng Hongfa knew that he had committed
too many evil deeds.)
(He was afraid of karma.)
(He tried to set up a living tomb)
(to bring luck and avoid disaster.)
Mr. Deng, you're here.
I've already prepared the items
you requested.
Do I perform the ceremony now?
Mr. Deng,
here are the clothes you requested.
(Ancestor, Deng Jian)
(I never expected)
(that someone else was
trying to kill Deng Hongfa as well.)
(Ye Cheng also wanted to kill him.)
(However, he couldn't do it.)
(I couldn't afford to miss out
on the opportunity either.)
(Mai Zhihong once told me)
(that a fellow patient of his)
(was the owner of a unit
in King Shun Building.)
(He didn't sell his unit
because he thought Ma Furong and Yan Hua)
(wasn't trustworthy.)
(But they set him up.)
(He was beaten up so badly
that his brain was damaged.)
(The number of innocent people
that those scums had harmed)
(was way more than just
the victims of the fire.)
(After that,)
(Mai Zhihong managed to escape)
(when he went outside)
(to pay respect to his mother's grave.)
(He continued to assist me
in seeking revenge.)
Thus, you employed
the same method you used 25 years ago.
You knocked Ma Furong out
with anesthetics.
(After that,)
(you arranged for the scene)
(to look like
an electrical shock accident.)
And, you tampered with
the autopsy report.
You brought forward
Ma Furong's time of death,
creating an alibi
for Mai Zhihong.
It misdirected our investigation.
(I found out that Ma Furong)
(had hotpot with his friends)
(from 6 P.M. to 8 P.M.)
(on the night of his death.)
I have a question.
Does that mean
Mai Zhihong's alibi
is invalid?
According to your deduction,
and if we take his autopsy report
into consideration,
his time of death
wouldn't be the result we came upon,
which was 7:30 P.M. to 9.30 P.M.
It should be after 12 A.M. instead.
Back then,
you weren't suspicious of me at all.
I instructed Mai Zhihong
to keep in touch with you
so that he could gather clues
from you all.
Finally, I found
a key figure.
That was Shi Dazhi.
A needle mark was found
on the victim's neck.
Therefore, it's possible that someone
injected anesthetics into her body
through her neck.
A needle mark?
It must be Mai Zhihong.
The underground money laundering center
was busted.
They might silence you at any time.
I'll go and get changed.
Your boss is trying to silence you.
Even so, you're still
hiding his identity.
Tell me who he is.
Sun...
Sundess.
Why did you force
Mai Zhihong to commit suicide?
I didn't force him.
He returned the ownership
of his life to me willingly.
(Mr. Chen, my life is yours.)
(I will do whatever you want me to do.)
(If you think my life)
(can be of use to you,)
(you may take it too.)
(Mai Zhihong would
understand the instruction)
(as long as he received the pen.)
(Zhihong's death wasn't in vain.)
(After his death,)
(your superiors
closed the case immediately.)
(Thanks to that, Sundess and his men)
(let down their guard.)
(That gave me the opportunity to strike.)
(I found out)
(that the painting of Sundess's wife)
(would be featured in an art exhibition.)
(But I wasn't sure)
(whether or not Sundess
would return to Hong Kong, China.)
(Therefore, I targeted Zhuang Xiaohua.)
(I kidnapped her)
(and forced her to lure
Sundess back to Hong Kong, China.)
(After that, I made her
tell me where their base was.)
Don't do it!
I'll help you out!
(I was going)
(to burn those scums to death.)
(I wanted them to know)
(what the victims)
(of King Shun Building Fire
felt back then.)
Do you think
that you're upholding justice
by murdering them?
My only goal
was to seek revenge.
As for whether or not I upheld justice,
the people can be the judges.
You burned innocent people to death.
Does that represent justice?
What makes you different
from those scums, then?
The difference is ...
Innocent people had died.
I didn't want this to happen either.
But sometimes,
sacrifices are needed
if we wish to achieve certain goals.
Is that your excuse
for murdering people, then?
You even manipulated Kaiqing.
Did you even take her
as your daughter?
Listen.
When Kaiqing was born,
I promised myself
that I should solve
these cases vigorously.
It's because I didn't want my daughter
to grow up
in a shady world.
I'm the same as you.
I'm also trying
to make the world a better place.
♪Day after freaking day♪
♪How long can you hold on to your lies?♪
♪How long can you hold them tight?♪
♪Day after freaking day♪
♪Today you know you're fighting,
you're lying♪
♪You're lying, you're fighting♪
♪You're fading, you're fading♪
♪You know it, you know it♪
♪You're shouting, you're fighting♪
♪You're fighting, you're lying♪
♪You're lying, you're lying♪
♪You're shouting, you're shouting♪
♪You're fighting, you're fighting,
you're fighting♪
♪You gotta look after your soul♪
♪Before your body can't hold the weight♪
♪Of darkness within each inch of smile♪
♪Of innocence out of each kill♪
♪You gotta look out for your will♪
♪Before the hands
get inside of the drill♪
♪Of many that won't make it to the end♪
♪Of none at all
that could bare to stand♪
♪Of many that won't make it to the end♪
♪Of none at all
that could bare to stand♪
♪Of many that won't make it to the end♪
♪Of none at all
that could bare to stand♪
♪Of many that won't make it to the end♪