One, two, three...
And back, one, two, three.
[Bus 073B arriving shortly]
Hello, Star Family, how are you?
I am Jae Min, the stargazer, keeper of the byeol (star), the star, l'étoile.
I've got a special story to tell you today.
Do you, my Star Family, know about "The Red Thread of Fate?"
The story of the red thread.
They say people who are really meant to be together
are connected by a red thread between their little fingers.
That thread can't be untied even if one wants to,
nor can it be tied to someone else's finger.
That's quite interesting, isn't it?
There's probably a lot of people looking at their little fingers now.
Then, shall we all raise our little fingers slightly above our heads
and try to find our one true love?
How did you do, my Star Family?
Have you all found your true love?
Now let's listen to a song that fits this mood.
♫ Your tone was a little different than usual ♫
♫ I feel like we're breaking up ♫
♫ Can we please just move on for now? ♫
♫ Even if it's just until tonight ♫
♫ Your color, your thoughts, your habits, your everything ♫
♫ I think I finally understand, so why?
You said you wanted to break up, why?  ♫
♫ How hard it must have been to be alone,
I’m sorry I couldn’t hug you ♫
♫ I don't think I'll ever forget you ♫
♫ Can you stay by my side, just for today? ♫
♫ Even if you don't love me anymore ♫
Excuse me. The student over there!
Wait a minute, my shoe!
Wait a minute!
♫ I'll try forgetting you tomorrow ♫
♫ Just be happy, that's all I need ♫
♫ Even if it's just for today ♫
[Song Shi On | Chu Young Woo]
[Jin Hong Seok | Won Hyung Hoon]
[You Make Me Dance]
[Three Years Later]
[Episode 1]
[Chachacha Capital]
Thank you for everything you've done for me so far.
[Resignation Letter]
You should've given me a heads-up at least. This does put me in a bit of an awkward situation.
Mr. Jin Hong Seok, do you even have a plan for what you're going to do after you've quit?
Manager Jin, that hand of yours looks the prettiest to me when you're counting money.
[CEO Cha Soo Ryeon]
Don't waste time on foolish dreams. Be satisfied with your reality.
That's not why I'm resigning.
I can trust you on that, right?
You should take care of this one before you go.
His debt isn't that huge, but he can be cumbersome.
I think it will be enough to just set the mood for him.
Young people these days have no manners.
They simply don't know how to give and take.
[Personal Information]
[Song Shi On. Resident Registration Number: 010209-3136229]
Oh no!
Hurry! Hurry!
Mom, have a nice day.
Happy...
[My Birthday. February 9th]
...day.
Get out of my way.
What did you run for?
You're here.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Turn around, kick,
turn.
And up,
Kick.
Turn.
And flip over.
Stop it!
Song Shi On, you can't keep doing this.
What?
Senior, what do you mean by that?
I don't want to go out of my way to help you anymore.
- Jung Hoon...
- You've been insincere for a while.
Only one person is going to get the lead role in the coming audition.
Just one. I don't want to waste my energy anymore. From now on, you are on your own.
I just like dancing with you, Senior.
Besides, you said so yourself, that we'd be friendly rivals—
You're so naive.
Also, your dance...
is lacking a story.
It feels quite nice to come to a university after so long.
Did you graduate college, General Manager?
I haven't. What about you, Team Leader?
Me neither. I only went up till middle school.
Gosh, it feels nice!
Aren't you cold?
Not really. I get hot quite easily.
I'll go ask where the Dance Department is.
Hey, there, student! Can you tell me where the Dance Department is?
It's right there. That building.
- The blue one?
- Yes.
[(Advertisement) Dear member of "Hey, you too," we have a special sale for you on your birthday.]
Everyone around me always leaves me.
[Happy Birthday Song Shi On! Sale on air purifiers, water purifiers and bidets.]
[Happy Birthday Song Shi On! Here's a free beverage coupon from Byeol Cafe for you to celebrate!]
[Messages]
Who are you?
It's him, right?
My, he's quite good-looking!
I'll sing a song especially for you.
♪ Hide well, or I might see your hair ♪
(T/N: It's a song sung by children when they play hide and seek)
♪ Don't hide in the flower garden. You'll step on the young flowers ♪
♪ You'll step on the lettuce seeds... Wait, lettuce in the flower garden? ♪
Hey, you!
Why are you so fast?
I'll catch you.
Wait.
Stop! Oh, wow.
Do you work out or something?
Can't you let me go just this once?
If you've borrowed money,
you gotta return it, kid—
Team Leader?
Manager, what are you doing just standing around?
I'll take care of it from now on.
You've worked hard today.
Ah, he's way too fast.
What an interesting birthday I'm having.
Mr. Jin Hong Seok?
I'm not Jin Hong Seok.
Is that so? That can't be, though. I'm sure you're Jin Hong Seok.
M-My name is Song Shi On.
I think you've got the wrong person.
Hello, Customer Song Shi On.
I'm Manager Jin Hong Seok, at Chachacha Capital.
[You Make Me Dance]
♫ Your tone was a little different than usual ♫
♫ I feel like we're breaking up ♫
♫ Can we please just move on for now ♫