=Dominion and Devotion=
=Episode 15=
Master Zhuo puts a lot
in his private treasury.
You're plotting behind his back.
If Master Zhuo discovers it,
he will definitely kill you.
Master Pei,
please show some respect.
I also wish this matter was my plan.
If it succeeds,
it'll relieve the bitterness
in my heart.
However,
Master Zhuo's private treasury
must be heavily guarded.
I assume it's safe and sound now.
Indeed, it is unharmed.
But the rumors about the treasury
have spread across the world.
The purpose behind this
is not hard to guess.
Since it is a secret treasury,
it will no longer be safe,
if the secret is exposed.
It can only be moved.
And during the transfer,
accidents are unavoidable.
Am I right?
I see.
Though even during the transfer,
the treasury is still hard to plunder.
Why?
Since it's a private treasury,
it's guarded by private soldiers.
If it is to be moved,
Master Pei, think about it.
Due to its importance,
if Master Zhuo
deploys Huting Army to escort it,
who'd dare to attack then?
It'd be going
against the entire Great Ning.
I'm glad Your Majesty knows.
Don't act rashly
to seek self-destruction.
I wouldn't dare.
After all, I only have my life left now.
Master Pei, as you know,
I
cherish life.
That's true.
Master Pei, please halt.
I'm wondering,
for such an important task,
who the person in charge of escorting
would be.
(But this time,)
I don't trust anyone else.
Why don't you personally
lead Huting Army to escort?
How about it?
You're such a sweet talker.
Just say you don't trust me.
After all, within this capital city,
the only force
that can rival Huting Army
is your Yilin Army.
My action
is merely for precaution,
in case your men
also covet the small fortune of mine.
You are joking.
Yilin Army's duty
is to protect the imperial city.
It would never do despicable things
like robbing private property.
Alright.
Then it's decided.
You will
personally escort
the transfer of my private treasury.
Of course, it's me.
But this matter is of great importance.
So I won't hold back.
Otherwise,
it will implicate me.
Then I wish you all the best
and a safe return.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
If it's you,
it will be easier to handle.
(The auspicious hour has come.)
(The universe revolves,)
(and Yin and Yang harmonize).
(This is the prime time for the ritual.)
(Your Majesty, please move
to the Fasting Palace)
(and worship reverently)
(to pray for the country's peace
and people's safety.)
Master Pei.
It's been two days.
Has His Majesty eaten?
No.
His Majesty's pious heart
is witnessed by heaven.
At midnight,
secretly get him some food.
Being so pious,
he seems suspicious.
I will test him for Master Zhuo.
Understood.
Wait.
If he won't eat,
force him if necessary.
Master Pei,
why is that?
It has its own meaning.
(Zi, Chou, Yin, Mao, Chen, Si,
Wu, Wei, Shen, You, Xu, Hai)
(The emperor is quite devout.)
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Please eat.
No one will know.
It has its own meaning.
Eat up.
No one will know.
(Is it you?)
"It has its own meaning"?
Fortunately, His Majesty ate it.
Me forcing His Majesty to eat?
Even if Master Pei is not afraid,
I'd be scared to death.
(Fasting Palace)
(It has been almost three days.)
(Why is there no movement?)
(If there truly are deities above,)
(I beg you for a favorable outcome)
(and bless us to eradicate
the country's enemy soon.)
Finally, there is movement.
Who is it?
By Master Zhuo's order,
I've come
to collect the disaster relief money.
Falsely claiming
the order of Master Zhuo,
you deserve to die.
Master Pei,
everything I said is the truth.
Just take a look.
Buddies,
get them if you want to live.
With this money,
we will have a chance to live.
The relief money is all here.
Whoever grabs it first, it's theirs.
Why are there so many people?
Buddies,
it's real fortune!
Hurry up!
I want to see who dares.
Why are they refugees?
Master Pei,
they are all unarmed refugees.
Should we kill them all?
All Huting soldiers, heed my order!
Stop now!
Master Pei,
Master Zhuo will definitely blame us.
What should we do now?
I see...
(Fasting Palace)
Your Majesty,
the praying is complete.
(Losing years of accumulated wealth,)
(Master Zhuo must
have been greatly weakened.)
(At this moment,)
(he's probably raging fiercely.)
Farewell, Your Majesty.
We'll take Your Majesty
back to the palace.
Who said I want to return to the palace?
They are not at fault.
Although soldiers act by order,
they should not act
against unarmed civilians.
Also, I ordered them not to fight back.
If you must punish,
punish me alone.
I'm disciplining my own Huting Army.
It's not your place to intervene.
That's the wealth I have painstakingly
accumulated over 20 years.
How could you let refugees plunder it?
Today, I'll kill whoever
I want to kill.
No one can stop me.
Why are you so angry, Master Zhuo?
Why are you here?
I
just finished praying for you.
I heard you were here,
so I came uninvited.
I deeply appreciate
Your Majesty's concern.
Why do you punish these soldiers?
The gold and silver for the gold statue
were stolen due to their malpractice.
They should be punished.
What?
But
I did not use the Tiger Tally.
Whose orders
were these Huting soldiers following?
So it was you who gave the orders.
Then it's not a problem.
However,
privately mobilizing Huting Army
is against the rules.
If you make a scene further,
news of it
will likely harm your reputation.
Step aside.
Forgive me, Master Zhuo.
I am the monarch of this country.
Now my innocent subjects are punished.
I
cannot step aside.
I am going to kill today.
No one can stop me.
I hope this slash
can ease your anger.
Fetch the imperial physician.
Master Zhuo,
I'm doing this for your sake.
I don't intend to disobey you.
Master Zhuo,
(People's Letter)
refugees gathering outside the palace
sent a People's Letter.
What People's Letter?
They want to thank you
for the relief money you donated.
I see.
I feel deeply ashamed.
I am narrow-minded
and misunderstood you.
I never thought
that you'd have such a caring heart
for the people.
You gave away
all your wealth for refugees,
relieving the capital's predicament.
When our national power is stronger,
I'll definitely
restart building the gold statue
for you.
I hope that can ease your anger.
Take care, Master Zhuo.
♪Candle lights the halls
through springs and autumns♪
♪Love and hate
are written in a few strokes♪
Refugees will remember
the kindness of you all.
I'll have someone
deliver medicine later.
Thank you all.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
♪Unending♪
♪Heaven falls♪
♪No concern for cause and effect♪
♪On the throne♪
♪Is it a shackle♪
♪Locking you and me up♪
♪Candle lights the halls
through springs and autumns♪
♪Love and hate
are written in a few strokes♪
♪Imperishable♪
♪Bloodstained vows
with a touch of tenderness♪
♪Fate is written by the universe♪
♪Unending♪
♪Heaven falls♪
♪No concern for cause and effect♪
♪On the throne♪
♪Is it a shackle♪
♪Locking you and me up♪
♪Break through the wind and clouds♪
♪A dream lasts a lifetime.
The world has changed♪
♪One step forward,
gaze back at the youth♪
♪At a glance,
all beings bow their heads♪
♪I'm in the midst of chaos♪
♪At the end of the night♪
♪Having the loneliest dream
in this world♪
♪Move on♪
♪Don't look back♪