She's the wrong one.
I thought you were giving that drink to Go Yoo Na.
You think I knew?
I had no idea Go Yoo Na wouldn't come and someone else would drink it instead.
So... will you do it to her instead of Go Yoo Na?
Are you crazy? She's an attorney!
She's totally different from someone like Go Yoo Na.
She might not be able to tell anyone because she's embarrassed.
Is that so?
I don't know, I don't know.
Each of these girls came over and harassed me.
My head is about to explode.
I'll take a nap inside and think about it later.
Keep an eye on her, okay?
What a coward.
What? Did she run away?
Hey, bastard! She ran away!
H-Help me.
This is driving me crazy.
What should I do? What should I do?
I...
I need to stop the bleeding.
Give me a towel.
Yes, let's do this.
You drugged me without me knowing, and you drugged her while I was asleep.
And you tried to rape her.
- What?
- I didn't do anything wrong.
I'm sure people would believe me.
You're a scumbag, but I'm the assemblyman's son.
Are you... done talking?
Why are you looking at me like that? Huh?
Hey!
Bastard!
You bastard...
Hey...
Move anywhere.
I'll come running to you immediately.
I'll tell you why I need the mask.
Come to my hotel room.
The mask I gave you.
Where are you keeping it?
Why do you want to know that?
I gave you that mask.
I have the right to know that much.
What about the mask?
By chance... Song Je Hyeok?
The call is not going through. You'll be connected to voicemail.
After the beep...
Rest a bit.
Please...
Please stay with me just for a night.
The door is opening.
The door is closing.
I tried to stop Leo, but he went to work again.
He went to Room No. 918 at Grand Kangbo Hotel.
What are you doing here, Je Hyeok?
You're keeping this from Yu Jeong, too?
What kind of situation is this?
Why are you here instead of Leo?
I asked Mr. Jung.
I asked him to provide us with a space, so I can talk to you privately.
With me? Privately?
What do you need to talk to your wife's friend privately in a hotel room about?
Give me... the card to beat Do Jae Yi.
I'm not sure.
I still don't have the assurance that you'll become the Tongju mayor yet.
Hae Mi, you must be having a hard time since the hanok hotel is no longer happening, right?
Yes.
If the hanok hotel is no longer happening,
Yeongun needs to give us the 10 billion won (~$7.4 million) we donated, too.
But they won't do that, either.
I know that you're in a very tough spot,
but please don't rush my Yu Jeong so much.
Please trust me and give us some time.
I'll make sure to take care of it somehow.
I know that you're a good husband, but I have a bigger fish to fry.
I wonder... if this would help with your stress.
Sometimes I stop by when I feel stressed, too.
It's completely confidential.
You can trust them.
I'll get going now.
It would look weird if we left the hotel together.
"Ice Party"?
By chance...
Ye Ji is staying in the backyard at this hour?
A mask?
Guys, you can do this well, right?
Yes!
Ahjussi, I'm Lee Yeon Ah, who was in the car accident the other day.
Could I talk to you for a bit?
Can I come in?
What? You're not even ready yet.
You haven't even changed.
Yeon Ah, the Angels are here!
I'll be out in a minute.
Okay, come out when you're ready.
The mask is the ticket?
What do they do inside wearing that?
Noona! I'm home!
Noona?
Where did she go with all the lights on?
You should've come a little sooner.
You would've seen something fun, then.
I came because I wanted to confirm something.
Why do you need that mask?
Are you back on Song Je Hyeok's side?
Gi Yoon Chul asked for it.
He said he'll make sure I'm no longer wanted if I give it to him.
Gi Yoon Chul? Why does he need that mask?
He said he needed a leash.
A leash to twist around Song Je Hyeok's neck.
Their relationship soured that much?
But you never thought about discussing that with me?
You're the one who betrayed me first.
I... saw you with Yu Jeong.
Your friendship brought me to tears.
You don't trust me.
You lied that the mask was at Kang Hoo's restaurant.
Is that why you brought Kang Hoo to the hotel?
Don't you think you're too childish?
I know I'm childish,
but I wanted you to feel it, just for a moment.
What it feels like to get something precious taken from you.
How painful and miserable it is,
and how difficult and heartbreaking.
I'm sorry.
I should've moved quickly for your daughter, at least.
I'm sorry, too.
You didn't do anything wrong.
But I feel so impatient because of Na Na.
Go Yoo Na. I need you.
You're the only one who knows who he is exactly.
I honestly... need you, too.
I'm scared
that I won't get to see Na Na again.
Go Yoo Na.
Yoo Na.
Let's start trusting each other and do this together.
Please?
You can do that, right?
Right, I...
I am free now.
Gi Yoon Chul canceled my fugitive status.
I'll try pursuing Je Hyeok more actively from now on,
so he can't hide in either a shadow or a bright spot.
By the way, how come you won't ask me?
Aren't you curious about Kang Hoo and me?
There's no way something could've happened, right?
Kang Hoo, I think I'll throw up.
I'm sorry,
but could you get me some ice at the ice room near the stairway?
Get some rest.
Kang Hoo.
Thank you.
What are you thinking so intensively about?
It's nothing. What is it?
You remember we have a magazine photoshoot this afternoon, right?
Please prepare for it.
Also, what Na Na wore last time, how shall I say it...
It was a bit too princessy, maybe?
She's a girl, but I prefer a healthy and strong image.
I know I can't avoid it,
but exposing Na Na for the campaign is a bit...
She might get stressed out.
It's something Do Jae Yi doesn't have.
A perfect family.
Well, do you have to leave right away?
Yes, I'm meeting with the party representative.
Right, you called me yesterday, right? I'm sorry.
We couldn't even talk because I came home so late.
So, what is it?
Do you need to tell me something?
No.
I'll tell you when I'm more certain about it.
See you later.
Why isn't she back yet?
Noona!
When did you come home? I was worried.
Should we take a bath together like we used to?
Noona!
Noona, what's wrong?
What are you doing?
Did you do it? I asked if you did it again!
Do Jae Yi, Go Yoo Na, Ju Yu Jeong, and...
Go Yoo Na, Ju Yu Jeong, and...
you're the only one who's left, Hae Mi.
Noona! Pull yourself together!
Pull yourself together!
Where did you go last night?
What happened with whom?
Leo, we...
should give up now.
What?
We were a customer and a host.
I already could see the end.
We dragged it out for too long already.
I know you're not in the right mind now,
but how could you say we're a customer and a host─
It's not because of the drug.
I mean it.
Let's break up. Please?
I beg you.
Noona, this still isn't right.
Leave.
Leave!
Get out of my sight!
- Please leave!
- Noona!
Noona!
Are you crazy?
Leave.
I beg you, please?
Please leave!
I don't want you to
see me looking hideous like this.
Please leave!
I'll leave, but... let me say this one thing.
I'm sorry.
I promised to help you quit, but I couldn't.
Call me if you need me anytime.
I'll be waiting.
Cha Leo.
According to Ace Bar's internal record,
Hae Mi's husband is the person in charge, not Mr. Jung.
Leo is definitely related to Ace Bar.
But how could he suddenly be the person in charge?
I think they're trying to make Leo take all the blame if something goes wrong.
Because Ace Bar is also under his thumb.
Attorney Do, did you see the polls that came out today?
He's running ahead of you in the polls for the first time.
I think the interview he gave during Assemblyman Gi's event
left a good impression on the voters.
I need to make sure to ruin his relationship with Gi Yoon Chul this time.
Please find out the places Gi Yoon Chul goes to.
How about we swap this photo for Do Jae Yi's ledger?
Do Jae Yi, Go Yoo Na, Ju Yu Jeon, and...
you're the only one who's left, Hae Mi.
Then, that was...
I told you last time, right?
When the Angels are here,
can you possess anything but the badge I gave you or not?
No!
That's correct. You can't!
You can't put anything else on you but the badge I gave you.
- Okay?
- Okay!
Okay, let's go, Princesses!
Hey, Ye Ji.
What's that on you?
Yes.
The Princes are next.
What's up, Hae Mi?
You sent me this, and you're asking what?
"What's up?"
Was it your goal to get Jae Yi's weakness from me?
Gosh, how disappointing.
I did that for you, Hae Mi.
They say nothing is more healing than giving drugs to an addict.
Does Yu Jeong know what kind of person you are?
A lot of people don't know what kind of person you are, either.
Well, like the chairman of Mariela Hotel?
Or your mother?
What?
So give me Do Jae Yi's ledger as soon as possible.
Otherwise, something unbelievably stressful that
even drugs can't handle will be waiting for you.
Hey, Song Je Hyeok!
You asshole!
Leo?
Leo!
By the way, why did you say "Leo"?
Does he ring the doorbell?
Why are you here? You didn't even call.
I went to the hotel because I had a surprise for you,
but they said you're on vacation.
That's why I came here right away.
You have another surprise for me? Even bigger than this?
What's wrong?
Did you and Leo...
Leo moved out.
I mean, I kicked him out.
How seriously did you fight that you kicked him out?
I don't want to say this since you're upset,
but I tried to stop you when you said you would marry Leo.
Someone with a job like that is rarely trustworthy.
"Someone with a job like that"?
How about Je Hyeok? How trustworthy is your husband?
Apparently, there's a phrase they use in gambling.
The one who wonders who the pushover in the game
is actually the pushover.
What are you talking about?
You're that pushover!
You think you're so classy and smart, but you get fooled more than anyone.
You're a fool, an idiot, and a pushover!
Hey.
Yoon Hae Mi, are you crazy?
Yu Jeong.
I won't tell you anything about your husband.
This is the last nice thing... I can do for you.
Bye now.
Jae Yi!
You should've come in.
Why were you hovering in front of the door?
I'm not hungry. I had blood sausage soup.
Eat just a little.
Right, you called me yesterday?
I was totally out of it yesterday because of Yoo Na.
- Yoo Na?
- She was here yesterday.
She asked me to pick up medicine, but she got so drunk while I was gone.
I had to take her to the hotel.
I see.
That's it. Aren't you curious about it?
Well, it's possible to take a drunk woman home.
Is the broth kind of bland?
I put ribs and chicken stock in it,
so I didn't add the soup mix.
What kind of ramyeon doesn't have soup mix in them?
No wonder. That's why it was kind of bland.
You should watch your health. You eat ramyeon all the time.
Thank you for taking care of me.
Jae Yi.
To be honest─
Kang Hoo Hyung!
Hyung! Are you in there?
You were in here.
I got kicked out,
but I have nowhere to go.
Since I married Noona Hae Mi,
I cut off ties with everyone.
Did you have a fight with Hae Mi?
Well...
That's what married couples do.
By chance, did she find out that you were working at Ace Bar?
Excuse me?
How did you know?
I'm running ahead of Do Jae Yi.
I am very happy about it, too!
If you help me out this time, I will never forget it.
Of course!
I'll see you tomorrow, CEO.
Thank you!
I need to talk to you.
Did something happen between you and Hae Mi?
Between Hae Mi and me?
Hae Mi said she was doing me a favor by not telling me about you.
What does that mean, anyway?
She has a secret, too.
But she told you my secret?
It's not even a secret.
Everyone has a history.
What do you mean "history"?
I used to work at Ace Bar.
I needed money to go to the US.
B-By Ace Bar...
You mean the kind of job Leo did?
What do you mean "that kind of job"?
Are you also the type of person who ranks people based on their occupation?
But...
But hiding something like that from me─
How about you? Aren't you hiding anything from me?
I don't get women.
You never know what kind of men they dated with elegant and pretty faces of theirs.
Wh-What men?
I won't say it with my own mouth.
That's my consideration for you.
Is it true that you're the person in charge at Ace Bar?
In charge of running the business?
A person in charge?
I just manage the VVIP customers.
I'm only doing that because Mr. Jung threatened me.
- Threatened?
- Yes.
Mr. Jung told me that if I don't do what he says,
he'll sell drugs to Noona Hae Mi.
He dragged you into the club because of Hae Mi.
Song Je Hyeok, that bastard is playing all four of us.
Song Je Hyeok is...
Noona Yu Jeong's husband?
Yes, for the customers you manage...
The real person in charge of the secret club is Song Je Hyeok.
What?
How could that be possible?
I was not going to tell Hae Mi and Yu Jeong
until I found out everything about him.
I thought that was a way to protect them.
But even they seem to be in danger now.
Have fun at the kindergarten, Na Na.
Ahjumma!
Wait here for a moment.
Seriously! Why did you come back this time?
You didn't answer my calls or texts.
You can't be doing this.
You know how much I paid you.
I'll give you the money back if you want me to.
But I'll be in trouble if I stay in touch with you!
Ms. Ju told me that if you came back one more time,
she would get a restraining order or something like that.
Forget about the money.
Let me hug Na Na for the last time.
That's okay, right?
Then, I don't need to give you the money back?
Na Na, just wait a bit.
We'll see each other again soon.
T-That's enough.
Let's go. Let's hurry.
You lifted your head up.
They say politics and golf have one thing in common.
You fail the moment you lift your head up.
Let's go for lunch.
We can discuss how to strike a ball with an impact, too.
Should we just have one drink?
You must be thirsty after exercising.
You must be having a headache because of Song Je Hyeok lately.
If you came here to tell me that he's the one who killed my son,
you're wasting your time.
I don't give up on people that easily.
You don't give up on people easily.
That's why you still want to keep him by putting a leash on him?
I heard you're trying to get the mask from Go Yoo Na.
But Song Je Hyeok told me that just because there's his blood on the mask,
it doesn't prove that he sexually assaulted me.
But if you still need that leash for him,
it means that the mask is still useful.
What did you try to do with it?
That's why I'm trying to find out the value of that mask myself.
You should come and join us.
Would you be okay?
To be honest, I'm not okay.
Thinking about that night, I still feel so scared and tormented even now.
But I've been waiting for 10 years.
For a day like this.
I was sexually assaulted.
- There was someone wearing a mask that night─
- Here we go again!
You're bringing up that mask again?
No one would believe me even though I told the truth 10 years ago.
Don't make the case get even bigger.
That would be better for you, too.
I'm no longer the same person anymore.
So, you should get stronger, so you can defend yourself.
Power is stronger than the law.
Now people pay attention to what I have to say.
Also, they will believe what I say to be true.
It's Do Jae Yi!
Thank you for coming, Assemblyman Gi.
Ms. Do invited me herself.
How could I not come?
You must've been surprised that I invited you.
I hope you believe what I have to say today.
Why do you think Jae Yi invited all of us?
I'm not sure.
I guess we're about to find out.
Hae Mi, you came.
You came, Hae Mi.
I'm waiting for you... to respond.
Respond to what?
I guess it's getting started.
Let's have a seat.
Yes.
Everyone, I want to greet you not as a candidate tonight but a different person.
Hello, I'm Attorney Do Jae Yi.
The reason I invited you here tonight is for the female victims of sexual assault.
Before we get to the main event, let's watch the video messages the victims sent me.
I almost died when I was date raped five years ago.
Thanks to Attorney Do, I was able to start a new life.
You saved my life. I love you.
Attorney Do even helped me learn how to do manicures.
I have a will to live now.
I'll never forget your kindness. Thank you.
I want you to become the mayor of Tongju and help even more victims.
I'll cheer you on.
I'm sure there are many more people who couldn't come forward.
That's why I'm thinking of being brave like them tonight.
To be honest, I'm a victim of sexual assault myself.
The reason I couldn't reveal it is
because no one believed me 10 years ago.
But I think things are different now.
In order to reveal the truth about that day, I've been collecting evidence.
I'm about to reveal who sexually assaulted me.
The culprit is...
This.
The man who wore this mask sexually assaulted me 10 years ago.
And I know the man who was behind that mask.
My gosh, what happened?
Isn't that Assemblyman Gi's son?
Are those the three of you in the video?
Is Assemblyman Gi's son the one who sexually assaulted you?
Are the three of you involved in Gi Do Shik's murder?
Are you the one who's in the video, Ms. Do?
Ms. Do! Ms. Do!
Do you have anything else to say?
Jae Yi!
I'll find out what's going on.
That's why I'm trying to find out the value of that mask myself.
You should come and join us.
You didn't believe me, but the public will believe in what I have to say.
Looks like you scored.
Jae Yi's event is all over the internet.
Are you here to thank me or something?
If you watch the video, you don't look like the culprit, at least.
It looks like it was one of the three.
I'm thankful that you tried, but I don't know what to say.
It was a wasted effort.
I'll reveal that I'm your ex-wife.
Having a murderer ex-wife will entirely ruin your image.
Looks like you're completely mistaken.
You married Jake, not Song Je Hyeok.
There's no record that Song Je Hyeok married you.
I knew you would deny it.
Do you know what this is?
It's the proof that Na Na's DNA matches mine.
You can't escape me as long as Na Na exists.
So give her to me,
and take off your disgusting mask and pay for your sin!
Either would be difficult.
I can't give you Na Na because she was already too exposed in the campaign.
And I already took off the disgusting mask.
I'm Song Je Hyeok all the way through.
I'll give you just one day to sort things out.
If you miss the deadline, you'll go back to being lowly Jake.
What's going on?
What the hell is...
How did a video like that...
Who would do this now?
By chance... could it be Yoo Na?
Do you think... I played that video?
You're suspicious of me again.
Can't you tell from the video? I wasn't there.
You were the ones who went to that room that day,
but I went to prison instead.
I had to go to the US, even after I got out.
Did you even imagine how unjust I felt?
I'm so sorry I didn't believe you 10 years ago.
But we were fooled, too.
You just found that out, too.
Yes.
You guys were fooled, too.
Let's not argue about the past.
What's important is that we're still in hell.
Because of that bastard.
Hold on.
I get that Yoo Na wasn't the culprit.
Who the hell is the culprit, then?
Jae Yi.
We're still in hell because of that bastard?
Who's that bastard?
Let me tell you.
That bastard Jae Yi was referring to... is Song Je Hyeok.
Your husband.
What?
That's why Jae Yi prepared this event, too.
Song Je Hyeok is the one who raped Jae Yi and killed Gi Do Shik!
She tried to expose him.
Are you crazy?
Stop.
Yu Jeong, I don't think it sounds totally ridiculous.
I mean, thinking about it, Yoo Na might be right.
Hae Mi, how could you do this now?
Your husband threatened me!
He wanted Jae Yi's ledger.
Your husband is a scary man.
Do you think he couldn't have murdered someone?
Yoon Hae Mi!
Seriously.
I admit it! He has flaws, too!
He said he used to work at a bar. But so what?
That's it.
He's not this horrible person you guys think he is!
Yu Jeong.
Yoo Na is right.
The one who raped me and killed Gi Do Shik is your husband, Song Je Hyeok.
Don't insult my husband!
If you insult him one more time,
I won't forgive you, even though you're my friends.
Hey, Ju Yu Jeong! I'm not done talking.
Let me finish!
Go away!
Yu Jeong, calm down and listen to me.
- I─
- Go away!
Hey! Ju Yu Jeong!
Don't touch me!
I'm pregnant.
But... according to you guys,
my baby's dad is a rapist and a murderer.
How am I supposed to believe that?
No matter what you guys say, I believe in Je Hyeok.
Because that'd be what's best for my child.
I don't think there's a choice anymore.
I think it's... over for us now.
Completely.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Baby, what kind of person is your dad?
What kind of man am I living with?
Ma'am! Ma'am! Ma'am!
Noona, it looked like something happened, according to the internet.
- Are you okay?
- Leo.
Help me.
I think I'm completely screwed!
What should I do?
Maybe it's all my fault.
I shouldn't have gotten involved in your lives to begin with.
There's only one way for us to survive.
Song Je Hyeok. Finding his weakness.
We still don't know who they are and what they do as a group.
But they all wear masks.
I'll become one of them today.
Wearing this mask.
When the lights go off at the orphanage that was filled with children's laughter,
their party gets started.
First of all, the party's symbol is masks.
In order to enter the party,
you have to go through a strict identification process.
If you go inside after you pass, an employee is waiting for you.
Come this way.
♫  Oh, now. Unmask  ♫
You came late.
♫  The curtain rises and will reveal everything  ♫
♫  Spotlight the truth  ♫
♫   beneath the door of closely guarded secrets  ♫
Have a pleasant time.
A deep and dark stairway is taking me to the secret party venue.
Could you please enter your membership number?
Checking identification one more time.
Leo, could you put me on the member list of the club?
I can't just add you,
But I can give you the number of a customer who is out of the country.
♫  Oh, Now. Unmask  ♫
♫  The curtain rises and will reveal everything  ♫
♫  Spotlight the truth  ♫
You've been confirmed.
♫  Beneath the door of closely guarded secrets  ♫
Ma'am. You need to turn in your phone.
You're not allowed to record anything inside.
♫  On top of the tightrope show, everything is blood stained  ♫
You've been confirmed.
Have a pleasant time.
The Angel's Club is unveiling in front of my eyes.
It's... a party of their own.
The space doesn't even have a security camera.
It's a completely secreti space where no recording is allowed.
They make the children work, but all they do is serving?
Why is this area being filmed by the security camera?
Hey, hey, because of you...
Go to hell,
along with the disgusting memories.
♫  The dark desire hidden behind a mask  ♫
♫  They're liars  ♫
♫  The truth is completely hidden behind a curtain  ♫
♫  My glamorous image  ♫
~ Preview ~
Is it true that the club's records were leaked?
The entire truth behind the club is on here.
Do you know how rashly your daughter has been behaving?
Too much of anything brings about trouble.
You know about cutting off the tail, right?
Make the members ditch Song Je Hyeok.
Do you know how I came all the way here?
Do you call yourself a human?
You show up now when she's in that condition?
Is that stupid election that important? She's about to die!
Na Na!
Hey, if I lose the election, I'm dead!
Everything comes after I win the election.
Mr. Jung, clone a phone for me.