You don't have to go.
Hae Mi was just joking.
I have to leave so you can have fun.
I'll stay put and wait for your call at home.
So have fun tonight.
Don't overdo it and join me in Suite 2401 at this hotel.
The door is opening.
The door is closing.
This is a secured area.
You can't just come in here.
Geez, look at all this money.
Thank you very much!
You came late.
We locked the door, thinking everyone was here.
Excuse me.
Why is this area being filmed by the security camera?
Hey. There isn't much happening today, right?
What's going on?
How will you get out?
There's no guarantee that you can get out without getting caught.
I'll create an emergency.
There's a method criminals use to subdue people.
It's venom from blowfish called "zombie power."
When you take it, you become paralyzed, lose the ability to speak,
and lose consciousness eventually.
Too much of it could be fatal,
but it's okay if you use a moderate amount.
Song Je Hyeok, why aren't you contacting me?
Do I really have to bring this to the media?
Be careful.
Be careful, be careful!
Na Na.
Na Na!
Na Na! Na Na!
Driver, please follow that ambulance.
Hurry! Hurry!
- What's going on?
- I'm not sure.
- What happened?
- He just had a drink.
- 9235038. Give me my phone.
- No, I can't.
No one can leave until the higher-ups allow it.
Give me my coat!
Someone passed out!
Don't just stand there. Give me my coat right now!
Run! Run! Run!
Do Jae Yi?
Block the entrance. So, no one can leave!
Got it!
Get in, Attorney Do!
Her temperature rose to 40°C, and she kept crying from a stomach ache since yesterday.
But today, she fainted.
I see.
There's a surgical mark on her stomach. By chance, did she─
She got Kasai portoenterostomy surgery.
She was diagnosed with congenital biliary atresia when she was 53 days old,
and she got the surgery when she was 65 days old.
She's only been receiving checkups regularly since she recovered well.
Did something go wrong by chance?
She has a bit of jaundice and hydrops. It must be cholangitis.
Are you the mother, by chance?
How did you know she was here?
I made it clear that I will report you if you show up again!
Report?
Please get her hospitalized first.
We can't leave her in the ER all night!
I have to discuss that with her guardian.
Please leave now if you have nothing to do with her─
I'm her mother!
Her biological mother,
so get her hospitalized now! Hurry!
Are you okay, Attorney Do?
Yes, I'm okay.
Kang Hoo.
Jae Yi, are you okay?
Kang Hoo, I found out what Song Je Hyeok does at the Angel's Club.
He was using children
to find the members' weaknesses, selling drugs, and engaging in prostitution, too.
I knew it.
So, should we report him right now?
It's no use since everyone has been evacuated now.
Instead, I'll send you the evidence I collected. Please check that for now.
Okay, come back safely.
Yeah, I will.
What the hell happened?
How did Do Jae Yi come in here?
I checked the list of names as usual, but...
I'm not sure.
Shut the place down.
The club will be closed for now.
We can't leave any trace, either.
Yes, sir.
The customer is not answering the phone.
Please try again later.
Is he ignoring me now?
By the way, where did Yu Jeong go?
While this is happening to her.
Don't ask me anything.
I don't know anything.
I'll find out myself, then.
Yu Jeong, Yoo Na is right.
The one who raped me and killed Gi Do Shik
is your husband, Song Je Hyeok.
Why? Is your stomach hurting again?
I told you not to think about anything and rest up.
You must relax no matter what.
Have you seen my phone, by chance?
It wasn't in my bag.
I'm not sure. Maybe someone took it when you fainted.
You shouldn't look at your phone, either.
Your guardian made me promise not to give you anything that could cause stress.
Take a rest.
I took a look at it.
It has everything, including the names of the members and transaction history.
But there's one thing I'm worried about.
It says the person in charge is Yu Jeong.
There isn't Song Je Hyeok's name anywhere.
That means even if I report them, he'll slip out, and only Yu Jeong would get hurt, right?
So I checked everything again, and all the transactions were made under her name, too.
Could she know about this club, too?
No, she would never do such a thing.
He disguised the club as an orphanage.
The members turned into sponsors, and the membership fees into donations.
While thoroughly using the children at the orphanage.
Then, why don't you meet with Yu Jeong?
She'd change her mind once she found out the truth, right?
No matter what you guys say, I believe in Je Hyeok.
Because that'd be what's best for my child.
It won't do anything.
Do you have pictures or videos of the club, by chance?
I didn't get to take any.
I had to hand in my phone upon entry, and there weren't even security cameras inside.
It looked like they were filming with a hidden camera attached to the kids,
but I couldn't acquire the footage.
How about we try to find an eyewitness?
They might testify who the real person in charge is, too.
Who would come to our side?
They're all under his thumb.
Well,
I know a child at the orphanage. Her name is Yeon Ah.
She's... traumatized by masks like you.
Traumatized by masks?
I'm not sure, but she might've experienced something similar to you.
So, Kang Hoo, please let me meet her.
I have to meet her.
The document is useless?
There's still a problem.
Do Jae Yi saw the club with her own eyes.
If the members find out, they won't forgive you.
Do you think I'm a fool?
Did you think I wouldn't know that?
Don't worry.
I'll completely destroy Do Jae Yi before the members find out.
Why aren't you contacting me, Hae Mi?
Are you testing my patience?
Hae Mi isn't like that.
That's how she became the vice president of that huge hotel.
I'm receiving another call.
You should come by sometime then.
You'll be treated generously.
Yes.
Yes, Minister Goo.
That's not true.
Yes, thank you for your concern.
Yes.
You're supposed to be the vice president of the best hotel in Korea. Why do you look like this?
Should we go shopping together?
Should we go sweep it all up?
Mom, I'm sorry.
What do you mean you're sorry?
Who hasn't made a mistake in the past?
A video like that will easily get buried by celebrity gossip!
Mom, that's not it.
Mom! Please help me!
Help me, Mom!
Is something else going on?
That bastard is strangling me using these pictures.
Mom, what should I do?
What am I supposed to do?
What do you mean, what should you do?
If he wants the ledger, we should give it to him.
It's that pretty Ahjumma!
Ahjumma, when did you come?
Na Na.
Are you okay?
Where's Mom, by the way?
Is she still sick?
Is your mom sick?
- It's Dad.
- Yes, Na Na.
Nanny told me everything.
Thank you for caring for Na Na.
Did it hurt a lot, Na Na?
It hurt just as much as last time.
My head and my stomach.
Last time? This wasn't the first time?
Let's talk outside.
You show up now when she's in that condition?
Do you call yourself a human?
Thanks to that, you got to spend all night with her.
Shouldn't you be thanking me instead?
Tell me.
How many times did this happen while I was gone?
A few times.
But she recovers quickly at the hospital. Don't worry.
How is that okay?
The doctor said the condition can't be cured completely!
She needs a liver transplant if it keeps causing problems!
I'm her legal guardian.
I decide whether she gets a liver transplant or not!
I can't take it anymore.
I'll take care of Na Na from now on.
Don't overreact.
If you keep bothering me, I'll send her overseas so you can never find her.
Thanks for everything.
Since the nanny's here, you can go home now.
I heard Yu Jeong is pregnant.
You don't need Na Na, then.
Na Na, needs care for the rest of her life.
I'll do everything. Please let me, yeah?
How many times did I tell you? Na Na has to be a part of the campaign!
Wait until the election ends!
Pick up the phone. Pick up the phone!
I apologize for making you worry regarding the controversial video of my wife.
But no matter what happened in the past, my wife is the love of my life.
So please blame me for everything and respect her dignity.
Thank you.
Gosh, I told you not to watch stuff like this.
I think you're too stubborn.
Can I get out of here now?
I'm worried if Na Na's okay and if she's going to kindergarten okay.
I can't reach the nanny, and you're too busy.
She hasn't been going to kindergarten.
I sent her on a trip with the nanny.
- Why?
- The reporters keep coming to her kindergarten,
and your video left quite an impact.
Stay here until things quiet down.
Being exposed to the media right now won't help you at all.
Do you know where my phone is, by chance?
Your phone?
I kept it safe.
Thank you.
I'll get going.
Are you leaving already?
Why? Do you need to tell me something?
Just because...
I'm not really sure what kind of person you are.
Are you suspicious of me about something?
I need to have faith, too.
Faith in you.
You're my wife, and I love you.
You're also my baby's mother.
Why didn't you tell me you're pregnant?
I missed the timing to mention it.
Just like how I gave you the baby as a gift,
I want you to give me a gift, too.
An absolute faith.
That way, I can protect you and our baby, too.
Take a rest.
I'll be back soon.
This is Yoo Na.
I know you're sick, but how could you leave Na Na alone like this?
Do you only care about your own baby?
I won't forgive you if something goes wrong with Na Na.
Understand?
She's pregnant.
- Pregnant?
- Yes.
But there's a chance she might miscarry.
She absolutely needs to relax for two weeks.
Yes, got it.
Now completely...
you became mine, Yu Jeong.
I can't congratulate you on your pregnancy,
but you should take care of yourself.
We need to meet up.
I still need to tell you about your husband.
Mr. Jung.
Clone a phone for me.
Yeon Ah, I'm the Ahjussi who almost got into an accident with you.
Could I talk to you for a moment?
Unni, could you come to the stationery store with me?
Okay, let's go together.
Let's go.
If he wants the ledger, we should give it to him.
We can't!
How could I hand over Jae Yi to a rapist and a murderer?
Then you shouldn't have fallen into his trap in the first place!
I think I'm going to go crazy!
We have no choice.
Give him the ledger.
Instead...
Where should I send the ledger?
Yeon Ah!
I came because I didn't get a reply from you.
Why did you reach out to me?
You must be Yeon Ah.
I asked him to because I wanted to see you.
I should introduce myself.
I'm Do Jae Yi.
I know.
Attorney Do Jae Yi.
You help the sexual assault victims.
Unni, what's sexual assault?
Well, I'm so honored that you recognize me.
So, I was wondering, could we talk somewhere for a second?
Is she your sister?
I noticed how much you care for her.
She's not my sister,
but the lengths of her legs didn't match since birth.
I felt bad that a small and precious child has difficulty walking.
So I basically raised her.
You must be like a mom to her.
I don't know how a mom would feel,
but I could do anything for her.
Anything.
You could do anything?
By chance, do you mean the kind of stuff they make you do at the orphanage?
Please leave if you expect me to testify or file a report.
I'll never do such a thing.
That's not what I expect from you.
I'm here to comfort you.
I... experienced the same thing as you.
Of course, you hesitate to testify.
Victims of sexual assault, like us, are different from other victims.
We're afraid that the shameful thing that happened to us would be revealed if we report.
We're trying to protect you.
There are many people who are way worse out there.
If I stay here, could you get leg surgery for Ye Ji?
Of course, we're a family.
Our sense of judgment weakens because of the anxiety
and we get to rely on bad people.
You just need to listen to me.
And the bad people take advantage of such victims' mental state.
So you can't report them and be on their side instead.
But they don't get punished even if you report them,
because they have so much power.
That's true. They say power is above the law.
But that power doesn't always mean having money and authority.
Being brave and not giving up.
Stuff like that can be power, too.
No matter how much you try, I can't report.
I'm not like you.
I have no courage, and I give up easily, too.
This is a secret.
I'm a coward, too.
It's been already 10 years, but whenever I think of that day,
I feel so scared and horrible. It even gives me chills.
But the reason why I don't give up on catching him is
because bad men don't do bad things just once.
And they don't just do it to one person, either.
If we stay silent, someone else might get hurt.
And it could be someone we love, too.
Yeon Ah, you don't have to do anything if it's too hard.
But you shouldn't give up on yourself.
That's what I want to tell you.
Make sure to contact me if anything happens.
Ye Ji, didn't they give you a pretty brooch at the stationery store?
The owner of the store said she gave you one.
Yes, she did.
Oh, yeah? You should keep that safe, okay?
If something happens to you, I'll run to you at once.
Do Jae Yi met with Yeon Ah.
Do Jae Yi met with Yeon Ah?
Ye Ji, too.
How could you manage the children so poorly?
What should I do? Should I trap them?
Will you trap them forever?
They start investigating if they miss just one day of school.
Do Jae Yi might've planted something with them.
Search their belongings. Everything, including the trash cans.
Yes.
You received a package.
Yes, give it to me.
This isn't Do Jae Yi's ledger.
This is Ace Bar's money laundering ledger.
I guess you really were an ace of the Ace Bar.
You made quite a bit of money.
How do you like this for a deal?
Hello, good day. This is the police station, right?
I wanted to make a report.
It's a bar called Ace Bar in the Gongguk district of Tongju City.
Ms. Do! You did this, didn't you?
- You stabbed him like this!
- I...
She looked very confused, but she denied killing Gi Do Shik.
I was sexually assaulted.
But she insisted that there was another man in that room
and she was sexually assaulted by him.
I searched the scene thoroughly,
but there was no trace of
a man other than Gi Do Shik in that hotel room that night.
But there wasn't enough evidence.
I heard they found a ton of ecstasy and condoms in the bathroom there.
Weren't you confused because you were high?
It was concluded that she was confused because she was drunk.
No one believed what Jae Yi had to say.
- Where have you been, anyway?
- Well, the thing is...
The employee at the security room happened to be gone during the incident
and he said the security cameras didn't work properly at the time.
It does seem like something's going on.
What's this?
Was there a camera?
There was a small camera and a charger in the room at the time,
but no memory card was found.
But this camera...
Hyung, it's been a while. How are things at the studio?
Could you have a look at the photos I sent?
Is that the correct charger for the camera in the photo?
This charger isn't compatible with that camera.
It's for a different model.
Thank you, Hyung.
Come to my restaurant soon. I'd like to see you.
Yes.
It means there were two cameras in that room.
Song Je Hyeok must've taken one.
But how about the other one?
How can you eat right now after making my son a rapist?
Well,
strictly speaking, I didn't turn your son into a rapist.
Song Je Hyeok is the rapist.
Tell me why you wanted to see me.
I heard the Angel's Club closed.
I don't know. I don't know anything about it.
You're playing ignorant, huh?
Then let me tell you what it is.
It's all on here.
What that club is, who goes there,
and what they do in there.
I'm curious if you're just a member or its body.
Or whether you're on Song Je Hyeok's side or not.
But it doesn't matter anyway.
What's certain is that Song Je Hyeok is already done.
If the members find out the file was leaked, they won't leave him alone.
You'd probably want to kill him first.
You know about cutting off the tail, right?
Make the members ditch Song Je Hyeok.
If so, you might be able to survive.
What do you mean the secret was leaked, sir?
That never happened.
You know how tight our security is.
There's no way you would get exposed─
Hello─ sir, sir─
How did the word get out anyway?
Tell me. What's the issue?
The VIP members of the club.
Some of them came here and made a fuss. They said they'd leave the club.
What was the reason?
Is it true
that the club's records were leaked?
What do we have to do for them if they leave?
Well...
"If the club's secret is exposed, we compensate double the amount of the membership fee."
Money is an issue, but wouldn't that put you in a bad position?
- If they flip the script out of anger─
- Hey.
Would that only hurt me?
Who's got the video of them partying with women while being high?
Tell the members to stay quiet.
I'll bury the leaked records, so it can't be exposed to the world.
Ms. Ju.
It's time to go to the ultrasound room.
Ultrasound?
It was difficult to see the baby in the earlier stage,
but you probably could see it today.
Hello? Yes, Ma'am.
Could you please come to the hospital?
How come you're eating meat all of a sudden?
I'm trying to get more energy.
I need to spurt at the last moment.
The last moment?
I suppose things are going well.
The members of the Angel's Club started berating Song Je Hyeok.
If they oust Song Je Hyeok, they will start fighting with each other.
When people are bound by a secret,
they become enemies the moment the secret gets revealed.
You think Song Je Hyeok would just sit and watch?
I'm sure he'd freak out.
But he can't do much when everyone turns their back on him.
But still, be careful.
He is capable of anything when he loses his temper.
Do you know how rashly your daughter has been behaving?
Answer me! I'm asking you a question!
Too much of anything brings about trouble.
- Pardon?
- You're trying to have too many things,
and you made too many enemies in the process.
I wanted you to become the mayor.
I wanted nothing more nor less.
Are you doing this now, too?
I'm so desperate right now because I'm trying to become mayor.
Do you know how I came all the way here?
I had to do all sorts of things.
Just wait and see.
I'll make sure to become mayor. And...
I'll create my kingdom in Tongju.
But if someone gets in my way, I won't just sit and watch.
Even if that might be your daughter.
What happened?
Why was Na Na sent to the ICU?
Her temperature won't drop, and some level went up.
Bilirubin level?
Yes, that thing! It went up, so they had to move her in a hurry.
She could go back to the general ward tomorrow since she is stabilized now, but...
But what?
Hurry up and tell me!
I think she needs a liver transplant.
Ask her dad about the details. He talked to the doctor on the phone.
Why do you keep calling me?
Song Je Hyeok, it's me.
Go Yoo Na?
Did you hear that Na Na needs a liver transplant?
Yes, I talked to the doctor over the phone.
But you're not doing anything? You're supposed to be her dad!
Do you want to hang up?
If you keep this up, I won't answer the nanny's phone, either.
I'll donate my liver.
Let's get the surgery done, okay?
How many times do I have to tell you? You don't qualify.
To donate your liver,
you must reveal the donor and beneficiary and the relationship.
But I don't want the world to know that you're my ex-wife!
Why don't you do it, then? You're her dad!
The election is less than a month away.
How could I have the time for it?
Also, if people find out I'm campaigning while my daughter is sick,
what would happen to my image?
Is that stupid election that important?
She's about to die!
Stupid election?
Hey, if I lose the election, I'm dead!
How could I care about anything else right now?
You...
You're really crazy.
Don't you care about Na Na because you have another baby now?
Whether it's a liver transplant or whatever,
everything comes after I win the election.
Now that it's come to this
all of this must be part of Na Na's fate.
Hey! Hey! Song Je Hyeok!
I asked you if that satisfies the deal.
Why won't you answer?
What? Are you happy about something?
No.
I'll explain it to you if things get cleared.
Okay, then.
Hold on.
I said a wide-mouthed glass is better for a full-bodied wine.
That way, the flavor comes out more.
Right.
I'll bring you a different glass, then.
You reached Cha Leo's phone.
I'm calling from Gongguk police station's narcotics division.
Why is the narcotics division calling him?
It's regarding Ace Bar.
Ah, is this not Cha Leo?
He's not here right now.
Could you please call later?
Excuse me for a second.
It was you, right?
The one who made the police go after Leo.
The police in Korea are so good at their job.
- Did they already contact him?
- Hey!
Do you want to die?
What are you trying to do right now?
You shouldn't be worrying about him right now.
I'm on my way to Mariela Hotel to see the chairman.
Why would you meet with the chairman?
You didn't give me Do Jae Yi's ledger.
So our deal must be over, right?
Stay right there.
I'll be right there.
Noona, where are you going?
Oh. There's an emergency situation at the hotel.
I'll be right back.
What are you doing here? Why would you meet with the chairman?
I told you earlier.
Our deal is over because you didn't give me Do Jae Yi's ledger.
What am I supposed to do?
The vice president started using drugs 10 years ago, but she hasn't quit yet.
I should tell him that.
You must've seen the ledger of Ace Bar I sent.
Do you think you'd be safe if I sent that to the police?
Ace Bar has nothing to do with me.
You said it yourself, the police were looking for Leo.
What does Leo have to do with Ace Bar?
I suppose you didn't know.
Leo is the person in charge at Ace Bar.
How do you feel about sending over the illegal activities of your husbands' business?
You bastard.
Leo went back there to save me from drugs.
But you blamed everything on innocent Leo?
Pick it up.
- You need that right now.
- Who do you think I am?
Should I take it back, then?
You bastard.
You're mocking me right now, aren't you?
I'm not the one who's mocking you.
Do you know who ruined your life using drugs?
Your lovely husband Cha Leo.
He says he loves you and he'll protect you.
Isn't that the greatest insult?
What are you talking about?
Leo is the one who introduced you to drugs.
Didn't you know?
Quit talking nonsense!
I started taking drugs because of Yoo Na, not Leo!
If that's what you really want.
Does your wife know, too?
About the kind of things you did?
You mean you'd tell her I'm the one who gave her drugs first secretly?
That's entirely up to you.
Then, when do you want me to start working?
So ditch Leo quickly and bring me Do Jae Yi's ledger.
If so, I'll postpone my meeting with the chairman for now.
This is your last chance.
This is the womb.
This is the ovum.
The size and the location of the baby are great.
The heartbeat is very stable, too.
Heartbeat?
I'll raise the volume for you.
That's... the baby's heartbeat, right?
It's very loud. The baby must be very healthy.
That should be enough, right?
Hold on a moment.
I want to hear it longer, Doctor.
Why is Ye Ji going there at night?
Jae Yi, it's me. It's been a while.
I found out what my husband was doing at the orphanage.
And I met with the children, too.
My husband is such a terrible person.
We should meet, Jae Yi. Please hear what I have to say.
The call is not going through. You'll be connected to the voicemail after the beep.
I got the brooch from Ye Ji.
Come to the location you're seeing right now.
I came here to confirm with my own eyes, too.
But I'd like you to come alone without telling anyone.
I don't feel confident about seeing anyone yet.
Okay, I'll meet you there.
♫  The dark desire hidden behind a mask  ♫
♫  They're liars  ♫
♫  The truth is completely hidden behind a curtain  ♫
♫  My glamorous image  ♫
~ Preview ~
Should I feel guilty for falling in love?
We loved each other.
I was scared.
I know it's too late to go back.
But I'll kill him, even though it might be late.
How could you do this? It was you, wasn't it?
So forget about that puppy and protect yourself.
A smart bitch can't beat a tough bitch, and a tough bitch can't beat a crazy bitch.
Oops?
I think I'll actually become a murderer this time.
I'll kill Song Je Hyeok.
What are you doing?
You're here, aren't you?
I'll complete the revenge.
You really are fearless, aren't you?
Song Je Hyeok, that bastard.
♫  On top of the tightrope show, everything is blood stained  ♫
♫  Ey yeah-yeah  ♫