♪Wandering around day and night♪
♪How many times have we passed by♪
♪Fate binds our lives together♪
♪Burning flames consume our past♪
♪How to break these binding chains♪
♪We decide our own fate♪
♪Who should I ask to end this plight♪
♪When cocoons break, we'll reunite♪
♪A sigh echoes in your memories♪
=Her Feast=
=Episode 14=
Sir.
Two bottles of Shaoxing wine.
Okay.
Coming.
I think you don't like Shaoxing wine.
Enjoy.
I didn't like it before,
but I like it now.
Can't I?
Take it.
Sure.
Cheers.
Pei Xun, I'm not drunk.
Put me down.
If you keep squirming,
I'll throw you into the restroom.
You wouldn't dare.
Try me.
Ever thought about hiring a driver?
The one who's always on call,
but also
cheers you up every day,
you can lean on if you're tired,
and you can
vent your anger if you're angry.
The one who can offer
whatever you want.
Where can I find such a guy?
You can have one if you want.
(If I can survive,)
(I won't let you go, Zhang Wange.)
(Everything is ready in the capital.)
(Action can start anytime.)
No.
He's good-looking.
No?
No.
He's got a nice figure,
can protect you,
maybe a rising star.
No.
What's wrong with you, Zhang Wange?
Why so picky about hiring a driver?
Actually, you do want something,
but just don't want me.
(The Capital)
(Tongrentang Pharmacy)
Senior Pei's here.
Hurry!
(Silk Shop, Tongrentang Pharmacy)
Dad.
Rest in peace.
Over a dozen girls
went missing this month.
(Interrogation Record)
Lu,
what's wrong with people nowadays?
Why so insane?
Now Sun is dead,
and we lost Meng's clues too.
With so many people,
they must find a hiding place.
Keep investigating.
Don't overlook any suspicious clue.
Yes.
By the way, Lu.
A tip just came from the capital.
What is it?
Pei Xun is dead.
How?
He's gone?
Yes.
The last bullet pierced his left chest.
And the best time for rescue
has now passed.
I'll publish the news tomorrow
that the capital was in turmoil,
and Pei Xun
died tragically in an accident.
You really
do things flawlessly.
But who sent you
that letter?
Any leads on the sender?
(Pei Xun discovers his identity.)
No leads at all.
The paper and envelope materials
are common.
The possible sources are too broad.
Maybe it's from someone with a grudge.
Let it go.
He's already dead.
Let bygones be bygones.
Actually, you should thank him
for warning you in time
about Pei Xun's murder plan.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't have escaped.
Seems like
Rong City has been
stirred up.
Grandpa.
You're back.
Your acquisition of Weina Jewels
went very well.
I'll monitor the progress.
To be honest,
you're more capable
than your eldest brother.
When he first joined Song Group,
he ruined two projects in a row.
But what could I do? He's my grandson.
I only let him reflect on his mistakes.
Though gaining power
isn't necessarily a good thing.
It breeds improper thoughts.
Now you're making such a scene.
Do you want to cancel the engagement
with the Zhou family?
Yes.
How generous you are.
Used such a destructive trick?
You and Zhou Nian
might not be meant for each other.
And we don't
necessarily need the Zhou family.
When I was in the capital
dining with Director Lin,
his daughter Lin Xin
mentioned you once.
Meet her when you're free.
Let my second brother do it.
He's going to the capital
for leg treatment anyway.
I think Lin Xin wouldn't look down on
a cripple.
Such a trivial matter
isn't worth your anger, Grandpa.
This is Song Group's
latest stock market trends.
You're bewitched by that woman!
Do you think controlling the group
makes you powerful?
Trying to secretly send
that woman away?
Do you think you'll succeed?
(Rong City Station)
(Rong City, Beizhou)
What?
The train ticket to the capital
has been altered.
How convenient to have wealth.
Make anyone vanish
whenever you wish.
Wange.
Having known you
for so long,
I advise you to leave Rong City.
Wherever you go,
you must thrive with your skills.
Is it Song Yanzhou or the Song family?
Zhang Wange.
Don't try to run.
If you run,
a mental incompetency verdict
will be issued,
and you'll be taken by force.
Don't even consider informing anyone.
Master Song has prepared everything.
This so-called kidnapping ensures
your financial security and freedom.
Every time after this,
will only be even worse.
So, where do you send her?
This vast world
is full of vistas to explore.
Let her go out
and see the world.
That'll cure her of grand ambitions.
You've accused the wrong person.
Targeting an unrelated girl
will shorten your lifespan.
You brat!
We pinned our hopes on you,
yet you're bewitched by a woman!
You used a bullet to
get your eldest brother killed!
Think we don't know about it?
Want to escape?
You owe this to the Song family!
You knew it all along?
Yes.
You secretly tampered
with the gun,
getting your eldest brother killed.
Had I known you'd betray
the family like this,
I'd have given the evidence
to the police.
Then do you know
that eldest brother
tried killing me thrice
to marry into the Zhou family?
So you knew it all along,
yet you let it happen
and allowed us
to hurt each other?
Is this the family bond you want?
The Song family
can have one heir.
To prevent divided authority,
I had no choice.
Then you shouldn't have let me be born!
Why not strangle me
in my cradle?
Yanzhou.
Who are you?
I've spent seven years cultivating you.
Think you're irreplaceable?
Think the Song family
can't function without you?
This man here is
Song Zhihang.
His education and upbringing
rival yours completely.
All he needs
is an opportunity and a title.
Grandpa.
The Song family has truly rotten
from the roots
under your control.
What are you waiting for?
Stop him!
Song Yanzhou.
Stop it now!
Do you want to see
that woman's corpse?
(Mr. Song.)
(Your harmonious family
must be blissful, right?)
(But that's not true.)
(Without family, I could imagine)
(and anticipate.)
(But now my family is here.)
(They're using me as a puppet
and draining me completely).
(They won't stop
until they've drained me.)
Stop.
Song Yanzhou.
Want to escape?
Everything you have now
is all given by the Song family.
Look at those
fighting for money and power.
But you were born
in a position others can't reach.
You do not appreciate it,
but betray us.
Can't even control a woman.
What a loser!
Mr. Song.
Master Song does everything
for your own good.
For my own good?
Break my legs,
give me crutches,
and then lecture me
that without him,
I can't even walk.
So I should be grateful?
At the train station,
did you let her escape on purpose?
I...
Go back to Master Song.
♪Watching the hour hand in slow motion♪
♪How ironic to think I was foolproof♪
♪Backing up intimacy as cold data♪
♪When you've deleted me from your heart♪
♪The cruelest distance♪
♪It's you in my memories♪
♪Walking towards tomorrow♪
♪Nostalgia is ongoing♪
♪Because we can't alter the ending♪
♪The most intimate distance♪
♪It's once done, now past♪
♪You're clearly in every breath I take♪
♪Yet drifting away♪