♪Wandering around day and night♪
♪How many times have we passed by♪
♪Fate binds our lives together♪
♪Burning flames consume our past♪
♪How to break these binding chains♪
♪We decide our own fate♪
♪Who should I ask to end this plight♪
♪When cocoons break, we'll reunite♪
♪A sigh echoes in your memories♪
=Her Feast=
Sir, this is for you.
Lu.
A letter.
A letter?
A little beggar delivered it.
(Wanle Club)
The missing people seems to be here.
This batch of girls
looks quite charming.
Before shipping them off,
why don't we three have some fun?
Sure.
As usual?
As usual.
Who are you?
The missing girls are here.
Escort them safely.
Yes.
Lu.
We found a female corpse
in the backyard.
And...
What?
She's naked.
Lu.
Lu! Lu, stop it!
We have to interrogate him.
If he's dead,
we can't explain to the chief.
What to explain?
During arrests,
injuries are normal.
=Episode 4=
Mr. Pei.
How about we play that old game?
Boring.
With a beauty here,
why would it be boring?
Didn't you say
women are like clothing?
Why cherish a piece of clothes?
Seriously?
How about this?
If I win this round,
have your girl
give me a kiss.
Consider it lending me some luck. Deal?
Dare not?
I reject.
Since your bet involves me,
I'll be the one betting with you.
You?
Do you know how?
Happen to know a bit.
Fine. Losers accept defeat.
If you lose,
don't cry
and refuse to kiss me.
Of course, if I lose,
I'm all yours.
Deal.
You really know how?
Zhang Yi grew up
playing billiard.
If I said I don't,
would you two end this game?
Just one round.
After you.
Are you fooling me around?
So, what do you want?
Money? Whatever.
Or I can
give you a kiss instead.
Since you lost,
how about barking like a dog?
Zhang Wange, are you insane?
Dare not?
Just barking like a dog.
You said losers accept defeat.
Zhang Wange.
You're taking it too seriously.
How about
you give him
a kiss?
You!
Don't try to hold justice
if you can't help him yourself.
You and Pei Xun
bet with me as collateral,
without even asking me.
I won't be your gaming chip.
Next time,
pick someone
who doesn't take it seriously.
It'll save you trouble.
Zhang Wange.
Don't be mad.
He was joking.
But I don't find this funny.
I can placate you,
but don't push your luck.
(The Pei family's downfall is coming.)
(Pei Xun, it's time for you to suffer.)
Wange.
Mr. Song's fiancée is here.
Prepare one more cup of coffee.
Okay.
Yanzhou.
Your fiancée is right in front of you.
How can you still focus on work?
Isn't your exhibition debut imminent?
Don't you go back and prepare?
I just want to spend more time with you.
Why are you so unromantic? Workaholic.
This is a workplace.
Yanzhou.
I heard you've invited
the renowned
Mr. Karen Pieno
in this jewelry design
project.
His design style
is always unique
and inspired.
I really admire him.
Yanzhou, you know.
I've always been
passionate about jewelry design.
I've even attempted
multiple independent creations.
How about letting me
take charge of
the design project
this time?
Okay?
The design concept isn't finalized yet,
but decisions require
careful consideration.
If you have draft designs,
you can submit them first.
I'll have the team review.
Why are you so rigid?
With our relationship,
can't you bend the rules for me?
Yanzhou.
Mr. Song.
Your meeting
with Mr. Gao of Weina Jewels
is scheduled for 10:00 PM tonight
at Lanhai Bay.
Don't try to hold justice
if you can't help him yourself.
You!
Did you study jewelry design?
Yes.
Join me for tonight's meeting.
Okay.
Miss Zhang.
Yanzhou barely ate
anything this morning.
Could you please
go to the café next door
to buy two cakes?
Thank you.
No need for formalities.
It's my duty.
Zhang Wange.
Have a chat.
Okay.
Go ahead.
What will it take for you to leave?
If I said
I want you to admit your plagiarism
and publicly apologize, would you dare?
Plagiarism?
So what?
Are you planning
to bring up the past again?
Or do you think
that joining Chenda
gives you power over me?
Zhang Wange.
You're being naive.
Right.
You're now Rong City's chief designer.
You have numerous creations,
and host many exhibitions.
What are you afraid of?
Does my
very presence
make you remember
you're a thief?
Shut up!
Zhang Wange.
Are you going to go against me?
I guarantee
you won't even know
how you'll end up.
(As expected,)
(evildoers will never feel remorse.)
Go against you?
I just want to do my job well
and assist Mr. Song in small matters.
If there's nothing else, Miss Zhou,
I'll take my leave.
You approach Yanzhou
to get back at me, right?
Miss Zhou, you got me wrong.
I've never thought to get back at you.
After all,
rotten fruits
will fall to the ground on their own.
It's a karma.
I don't need to do it myself.
(Zhang Wange!)
(The World)
(Chenda Jewels Banquet)
Miss Zhang,
this is my newly hired assistant,
Zhang Wange.
All upcoming business
will be managed by her.
Thank you.
Hope you'll
work well.
Miss Zhou.
(Zhang Wange.)
(I have plenty of tricks)
(to ruin your reputation again.)
Come here. Come on.
Chat with her.
Miss Zhang,
thank you in advance for...
Miss.
This is from that gentleman.
(Tang Qi)
Hello.
Mr. Song
seems to be out of wine.
Mr. Song.
To the success
of our collaboration.
(Zhou Nian.)
(The trap you carefully set)
(boosts my plan.)
Mr. Song, are you alright?
Tell Fang Cheng to call a doctor.
Alright.
Don't let anyone know.
Where's Yanzhou?
Wasn't he
with you?
Do you like it?
Why are you here?
Where's Zhang Wange?
She...
She was just there.
Where is she now?
Don't panic. I'll go look for her.
The drug I used is potent.
She can't go far.
(Yanzhou and Zhang Wange are missing.)
(Could it be...?)
Mr. Song, what's wrong?
What's wrong, Mr. Song?
Mr. Song, I'm not your fiancée.
I'm Zhang Wange.
Song...
(Zhou Nian,
you lit the torch in the maze)
(that showed me the shortcut.)
(How dare someone
bring this kind of thing here?)
He is Tang Qi.
He put the drug
in the wine.
Who's behind it?
It was...
Miss Zhou.
You'd handle it.
I am innocent!
It wasn't me!
Spare me!
I beg you, please!
I don't want to die!
(Chenda Capital)
Where's she?
She...
Wange submitted her resignation.
Mr. Song.
Zhang Wange.
Open the door!
I know you're inside.
Let's talk.
Mr. Song.
I've already resigned.
But I didn't approve it.
Thus, the resignation is invalid.
What do you want?
About last night,
I'm sorry.
Nothing happened between us last night.
I'll go to work.
I'm really curious
about your purpose
for coming to Chenda.
Whatever it is,
we're simply
using each other to get what we need.
(So she knew it all along.)
♪Watching the hour hand in slow motion♪
♪How ironic to think I was foolproof♪
♪Backing up intimacy as cold data♪
♪When you've deleted me from your heart♪
♪The cruelest distance♪
♪It's you in my memories♪
♪Walking towards tomorrow♪
♪Nostalgia is ongoing♪
♪Because we can't alter the ending♪
♪The most intimate distance♪
♪It's once done, now past♪
♪You're clearly in every breath I take♪
♪Yet drifting away♪