Episode 16
If Su Bai Yi enters the city,
we can only fight to the death in the Demon City.
Su Bai Yi is my wife's son.
I want to save her.
From now on,
our mission is no longer to take Su Bai Yi away.
We have to take this opportunity
to destroy the Demon City.
Since you are willing to retreat with me,
please be prepared.
This is a battle of life and death.
I'll break the formation.
Let me do it.
If we don't have a ship to lend a sword,
we can't get in the wind.
If we want to win,
we have to build a bridge.
Brother.
The Xie family is willing to be the queen.
If the god is not here,
you can't protect them.
We have to try.
What if I'm here?
You want to leave?
I'll take care of you.
You are good.
Can you fight well?
Are you afraid of shame
for all the tricks?
You are right.
The advantage of formation is not in the majority.
It's time to break the formation.
I'll follow the order of the chief.
Brother.
Let's fight!
The formation of deadly cloth
olinates!
You...
This...
Ying Qingcheng, come out!
Wasn't it me you were looking for?
Why did you rush to my senior sister?
Do you care about your senior sister so much?
You want to threaten me with your senior sister?
Your senior sister was badly injured by my kick.
If you keep delaying it,
I'm afraid you'll have to stay in the sickbed for the rest of your life.
What do you mean?
I know how to teach your senior sister.
Your master can also go down the mountain.
What about the conditions?
Xiaoqian.
What is it with you?
Senior sister,
it's all over now,
what are you going to do?
Senior sister.
I played a went to discover a treasure,
The last one is the New Law,
called the Dream.
Everyone knows
the Book of Immortals is the best martial art.
But they don't know
the Dream New Law
can restore people's meridians.
No matter how serious the injury is,
it can be repaired.
Back then, your second brother, Nan Yulou,
broke into Shanglin Heavenly Palace alone.
He was injured.
The injury in his body has been
incurable for so many years.
What a pity.
The Dream New Law
was taken away by my master.
That's right.
The Dream New Law
was taken away by my master.
If I'm not wrong,
your master, the old fox,
should have
put the Dream New Law
in your head.
He can only learn it from you.
You guessed it.
Then why did you
send your substitute to kill me?
What did you say?
I just asked him
to bring you here.
I see.
I'm afraid you have a different purpose.
You want that immortal book, too, right?
It's really the dark one.
Since you've killed him,
let's not talk about him.
You give me
the Dream New Law here.
Then I'll cure your senior
and send you down the mountain.
The new law can't be learned
in a day or two.
Didn't you just say
my senior's injury can't be removed?
Back then, I was the first
to be ranked the best
with a good understanding.
I've never been able to
master a martial art for more than three days.
Okay, I promise you.
Senior.
Jingwu, you despicable man.
He...
He's the one who killed the chief.
Why?
Because he said he wanted to
stir up trouble.
Then...
I'm the deputy of the criminal court.
I was ordered to punish him
for betraying the Holy Spirit Palace.
I... I didn't do anything wrong.
Did you do anything wrong?
Are you sure you can explain it
to my senior and your brother?
You're arrogant.
You think I'm afraid of you?
Beat him.
You're not a good subject.
How dare you hit your senior?
Let's go together.
Arrest him.
Go.
Don't worry.
Leave the rest to me.
I believe you.
The six-stripe formation is hard to break.
Even the blood dance is like this.
I'm still behind you.
I've had many chances
to stop all this from happening.
But I still didn't do anything.
So,
the Holy Spirit Palace
has become what it is now.
What do you mean?
Since I made a choice today,
then some things
should be changed because of me.
I'm sorry.
Senior, don't.
When I was climbing the South Fishing Tower,
he said to me,
he said,
there's no destiny.
I'm a star master.
I don't believe it.
But today,
I want to try.
It's not up to me to
achieve one more thing.
I don't know what I will do
when I have enough time.
Why don't you ask me
if there is still a chance?
There is a chance.
If there's a chance,
But I need to pay for my life.
Stop running.
plate pass
My friend.
Bracelet
I suddenly have a bad feeling.
The Lin Tian Palace is going to be in chaos soon.
The Jianghu is also going to be in chaos.
That's why I'm worried about those young people playing chess with me.
The first snow of the Dragon Mountain should have fallen.
The snow in there is too far away from us.
I'm more concerned about the people who are playing chess with me.
It's the battle now.
Mr. Long, although it's already this moment,
I still want to say
that it's not worth it for the present Shanglin Tian Palace.
It's not worth it.
It's just whether I regret it or not.
Then do you regret it now?
I've tried my best.
You died in the battle.
Qingming Garden lost its people.
The future Shanglin Tian Palace,
Qingming Garden will not be able to live up to glory.
Qingming Garden has never had glory.
We are all people living in darkness.
He fell into the dark in this way.
He must have some regrets.
I left an order before I came.
If I die,
Qingming Garden will be disbanded.
Why?
Qingming Garden's era
will end today.
In Mr. Long's heart,
there is a will.
There is no will.
I just want to kill you.
Mr. Long is dead.
Bai Qi Le,
you are the next one.
Mr. Long,
Mr. Long is dead.
vegetable
The
North China Sea
and the Far East 많이
We won
ouselves experienced gr об
Our chess chess just moved
It seems that two 50-50
must not be mixed
I'm sorry.