The sky is clear, the wind is strong, the clouds are high, the sky is clear, the clouds are high
The clouds are high, the clouds are high, the clouds are high
The sky is clear, the clouds are high, the clouds are high
The Clouds of Dazhen
Episode 1
How is your training going?
It's going well.
That's good.
I heard you say last time that the second most powerful Xue Shen Guan,
what kind of person is he?
Brother, don't mess around.
Xue Shen Guan broke into Shang Ling's palace
because Tian Wu Bao made him the second most powerful
but Ning Qing Cheng was the first most powerful.
Xue Shen Guan was not convinced and wanted to fight Ning Qing Cheng.
But he was stopped before the Star Academy.
He left after playing a game with the Star Academy.
He's not as good as Nan Yu Lou.
Nan Yu Lou really hit the Sky Water Tower.
That's not true.
Nan Yu Lou climbed from the bottom of the mountain to the top of the mountain.
It took only an hour.
But Nan Yu Lou claimed that he played two hours of chess with the Star Academy.
That's because at the base of the Star Academy,
the flow of time changes.
Have you heard of the Lan Ke chess game?
Brother, can you stop messing around with your knowledge?
Then I won't mention it.
Nan Yu Lou fell into the chess game of the Star Academy.
But he couldn't get out.
Xue Shen Guan is different.
He didn't fall into the chess game at all.
He played chess with the Star Academy for five hours.
He trapped the Star Academy.
Xue Shen Guan is a chess player.
He played chess and didn't want to leave.
He won the game and was in a good mood.
He didn't want to fight and went down the mountain.
What a chess player!
The Star Academy said that Xue Shen Guan was a very sincere person.
So his chess game couldn't trap him at all.
If he were here today,
he would have been able to get out of the water.
No, no, this skill doesn't suit me.
What you want to practice is not this martial art,
but to train your mind.
Your mind is too disrespectful.
Otherwise, with your talent,
you could have surpassed me.
You and the Tower Master are too serious.
If there is no me in the tower,
it's better to change the name of Fusheng Dream Tower to Fusheng Koshui Tower.
By the way, where did Xue Shen Guan go?
He disappeared.
No one knows where he went.
So the four families released the news
that Xue Shen Guan would appear at the Heroes Conference.
That's why it's so hot in the martial arts world.
Besides being the second most famous martial artist in the world,
what other specialties does Xue Shen Guan have?
Everyone is looking forward to him appearing.
The reason why Xue Shen Guan is called Xue Shen Guan
is because his martial arts are so mysterious
and mysterious.
It's like a magic trick.
He hides secrets and knows the Heaven's plans.
That's a martial art that everyone in the martial arts world dreams of.
It's not like the immortal book.
That's why there are many people watching him every time he appears.
Tower Master.
How is it going?
If there is no interference from the outside world,
it can be done by walking on the water.
The cultivation of the inner world is not different from the outside world.
That means there is no practice.
Sorry, Tower Master.
Forget it.
You guys leave the city today and go to Jiangnan.
The Wang family is holding their Heroes Conference.
Why should we go there?
They are just relying on an old man.
Once that old man dies,
the Wang family can't even control the four families.
They still want to become the leader of the martial arts world?
Su Bai Yi will appear there.
Do you have any news about him?
No.
But Nan Gong Xi has gone down the mountain.
He also went to Xuanwei City.
So it's very likely that Su Bai Yi will appear there.
Your sword skills are good.
It seems that you have gained a lot this time.
Of course.
I'm not only going to be the strongest man in the school,
I'm also going to be the strongest man in the world.
I'm tired.
Let's take a break.
Do you know that Senior Sister has gone down the mountain?
I heard that Su Bai Yi wrote a letter on the wall.
He didn't write a letter or a letter.
He didn't treat us as brothers.
Is this the point?
Senior Sister thinks that this is dangerous.
And there is only one word that is hard to confirm.
So she doesn't want us to go with her.
Or maybe Senior Sister wants to be alone with Junior Brother Su.
She doesn't want us to be involved.
As a junior, you should understand Senior Sister.
You shouldn't cause trouble for her.
Then we won't go.
The carriage is already prepared outside the school.
I'm waiting for you to come to me.
The most beautiful thing in the south of the spring sun.
Miss Nan Gong, you came at the right time.
The city of Qian Tang is 10 miles away.
Compared to this city, it's much more beautiful.
It's a pity that our Su Bai Yi didn't see the beautiful scenery.
Yujiu House.
Where is Yujiu House?
There is Yujiu House.
Come.
Good.
You are so bold.
I told you to look.
Why are you looking?
Come.
Good.
The food was really good.
It's beautiful.
Senior Sister, you came.
It seems that this is the most famous place in the school.
The name of Qingyi Lang is the most famous.
Okay, let's talk about the official matter first.
Have you confirmed whether it is Su Bai Yi?
Wait for Senior Sister to confirm it with you.
Sir, have you seen the man in the painting?
This person...
seems to have such a small impression.
Think about it again.
I remember.
A few days ago, I was talking about some stories in the martial arts world.
He suddenly made a mess for me.
That's right, that's the face.
There is also an old man who came with him.
Old man?
I was still outside just now.
If you continue talking, you will die.
Who?
In the martial arts world, there are many people.
If you want to see me,
I will kill you all.
Senior Sister, you don't sound like you want to.
I want to try.
I didn't see him stop.
Qingyi Lang.
I'm fine.
Who are you?
Do you want to find Su Bai Yi?
Hand over Su Bai Yi.
This sword is interesting.
Cheers!
I'm here.
Can't you wait for me to find a comfortable position to make a toast?
What are you doing?
You brat.
You dare to leave a message to your senior sister while I'm not ready.
Really?
If you leave a message,
just leave the address of our inn.
Take care.
Go.
You old man.
You are too cruel.
Su Bai Yi.
Miss Nangong.
That old man ran away.
Who is this person?
There is no news of this person in the peak.
With his martial arts,
he can't be in the martial arts world.
Let's go find him.
Su Bai Yi.
Shuyuan, slow down.
My qiaoqi is getting worse.
My senior sister has been played by you.
Qian Wei, what are you afraid of?
I'm not hiding from your senior sister.
This Xuanwei City,
I felt something wrong when I stepped into the first step.
Now I understand.
There is a master who is determined to fight here.
I had a real qi outside the jade wine building.
He led me.
I also felt him.
It's not easy to die.
If you don't want to die,
just put away your thoughts of being a monster.
I'll follow you.
Okay.
It's been a long time,
Xue Shen Guan.
You are not Xue Shen Guan.
This brother's martial arts are so extraordinary.
He is not a nobody.
But he is a great martial artist.
I can't guess his identity.
Wang Ling Xiao?
You know me.
I not only know you,
but I also fought with you.
I didn't expect that after decades,
your martial arts have improved a lot.
Who are you?
My surname is Su.
Your grandfather should have a scar.
I cut it.
My grandfather Su Qian
is still alive.
Yes, I'm still alive.
I didn't expect that after years,
I could meet an old friend.
An old friend?
He is still alive.
I'm sorry.