You have to believe in fate.
[Previously on Never Mind, It's Youth!]
For example,
when you turn around,
it's likely that you will see my sister.
What is it?
Hey!
What are you doing, Rijiu?
I've been out for a long time. It's time to go back.
Take care of yourself.
FBK suddenly asked you to come over.
It's to use the closed space of our private library,
and sudden power outage,
to create the inner turmoil,
make the two meet
and promote mutual affection.
This is my battle plan.
Never Mind, It's Youth!
Episode 10
I...
Chairman, chairman.
Calm down, calm down, calm down.
Come on, come on.
Calm down, calm down.
Are you okay?
Why don't you try it too?
I don't need to.
You wouldn't be so mean, would you?
Come here and help me to see
whether it's swollen.
It seems it's swollen indeed.
Are you okay?
♫ Every single look in your eyes ♫
♫ is like the stars in the night sky, ♫
♫ shining on lovers who truly love each other. ♫
♫ Love is like a letter. ♫
You...
Does it hurt?
♫ I wrote it down and hid it in the heart. ♫
It doesn't hurt.
♫ But I don't have the courage to send it. ♫
♫ I carved your name on my hand, ♫
♫ waiting for the word I do. ♫
♫ Show me your love. ♫
A little closer.
A little bit closer.
♫ Show me your love. ♫
Kiss her, Rijiu.
♫ The hug you gave me is neither more or less. ♫
Kiss her.
Kiss.
♫ It's the antidote to longing. ♫
♫ Show me your love. ♫
♫ I'll give you the only vow I'll keep. ♫
♫ I want to hold your hand, ♫
♫ telling the world I love you. ♫
Kiss.
Oops.
Oh!
I found it.
Ice compress can reduce the swelling.
Do you know you look like a national treasure now?
Who is it for?
Take it.
Do you want me to put it on you?
No thanks.
I'll put it on for you.
It's because I feel bad that I beat you up.
Don't think too much about it.
Don't you feel any compunction?
In fact, it's not my fault.
Why did you scare me?
I called it self-defense.
As you brew it, you must drink.
Except you, you idiot,
who would believe in ghosts?
You want to commit murder?
Yes, the female ghost is trying to kill you.
Bite me!
I'm afraid you'll give me the idiot disease.
You're the one with the idiot disease.
Don't move.
If you move again, I won't put ice on you.
Be gentle.
That's right.
This is how it should be.
With the suspension bridge effect,
we created the perfect atmosphere for the two to stay alone.
They missed the opportunity to kiss.
But,
it doesn't affect the overall situation.
Butler Jin,
please give your instructions,
to proceed with the next battle plan.
Yes, chirman.
Execute the next battle plan.
Lights, music, blower,
and snow drifting get prepared.
The power is back.
What the hell?
Wow!
It's snowing!
It's snowing on this set!
It's fake.
Artificial snowflakes, okay?
I think calling you an idiot
is belittling the intelligence of idiots.
But it's romantic and beautiful.
Don't you think so?
Yes.
Very beautiful.
I love snow,
because it holds my warmest memories.
It also hides my most precious secrets.
So,
even if it's artificial snowflakes,
I feel very happy too!
Ren Keying.
What?
I...
Get out of the way!
What are you doing?
Let me in!
You're illegally detaining our Keying!
Do you believe we will call the police?
Let me go! Let me go!
Don't come any closer! Don't come here!
Sir!
Let go, let go, let go! Don't come over!
Don't come any closer!
I tell you
it's not good even for FBK.
This is nonsense!
Chairman!
What are you doing in the middle of the day?
Keying, let's go.
Mei.
What are you doing?
It's restriction of personal freedom
and illegal detention, right?
Get out of the way!
Didn't I say that no one is allowed to enter?
Are you all losers?
We're sorry, chairman.
No one can come in.
Butler Jin.
I told them to leave.
My son,
are you okay?
Mom was just trying to help you.
I know.
I'm fine.
Thanks, Mom.
It's nonsense! Absolutely nonsense!
If I hadn't found people on the set
were driven away,
and you couldn't be reached on the phone,
we'd be in big trouble today.
Well, It's okay.
I'm not in trouble anyway.
You're fine.
Do you know
if the paparazzi take pictures of
you staying alone with the son of FBK's president,
that will be a big story.
The son of FBK's president?
Yes.
Do you mean Lin Rijiu?
What else?
He's my classmate from college.
He's the vice president of the student council of Starfire University.
He stayed at our house the other day.
How could he possibly be...
You said he stayed at your house?
I suddenly remembered I still have work to do.
I'm going home now, Mei.
Taxi! Taxi!
Damn girl, stop right there!
Tell me clearly.
You.
You're a bunch of losers!
Please clean up.
and prepare to reopen.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
Big news. It's definitely big news.
The president's son confesses his love for the vigor girl.
It's definitely the headline of the day.
No, it's the headline for the next few days.
I never thought I wandered around the set
and happened to find hot news.
Oh, no.
That's not right.
He didn't confess his love.
Just with this atmosphere, we got photos of such a scene.
Confess or not, it's up to us, right?
That's right.
[Sirius Street Dance Competition]
Wow, that's great! So handsome!
I love you.
Xia Bai, Xia Bai, I love you.
So handsome!
Too handsome!
Prince charming!
So handsome! So handsome!
Prince charming, prince charming, handsome!
I love you.
Thank you.
Go for it!
Congratulations! You've successfully qualified to the next round.
Oh my, that's great!
You're remarkable!
The performance was very good.
Especially the dance just now,
it's very energetic.
I think highly of you.
Go for it!
Keep up the good work!
Thank you.
[Pass card]
Wow.
I love you guys!
Captain,
after this competition,
is there anything you want to do?
For example,
inviting us to eat pizza.
Don't just think about eating.
You aren't afraid to eat too much and turn from little Li
into the little Li's water gun, are you?
But...
I really have something I want to do.
What is it?
I want to see a movie.
Captain,
can you have some pursuit?
I'll invite you to watch whatever you want when getting back.
Not with you.
It is with the right person to watch a movie together.
Oh...
I love snow,
because it holds my warmest memories
and my most precious secrets.
So...
I feel happy even if it's artificial snowflakes.
Who wants to play with such things?
What's this?
It's ugly.
It's terrible.
You're right.
Right.
Freak.
Ah... What are you yelling for?
- Run, run, run... Who are you?
Let's go!
Go!
Hurry up, go!
Freak!
What did you say?
I'm bullying. What's wrong with bullying her?
Don't bully her!
It's none of your business.
You, get out of here!
You!
Don't bully her!
We don't like her!
Go away! Go away! Go away!
Go away, all of you!
Go, go, go! Let's go!
Go away!
Let's go!
Are you okay?
Thank you.
Let's play hide-and-seek.
Okay, okay.
You're so childish.
I don't want to play.
Then we have a deal.
I'll be the ghost. You guys hide.
Then I'll go hide.
One
I'll hide.
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Ten
Eleven
Twelve
Thirteen
♫ I haven't heard from you for a long time. ♫
Fourteen
Fifteen
Sixteen
♫ How long will it take to get used to such an ending? ♫
Seventeen
I will start looking for you.
♫ It's better to be alone, no more quarrels. ♫
Come out, I'm not playing anymore.
♫ Sitting quietly in the room, I hide in the corner, ♫
Come out quickly.
Why aren't you coming out?
♫ Walking in the street, I look at the crowd. ♫
Come out, I'm not playing.
- Come out, come out!
♫ I can always see a familiar figure. ♫
Come on out!
♫ I understand I know it's not you. ♫
♫ I want to hold on to you but it's too late. ♫
Ren Kexing
♫ I wish you hadn't left, even as a friend. ♫
Ah.
♫ Who's holding your hand now ♫
♫ and pulling your finger? ♫
♫ I wish you could understand it's not because I didn't want to make you stay, ♫
You...
♫ but I knew we're not going to make it. ♫
Are you an angel?
♫ How I wish you hadn't left, even as a friend. ♫
♫ Who's holding your hand now ♫
♫ and pulling your finger? ♫
♫ I wish you could understand it's not because I didn't want to make you stay, ♫
♫ but I knew we're not going to make it. ♫
We never forget the past.
It's because the past
contains too many things that we have lost.
That's why
we never want to share it with others.
♫ I knew we're not going to make it. ♫
It's gradually hidden in our hearts,
becoming our secret.
Look,
I'm not a very conflicted person, am I?
Yes.
Very conflicted.
Very contradictory.
I was so desperately looking for it.
Because of the loss of contact,
I was desperate like a child
who lost the most beloved toy.
But when I really found it,
I'm at a loss.
Don't think about who likes you more.
You should ask yourself
you
like who better.
Life
is a train
that never turns back.
You used to think a certain station is your destination.
In fact,
you're not even sure
what the end
looks like.
We keep moving forward
and keep making ourselves strong.
Isn't it to find
an end that we like better?
The end we like better?
Well...
If there's nothing else, let's go home.
Do you want to sit here until dawn like a homeless person?
The mosquitoes will thank you for your selflessness.
And...
Don't turn off your phone next time.
Mei is almost crazy.
Let's go.
[FBK president's son confesses his love for the "vigor girl"]
[Xia Bai]
Hey!
Keying.
You're still up. It's so late.
Don't you have a competition?
After the qualifying round,
let's go and see a movie together.
Okay.
Then that's it. Good night.
Good night.
But...
Secrets are the past.
It's like what Alice said.
Life
Is a train that never turns back.
Once you think that a certain stop is your destination,
but you're not even sure
what the end really looks like.
We keep moving forward
and keep making ourselves stronger.
It's not for a temporary stop
filled with memories and secrets,
but to find the end
that we like better.