[The Dark Romance]
[Episode 7]
-Miss Wang, hurry up.
-Okay.
Which one of you is the killer's parent?
Attorney Zhou and I represent Yuan Ye.
And these two are...
These two are Yuan Ye's teachers.
Sit down. Okay?
Let's sit down and talk.
The killer's parents
don't even dare show up.
What's there to talk about?
Mr. Xu,
it's not that Yuan Ye's parents
didn't want to come,
but they truly couldn't.
Five years ago,
her mother killed her father.
She's currently serving time
for negligent homicide.
I didn't know that.
Look at the kind of people you mess with.
She lied to me.
Stupid.
I am the victim's representative lawyer.
After taking all the actual circumstances
into consideration,
Mr. Xu, in a spirit of generosity,
is willing to propose a settlement
covering medical expenses,
hospitalization meal subsidies,
nursing care, nutrition,
transportation,
and compensation for emotional distress,
totaling 1 million yuan.
Settlement
was proposed by you.
If the conditions cannot be met,
we'll see you in court.
Mr. Xu,
the two of them did have a relationship,
and at the time of the incident
neither side was calm.
Xu Feng,
you wouldn't want your former girlfriend
to spend her youth in prison, would you?
Given my client's special
family circumstances,
1 million is indeed too much.
Then what's there to talk about?
Excuse me.
Can I say a few words?
I didn't introduce myself
properly earlier.
I'm a psychiatrist
at Renxin Municipal Hospital.
My name is Luo Liang.
Attorney Zhou and Xiang invited me
to attend the hearing,
mainly hoping to take this opportunity
for me to explain Yuan Ye's situation.
What Xu Feng just said
was the truth.
When Yuan Ye was dating him,
she did lie about her family background.
Mr. Xu,
young people aren't as
mature and steady as you,
nor have they been through
life's ups and downs.
They're simple and easily trusting—
that's understandable.
It also shows that Xu Feng is,
at heart, kind and sincere,
a testament to your fine upbringing
and his good fortune.
But Yuan Ye
hasn't been nearly as fortunate.
Ever since she was old enough to remember,
she had been dragged around by her mother,
chasing down her father—
trying to catch him cheating,
going after mistresses.
You seduced my husband!
I'll kill you!
How dare you seduce my husband?
You home-wrecker!
Get out!
You can't keep your own husband in check!
Are you done?
You bring the child every time!
Endless arguments between her parents
and extremely irrational violence
and beatings
were her main childhood memories.
Excuse me,
is there
a girl named Yuan Ye living around here?
Yes, on the third floor.
Until 5 years ago,
Yuan Ye, having just graduated from
a vocational high school,
witnessed her mother,
unable to tolerate her
repeatedly cheating father anymore,
grab an axe
in a fit of rage
and hack at her husband,
thus
causing an irreversible tragedy.
This unfortunate girl
has never experienced
a healthy relationship.
She yearned for love,
but doesn't know how to love.
What she needs
is not just punishment,
but perhaps more guidance and help.
Just as Mr. Xu questioned
at the beginning,
none of us are Yuan Ye's family.
But we came here today,
primarily hoping to act on her behalf
to seek your forgiveness.
After all,
her childhood and birth
were not her choice.
But you
can give a child
who has temporarily gone astray
a chance to start over.
Please.
Mr. Xu.
You mean
she is justified because she is weak,
so our
carefully raised,
healthy kids
deserve to be hurt by her?
If being excusable means being forgivable,
then what is the law for?
Xu Feng,
what do you say?
Teaching her a lesson
is the best choice for her.
Xu Feng,
you repeatedly
dated several girls at the same time.
You deliberately
provoked Yuan Ye's emotions.
But she was completely sincere to you.
Even now, she is still
suffering and blaming herself
for hurting you,
and wishing she were dead.
Don't you have any compassion at all?
Is it illegal to date
multiple girlfriends at once?
They were only with him
because he had my money in his pocket.
Now that they've broken up,
she goes crazy and stabs someone;
does a person like her
deserve any sympathy?
Xu Feng,
can I have a word with you alone?
Sorry.
I couldn't be of any help.
You did your best.
It was actually expected.
The victim's family isn't short on money,
and judging from their attitude,
there's hardly any room for negotiation.
Here's the thing.
Mr. Xu and his son
have taken the other family's
circumstances into consideration.
They've agreed to reduce the compensation
and have signed a letter of understanding.
As for the specific settlement terms,
I'll be handling the negotiations in full.
What exactly did you say to Xu Feng?
A few words made him change his mind.
I didn't actually say much to him.
Have you ever heard
of intergenerational transmission?
What do you mean?
It means the parents' behaviors and ideas
are subtly passed down to their children.
Yuan Ye's mother killed her father.
If Yuan Ye finds out
that Xu Feng doesn't forgive her
and even agrees to let her go to jail,
it could cause a huge blow
to Yuan Ye's mind.
Maybe after she gets out of prison,
she won't let Xu Feng off the hook.
I just explained
this concept to Xu Feng.
I knew it.
People like you who have moral obsessions
would never accept me saying that.
No, no.
Actually, I could guess a little.
Because after you talked to him,
I saw fear in his eyes.
He should be afraid.
Making him afraid
finally got us a decent result.
Shouldn't we celebrate
and have a nice meal?
I really should treat you to a nice meal
to appreciate you.
I didn't even know
you went to investigate
Yuan Ye's family situation.
Do you remember this?
What is it?
The first time we went to Xu Feng's school
and met Yuan Ye,
didn't you get really angry
and slam a lighter onto the table?
I've been to this nightclub.
It turns out Yuan Ye worked there.
Then I found out about her family,
and learned they had
this kind of story behind them.
Really, thank you
for doing so much for her.
But...
After all that buildup of gratitude,
aren't you just leading up to saying
you don't have time
to have dinner with me?
No, no.
Actually, it's okay.
Every time I ask you out for a meal,
I'm just pushing my luck.
I'm already very used to
being rejected by you.
That's not what I meant.
By the way,
I washed your clothes.
Thank you.
That's good.
I'll pick the place.
I'll take this time to go home,
take a shower, and change clothes.
Does it have to be so formal?
Of course. The sense of ceremony
is important.
We can't just meet every time
dressed like we're going to work.
You can always put on a nice outfit
and have a relaxing meal.
Then I have to go home and change.
Dinner will be even later.
It's okay.
To see a different side of you,
it's worth the wait.
[Police]
[The chips are delicious.
The chips are delicious.]
[China Police]
[The chips are delicious.
The chips are delicious.]
No wonder.
Wait, you...
Aren't you the...
You're our comrade.
What's up?
[China Police]
[Name: Pongsri Leekpa]
How do you have this?
It's exactly the same. Look.
Come with me.
Where are we going?
[China Police]
Does the task force provide food?
Yes.
Can I use my institute meal card
in the task force?
No.
It's fine.
Clear this area.
Who is it?
What are you doing?
We just finished eating.
Hold it up!
This...
You're playing a game, right?
I'm not going to scold you.
Why are you so nervous?
It's a new game.
Dad and I have been waiting for days.
We make a great team.
Listen to Dad.
I'm home. I'll hang up now.
Dr. Luo,
I'm home.
Don't move.
Who are you? What are you doing?
Is there anyone else in the house?
Yes!
Where are they?
Come out!
People in the room, come out!
Liu Ping?
What do you want?
I'm calling the police!
You dare call the police?
Tell me, where is she?
Where did you hide Yu Kexin?
She...
She went back to Australia
to find her mom.
Bullshit! What Australia?
What Mom?
You are all lying to me!
Why would I lie to you?
What did I lie about?
I personally took her to the airport.
I saw her walk in with my own eyes.
Please calm down.
Don't be impulsive.
Put the knife down, okay?
She's still pregnant with your child.
She wouldn't lie to you.
Bullshit! What child?
It's all fake!
I don't even know
if I've ever had a child.
What do you mean?
I don't understand.
After we finalized the divorce,
I moved out.
A few days ago,
property management called and said
the bathroom was leaking
and flooded the apartment downstairs.
So I tried to get it fixed.
But when I called her,
the number was out of service.
I checked and she canceled the number.
So I had to rush home.
I found out she had moved out
a long time ago.
She just left a key
with the property management
to sell the house.
That's normal.
She probably wanted to
make a clean break with the past.
I thought so too at first,
but then I found this.
What is this?
It's a benzodiazepine-based,
highly potent sedative-hypnotic.
It's a strictly controlled
psychotropic drug.
It is commonly known as
obedience powder or date rape pills.
It's even more potent
when mixed with alcohol.
Looking at this packaging,
it might have been illegally imported
from abroad.
Xinxin,
get me a glass of water.
Xinxin!
You mean
Yu Kexin gave you this drug
and then faked a domestic violence scene?
Then,
what about the injuries on her body?
She couldn't have beaten herself up?
Anyway, it definitely wasn't me.
The doctor also said
that this medicine
knocks you out completely.
I had no ability to move at all.
How could I have the strength
to hit anyone?
How could someone
be so cruel to themselves?
She's also pregnant.
The domestic abuse was fake—
how could the pregnancy be real?
Later, I checked
every OB-GYN hospital
in Lihai City.
There's no record of
her ever visiting
or registering at any of them.
The most important thing for you now
is to take care of your health
and stay emotionally stable.
After all, you're responsible for
two people now.
I can raise you on my own,
can't I?
This is too absurd.
She came to me
to borrow money
so she could hide out for a few days.
She said
all her money was with you.
I've seen her Weibo.
She's quite wealthy
and even has a house.
[Clairet Xin, Stay Happy]
She deleted all her Weibo posts.
Later, I went to that so-called home
to look for her.
She said her mom bought it for her,
but actually,
that house was rented
and only for a little over two months.
After we got married,
it was always me giving her money.
She didn't leave a single penny with me.
The tattoo.
I found you because of the tattoo.
She said you got that tattoo
for her.
Did you know she took out a nude loan?
What nude loan?
She made me
get this tattoo when we got married—
kept pushing me until I gave in,
said it was to commemorate our love.
This...
Liu Ping, aren't you disgusted?
I never thought you were
this kind of person.
No, no.
Xinxin.
Listen to me.
Don't touch me!
Xinxin, I'm not...
It's really not what you think.
I called a few
colleagues
who were working overtime,
both men and women.
Are female colleagues
necessarily good people?
If there's really nothing between you two,
why is her hair on you?
I... I don't know either.
You don't know?
Xinxin.
Calm down.
I...
Phone.
Here.
I'll call your colleagues right now.
I'll call them one by one
and ask them clearly
what exactly is going on!
Xinxin, I beg you.
Calm down.
Really. We're married.
I couldn't possibly be involved with
another woman.
Is that so?
Then swear it.
I swear.
I, Liu Ping,
I swear, well...
You can't even swear properly!
Do you think just talking is enough?
Why should I believe you?
I...
I'm asking you
how you're going to prove it to me.
Xinxin.
Xinxin, calm down.
Xinxin, don't be angry anymore.
I'll prove it
however you want me to.
Don't be angry anymore.
I'm begging you.
Then go get a tattoo.
A tattoo?
Get the exact same design tattooed on you
to prove you love me
and that you belong only to me.
If any woman
sees this design on you,
I curse the two of you adulterers
to die a horrible death.
Xinxin.
You don't agree?
No.
I want you to get a tattoo
just to prove you love me
and that you belong only to me.
Because I love Leilei.
Since I love her,
I must love all of her,
including her flaws.
I was forced by the creditors
to get a tattoo as they demanded.
The tattoo on Leilei
was probably also done
as these people demanded.
Hello. Is Officer Li there?
Who is this?
My name is Yan Ling.
I'm a friend of a client
from one of his previous cases.
I have some information to tell him.
He's left for the provincial department.
He left?
The task force is confidential.
He can't be reached.
You can't get away.
Let me tell you,
I'm not done with you today.
-You can't get away.
-What are you doing?
Someone!
[Police]
[110 Emergency Call Center – Service Hall]
Hello. The number you dialed
is out of service.
Please check and dial again.
Hello. The number you dialed
is out of service.
Please check and dial again.
I was forced by the creditors
to follow their
demands and get a tattoo.
I even held my ID card
and took those kinds of photos.
What nude loan?
He said he felt sorry for me.
So I figured
she was probably just
following their instructions...
To witness our love...
Then he went and got the same tattoo
as me.
[Police]
I'm sorry.
I had so many things to do today.
I'm late.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You are really busy.
I
can tell.
Are you okay?
It's all my fault.
I felt like I was drugged.
I believed whatever Yu Kexin said.
This Yu Kexin
seems to know you very well.
She hits all your weak spots.
She lost her father in childhood,
met the wrong guy like Li Changning,
and both were pitifully hurt.
She said the tattoo
was because of a nude loan,
and Xia Yi said the same thing
about Leilei.
And I just believed it.
I didn't even question it.
Maybe they are all liars.
Could they know each other?
Xia Yi is Leilei's ex-boyfriend.
Leilei must have mentioned you to him.
They exchanged information
and plugged all the holes
that would make you suspicious.
At the same time, they used your guilt,
because you are still
in grief and self-blame
over losing Leilei.
So it's easier to believe
Yu Kexin, who faked a similar experience.
What I can't forgive myself for the most
is how I could believe
that Leilei
would get a tattoo,
and take out a nude loan.
Do you feel
that you betrayed Leilei?
How could I doubt Leilei like this?
I'm her best friend.
Drink less.
Getting drunk won't solve the problem.
Listen,
we are human.
Making mistakes is our factory setting.
What's more,
this scam was tailor-made for you.
If it were any of us,
it'd be hard to guarantee
not being scammed.
Don't blame yourself like this.
You act like a superwoman,
trying your best to protect Li Changning,
Yuan Ye,
and even Yu Kexin.
Do you know why?
You blame yourself
for your best friend's suicide,
and that's why.
You are trying hard to make up for
the regret of not helping Leilei.
Those who always save others
are actually
saving themselves.
I don't know what you've been through.
But I always feel that,
subconsciously,
when you hit rock bottom
and are in deep pain,
you yearn for someone like you
to reach out and help you.
I want to tell you that,
if you are willing,
I will be there.
Ling!
Ling.
No!
Let me go!
I don't need you! Go away!
I know you are suffering.
I know you miss him.
But he wouldn't want to
see you like this from heaven.
If your father saw you like this now,
he would be very sad.
He would be even sadder than you.
You still have me.
Yan Ling, you still have me.
You still have me, Yan Ling.
Leilei.
Don't worry, Leilei.
This is not over yet.
I will definitely clear your name.
[Dream Traveler, Traveler Quadrant]
[Liu Ping, Kexin]
[Pongsri Leekpa, Pazion, Xia Yi]
[Lihai Tattoo Forum]
This tattoo of an eye and an octopus
is so beautiful.
He knows about this tattoo.
You know it's an octopus and an eye.
Where did you learn about this pattern?
[Who knows this tattoo?]
[Eric]
If you see my message,
please make sure to reply.
[Xinsheng International Law Firm]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Senior.
I was too gullible.
I introduced a scammer to you all.
Right now, I just want to be able
to find this Yu Kexin.
This way, not only can I
give Liu Ping an explanation,
but I can also help my friend
find the person who scammed her.
I once told you that
Yu Kexin seems capable of
protecting herself.
She's not as innocent as you thought.
But she is my client.
Everything she provided
must be kept confidential.
Even after our client relationship ends,
I still must keep it confidential.
That's the law.
I know.
Well,
so there's really nothing
we can do to her?
From marriage,
to divorce
to the division of assets,
everything she did was legal.
Unless Liu Ping can prove
the domestic abuse never happened,
or that Yu Kexin's motive
for marrying was solely to divorce
and take the property,
we have no legal leverage
against her.
But she obviously...
Attorney Zhou,
Yu Kexin executed everything
so flawlessly.
You can tell she's experienced.
She's definitely going to
find her next target,
and more people will end up being hurt.
Let me give you a little legal insight.
Do you know how insurance is divided
after a divorce?
According to our country's Insurance Law,
there must be an insurable interest
between the policyholder and the insured.
After a divorce,
that relationship disappears,
so the insurable interest
no longer exists.
At this point,
if the policyholder and the insured
are not the same person,
the policy needs to be updated.
You mean
they purchased insurance
and then changed
the beneficiary
during
the property division?
Regarding customer privacy,
I have no comment.
This is it.
This is the insurance company.
She brought the brochure back then.
She said
she was both the policyholder
and the insured,
and I was the beneficiary.
She told me that if she ever got sick
or there was some disaster,
I'd still get a sum of money.
Even though I paid for the insurance,
I was really touched at the time.
Do you remember how this insurance
was divided when you divorced?
It wasn't divided.
I gave all the money to her.
Even though her lawyer said
I had the right to take back
50% of the benefits,
I didn't
want it.
But changing the beneficiary
requires your signature.
Yes,
but I wasn't in the mood back then.
To be honest,
I
didn't even read it carefully
and just signed.
By the way,
she said
she wanted to change the beneficiary
to her mom.
Do you have her mom's information?
What about the insurance broker?
Do you know them?
Yu Kexin handled all of this.
When I was signing,
I think I saw the broker once.
That's not right.
Attorney Zhou
wouldn't bring this up for no reason.
Ms. Yan,
how's your acting?
What?
Welcome to Anning Property
Insurance Customer Service.
Please hold while we connect you.
Number 824 is at your service.
Hello, thank you for waiting.
How can I help you?
Hello.
I recently had a life insurance policy
where the beneficiary was changed.
I'd like to confirm
whether the change
was successful.
Okay.
May I have your name and ID number?
-I'll write it for you.
-I'll check it for you.
My name is Yu Kexin—
Yu as in "niannianyouyu
(abundance every year),"
Ke as in "keyi(okay),"
and Xin as in "xinxinxiangrong
(flourishing)."
My ID number is
19890417
8562.
Please hold, I'll check for you.
Okay.
My records show
that on April 23rd of this year,
you changed the death beneficiary
of your Anning Life Insurance
to Yu Mingjie—
Ming as in "guangming (brightness),"
and Jie as in "haojie (hero),"
is that correct?
Yes.
Could you help me confirm
Yu Mingjie's ID number?
Okay.
Yu Mingjie's ID number is
20160513
8932.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'll hang up now.
Yu Mingjie?
2016?
He's only 3 years old.
Do you know him?
I don't know him at all.
Such a huge fortune
was left only to a child.
He must be a close relative to her.
I will definitely find him.
[Dongchuan Public Security Bureau]
Since the beginning of this year,
multiple reports have come in
from across the province.
A large number of victims
[Report]
were lured into investments
[Lihai] [Dongchuan] [Longhai]
through relationships
[Report] [Kunxi] [Minggang]
formed on social media,
resulting in both financial
and emotional loss.
Some victims were even driven to
the brink of collapse
and took their own lives.
Leaders and experts
from the provincial department
analyzed the cases
after linking them together.
This is a new type of
telecommunications fraud
packaged as emotional relationships.
It's highly likely to be carried out
by the same criminal gang.
We have successively caught
some underlings on the periphery.
[Dongchuan Public Security Bureau]
We can roughly determine that the gang
is located in the Pazion region,
close to our border.
They also recruit people in our country
[Serve the people]
by means of high-salary recruitment.
On March 27th,
the CID of the Lihai Municipal Bureau
caught a technician
responsible for
building fraudulent websites,
[2. 18 Task Force]
Cai Zhiyu,
also known as Cai.
[Cai Zhiyu]
Finally, a big hole
was torn in this gang.
It also verified our judgment.
According to his confession,
Julong Company has about 300 people.
[Supply Unit]
[Communications Unit]
[Technical Unit]
[Money Laundering Unit]
The entire company has a
complete organizational structure
with a clear division of labor.
[Supply Unit—Collecting
Personal Information and Screening Users]
The Supply Unit
is responsible for
collecting personal information
and screening precise users.
The Communications Unit
makes friends with the victims
[Communications Unit—
Befriending Victims
and Building Emotional Trust]
to cultivate relationships
and carry out fraud.
The Technical Unit
is responsible for
building virtual investment websites
to absorb and transfer victims' funds.
The aforementioned Cai Zhiyu
[Technical Unit—Setting Up
Fake Investment Websites]
was in charge of this department.
[Absorbing the victims' funds]
[Money Laundering Unit—Using Card Machines
and Various Methods]
There is also a Money Laundering Unit.
They use credit card machines
and various other methods
[to break down the funds]
to break down the funds layer by layer
before taking them out.
Each department is isolated
from the others
and real names are not used.
Cai Zhiyu's rank was not high enough,
so he didn't know
the true identities
of the company's senior management.
He only knew
the chairman
is nicknamed Master Bei.
[Chairman, Master Bei]
[Top Figure—Relative]
The second-in-command,
[Second Brother—No. 2 Figure,
in Charge of Finance and Operations]
nicknamed "Second Brother"
is his relative.
He's mainly responsible for
the company's finances
and overall operations.
There are also two
very important romance trainers.
[Training Code name: Lu Ban]
They work within the Communications Unit
and are mainly responsible for
developing and refining scam scripts.
It's said that
this method of romance before fraud
was developed by them.
One of the trainers
is Pongsri Leekpa,
from Pazion.
[Xia Yi's passport]
Known as Mr. Wang,
he's excellent at Chinese,
and suspected to be ethnic Chinese.
He previously used the alias Xia Yi
to commit fraud in our country.
We found he has multiple
entry and exit records at China Customs.
[Xia Yi's passport] [Xia Yi's sketch
before plastic surgery]
Every time he entered,
he disappeared.
We highly suspect
he has a domestic identity.
This Pongsri is highly likely
to have had plastic surgery.
This is a reconstructed portrait of him
before surgery,
drawn by experts based on
our analysis and estimates.
Based on the portrait and age range,
we screened
more than 30 suspects
among those with a criminal record.
[A sketch before Xia Yi's plastic surgery]
[Xia Yi's Entry and Exit Records]
We are currently investigating
and eliminating them.
Another trainer,
nicknamed Lu Ban
[Trainee Lu Ban, in charge of
the Communications Unit]
is someone
whose true identity we still don't know.
[Development and upgrade
of the prank play]
That's all we know about the whole case.
[Dongchuan Public Security Bureau]
[Scroll]
You haven't left yet, Paw Patrol.
[2. 18 Task Force]
Sorry for
waking you up.
What did you just call me?
Paw Patrol.
Just kidding. Wait,
but I think this nickname
suits you very well.
We are all police.
Every time you go out on a case,
it's like Paw Patrol.
Whenever there's trouble...
BGM.
Is it funny?
It's okay, I think.
Did I laugh?
Why are you here?
I
thought of some clues.
What clues?
It's you, that...
Tell me!
No,
look.
Xia Yi
and Lu Ban
are both trainers in their company.
So is it possible
that Xia Yi and Lu Ban
went abroad together
and came back together?
Think about it,
they are all acquaintances.
It's very convenient
to discuss lesson plans
and upgrade the script on the plane.
So I think...
Excluding children, women
and the elderly over 60,
[Entry and Exit Flight Records]
[January 2019]
this is the list of everyone
on the same flight as Pongsri.
[出入境航班信息记录表]
[January 2019]
[2. 18 Task Force]
This...
Did Cai
go through them?
He said there is no Lu Ban here.
I thought I found a breakthrough.
Got my hopes up for nothing.
You see, I finally came here once,
and I can't help with anything.
It's quite awkward for me.
I didn't expect you to be able to
help anyway.
Exactly.
In terms of CID techniques,
interrogation methods,
or even physical ability,
you don't really rank.
We called you here
not for this reason.
So direct.
Wait.
That day,
you came to our station,
stood behind my desk,
looked at me
with a pleasant surprise and said,
"Oh, no wonder."
What does it mean?
[Qingzhou Branch,
Lihai City Public Security Bureau]
[Police File of Sanjie Police Station]
I'm much fatter than in this photo.
I was very thin back then.
Later, I mainly focused on
text and archive work.
Everyone has their own strengths.
Yes, so your value lies in
that you are the only one among us
who has had contact with Pongsri.
He and Lu Ban are like ghosts to us,
but to you, they are at least
real scammers.
Think hard.
Are there any details
that you missed?
Just stay here today
to
work overtime.
Thanks for your hard work.
Close the door when you leave.
Okay.
[The Dark Romance]
[drift]
Now you understand
why Yuan Ye stabbed you.
She learned it from her mom.
If you can't learn to drift,
you'll just get into trouble
time and time again.
You won't even know
how you'll die.
[Drifting–a driving technique,
also known as "drift"]
Young Master,
you didn't fasten your seatbelt.
Shut up!
Just drive.