♪A gaze cuts through
the edge of the world♪
♪Your nearness
hides a secret I can't read♪
♪Every move you make, your silhouette♪
♪I hear you breathe,
but I can't break free♪
♪Let me, let me
keep searching endlessly♪
♪I try to get close,
but you're still out of reach♪
♪No one set the rules for staying safe♪
♪I test the line of clarity,
trapped in what I can't escape♪
♪I'm falling♪
♪I'm waiting♪
♪Caught in doubt♪
♪Between us now♪
=Double Fugue=
=Episode 18=
Tang Bei!
Before I met you...
♪When I wandered
into your still, deep night♪
I wanted to hear you out.
But after hearing too many lies,
I guess it's time I wake up.
♪I could never forget♪
Baoyan.
♪Full of stars♪
I'm sorry.
♪Time♪
My
identity
and status...
Everything was fake.
I was never some
rich Chinese heir born overseas.
That was never what I cared about!
♪I let all my guards fall. The disguise♪
Tang Bei.
♪You are my tender♪
Wang Yayin sent you to get close to me.
♪You are my sender♪
♪All my inspiration♪
You two played me like a fool.
♪Is lit by this warmth♪
I was just like an idiot!
♪You are my tender♪
Did I entertain you?
♪You are my defender♪
It's not like that.
♪I drift past the winds
and anchor in your sea♪
Baoyan.
Since I was a kid...
♪Let time carry me far away♪
I never knew what love was.
You
taught me what love is.
Tang Bei.
♪You are my tender♪
This is the first time
I ever loved someone.
♪You are my sender♪
Never again.
♪You bring imagination
to each day's story♪
♪You are my tender♪
♪And love will be forever♪
Baoyan.
Go away!
You have no right to care about her.
Yayin.
Wait in the study.
That was a good move.
Feels like it's been ages
since we last played together.
Yayin.
If you hadn't
been by my side all these years,
I don't know
if I could have survived until now.
You've always been
the person I trust most.
So
whatever mistake
you may have made,
I'll always forgive you.
Of course,
I trust
you wouldn't do anything to betray me.
Right?
Of course.
I'd never betray your trust.
All these years,
I never told anyone
how you climbed to this position
and
who
you harmed.
That's why
you're the darling I trust the most.
Lately,
it's been chaotic here.
Why not take a trip?
How about you handle
the Yong'an Group project
in South City?
Shilun.
You've really thought of everything.
Your move.
Why are you still here?
What do you think?
(Shilun Group Corporation Limited
Memo on Wang Yayin's Reassignment)
Now you know
what goes around, comes around.
Just wait and see.
Wang Yayin got promoted?
That's strange.
Knowing what Su Shilun is like,
there's no way
he'd let her go that easily.
Something shady must be going on.
- (Yong'an Real Estate Project Imploded)
- Thank you.
(The person in charge
may face over ten years in jail.)
So Su Shilun had arranged
for her to take the blame.
He used women to get to the top
and used a woman as a scapegoat.
All these years,
he's always been the same.
The way he treated Wang Yayin
was just how he treated my mom.
Luckily,
your mom spent her later years
with you.
She wasn't entangled with Su Shilun.
Yuebai.
Don't worry.
Even the strongest have weaknesses.
Let's work together
to find Su Shilun's weakness.
We'll face it together.
Su Shilun's weakness?
I know what you want.
Could there be a misunderstanding?
What you really want
must be my mother's painting.
Very well.
Name your price.
Could it be my mother's painting?
He was searching
for it at my mother's funeral.
My mother must've left a message
in the painting she left to me.
Su Shilun.
You jerk.
You played me!
You look beautiful when angry.
I played you?
When have I ever played you?
Take a good look at the contracts.
Aren't those your signatures?
Widen your eyes.
Look closely. Are they yours?
Let me tell you.
Your signature is worth a lot.
It's enough to lock you up
for ten years.
Ten years.
So many years have passed,
yet you're still beautiful
and adorable.
You're even cuter when angry.
Instead of losing your temper,
why not think about how you'll spend
the next ten years in prison?
How about
singing me a song?
The one you always sing
with your little lover.
Drunken Concubine.
Can't sing it?
I'll help you.
Like Chang'e descending
from Heaven,
alone and forlorn
in the Moon Palace.
I'm telling you.
No matter how pretty Chang'e may be,
she'll live alone
in that palace forever.
What a pity.
♪I see His Majesty♪
♪Sleeping fully clothed within the tent♪
(Yong'an real estate project imploded,)
(the person in charge, Wang Yayin,)
(is detained for duty-related crimes.)
(She may face over ten years in prison.)
(The full story coming up next.)
Go away!
Baoyan.
You have no right to care about her.
I'll kill you!
Who said you could speak?
Orphaned country bumpkin.
Stop! What are you doing?
I'll beat you!
This is kid business.
Adults shout stay out of it.
If you continue,
I'll call the police
to arrest all of you.
- Buddy, let's go.
- Let's go.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
What's your name?
My name is Tang Bei.
Tang Bei.
(Listen here.)
(Running solves nothing.)
(You must always)
(be in control of the situation.)
(Building 35, Unit 1)
Qin Yuebai.
I'll make sure you pay the price.
(Hello.)
(The number you dialed)
(is currently unavailable.)
(Please try again later.)
(Sorry.)
(The number you dialed)
(is currently unavailable.)
(Please try again later.)
(Tang Bei: Qin Yuebai is with me.)
Yuebai!
Great Artist,
you finally showed up.
Tang Bei.
Where did you hide Yuebai?
This has nothing to do with her!
How could that be?
Before she came,
we were all...
We were all doing fine.
After she showed up,
everything turned upside down.
So
I want you to experience
what it feels like to see
someone you love
slowly die in front of you.
Tang Bei, are you insane?
Wang Yayin is using you.
You want to be used forever?
She loves me.
And I love her.
Without her, I wouldn't be here.
Yes.
Stop acting in front of me.
Tell me
where you hid Yuebai!
Qin Yuebai.
I remember she has
claustrophobia.
What do you mean?
She's in the shipping container
behind me.
It's not even locked.
But I forgot
her exact location.
Time's almost up.
She's dying.
I've prepared a ladder for you.
It's over there.
Yuebai.
Yuebai!
Is anyone there?
♪When I wandered
into your still, deep night♪
♪I could never forget
that sky full of stars♪
♪Time sketched between every stroke♪
♪Because you were by my side,
I let all my guards fall♪
♪The disguise♪
♪You are my tender♪
♪You are my sender♪
♪All my inspiration
is lit by this warmth♪
♪You are my tender♪
♪You are my defender♪
♪I drift past the winds
and anchor in your sea♪
♪Let time carry me far away♪
♪Tender♪