♪A gaze cuts through
the edge of the world♪
♪Your nearness
hides a secret I can't read♪
♪Every move you make, your silhouette♪
♪I hear you breathe,
but I can't break free♪
♪Let me, let me
keep searching endlessly♪
♪I try to get close,
but you're still out of reach♪
♪No one set the rules for staying safe♪
♪I test the line of clarity,
trapped in what I can't escape♪
♪I'm falling♪
♪I'm waiting♪
♪Caught in doubt♪
♪Between us now♪
=Double Fugue=
=Episode 19=
Is anyone there?
Help!
Yuebai.
Yuebai!
Where are you?
Yuebai, can you hear me?
Yuebai!
Yuebai.
Don't
be afraid.
Slowly
close your eyes.
Don't mind the darkness!
Just pretend
the darkness is golden wheat.
Slowly
crawl to the door.
Push it open.
Can you hear me?
Yuebai!
Don't be afraid!
I'm right here.
Slowly
crawl forward.
Crawl forward slowly
and gently push the door open.
Can you hear me, Yuebai?
Lu Li.
Are you okay?
It's you.
Don't be afraid.
Yuebai.
Since you love each other so much,
I'll let you be together.
Don't be afraid.
Get out of the way!
How did it go?
Everything's done.
Financial crimes,
murder, and kidnapping.
She's in deep trouble.
Hopefully,
she'll never get out.
Yes.
About Lu Li...
(Lu Li File)
Should we...
What a good daughter.
How dare she fool me with a fake?
Keep an eye on them.
Report everything to me.
Yes.
Go on!
(Shilun Group Internal System,
Access Denied)
What's wrong?
Su Shilun locked most of my access.
Most of it?
Seems like we need to decode
the painting's secret soon.
Planning to stare a hole in it?
Why can't I figure out
this painting's secret?
What is it?
It's strange.
This color
looks different than yesterday morning.
How different?
I got it.
Some painters
use special layers
on the surface
to hide the true meaning.
Do you have a UV light?
UV light?
I'll go check.
This one?
Yes.
127?
December 7th?
Is that an important date?
Not really.
Is it related to your mother?
Where are you going?
This is my mother's diary.
Her diary?
November 3rd.
December 6th.
But no December 7th.
Wait a minute.
Looks like
there's erased writing.
(Su Shilun.
I only have hatred for that name.)
(He takes advantage of my feelings
for him like a hidden snake.)
(There are some rumors)
(spreading everywhere online,)
(but they're only unfounded rumors.)
Let me make announce formally.
I'm Su Baoyan's boyfriend.
♪When I wandered
into your still, deep night♪
♪I could never forget
that sky full of stars♪
♪Time sketched between every stroke♪
(Baoyan.)
(Since I was little,)
(I never knew love.)
♪I let all my guards fall. The disguise♪
(You)
(taught me what love is.)
♪You are my tender♪
♪You are my sender♪
♪All my inspiration♪
If you want to starve,
do it outside,
not in my house.
Thank you.
You put yourself
in such a state for a man.
How impressive.
I... It's not just about Tang Bei.
It's also about my dad.
I...
I keep feeling
he's different
from before.
Maybe
you never really knew the real him.
No way.
My dad always doted on me.
Do you know
why Wang Yayin ended up like this?
Isn't it
because she was greedy for our fortune?
Wrong.
Your dad deliberately gave her
a company with problems.
Wang Yayin used Tang Bei to trick you
and embezzled company assets.
She deserves punishment.
But Su Shilun wasn't satisfied.
He pinned all his crimes
on Wang Yayin.
Lu Li's parents
are also dead because of him.
And my mom.
No way.
Stop slandering him.
My dad's not like that.
You'll face it eventually.
(Tang Bei.)
(Stop making mistakes.)
Mistakes?
Why say I'm wrong?
What did I do wrong?
It's Qin Yuebai who's wrong.
Qin Yuebai's wrong, got it?
I...
I just want to protect Yayin.
I want to protect you.
I want to protect all of you.
I just want to protect all of you.
Once Qin Yuebai is gone,
everything will be fine.
Tang Bei.
Look at me.
Can you do it
just once for me?
Please don't do this.
It's not too late.
You could have a bright future.
But if you really kill someone,
what about me?
You already abandoned me once.
Are you going to abandon me again?
I'm sorry.
I...
I'll turn myself in.
Lu Li.
You've lost everything,
yet you still want me
to help bring down Su Shilun?
If you want to discuss the deal,
you should show some sincerity.
What leverage
do you have left?
Lu Li.
Are you here for this?
Now that I look closely,
your eyes
really resemble your father.
You're not worthy to say their names.
You even have the same temper.
No rush.
Is this what you want?
You know what?
This is my proudest creation.
You're a great artist.
A genius artist.
I believe
you understand
this passion for art.
You're a genius artist.
A genius.
I know you schemed
to get close to my daughter
just to reach me.
You only wanted these things.
It's a pity
you fell in love with her.
You believed in love too much.
Just like how your parents
believed in me.
You know we're all animals
in this world,
but animals are divided
into high and low levels.
If you believe in love,
you become a low-level animal.
Fire.
Are you afraid of fire?
You're afraid of fire too.
They were burned alive
in that car back then.
I often have nightmares.
I dream of them
struggling in the car
and screaming for help.
I often wake up terrified.
Maybe it's their punishment for me,
but it's useless.
Everything has turned to ashes.
Just like this evidence.
It will all turn to ashes.
You'll get nothing.
Fool.
Don't struggle.
Enjoy all this.
(Exclusive
Artist Representation Agreement)
(Party B: Lu Li)
Is this sincere
enough?
Lu Li.
You used your lifetime agency contract
to exchange
for evidence of Su Shilun's crime.
Do you think it's worth it?
(Su Shilun)
Here, Mr. Sun.
Take a look.
After all that have happened,
it's still the two of us.
With you joining us,
our group will only grow stronger.
Mr. Su.
Don't flatter me.
I'm only benefiting
from your lead
in this acquisition.
It's the boss behind me
who's wealthy
and capable.
Mr. Sun.
I haven't even met that boss
behind you.
How about this?
I'll arrange
the signing ceremony.
We're forming a powerful alliance.
I need to publicize it.
Please don't.
That person
likes to stay low-key.
Let's not ruin things.
Leave
this matter to me.
I'll leave it to you then.
Farewell.
Mr. Sun.
Mr. Su.
Here's an overview
of our acquisitions abroad.
Please take a look.
♪When I wandered
into your still, deep night♪
♪I could never forget
that sky full of stars♪
♪Time sketched between every stroke♪
♪Because you were by my side,
I let all my guards fall♪
♪The disguise♪
♪You are my tender♪
♪You are my sender♪
♪All my inspiration
is lit by this warmth♪
♪You are my tender♪
♪You are my defender♪
♪I drift past the winds
and anchor in your sea♪
♪Let time carry me far away♪
♪Tender♪