♪The spring breeze
outside the window moves the stream♪
♪Who is disturbed
by the williow catkins?♪
♪You're there when I look back,
toying with my heart♪
♪Everything has become an ornament♪
♪A pair of lovebirds are flying
under the roof in the drizzling rain♪
♪Whose secrets have drifted
to the chamber?♪
♪The night when the moon shines,
I'll have a drink with you♪
♪Let's keep each other company
for the rest of our lifes♪
♪The mountain and water carry me
through my lifetime relationship♪
♪Oh, wind and rain,
you're as romantic as spring♪
♪Like the star and the moon,
I wish you all well♪
♪Don't think about him,
I'm right by your side♪
♪Oh, my dream keeps changing
because of you♪
♪I'm still waiting for you
to look at me♪
♪It's hard to let go
once one falls in love♪
♪My life is not wasted
while being with you♪
=Choice Husband=
=Episode 19=
I wonder how to determine this matter.
Here comes the imperial decree.
From Heaven's blessings,
behold the Emperor's message.
Qin Zuze embezzled the military fee,
tried to murder the Emperor
and revolted, he shall not be pardoned.
He is executed to decapitation.
The Qin's bloodline is
punished by exile.
Empress Dowager assisted
the evildoers out of jealousy.
She should have been exiled as well.
But His Majesty is filial.
For the sake of her poor health
and her permanent illness,
she'll stay at the mausoleum
of the late emperor and reflect herself.
Pei Yanzhen deserves credit
for the mutiny.
He's bestowed with the title
of Regent
and ten thousand taels of gold.
Song Xiyuan has contributed
to the political situation.
He'll secede
from the merchant community,
and be bestowed with the position
of Minister of Revenue.
He'll be in charge
of the market and city, the fishery,
the salt and tea business, cash and tax.
That's all.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
Eunuch,
what is this about?
Every affair in the imperial court
will be at Regent's command.
Congratulations, Regent.
Miaomiao's crisis has
finally been resolved.
Now,
it's time for me and you to settle up.
(Shen's Residence)
Since last night,
we've arrested over 100 members
of the Qin family.
According to them,
Qin Miuzhen and 100 guards are
still on the run.
And a team has
abducted Old Master and Old Madam Pei.
They might've come to the capital.
Qin Miuzhen is very cunning.
Last night, she deliberately made me
fight at Shen's Residence.
Yet, she secretly deployed
the main army force to Pei's Residence.
How am I supposed
to explain this to Pei Yanzhen?
He just took over the reins of power.
Qin Miuzhen is not the only one
who's with evil intentions.
Be more careful.
Don't give them an opening.
Noted.
Young Master!
Someone, Young Master fell in the water.
Is there anyone?
Zai was perfectly fine.
Why would he fall into the water?
He can't swim.
Why didn't you stop him?
Young Master got bored
staying at the residence.
He saw the lotus blooming.
So he tried to pick a few for Madam.
Maybe it's because
of the slippery duckweed.
That's how he fell.
Go get a physician over.
Yes.
Guard Zhan,
now that Zai's life is in danger,
what else do you want?
Guard Zhan.
I'll go get a physician.
You stay here.
(Shen's Residence)
Zai.
Young Master.
He's
just having a fever.
Why would he cough up blood?
He has tuberculosis.
Tuberculosis
is contagious.
He only fell in the water.
How could this happen?
Check on him again.
It's incurable.
Physician!
Zai.
Young Master.
Get out!
If anything happens to Zai,
I'll never let you off.
Get lost!
Zai.
- Zai.
Did you hear about it?
Someone in the Shen family
has tuberculosis.
He's terminally ill
and dying.
Tuberculosis?
So the only thing
they can do is to prepare
for their funerals and wait for death.
The Shen family, the richest family,
is just like a sitting duck.
They're screwed.
Well, let's not approach
the Shen family in recent times.
Quick, hurry up.
My fish.
Okay.
Tonight, we're going to make
sweet and sour fish.
Madam, you're good at dealing with fish.
(Shen's Residence)
Madam,
stop crying.
Just let her be.
Just cry it out.
You'll feel better.
Zai,
just rest assured and leave.
Pretty soon,
I'll come and find you.
What I owe you in this life,
I'll repay it in my next life.
Official Zhan,
we got news from the capital.
What did Official Pei say?
He's just been bestowed
with the title of Regent.
Those reluctant ones are
stirring up trouble.
He can't make it here now.
The Shen family will be
at your discretion.
Aunt.
- Madam.
- Aunt!
Aunt.
Madam.
Aunt!
Zai.
Madam.
I'm coming with you.
Aunt.
Go get a physician.
- Go!
- Wake up, Aunt.
Madam.
- Aunt, don't leave me alone.
- Madam.
Aunt!
(Shen's Residence)
Stop right there!
You've got some nerve.
I want to see Zhan Yue.
Zhan Yue!
Zhan Yue, I finally found you.
What's going on in the capital?
Why did the court send the guards over
and stop me from going out?
I tried so hard to get out of there.
When I was on my way here,
they said
Uncle was dead.
Pei Yanzhen became the Regent.
Is that true?
Your Highness,
just go back.
I'm in a hurry.
When I settle the Shen family,
I'll go to you.
(Shen's Residence)
What happened to the Shen family?
Where is Shen Miao?
Just let me see her.
I know you think I'm an unworldly girl.
But I'm not a fool.
They are all Pei Yanzhen's men.
Did you surround this place?
What for?
Just tell me.
Leave, Your Highness.
Zhan Yue,
I beg of you.
I know you have your reasons.
But,
many things have happened
in the court.
Shen Miao and I are acquaintances.
Why don't...
Why don't you just let me see her?
Okay?
♪I'm waiting for the wind and you
to share a simple happiness♪
Miao,
stop drinking.
If you want to drink,
I'll accompany you.
Your Highness,
you've come.
♪The tangling love
becomes the river under the sky♪
Everyone shuns the Shen family now.
You're royalty.
Aren't you afraid of getting infected?
Pei Yanzhen has succeeded
in eradicating Uncle
and becomes the Regent.
Miao.
I'm sorry.
If I could figure out
about the plan
that Brother and Pei Yanzhen made
and tell you about it sooner,
you wouldn't have...
I should be the one
who apologizes.
I trusted and loved
the wrong person.
Otherwise,
the Shen family wouldn't have
broken apart.
If I didn't see it myself,
I would've thought
that Pei Yanzhen was true to you.
It's not your fault.
He's too good at pretending
and he's very cunning.
I can't imagine
that this powerful
and capable Pei Yanzhen
is the same person in my mind.
How I wish that everything was
a bad dream when I woke up.
Miao,
perhaps there's a chance
to turn things around.
When the furor in the capital recedes,
I'll ask Brother for help
to exonerate you.
Shen Miao,
believe me.
As long as Brother and I are around,
Pei Yanzhen wouldn't dare lay
a finger on you.
♪Grant me happiness for
the rest of my life together with you♪
You have tuberculosis too?
I'm afraid
that I can't live to see that day
when the furor recedes.
Don't say that.
Shen Miao.
You said
you'll take me to the Western Regions
to do business.
You even said
you'll take a tour
of the capital with me.
I'm just like
a walking dead now.
Your Highness.
Can you promise me
two things?
First off,
when Aunt passed away,
there were many kinds
of sacrificial offerings.
But Madiao from her hometown
was not included in it.
Making her leave with regret.
I didn't fulfill my filial duty.
The Song family sets foot
in all kinds of businesses.
Third Master Song is not around.
You can ask his underling, Tie Niu,
to look for it.
In this way,
it can comfort Aunt's spirit in heaven.
It's kind of a small gesture
of respect from a dying person like me.
Secondly,
my dad told me
that the Shen family
must live
and die together.
Your Highness,
please tell Zhan Yue
that if I die,
be sure to bury me
at the Shen family's ancestral tombs.
Will you do it?
Shen Miao,
you can't die.
Are you going to let
Pei Yanzhen bully you like this?
You have to stay alive
to seek revenge, Shen Miao.
I'll do it in my next life.
Promise me,
will you?
(Shen's Residence)
Let's go.
We have to stay away from this place.
The Shen family is so miserable.
Two members died at once.
Let's break it up.
Break it up.
Come on, let's go.
(Shen's Residence)
Miss,
you're looking better today.
I'm sure you'll get well
after taking this medicine.
I'm afraid this is a terminal lucidity.
Do not talk nonsense.
When the physician comes,
he'll cure you.
It's not necessary.
Tuberculosis is
an incurable illness.
The outcome is still the same
no matter how hard the physician tries.
Miss Shen,
I've brought him over.
All of you may leave.
I have something to tell Tie Niu.
Come on.
Let's go.
If Young Master Song sees you like this,
it'll surely break his heart.
The Madiao you're looking for,
what does it look like?
Any last word?
Shut up!
How dare you curse her?
Never mind.
Tie Niu,
do you know
what your master is doing
in the capital?
Forget it.
Asking you to find Madiao is
just an excuse.
I do have something to say
before I die.
Now
my family has left me.
And I'm dying.
Xiao is the only one left.
Besides me and the Shen family,
Third Master Song is the person
whom Xiao
trusts the most.
Now that Xiao
is missing.
I, as his mother,
might not
have the chance
to see him
one last time.
Madam.
All I wish is that
Third Master Song could take Xiao
to my grave and worship me
on the first seventh day
after my death.
But,
do not bring Pei Yanzhen along.
I don't want to see him.
Madam.
Miss.
Shen Miao.
About Madiao's
place of origin,
color,
image,
and size,
are you clear about them?
I remember them, Madam.
Thank you.
Stop talking, Shen Miao.
- Physician.
Yes, I'm here.
Hurry up, Physician.
How is she?
Your Highness,
Sir,
Miss Shen is in the last stage
of tuberculosis.
I'm afraid there's no medicine
that can cure her.
What are you talking about?
Sir,
based on her condition,
even the divine healer is
not able to cure her.
It won't help
even if you kill me.
Zhan Yue,
let him go.
I'm well aware of my condition.
Just consider it as accumulating merit.
Miss,
don't say that.
No matter what,
you have to wait
for Old Master and Xiao to come back.
I wish they'll never step
into Shen's Residence.
Miss Shen.
Wait a little longer.
I've sent a letter to the capital.
Pei Yanzhen is traveling day and night
to get back to Lingzhou.
I'm afraid it's too late.
Zhan Yue,
listen to me.
Tell him
that I, Shen Miao, am not important.
What matters is
to bury me
at the Shen family's ancestral tombs
after I die.
And...
And Xiao.
Xiao
is his biological son.
Be sure...
Be sure to treat him nicely.
Also,
I dare not ask more from him.
We were husband and wife once.
All I ask is
that he could let my dad live
for the sake
that the Shen family's fortune is
going to be transferred
to the national treasury.
Miss Shen,
just wait a little longer.
I've informed the capital.
Just one day will do.
Pei Yanzhen will be back soon.
Wait for what?
Wait to be imprisoned?
Wait to be annihilated?
Or
wait for Pei Yanzhen to come back
to kill me
and my family?
Pei Yanzhen won't do that.
I can't.
I'm afraid
I can't wait any longer.
- Miss Shen!
- Madam!
♪A long-lasting love is
to be envious of♪
♪Only love can burn you up
and get your heart pumping♪
Miss!
Miss Shen!
Miao!
Miss!
Wake up, Miss!
- Miao!
- Miss!
Miao!
Miss!
Wake up, Miss!
Wake up!
(Shen Miao's Tomb)
(Miao, hang in there.)
Miss.
Bury the coffin.
Stop!
Your Highness.
Do not bury it.
Move aside!
You can't revive the dead.
I'm sorry.
Your Highness,
she has passed away.
Please let us bury her
so she can rest in peace.
I beg of you!
What did you say?
Miao is dead?
She is dead.
The weather is hot.
And she died of tuberculosis.
If we don't bury her now,
I'm afraid her body will rot.
Your Highness,
you crucified the Shen family
and got us into this.
You and her were man and wife once.
Please let her peacefully...
Shut up!
Whoever says Miao is dead,
I'll kill them.
Pei Yanzhen,
others might fear you but I don't.
When Shen Miao was alive,
you tortured her terribly.
Now that she's dead,
you still won't let her go.
Are you trying to make her
turn in her grave?
♪There are many devoted lovers
in the mortal world♪
♪It's hard to understand love♪
♪If I have another chance,
I won't be late again♪
♪All I wish is for you to be well♪
♪Don't ask me if this is worth it♪
No!
Stop!
Pei Yanzhen,
I've never seen a hypocrite like you
who's heartless!
Miao!
Your Highness!
Pei Yanzhen!
- Your Highness!
- Master Pei!
♪There's an unfinished story
between you and me♪
♪How am I supposed to continue my life?♪
♪The moon rises and sets,
a day has passed♪
♪I just want to protect you
until old ages♪
♪And make a vow about you♪
♪I'm willing to be obsessed with you♪
Miao,
didn't I tell you
I'll be back soon?
Shen Miao,
you can't die
without my consent.
♪Don't ask me if this is worth it♪
♪However, love is♪
♪Turning into lovesickness
when it deepens into your heart♪
♪Even life and death can't frighten me♪
♪I've been through the good times
and bad times♪
♪But the person I've been waiting for
is not aware of it♪
(Miao,)
(I'll take you home.)
Pei Yanzhen!
No! Don't do this!
- Pei Yanzhen!
- Miss!
No!
I'm useless.
I can't let her rest in peace.
Now that I'm evicted
from Shen's Residence,
what should I do?
Miss Lvying,
don't be upset.
My mom always says
that everything is gone after death.
Since Madam's soul has ascended
to heaven,
though her body is taken away,
I guess no one can disturb her
in the afterlife.
Tie Niu.
- Tie Niu.
- Miss Lvying.
What did you say?
What happened to Miaomiao?
Third Master, please save Miss Shen.
You're the only one
who can help me now.
Master,
don't be sad.
Madam has
passed away.
Miaomiao, she...
Did she really...
Miao, you liked
to eat sweets.
Try this tea.
Please calm down, Your Highness.
- Please calm down, Your Highness.
Tale of Ancient Sword is
Miao's favorite show.
If you make mistakes,
she'd get mad.
Miao,
many things have happened
during this trip to the capital.
There are many things
I want to tell you.
You liked to watch shows.
If I kill them all,
would you intercede for them?
I've said
that no noise
at Shen's Residence.
Please calm down, Your Highness.
It's...
It's Official Song.
Miao,
I'll be right back.
Keep going.
Move aside.
Regent has said
that no one is allowed
to barge into Shen's Residence.
Official Song, please don't make
things difficult for us.
He's the Regent, so what?
No one can stop me
from doing what I want.
Stop!
Pei!
Where exactly did you hide
Miaomiao's body?
She's my wife.
Why do you care?
Do you deserve her?
I thought
you were true to Miaomiao.
Now that she died because of you,
what else do you want?
Are you going to crush
her bones into ashes?
Get out.
Don't disturb her.
If you don't hand over
Miaomiao's body today,
I won't leave.
Try me.
You've been sanctimonious
and making profits all these years.
You can't pretend anymore.
I've always wanted to fight you.
I can take this chance
to avenge Miaomiao.
With Master's martial arts skills,
he can't hold him up for long.
Hurry up.
A martial art expert like you has
hidden your skills for decades
for the sake of your revenge plan.
No wonder
you'd despise the lives
of the Shen family.
He's a leading official now.
Don't do anything outrageous.
Song Xiyuan,
you're no match for him.
Just go.
Now, I just regret
that I didn't take her away
from here back then,
causing her to end up
in such a miserable situation.
Your Highness,
something happens in the foyer.
Someone is trying to abduct Madam.
It's you.
Come, Lvying.
Miss.
Put her down.
I'll spare your lives.
Master.
Miao,
you've been asleep for three days.
It's time to wake up.
Fine.
I'll watch over you.
I'll look after you
until you wake up.
I'll wait for you.
My parents had died for me.
Do you have the heart
to leave me alone?
I still have
a lot of things to tell you.
Official Pei,
please give her back to me.
Shut up.
One more word,
I'll kill you right away.
Miao,
I hate hearing someone say you're dead.
I'll kill all the servants
of the Shen family
and the martial artists
so they can go down there
and keep you company
until the day you wake up, okay?
Miaomiao.
Pei Yanzhen,
that's enough.
Miao,
you're still alive.
Wonderful.
You've misunderstood.
This is terminal lucidity.
♪There are many devoted lovers
in the mortal world♪
♪It's hard to understand love♪
♪If I have another chance,
I won't be late again♪
♪All I wish is for you to be well♪
♪Don't ask me if this is worth it♪
♪However, love is♪
♪Turning into lovesickness
when it deepens into your heart♪
♪Even life and death can't frighten me♪
♪I've been through the good times
and bad times♪
♪But the person I've been waiting for
is not aware of it♪
♪There's an unfinished story
between you and me♪
♪How am I supposed to continue my life?♪
♪The moon rises and sets,
a day has passed♪
♪I just want to protect you
until old ages♪
♪And make a vow about you♪
♪I'm willing to be obsessed with you♪
♪I wish we could be together
in our next lifes♪