I can't believe we're actually here!
Look, they're waiting for us!
- There they are!
- Okay, here they come.
- Hello, welcome!
- Let's go!
- There are so many of them!
- Hello!
- Hello, everybody!
- Welcome!
- Nice to meet you all!
- Are you here by yourself?
- Yeah, I came alone.
- It's so very nice to meet you all.
WELCOME
Hey, you guys! Nice to meet you.
Make sure the luggage
doesn't get mixed up.
SURPRISED
- What's wrong?
- Hello!
DO THEY KNOW EACH OTHER?
- Hold on.
- Hello.
Ye-eun, wait. Do you know him?
- Do you know him?
- He's my little brother!
- For real?
- Yeah, my brother.
- I thought I'd seen him before.
- What the heck?
- For real?
- Why didn't you tell me?
(LOOKS AWAY)
Remember, he's a guest.
- Okay, set down your bags for a sec.
- Nice to meet you!
Come on guys, get excited.
Let me hear you!
Yay!
- Hold on, how many do we have?
- Four, five…
Yeah, that's everyone.
- Fantastic. Okay, then.
- They're here.
We'll start with the B&B orientation.
- All right.
- Let's keep it short and sweet.
Come this way, please.
You can put your bags down
and come this way.
THEY FINALLY STEP ONTO THE YARD
They must be a couple.
I think so. There's another couple
here somewhere.
You guys,
I can't believe my brother's here.
- Your brother?
- Yeah, my little brother.
I'm so nervous. Oh, man.
- Must be awkward for you.
- Watch your step, please.
Yeah, it's so awkward!
Why on earth didn't he tell me?
It's a nightmare.
Imagine if my sibling showed up?
I wanna go home.
All right then, everyone,
please come this way.
- Look at that! Is that a stage?
- Here we go.
NOT A STAGE, A PODIUM
JAE-SEOK'S B&B RULES!
UP FIRST: B&B ORIENTATION
STOMP, STOMP
- This isn't a army boot camp, is it?
- No.
Oh, my.
- Whoa!
- Is that the general's spot?
All right. Hello, everyone.
Welcome to Jae-seok's B&B Rules!
Yu Jae-seok!
Uh, everyone, please--
This isn't the place for that.
I'm serious. It's not that kind of place.
- Would the staff please join me up here?
- Yes, sir!
Okay, without further ado,
let me introduce the staff members
at our B&B, one by one.
First up, we have
Mr. Lee Kwang-soo here joining us.
MOSQUITO
So handsome!
- All right, next up…
- We love you!
All right, next up,
introducing our next staff member,
Mr. Byeon Woo-seok.
Hello, everyone.
FANGIRLING
Whoa!
He's good-looking.
All right, and next,
we have Ms. Ji Ye-eun.
Hi.
- We love you!
- Ji Ye-eun!
SHY
Okay. Before we move on,
I heard something shocking just now.
I hear Ye-eun's youngest brother is here.
Ye-eun's youngest brother is here. No.
- They look alike.
- They look like twins!
- No, but…
- Why is he here?
All right, first of all, as you can see,
it's a beautiful day today.
It's almost like the sky itself
is welcoming all of you
to Jae-seok's B&B Rules!
Just get a load of that sky.
So crisp! So clear and blue!
- He's giving school principal.
- I know.
With your new energy mixing in
with all this fresh air,
this couldn't be a better start
to Jae-seok's B&B Rules!
Thanks for joining us.
I sincerely welcome you all.
Welcome to Jae-seok's B&B!
- Okay. Uh, Mr. Lee?
- Yes?
- Keep it down. Thank you.
- I was just trying to hype things up.
DRILL SERGEANT + HYPE MAN
All right, first of all, the B&B rules
aren't anything special. They're simple.
B&B ORIENTATION ORDER
2. B&B RULES
Earlier, I texted some of you here
and learned your names.
But I don't know any specific details
about any of you.
- Ah!
- Oh…
At our B&B,
we won't ask questions
or pry into your personal details.
There's a difference between
starting out knowing everything
and getting to know each other over time.
I don't want us judging each other
based on some basic info.
When a bit of trust has been built,
you can choose to share
whatever details you want.
Not to pry, but someone here
is a chef, no?
But I bet there's a chef here.
You're in fashion, right?
- His body. It feels like he works out.
- Yeah.
Are you an athlete?
We won't necessarily ask questions
or pry into your personal details.
If you don't want to share,
you never have to.
All right, everyone. For our next order
of business, let's say the B&B pledge.
- This is hilarious.
- Please say it along with me.
Let's line up, guys! Everyone in line!
- Line up like this. Okay, we got it.
- Ah, you all remember.
- Nice.
- Okay, stand side by side.
In two rows.
IN 2 ROWS?
- Two rows?
- You got it. This is perfect.
- We got it.
- Sorry, in four rows. Four rows.
- Yes, four rows.
- All in four rows!
- We need someone here.
You can stand in the front. Great.
Stand so the head of the person
two rows in front is blocked.
Well done. You probably haven't stood
like this since grade school, have you?
- Yeah!
- The first time they're all together.
All right, then, let's get this started.
WRITTEN BY JAE-SEOK THIS MORNING
I AM MY PARENTS' PRECIOUS CHILD
Okay, everyone, please repeat after me
when I say "pledge." Okay?
- I pledge.
I pledge to live
by the following principles
during my time at Jae-seok's B&B Rules!
One:
The guest is king, and so am I.
In the past, it was always just
"the guest is king."
And we want to have that mind-set
when guests do arrive.
But I hope our guests show respect
and courtesy as well.
We're all precious at the end of the day.
"The guest is king, and so am I."
SILENCE
You can repeat "so am I."
- Okay.
The guest is king, and so am I!
So am I!
- Don't they wait till you're done?
- Right, when I finish, that's your cue.
How many times do I have to say it?
- Sorry, sir.
- We're sorry!
Okay, one:
The guest is king, and so am I.
- So am I!
- There we go.
- Two. I am--
- Two!
No, don't say two.
- Don't say two?
- We're out of sync.
- Could you be more specific?
- Yeah!
Two: I am my parents' precious child.
Precious child!
And so are you!
So are you!
I pledge that for two nights
and three days,
I'll hold nothing back, talk nonstop,
and play hard to my heart's content.
Sworn this October 2025
by all those present.
At ease.
"I'm my parents' precious child"
really hit close to home for me.
When he said, "Let's get this started,"
it was like all of a sudden
a switch flipped in me.
It felt like he was saying,
"Let go of everything and just have fun."
Ah, wait.
We have to clean all this up.
Did they have to pop so much?
All right then,
since we have all of you here,
and we have our team captains,
now is as good a time as any to split you
into your respective teams.
In just a moment, we're going to ask
all of you to make a choice.
Captains, please turn around and face me.
- We're doing this now?
- Yes. Just move back a touch, please.
Remember, this isn't a popularity contest.
It's just a matter of preference.
- Would you like to start?
- Yes, I'd like to.
- Okay, go ahead.
- Man, I'm nervous.
Hello, everyone. I'm Lee Kwang-soo.
(THANK YOU)
If you join my team,
I guarantee, start to finish,
you will have freedom!
You can chill!
You won't have to lift a finger!
That's such a lie.
Not with me! That's my promise to you!
Lee Kwang-soo! Lee Kwang-soo!
Lee Kwang-soo!
Next, Byeon Woo-seok.
Those were all lies.
But for real, though.
If you really don't want to lift a finger,
I'm your guy.
Trust me. I'll do my absolute best!
Byeon Woo-seok! Byeon Woo-seok!
He's lying too.
I'll make sure you don't work hard.
Plus, we'll have deep,
meaningful conversations.
Just team up with your little bro!
- Seriously?
- All right, are you ready?
Team captains, please turn and face me.
Now, choose the captain
you want to spend two nights
and three days with.
All you have to do is stand behind them.
Are you ready? Okay, start lining up.
- Who do you want?
- Definitely Kwang-soo.
- Who should we pick?
- You pick. It's up to you.
You want Woo-seok Hyung, no?
If you join my team,
I'll give you some money.
Can I say one last thing?
- I'm literally going to cry.
- Please make your decision.
And, captains, don't look back.
THIS WAY? THAT WAY?
- What should we do?
- Let's take him with us.
Let's take him with us.
TRYING NOT TO LAUGH
Ugh, what's happening?
I didn't think
we'd jump right in like this.
- Wow, if you only knew…
- Why? Is it brutal?
Is it brutal?
Final call.
Okay, ready to look?
Okay, captains, turn around
on the count of three.
- Oh, please.
- Okay, one, two, three.
YAY
- Wow, thank you!
- Lee Kwang-soo!
Set!
What?
Whoa!
Why are you here?
Seriously, what are you doing here?
- Your parents must be so proud of you.
- I hate this! Ugh! I…
Hold on, so this is your brother,
and they're his friends?
Yeah, these are my bros.
- Ah, they're your bros.
- Jealous.
Well, they've made their choice.
The team captains can't do anything now.
- So, five here… This team has?
- Six total.
Are there seven total?
Seven. Seven total.
I can tell you, he should be
the easiest captain to control.
- Why would my team control me?
- All right, everyone.
Like I said earlier,
it's time for an activity.
We're going to try something simple.
Nothing big.
- Captains, you've got to do well here.
- Okay.
Because the winning team
gets something special.
The team that finishes first will also be
the first to enter the accommodations.
- First pick of the beds!
- Yeah, let's do this!
- You get to pick your beds.
- We've got this.
- I believe in you.
- We got this, don't worry.
- Let's go!
- Captains, listen up.
- Yes, sir.
- Here's the game.
Starting now, the first captain
to successfully memorize
and say all their team members' names
will be the winner.
Given names only.
- Ah, this is easy.
- Woo-seok's an actor. He's got this.
- Your names.
- I'm Hyo-jung.
- Hyo-jung.
- I'm Seong-joon.
- Seong-joon. Hyo-jung, Seong-joon.
- Given names only.
- I'm Bo-ra.
- Bo-ra.
- Chae-lyn.
- Chae-lyn, Bo-ra.
- Bo-ra.
- Okay, this is so easy.
- Yeah.
- Hyo-ri?
- No, Hyo-lim.
- Jun-hyuk. Jun-hyuk.
- Jun-hyuk.
- Ae-yeong.
- I'm Eun-jung.
- If you're ready, please come up here.
- Hyeong-seon.
- I'm Bo-ra.
Hyeong-seon. Jun-seong.
- I lost it all.
- Hyo-lim.
- Hold on.
- Wait a minute. Focus.
- Our team's big.
- It's Jae-hyeong.
- We have the most people.
- Jae-hyeong.
- Given names.
- Jae-hyeong, Joo-hyun.
- Dong-kyu.
- Kyo-young, with a Kyo.
- Ah. Kyo-young. Kyo-young.
- Ka-ram.
- Jae-seong.
- Yes.
- Eun-tae.
Ah, Eun-tae.
- If you're ready, please come up here.
- Me, me, me, me.
- We have fewer people, so…
- Are you ready? Okay.
Dong-geon, Hyo-jung,
Seong-joon, Bo-ra, Chae-lyn.
Okay, Team Ye-eun, correct!
YE-EUN GOT IT ON THE FIRST TRY!
Okay, Team Ye-eun, correct.
(EVERYONE IS CHEERING,
EXCEPT FOR THE BROTHER)
- We don't have time for this.
- I know, I know.
- Ae-yeong--
- Jun-seong.
I'm really sorry.
I don't think I can do this.
- No, no, no. Don't give up.
- Don't give up.
- Okay. Byeon Woo-seok.
- He's got this. He's ready to go.
- Okay, Byeon Woo-seok. Ready, set?
- Come on, you can do it!
Ae-eun, Hyeong-seon.
- Ae-yeong.
- Okay, fail!
- Uh, Team Kwang-soo!
- Go ahead!
- Here goes!
Jae-hyeong, Jae-seong, Joo-hyun,
Dong-kyu, Gyo-za.
- Gyo-za.
- Okay, fail!
- Okay, you've failed.
- My bad.
What is she, a dumpling?
Ae-yeong, Hyeong-seon.
- You still at it?
- Jun-hyuk.
- Try again, Woo-seok.
- I memorized them all! Let me go!
All right, so…
- If you're ready, go ahead.
- Hyo-lim, Ae-yeong, Hyeon-seon.
Wrong! Okay, fail!
I'll go!
Jae-seong, Jae-hyeong, Joo-hyun, Dong-kyu,
Ka-ram, Eun-tae, Kyo-young.
- Correct!
- Let's go!
Lee Kwang-soo! Lee Kwang-soo!
We're not last place!
No, I… Well, this is hilarious.
It's okay, we'll just sleep out here.
We'll sleep right here.
No. No way.
You don't have to sleep here.
We have lodging for everyone.
- You can pick first. We'll sleep here.
- It's okay, it's okay.
Everyone, here at Jae-seok's B&B, we have
all kinds of activities just like this.
I know you're curious about them.
Do you feel the excitement yet?
Let's get it!
EXCITEMENT THROUGH THE ROOF
Okay, so for bed selection,
Team Ye-Eun will go first,
followed by Team Kwang-soo
and then Team Woo-seok.
All right, then.
As I mentioned earlier,
I hope your stay here
is safe, comfortable and fun.
Go make lots of great memories.
Congratulations on checking in.
JAE-SEOK'S B&B RULES!
NOW BEGINS!
Do we pick our beds now?
- Before that, take a quick look over here.
- Okay.
Check this out.
Wow, this is really nice.
We are the ones who have to clean.
TRACES OF EARLIER CHAOS (?)
It's actually pretty easy.
But this is pretty nice, huh?
It's so nice.
FINALLY SEEING THE WATERFALL
Everyone, here's the waterfall.
- Wow! Amazing!
- What is this?
I love places with water.
I honestly love the whole vibe.
Even the waterfall
with the bean bag set up in front of it…
The scale of everything was huge.
It was at least ten times bigger
than what we expected.
This is nice!
You can have some coffee
and read books here too.
- Can we get in?
- Oh,
it's probably best not to.
- Oh, okay.
- I see.
Wait, guys. I wouldn't recommend going in.
- Got it.
- No washing your face here either.
You can read books here.
Or if you've got work to do, do that.
- Wow!
- Nice!
All right, come this way, please.
Over here, we have a place
where we can chill.
This is where we can hang out, chat a bit.
And this is the stage where we'll do
some activities we've prepared for you.
Check it out!
THE DOME TRANSFORMS!
A blazing hot Saturday night.
THE ART OF CUTTING LOOSE
You are a gift from the heavens
- Some of you like to work out, right?
- Yes.
Here's the gym.
I mean, an outdoor gym
is the dream, right?
Something you only get in California.
CALIFORNIA VIBES (?)
And over here…
- Wow, snacks!
- Wow!
All of this is free.
Free snacks! Yeah, let's go!
- It's a snack bar.
- Whoa, amazing! Yeah!
INSIDE THE FRIDGE
Yeah!
ICE CREAM GALORE
Oh, he's good.
That's the reason
he's Korea's number one host.
KOREA'S TOP MC'S PERFORMANCE ART
All free!
You can eat as much as you want.
Yay! It's free!
Yeah, that snack bar… I loved it so much.
And over here,
this is where you'll be dining.
I'm dying to see this.
SCURRYING
B&B DINING AREA
Scarf it down. Enjoy! Enjoy!
- Thank you for the food.
- Delicious.
GROUP MEAL SERVICE SYSTEM
At our B&B, you're guaranteed three
meals a day. So don't worry about that.
ALL THREE MEALS PROVIDED
Sounds good.
We're off duty.
- I love this.
- I love that I don't have to cook.
Man, look at the rice.
It's steaming already. Wow!
I'm hungry.
- Oh, I smell cooked rice.
- Comes with a rice cooker.
- This B&B comes prepared. Yes.
- Wow, I love this!
Oh, right. I could
definitely have something to eat.
Yeah, I'm hungry. So hungry.
All right.
Everyone, it's time to check out
the lodging.
What do you say? Shall we grab
our bags and head over now?
Sounds good.
We'll help move most of the stuff,
so don't worry.
STAFF WILL HELP MOVE THE LUGGAGE
You can leave your bags here for now.
Leave them here for now.
Okay.
All right, everyone.
Finally.
This is where you'll stay
for the next three days.
Finally.
I'm so curious.
NOW, THE BIG REVEAL
What is this?
Whoa!
Wow, really? Here?
WIDE-EYED
Come on in.
Come on in, come on in.
You know what?
I'm just glad that they seemed satisfied.
This is so nice.
LOOKING AROUND
Hold on, that's not a room.
Are these the beds?
IS THIS THE DOOR?
Oh, do we sleep up there? For real?
Do we sleep inside this thing?
- What?
- Do we sleep inside here?
All right. Everyone,
take a good look around first.
This is really nice.
Now, as for where you'll be sleeping…
WHERE YOU'LL BE SLEEPING!
- For real?
- No way!
Oh, that's awesome!
No way. Hold on.
There were these things
that looked like closets,
so I thought, "Oh, maybe they'll pull out,
and we can take the bedding
out from there to sleep."
But then I saw the wheels… I was shocked.
It's a sleepover!
ACK!
I definitely wouldn't have
thought to sleep in a school auditorium.
But I like it. It's new!
VERY ORIGINAL
WHY DID JAE-SEOK CREATE
ALL THESE FACILITIES?
In our day to day, life can get
pretty hectic and draining, right?
I wanted this B&B to be a refuge,
the kind of place where you could just
be happy and enjoy yourself.
A place you can return to in
your imagination when things get hard.
Like in cartoons or movies,
someplace like that.
There are even outlets
for your chargers! Let's go!
Does this open? Wow.
We can put our stuff in here.
- There's a light too.
- Really?
What's this?
- This whole place is state-of-the-art.
- I wanna scream it's so nice.
- Nice, isn't it?
- Seriously, I'm screaming.
We really put a lot of thought into it,
my staff and I.
- This is amazing.
- Yeah? Does this look okay?
TOTALLY SATISFIED
- Do you like it?
- Yeah!
- We should hand out towels now, right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Ah, the towels.
- Oh, towels.
- They're handing out towels. Nice.
When you use them all up,
feel free to ask for more.
- And here…
- Yeah?
…we have these special slippers
for you to wear.
- Can we put them on now?
- Go right ahead.
- Our names are on them.
- Wow!
PERSONALIZED FOR EACH GUEST
- Awesome.
- Joo-hyun, Bo-ra.
- Next up…
- Wow.
- They're so cute.
- Yeah, so cute.
Here are your towels. Yeah, two each.
You can use them and take them home.
Thank you. We can take them home. Nice.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, two each.
All right, now that you've all received
your towels, as mentioned earlier,
- let's start with Team Ye-eun.
- Okay.
- Go ahead and choose. Wherever.
- Sure.
- Over here?
- They're heading to the end.
- They want the ones by the bathroom.
- I'll take the one over here.
- I'll take this one, then.
- I thought you'd take this one.
- Team Kwang-soo, you're up.
- Okay.
To be honest, I might snore, so…
I'll take the corner spot,
if it's okay with you.
By all means. I'm good with that.
Does anyone else snore?
Oh, that's nice.
Everyone's being considerate.
The snorers volunteered
to take corner spots.
If it's hard, we'll roll it out for you.
- Want some help?
- Yes, please.
Sit tight.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, wow!
- Hey, there's a towel on your bed.
- Is there?
- Yeah.
- What towel?
Number 23. Look.
Wait, what's that?
Looks like a gift.
A GIFT?
What the…
- Just ask.
- What should we say?
- Let's ask about it.
- Excuse me.
Could you come here, please?
Oh!
Oh, that's our little surprise!
- It's our little surprise.
- Right.
MY LITTLE SURPRISE
- It's a surprise we prepared.
- Did you win the surprise gift?
- No, it's Dong-geon.
- Oh, Dong-geon?
Nice, Dong-geon!
Ye-eun worked really hard on that.
- Seriously?
- Hey, congratulate him.
YOU AGAIN…
Can someone else switch with me?
Someone else take it.
- No, not a chance.
- No way.
No switching spots! Number 23!
- Ye-eun put so much care into this.
- Man…
Ye-eun put the rose,
she made that heart with the rose petals…
Man, this is so funny.
- Go congratulate him.
- Yeah, go say congrats.
Yeah, I guess I should.
Thank you, thank you.
I'll go get my stuff. Okay.
All right, now, uh,
you'll need some time to unpack, right?
- Yes.
- You can do that now,
while we go and prepare
the meal for you all.
- We'll be eating shortly.
- Okay.
You guys hungry?
Right. Of course.
Oh, we forgot to mention this earlier.
- Yeah?
- What is it?
- Uh…
- Hyung.
What are you…
- So the thing is…
- What is it?
…you'll get three meals a day
for the next three days.
These meals will be prepared
by the captains and myself.
Since we run this B&B, your meals
and safety are our top priorities,
and we will do our absolute best.
That said, I can't guarantee anything
about our cooking skills.
- Oh, that's okay!
- Please just keep that in mind.
- It's all right.
- You're okay with that?
Yeah!
- Meals are guaranteed, no matter what.
- Got it.
But I can't guarantee
that you'll like them.
- We like everything.
- Are you sure?
Okay, let's move on, then.
- We have a suggestion box here.
- Okay.
If you have any suggestions,
write them down and drop them in.
Later on, we'll collect them,
and we'll do our best
to accommodate what we can.
Also, you'll find
the registration form here.
Feel free to just fill in the basics.
All right, everyone, you can bring
your bags in and unpack now.
Okay.
All right, so everyone fill out that form
and get some rest.
We'll let you know when the food is ready.
- Okay.
- And leave a suggestion!
All right, wish us luck!
- I think I'm spent for today.
- What?
Really.
I'm beat.
After I introduced myself,
I was totally done for.
Woo-seok.
Hey, you know what?
Scratch that. We're just getting started.
Hey.
Check the rice.
Is the rice done?
- Wait, it's turned off.
- What?
Should we open it?
Whoa!
- Looks good, doesn't it?
- It looks pretty good. Careful.
- I think it's good.
- Besides, we've got toppings.
- Yeah, this is good.
- It is a bit…
Put some rice here.
Let me taste it. Put it here.
That's good. Just a little bit.
OUCH, IT'S HOT
Oh, just hurry up and try it.
PICKING IT UP AGAIN
FAIL
I bet it's really hot.
- We don't have time for this.
- Okay, okay, I'm trying it.
- How is it?
- Want some help?
- Yeah.
- It turned out well.
- Wait, are you sure?
- Let's keep going.
But what are we serving this with?
SO FAR, ALL WE HAVE IS RICE
We're making deopbap with gochujang.
I don't know if this will ready for lunch.
Man, we should've prepped earlier.
Hold on.
Please wait a minute
while we connect your call.
- Hello?
- Ah, yes, hello, ma'am.
Do you think we could get about
25 servings of bulgogi to go?
- We'll make it right away.
- Oh, great. Then we'll head over now.
Ma'am, sorry to ask,
but do you grill it for us, or…
- No, we can't grill it for you.
- Ah, all right.
Then we'll just pick it up as is.
Please pack it to go. Thank you.
- We grill it ourselves.
- We have to grill ourselves.
Or should we grill it
and serve right away?
- We'll do it quick.
- Okay.
What else do we need to buy? Eggs?
- Fried eggs?
- Eggs?
- Gim?
- Gim sounds good.
Let's just buy some gim and eggs.
- Then Ye-eun and Woo-seok?
- Yeah.
- You two stay here and get that going.
- Got it.
Kwang-soo and I will go.
SUDDENLY FEELING RUSHED
Gosh.
Here we go. Man, this is stressful
all of a sudden.
We'll stop by the supermarket
and get the eggs first.
Eggs. Kim… Kimchi.
Okay.
Wait, what about dinner?
Let's just get through lunch first.
But honestly, at his rate,
I feel like we're just gonna be cooking
meals the entire time we're here.
We'll have to cook first thing.
We'll have to cook, go to bed,
then do it all over again.
Wow.
- Hello.
- Hi, there.
- Um, feel free to take a look around.
- Oh, okay. Thank you.
- No problem.
- Whoa, he really is handsome.
- Right?
He's super handsome.
Everyone seems settled in.
"Things you want to do at the B&B."
Mmm… talk all night?
I want kimchi bokkeumbap. Kimchi jjim too.
EVERYONE IS FILLING OUT
THEIR FORMS
Unni, what do you… Oh, my gosh!
- Oh, man!
- I forgot how handsome he is.
Hi, everyone.
HAS A KNACK FOR STARTLING PEOPLE
Anyone need anything over here?
Wow, look at him. He's so pretty.
- Anything at all?
- Shouldn't you be cooking?
- Food, right.
- Yeah.
- We're hungry.
- We're working on it.
But it's going to take a little while.
So if you're really hungry,
you should just feel free to grab
- something from the snack bar.
- Sounds good.
And, of course, if you have
any questions or anything…
Oh, so these slippers are
just for indoors, right?
- Yeah, just indoors.
- We shouldn't wear them to the bathroom?
Yes, I think that would be best.
FOR A GUEST TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM
1) TAKE OFF SLIPPERS
2) CHANGE INTO THEIR OWN SHOES
3) SWITCH BACK INTO SLIPPERS
INCONVENIENT
It might be a little inconvenient,
so I'll look into it.
- Okay.
- I'll check on it and let you know.
- Okay, thanks.
- You're the best, Woo-seok!
Thanks.
Who's that?
Byeon Woo-seok.
Hey, Woo-seok.
- Hyung, um, we got a complaint.
- Already?
HEART DROPS
So, we have everyone wearing
indoor slippers, right?
- Right.
- But since the bathroom is outside,
I think they find it
a little inconvenient.
- Ah-ha… I see.
- What should we do?
We could buy bathroom slippers.
They sell those at the supermarket, right?
- Right. We'll buy some extra slippers.
- Yeah, we'll buy some bathroom slippers.
Okay, got it.
See? There's always something.
- That didn't even cross our minds.
- Yes, exactly.
Wearing the same slippers
in both might feel a bit…
It's because that place
used to be a gymnasium.
Right, of course.
- Man, I'm starving. Oh, boy.
- Yeah, me too.
We haven't eaten yet.
CURRENT TIME 12:00 P.M.
I mean…
- Yeah?
- …this is a B&B, right?
But other than eating and washing dishes…
What?
Well…
we need time to actually do stuff.
First off, let's just focus
on getting food on the table.
Man, we're pressed for time.
Okay.
- What time is it?
- Five past 12:00.
- If we move fast, we can eat at 1:00?
- Yeah, let's move fast.
LET'S AIM TO SERVE FOOD
IN 1 HOUR!
Kimchi.
- The kimchi we had last time was good.
- It was over there somewhere.
Huh? Oh, here it is.
Where?
What did we have last time?
That kimchi was good.
Just buy whatever.
- This isn't it?
- No.
- Got it.
- But, Hyung, this is…
Yeah?
We need to buy 25 servings of the kimchi.
- This is just…
- For crying out loud.
WILL THIS BE ENOUGH
FOR 25 SERVINGS?
Man, this is…
- Okay, this is it.
- And you thought we could run a B&B?
What's next?
How are we supposed to do this?
How are we supposed to survive three days?
I've never fed
20-something people in my life.
- I mean, this is ridiculous.
- Hey, Kwang-soo. I see eggs.
Is this much kimchi enough?
Oh, God.
Hey, Kwang-soo.
- That should be enough, right?
- Okay. No, wait.
Gim, gim, gim!
NEXT UP, GIM
Hey, hey, Kwang-soo.
I've never bought this much
at a supermarket before.
- Hey, look at all this, man. Whoa.
- Hey, Hyung.
Hurry up.
- What's next?
- Slippers.
Oh, boy.
- Where are they? Right here.
- Oh, there they are.
- We need at least ten of these, don't we?
- If not more.
BACK IN THE QUAGMIRE OF NUMBERS…
But if it's for the bathroom,
we need at least 20.
Don't you think that's too many?
If it's one per person,
then we'd have to write names on them.
- Sounds like a hassle.
- Just buy them.
- You sure?
Wait. Come on, listen to me.
People don't pee at the same time.
They don't all…
Okay, fine. Let's go.
Let's just buy this many.
Oh, we need this.
For the coffee.
If we're going to put coffee out,
we'll need something to…
What if we use this?
An electric coffee pot.
But if we get that,
then we'd have to clean it.
Then we can just clean it.
We can just clean it!
Do you know how much work we already have?
No, I mean, we can split tasks
and have one of us clean it.
Here, gimme those. You bring that over.
- Did we get everything?
- Yeah, we got everything on the list.
- Good.
- Hold on.
Oh, I'm sorry. It's a lot.
No, it's fine.
- Oh, thank you.
- No problem.
- Carry the fragile items.
- Cash or card?
Oh, that's right.
- Hyung.
- Sorry about that.
Get it together, man.
I'm all over the place. Gimme a slap!
GET IT TOGETHER
I'm really all over the place.
I'm out of it.
I can't get it together.
I'm not even joking.
- We need lunch by 1:00 at the latest.
- I don't think we'll make it
- by 1:00.
- Just go.
Hello, ma'am.
We ordered some pork earlier.
- Oh, the order. Come this way.
- Where is it?
- Please come this way. Give me one sec.
- Smells great.
- Of course.
- Wow, that smells so good.
Man, I'm exhausted.
Kwang-soo, look, there's coffee.
Thirty servings.
TIME FOR A CAFFEINE BOOST
Oh, man.
- This is nice.
- It is.
- Thank you, ma'am.
- Goodbye.
We need to wrap this up by 1:00
or 1:15 at the latest, right?
Yeah, we can try.
Hey, how's it going?
What have you been up to?
- We're decorating the board.
- Oh!
It's kind of turned into a contest
over who decorates
their team captain's name the fanciest.
- Oh, wow.
- We went all out.
So cute. I love it.
I love mine.
Really?
- We've taken a ton of photos.
- Wow.
Wow!
DONG-GEON, HYO-JUNG,
SEONG-JOON LET'S GO!
AE-YEONG, EUN-JUNG,
HYEONG-SEON, KOSONI
Wow, it's so nice out.
Twenty.
Whoa!
Are you sure you're doing it right?
Oh, my mom. Hello?
Hey, Mom.
You know where Dong-geon is?
Mom, he's here at the B&B.
I was so surprised to see him here.
I guess he applied
because he wanted to come.
Yeah.
Seriously, him being here
is stressing me out.
Wait, Mom, here he comes. He's right here.
Why didn't you tell Mom anything?
Who submitted you?
I did, but I didn't know you'd be here.
You didn't know?
No.
SHRINKS
(GUEST ALERT)
- You really didn't know?
- I didn't.
- When did you find out?
- Uh, when the article came out.
- Did you interview?
- Yeah, in the summer.
- And you said you were my brother?
- No.
I didn't know it was your show.
Really?
Do you know what time
we'll be having lunch?
It should probably be
in about 40 or 50 minutes.
Oh, sure.
- You might wanna grab a small snack.
- Got it.
Hey, Kkoedori.
- I love this stuff.
- Yeah, that cooler is totally stocked.
Great. You had this?
It's good.
You eat junk food?
Yeah, I love it.
- So you really eat snacks?
- I love snacks.
Oh, really?
You don't seem like the type.
I try to eat well, but I work out too.
So if I eat more than usual,
- I'll work out a little longer.
- Right.
AFTER THE SMALL TALK,
STRAIGHT TO DOING DISHES
- You're doing the dishes now?
- I can't believe it!
Huh? What?
- I thought you'd be cooking.
- He must not be the cook.
Oh, no, I mean…
Everyone's out… buying some stuff.
I'm going to cook later.
- Later.
- You got this.
- Good luck.
- All right.
AFTER THE GUESTS LEAVE
MAKES A CALL RIGHT AWAY
- Hello?
- Yeah?
- Hyung, there's a big problem.
- What?
They think
we're actually cooking everything.
- Yeah, of course they do.
- Listen.
Don't say anything unnecessary.
Let's go with that.
- Don't overthink this.
- I didn't say anything.
Just focus on one thing:
We're providing them
with a delicious meal.
That's all they need to know.
(THOUGH IT MAY BE PREMADE)
I'm not telling you to lie.
Just don't say anything unless they ask.
- No, I won't. I didn't say anything.
- Okay, good.
Good. We're headed back.
So where is everyone now?
They're all outside.
They're just walking around and stuff.
Then I'll drive the car all the way inside
so they don't see anything.
Yeah, that's better.
It'll look less suspicious.
- Let's keep it natural.
- Yeah, you're right.
We're here.
- Drive in as far as you can.
- Okay, I got it.
Nice and easy.
- I'm gonna pull in there and back up.
- Wait, the dining area's packed?
- Oh my gosh, they're all outside.
- Oh, man.
- I bet he was really freaked out.
- That's crazy.
Hey look, they're here!
- Huh? They went out?
- They went grocery shopping.
Looks like they're back
with the groceries.
Oh, I see.
So then, that means they haven't
even started cooking yet, right?
I guess so.
They're looking over here. Careful.
Tell you what.
I'll turn the car around and back up.
If they look this way, the game is up.
They're still looking.
WOO-SEOK SNEAKS UP AND WAITS
- We bought gim!
- Hang on.
I'll cover it with this.
THE GIM SHIELD
They're coming, they're coming.
- They're coming, they're coming.
- Do you need any help?
No, it's fine, it's fine.
Just stay put. No, stop.
- You can help us later.
- You're a good guy, Dong-geon.
Just stay put over there.
We're all good here.
- We'll ask for your help very shortly.
- Okay, let us know.
Just rest for now.
I mean, it's a B&B, after all.
- Lunch will be ready soon!
- That's right.
- All done.
- Why are they hanging out right there?
I can't wait to see what they make for us.
- Did you guys eat something?
- Oh, yes.
Ah, that's great. Communal slippers.
For your convenience
when going to the bathroom.
- So, I bought these for you guys.
- Just what we needed.
Do me a favor and put them out front,
will you?
Thank you.
CURRENT TIME 12:50 P.M.
It'll be ready soon.
It'll just be 25 minutes,
then we can eat, okay?
They seem really hungry.
I know. They keep circling around
the dining area like vultures.
- I'm hungry.
- Yeah, me too.
- I'll start on the eggs right now.
- Okay.
I'll start grilling.
RICE, GOCHUJANG
SAMGYEOPSAL,
FRIED EGG, KIMCHI, GIM
Which oil should I use? Olive oil?
Anything. Just use anything.
- Speed is the most important thing now.
- Okay.
PICKS OUT A COOKING OIL
AT RANDOM
We should set out the dishes too, right?
Don't you think?
GOCHUJANG BULGOGI HEAD CHEF
TURN ON THE STOVE FIRST
Whoa, this is legit.
BOOSTS HYDRATION
BEFORE OFFICIALLY COOKING
- Whoa, hey!
- Huh?
- Oh, my goodness!
- Oh!
WHITE SMOKE IS RISING
FROM THE WOK
- Oh, my goodness!
- Oh!
Whoa, hey!
Oh, my goodness!
Everything's fine!
Kwang-soo, hurry up.
STARTS GRILLING
AS IF NOTHING HAPPENED
Oh, no!
ALL HE DID WAS PUT MEAT
IN THE PAN
AND NOW IT'S CHARRED BLACK
Wait a second. I'll do it.
What's going on?
It's nothing.
Why was it doing that? Why was it on fire?
- This batch is burnt.
- Aren't you supposed to use that?
I don't understand.
This much is okay.
GOCHUJANG SAMGYEOPSAL,
THE DISASTER EDITION
- That won't work.
- What? Why?
What's wrong? Oh, shoot.
- Don't worry, Hyung. I got it now.
- Move, move.
It's because its marinated.
Oh, it's the sauce. Hold on.
I'll just jump in and help.
- It's a two-man job.
- Yeah, I got it.
Be quick!
Man, what are we gonna do?
This burns so fast.
THE GOCHUJANG BULGOGI
KEEPS BURNING
The gochujang sauce
is making it hard, right?
Oh, no. What now?
The sauce keeps burning
before the meat's even cooked.
We'll just have to keep wiping as we go.
Something's burning. I hope they're okay.
THE BURNT SMELL
REACHES THE GUESTS
Uh-oh.
Uh, don't worry.
We still have plenty of time.
- Smells good, right?
- Yeah.
Just a little longer.
- We've been prepping since yesterday.
- Oh, boy.
It's all good.
What time is it?
Now? It's 1:07.
- Yeah, 1:07.
- Yeah.
- He said 1:15.
- Think it'll be ready by then?
TIME LEFT UNTIL SERVING
Wait. It's burning too much.
How are we going to cook all this?
STILL A MOUNTAIN OF MEAT LEFT
This isn't gonna work.
AND THE MEAT KEEPS BURNING
I was so flustered.
I wasn't sure what to do
since the meat kept burning.
None of us had ever experienced
anything like it.
This isn't gonna work.
- Man, this is bad.
- What's wrong?
- Well--
- Are these burnt too?
- I think the fried eggs are cooked.
- I know.
You have to add oil.
I did add oil, but…
At this rate,
we'll be in tears by dinnertime.
Wow. I never thought
I'd find myself crying here.
36 HOURS LATER
Don't be surprised if I disappear
in the middle of the night.
18 HOURS LATER
- Where did he go?
- Jae-seok!
- I don't believe it.
- This is all my fault.
We have to start prepping dinner
right after this.
What are we gonna make?
I don't know.
Let's not think about that right now.
This feels hopeless.
How are you supposed
to get this evenly cooked?
Let's stay calm.
Just breathe and stay focused.
Let's get it together.
Stay calm, everybody.
It's fine not to use any oil.
- No oil?
- I think that's why it's burning.
Cook it on low. Don't use high heat.
Ye-eun, it's done. Look.
- Yeah, it's done. I think that looks good.
- Just don't add oil.
So you cook it over low heat like this…
Turn it up a bit. Medium should be fine.
Kwang-soo, put it on medium.
It was burning because of the oil.
Right, because pork belly already has fat.
That's right. Who added the oil?
You need some oil so it doesn't stick.
Oh, yeah, that's it.
It smells really good.
- Looks done. Hey, it's done.
- It's done?
- Woo-seok, you just focus on the eggs.
- Oh, okay.
Wow.
There's a lot here.
Although they look a bit rough.
- It's a mess, isn't it?
- Hey, it's fine. We'll have to make do.
Man, I should really learn how to cook.
- Let me try cooking the meat just in case.
- Are you done with that?
No, I just feel like I'm not doing
a good job with the eggs.
- Should I do the eggs?
- Yeah, sure.
Maybe it's because
you're on a cooking show, Ye-eun.
- Right. I am on a cooking show. Yeah.
- You're surprisingly calm.
True.
- Can I get that tray over here?
- I'll wash it and hand it over.
- Oppa, you need more eggs, right?
- Yeah, I think I'll need more.
PROFESSIONAL KITCHEN WORKER
HAHAHA!
I think they're starting
to make friends already.
Yeah, and their energy is amazing.
- Yeah, totally.
- They're so excited.
You're so unhinged!
GUESTS FULL OF ENERGY
GUESTS ON ENERGY OVERLOAD
Hey, hey, hey!
- How much longer could lunch take?
- I know, right?
There was a bunch of smoke before.
It's a mess.
- There was, right?
- Let's go check it out.
Okay!
CURRENT TIME
(5 MINUTES PAST PROMISED TIME)
But we still have a lot left.
I think this should be
around ten servings.
Ten servings done.
But if they come eat now,
ten servings will be gone in no time.
- Low heat, like before.
- Okay.
Should we say 1:30 sharp?
Is that too early?
- Should we tell them?
- How about 1:40?
1:30 should be good.
- Are you sure?
- 1:35.
No, 1:30. Hold on a second.
Okay, tell them
we'll start serving at 1:40.
- So, 40 past?
- Yeah, stir-fried pork bibimbap.
- What's the real name of the dish?
- Stir-fried pork.
It's gochujang bulgogi, no?
Gochujang pork.
Just call it gochujang stir-fried pork.
If we call it gochujang bulgogi,
they'll know we bought it.
Hey, just call it meat-deopbap.
Meat-deopbap it is.
- That sounds good.
- Meat-deopbap?
- Yeah.
- We'll start serving at 40 past. 40 past.
- Okay. Yay!
- Gochujang.
What was it again?
Gochujang bulgogi-deopbap?
Meat-deopbap?
The menu's meat-deopbap. Yep.
Ooh, sounds tasty.
- We can't have any more delays.
- I know. We're good.
Hyung, how's this?
- Looks done.
- Yeah, looks good.
- It looks good.
- Okay, almost done.
- You're good at this Mr. Byeon.
- Thank you.
Doesn't this feel like a shoulder workout?
Yeah, my shoulder blades!
My shoulders and wrists are killing me.
- The forearms.
- Yeah, forearms too.
Wow, cooking's hard
even with prepped ingredients.
If it were three to four servings,
we'd be done already.
- Exactly.
- It'd be no big deal.
But cooking for a group of 20 people
is no easy task.
Still, seeing them enjoy the food
will feel so satisfying.
- Right.
- A good meal makes all the difference.
- It's really true.
- Right, right.
- That's right.
- I just hope it tastes good.
- Same here.
- Wow, it's almost full.
Hey, I think we can finish by 1:40.
Yeah, I think so.
SET UP THE GIM
SET UP THE WARMER
TODAY'S MENU
GIM, FRIED EGGS
Hey, it's 1:40.
- It's 1:40.
- Is it time to eat yet?
- Can we go in now?
- Forty? Yes, come on in!
Did he say we could go?
- Let's go, let's go!
- I'm so hungry.
- Finally!
- You must be hungry.
- Okay, it's self-serve. Dig in.
- Oh, it's buffet style.
- Wow. Amazing.
- That looks great.
- Whoa, that looks so good.
- Yeah.
Enjoy the barbecue. Help yourselves.
Enjoy your meal.
Scoop some rice, and then you can
top it off with a fried egg.
Oh, eggs.
Can't go wrong with that. It's foolproof.
- I'm kind of feeling nervous.
- Yeah, of course you are.
- What if it's bad?
- Here goes.
Wow, this looks so good.
Yeah, it looks delicious.
Refill coming right up.
INSTANT MEAT REFILL
Have we got a show for you!
- That's a lot of rice.
- Did I take too much?
PILED HIGH
Help yourself. Don't be shy with the meat.
- Okay, will do. Thank you so much.
- Copy that.
What time are we having dinner?
Huh? Sorry?
Whenever you want.
No, I just want to adjust how much
I eat depending on the timing.
Don't adjust a thing.
Eat as much as you want.
- We'll be cooking one way or another.
- Dinner will be served around 7:00.
Okay, so around 7:00.
At our B&B, we've got
all three meals covered.
Don't worry.
JAE-SEOK'S B&B PROVIDES
THREE MEALS A DAY!
- This egg.
- Yeah.
- It's runny.
- Yeah, it is.
Wow.
The meat's good!
Enjoy your meal.
SOME OF THE GUESTS
SUDDENLY LEAVE
Why are they leaving already?
Why are they walking out mid-meal?
KWANG-SOO IS DISPATCHED
Who left? Oh, for drinks?
Let's get two and share. I want Fanta.
They went to get drinks.
Oh, for drinks?
I thought they walked out on us.
FALSE ALARM
How's the food, Dong-geon?
- I haven't eaten yet.
- Oh, you haven't eaten yet.
Man, this meat.
PRAYS BEFORE EATING
THE MEAT COOKED BY HIS NUNA
- Wow, it's so good.
- Thanks for the food.
- Is it good?
- Yeah, for real.
- Oh, thank goodness.
- I mean it.
It's good.
Mmm.
Is there anything you'd like for dinner?
- Meat.
- Yeah, meat.
You want more meat?
MORE MEAT?
- Some soup would be nice.
- Soup. Thought so.
- Ooh. Doenjang-jjigae too!
- All right.
Oh, kimchi-jjigae.
They're saying it'd be nice
to have some soup.
Sure. That makes sense.
Okay, everyone. Listen up.
Since we had meat for lunch, we should
have something brothy for dinner, right?
- Yes, sounds good.
- Yeah!
- Wow, the weather is so nice today.
- It really is.
- It's so nice.
- Wow, what a day.
Man, it's so beautiful out.
THE FOOD TASTES GOOD
Anyone want more meat?
- Oh, this is great. Have another egg.
- Oh, thanks.
The meat is really good.
- Yeah.
- It's good?
Who made the marinade?
The marinade…
Well, I mean, you know,
Ye-eun here is on a cooking show, and…
- Right.
- …you know what that means.
- What are we doing after lunch?
- Sorry?
- What's after lunch?
- Oh, after lunch.
First, we'll give you some free time,
let you relax a bit, and digest.
- Okay.
- We'll have around one activity a day.
It's nothing special.
But we have some surprises in store.
Hey, Dong-geon. Dong-geon.
- Don't talk to him.
- How was it?
- How was it? Be honest with me.
- It was fun.
- Huh?
It… It was fun?
- He's asking about the food.
- Oh, the food. It was delicious.
I hear he was just
as surprised as we were.
He signed up for the show by himself.
His sister was announced after.
- Yeah, that's right. I had no idea.
- Exactly.
- If you'd known, would you have signed up?
- Of course not.
It's the same for her.
I'm sure she feels the same way.
It's nice to see you're enjoying the food.
- It's so good.
- Oh, really?
- It tastes great.
- Thank you.
- It was all a team effort.
- I feel so proud.
Seeing you enjoy the food we made
brings us such joy, you have no idea.
Now then, lunch?
- Solved.
It was great.
- Now start dinner!
- Let's go!
HOW WAS THE MEAL?
- Satisfactory. Yeah, I'm satisfied.
- Did you vote yet?
You can choose "unsatisfactory"
if you'd like.
But I mean, he's standing right there.
It was good.
- I'm voting blue!
- We vote blue, we vote blue!
Geez, these kids are too adorable!
They all said it was satisfactory.
- Oh, yeah.
- Hey, there's one yellow.
THE GUESTS ENJOYED THE FOOD
DESPITE IT BEING A BIT SALTY
So-so.
It was a little bit… a little bit salty.
The sauce, I mean.
It's a bit salty, right?
- Just a bit.
- A bit.
Even so,
I could tell it was made with
so much care, so I really enjoyed it.
THE GUESTS ENJOYED THE FOOD
DESPITE IT BEING A BIT SALTY
- We should have a bite.
- I want some.
STAFF LUNCH BREAK
Whoa, I feel like I'm gonna faint.
- My mind's gone blank.
- All I care about is the food.
- Seriously.
- I'm totally drained.
- Yeah, same.
- It's so draining.
Oh, boy. Phew!
FINALLY SITTING DOWN
AFTER THREE HOURS
Thank you for the food.
I feel better already.
JAE-SEOK TAKES A BITE
(VERY TASTY) (DELICIOUS)
AND TOPS UP ON HYDRATION
- Guys, this is good.
- It's good.
- Wow, it's really good.
- So hungry.
- It's great.
- Me too.
But remember what I said earlier?
If we start off with something this good,
what do we serve next?
For dinner?
Yeah.
What do we have written on there?
Let's see.
B&B DINER TODAY'S MENU,
MENU WISH LIST
We've got to take at least one suggestion.
Hyung, it says samgyeopsal, malatang,
muksabal,
budae-jjigae and sujebi.
- Okay, budae-jjigae.
- For real?
No, but budae-jjigae is…
But you know what you're really good at
is kimchi-jjigae.
Hyung, I'm dead serious
right now. I-- I just can't.
KWANG-SOO'S KIMCHI-JJIGAE
- We can add some ham to it.
- I think that's all we need.
Do we need anything else?
Should I make gyeran-mari?
Man…
You and your eggs.
- I'm just all about the eggs.
- Were you an egg in a past life?
You're the main chef for dinner tonight.
And you.
- Gyeran-mari.
My heart just skipped a beat.
Wait. Who's that over there?
Oh, Kwang-soo's castmate.
He was in that movie with you.
- Hello.
- Hello. Oh!
- Hey, man!
- Whoa!
- Do you know each other?
- We shot The Pirates together.
- Yeah.
- Hey, man.
- Hello.
- How have you been?
- Welcome aboard.
- Thank you.
- Right over here.
- Hello.
Wow, the sky's lookin' pretty.
JOO EUN-TAE: ACTOR
LEE JAE-SEONG: ACTOR
STARING
Guys, we gotta keep the show moving.
That alone is stressful.
All they've done is arrive,
unpack and eat. That's it.
Some walking around too.
Let's do that quiz game later.
- We'll tell them about it in a second.
- Okay.
- The Cushion Quiz!
- Yay!
Correct!
All right!
YU B&B'S FIRST ACTIVITY
It's finally time for today's activity.
Okay, let's gather in the gymnasium
around three o'clock.
JAE-SEOK'S B&B RULES!
Should we do the dishes now?
We'd better get some
of it done now. I'll take care of them.
For ingredients? Who's buying them?
Another grocery run?
Later, at three o'clock.
- But if we go out to buy the ingredients…
- We have kimchi.
Oh, but we need coffee too.
They're gonna want coffee.
Oh, coffee…
Can you go buy some?
Today?
We have to buy it today? Wait.
Should I make the announcement first?
That we'll meet at 3:00?
I don't know about that.
3:00 might be too early.
- We only have 30 minutes. Yeah, 30…
- It makes no sense.
- We need to rest too.
- Hyung, just five minutes.
Seriously… I mean, we haven't
even been able to sit down.
We're kings too.
Is that how you treat a king?
- My apologies.
- We're working like dogs!
- What do you mean, we're kings?
- Hold on. The guests are coming.
- He sounds upset.
- Yeah.
Okay, let's not let
our internal complaints get out
- and reach our guests, shall we?
- Got it.
Let's make this promise
to each other, okay?
Criticizing is fine between us.
But the guests shouldn't have to hear it.
Of course. I'll keep that in mind.
We at least need time to brush our teeth.
Forget about it.
NO BRUSHING TEETH
- When you talk, talk like this.
- Oh, come on.
I've still got pork stuck in my teeth.
I have to brush my teeth right now.
- No time for brushing. No brushing.
- No brushing.
A B&B THAT WON'T EVEN GIVE YOU
TIME TO BRUSH YOUR TEETH
- What about this?
- Yeah?
Let's have the losing team
later do all the dishes.
- If there's around ten people…
- Right.
The more people there are,
the faster it goes.
- Ye-eun.
- The more, the faster.
How about we bring Dong-geon
and his friends over?
Nice!
Okay, sounds good.
Hey, Dong-geon!
- Hey, Dong-geon!
- Yeah?
- Can you and your friends come over?
- Coming.
- Oh, boy.
- Thank you.
SUCCESSFULLY LURED
It's kind of adorable seeing them play.
Hey guys, our schedule is
a bit tight today.
So if you don't mind,
since it looks like the three of you
aren't doing much important right now…
- You said we had free time.
- Oh, I sure did.
So why don't you help, uh, do the dishes?
- Sure, we can help.
- Let's go!
He did offer to help
with the dishes earlier.
- All right, this is great.
- Oh, then you guys can do the dishes.
We've got so much else to do.
- We do.
- All good, we got it.
- You stay here and help out.
- Okay, sounds good.
SCRUB, SCRUB
THE STAFF STARTS CLEANING UP TOO
Should we help with the stuff
they put down there?
- Help them how?
- I don't know.
- Don't they need to be washed?
- Give it to us. We'll do it.
What are you doing?
No, seriously, we're fine!
- Oh, come on.
- Come on, just this one. Please?
It's just one thing.
This is the last time you're helping,
you hear me?
- Jae-seok's B&B isn't like that, okay?
- Okay, got it.
IT REALLY ISN'T, BUT?
It's easier when we all pitch in.
Right, it's all about
doing things together.
- Oh, please. Don't do this, guys.
- I'll give it a go.
Where on earth did you find guests
that are such angels?
THE STAFF ARE WORKING HARD TOO
THE CLEANUP IS ALMOST DONE
Working together is faster, huh?
I swear, next time,
we do it all ourselves.
All right everyone, let's all
gather around at half past.
Al right everyone, let's all gather around
at half past.
We'll have a discussion about what time
we all wanna get up in the morning.
- Got it.
- Yeah, sounds good.
FOOD IS POWER
LET'S SCARF IT DOWN
CURRENT TIME
40 MINUTES UNTIL GATHERING
DISHES FOR 22 PEOPLE: DONE
Hold on, let me go get the coffee first.
Hyung, while we're out picking that up,
should we buy dinner ingredients too?
You have to. You're the main chef,
and you're Mr. Eggs,
so the three of us should head out soon.
Tomorrow's breakfast? What about that?
I bought some bread, so let's keep
breakfast simple with toast and cereal.
If we have a toaster,
we could make grilled cheese.
Sorry?
But toasters only make
two slices at a time.
Ye-eun, since your brother's here and all,
can you organize things for us?
- Me? Uh… Yes.
- Yeah, that all right?
- Good.
- I'll just use the bathroom first.
- Make it quick.
- Okay.
TO-DO LIST: GROCERY RUN FOR
DINNER & BREAKFAST, BUY COFFEE
How is this day going by so fast?
LOADS THERMOS DISPENSER
FOR THE COFFEE
Okay, everyone, I'll see you all at 3:30!
Okay!
Oh, boy. This is killing me.
OFF TO BUY COFFEE & GROCERIES
Oh!
I forgot the others.
FORGOT TO BRING MAIN CHEF
& MR. EGGS
Guess I have to turn back.
I'm so scatterbrained.
I must be possessed or something.
(U-TURN)
Hey, Kwang-soo!
Yes, Hyung?
- Hey, Woo-seok!
- Yep!
Let's go.
I loaded the coffee dispenser.
HEADING OUT FOR REAL
Just now, I loaded that thing in the car
and just took off by myself
without thinking about it.
I got to here and suddenly went,
"Oh, I left them behind."
It's only day one. I'm worried for us.
I can't believe it's already 3:00 p.m.
THEY'RE ALREADY EXHAUSTED
AFTER LUNCH
This is kinda therapeutic in a way.
How so?
Because you can't think.
Ah, I see.
We really have no time to think, Woo-seok.
That's true.
Minced garlic, kimchi,
ham, sausage.
THE ONLY THOUGHT ALLOWED:
GROCERIES
What do you think?
Should we make two different types
of gyeran-mari or just one?
And do we need any condiments?
Yeah, we need ketchup.
I swear, you blink, and it's time to eat.
So, on our way there, we'll drop off
that dispenser at the café…
- Okay.
- …ask for 20 liters of coffee, and…
Ah!
I hope they don't give us acidic coffee.
That's just your preference.
- Right, it's not just for me.
- You're making it sound like a crisis.
- We'll drop off the dispenser.
- Yeah, drop it off here.
Hello. Hello.
- Thank you.
- We can pick up the coffee later.
Okay, let's do that.
Do you think we should wear name tags?
Yes. What's your name?
- Jae-hyeong.
Thank you.
Ji Dong-geon.
Honey, come sit with me.
Oh, you two.
I'm so curious about your love story.
I'm so curious about everyone.
- Did the three of you come together?
- Yes.
- I gotta know.
- I don't wanna say.
Yeah, same.
- You three are siblings, right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, they're siblings.
They're siblings. One here, one there.
I have two brothers.
How are so close with your siblings?
- You're one of three too.
- Right.
- You're the eldest.
- We're totally…
- Are there any perks for us?
- I don't think there are any.
- Yeah, we don't have any.
- Honestly, there aren't any.
- Did you get the ham?
- We have it here.
We got it.
Kwang-soo, did you get the garlic?
I got the minced garlic.
We got everything.
Wait. Did you get the cereal?
- Oh, I forgot.
- Man…
What kind of cereal should we get?
We should get a few different kinds.
Some people really like this stuff,
you know.
Uh…
HESITATES
Almond-free? Since some people
might have nut allergies.
TIME FLIES
WHILE HE'S IN A DILEMMA
Now we just need to get milk.
- Okay, okay. Milk?
- Yeah.
HESITATING AGAIN
Uh-oh. No lactose-free milk.
No lactose-free milk!
We should probably go
with regular milk then.
Right. Some people might… Wait.
- Oh, there's the lactose-free.
- This should work.
Why are we getting milk again?
Oh! For the cereal.
Is that everything?
Tuna, tuna!
- We need tuna. Tuna.
- Oh, shoot.
It won't taste the same
if we don't add tuna.
- Let's get the mild one then.
- Okay.
Oh, we need ketchup.
Right, ketchup.
- Now is that everything?
- That's everything.
They'll probably want some fruit.
- Huh?
- Try some of these.
This would be perfect
to leave out for everyone.
- Could we try one too, please?
- Sure.
Tasty, right? They're good.
Hey, let's get these.
- Let's get two.
- Two boxes.
- Thank you, ma'am. Here.
- You're welcome.
Man, I really wanna go home.
Oh, I wanna go home so bad.
Oh, boy, Kwang-soo.
- Oh, Woo-seok.
- Yeah.
We gotta go pick up the coffee.
- Right.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Yep.
THEY PICK UP THE COFFEE
Hey, get a load of my staff!
They really know what they're doing, huh?
- Okay, there we go.
- My goodness.
Time really flies out here, huh?
It's already 4:00.
Should we call everyone over?
I don't think they're back yet.
Did they go far?
We said 3:30, but it's already 4:00.
It takes around ten minutes, right?
From here?
- Right. What, what, what?
- Huh?
What, what, what?
It's leaking a bit.
- A lot?
- No, just a little. It's fine.
So how should I make it?
Yeah, I guess a wok
is different from a frying pan.
- It's because we're going uphill. Whoa!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
THIS TIME, THE LID ESCAPES
- No! No!
- Did it all spill?
JAE-SEOK'S B&B RULES!