Okay, hang on a minute.
Someone get the wet wipes.
- You know what, just go.
- I don't have any wipes.
- It spilled 'cause we're going uphill.
- Check in there.
- Whoa.
- Whoa, hold on.
THE LID POPS OFF
- No!
- Did it all spill?
- It's okay. I got it.
- It's okay?
- Keep going. Keep going.
- Hey, Woo-seok. Hold on, we to--
- Whoa!
2ND ESCAPE
OH, OH, OH, OH
Hey, careful, Woo-seok.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
- Are we good?
- It's fine, we're good.
- We're good?
- Yeah.
- It didn't spill?
- No.
PROTECTING COFFEE WITH LEFT HAND
- You can keep going. We're good. No.
- It really didn't spill?
RIGHT HAND SECURING WATER
All right.
CRAWLING IN FEAR
Shoot.
THEY'RE IN A HURRY,
BUT THINGS AREN'T GOING THEIR WAY
Shoot.
It's all uphill from here.
I think we're good to go
a little faster, hyung.
So tell me, where are you all coming from?
- We're from Cheongju.
- Cheongju?
You said you're from Seoul, right?
- Mapo in Seoul.
- Yeah, we're from Seoul.
She looks like a typical Seoul girl.
She's pretty.
- Yeah, definitely.
- What do you mean?
You're in a different league over there.
- No, come on.
- I'm serious.
Really.
I'm so glad they're cooking for us.
I was like, "Do we have to cook?"
- I was seriously worried.
- Yeah, I thought we'd have to cook.
It's better that we're not.
- I'm already sad thinking about leaving.
- I needed the break.
Yeah, I'm already sad,
and it hasn't been a day yet.
REASONS FOR APPLYING:
TAKE A BREAK FROM WORK & KIDS
You guys want a group photo?
AND MAKE UNFORGETTABLE MEMORIES
WITH HYEONG-SEON AND AE-YEONG
- I think I got us all.
- I think you did.
- Good one.
- Yay!
DAY 1
LET'S GO!
Nicely done!
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
DANCING OUT OF NOWHERE
- What was that move? That was awesome!
- Do it again.
THE FLASHY MOVES KEEP COMING
What?
NAME: KIM HYO-LIM
REASON FOR APPLYING:
I NEVER GOT TO GO ON AN MT
IN COLLEGE BECAUSE OF COVID-19
- Save it.
- All right, I should stop.
That's how we do.
THINGS YOU WANT TO DO
AT THE B&B: DANCE INITIATION
What are you doing?
We can't show all the moves yet.
- Right, not yet.
- We can't show them yet.
Not yet. I'm sorry.
- We're here.
- Whoa.
16:04 - ARRIVAL AT B&B
- They're back.
- We got coffee.
- Should I deliver it?
- Yes, please.
Okay.
Took you long enough.
- 'Cause we had to pick up the coffee.
- Oh.
SETTING UP A COFFEE STATION
- O.M.G.!
- They're in season right now.
AND TANGERINES THEY BOUGHT
ON IMPULSE
- Should I go get the others to come over?
- Tell them we have coffee.
- And tangerines if anyone wants some.
- Coffee and tangerines.
We've got coffee and some tangerines.
- Good catch.
- Whoa!
IN FULL MAFIA MODE OVER HERE
- How about we come back with some coffee?
- Okay.
- Wow, that was close.
- Are you a coffee person?
RECEPTION PREP, ORIENTATION, LUNCH PREP,
COFFEE PICKUP & GROCERY RUN
Here, we've got coffee.
Oh, coffee! Oh!
CAFFEINE BOOST
Oh, that's good.
Uh, shall we all sit down and talk here?
- Yeah.
- Let's do it.
- Bring it in.
- Let's have a seat.
TIME TO SET B&B RULES TOGETHER
So, it's nothing major,
and I don't really mind,
but I've been thinking
about what you call me.
I think "sir" sounds
a bit too authoritative.
- If anyone has another idea…
- "B&B Owner"?
"B&B Owner?"
- B&B Owner?
- Yeah, B&B Owner.
- Interesting.
- Not that. He doesn't like it.
Yeah, definitely not.
No, "B&B Owner" is good, but…
- "Director"?
- "Chief"?
- "Village Chief"?
"Village Chief"?
- Chief Yu.
- Yeah, Chief Yu.
- Oh, Chief Yu.
- Chief Yu.
Team Woo-seok! Team Woo-seok!
- Nice one.
- All right.
- That's our captain.
- "Chief Yu", approved!
"CHIEF YU" CHOSEN
AS JAE-SEOK'S TITLE
Okay, Chief Yu it is.
Now this is a B&B, and I know everyone
goes to sleep at different times.
- Yes.
- Some go to bed early,
others go to bed late.
But as a basic rule,
the lights go out at 10:00 p.m.
- That's great.
- That's way too early.
For the wake-up time,
six would be too early, right?
Yeah, that's too early.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- Way too early.
- But 8:00 a.m. would be too late.
- Too late.
- Yes, it's too late.
- Way too late.
- It's too late.
So what time is left?
- 7:00 a.m.!
WAKE-UP TIME IS 7 A.M.
AT JAE-SEOK'S B&B
All right then. Let's meet over there
at seven tomorrow morning,
before anyone gets ready for the day.
Wait, so meeting at seven,
or waking up at seven?
- You said "wake-up time."
- Well…
Hey! We're on the same side.
Why'd you embarrass him like that?
You feel good about yourself?
I just think
the information should be accurate.
- Don't you agree?
- Okay.
- Don't you see I'm on your side?
- Kwang-soo, sit down.
- I'm trying to support you.
You know what?
Woo-seok is absolutely right.
What? I was defending you.
- Hey, I was the one defending you.
- Kwang-soo, listen.
UPSET
SMUG
By 7:00 a.m., do I mean
meeting outside at seven
after your morning routine?
Or do I just mean waking up at seven?
I mean the alarm will go off at seven.
ALARM WILL GO OFF AT 7 A.M.
We're here in the mountains.
The morning air is going to be amazing.
You should take it in
and enjoy it while you're here.
That's right.
You'll all be going back to your lives
on Monday, right?
Some of you will be going back to work.
- Right.
- Oh, you're not?
YOU'RE NOT WORKING?
- Don't dig too deep.
- We don't know their circumstances.
I said I wouldn't pry
into your personal details, but…
Oh, you're not? That kind of question…
- I'm sorry. I apologize.
- He keeps asking about our jobs.
- I said I wouldn't pry.
- I know you're curious, but ease off.
You're in fashion, right?
- Hyung, hyung.
- Fashion?
SQUEEZE, SQUEEZE
- Look at his outfit.
- Don't dig too deep.
Whoa.
His body. It feels like he works out.
- Big muscles, huh?
- Are you an athlete?
Maybe he's trying to hide it
with his sweater.
IS JAE-HYEONG AN ATHLETE?
I mean, I can tell. His lats are huge.
- Yeah, his lats.
- Do you work out?
- Like, for my job?
- No.
- Why are you prying?
- Hyung.
You're digging again.
- Why are you prying?
- Who's prying? Who's prying?
No, I just…
- You keep asking questions.
- I didn't ask more than once, did I?
- I mean…
- He never gives up.
Why are you so hung up on this?
I won't ask. I won't ask.
- What does it even matter?
- So don't ask me about my job either.
- All right? Don't ask me either.
- We're not curious at all.
So, I'm hearing
that some of you are interested
in playing one of my famous quiz games,
like we do on variety shows.
- Something like that.
- That's right.
This one's a classic,
so some of you might remember it,
and some of you might not.
The Cushion Quiz!
- The Cushion Quiz!
- The Cushion Quiz.
YAY
Wow, this is gonna be awesome.
It's the one where you yank out
the cushion.
- The Cushion Quiz!
- The Cushion Quiz.
Back by popular demand…
- The Cushion Quiz!
A SEGMENT FROM THE POPULAR
2000'S VARIETY SHOW
A MIX OF ENTERTAINMENT, GENERAL KNOWLEDGE,
SPORTS, AND NONSENSE QUESTIONS
AFTER THE QUESTION IS READ, THE FIRST
TO RAISE THEIR CUSHION GETS TO ANSWER
Wait, I know, I know.
- The Cushion Quiz!
- This is awesome!
That's the one!
I've always wanted to play this game.
- I knew it! I knew it!
- The Cushion Quiz!
Doing the Cushion Quiz
is a dream come true.
This is exactly what I signed up for!
All right, so,
we've got the three teams here.
- You all have your team captains…
- Yeah.
…so it's going to be
a team-versus-team competition.
But it's not much fun without some stakes.
Right. There should be a prize.
All right, so, everyone…
do you see now why your beds have wheels?
NO WAY
- Seriously?
- Really?
- No way.
- We're rolling them outside?
The whole bed.
- Are you serious?
- Seriously?
We'll bring it down here.
ANOTHER REASON WHY
THE BEDS HAVE WHEELS
THEY'LL ROLL THEIR BEDS OUT
AND SLEEP OUTDOORS
You'll sleep with the sky as your blanket.
He looks excited.
You'll bring it down here.
You mean we'll roll the whole bed outside?
The team that comes in last
sleeps outside. Yeah, exactly.
And the team that comes in second
has to make lunch.
TEAM THAT COMES IN 2ND
MAKES LUNCH TOMORROW
Oh, like Hit and Miss.
Do you all agree?
- Yes!
All right then. Without further ado,
I present to you the Cushion Quiz!
LET'S START THE CUSHION QUIZ
RIGHT AWAY
Let's get inside, shall we?
Oh, I'm getting nervous. I'm so silly.
CUSHION QUIZ
- I really don't want to come in third.
- That can't happen.
I can't be sleeping outside. No way.
- Let's do this! Let's win.
- Whatever it takes.
This is gonna be fun.
Come on up here.
Huh? Up there?
- What's up there?
- The stage?
- Is it big enough?
- Wait, what?
- What?
- Huh?
- No way.
- Okay, what now?
AS THE CURTAINS OPEN
A SECRET DOOR APPEARS
- What is this?
- What? No way!
- Huh? A secret door!
- Oh my.
- Come on up, everyone.
- He wants us to come up. Let's go!
- Really?
- Oh, my gosh! What is this?
Oh, man. No way.
THE SECRET DOOR OPENS TO
WOW
Incredible!
THE HIDDEN SPACE IN JAE-SEOK'S B&B
THE GAME ROOM
After spending some time with the guests,
it seems like a lot of them wanted to try
the quiz and experience it for themselves.
Well, that's what
this place is all about, right?
So I figured this would be the perfect
opportunity for them to give it a go.
- Look over there! Those are the cushions.
- You know it!
The delivery box!
There's the delivery box!
All right, everyone. The captains
will pick their team uniforms now.
We've got different colors.
Come on up and choose.
THE CAPTAINS PICK
THEIR TEAM COLORS
- We'll go with white. It's cute.
- White, it is.
All right, you can bring them over
to your team.
Okay, we'll go with black.
BLACK FOR TEAM KWANG-SOO
- The jersey's so cute.
- My size.
ORANGE FOR TEAM YE-EUN
Captains, we've got name tags.
You put it on the back.
Woo-seok.
This goes on the front.
It rips right off.
- No name tag ripping.
- Okay.
I'm nervous.
I usually start the Cushion Quiz with…
Ding-dong-ding-dong
Bam-bam-bam, bam-bam, bam-bam
Ba-ra-bam-bam, bam-bam
Bam-bam, bam-bam
All right, this is how
we kick off the game,
so let's all do it together nice and loud.
- Great, okay.
- Yeah.
I know this is what you've all been
thinking about since coming to my B&B.
The game you've all been dying to play.
Ding-dong-ding-dong-ding
- The Cushion Quiz!
- Quiz!
Bam-bam-bam, bam-bam, bam-bam
Ba-ra-bam-bam, bam-bam
Bam-bam, bam-bam
Sit down, sit down.
Hyo-lim, take a seat.
Sit down. All right.
- Okay, enough.
- Guys…
Wait. A second. I think we need to do
something about Hyo-lim.
- I mean, did you see those dance moves?
- Hyo-lim.
Okay.
- Everyone.
- Did you see that?
Guys, there's no need to show off.
Just go with the vibe and enjoy it.
You can't do…
JUST GO WITH THE VIBE
Yeah, that's way too much.
This isn't a club, Hyo-lim.
We're all supposed to enjoy this together…
- Understood. Got it.
- …but if you do that,
it kind of intimidates everyone else.
Who does this at a B&B?
- Hyo-lim, that was great…
- Right.
- …but there's a set move actually.
- Yeah.
- This. This is it.
- Keep it at this level.
- Got it.
- Stick to it.
- Let's just keep it fun and exciting.
- Sure.
- All right.
- This is what you've been waiting for.
- Are we starting over?
- We're starting over?
- We should start over.
Okay.
All right?
I know this is what you've all been
thinking about since coming to my B&B.
The game you've all been dying to play:
- the Cushion Quiz!
- Quiz!
Bam-bam-bam, bam-bam, bam-bam
Ba-ra-bam-bam, bam-bam
Bam-bam, bam-bam
Bam-bam-bam, bam-bam, bam-bam
Ba-ra-bam-bam, bam-bam…
All right. Good. Sit down, sit down.
- Wow.
- Nice.
- This was great.
- That was good.
You know, I've done this
plenty of times with celebrities,
but I'm pretty sure this is actually my
first time doing it with non-celebrities.
HE'S NEVER DONE THIS
WITH B&B GUESTS
I mean, we just met today.
The majority of us
are basically strangers,
and that's a first for me.
All right, everyone.
Let's start the Cushion Quiz!
No, wait, we haven't done
the cheering contest.
ALMOST FORGOT
THE CHEERING CONTEST
- Let's do a quick cheering contest.
- He thought we forgot.
Chief Yu, do we get something for winning?
You get good energy, for one.
- It's just for fun.
- It lifts your spirit.
Yes, it's about the spirit.
So, which team wants to go first?
How about Team Ye-eun?
- Team Ye-eun.
- Okay. I hope this works.
All right,
let's start the cheering contest.
- Team Ye-eun, you're up first.
- Here we go.
- All right, good.
- They look cute.
Just like K-pop idols.
(GLANCING)
I'm so embarrassed.
Ye-eun and Dong-geon, let's go!
Let's go!
Ready, go.
Drink some milk shake
Let's get hyped, yeah!
Make it special
- Let's go!
All right, next up is Team Kwang-soo.
- Let's hear it.
- Right then left.
Hyung, you have to look cool at the end.
Try to look cool, seriously.
- I can't wait.
- Try to look cool.
One, two, three, four.
Earring Prince Lee Kwang-soo!
Bling, bling, bling, bling, yeah!
EARRING PRINCE
Hey, that was good.
- Earring Prince. Wow.
- Go, team!
- Yeah!
Wow. Earring Prince, huh?
We'll call him EP.
"EP"?
EP? Why would you shorten it?
No, I mean, we're all
someone's precious child.
That's right. Wow.
Hey, EP.
The earrings look great on you.
All right. Next up is Captain Woo-seok.
LAST UP IS TEAM WOO-SEOK
One, two, three, four.
There's no turning back!
Team Woo-seok is on attack!
Byeon, Byeon, Byeon, Byeon, let's go!
Actually, put Hyo-lim in the middle
and do that dance from earlier.
That's right, lets go. Front and center.
Yeah, this one.
Five, six, seven, eight.
There's no turning back!
Team Woo-seok is on attack!
Byeon, Byeon, Byeon, Byeon, let's go!
Hey, what's this?
I mean, wow.
This is amazing!
NEW SKILL ACQUIRED
Wow, that was so cool.
Well, all right.
Guys, you're all getting closer
to each other without even realizing it.
Things are getting more interesting now,
don't you think?
- Yes!
- That's the beauty of the Cushion Quiz.
Now, let's have one representative
from each team come up front.
- Yeah, I'll give it a go.
- Go for it.
Let's go! Come on, you can do it!
JOO-HYUN FROM TEAM KWANG-SOO
CHAE-LYN FROM TEAM YE-EUN
- Go, Chae-lyn!
You got this.
HYO-LIM FROM TEAM WOO-SEOK
We'll start with Chae-lyn,
Joo-hyun, and Hyo-lim.
Any category you want?
Entertainment.
All right then. The category is enter…
…tainment!
"Yu Jae-seok, Lee Hyo-ri, and Rain form
a musical and art collective known as…"
FLINCHING
- SSAK3.
- Yes.
All right. "Which of the following
is the correct title
- of their hit song?"
- Oh, you know this.
It's multiple choice,
so listen carefully before you answer.
Number one, "Here at the Beach."
- Number two, "Now at the Beach."
- Oh, I'm confused.
Number three, "Summer at the Beach."
Now listen carefully
or you might miss the right answer.
- Okay.
- Don't just assume
it'll be one of the last ones.
Number four,
"Back to the Beach."
Number five, "At the Beach Again."
- This is confusing me.
- I'm completely lost.
All right, Number six,
"Beach Again."
- Got it!
VOLUNTEERING TO ANSWER
ALMOST SIMULTANEOUSLY
Okay, Joo-hyun was a bit faster.
Joo-hyun?
Number six, "Beach Again."
Okay, number six,
"Beach Again and Again and Again."
6. "BEACH AGAIN AND AGAIN AND AGAIN"
He wasn't finished yet.
Don't fall into the trap.
"Again and Again and Again."
"And Again and Again."
- Do you get the game now?
- Okay, I got it.
- Remember?
- Yeah, I remember, I remember.
Okay, number seven,
"Beach Again."
- Got it!
What's your answer?
Number seven, "Beach Again."
Okay, number seven,
"Beach Again,
O-P-Q-R-S-T-U."
- Listen until the end, okay?
- He got you.
You have to keep trying though.
It even went up to 13 once.
That's my record.
Number eight,
"Beach Again."
- Got it!
- What's your answer?
Number eight, "Beach Again."
Okay, number eight,
"Beach Again,
Really?"
Oh, it's a question.
- It's stressful, isn't it?
- Yes.
Your daily life
is already stressful enough,
but now you're getting stressed out
in here.
- Yes. A little.
- All right, hang in there.
- Guys, hang in there.
- Okay.
Now, number nine,
"Beach Again…"
Got it. Number ten, "Beach Again."
- Oh.
- Good work.
- Let's go.
- Good call.
Wow, you skipped one.
Okay, number ten.
- Number ten.
- There's no number ten.
- Got it! Got it!
- What's your answer?
Number nine, "Beach Again"!
Number nine, "Beach Again." Correct!
9. "BEACH AGAIN LOL" (?)
- Oh, that was thrilling.
- It was.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Wow!
I threw out some bait,
- and Hyo-lim took it right away!
- Ah!
This is why I do this. This is why.
A THRILL HE HASN'T FELT
IN A LONG TIME
Man, that was great.
You having fun?
- Wow!
- This is what I'm talking about.
TEAM KWANG-SOO WINS ROUND 1
TEAM KWANG-SOO: 1
TEAM YE-EUN, TEAM WOO-SEOK: 0
Okay, next up…
How about the team captains this time?
Let's go, let's go!
THE TEAM CAPTAINS
WILL COMPETE NEXT
Let's do this.
- Let's go, Ji Ye-eun!
- Ji Ye-eun!
- Let's go, Woo-seok!
Earring Prince Lee Kwang-soo!
It's still early in the game,
so don't you worry.
Oh, I'm so nervous.
The category is General Knowledge.
- Oh, no. Wait.
- So, general knowledge question.
- Oh, no.
- You got it.
- You got this.
- Here comes a general knowledge question.
- Okay.
Hyung, I don't have any.
"The father of music is"…
- I know! Bach.
- Yes?
Bach, that's right.
- Whoa.
- Wow.
"If the father of music is Bach,
- then Kwang-soo's father is?"
- What?
- Me!
- Yes?
Lee Jong-ho.
Mr. Lee Jong-ho. That's right.
All right, now…
- Wait, what?
- Wait a minute.
Why are you asking about my dad
all of a sudden?
- Is that really part of the question?
- What?
- What's going on?
- It is part of the question.
It is part of the question.
DUMBFOUNDED
What does my dad have to do with…
- You didn't have to answer.
- Exactly.
- What?
- You didn't have to answer.
All right, now,
"Who is the father
of evolutionary theory?"
What? Evolution?
- You mean like apes and stuff?
- The father of evolutionary theory.
I have no idea.
All right, guys, you'll probably know
once you hear it.
Me! Me!
Yes?
Newton.
No. He discovered gravity.
- That was close.
- It's another English name.
- You're on the right track.
- How was that close?
- You got this.
- Me! Neuron.
- Yes?
- That's a type of nerve cell.
- Oh, right.
Good. Nice try.
- It was a good approach.
- Good try.
Here's a hint. His first name…
- Charles.
- Got it!
- Yes?
- Barkley.
Charles Barkley is a basketball player.
Oh.
- Me.
- Yes?
Charles Enter.
Not Charles Enter. No.
Another hint.
It will help you "Win it all."
- "Win it all."
- Oh!
- I got it.
Oh, I know this.
- Got it!
- Yes?
Allwin. Charles Allwin.
Wrong!
You're almost there.
- Oh, me!
- Yes?
Charles All-in.
- Not All-in.
- All-in?
- Me.
- Yes?
Charles Win-It-All.
CHARLES WIN IT ALL
Hang on, you're getting further away.
- Not it?
- It's not Charles-Win-It-All.
All right, here's a hint.
It's Charles something-win.
- He's so close.
- I know!
- Yes?
- Charles Darwin!
CHARLES DARWIN
- Correct!
- Yeah!
Earring Prince Lee Kwang-soo!
All right, it was "Charles Darwin."
- That was tough.
- Yeah, it was.
It's okay! It's okay!
- Charles Win-It-All!
- That was really good though.
Good job!
TEAM KWANG-SOO: 2,
TEAM YE-EUN, TEAM WOO-SEOK: 0
All right, now who's up next?
- Did you know it was Charles Darwin?
- Mm.
- You go.
All right, all right.
DONG-GEON STEPS FORWARD
TO RESTORE HIS SISTER'S PRIDE (?)
- Ji Dong-geon, let's go!
- Dong-geon, let's go!
Dong-geon, let's go!
Dong-geon, Jae-seong,
and Hyeong-seon.
The category is "Slang."
ROUND 3: NEOLOGISMS
- Nice.
- You should be good at this.
He's the youngest one up there.
Uh-oh.
- It's okay. You got this!
- There's still a chance!
- It's okay! You can definitely do this!
- Come on, let's go!
You're still young.
All right, here's the question.
In the phrase "Do you moshow or nishow?"…
What the…
- What's that?
- …what do "moshow" and "nishow" mean?
"Do you moshow or nishow?"
- What?
- Moshow?
MURMURING
Moshow and what?
- Moshow… Oh, hey.
- What?
I repeat,
in the phrase "moshow" or "nishow"…
Ah!
They're abbreviations.
What do moshow and nishow mean?
That's the question.
- I got it!
- Yes?
Morning shower or night shower.
"Morning shower" or "night shower"?
And what number answer is that?
All right!
Nice!
Good, good. It's multiple choice.
What's the number for
"morning shower, night shower"?
- Please say a number.
- Just guess.
Twice?
- Twice?
What are you talking about?
- Wait, twice?
- Oh, he means,
once in the morning
and once at night, so twice.
What are you talking about?
No, what's the number?
It's multiple choice.
All right, wrong. There's no "twice."
- Me!
- Got it!
- All right, your answer, Jae-seong.
- Number five!
Number five, what?
Morning shower, night shower.
Number five, morning shower, night shower.
- Correct!
- Whoa!
JAE-SEONG FROM TEAM KWANG-SOO
GETS IT RIGHT ON THE FIRST TRY
FACEPALMING
- Hey, Dong-geon, what were you thinking?
- Twice? What is that?
I mean, it's multiple choice!
The correct answer is number five,
"morning shower, night shower."
- Wait!
- Yes.
I think what Dong-geon meant was showering
twice, once in the morning, once at night.
I didn't understand.
You thought I was asking how many times…
Okay, so, showering twice a day,
Dong-geon must shower a lot.
I thought you were asking how many times.
DONG-GEON SHOWERS FREQUENTLY
All right, Team Kwang-soo
has scored three points so far.
That's right.
TEAM KWANG-SOO HAS WON
3 ROUNDS IN A ROW!
TEAM KWANG-SOO WINS ROUND 3
CURRENT SCORE
TEAM KWANG-SOO: 3,
TEAM YE-EUN, TEAM WOO-SEOK: 0
- You guys should try harder.
- No, we have to win.
Come on, let's go! Let's go!
Name all seven members of BTS…
- Me!
- …in five seconds.
- Five, four, three…
- Nam-joon, Seok-jin, Yoon-gi…
Five seconds are up.
Got it! Jin, V, RM, j-hope, SUGA…
- That sounded like "Chuga."
- Got it!
- Okay, go. Five…
- Jin, V, j-hope, SUGA, RM,
- Jimin, Jung Kook!
- You got it!
"What does this toast stand for?
Madonna."
- Madonna?
- Oh, I know!
- Yes?
- "Make it, do it and knock it."
That's correct!
TEAM WOO-SEOK GETS IT RIGHT
"Which of the following K-pop idols
is not a Korean national?"
- Got it.
- Your answer, Jun-seong?
Number seven, SANA from TWICE.
Correct!
TEAM WOO-SEOK'S JUN-SEONG
GETS IT RIGHT
So the score is now 1-3-2, yeah.
Nice going. Well done.
We have to get the next one.
- We got this.
- Yeah, we can't come in last.
All right, to change things up,
we're doing a team round next.
- Oh!
- Let's go! We got this.
Let's have four people from each team,
including the team captain.
The person in front calls out to start,
- then you answer in order.
- Okay.
This question is about naming capitals.
Naming capitals.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Wait.
- Can we switch players?
- No, you can't' do that now.
- Wait, time-out, time-out.
- Oh, no.
- You can't switch players now.
- Time-out!
All right, team captains,
please stay in front.
- France?
- Got it.
- Yes?
- Paris.
- Italy?
- Rome.
- Portugal?
- Al right.
TIME'S UP
- Lisbon.
- I don't know either.
- Lisbon. It's Lisbon.
- All right. A different country.
- Germany?
- Got it!
- Go ahead?
- Berlin.
Spain?
- Madrid!
- Too late.
Too late.
You answered too late.
Seriously, what do I do?
- Can we switch places now?
- What?
Can we switch places?
- Yes, you can.
- Oh, okay.
- I can't do it. Hey, guys.
- Wait, what?
- Unni, you're up.
- Oh, me?
- Hey, guys.
- Wait, what? No.
- You're good at this.
- No, no, no.
- We should switch places too.
- Right, we should switch.
- Someone good should be in front.
- You should stay up front.
- Can we switch players? Switch players.
- What?
You cannot switch players.
Oh, come on!
- I said no.
- Pretty please?
I said no.
Okay, that's a warning.
- I can kick you out.
- You can?
I can kick out anyone.
- Okay.
- All right?
Let's go, Jae-seong! Let's go!
BIG SHUFFLE COMPLETE
Let's go, let's go!
Captains, why are you all at the back?
We're giving them a chance to, you know.
They should have a chance to show off.
All right, good. Here's the next question.
Sweden?
- Got it! Stockholm.
- Yes?
- Poland?
- Finland?
POLAND, FINLAND?
What's he thinking?
- I'm sorry.
- What is this, telephone?
HE APOLOGIZES
AND SWITCHES PLACES
Oh, my gosh, it's so funny.
Poland, Finland. All right.
- I'll give you an easy one.
- Okay.
- Germany.
- Got it!
- Yes, go ahead?
- Berlin.
Okay, Berlin.
- Spain?
- Madrid.
Italy?
Oh, no.
TIME'S UP
Even I know this one!
- You know this one?
- Yeah.
- Oh, no.
- What's the answer?
Rome!
Why didn't I get that one?
Well…
That's so funny.
By the way, Woo-seok, why are you
so nervous about capital questions?
You're grinding your teeth back there.
He doesn't want to get busted.
- Poland?
- Finland?
WHEN EVERYONE ELSE WAS LAUGHING
- Come to the back. Let's go.
- What's the capital of Poland?
- Isn't Poland the capital?
- No!
What's the capital of Poland?
What's the capital of Switzerland?
(BANGKOK, BANGKOK!)
(ROME!)
WOO-SEOK WAS MORE NERVOUS
THAN ANYONE
He's afraid.
I'm scared I'll get busted.
You'll all find out how dumb I am.
- You're scared you'll get busted?
- I'm scared I'll get busted.
- Hey, I'll protect you.
- No, it's fine.
- You want me in front?
- You want to switch?
- I'll go to the front.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Jae-seong, move back one.
- I'll call out faster. Come here.
- Oh, all right.
All right, let's go!
- Yeah!
- Let's go!
All right, I'll give you another one.
An easy one.
- Dong-geon, just go for it.
- This is crazy.
All right.
- Greece.
- Got it!
- Me.
- Whoa, hold on.
Wow, Woo-seok was faster.
No, Dong-geon was faster.
That was so fast.
- All right, let's try again.
- He's got this.
All right. That was incredibly fast.
Sit back on it.
Sit back on it like Dong-geon.
- His knee.
- Make sure you stay seated.
Don't put your knee up.
Don't whip it out like a sword.
NO WHIPPING IT OUT LIKE A SWORD
Don't pull it out from the middle.
Don't pull it out from behind.
- How am I supposed to pull it out?
- From the side.
How am I supposed to pull it out?
- Pull it out from the side.
- Oh, from the side?
SUPER FOCUSED
- Portugal. Okay, go ahead.
- Got it!
- Oh, no.
- All right.
- Got it!
- Go ahead.
- Time's up.
- Got it!
- Go ahead.
- Lisbon.
- Spain?
- Madrid.
- Italy?
- Athens.
It's Rome!
No!
All right. All right.
Calm down. Wait a second.
- Okay, here we go.
- Hold on, time-out, time-out.
Rome!
Ugh! I must be out of my mind.
All right. Listen carefully.
Okay, we're listening.
- Italy.
- Got it!
- Okay, go ahead.
- That was fast.
- Athens.
- No!
ITALY, ATHENS
- Go, go! Dong-geon, go!
- Me!
- Go ahead.
- Rome.
- Rome. Spain?
- Madrid.
- Portugal?
- Lisbon.
Greece?
- Athens.
- Yes!
You got it!
TEAM YE-EUN
FINALLY GETS IT RIGHT
Yes, let's go! We did it! We did it!
Team Ye-eun gets a point.
Dang.
DEJECTED
- Well done.
- We've got two points now.
We got this.
So the current score is 2-3-2.
- This is insane.
- Wow.
- Totally insane.
- It's neck and neck.
Anyway, we can't keep playing forever,
so the team that gets
the next question right wins.
LAST QUESTION WORTH 2 POINTS
- And…
- A team round.
A team round?
- Yes, a team round.
- Yeah!
- All right then.
- A team round.
Well, ladies and gentlemen,
you've waited a long time for this.
- Next up is the Delivery Box Quiz!
- Quiz!
THE DELIVERY BOX QUIZ
I can't believe it.
Feast your eyes!
- Check it out.
- Awesome!
Yeah, sleight of hand. Here it is.
- Wow, it's been so long!
- You remember this?
Wow, look at those skills.
THE DELIVERY BOX MASTER
YOU MET AT A B&B
All right, everyone.
Take a close look at what's inside
the delivery box.
Call out to answer
when you know what it is.
First, let me check what's inside.
- We all get to look, right?
- Yes, you all see it together.
- We're all doing it.
- Get closer. Come on.
- Come on.
- Get close.
This is a team round, right?
Yeah, it's a team round.
All right.
Okay.
THEY LOOK LIKE…
We look like a dance crew right now.
DELIVERY BOX DANCE CREW
- It's too cramped.
- It's too crowded.
- Wait, hold on.
- Make room.
- That's the fun.
- I can't move.
We've got this much space.
It's like we're crammed into a tiny room!
There's no room.
But you're in the middle.
Can we pick our spots?
- We're sandwiched here.
- It's so tight.
OVERHEATED
Jae-seong, come here.
Sit in front of Ye-eun.
- No way.
- Okay, you can't do that.
- Why not?
- I can't?
- Okay.
Don't cross into another team's space.
- It's their space.
- Be careful, okay?
- Don't hurt yourselves.
Focus. Don't blink.
THEIR FATE DEPENDS ON
THIS ONE DELIVERY BOX
- This is driving me crazy.
- Over here.
- I can't see.
- Careful. All right?
This is what
I'm going to be doing. Like this.
- The bottom. Oh!
- Like this, like this…
- He's good.
- Like this.
Like this, like this…
And like this.
THIS IS HOW GOOD HE IS.
Wow, he's good.
This is the game that makes him
a living national treasure.
All right. All right.
Here we go.
Look closely.
OPENING IT JUST A CRACK
I didn't see it.
Hey, he's getting way too close!
Hey, come on.
That's too close, Kwang-soo!
That's cheating!
- It's just because he's tall.
- Okay, that's a fair point.
Totally fair. He's just really tall.
All right, guys.
- Get back.
- Okay.
DIALING DOWN THE HEAT
Get back!
That means you, Lee Kwang-soo.
PERSON OF INTEREST:
LEE KWANG-SOO
All right, look closely.
WHIRL, WHIRL
Oh, my eyes.
BOO
THE LIVING NATIONAL TREASURE'S
FANCY MOVES IN THE DELIVERY BOX GAME
ZOOM
THE BLAZING SPEED
OF THE LIVING NATIONAL TREASURE
ZOOM
- Oh, I know!
- Got it!
Got it!
- Oh, I got it!
- All right.
- I got it!
- Yes?
Go ahead.
A persimmon.
A DRIED PERSIMMON?
- Really?
- Is that it?
A persimmon…
That's correct!
A FRENZY OF EXCITEMENT
A persimmon?
Take a look.
- How did you catch that?
- I didn't see anything at all.
IT'S ME, A DRIED PERSIMMON
- Wow.
- Wow, that was fast.
SPEECHLESS
- Wow.
- All right then!
The winner is Team Kwang-soo!
TEAM KWANG-SOO WINS
- Wow, that was impressive.
- All right now.
- Amazing.
- Let's decide second place.
WHAT MATTERS IS
WHO COMES IN LAST
- Making lunch or sleeping outside.
- Sleeping outside.
- Next category: Korean movies.
- Okay, I'm really good at this.
Korean movies. Nice.
- Barefoot…
- Got it.
- Okay, go ahead.
- Gi-bong.
BAREFOOT GI-BONG
- Nowhere…
- To Hide.
- Mara…
- Tang?
What is it? Mara what?
MARATANG?
Oh! Oh…
You guys didn't know either.
Oh, "tang." Like Malatang.
- Scandal…
- I got it.
- Yes?
- Makers.
- The…
- Priests.
- Tae Guk Gi…
- Brotherhood of War.
- Memories of…
- Murder.
Deliver Us…
- From Evil.
- You got it!
TEAM WOO-SEOK: 2ND PLACE
THEY'LL MAKE LUNCH TOMORROW
Tonight's outdoor sleepers
are Team Ye-eun!
TEAM YE-EUN: 3RD PLACE
THEY'LL BE SLEEPING OUTSIDE
All right, Team Ye-eun.
Get ready to sleep outside later.
That wraps up the Cushion Quiz
we prepared for you
here at Jae-seok's B&B!
2 AND A HALF HOURS
OF FULL-ON CUSHION QUIZ FUN
Oh, that was fun. Second place.
- Good job, guys.
- I'm relieved.
Great job, you guys!
Aw, "Mara-tang" was hilarious.
- Come on, Seong-joon.
- "Mara-tang."
- It's Marathon?
- Really?
- Seong-joon.
- No, we did well.
- We did well.
- Great job.
- When else would we ever sleep outside?
- Exactly.
How does he do the delivery box?
I know, right? That dried persimmon.
He's so good.
- Yeah, he's really good at spinning it.
- Seriously.
What's the capital of Poland anyway?
Beats me. I still don't know.
Warsaw.
- Warsaw!
- Warsaw.
- Right. Warsaw, yeah.
Well, capitals aren't something
you usually…
- That's right. How would you know?
- Exactly.
- Poland was a tough one.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- It's cold. Oh, it's raining.
It's raining a lot.
It's raining pretty hard.
IT'S ACTUALLY RAINING
QUITE HEAVILY
That's correct!
2 HOURS 30 MINUTES AGO
THE SUN QUIETLY SET WHILE
EVERYONE WAS DEEP IN THE GAME
- Oh, it's hot.
- It's so hot out.
AND THEN IT STARTED TO RAIN
A QUICK CHECK OUTSIDE
IF IT KEEPS RAINING LIKE THIS…
Is it raining?
- Oh, yeah. It's really coming down hard.
- It's pouring.
Oh, it's raining!
WHAT IS CHIEF YU'S DECISION?
All right.
- Uh…
- It's raining hard.
It's raining pretty hard,
so I don't think you can sleep outside.
How about you make dinner instead?
- Make dinner?
- Sounds good!
- We'll make dinner!
- Guys, let's go make dinner.
- Okay.
Good thing it started raining, huh?
- We could've been in real trouble.
- We'll make a really good dinner instead.
Let's go.
- It's supposed to rain until tomorrow.
- I know.
Let's do this.
Budae-jjigae, budae-jjigae.
TONIGHT'S DINNER IS
SPICY SAUSAGE STEW
Wait, Kwang-soo is supposed to be
the main chef.
MAIN CHEF FOR SPICY SAUSAGE STEW
LEE KWANG-SOO
Is it just budae-jjigae?
Budae-jjigae and gyeran-mari.
- Oh, that too.
- Woo-seok said he'd make that.
GYERAN-MARI BY BYEON WOO-SEOK
It's still raining.
It's just a drizzle, but it won't stop.
- Woo-seok, check if that's enough rice.
- Is it too much?
I used even more, actually.
CONFIRMING THE AMOUNT OF RICE
Will these eggs be enough
for me to make gyeran-mari?
Oh, gyeran-mari?
- We'll do it together.
- Okay.
I'LL MAKE IT MYSELF!
Make it with him.
So, I'm the chef?
I'M THE CHEF
You need to use enough oil.
THE DUO WORKING THE PANS
- Yeah, add more oil as you go.
- Okay.
TWO LADLES OF WELL-BEATEN EGGS
So, do you like cooking?
- No, I don't.
- Oh, really?
- But I'm gonna have to start learning how.
- Yeah?
- What's happening?
- I'm taking lessons. I'm getting married.
OH MY
- No way.
- Yeah.
I'm actually getting married next week.
My fiancée let me come here.
THE GROOM GOT PERMISSION
TO BE HERE
So you're learning
so you can cook for your wife, is that it?
Yeah. I'm going to try.
She'll love that.
That's like every woman's dream.
(FLIPPING)
Whoa, that looks really good.
- Really?
- Yeah.
To be honest,
I haven't done this much either.
I just watched some YouTube videos.
- I just learned this from my mom.
- Really?
During the holiday.
You've got to keep
pressing it down, like this.
Oh, like this?
- Hey, you're getting better.
- He's actually really good.
- Yeah, we're both…
- It almost looks… Wow!
That's like something
you'd get at a restaurant.
RESTAURANT-QUALITY
Looks good. You're doing great.
- Kwang-soo, you're the main chef.
- Yeah.
THERE'S OUR MAIN CHEF
FOR THE SPICY SAUSAGE STEW
- Dong-geon, you're my assistant.
- Okay.
DONG-GEON IS CHOSEN
AS THE SOUS-CHEF
Kimchi, please.
Kimchi?
NONCHALANT DELIVERY
- Ye-eun.
- Yeah?
You could talk to him a little.
Don't be so cold all the time.
- Kimchi, remember?
- Where is the kimchi?
- In the fridge.
Dong-geon, I don't have to
spell everything out for you, do I?
Where else would it be?
Okay, found it.
HE FINDS THE KIMCHI
IN THE FRIDGE
DROPPING KIMCHI
INTO THE HEATED POT
Oh, it smells good.
Chef Kwang-Soo, should I cut all of this?
- Just half.
- Half?
This is one pack of tofu.
Should I get more?
- Just a little. Half a pack.
- Half a pack. Got it.
PREP GOES SMOOTHLY
UNDER KWANG-SOO'S COMMAND
MEANWHILE, JAE-SEOK
IS STIR-FRYING KIMCHI
STILL STIR-FRYING IT
This is plenty of kimchi, right?
Yes, that should be enough.
It already smells good.
- This should do.
- Yeah.
NOW BEEF BONE GOES IN
FOR THE BROTH
MINCED GARLIC
CHILI POWDER
SUGAR
Should I add gochujang?
GOCHUJANG
CHEF KWANG-SOO'S SECRET INGREDIENT
FOR SPICY SAUSAGE STEW IS GOCHUJANG
TASTING
ON THE FENCE
JAE-SEOK TASTES IT TOO
Good?
HMM
It's gonna get better, right?
It's fine.
SOMETHING'S MISSING
Oh, I'll get it for you.
I HAVE TO FIX THIS
BECAUSE I'M THE MAIN CHEF
(LOOKING AROUND)
RUSTLING
GLANCING OVER
DIVERTING ATTENTION
- Well, there's a tarp over there.
- Is there any more of this?
HIDING SOMETHING IN HIS HAND
SNIP
It's okay.
This is what it needs right now.
A GENEROUS DASH
OF HOMETOWN FLAVOR
Right, yeah.
It won't taste good without it.
It's lacking depth.
GLANCING OVER
QUICKLY DISCARDING EVIDENCE
CHIEF YU TASTES IT AGAIN
NOW THIS IS THE STUFF
Give it a taste.
- Is it good?
- Not bad.
- It's good now.
- It's coming together.
Yeah, it's coming together.
- Can I try some of the jjigae?
- Yeah, sure. Hold on.
JUN-SEONG GIVES IT A TASTE TOO
What do you think?
WOW
Wow!
- Oh, is it good?
- It's good, right?
It's so good. Wow.
Did you use a packet?
- Nah, we didn't.
- You didn't?
- Come on! No!
- Wow, that's…
You saw us putting in gochujang earlier.
Wow.
- It's good.
- Really? Is it that good?
I actually wrote budae-jjigae on
the survey asking what we wanted to eat.
Oh, really? No way.
ONCE IT BOILS, ADD ASSORTED HAM,
AND TOFU AND IT'S DONE
Look at this tofu. Good job cutting it.
All right,
I think we can call them over now.
MEANWHILE, THE WINNERS ARE…
Mafia, please lift your heads.
PLAYING MAFIA AGAIN
- Who's the detective?
- Who's detective?
- It's me.
- Detective and…
DETECTIVE
Detective, doctor.
- I didn't solve it.
- She's the doctor.
PEEKING
Come on, guys. Dinner's ready.
- Who's the mafia?
- It's a shame.
- Who is it?
- Dinnertime.
It's one of you, right?
- Wait, are you all mafias?
- You picked right!
- I caught you right away, but no one else.
- Ah, so close, so close.
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry too.
- Oh, it's still raining.
- It's raining pretty hard.
- Thanks so much for cooking, guys.
- What were you guys up to?
- We played Mafia again.
- Mafia.
- You played it again?
- Yeah.
You've been playing Mafia all day.
All right, guys, dig in.
TODAY'S MENU: RICE,
SPICY SAUSAGE STEW, ROLLED OMELET,
PICKLED PERILLA LEAVES,
ROASTED SEAWEED
What a great spread.
- You like the menu?
- Yeah, I love it.
It smells incredible.
Have you seen
how perfect this gyeran-mari is?
- You're right.
- Like, really?
- I've never seen it look this good.
- Right, look at that.
- This one's the best.
- This is it.
- Wow, it's so clean. Look at that.
- Right?
It's all cleaned up already.
- This is perfect, isn't it?
- Can you believe this?
SPOTLESS
- We really…
- I mean, what is this?
- Seriously, what is this?
- Wow. It's so clean.
- It's like a fairy tale.
- I was shocked when I turned around.
- The elves cleaned up behind our backs.
- It's so clean.
TEAM YE-EUN CLEANED UP
AS THEY COOKED
Wow, it's so clean. Look at that.
- All right, staff. Come on. Let's eat.
- Okay.
- Enjoy.
- Yeah.
- I didn't think we'd be able to join them.
- I know.
Thanks for the food.
CURRENT TIME
7:50 P.M.
(A SIP OF THE BROTH)
- Wow, this is…
- It's good!
- Really good.
- Wow.
- Delicious.
- The budae-jjigae's good.
- Now I'm craving malatang.
- Malatang?
- Wow, the budae-jjigae is delicious.
- Really?
- The budae-jjigae is good.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
Wow!
This is great.
It's so good.
- The broth is great.
- There's some broth left.
Yeah, I'll be having seconds.
There's still plenty.
REFILL
ANOTHER REFILL
- Jae-seong, I'm glad you like it.
- Thanks. It's good.
It's really good, you know?
- Kwang-soo did a wonderful job.
- Yeah.
- It's so good, seriously.
- That's our captain.
PROUD
I've never made it before.
This was my first time
ever making budae-jjigae,
and honestly, it was great.
It might be the best dish
I've ever cooked.
I felt like a mom.
I was full just watching them.
And Woo-seok and Hyo-jung
made the gyeran-mari?
Wow, it's really…
Team Ye-eun did a great job.
Spicy broth in the rain is perfect.
Mmm, yeah, I know.
IT'S STILL RAINING OUTSIDE
I'm loving the rain.
- Me too. It's peaceful.
- Right?
Yeah, it's so nice
getting to listen to the rain.
- Yeah, outside is great.
- I love it.
Not to pry,
but someone here is a chef, no?
There he goes.
I mean, there's got to be.
- That's straight up asking, isn't it?
- Yeah.
No, I was just talking to myself,
perhaps a bit loudly.
- Right, exactly. Nothing wrong with that.
- Oh, just talking to himself.
- But I bet there's a chef here.
- He's crazy.
There is a chef here.
Yeah. I can tell. Yeah.
- It seems like you're really curious.
- Sorry?
- No.
He keeps guessing and asking questions.
No, I'm not interested.
I'm the kind of person who thinks
prying into other people's jobs is tacky.
I don't need to know who it is,
but if there is a chef,
draw a circle on a note
and put it in the suggestion box.
I just want to know if there is one.
JOB GUESSING RADAR ACTIVATED
JUN-SEONG IS DOING THE DISHES
RIGHT AFTER EATING
Wow, look at Jun-seong
doing the dishes over there.
I have a feeling Jun-seong is a chef.
- That's not how a normal person works.
- Maybe he cooks part-time.
Whatever it is,
I noticed Jun-seong couldn't sit still.
I might be a bit more help
than my sisters.
CLUE 1. HE VOLUNTEERED TO HELP
CLUE 2.
HE NAILED THE RICE-WATER RATIO
CLUE 3.
HE CLEANED UP WHILE COOKING
- I've had a lot of chefs on my shows.
- Right.
One thing that I've learned about chefs
is that they clean up
right after they're done.
CHEFS CLEAN UP RIGHT AWAY
(AM I RIGHT?)
Maybe food service?
IS JUN-SEONG A CHEF?
Should we do our own dishes?
- Should we?
- Sounds good.
- Let's do our own dishes.
- I was gonna do it.
Just clean up after yourselves.
Or we could play a game
and have one person do it.
LOSER DOES ALL THE DISHES?
- You guys worked hard, so that'd be good.
- Should we do that?
You're having one person do it?
- That's not a bad idea.
- Do you want to?
Odd one out.
- The least common one is out.
- Two people.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
- It's me. I'm out.
- Oh, man.
- The least common one.
- Ye-eun and…
shoot!
Let's go!
No, it's me, it's me.
HAPPY TO BE OFF DISH DUTY
Oh, man.
- Shoot!
- Yes!
- They're out.
- Two papers.
It's those two.
All right, your turn.
Shouldn't they play normal now?
- Yeah, normal rules.
- Normal rules.
NOW, THE REGULAR
ROCK-PAPER-SCISSORS
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
- All right!
- Yes!
Loser takes it all?
- Loser takes it all?
- Final round?
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
WOO-SEOK STUCK WITH
DISH DUTY FOR 8
- Oh, our captain.
- It's okay.
- Captain.
- It's okay. I'll…
- Shoot!
- Yay!
DONG-GEON IS ON DISH DUTY
- Oh, no, I feel bad.
- No, I can't.
DONG-KYU & KYO-YOUNG
TAKE ON DISH DUTY
- We'll throw this out.
- Go get some rest.
- Okay.
- "Excellent."
THE WINNERS CAST THEIR
SATISFACTION VOTE AS THEY LEAVE
Another satisfactory.
I really enjoyed the meal, by the way.
- Yeah, I really enjoyed it too.
- I loved it.
- It was good, right?
- It was great.
- The dishes keep coming, huh?
- We'll wash these outside. The big ones.
THEY DECIDE TO DO
THE BIG WASHING-UP OUTSIDE
We're going to sleep well tonight.
- What?
- We're gonna sleep well.
Yeah, we'll pass out.
We don't even know
what's happening in the world.
You're right.
- We're not even checking our phones.
- We don't have time for that.
Other than what should we eat next,
- and what do we do next…
- Right.
- …there's nothing else to think about.
Oh, my back.
GROANING
Seriously, my whole body hurts.
I feel like I got run over.
Well, we're all done.
BODIES FEEL LIKE LEAD
Let's clean up the floor real quick.
- Okay.
- Hey, Chief Yu, I was wondering,
do we have any beer or anything?
Oh, beer?
Well, we didn't buy any.
I mean, I'm not asking for myself.
I don't…
Okay, so you want beer.
KWANG-SOO'S TAKING
A QUICK WATER BREAK
Okay, so you want beer. All right.
Kwang-soo, beer…
Could you…
- Get the mop.
- Do you want me to run out and get some?
No, no, the store is quite far from here.
Oh, well, we could take the car.
No, no, you could,
but I'll go get it. It's fine.
- Could you mop this up?
- Okay.
- Not a problem. I'll finish cleaning up.
I actually thought about getting
some beer, but I didn't.
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN BETTER
Wait.
One sec.
Ah, it's wet.
RUSHING
- Chief Yu.
- Yeah?
Were you only planning on getting beer?
Because I actually brought
a small bottle of soju.
You brought soju?
A FEW MINUTES EARLIER
I brought some booze.
Really?
- It's soju, 24%.
- No way.
I picked it up on a trip.
- Now I feel bad I didn't bring anything.
- Oh, it's fine.
JOO-HYUN BROUGHT DRINKS TO SHARE
But considering how many of us there are,
it might be good to have some more.
- More soju? Oh, all right.
- Yeah, okay.
SOJU, GOT IT
Yeah, some drinks.
I did think about that earlier.
EXHAUSTED
Ye-eun, you know a lot
about alcohol, right?
Well…
Joo-hyun is crazy.
She ran up to us in the rain
and asked us to grab more soju.
- Oh, really?
- Mm.
That girl's something else.
I mean, it makes me curious.
I'M SO CURIOUS ABOUT
THESE PEOPLE
It's driving me crazy.
The funny thing about this is
- even though we all have different jobs…
- Yeah.
…and I don't even know
how old everyone is,
when we played that game,
I realized we're all the same.
- Yeah, of course.
- Yeah.
It felt like we went straight back
to our childhood.
- To being kids.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
- But if we'd known what everyone did,
how old they were, I don't think
we could have connected like that.
Hmm.
Like, for example,
if someone was a company CEO,
or really young,
or there was a big age gap,
it would have been harder to talk to them.
- Totally.
- You're right, you're right.
Everyone seemed like they were having fun.
I know.
Hey, I didn't even have time to call home.
Wow, Jae-seok, seriously…
How do you live like this?
- What do you mean? Live like what?
- I mean, you work every day.
Like, every single day,
but you don't have any free time.
- Eventually…
- Yeah?
…everyone becomes free.
And then you'll miss this time.
Still, it's amazing.
I can take that.
MEANWHILE AT JAE-SEOK'S B&B
- All right, thanks.
- Here.
MORE DISHES
- This too, please.
- Okay.
MORE DISHES
A PILE OF DISHES
- Well, I feel bad. Yeah.
- I know.
There are too many cups and plates.
All right, I'll… I'll wash them.
It's really okay.
You should get some rest.
Let me wash. You can rinse.
I've got nothing to do.
All right. We can do it together.
We're a team. We're on the same team.
Thanks for helping.
- I had so much fun playing the game.
- Yeah.
- I totally lost track of time.
- It's a shame.
Three days and two nights
is way too short.
I know. It's already been a whole day.
- It will be a great memory.
- Right.
I hope everyone feels the same way.
I think I would want to come back too.
I mean, something like this
doesn't happen very often, you know?
You're right. Totally.
- You know…
- Hmm?
…this weekend, it feels like a dream.
It feels like a dream.
- What do you mean?
- This whole thing.
It feels like I'm dreaming.
Hearing you say that…
it makes me really happy.
- You know…
- This just makes me happy too.
Uh…
I want you even happier.
When she told me
that this moment felt like a dream to her,
every word she said…
just really, you know,
hit me right in the heart.
Hearing that made me really happy.
- I hope while we're here…
- Mm?
…we can make a few more
fantastic memories for you.
That sounds amazing. I'd love that.
I'll be really sad when this is over.
Are you gonna have a beer?
Me? No, I'll just have a coffee.
- You don't drink at all? Oh, really?
- No.
I used to drink, but not anymore.
It can't be easy to hold back.
By the way,
you look like a trot singer right now.
A trot singer waiting to go on stage.
A trot singer? I like that.
Well, I got nothing to do.
I'll mop the floor.
CLEANING DILIGENTLY WHILE
THE STAFF IS OUT BUYING BEER
CLEANING DONE
They went to buy beer.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- Oh, that's great.
- Beer sounds amazing.
Oh, the detective's here. The detective.
- Detective, detective.
- How did you know?
- Detective.
- Huh?
- Are you a cop?
- He's a cop?
- Seriously?
No, it's about Mafia.
- Really?
- For real?
- Are you serious?
- No, no.
- Like in real life?
- Maybe he is.
So, not just in Mafia?
Maybe he's really a detective.
He does have that vibe.
You mean the detective in Mafia, right?
You surprised me.
- I think he might be a detective.
- He said, "How did you know?"
"I pledge."
(RIGHT ON THE BEAT)
"I PLEDGE"
CRISP AND PROPER
HE GOT THE LAY OF THE LAND
AS SOON AS HE ARRIVED
Oh, so we got sleeping bags too.
That's a barbecue. There are gloves too.
A THOROUGH FIELD INVESTIGATION
WHAT'S JAE-HYEONG'S
TRUE IDENTITY?
- I think those two are designers.
- Designers?
DESIGNERS?
No, I think they're dancers.
I think they're dancers.
No, that would be too obvious.
- Too obvious.
- You think so?
THEY MADE ONE FLASHY ENTRANCE
We even coordinated.
- Honestly, I really like our last outfit.
- Me too.
ARE THEY FASHION DESIGNERS?
Do the shuffle.
OR
- Two, three, bam!
- That's it.
WHAT DO JUN-HYUK & HYO-LIM DO?
- Look who's here.
- What about hairdressers?
- A stylist? I can see that.
- Are we guessing jobs?
Yeah.
Should I leave?
Something tells me you're an actor.
- That's right.
- I'm thinking about trying it, actually.
This is great.
If there's anything you don't like,
just drop it in the suggestion box
- and we'll take it into account.
- Great.
Well, trash cans might be nice
in our dorms.
Oh, there are no trash cans?
Since they're at the store…
Hey, Hyung.
They're saying there are no trash cans
in the dorm.
Think you can pick some up?
- Oh, trash cans.
- Will they have those?
Oh, okay, we should get some.
Let's see. Trash cans…
- Oh, here they are.
- Where?
- Oh, this is perfect.
- Very good.
- Hyung, I'm getting beer.
- Go ahead. Grab it.
Should we get some apple juice
and one of these as well?
- While we're at it.
- So two boxes of green grapes?
Two? These are good.
MIGHT AS WELL GET YOGURT TOO
- Isn't that too much?
- This should be enough.
Look. Snacks to go with the drinks.
Not bad, right?
Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
- Good night.
DAY 1 FINAL GROCERY RUN
Hey, the rain's really picking up.
It's really coming down.
- They're back.
- Oh?
Oh. Everyone's waiting for the drinks.
All right.
- I'm sorry to trouble you.
- Hey, it's no trouble.
Well, it came up
while we've been chatting.
Oh, you've been chatting?
Go inside. You're getting wet.
Oh, soju, soju, soju.
- We've got makgeolli.
- All right, makgeolli!
TRASH CANS CLEANED
BEFORE DELIVERY
Okay.
- Were you chatting instead of cleaning?
- Us?
- We talked the whole time.
- We sat there and…
I see, but you don't know everything
about each other, right?
No, not yet.
- Kwang-soo.
- Yes?
- You curious too?
- It's killing me.
There's three people I want to know about.
Three?
I said I wasn't curious,
but I can't help it.
Gotta ask questions.
- Right, yeah.
- Yeah, you asked if there was chef.
- It's like we're playing 20 Questions.
- Yeah.
- Mark my words…
- Just a few clues here and there.
…one of them is a chef, I'm telling you.
- That's not easy to do, you know?
- Cleaning up like that is a giveaway.
ABSOLUTE CERTAINTY
Okay.
- Where's the restaurant?
- Sorry?
Where's the restaurant?
- Restaurant?
- It's right here.
- Right here.
The one you run.
Me? I don't run one.
Oh, you don't?
Well, I guess we were wrong.
- Why do you keep asking?
- Sorry. I'm sorry.
I thought you might slip up.
We're gonna take a second
to check out our rooms.
- See you later.
- See you.
9:30 P.M. STAFF REGROUPING
Get some rest.
- Did you take a shower?
- Yes, I did.
Is the water nice?
- It was perfect.
- It's great.
- Nice and hot?
- Yes.
- It was great.
- Good, good.
Wait, where are my shoes? "Yu Jae-seok."
Oh, these aren't mine.
"YU JAE-SEOK" EVERYWHERE
Shoot, wait. "Yu Jae-seok." Here they are.
We need to take the registration forms.
Yeah.
HE PICKS UP
THE REGISTRATION FORMS
Oh, there's a lot.
AND CHECKS THE SUGGESTION BOX
Wait, this the first time
we're going to the staff quarters
since dropping off our luggage.
That's right. The other way, hyung.
Oh, right. My gosh.
Damn.
FEELING THE EFFECTS
OF THE 14-HOUR SHIFT
Jeez. Oh, man.
Hey, good work.
GROANS AND SIGHS EVERYWHERE
CHUCKLING
- Seriously.
- Huh?
I'm just so wiped.
This might've been
the most hectic day of my life.
Man, seriously.
I really want to go to sleep.
Tell me about it.
LOADING UP ON SUPPLEMENTS
Seriously.
AN EXHAUSTED YE-EUN
ALSO GROANS ON HER WAY BACK
TO HER ROOM
Dong-geon.
- Dong-geon.
- Yes?
Is there any water?
Bring me a bottle.
LOTION ON HOLD FOR A WATER RUN
Thank you.
ORDERED AROUND
EVEN OUTSIDE OF HIS HOME
- Staff, let's get washed up first.
- Yeah.
LET'S GO WASH UP
- All right, we'll be back.
- See you in a bit.
WHILE THE STAFF FRESHENS UP
THE GUESTS WASH UP
AND START GATHERING ONE BY ONE
(HOVERING)
I don't think there's enough room
for me to get in there.
CORNER BED NOT EASY TO GET INTO
I think we may have picked the wrong spot.
Exactly.
THEY DECIDE TO MOVE THEIR BEDS
You know what?
It might actually be fun
to take this out and sleep outside.
EUN-TAE JOINS THE BED MOVE
Should we put all our beds together?
Why not?
Should we move them all to the center?
Yeah, this way we can all talk.
Well, isn't this nice?
EVERYONE'S MOVING THEIR BEDS
(TWIRL)
Hey, you know what? This is kind of fun.
It feels like a parade.
LIKE A SCENE FROM A PARADE
Like this?
A little more.
- Here?
- That's good, that's good. Stop, stop.
This is a special,
once-in-a-lifetime experience.
There.
- There.
- Looks good.
Looks good.
You sure about this?
ARE WE REALLY SLEEPING
LIKE THIS?
It looks like we're here
for a clinical trial.
Are you having beer?
- Are they going now?
- Yeah.
Let's get it.
- Let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Let's get it.
THE STAFF ARE BACK
FROM THEIR SHOWERS
Here. Space them out, will you?
I hope nobody snores.
SPACED OUT
FINISHING UP WITH HIS HYUNG
Oh, a bed.
TOTALLY WIPED OUT
Seriously though…
You worked so hard today.
You too.
Seriously. Wow.
This was the toughest day ever.
I mean, we didn't take any breaks.
That's true.
JAE-SEOK'S B&B RULES!
RECEPTION PREP
- Can we do the towels?
- We don't have time.
I'll hold nothing back, talk nonstop,
and play hard to my heart's content.
ORIENTATION
LUNCH PREP AND LUNCH
What the heck are you doing?
COFFEE PICKUP
- Did it all spill?
- No!
THE CUSHION QUIZ
- Got it!
That's like something
you'd get at a restaurant.
- I'm getting beer.
- Go ahead, grab it.
DINNER
GROCERY RUN
PRESENT
ALL OF THIS HAPPENED IN ONE DAY
We came here at 9:00 a.m.
and haven't had a break since.
Except for the shower just now.
The only break I had the whole day
was the 30 seconds I had to pee.
My phone battery's still at 85%.
That never happens.
- Also, it's not just the three of us here.
- Right.
We're with people we don't know,
and it feels more…
- You're more aware.
- Yeah, you're more aware.
- You want to be on your best behavior.
- Yeah.
That's true.
OUR DEAR GUESTS
Hyung, it's one minute until lights out.
Those who want to sleep can sleep.
Huh?
Where is everyone? Huh?
Wait, it's supposed to be lights out.
We have to make the announcement…
Wait. We, uh…
Well, the thing is,
since it's only three days and two nights…
You're right. Yeah.
There they are. There.
- Look, everyone's over there.
- Aren't they tired?
They're all…
- Uh…
- Some of them don't drink, but…
All right, everyone.
No one's here.
What kind of announcement…
- Who are you talking to?
- This is embarrassing.
They could've at least stayed
until the announcement.
- I mean…
- Yeah, nobody's there.
They could've stayed
until the announcement. Where did they go?
Where did they go?
THEY CAN STILL HEAR HIM
- It's lights out.
- We're over here.
Is anyone here?
If you are,
could you come out to the center
and wave your hand or something?
EMPTY
Well, this is a first.
They completely blew us off.
I mean, we clearly said
we'd announce lights out in 30 minutes.
All right.
According to the rules of Jae-seok's B&B,
we'll be turning the lights out…
- Who are you talking to?
- Well, we still have to do this properly.
Lights out.
- Who's that?
- Where were you?
Oh, you're here.
Did you hear the announcement?
Oh, are you going to bed?
Then what?
- You're going out?
- After the announcement?
PERSISTENT, OBSESSIVE
Oh. All right, then.
You all did great work on the first day
here at Jae-seok's B&B.
We'll see you all tomorrow morning.
Lights out now.
Lights out. See you tomorrow.
GOOD NIGHT
I'll go turn off the lights.
Oh, you have to do them yourself?
They're not automatic?
They don't go out automatically. Jeez.
Well, they set up the beds really nicely.
They got water and everything.
Oh, look, hyung.
Everyone really made themselves at home.
THE LIGHTS GO OUT
AND THE MOON COMES DOWN
FIRST NIGHT LIGHTS-OUT COMPLETE
(THOUGH NO ONE'S HERE)
Whoa, hyung,
it really looks like the moon.
All right, the staff should have
a quick chat.
- Ye-eun.
- Yeah?
THE DAY ISN'T OVER YET
Come here.
- Whoa.
- What's that?
- A mask?
- A mask.
- For only part of your face?
- I'm an actress.
An actress?
I'm an actress.
But do you have to…
- I do it daily, yeah.
- Daily?
Well, let's sit down first.
Good work today, everyone.
How'd it go for you today?
Does anyone have any suggestions
or things you'd like to share?
I honestly had a great time.
- Yeah?
- The one thing I'd say is I actually wish
we could talk more with the guests.
There were moments we were so busy
we couldn't talk to them at all.
- So that was…
- That's okay.
- Oh, okay.
- It's okay.
This is similar
to what Woo-seok just said,
but I wish we'd had more
physical interaction with the guests.
Yeah, I mean, today,
we started a bit late.
Yeah, right.
We also had our first meal
just among ourselves, so there's that,
but there are bound to be some issues
as we figure things out.
Yeah.
- Like the snack bar…
- Wait.
- What?
- Wait, why…
- Wait.
- What is it, Ye-eun?
Chief, come on.
We can't just let this slide.
I mean, because… What's funny about this?
- We're all being serious right now.
- Wait, Ye-eun. Why are you laughing?
He looks so funny.
- Sorry.
- He looks funny?
- What is she talking about?
- No.
- Mr. EP?
- Yeah. His earrings…
All right, well…
Hold on. So, can I finish, or…
- I got cut off just now.
- Oh, well, what did you want to say?
- So, we get up early tomorrow, right?
- Yeah.
We'll make everyone breakfast,
then we get some free time?
I don't think…
Yeah.
- There's too much to do in the morning.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- I think we can have breakfast at 8 a.m.
Clean up should wrap up
around 9 a.m, right?
But I'm pretty sure that's when
we have to start prepping lunch.
Oh, right.
SNORT
Is this supposed to be like this?
- Seriously.
- You turn around and it's time to eat.
Are you crying?
You're not crying, right?
Now these are the registration forms.
- Hey, you know Hyo-lim?
- Yeah.
- The one with the killer dance moves?
She started college during the pandemic,
so she never got to go on a retreat.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
So one of the things she wants to do here
is a dance initiation.
So that's why she was dancing earlier.
Wow, Hyeong-seon?
Oh, "work and childcare."
Oh, she's married.
I guess she's just swamped
with parenting these days.
Hey, guess what Dong-geon wrote
as his concern.
"Things might get even more awkward
with my sister."
THINGS MIGHT GET EVEN
MORE AWKWARD WITH MY SISTER
- That must be real.
- I noticed you're avoiding him.
Is that right?
It's kind of uncomfortable for us too.
You have siblings, right?
You know how it is.
I talk to my sister a lot.
Well, there are siblings like that,
and then there are
siblings like us. Right?
Good work, everyone.
- Good job.
- Good work.
THE LATE-NIGHT MEETING ENDS
Look, everyone's still there.
- Aw, they're still so young.
- Wow.
BUT THE AFTER-PARTY CONTINUES
Endless energy.
MEANWHILE IN THE DINING AREA
- I had a blast with all the games today.
- It was really fun.
STILL TALKING ABOUT THE QUIZ
The delivery box at the end was
the funniest. Everyone was like…
Yeah, it was so crazy.
Oh, it's midnight.
Let's wrap it up, shall we?
BEDTIME FOR REAL
ONCE ALL THE LIGHTS GO OUT
THE STAFF ALSO
GETS READY FOR BED
THEY CAN'T HELP BUT GROAN
Oh, I'm so tired.
THEIR 1ST NIGHT
AT THE B&B DEEPENS
Oh, boy.
EVERYONE IS SOUND ASLEEP
AT JAE-SEOK'S B&B
Please save me!
- Please save me!
- Good morning.
If you don't save me
The hunter will shoot me, bang!
Good morning, everyone.
We've got a little surprise for you.
WOW
Good morning!
Please save me!
No, please save me.
WHERE PEOPLE BEG FOR THEIR LIVES
Please save me!
Comrade, save me.
THE TERRIFYING DAY 2
AT JAE-SEOK'S B&B BEGINS
JAE-SEOK'S B&B RULES!