Oh, I'm a guest who…
who got here a little late.
Can I come in now?
You've got the red carpet
rolled out for us, right?
Who is this?
It's Hyo-ri.
What? Who is it?
Well, I just got here.
Where are you?
Where?
- Is this for real?
- Wait, really? Hello?
Hey, oppa.
Hey, Hyo-ri. Where are you?
- I don't know. I'm in some parking lot.
- Where is she?
- I'll come pick you up.
- We're coming. Hold on.
I'm expecting a limo.
Okay. Okay, got it.
Whoa, I can't believe this.
- I'm a huge fan.
- Seriously?
Was that really Lee Hyo-ri?
I think it was.
No way.
- I gotta see this.
- It was for sure her voice.
- Yeah, it was definitely her voice.
- Come on. Let's go.
We have to go see her.
- Absolutely.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
SWARMING
She wants a limo and a red carpet.
- Let's go find one.
- Seriously?
- No, stay there. Stay there.
- Stay there.
Everyone, remain calm!
- Hang on a sec.
- What do we do?
- Should I stay here?
- Yeah. Wait here.
Okay.
WOO-SEOK MISSED IT ALL
WHILE HE WAS IN THE BATHROOM
I can't believe she's actually
coming. She was asking for a limo.
Let's go find a red carpet.
(WHAT'S THE FUSS ABOUT?)
Oppa! Hyo-ri is coming.
- Wait, really?
- Isn't that amazing?
Hyo-ri's here?
Is this for real?
Is she really here?
Wow. This is huge.
WE'RE COMING TO PICK YOU UP
Can she cook?
Hyo-ri is a good cook.
This is great.
The plan for dinner wasn't even
decided on yet,
- so maybe…
- Oh, yeah.
- I didn't even think about that.
- This is awesome.
It'll be great.
- We were out of ideas.
- Yeah, I know.
Amazing. Look there.
Isn't that her?
- We need to go around here.
- Wait, hold on.
- Is Sang-soon with her?
- She came with Sang-soon.
Here they come.
- What? You're actually here.
- Hey, guys!
- Hey, Sang-soon.
- Hello.
HYO-RI AND SANG-SOON
DOUBLE THE JOY
- Gosh! What's going on?
- Hi there.
- Hey.
- Wow, this is crazy.
- Kwang-soo.
- How have you been?
- What's with the bling?
- Oh, it's for something I'm filming.
You've changed a lot, Kwang-soo.
- You've changed a lot.
- It's great to see you.
Director Lee.
- I'm sorry but…
- Welcome.
…you can't even handle
one show on your own?
- Wait.
- Do I really have to come and help you?
Hey, Sang-soon!
- This is great.
- I'm so happy to see you.
I was really surprised.
They actually came.
Sang-soon and Hyo-ri
are basically the originals,
the pioneers of B&B variety shows.
So their experience and know-how
really give me something to lean on.
Having them here makes me feel reassured.
All right, get in. For real, we gotta go.
- This is great.
- I'm so glad you guys are here.
- Did you need us that badly?
- What do you need?
Well, the thing is…
we just made kimchi fried rice for lunch,
and now we've got to start working
on dinner which is coming up soon.
We were like, "Man,
what should we even make this time?"
Well, oppa's good at cooking, so…
I'm actually not.
I meant Sang-soon. He's good.
That's right. Sang-soon's good,
and so are you, Hyo-ri.
So what is this exactly?
- It's not a guesthouse, right?
- No.
- What are we doing here?
- Well…
It's a B&B.
- A B&B?
- Uh-huh.
- Like some kind of retreat?
- Yeah, something like that.
- Oh.
- So, at the moment,
we have about 20 guests staying with us.
- Twenty?
- Twenty, that's a lot.
How do you cook for all of them?
- That's kinda where we--
- That's actually
- our biggest problem.
- Our biggest struggle.
- It's not just the two of you, right?
- No, there's Woo-seok too.
- Woo-seok and Ye-eun are here.
- Ye-eun?
And they can't cook either?
- They're hopeless.
- No.
- Too salty! Too salty!
- Oh, it's out.
- We're all out of ideas.
- Basically, that part's been a mess.
Just get delivery.
Well, we could, but still,
- that wouldn't be right.
- I see. You want to cook everything
- for them yourselves.
- Think about it.
Of course.
Wow, this is really awesome.
OFF TO THE B&B
When did you get here?
- This morning.
- This morning?
This isn't your first shoot though, right?
- Right, it's--
- It's our second.
- Oh.
- We already had our first group of guests
- stay with us last month.
- The first's already come and gone.
- This is the second group.
- Was the first group fun?
- It was fun.
- Really fun.
- I heard a rumor that you lost your voice.
- That's true.
- What did you do?
- Wait, how?
- What goes on here?
- Yeah.
All kinds of things.
Well, we did a quiz and…
YOU SEE, AT OUR B&B…
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
THEY WILL BE PLAYING HARD
- Whoa!
Check it out.
MESSING AROUND
…a talent show type thing.
AND TALKING NONSTOP
Whoa, where did that come from?
So they're not here to rest.
- Who, these people?
- Yeah.
They're not the kind to sit around
all day doing nothing.
So, they're like that then.
THIS IS A B&B WHERE YOU'RE FREE
TO TALK NONSTOP,
PLAY HARD, AND MESS AROUND
PLEASE NOTE IT'S VERY DIFFERENT
FROM HYORI'S BED & BREAKFAST
You know, our Bed & Breakfast
was more about relaxing and recharging.
Well, here, people are always asking,
"Hey, aren't we going to do something?"
Look, see? They're already outside.
- Is that them?
- They're so excited.
They heard you were coming.
They heard your voice on the phone.
- They're going crazy right now.
- They're back!
- They're back, they're back.
- Oh!
Oh, Lee Sang-soon came with her?
- You're right!
- They came together?
No way.
- It's really Lee Hyo-ri.
- So cool.
- The two of them came together.
- Really?
- Lee Sang-soon too? Crazy!
- Yeah, it looks like they're both here.
All right, Lee Hyo-ri
and Sang-soon are here!
MASSIVE CHEERS
What are they all doing
standing around out here?
They all just ran out.
Oh, my gosh. This is crazy!
Oh, my gosh.
Ah, they were all inside before?
There's Woo-seok.
Hello, sunbae. I'm Byeon Woo-seok.
- Nice to meet you.
- Oh, my gosh!
- Hello, sunbae. I'm Byeon Woo-seok.
- Oh, my gosh.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- How're you doing?
- Hey, Hyo-ri.
- What?
- Hi, there.
- Oh, Ye-eun!
Hello! I'm such a huge fan.
- You were happy to see Woo-seok, right?
- Yes. Yes, of course.
I'm just happy that she's happy.
- Hello.
- Hi, lovely to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
ALMOST LIKE A FAN MEETING
Meeting Lee Hyo-ri
in person was so special.
I could really feel her aura.
I'm a fan of Lee Hyo-ri's.
I've liked her since high school.
I thought,
"I see what this show is about."
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet all you.
- I'm such a fan.
So great to meet you.
(HOP, HOP)
You should have seen them earlier.
We didn't get that kind of reaction.
THREE HOURS EARLIER,
AT ORIENTATION
THREE HOURS AFTER CHECK-IN,
BRYAN'S FINALLY SMILING BRIGHTLY
To meet the celebrity of celebrities
was amazing.
I was shocked.
I was like "How is this real?"
EVEN THE CALM NAM-JIN
IS ALL SMILES
- Hello.
- So glad to meet you!
- All right, these are…
- Yeah.
These are all our guests here,
- as you already know.
- Right.
They were told not to share
their jobs or ages with each other yet.
Oh, kind of like I am SOLO?
- Well, it's a little different from that.
- No, not like I am SOLO.
Why aren't they telling that?
Well, you know, it's kind of…
How should I explain?
- Some of them don't wanna share that yet.
- Some people don't want to reveal that.
- Oh.
- To avoid stereotyping.
That's right.
Oppa, say hi. Why are you lurking?
- Yeah, Sang-soon.
- Hello.
- Hi!
WE WELCOME YOU TOO,
MR. SANG-SOON
I was just waiting.
This was a surprise for me as well.
I only found out today
that Sang-soon and Hyo-ri were coming.
Seriously.
I'm guessing the two of them
will be staff, just like us.
Oh!
I mean, I sure hope they'll help us out
with their expertise.
- Staff? That doesn't really suit us.
- What would you prefer?
How about landlords?
Okay.
- But he's the owner.
- Yeah.
- Let's say you're the founders.
- Make yourselves at home.
Let's go with that.
Think of them as the founders.
All right, well,
introductions are done, so…
You have free time.
So they can do anything right now?
- It's free time.
- Yeah. We just ate, nuna.
Oh. Gotcha.
And in here…
- Wow.
- They all get one of these.
- They sleep here together?
- They sleep here?
- Exactly.
- They each have their own bed.
This must be a really fresh
and new experience for the guests.
This is…
We all sleep here together?
This is for the guys.
Ye-eun's in the other room by herself.
I need to sleep with my husband.
What did you say?
We're married.
How can we sleep separately?
- She's right.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- She's right.
- Uh, in that case…
- We'll just use this room then.
- The big room?
- Yeah.
Well, you're married,
so I guess that makes sense.
Maybe we decide on that later.
Yeah, later.
- You can unpack first. Later, we'll…
- Yeah, sure.
So there's nothing we're supposed
to do or anything? We just…
We do one activity per day.
And what's today's activity?
Today, uh, we're going to do
a special quiz later.
- Oh, yeah? A quiz?
- A quiz?
You know the cushion quiz from my show?
- Yeah.
- We're gonna do that.
But it's just one night here,
so it's pretty short, right?
It's two nights, three days.
Two nights and three days?
- Yeah, two nights, three days.
- So we're the only ones staying one night.
- You leave tomorrow?
- Yeah.
What time?
- Well, after lunch I guess.
- Probably… Yeah, we should go.
Can't you stay for two nights?
- Would you like us to?
- Of course.
You heard him!
Did you see the look in his eyes?
- Are you kidding?
- He was so earnest.
"Can't you stay for two?"
I haven't heard you speak
that gently in a while!
"Would you like us to?" What was that?
It just feels like we have
someone who understands now.
Well, since you're here…
we'd love the help.
Sang-soon, you brought
the old six-string with you, right?
"Six-string."
Are we having a campfire?
- That'd be good for the evening.
- A campfire? Sure.
Oh, Hyo-ri's into yoga, right?
- Should I do a class?
- You can do it in the morning.
You think they would want to do yoga here?
Come on.
It'd be nice to do it first thing.
- Okay, some stretching.
- To help us wake up.
Great. So tomorrow morning,
we can do some yoga.
Yeah, that's exactly what we need.
This is great.
So we provide three meals a day.
You barely have time to breathe
before you have to cook again.
Then I guess we should start cooking soon.
- Speaking of dinner…
- What are you thinking?
- We were thinking we could do pork katsu.
- How?
- For Pork katsu, we--
- Where's the meat from?
The meat? We're picking it up.
- Ah!
- So we just need to deep-fry it?
- Deep-fry.
- Deep-fry, okay.
But we can't just have pork katsu.
- We can slice up some cabbage.
- We were planning to slice up cabbage.
Did you order it?
- I knew you'd get it.
- That's good.
- Will that be enough? Maybe--
- Pickled radish.
Pickled radish. Good.
- We gotta do that. Pineapple too!
- That's a great idea.
This is really coming together.
Don't we need
something like doenjang soup?
That's right,
pork katsu can be a little dry.
- We should have soup.
- Is it quick to make?
We just need tofu, spinach,
seaweed and doenjang.
- You guys are seriously next level!
- Anchovies too.
It's nothing special. It's the basics.
If this is impressive to you, I don't--
- You should've seen what we served before.
- Exactly.
How do you invite people without a plan?
You sure you can't stay longer?
Seriously.
- Jae-seok.
- Yes?
- When are we playing the game?
- We should go now.
It's 3:12.
- Where are we going?
We gather there.
- Down there?
- Mm-hmm.
All right.
We do one activity per day,
and in a moment,
we'll be starting the first activity
of your stay with us.
Everyone inside and outside,
please gather in the gymnasium.
We'll see you in just a bit.
Thank you.
JAE-SEOK'S B&B RULES!
Let's head down.
ONE ACTIVITY PER DAY
It's gonna get hot.
- Where did you get that Kancho?
- Oh!
Sorry, it's for Woo-seok.
It has his name on it.
- No way!
- You found it?
- I did.
- Whoa! No way!
- You found it?
- Found what?
I've been looking for this!
- Really? You found "Woo-seok"?
- Yeah.
BYEON WOO-SEOK
- I wish you'd found Jae-seok.
- Hey, back up.
- No!
- Hey.
- You saved the one with a heart.
- Yeah, that's right.
Why haven't you found mine?
TEAM KWANG-SOO: HA-NA, I-AN
TEAM YE-EUN: HYE-JEONG, MIN-JU
Don't you guys eat Kancho?
- They don't have a Kwang-soo.
- I don't think there's a Kwang-soo.
- They only have common names.
- Why not?
Yeah.
I don't know a single other Kwang-soo.
- Yeah, not one.
- No one.
Except on I am SOLO.
Honestly, neither have I.
Oh, really?
- One of a kind.
- Right?
- What game are we playing?
- All right.
I told you we'd be doing
one activity per day.
Let's start your first activity right now.
First things first,
let's all go check out the game room,
and we'll find out what we'll be playing.
- Oh, there's a separate game room?
- I guess they must have one
in the back over there.
Oh, looks like we're going inside.
Let's all go check out the game room.
- What? Game room?
- I didn't see that.
- Where is it?
- I guess so.
- Right?
- I'm scared.
- There must be another space behind that.
- Oh, really?
I think there's
something behind that wall.
Oh, really?
Are you surprised?
Whoa!
Wow, no way!
- I didn't see that coming.
- I now present to you all…
the game room!
PROUD
Amazing!
PROUD 2
- I can't believe it.
- This is so cool.
- Come on in.
- This is unbelievable.
I love it!
HIDDEN SPACE
THE GAME ROOM
Whoa!
How cute!
Is that for the cushion thing?
This must be that game
they used to play with the cushion.
- Isn't it cozy?
- This is great.
- So cool.
- Awesome.
They have a lot of stuff.
All right. First, get in your teams.
- Yes.
- You see the uniforms over here?
You'll be using them.
- Do we pick colors?
- Yeah, the captains choose.
- All right.
- Now,
Ye-eun's team has fewer people,
so Sang-soon and Hyo-ri, why don't you…
- Join her team?
- …join her team, yeah.
Would you like to stay together?
- Oh, we'll stay together.
- I thought so.
Okay great. I've got you both. Yay!
- All right, Ye-eun, uniforms.
- You know I have separation anxiety.
- How about orange?
- Yes, orange.
- The orange ones look really good.
- Orange all the way.
TEAM WOO-SEOK CHOOSES WHITE
- Here.
- Thank you.
Press it down so it doesn't fall off.
TEAM KWANG-SOO CHOOSES BLACK
CAREFULLY PUTTING ON NAME TAGS
- Thanks.
- Sure.
- Let's sit here.
- Let's sit.
- I'm ready.
- This is gonna be fun.
I know, right?
- We have to sit in a line.
- In a line.
CHUCKLE
You know, it's quite refreshing to see
our special guests
Sang-soon and Hyo-ri
lined up as team members.
It's new.
A REFRESHING SIGHT
All right, everyone. I told you
we'd be doing one activity per day.
First up is the Cushion Quiz.
I used to do this on Dongeodongrak.
That's right.
Some of you might know it,
and some of you might not.
- What is it?
- Those don't know,
- raise your hand.
- The Cushion Quiz.
THE CUSHION QUIZ IS NEW
TO SOME GUESTS
- Oh, Sang-soon, you should know.
- I don't know. Really.
Come on, hyung. Stop pretending.
- What is it?
- The Cushion Quiz.
- I can't remember.
- The Cushion Quiz?
We took note of the requests
in your applications.
We found that the Cushion Quiz
consistently ranked pretty high
on the list of activities
you all wanted to try.
So we figured we'd give it a go.
- The category is general knowledge.
- I'm so nervous.
- I know!
- Yes?
Charles Darwin!
- Correct!
- Yeah!
THE FIRST TO RAISE THEIR CUSHION
GETS TO ANSWER
Depending on the results of this quiz,
the team that comes in last
will sleep outside.
Wow, no way.
I think I'd like that.
The team that comes in second will do
the dishes after breakfast tomorrow.
And the team that comes in first,
of course,
gets to relax until tomorrow morning.
All right?
All right, let's see
who will come in last.
But first,
- starting with Team Lee Kwang-soo…
- Yes.
…let's here from you all
your best team cheer.
What?
A SUDDEN REQUEST
FOR A TEAM CHEER
A cheer. Let's hear your team's cheer.
LOL
Guys…
Discuss it. Go ahead and discuss it.
Discuss it.
Does anyone have a special move?
- I only know, "Hey, hey, hey!"
- Ah!
You've never done the Cushion Quiz?
- I don't think so.
- Really?
I don't think I was ever on Dongeodongrak.
- Yeah.
- So you must've been on X-Man.
- I was on X-Man,
and I was on the first episode
of Running Man as a guest.
BEEN ON COUNTLESS VARIETY SHOWS
BUT NEVER DONE THE CUSHION QUIZ
Listen, you've got to do your cheer
with confidence. I said confidence.
CRACKS UP (?)
Hyo-ri, you're gonna have
to stop staring at me.
You're gonna have to stop staring at me.
Stop giving me that piercing look.
WHEN JAE-SEOK WAS TALKING
Those of you who were born
in the late '90s and the 2000s…
SHE WAS WATCHING HIM INTENTLY
You know, Hyo-Ri and I
used to film things together all the time
but now it's weird having her
watch me from the sidelines.
It's like your younger sibling
coming to your workplace and watching you.
It's so uncomfortable.
- I can see you're working hard.
- Right.
All right, then.
- Let's start with Team Kwang-soo.
- Okay.
- Ours is short.
- That's fine.
It's okay even if it's short.
- Should we start?
- Yes, go ahead.
Team Kwang-soo!
We're not fools!
What?
What did they say?
"We're not fools."
- "We're not fools"?
- This wasn't my idea, all right?
- "We're not fools," because--
- I didn't come up with this.
I don't think anyone said you were fools.
"Team Kwang-soo, we're fools"?
- Not fools.
- "We're not fools."
- You know exactly what we said.
- You heard us.
Sure you aren't.
JUST PLAIN TEASING
- My teammates came up with it.
- Oh, they did?
- Yes, that's right.
- I see. Please sit down.
All right, next up is Team Woo-seok.
- All right, please go ahead.
- Okay.
- It's Team Woo-seok.
- Ready, set, go.
Handsome guys! Pretty girls!
One, two. Hey, hey, hey!
Oh, that was a good one.
- Next, Team Ye-eun, let's hear yours.
- We should all face that way,
don't you think?
Let's get in a line.
In a line?
- All right, Team Ye-eun.
- Yes.
Everyone…
Watch yourselves!
- Victory…
- Is ours!
That's cute!
That was funny.
Look, I'm sorry.
I appreciate your enthusiasm,
but "Victory is ours"?
- It's not the most original.
- Victory is ours!
A VERY CLASSIC CHEER
It was me.
I can only think of school ones.
- Something like "Victory is ours."
- Oh, I like that.
Victory is ours!
Okay, everyone.
- The Cushion Quiz!
- Quiz!
All right,
let's get the Cushion Quiz started.
One person from each team,
please come up to answer the questions.
Let's go, let's go!
- Ye-eun, let's go!
- You got this!
THE TEAM CAPTAINS GO FIRST
Whoo! Kwang-soo is not a fool!
Lee Kwang-soo!
- Yes?
- Watch yourself.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING
- The category is entertainment!
- …tainment.
All right.
Here's the question.
Lee Hyo-ri's signature song is…
- Got it.
- Got it!
- Yes?
- "10 Minutes."
That's correct.
Now, in the lyrics of "10 Minutes,"
what was she doing
during the ten minutes she was away?
- Got it!
- Yes?
She fixed her earrings, her makeup and…
WRONG
Shoot!
"Fixed her earrings and makeup."
Try to remember the lyrics.
TRYING TO REMEMBER THE LYRICS
No helping from the back.
- Got it.
- Yes?
Touched up her makeup.
Even Hyo-ri's having trouble remembering.
No helping from the back.
REALLY CAN'T REMEMBER
- Oh, I got it.
- Yes?
Touching up her mock-up With red lipstick
It's not "mock-up."
- Got it!
- Yes?
Touching up her makeup With red lipstiiick
"Stiiick"!
Excuse me!
- It's not "stiiick."
- Got it!
Touching up her makeup with…
Nope, your voice cracked.
- Got it!
- You.
- I got it!
- Got it! Got it!
- Calm down. Be precise.
- Got it!
Me! Me! Me!
THE CAPTAINS ARE NOT CALM AT ALL
Go for it.
I got it!
- Got it!
- Sit down first. Sit down.
Okay, it's not "mock-up" or "lipstiiick."
- Got it!
- Me!
You have to sit on the cushion.
- Got it!
- Yes?
Red lipstick She touches up her makeup
All right!
All right! You did it!
TEAM WOO-SEOK GETS IT RIGHT
THE ANSWER - RED LIPSTICK,
SHE TOUCHES UP HER MAKEUP
TEAM WOO-SEOK WINS ROUND 1
All right.
Kwang-chul, Seung-jun and Nam-jin…
Nam-jin.
- …the category is entertainment!
- …tainment!
Okay, entertainment.
There's a Chinese, four-character idiom
that means "a match made in heaven."
It's "cheonsaeng-yeonbun."
All right, everyone,
you have five seconds
to name five celebrity couples
who are a match made in heaven.
How can you do that?
- …who are a match made in heaven.
- Five couples?
- Whoa, that's way too hard.
- All right, five celebrity couples
who are a match made in heaven
in five seconds.
- Lee Hyo-ri and Lee Sang-soon.
- Yes.
Lee Hyo-ri and Lee Sang-soon,
Hyun-hee and Jasson.
Hyo-ri and Sang-soon, Hyun-hee and Jasson.
BLATANTLY FEEDING HIM THE ANSWER
- Kyung-eun and Jae-seok.
- Yeah, do that.
Okay, don't feed him the answer
from behind. Hey, no helping.
- Rain. Rain and Kim Tae-hee.
- Rain and Tae-hee.
- Okay, don't feed him the answer!
Wait, they're not listening to you!
Hey, I told you not to tell him.
- I told you not to tell him.
- Hong Hyun-hee and Jasson.
They're giving him the answer
even after you told them not to.
TEAM WOO-SEOK CHEATING QUIETLY
THEY'RE OUT OF CONTROL
Hang on.
- Choi Soo-jong and Ha Hee-ra.
- Right.
- Sean and Jung Hye-young.
- Kyung-eun and Jae-seok. Hurry!
- Yu Jae-seok and Kyung-eun.
- I got it!
- He got it!
Okay, go!
- Five, four, three…
- Hyo-ri and Sang-soon…
- Jasson and Hyun-hee…
- …two, one. That's five seconds.
- Got it!
- Go! Five, four,
- three, two…
- Choi Soo-jong and Ha Hee-ra…
- Ugh, shit.
- Okay, you only got one couple.
Five seconds is up.
Man, Nam-jin talks so slowly.
- Seriously.
- I don't know him!
Do your best. You've got five seconds.
- Five seconds is too short.
- Yeah, too short.
- Got it.
- Yes?
- Five, four…
- Na Kyung-eun and… Oh, sorry.
He's right in front of you!
Wait, you just made Na Kyung-eun single.
- You just made her single.
- You only got half.
Got it!
Kim Tae-hee and Rain,
Haha, Byul and Sang-soon--
- That's so wrong!
- Byul and Lee Sang-soon?
Oh, my goodness.
A CRAZY LOVE TRIANGLE
Byul and Sang-soon?
- How could you get that wrong?
- Byul and Lee Sang-soon?
- Amazing.
Oh, I'm sorry!
- How could you get that wrong?
- Got it!
Byul and Lee Sang-soon.
Tae-hee, Rain, Byul, Jae-seok, Kyung-eun,
Hyo-ri, Sang-soon, Soo-jong and Hee-ra!
- He got it! That's it!
- Oh, yeah! Come on! Come on!
- He got it!
Come on! Yeah! Yes! Yeah!
WINNING IS GREAT, BUT…
EVERYONE WITNESSED SOMETHING
Yeah! Yes! Yeah!
Wait, what…
What did I just see? Oh, my Lord.
Come on!
A FRONT-ROW SEAT VIEW
HE DIDN'T WANT
- No, wait!
- What just happened?
He was right in front of me.
This father's got his two daughters
right here, and he goes…
…oh, yeah!
I SAW IT TOO
That one's an old move. It's classic.
Seriously? This is classic? I mean, what?
GIRLS, CLOSE YOUR EYES
- Chae-won, do this.
- Oh, Dad.
Captain Ye-eun, let's have you up here.
- Go, Captain. You got this!
- I'm really bad at this.
Victory is ours!
- Kwang-soo, come on.
- Yeah!
- Victory is ours!
- …is ours!
Is ours!
Hey! That's our chant!
- Victory is ours!
- …is ours!
Victory is just ours!
Wait, give me four "ours".
- Victory is ours, ours, ours, ours!
- …is ours, ours, ours, ours!
Victory…
…is ours, ours, ours, ours, ours, ours!
"Victory is ours" is driving me crazy.
Now I see why you lost your voice.
Now, the next category is enter…
…tainment!
All right, here's the question.
What's the famous line
from the movie Sunflower?
You know, the one he says while crying!
"You had to do that to feel satisfied?"
Right?
The one he says while crying!
Oh, I got it!
"You had to do this to feel better?"
"You had to"? No.
- Got it!
- Okay.
"You had to…"
Okay, it's not "you had to."
- It's not "you had to."
- Oh, not "had to." Hang on.
Got it!
"Did you really have to…"
- "Have to take everything."
- "…take everything…"
- "To feel."
- "…to feel…"
- "Better"! "Better"! "Better!"
- "Better"!
"…satisfied"?
- That was too late.
- Okay.
What number is that?
Huh?
- Oh, this again?
- What happened?
The number. You know, multiple choice.
If that's the answer, what number is
- "Did you really have to take everything…"
- Oh, I got it!
"…to feel satisfied"?
- Number five.
- Wait.
Okay, number five.
"Did you really have to take everything
to feel hot and humid?"
RIGHT UP THEIR ALLEY
- Got it!
- Yes?
Number seven.
"Did you really have to take
everything to feel 'satisfactified'?"
- "Satisfactified."
- Got it!
Got it!
Number eight. Number eight.
Oh, here we go.
- Number eight. Say it.
- Okay.
"Did you really have
to take everything to feel…"
- What's wrong with him?
- He's doing it.
Hang on, that was good!
- He sounded just like him!
- I can't do this.
- Wait. Kwang-chul was that a period drama?
- No, no.
It sounded like one.
- Got it!
- Yes?
Number eight, "Did you really
have to take everything
- to feel satisfied?"
- That's too much.
- But that was it. I said it!
- No, it's too much. Okay?
- It's too much.
- Seriously!
- You need to keep it simple.
- That's what he sounds like in the movie!
(DIALING DOWN THE EMOTION)
- Go.
- "Did you really have to take everything
to feel satisfied?"
What was that? Pansori?
What is this? A folk tale?
Okay, me.
- Me. Number eight.
- Okay, go.
"Did you really have to take everything
to feel satisfied?"
DING, DING, DING, DING
Yeah!
- You got it.
- Oh, sorry.
- Don't do the dance!
- That was it.
- Come on, what's the difference?
You got it.
- What's the difference?
- He gave the right performance that time.
Okay, Kwang-chul, you got it.
Which scientist proved
the heliocentric theory?
- Got it!
- Yes?
Galileo Galilei?
NAM-JIN FROM TEAM KWANG-SOO
WINS ROUND 4
- Whoa! Who are you?
- Yeah!
Hey, now that's my brother!
What is the meaning of "IMYS"?
"I'll make you a superstar."
SANG-SOON FROM TEAM YE-EUN
WINS ROUND 5
- You have three seconds.
- Got it!
- I got it!
- Sung Yu-ri, Lee Jin.
You got it! Correct.
TEAM YE-EUN WINS ROUND 6
- Got it!
- Yes?
Yeah!
Everyone, this time, it's a team round.
Please sit in a line, six per team.
I'm waiting for the physical one.
Everyone, it's a close game right now,
so let's hear your cheers.
Okay. Team Ye-eun, ready? Go.
- Victory…
- …is ours!
- Team Woo-seok.
- One, two, three.
Hey, hey, hey!
- One, two, three!
- Victory is ours, ours, ours!
WHISPERING ABOUT SOMETHING
- They're copying us again. Stop it.
- They're copying us!
- Team Kwang-soo.
- Victory! Victory is…
…ours, ours, ours, ours!
Oh, come on.
Your cheer is a bit… you know.
- It's a bit lame.
- That's right.
Yeah.
All right! For this next round,
when I point to you, you're going to take
turns completing the phrase I start.
- Okay, I see.
- Got it?
- Are you ready? Okay.
- Yes.
DRAMA SERIES
- Reborn…
- Rich.
It's Okay… Okay, next.
I guess Sang-soon doesn't watch TV at all.
He doesn't watch any TV.
How is he supposed to know?
Even if he doesn't,
- there's nothing I can do.
- You should sit this out.
I can't help him out, I'm sorry.
All right, here we go.
Daily Dose of…
- Sickness.
- Nope.
- Sickness?
- It's "sunshine."
- "Sunshine," okay?
- What are you talking about?
It's "sunshine."
Oh, "sunshine."
"Sunshine." Yeah, that's right.
All right. Here we go.
21st Century…
Earth Boys.
- Oh, Byeon Woo-seok stars in it.
- Oh, yeah, that's right.
21st Century Girl.
- Oh, yeah. Yeah, exactly.
- Let's go.
Okay, let's go. Taejo…
Baek Jong.
What did you say?
It actually is Wang Geon, isn't it?
- "Taejo Baek Jong"?
- Come on, I made a mistake.
- You certainly did. "Taejo Baek Jong."
- Let me try again.
You missed your chance.
- Youth…
- Comic.
- "Record."
- Come on, you starred in that!
You starred in it.
YOUTH RECORD STARS WOO-SEOK
Hey, that's not cool!
- Wow, seriously.
- That was a tough one.
How do you think that makes
your costars feel?
Youth Record.
Hey, sometimes it just
doesn't come to you right away.
Right.
I'm sorry, but are you
Woo-seok's guardian angel?
- I mean, he's on a different team, so why…
- Why defend him?
- Sometimes it just doesn't. That's all.
- Yes, very true.
- Okay, here we go.
- Let's go, Ha-na!
Let's go!
SONG TITLE
- "Password…"
- "486."
"Time of…"
- "Our Life."
- Oh, good.
"Dy…"
BAILING
Ah.
- What's "Ty"?
- "Dynamite. Dynamite."
Oh, "Dy"?
You've got to pronounce it clearly!
- I thought it was "Ty."
- Articulate!
Why are you getting upset?
- I thought you said "Ty."
- So did I!
What'd you think it was?
- Boo!
- I thought you said "Ty," seriously.
- Boo.
Boo.
You all heard it wrong! Boo.
GOING OFF
- What are you doing?
- What do you mean?
You're the ones who heard it wrong. Okay?
- It was "Dy."
- "Dy."
- We got this.
- Okay. Here we go.
- Reborn…
- Rich.
- I'm Sorry…
- I Love You.
What Happened…
- In Bali.
- What happened… in Bali?
- He's foreign.
- Cut him some slack.
- He's a foreigner.
- He's a foreigner! He wouldn't know.
- No, wait a second.
Bryan, I'm so disappointed in you.
You didn't know the answer,
but when Lee-joong told you,
you looked all innocent
and went, "In Bali?"
- He's a foreigner.
- Unacceptable!
- No! Why?
Okay. Here we go.
Because This is…
My First Life.
- The Tale of…
- Lady Ok.
- Good.
- I'm Sorry…
I Love You.
Coffee Prince…
- The 3rd Store.
- The 3rd Store!
The 1st Shop.
COFFEE PRINCE THE 3RD STORE?
- There's a third store?
- Wait.
Wait, what do you mean, third?
- Is it a franchise?
- It's a franchise.
Well, they must've made a lot of money.
They could've had more.
- When did they open a third store?
- Seriously.
Gong Yoo must be rich by now.
- Okay. Here we go.
- Oh.
Let's go. Focus, this is our chance.
- Old…
- Boy.
- One Fine…
- Spring Day.
- Tae Guk Gi…
- The Brotherhood of War.
- 12.12…
- The Day.
ONLY 2 PEOPLE LEFT!
That's too easy!
- Welcome to…
- Dongmakgol.
- Architecture…
- 101.
THRILLED
It's okay. Good job, everyone. Good job.
The winner of this round
is Team Kwang-soo.
TEAM KWANG-SOO WINS
THE TEAM ROUND
Of course we won. Well done, everyone!
All right.
Next up is the Delivery Box Game!
- Let's get started. Please gather around.
- Up to the front. Come on.
- Let's get closer. Need to be able to see.
- Like this, right?
So, for the Delivery Box Game,
the way it works
is whoever guesses
what's inside the box first wins.
Let's take a look.
CHECKING WHAT'S INSIDE
All right.
Look closely.
ONCE TO THIS SIDE
ONCE TO THAT SIDE
- I think it must be on the top shelf.
- Yeah, it must be.
I can't see.
Please! Turn it around. Please.
All right,
I'll give you all a little hint.
What?
- What?
- Here, here, here.
A QUICK PEEK
- I know.
- Yes?
- A balloon.
- It's not a balloon.
- I got it. A sock.
- No.
- I know. Colored paper?
- I'm pretty sure it was pink.
- I know.
- A sponge. It's a sponge.
- No.
I know. I know!
Okay, take another look.
Wait, hyung. Come on!
I called it right after she did.
Why are you…
- He seems upset.
- I said it right after her!
There were too many guesses.
Look closely again.
I'll bring it right up to your face.
DELIVERED RIGHT TO YOUR FACE
My eyes are going.
Focus.
You never know when it's going to open.
Oh! I missed it!
What? Wow.
- That startled me.
- That was super quick!
- Damn, that's crazy. Seriously.
- That was super quick. Like lightning.
I couldn't see.
RIGHT ON TO THE NEXT MOVE
All right.
- Got it!
- I know!
WHIPS IT WITH THE COVER OPEN
- Got it!
- I know!
- Yes?
- A toothbrush.
- Not toothbrush.
- Got it.
- Yes?
- An onion bag.
Not onion bag.
It's pink and kind of long like this.
- It looked like some kind of netting.
- Okay.
Look closely again.
FOCUSED
Get ready.
Oh!
What is it?
Oh, my gosh.
- Oh, I know!
- Okay. Yes?
- I know!
- A bokjumeoni.
Not bokjumeoni.
- A cone hat.
- Not cone hat.
- A jegi.
- Not a jegi.
I know. An hourglass.
- Not hourglass.
- What is it?
- It was some kind of fabric.
- Yeah.
Like, it was all frayed.
I know. A norigae?
Your answer is a norigae. That's correct!
I-AN FROM TEAM KWANG-SOO ANSWER:
A NORIGAE
- No way!
- Here, it's a norigae.
Well done.
- How?
- Ah!
- That was tough.
- What?
I didn't even know
that's called a norigae.
- Well done.
- That was tough.
Really, that was a tough one.
How did she know?
BIG PLAY
Well done, everyone.
- That was awesome.
- This was tough.
All right, then.
How about a final round for two points?
- Whoa.
- A team round.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- We got this guys, focus.
- Get ready for a team round.
- For two points, right?
- Yes.
It's worth two points,
so any team can still take first place.
- The category is culture and arts.
- Okay.
It sounds hard.
Oh. Sounds tough.
TENSE OVER
THE CULTURE & ARTS QUESTION
RING, RING
A PHONE RINGS FROM SOMEWHERE
Sorry.
Hey, that scared me. What?
Is that your cell phone? Hey!
That scared me!
I thought I was supposed to do something!
Yeah, me too.
I thought it was part of the question.
I thought we were getting
a surprise mission.
That really scared me!
What are you thinking
having a ringtone like that?
- That's usually the mission cue.
- Terrifying.
- I know.
- Yeah.
All right.
The category is culture and arts.
In traditional East Asian painting,
the Four Gentlemen refers
to paintings of four plants.
- Got it!
- Yes?
POCB.
- Oh, that's right.
- All right.
Name the four plants of POCB.
- Got it.
- Got it. Plum blossom…
- Bryan!
- Plum blossom, orchid,
chrysanthemum, bamboo.
He got it right.
- What's with all the suspense?
- He's right.
CORRECT
- Wow. Amazing!
- Ice water in his veins!
- Impressive!
- What?
- Wow, he's good.
- Bryan.
Bryan!
- Unbelievable!
- Wow.
This is why it's important for you
to always remain calm under pressure.
All right, now we have a winner!
The winner is Team Ji Ye-eun.
1ST PLACE: TEAM YE-EUN
- Victory…
- …is ours!
Team Lee Kwang-soo takes second place.
Team Byeon Woo-seok
takes third place. So close.
Did you enjoy the Cushion Quiz?
Yes!
Now it's time for dinner.
I'll see you all in a bit. Thank you!
THE CUSHION QUIZ IS OVER!
Great job, guys.
- Great work.
- I had so much fun.
- Good job, everyone, good job.
- Great job.
Wow, Bryan.
How did you know POCB?
I mean, that was something.
My throat is so sore. I yelled too much.
Sore throat?
I haven't yelled like that in a long time.
It's tiring!
We should have dinner around 6:30 or 7.
Yes.
Good job, guys.
- That felt like a dream.
- You're right. It was great.
- This is fun!
- Yeah.
AFTER THE GAMES,
THE PLACE FEELS DIFFERENT
It's a lot of fun playing a game from TV.
- It is, right?
- Yeah.
Wanna get a snack?
- Yeah, I want coffee.
- All right, let's go.
I'd love an Americano.
A pick-me-up.
- Honey.
- Yeah?
I'm so tired.
You're tired already?
Is this okay?
Lie down.
OUT OF ENERGY
You need to work on your social skills.
Everyone yells.
You won't survive in this world
if you don't yell.
What kind of life have you been living?
This is a world
where you have to yell to be heard.
It was hilarious.
- Jae-seok's good, isn't he?
- Yeah, he's so funny.
The top shelf is pizza,
these are red bean…
- Ah, red bean.
- …and these are vegetable.
- Okay, vegetable.
- Looks good.
- These are vegetable. Yeah.
- Sweet potato.
Mmm.
It's good.
SUGAR BOOST WITH WINTER SNACKS
Wow, Bryan, you're just…
Bryan.
You knew the Four Gentlemen.
I bet you did well in school.
Oh, no, not really.
Right, we're not supposed to ask.
This is frustrating.
EVEN KNOWS THE FOUR GENTLEMEN
WHAT'S HIS IDENTITY?
- Should we head out now?
- Let's go.
GROCERY RUN FOR DINNER
When I lived on Jeju,
I went to the store all the time.
But since I moved to Seoul,
I haven't been.
- Ah, you get delivery.
- I get delivery.
I love it.
Were the three of you close before this?
- We met here for the first time.
- We just met.
- Oh, with the last group.
- That's right.
What's your MBTI, Sang-soon?
I'm an INFP.
Oh!
- What's yours?
- I'm an ISFP.
- I? I see, you're an introvert too.
- I'm an ISFP too.
- You are too?
- Yeah, me too.
- We're all I's.
- I'm an INTJ.
- Jae-seok is an ISFP too.
- Yeah.
What about Hyo-ri?
- ENFP.
- ENFP?
But, hyung,
you don't seem like an I to me.
- Right. Honestly…
- Oh, really?
- …Kwang-soo seems like an E.
- I got to say, hyung, you really don't.
Maybe. But I'm shy
around strangers. I'm reserved.
Yeah, that's true.
And it's hard to get close to you.
Right, yeah.
What stage are we at, hyung?
With you guys? We're close.
- Really?
- I'm totally comfortable with you now.
- Oh, really?
- So does that mean
I can tell people we're close?
- Are you kidding? Of course you can!
- Aw.
GRINNING
- Hello.
- Hold on.
- Should we go in order?
First, we need green onions.
- This will do, won't it?
- Yeah, looks good.
Yeah. And cabbage.
Hyung, two of these?
- Let's use one more. Yeah.
- Three?
Will two tubs of doenjang be enough?
Grab two more.
Should we get two packs
of spinach or just one?
- Three.
- Three?
Yeah, we need a lot for the soup.
- Really?
- We need a lot of spinach.
Let's go with seafood broth packets.
Tofu for stew, pork cutlet sauce,
pickled radish. That's it, right?
GROCERY SHOPPING DONE
That's everything.
Man, you were so funny.
MEANWHILE AT JAE-SEOK'S B&B
- Aren't you tired, oppa?
- No, I'm fine.
But when we made 20 servings
of kimchi fried rice for lunch earlier,
man, I was wiped out.
Before we started the game, I thought,
"I'm too old for this,"
but I was wrong!
We played a lot of games on Family Outing.
- Yeah, that's right.
- And that was 15 years ago.
Can you believe how much time has passed?
It was really fun back then,
playing those games.
We had a blast.
We can't do it like that anymore.
No, we can't.
- Want a snack?
- Is there a snack bar?
- Yeah, we've got everything ready.
- Ooh!
- I'll do that.
- I got it.
- Go ahead and get some snacks.
- Okay.
WHILE HYO-RI GOES
TO GRAB A SNACK
JAE-SEOK SNEAKS IN A QUICK CLEAN
- Hello?
- Your delivery's here.
- Oh, you mean the pork katsu?
- That's right.
Gosh. Hold on.
THE PREORDERED PORK KATSU
HAVE ARRIVED
Food…
OFF TO PICK UP THE PORK KATSU
So this is the snack bar.
Hyo-ri is coming. What do we do?
- They've got sweet potatoes, huh?
- Hyo-ri, have some of this.
- What's that?
- Honey hotteok.
- It's honey hotteok.
- Oh.
Are you going to stay
with us the whole time?
- We're leaving tomorrow.
- Aw.
- That's a shame.
I'd love to do yoga with Hyo-ri.
How about tomorrow morning?
I'd love to. Definitely.
- Oh, my gosh, I can't believe this.
- This is so cool!
- Oh, yeah.
- Awesome.
HYO-RI'S YOGA CLASS
Do you guys make reels and stuff?
- Just some dance videos.
- Why don't we make one together?
- Oh, my gosh!
- Wow, really?
- Are you serious?
- Pick a dance.
- I need to learn it first.
- Of course.
Is it hard?
Pick something a girl in her 40s can do.
- Bam, bam, bam.
- One, two, three, four.
- One, two, three and four.
- Right arm like this.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Careful, dude, you're making us seem old.
- Should we try it with the music?
- Yes!
- Everyone, look at the mirror.
- Let's do it!
A 1ST-GEN K-POP GROUP LEADER'S
REEL TIME
Let's just try the step-out.
- One, two, bam.
- Bam.
I should've gone out farther. Again.
- Don't go too far.
- Okay.
Dad's in the center. You don't step out.
- Just spread your arms.
- Like this.
Hey, would you mind blowing
the bubbles over this way?
- Oh!
- Yeah.
Over us, like this.
- Wow.
- That's lovely.
Okay, good. More, more, more.
This way.
Ready, set, go.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
Yeah, come on.
Come on.
- Ooh, yes. Come on. Yes.
- Come on.
OUT OF NOWHERE,
IT'S "COME ON" TIME
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
GIVES UP
Why does he keep saying "come on"?
What's wrong with your dad, Chae-won?
I can't get into it otherwise.
I need a "come on."
I bet your dad
used to party back in his day.
I bet he got something good.
All right, it's pork katsu!
Pork katsu!
All right, please take them inside.
Sure.
No way.
- We have to deep-fry it.
- Oh, they're gonna deep-fry it here?
- Yeah, they do it here.
- Wow.
- Pretty fancy, huh? Right?
- Yeah.
When it comes to food, we don't hold back.
Aren't you here with your brother?
- Yeah, I am.
- Who's your brother, Nam-jin?
- Nam-soon.
- Oh, Nam-soon.
He's over there.
We're not brother and sister.
I know that now.
You guys are brothers, here together.
NAM-SOON, OCCUPATION: ??
NAM-JIN, OCCUPATION: ??
Hye-jeong, did you make a video?
Oh, yeah, we're making
a video together. Join us.
What kind of video?
Wow!
LAUGHING
IN THE ZONE
- What are you doing?
- What?
What's with…
You're supposed to make up
a dance like this at the end.
- What's this?
- Free-style at the end,
- right?
- Hey, Jae-seok.
- Yeah?
- Can you make a reel with us?
What you got?
First, Hyo-ri and I will stand here
and shoot you up.
- You just jump like this.
- From both sides?
- Come closer.
- Can you tell me what it's for first?
- Just do it.
- Yeah.
- One…
- One, two, three.
…three.
- Like this?
- Yes, that was good.
Do body rolls like this.
- Like this?
- But face that way.
- But that way.
- Yeah.
Don't jump at us!
- I'm not jumping at you. What?
- Just get closer. Closer.
NOT SURE WHAT'S GOING ON,
BUT DOING AS TOLD
Oh, like…
- You and me…
- You and me walking down the street
This is actually kind of a workout,
- right?
- Yeah, it is.
AFTER A FULL ROUND OF REEL FUN
- Are you hungry?
- Yeah.
Wait, what's going on
with these sweet potatoes?
Are they cooking or not?
I don't think they are.
CRUNCHY
Yup, that's raw.
- Get the big ones, Kwang-soo.
- Okay.
PREPPED SINCE 10 A.M.
This machine isn't working.
STILL NOT COOKING HOURS LATER
The temperature?
- It should be higher, right?
- Maybe that's the problem.
- This is as high as it goes.
- Right.
- What is it?
- It's not working.
WHAT COULD BE THE PROBLEM?
- Oh, come on! I made a mistake.
- You're supposed to use this.
There's a space underneath the coals
where you're supposed
to roast the sweet potatoes.
This is where you put
the ones that are already cooked.
Man, of course.
We've been trying to cook them
for ten hours.
No wonder it wasn't working.
(FINALLY IN THE RIGHT PLACE)
Of course, that's why.
I just kept thinking,
"Why aren't they cooking?"
How old did you say you were?
- We're not supposed to tell yet.
- Ah.
- But you're around my age.
- That's why I haven't told.
When I was a high school senior,
my dream was to marry you,
I tried to study,
but you kept distracting me like…
Here, look at me.
So I kept looking at you
and couldn't concentrate.
You know, his jokes aren't funny,
but he really tries, huh?
Is he always like this?
Yeah, he likes to joke.
WHO IS THIS DAD WHO'S SO HUNGRY
FOR DANCING AND JOKES?
CURRENT TIME 5:30 P.M.
(1 HOUR UNTIL DINNER)
- Are we gonna cook in here?
- Yeah.
The pork katsu's already here.
Oh, it's here?
- Do we have plates though?
- Yeah, we do.
How much water do we need for soup?
Whoa!
Let me get that.
You're all talk.
You just said you'd get it.
- You only said it to get it on mic.
- No, that's not--
You knew nobody can
actually see down there.
- No, I said I'd get it.
- Your hands weren't moving.
No, I got it.
You said you would
but you didn't even move your hands.
Oh, get out of here.
More?
- Just a little more than half. Yeah.
- Mmm.
- Whoa, you just sounded like…
- I sounded like… like a pro, right?
Like you owned a gukbap joint
for 40 years.
I'm boiling the water.
BOILS WATER FOR DOENJANG SOUP
AND HEATS UP OIL FOR PORK KATSU
- Okay, they're back.
- Oh, they're here.
- Good job, everyone.
- Well done.
Good work.
Oh, honey.
- Channeling Jang-geum?
- Who, me?
The vibe's already different.
So I guess we'll be running
everything by you two today.
HAIR UP
APRON ON
HEAD CHEF LEE HYO-RI
SOUS CHEF LEE SANG-SOON
How can I help? What should I do?
It'd be great if you could slice this.
Sit over there.
- Should I cut the onions?
- Yeah.
- Ye-eun, we need to slice the tofu.
- Oh, okay.
- Then you cook the rice, oppa.
- All right, I'll do it.
(RICE) - (GREEN ONION)
(CABBAGE) - (TOFU)
TASKS ASSIGNED IN A FLASH
It's so nice to have
someone take charge of the food.
It's easier. So much easier.
Hey, Hyo-ri, it's really great
to have you and Sang-soon.
Man, I've got nothing to worry about now.
MEASURING OUT RICE
Do we need more?
- We're gonna need way more than that.
- Really?
That right there is only enough
for six or seven people at most.
Just two more cups should do it. Yeah.
- This should do it.
- Yeah.
- I'll let the rice soak a bit first.
- Okay.
We don't have enough time
to soak it, so just cook it.
- Oh, you heard that?
- Yes.
- Thanks for paying attention.
- Sure.
I'm always watching you.
Can I cook this behind you?
It's kinda crowded there.
- You can do it behind me.
- Yeah, that's okay?
You know, I think
you're especially nice to Woo-seok.
Nuna, we have these!
We have these too.
Oh, good.
(DONE)
Come on, give Kwang-soo
something more than that.
Nuna, it was really hard to find these.
Kwang-soo, you're…
- I wasn't gonna say anything…
- You've been doing a good job.
You treat the two of them so different.
- They were hard to find.
- Right, I see.
- Thank you so much.
- All right.
PLEASED
MEANWHILE, WOO-SEOK IS…?
FOCUSING ON SLICING CABBAGE
- You're better than I expected.
- You're good at that, oppa.
I guess eggs just weren't my thing.
This feels good.
EGG GUY FINDS A NEW TALENT
I think I'm good at chopping onions.
I think I'm good at slicing cabbage.
Look how even it is.
A lot of people end up cutting themselves.
SMOOTH SAILING AT EVERY STATION
This big?
Hey, you know what?
For the first time, this kitchen
actually feels peaceful and organized.
- Totally.
- Honestly,
my confidence just went up.
I actually feel like I'm good
at cooking right now.
- We're doing it!
- I know, right?
When are they gonna share
their jobs and personal life?
Tomorrow. Their jobs and ages.
Tomorrow?
That's right.
YE-EUN FINISHES CUTTING TOFU
FOR THE DOENJANG SOUP
Done.
I'll cut the radish.
MOVING RIGHT ON
TO CUTTING PICKLED RADISH
But maybe don't do it here because it…
- it might get on the cabbage.
- Oh, I see.
Then what do I do?
- Just imagine there's a line here.
- Okay.
I'll stay on this side.
- Is this about the right length?
- Yeah, that looks good. Mmm.
I don't know.
CHOPPING IN BIG CHUNKS
- Wait, the radish…
- What about it?
You keep inching over this way.
Oh, really?
(PROTECTING HIS CABBAGE)
Try cutting a bit more neatly.
Instead of cutting it all at once,
how about doing five pieces at a time?
The cabbage is getting pickle juice
all over it right now.
It's all covered.
- Ye-eun.
- Oh. Yes?
DO BETTER, WILL YOU?
Hyo-ri didn't use to let that slide.
"Hey, Ye-eun!"
He's right, yeah.
Just be glad you met me now.
Back in the day, she wasn't so patient.
THE SOUS CHEF'S COOKING QUIETLY
BY HIMSELF
CAREFUL HEAT CONTROL
PRECISE TEMPERATURE CHECK
The katsu look amazing.
Whoa!
Look at the katsu.
- Wait, what? You already fried them?
- Look at them, hyung.
They look store-bought.
- That's a nice color.
- It's just about there.
Whoa!
I think we should give them
one more quick deep-fry.
DOUBLE-FRYING
FOR EXTRA CRISPINESS
Hyung, try one.
- All right.
- See if they're cooked well.
HOW DOES SANG-SOON'S
PORK CUTLET TASTE?
Wow.
- Mmm!
- Whoa!
- Is it good?
- Very good.
Okay.
- It's good? Is it cooked through?
- It's so good. Yeah.
- Really, really good.
- Well done.
DEEP-FRYING FISH KATSU
FOR HYO-RI
Put them here and I'll cut 'em.
Nice cutting.
It's all sliced.
The pork katsu looks insane right now.
PORK CUTLET SET COMPLETE
TO THE DOENJANG BROTH
+GREEN ONIONS
+TOFU
WITH SPINACH PREPPED BY HYO-RI
Okay, the soup's done.
DOENJANG SOUP COMPLETE
I'm actually excited for our meal.
Yeah, me too.
Feels like a hotel.
If I could cook like you guys,
this would actually be fun.
I wish the first group of
guests could've gotten a meal like this.
Ah, man.
- What time is it, oppa?
- It's about 6:20.
The timing's perfect.
We're all set, right?
- We should eat while it's hot.
- You think so?
- I'll call them over then.
- Yeah.
All right, you must be hungry.
- It's dinner time!
- Nice!
RELAXED, CONFIDENT
- Okay!
- Oh, okay.
- Nice.
- Let's go.
This place
really has a nice vibe at night.
It's all the lights.
I'm hungry. Yeah.
- Smells good in here.
- Welcome.
We've got pork katsu.
- This is doenjang soup.
- Yeah.
The ones at the end are fish katsu,
so if you don't eat pork,
you can have those.
If you like fish, feel free to have it.
I'm just gonna put
some fish katsu aside for Hyo-ri.
I'll put your soup here.
Thank you.
This is basically a hotel.
Looks a bit better than lunch, right?
- Yeah, it looks way better.
- Totally.
You don't want this?
- No.
- No veggies for her.
Oh. We worked really hard on it.
- Oh, then I'll have some.
- Thanks.
- This much?
- Yeah.
Great. Wow.
Can I take over?
Sure, but this is actually
pretty hard to scoop.
- Oh, no. Let's just share one.
- Got it. He's ladling it out for us too.
- I know, I can see.
- Are there enough plates?
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm taking this home.
Do you want the ladle too?
LIMITED EDITION WOO-SEOK MERCH
Do you like spinach and tofu?
- Oh, yeah.
- I like them.
- Okay, enjoy.
- I'll eat anything you give me.
You're so silly.
All right, enjoy, everyone.
- Thank you for the food.
- Enjoy!
Oh, man!
The pork is good.
This is good.
Mmm. Oh.
- It's good.
- Yeah, it's really good.
I don't know.
- Maybe I should take some medicine first?
- Huh? All right.
- Want me to go with you?
- Why? What's…
Her stomach's a little upset.
Oh, really? You want something for it?
Hyung, would you take over?
- I got it, it's okay.
- Thanks.
- If you wait inside…
- Oh, okay.
…I'll go check to see
if we have some antacids.
FIRST SICK GUEST AT THE B&B
Does it feel like you ate something
and it's not sitting right?
No, I just have this pain in my stomach.
BRINGS HER SOME WARM WATER
- Here's some water.
- Oh, okay.
Thank you.
Here it is.
We've got Tylenol
and something for indigestion.
- I'll try these.
- Mmm.
You don't usually take
anything specific, right?
- That's right.
- Hmm.
Thank you.
One pill should do it.
- If it gets worse, just let me know…
- Sure.
- …and I'll do whatever I can.
- Oh, okay. Thanks.
I'm here to help.
Just ask.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
CALMLY COMPLETES FIRST AID
It's our turn now.
- Hey, Woo-seok, come eat.
- All right.
This is good.
- The amount of rice is just perfect.
- Yeah?
If you hadn't added more,
it wouldn't have been enough, right?
You were right on the money.
- It's just right.
- Wow, that's incredible.
Yes, it is.
A BITE OF FISH CUTLET
Mmm.
- The fish.
- Wow.
It's so good.
Ah, the soup is great.
Wow, it's really good.
So, pros just don't miss.
But I think this is my first time
cooking this much food.
EVEN 1ST-GEN B&B HOSTS
NEVER COOKED THIS MUCH
Back on Family Outing,
when we made doenjang soup,
it was supposed to be six servings,
but he'd toss in, like, three anchovies.
I'd never made it before.
Still, you should've known
better than that.
Bryan, how's the food?
- It's delicious. Yeah.
- Is it okay?
Get enough, Chae-won?
- Yeah, I had a lot.
- Oh, yeah?
SEUNG-JUN GETS
A PORK CUTLET REFILL
You're really digging in.
I only got three hours
of sleep last night,
so I figured I should at least eat
a lot to get some energy back.
Why so little sleep?
Too excited?
Oh, um…
Do you get off work at two?
- I was on the phone.
- With who? Your girlfriend?
- Hey, now…
- She's grilling him. So intense!
- No questions.
- So scary!
You can't get into that much detail here.
But you're curious.
Don't you wanna know who he called?
I get the sense you're a musician.
- I'm nowhere near being a musician.
- Oh, okay.
Well, I was just guessing.
I had a feeling I was way off.
- May I dip it in your sauce?
- Yeah.
STEALING HIS SAUCE
Sang-soon, I heard you played
metal music for a bit.
- Yeah, I did, when I was younger.
- Oh, yeah?
Is there a reason you didn't stick
with metal and moved on to another genre?
- He must be a musician.
- Yeah.
I just like music.
I listen to pretty much everything.
WHO IS SEUNG-JUN,
THE ONE HYO-RI'S CURIOUS ABOUT?
Are we doing
another activity after dinner?
- Fire gazing.
- Oh, yeah?
Hey, Sang-soon.
When we have the fire later,
why don't you pluck out a tune for us?
Well…
- Like a chicken?
- What?
You said "pluck," didn't you?
This is fish.
Oh, yeah, thanks.
Good for you, Min-ju.
Oh!
- Enjoy your meal.
- Hope you enjoy.
- Dig in, everyone.
- Enjoy your meal.
QUICKLY CHECKING HOW SHE LOOKS
We've got plenty of katsu,
so grab more if you'd like.
Okay.
DIZZY
She's totally lost it.
You're acting like a little girl
with her first crush.
- She found her crush.
- You're blushing.
So, during the off-season,
do you take a break
or do you keep training?
Personally, I take about ten days off,
then get back to training.
- Yeah, something like that.
- Wow.
But honestly, even when I'm on a break,
I still go to the gym and work out.
- That's your break?
- Yeah.
That's amazing.
Whoa. Whoa!
What's wrong with her?
Your ears are all red.
SUSPICIOUS BEHAVIOR DETECTED
- Hey, hold on.
- Yeah?
Yeah?
Just… No, wait.
You're looking at Woo-seok like…
Hye-jeong, what's going on with you guys?
You were staring at him!
I mean--
- This is Jae-seok's B&B.
- Oh, right.
Time to snap out of it!
- Yes, Mr. Host.
- I'm sorry, this is Jae-seok's B&B Rules!,
not Woo-seok's.
All right?
Oppa, look. They're satisfied today.
ALL SATISFIED
"SATISFACTORY"
WITHOUT A SECOND THOUGHT
This deserves two of these,
seriously. It deserves two.
I'm glad. Really glad.
I'll wash. You guys rinse.
- You can put some of them in here.
- Can we use that?
- The scrubber?
- Yeah, I'll use this.
Hello.
Hey, rocker.
I think everyone knows.
Knows what?
You're a rocker, right?
I'm not that good,
- but I just sing with confidence.
- Are you the lead singer?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
I actually major in computer engineering.
What do you think about AI
replacing everything these days?
I do think it's possible.
You think that'll happen soon?
What if AI ends up controlling humans?
Are you interested in AI? 'Cause you--
Well, it's just that these days,
when composers send me songs,
- like, demos…
- Yeah. Oh, I see.
…they send them using my voice.
- So it's already being used like that?
- Mmm.
I think you get more depth
from a real voice.
Mmm.
That instant emotional pull?
It still feels like AI
can't quite do that yet.
Hyung,
should we get the firewood?
Yeah, let's get the wood.
Dad actually runs a camp ground.
- He runs one. Yeah.
- Wow, really?
- He's great at fires.
- Oh, really?
- Can you come with us?
- Jae-seok!
- What?
Why?
- Hyung! Their dad runs a camp ground.
- Oh, really?
SMILING FROM EAR TO EAR
- Is that so?
- We were helping him out just last week.
Let's go then. Come on, come on.
We were there handing out
roasted sweet potatoes.
That sounds great.
Is this the firewood here?
- Yeah, it is.
- That's right.
6,000 won, please.
6,000 won?
- Sure, let's do it together.
- Wanna give us a hand?
- You wanna pass it to me?
- I'll take it from here.
You know how this works.
LOADING UP ON FIREWOOD
All right. Okay.
Over there, to the middle of the field.
I bet you know how to stack 'em too.
Yeah.
Perfect timing.
- Right?
- Clockwork.
- So, for fire gazing…
- These are better?
- Yeah, dry firewood is better.
- That's right.
Make a hashtag shape.
I'm so glad you know what you're doing.
SETTING UP CHAIRS
AROUND THE FIRE
AND STARTING THE FIRE LIKE A PRO
Oh, nice, it's catching.
All right, would all our guests
who are loving their time
at Jae-seok's B&B,
- come to the fire gazing?
- Okay.
- I should go bundle up.
- We've got a bonfire
outside to keep things warm.
Come on out, gather around,
and warm yourselves up by the fire.
This is what I'm talking about.
Come on out.
THEY GATHER BY THE FIRE
The fire's going strong.
- It's big, right?
- Yeah.
- This is it.
- Oppa, come sit.
THEY ZONE OUT BY THE FIRE
TOGETHER ON THEIR FIRST NIGHT
By the way, I wonder where Woo-seok is.
I wonder where Woo-seok is.
LOOKING AROUND FOR WOO-SEOK
WHO HASN'T SHOWN UP
Woo-seok isn't coming.
- What?
- Really?
- Yeah, he's not coming.
- Why?
I told him to get some rest inside.
- Oh.
- Really?
I'm suddenly tired.
JUST THEN, A TALL GUY SHOWS UP
KWANG-SOO INSTEAD OF WOO-SEOK
Why are there papers on your coat?
They're not papers.
It's part of the design.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
Looks like you got into a fight.
No, it's the design.
It's the coat's design.
He's trying to go head-to-head
with Woo-seok.
What do you mean, head-to-head?
It's a real competition now.
HIS RIVAL SHOWS UP
A WAVE THAT MAKES
YOUR HEART RACE
You're here.
- Your eyes will sting over there.
- The smoke. Sit over here.
Come sit here.
- Oh, he's sitting there.
- He went the other way.
Hyung, can't you see I'm crying over here?
What does it matter
if you're crying, Kwang-soo?
- Kwang-soo.
- Go on, cry your eyes out.
MOVES HIS SEAT ON HIS OWN
FIRE GAZING TIME
It's nice to stare into the fire.
I haven't done this in forever.
- It's warm.
- It is, isn't it?
It's nice and toasty.
Ah, it's really warm over here.
- Wow, look at the leaves falling.
- Wow, that's beautiful.
- Wow, look at that.
- Whoa.
- Wow, they're really coming down.
- Oh, my.
- Autumn's really settling in.
- It really is.
AUTUMN DEEPENS
Yeah.
AND THE NIGHT DEEPENS TOO
Wow, this is romantic.
This is the best campfire ever.
GATHERED UNDER THE AUTUMN
NIGHT SKY, GAZING INTO THE FIRE
This is so satisfying.
Hey, Sang-soon, play us some guitar.
Should I?
HE BROUGHT HIS GUITAR
FOR THIS MOMENT
- Wow, really?
- This is awesome.
I guess this is what I'm here for.
I can't believe I'm seeing this in person.
- I know.
- Incredible.
PRO MODE ON
- Oh, "Beach Again"?
- "Beach Again."
- Oh, wow! Sounds great.
- "Beach Again." Yeah.
"BEACH AGAIN" IS
A PROJECT GROUP SONG
BY JAE-SEOK, HYO-RI, AND RAIN,
COMPOSED BY SANG-SOON
WITH LYRICS BY HYO-RI
Ah, this is nice.
"BEACH AGAIN" BY SSAK3
Everyone, all together.
My heart
Is fluttering again
Being here with you
Breathing the same air
In this moment
I thought I'd never
See you again
That you were just a memory
So I put you away
Tucked deep inside a drawer
- Oppa, it's your part.
- Mine?
As time kept flowing
The memories of you and me
Only faded more and more
I thought it was over
ONE! TWO!
Last summer at the beach
Wait, you want me to sing?
Just the two of us
DOESN'T KNOW THE LYRICS,
JUST FEELING IT
Because I was with you
I shone even brighter
And became a star
Uh, we should start over.
Let's start over.
CAN'T HIT HIGH NOTES
All Min-ju's fault.
A round of applause!
THE BONFIRE TIME CONTINUES
Whoa!
Oh, that was good.
THE NIGHT DEEPENS
AROUND A SINGLE FIRE
All right, so,
it's just about 8:30 right now.
The night's starting to wind down.
The fire's still going,
so feel free to enjoy it a bit longer.
Then, right at 10 o'clock will be…
- Lights out.
- …lights out.
And as for tomorrow,
I think you can wake up around 7.
Sound okay?
- Yes.
- At seven.
Now, as we mentioned earlier,
Director Lee Hyo-ri will graciously
be leading a yoga class in the morning
for you all, as a special event.
If you're interested,
you can join her in the quiz room.
Captains, anything you'd like to say?
Captain Byeon?
I hope you are comfortable
for your first night here.
And I hope this moment
becomes a great memory for you.
- Aw!
- Good night, yeah.
Okay, I'm done.
- Okay, hold on.
- Yeah, I had a great time today.
COPYING EVERYTHING
WOO-SEOK DOES
It's such a shame
the day's already coming to an end.
I hope you all have a warm night.
Thank you.
It was a lot of fun.
- All right, thank you!
- Thank you.
By the way, what did we decide
about sleeping outdoors?
Oh, that's right.
NOW IT'S NOVEMBER, THE DAY-NIGHT
TEMPERATURE GAP HAS WIDENED
CURRENT TEMPERATURE 4ºC
Aren't you cold?
Yeah, but I'm okay for now.
- You're okay?
- Yeah.
Should I close the doors?
- It's a bit cold.
- Right. Yeah.
JAE-SEOK'S BEEN WORRIED
ABOUT THE COLD WEATHER
I don't think they can
sleep outside tonight.
By dawn, they'll be frozen stiff.
I think it's going to be too cold tonight.
If you can't sleep outside,
we'll look for another option, like
helping out with breakfast or something.
TEAM WOO-SEOK'S PENALTY:
BREAKFAST DUTY
The moon is not even full
and it's so bright.
Wow!
It's so pretty. I should make a wish.
It's not a perfect full moon though.
PLEASE DON'T LET ME CRY
Woo-seok, it's not a perfect full moon,
- so even if you make a wish…
- Oh, I just did it because I wanted to.
- Yeah, but--
- It doesn't matter
if it's a perfect full moon or not.
I just…
Oh, but… I…
NITPICKING EVERY LITTLE THING
WOO-SEOK DOES
…I heard you're not supposed
to make a wish on a moon like that.
- Oh, really?
- It's the law.
What law?
Is that actually written somewhere?
- I don't know exactly where.
- Where? Where exactly…
But I remember hearing that somewhere,
so I thought I'd let you know.
Can you tell me specifically
where you heard that?
- Thank you. Good night.
- See you tomorrow.
- Good night.
Thank you. Good night.
- Good night. Yeah.
- Okay.
KWANG-SOO & WOO-SEOK DOUSE THE
BONFIRE WITH THE REMAINING GUESTS
I saw some cereal. I'll have some of that.
You're hungry now?
Oh, yeah. Now that I'm feeling better.
- Hang on. I'll get it for you.
- You're such a mess.
Or we have some leftover soup.
- Oh, yeah, I would have that.
- All right, hold on.
CHECKING IF THERE'S ANY RICE LEFT
We have a little rice left.
Looking for food?
- Sin-jeong didn't eat.
- Yeah.
Now that she's feeling better,
she's starving all of a sudden.
That's a relief.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
Rice and soup? You want some kimchi?
Yeah.
You don't really say "no" to things,
do you?
That's hilarious.
SERVING UP A NICE, HOT
BOWL OF SOUP
AND SETTING OUT SOME KIMCHI TOO
- Thank you so much for the food.
- Sure, enjoy.
Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Good night.
- See you. Have a good night.
- Thanks so much.
- See you.
- Enjoy. Good night.
Hey, great work today.
- Yeah, you too.
- Yeah, thanks, you too.
FINALLY, A MOMENT TO BREATHE
Geez.
The day's over at last.
Let's take a look.
- Oh, Chae-won is the…
- The kid.
"I want to play the games
I've only seen on TV."
WISH GRANTED
Chae-eun.
NEXT IS HER SISTER CHAE-EUN
For her captain choice she wrote:
"Anyone, but the handsome
Woo-seok most of all."
That's so funny.
Everyone put down "Byeon Woo-seok."
- She could've left out the handsome part.
- Everyone.
Here. For the food
she wants to eat, Hye-jeong wrote,
"Anything Woo-seok makes,
or the thick-cut samgyeopsal."
Oh, my goodness.
CAPTAIN BYEON IS
ESPECIALLY POPULAR
Wow, all Nam-jin wrote
is he wants to make memories
with his brother.
- There's nothing else he wants to do.
- Wow.
DONE CHECKING
ALL REGISTRATION FORMS
First of all, great work today, guys.
Tomorrow, we'll make porridge
with Sang-soon and Hyo-ri,
and some toast for breakfast.
You said you wanted to make a salad too
- with persimmons and apples?
- Ah, sounds great.
Wait, Sang-soon. Tomorrow morning,
you said you'd make coffee.
Mmm. Oh, yeah, right.
- The coffee.
- But then he'll have to make
the salad, the porridge and the coffee,
so we should take one of those
off his plate.
Peeling and cutting the persimmons,
getting the tangerines ready,
slicing up all the apples.
- Oh, yeah.
- Maybe you guys could assist me.
- We'll just do whatever he tells us to do.
- Yeah.
Just tell us what needs to be done,
and we'll handle it.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Let's get some rest now.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Maybe go to bed early.
- Hold on. What about where we sleep?
Oh, that's right.
Where do you wanna sleep?
Well, I'll just sleep with Ye-eun.
- Just for tonight.
- Are you okay with sleeping separately?
I'll lend him to you.
Then Sang-soon will sleep with the guys.
All right, then. See you guys tomorrow.
- Good work today.
- Yeah.
- Good night, nuna.
- So that's it? Nice and clean.
- Well, let's go.
Nice and clean, right? Namaste.
- Namaste.
- Shanti, shanti.
- Yeah. Shanti, shanti.
GUESTS WASH UP
AND GET READY FOR BED
KWANG-CHUL HEADS OFF ALONE
AFTER SOME UNUSUAL
WARM-UP STRETCHES
THE LATE-NIGHT WORKOUT BEGINS
NOT YOUR AVERAGE BUILD
HIGH-LEVEL MOVES DONE WITH EASE
WHAT'S KWANG-CHUL'S IDENTITY?
AND THERE'S SOMEONE WATCHING HIM
You must work out a lot.
- I try to stay consistent.
- Oh.
If you don't stay consistent,
you fall behind.
SIP
LIKE A PRO
THE GYM'S FILLING UP
ANOTHER ONE STARTS WORKING OUT
WORKING OUT THERE
WORKING OUT HERE
BRYAN - SEUNG-JUN - LEE-JOONG
OCCUPATION: ??
ARE THEY ALL ATHLETES?
A REAL ATHLETE WALKS IN
I'll show you how to do lateral raises.
All right, keep count.
One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven…
NATIONAL TEAM
A WHOLE DIFFERENT LEVEL
I can still feel it here.
What if I wake up at five
in the morning tomorrow?
Come here.
- Huh?
- Come here.
Let's go to sleep.
I'll just hide here.
You look beautiful.
Come here.
CHIEF YU'S BACK FROM HIS SHOWER
Huh?
Uh, what are you doing?
- What?
- She's gonna sleep here.
- But--
- We're married. Why not?
What… Oh, for God's sake.
Look, this isn't a date.
What is the matter with you?
JAE-SEOK'S B&B RULES!