Do you think you can take it out?
I will try.
A human cannot carry the Bead for long anyway.
How long can a human hold it then?
A year, at most.
So that means after one year of carrying it,
it will be resolved one way or the other.
Doesn't it?
Then what happens if it's not taken out in time?
You will die.
What?
Miss Dam,
you will die.
What are you talking about?
Why are you only telling me this now?
What do you mean, I'm going to die?
Wait.
You don't have to worry.
I just wanted to share the worst that could happen.
We still have a year of time,
so I'll try to find a way.
You should get some rest.
Good night.
Look how relaxed he is about this.
Is it because it's not his life?
Anyway, why didn't he say he was going to teleport? So startling.
Whoa.
What are you doing out there?
I got depressed, so I came out to get some air.
Oh, I see.
You must be busy trying to meet your deadline, Mr. Gumiho.
There's a deadline on your manuscript and on my life.
- Miss Dam—
- I didn't even hit you that hard.
How could it pop right out?
Don't you have any muscles? Do you ever work out?
Miss Dam, what are you doing down there?
This sausage fell.
Why are you suddenly—?
I got hungry after taking a walk.
You're probably wondering why I would want a snack now,
but I may have less than 365 days to enjoy late-night snacks.
I'm going to start stir-frying now to leave no regrets.
So.
Have you thought about
how you can take the Bead out?
Oh, that...
I hope! You think! Of something! Very soon!
Will I get to see these fall colors next year?
I hated you, campus lovebirds,
but I'll miss you a lot.
Jae Jin, my friend. I'll miss you, not!
It's all your fault. You deserve a good beating!
What's this, are you crying?
Jin Ah...
got a new boyfriend.
We just broke up after she cheated on me, but she already...
Be quiet.
That's the end of your relationship, but I'm facing the end of my life.
Your girlfriend abandoned you, but fate has abandoned me!
I have no idea what you're talking about, but that sounds really sad.
My heart aches.
This is all your fault!
Fried chicken was Jin Ah's favorite.
Fried chicken is also my favorite.
Will I be able to see this again next year?
Of course. It's not like chickens will go extinct.
What is this sudden turn of events?
I'll leave if I must, but I won't leave with a piece of regret.
So I'll eat every single piece I can.
Excuse me! Another order of seasoned chicken and one more draft beer, please!
Dam, thanks.
Thanks for getting hammered with me.
Everyone else ignored me when I reached out.
Hey, Jae Jin.
Yes?
You need to learn how to deal with the feelings
after you break up with someone.
What will you do without me?
Why wouldn't you be there?
And as for women...
don't get so obsessed with them.
Be good to yourself.
You're a pretty great guy.
Really? I'm a pretty great guy?
- Say that one more time.
- Whatever.
- Just one more time.
- Whatever, you idiot. Get lost.
Get out of my life.
Bye.
That pathetic, yet annoying jerk.
I feel sick.
Did I have too many drinks?
Bead!
The Bead popped out!
Mr. Gumiho!
Hey, Mr. Gumiho!
Hey, Mr. Gumiho! This is awesome!
I fell down after hitting my chest a few times,
then the Bead popped out from the impact.
What?
Look. I'm not going to die anymore.
This is...
This isn't the Bead. I think it's a candy someone spat out.
What?
Bead!
The Bead popped out!
Hey kid, you're going to get sick.
Darn it. I thought I had saved myself.
Hey, Miss Dam.
At this hour, it's very dangerous for you to walk around in this drunken state...
Are you all right, Miss Dam?
What is she looking at?
That's
the celadon made by the master who made one of the national treasures.
What? Where did they go?
What's going on?
What?
Let's see.
Am I seeing things? I must've had too much to drink.
I can't believe I'm using my powers for this.
That was startling.
Miss Dam?
Mom... Mom.
Mom, what am I going to do now?
Mom, what am I going to do?
Excuse me, Mr. Gumiho.
- Did you get a good sleep?
- Yes.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I'm not the type who gets drunk and makes a scene...
Miss Dam, may I have a word with you?
Sure.
What is this?
I wrote up an agreement.
There are a few things I need you to keep in your mind.
Shin Woo Yeo, Party A from hereon.
Lee Dam, Party B from hereon.
Party B is obligated to keep Party A's Bead safe for a year,
and comply with the clauses below to keep the Bead safe.
One, no contact with the opposite sex born in the Year of the Tiger.
Two, quit drinking to stay in good health.
Three, do not consume chickens.
Wait, what is this?
Nothing makes sense starting with clause one.
I can't get in contact with the opposite sex born in the Year of the Tiger,
but how would I know which year they were born in?
Doesn't this basically mean I cannot be in contact with any men?
- It does.
- What?
Then I can't kiss any guys and do this or that with them?
This or that?
And I can't drink or eat chicken?
Then why would I want to live?
The Bead is very susceptible to your condition.
You haven't been living a healthy life due to excessive drinking.
So it'll be a good idea to quit drinking.
What about chicken? Why can't I eat chicken?
Tigers are the natural enemy of foxes, but chickens are fatal for gumihos.
From ancient times, chicken blood was used to ward off bad luck.
So you better not eat it.
No, I think I should.
I had chicken yesterday, and I was totally fine.
Are you sure?
Well, I felt a little sick, but it was tolerable.
That's just the first time. It can get more dangerous over time.
I mean, I could die in a year,
but I have to spend my remaining life feeling depressed?
Miss Dam.
I don't plan on letting you die.
So please trust me, and let's focus on the things we can do.
I'll look for ways to retrieve the Bead, and you can focus on keeping it safe.
I think that's the way for you to survive.
- Hey, Dam.
- What?
What happened at the club? Where did you suddenly go?
Oh, something suddenly came up.
You left without a word?
- Yes.
- What?
My phone died, so I couldn't contact you.
Sorry. Did I keep you guys from partying?
That's not the case. We had lots of fun partying.
I never get bored if I got some beats.
I got, got, got,
got, got, got, got...
That was loud.
Who the heck drives like that?
I think that's Seon Woo.
What? Gye Seon Woo? From the class of 2017?
- The playboy?
- Yes.
The legend of the history department who dated over twenty women, Seon Woo.
We're doing a group project together, so I know him.
He returned to school.
I'm jealous.
Let's go eat.
Hey, wait for me.
It's already on Everyday Time.
(T/N: Korean university community forum)
"I'm in class with Seon Woo. Lucky me!"
Look, there are three hundred comments.
Wow, look.
So what? He's a bad playboy who makes women cry a river.
Doesn't that sound better than you, the crybaby, that gets played on all the time?
No.
I think it's better that I cry than to make someone else cry.
I've been hurt a lot, but I love how I never hurt anyone else.
What? Have you been going to church?
It's what Dam said yesterday.
She said I should be good to myself because I'm a good guy.
Did you read a book written by Monk Bopjong?
(T/N: He was a Buddhist monk and writer in South Korea)
That's the alcohol talking.
Anyway, I finally realized this after hearing that.
Before I try so hard to get loved, I need to learn to love myself.
After I made that decision, I realized how loveable I am.
- You are?
- Yes.
I looked at myself in the mirror, and my face looked so good.
Then when I grabbed the bus strap, my biceps looked so hot.
Then I have a mid-low range voice, which makes me sound so sweet.
So lame, so stop talking before I shoot you.
I'm leaving. I have to go get some books.
Why? You aren't going to finish?
I'm full.
- Bye.
Okay. In order to survive, I have to keep the Bead safe.
Excuse me.
Isn't he Gye Seon Woo?
The class of 2017, so he was born in the Year of the Tiger!
You dropped this.
I'm sorry, but could you just leave it on the floor?
- What?
- Just leave it on the floor.
Thank you.
What's with her?
What? Cohabitation?
I get that the Bead just rolled into that woman,
but how did you of all people decide to live with a human woman?
Well, at first, I thought it seemed interesting,
so I wanted to keep her by my side, and...
And? What?
Forget it.
Why won't you finish your story?
Why? Is she your type?
Did you finally meet your ideal type who opened you up
after hundreds and hundreds of years?
Don't be so cheeky.
She's a human whose head is still wet from blood.
(T/N: Korean idiom similar to being wet behind the ears)
Wet from blood?
What did you do to make her bleed? Did you beat her?
It's a figure of speech.
It's used to express when someone is very young, a figure of speech used by humans.
I see. Is that so?
There are way too many things I have to remember as a human.
I have to memorize idioms and neologisms.
And to order a Croque Monsieur, I have to memorize English too.
That's French.
I can't believe how you managed to be annoying for seven hundred years.
I'm sure it'll be very tough for that human woman who lives with you.
Anyway, does she know that she can die if the Bead keeps taking her energy?
I'm not going to let her die.
Okay. I'm glad you made that decision.
I hope you won't have to take the Bead from her dead body like back then.
Anyway, there's something I would like to ask.
Danger! Danger!
- Dam!
- No, Sunbae, don't catch me!
(T/N: Sunbae - informal way to call a senior)
Are you okay?
Sunbae, you're in the class of 2017. Aren't you a Tiger?
I was born early, so I'm a Rabbit.
Early? You were born early in the year.
Sunbae, thank you so much for being born in the Year of the Rabbit.
I'm very glad that you're a Rabbit.
Did you come to school drunk again?
- No.
- Anyway, have you heard?
We're doing a general assembly.
I can't be there. I'm currently staying away from drinks—
- We're getting meat.
- I'm there.
I can go. I'll be there. I'm coming.
Okay. Go.
Yes!
♪  Meat! Meat is my vitamin   ♪
♪  Meat is my antidepressant   ♪
♪  Meat, meat, meat, meat   ♪
♪  Pork neck, pork belly   ♪
Happiness isn't far away.
It's freaking far away.
Hey, don't people usually refer to pork or beef as meat?
This is just chicken.
- Why? You're crazy for chicken.
- You are.
I am. So I'm about to go crazy.
- Jin Ah used to eat like that too.
- Cut it out.
Just one bite. May I have just one bite?
Just one piece of the wing would be fine, right?
No, if I eat this, I might really die.
Forget it. There's no reason to live, if I can't eat chicken.
- I'll just eat it.
- Do you want to die?
No, I don't. I won't eat it.
No, everyone is waiting for you.
Hey, enough. I'm here.
- Seon Woo.
- Hello, Seon Woo.
- Hello.
Hello, Seon Woo.
- Hey, Seon Woo.
- Over here!
-  Hello, Seon Woo.
- Hey!
- Why are you so late?
- Hey, Seon Woo.
- Have you been well?
- I thought you weren't coming.
- Hey, grab a drink.
- Grab a drink.
Here.
- A toast?
- Okay, let's make a toast.
- Okay.
- Cheers.
Hey, I can't do this. I'm leaving.
- Already? You haven't eaten.
- Hey.
Yes.
I have to leave. Could you take a step aside?
You're leaving? Let's grab a drink together.
Things are too loud over there.
Stay, Dam. You couldn't be here even if you wanted to in your fourth year.
You should sit just as our sunbae suggests.
Yes, we aren't that rude. Take a seat.
I'm sorry for the group project.
It's okay. Things can happen right after you get discharged.
- Are you Jae Jin's friends?
- Yes, Choi Soo Kyeong.
I'm pretty and the top of my class,
so people call me the Kim Tae Hee of Seogwa University.
(T/N: South Korean actress who is famous for her looks)
That's your nickname? No one ever calls you—
- Aren't you going to drink?
- I have bad kidneys.
- Then some chicken—
- I love animals.
Lee Dam, are you insane? What's this crazy talk?
- Shut up.
- Lee Dam?
Your name is one syllable? Dam?
Yes, right.
Do you know my name?
You're Gye Seon Woo.
Let's be acquaintances from now on.
Let me pour you one, too.
- What's with her?
- What's with this guy?
- What's wrong with you?
I have to take this.
Hey, Eun Jung. Yes.
- My gosh.
- I can talk.
You have bad kidneys?
- What?
- You loved animals?
What? Oh, right.
I have to go. See you tomorrow.
Hey, go home after Seon Woo comes back!
Okay.
Are you okay?
Did she just roll over trying to avoid touching me?
What's wrong, Miss Dam?
What's wrong, you ask?
I fell over trying to avoid a guy born in the Year of the Tiger.
And I went to a chicken place for the general assembly,
but couldn't eat anything there.
I was the only one who ate the macaroni salad.
I see.
"I see"? That's all?
I had such a tough time today, yet you sound so indifferent.
I went through so much today, especially staying away from chicken.
You must know how it feels to turn down a fried chicken.
I don't.
You liar!
There was a crunchy and chewy chicken lying there in front of me,
yet I felt tortured because I couldn't even take a bite.
You really don't know what it's like?
I really don't.
Why don't you know?
Because I don't eat chicken.
Right.
Then change that into something you like and think of the same situation.
Yes, these cigarettes.
How do you think you'd feel if you suddenly had to stop smoking?
I'll just stop, then.
I doubt it. I heard it's really tough to quit smoking.
Some say you should never associate with those who quit smoking,
because they're the most persistent type.
I'm not sure.
That's for humans, who have a very weak will.
Smoking was just a means that helped me spend my tedious days.
I'm not exactly addicted, so I think I'll be fine.
Then quit smoking.
- What?
- Quit smoking.
You do know secondhand smoking is bad for me, right?
So please quit smoking for the sake of the Bead.
Now that we're on the subject, I want an agreement, too.
I'd like to make three requests just as you did, Mr. Gumiho.
What are these?
Lee Dam, Party A from hereon.
Shin Woo Yeo, Party B from hereon.
B is obligated to keep A and A's Bead safe,
and comply with the clauses below to keep A and A's Bead safe.
The first rule is already ridiculous.
What do you mean, "share the progress"?
Well, you've been only coming up with lame ideas.
This way, you will try harder so you have something to share with me.
All right.
Then what does the second one mean?
"No cold gaze"?
Let's be honest. A gumiho can look scary even when it smiles.
Whenever you give me a cold look, I feel a bit...
When did I look at you like that?
Just now. And also sometimes when you pass by.
Well,
we talked about the number three already, so could you sign it now?
It's going to be hard, right? Especially number three.
If you think you can't do it, we can make a deal.
For example, I can let you smoke
if you let me eat chicken every two weeks...
Do you have a minute?
I would like you to brief me about the progress.
Now?
As it's written on the agreement,
you must find a way to retrieve the Bead out and share the progress every Friday.
And today happens to be Friday.
So... did you find a lead?
Well, not yet.
But you don't need to worry.
As I said, I don't want to let you die.
I don't want a vague answer like that.
I want something solid.
Mr. Gumiho.
Where's the spirit you showed me when we first met?
You used to take the Bead seriously and had the guts to ask me to move in.
That's what impressed me.
Your dull attitude really disappoints me.
Let's call it a day.
Please don't be upset and keep my advice in mind.
We didn't gather in this house to make friends.
See you then.
Good morning.
Hi.
It looks like you're having a hard time quitting cigarettes.
No, I'm not.
By the way, Miss Dam,
have you heard of the idiom, "A tangerine becomes an orange"?
Tangerine? This?
A tangerine becomes an orange.
Just like that, the environment changes people.
Could you clean up the place
so you can keep your body and mind healthy?
I was going to clean it up when I'm finished eating.
This is not what I'm talking about.
Your socks are rolled up in the washing machine,
your hair is everywhere, and when you recycle...
Anyway, please be careful.
I'm sorry.
He sounded somewhat irritated. Or am I just imagining it?
It's tasty.
Hey, Jae Jin. Do you have my Korean History book?
I knew it. Do you want to die?
You should've given it back to me if you're finished reading it, you jerk.
Bring it when you come to school later.
If you forget it, I'll crush your head.
Okay.
This idiot must have lost his mind.
According to "Mingxin Baojian",
(T/N: The Mingxin baojian is an early Ming collection of aphorisms and sayings)
one's mouth and tongue are the doors to anger and worries,
and they are axes that kill one's body.
From now on, I want you to use only good words.
"Mingxin Baojian". I'll keep that in mind-xin.
I don't like puns.
"I don't like puns."
I don't think I was just imagining it.
He is being sensitive. It must be from quitting smoking.
I'm going to school.
Miss Dam.
According to "Sajasohak", one must be clean-cut and well-dressed.
(T/N: Text used to learn Chinese characters and basic ethics through practiced calligraphy)
It means you should be neat and dressed nicely.
But...
You're going to school,
and it looks like you didn't care about how you're dressed.
By any chance, does everything in this world irritate you?
- What?
- Because I think
you might be suffering from some withdrawal symptoms.
No way.
Be careful and get back safely.
I will. I'll see you late then.
He is having withdrawal symptoms.
It was easy for you to say when you told me to quit chicken and drinking.
Serves you right.
She even left the TV on.
Last week, in the middle of the day, in the middle of the city,
one woman has been murdered brutally.
This is also known as "the Downtown Murder".
Over two hundred thousand people pass this area daily.
There's no evidence found from any CCTVs and dash cams and
there are no witnesses, which makes it hard to guess the culprit's whereabouts.
This is the biggest hallmark of this incident.
Hi.
He takes this class, too?
Hey, Dam.
Do you have some coins?
Could you get me a drink?
Okay.
Sure.
I owe you ₩800 ($0,71). I'll pay it back.
It's okay. You can just forget about it.
By the way, why do you keep avoiding me?
What? When?
Let's say you didn't then. Give me your phone.
Why?
Why do you think?
Why do you ask me?
Just to check the time.
Oh, time. It's three...
Here. Call me if you want to drink something.
They say one's life lives up to one's name.
"Seon" means kind and "Woo" means friend.
My parents gave me this name because they wanted me to have
kind friends and be a kind friend myself.
Hey, you are such a jerk.
Did you just say you're sick of me and our personalities don't match?
- You think I'm an idiot?
- Yes.
What?
No. Go on.
But they seem to have given me the wrong name.
Excuse me. Can I have your phone number?
I'm good looking.
My gosh. I didn't know you were going to such a prestigious school.
I'm smart.
Plus, I come from a rather wealthy family,
so life seems too easy for me.
I had waited two years for you to come back from the army.
You just came back and you're saying you want to break up. Are you crazy?
Who is it this time?
Did you go to a club? Is it a freshman?
Tell me!
I've got to go.
- That's
- Hey.
the person I am.
I don't want to.
- What?
- Why did you take my phone without asking?
Are you yelling at me now?
Keep the ₩800.
I'm Gye Seon Woo. Save my number.
Hi. Gosh, you scared me.
My phone.
I still have more than a year left until the contract is over.
Darn it.
Mr. Gumiho.
What are you doing here, Miss Dam?
I'm sorry. I'll leave now.
Please let me get out of here.
I can't.
Why not?
Because I'm locked up here, too.
What?
The doorknob broke,
so I was trying to fix it with the drill.
I even put the wooden block there
to stop the door from shutting.
Why did it fall out then...
Did I by any chance...
kick it when I came inside?
Yes.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
Did you think I locked you up on purpose?
What? No.
No way.
By the way, how do we get out of here?
I guess there's only one way.
Right.
What are you doing?
What?
I was going to ask you if I could use your phone.
To call a repairman.
I thought you were going to teleport us.
We can't teleport here.
Why not? You did it just fine a few days ago.
Teleporting causes a wave,
which can affect the things around you.
And I have many important things here.
I see.
Right.
Here.
Hi, I'm the resident in 78-12, Samcheong-dong.
The doorknob in the basement broke again.
And I think the light will go off soon...
The light went off too.
Okay. Please repair this too.
Okay. Bye.
There must be something over there to light up this place.
Wait here.
Hold my hand.
I'm good.
Okay.
Is this a kerosene lamp?
What are all these?
Things that were naturally collected over time.
My gosh.
This is a bronze dagger, right?
Gosh, this must be a white porcelain from the Joseon Dynasty.
No way!
Is that Shin Yun Bok's painting?
(T/N: Shin Yun Bok was a Korean painter from the Joseon Dynasty)
How do you have that?
I once worked as a trader during the reign of Jeongjo.
(T/N: Jeongjo was the 22nd ruler of the Joseon Dynasty)
Gosh, that's amazing.
What's that?
It's a sketch.
I once worked for the science department.
You were a scientist? You were such an elite.
And what else have you done?
During the reign of Seonjo, I fought against the Japanese,
leading the country to victory.
You were in the military too.
That's why there are swords and bows.
- Gosh.
- Miss Dam.
You seem to be very interested in history, unlike most young people.
Haven't I told you yet? I major in history.
Some kids applied for this major because of their grades,
but in my case, it's because I love history.
I have always liked to watch historical dramas since I was little.
Gosh.
I want to be a museum curator after graduation.
But I'm not sure if I can live until then.
Anyway, this is really cool.
I have always wanted to travel back in time like in TV series
if I could.
I'm so envious that you got to live in so many eras.
How does it feel to live a long life?
Nothing.
It doesn't feel like anything.
Oh, there's a pipe too.
Have you used it yourself?
Yes.
Since when?
Since tobacco was imported in 1592.
1592?
When Japan invaded Korea?
Have you been smoking cigarettes for over four hundred years then?
And I made you quit that?
Just keep on smoking.
What am I to stop your four hundred years standing habit?
Actually, I thought it would be easy.
I thought it shouldn't be too hard to change one habit.
But it turned out to be hard.
It made me realize that I might have made unreasonable demands.
So I want to keep myself from smoking during the contract period.
To share your pain.
I'm okay though.
So you have been smoking for four hundred years.
Then how old are you?
I'm 22. Born in 1999, the Year of the Rabbit.
I'm 999. Born in 1012, during the reign of Hyeonjong of Goryeo.
- Relax.
- I mean...
Now that I hear your actual age, I realize how ancient you are.
As a matter of fact, you've been scolding me so much
I felt like I was living with a great grandpa.
But if you think about it, you've lived longer than my great great grandpa.
Now I get why you have been speaking like a fossil...
Oh, it's a wind chime.
It's so pretty.
I have seen fish-shaped sails,
but I haven't seen a leaf-shaped one like this.
You can have it if you like it.
Are you sure?
It looks at least a few hundred years old.
I bought it in Insa-dong. At ₩7,000 ($6,23).
Hello?
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Braised spicy chicken.
It looks so tasty.
I'm just looking at it.
You quit cigarettes, which you have been smoking for over four hundred years.
And I've been eating chicken for only twenty years.
I can hold it for one year.
♫   The drawing of our beginning   ♫
♫   When I close my eyes and feel you, I can draw you out   ♫
♫   Let’s start, baby   ♫
♫  At some point, I started thinking of you on a white canvas  ♫
♫  right here, follow your heart and draw  ♫
♫   The drawing of our beginning   ♫
♫  and lingers there  ♫
♫  Do you see that blue ocean,  ♫
♫  and those dark eyes of yours  ♫
♫  So beautiful, should I draw them here?  ♫
What's all this?
You can't eat your favorite food, chicken,
and I felt bad to put you through such pain.
So I made spicy stir-fried chicken using duck.
Wait. Can you eat duck?
No, I can't.
I can't have enough of it!
Thanks for the food.
It looks tasty.
Seriously? The flavor, seasoning, and texture are all horrible.
How does it taste?
Do you like it?
Yes.
It's tasty. It tastes really good.
- I made a lot of it. You can have it all.
- No, wait!
It's not tasty, right?
Well...
I'm sorry. I appreciate your kindness though.
I'll go get something to eat.
Don't. I'm okay.
I don't want you to starve because of me.
I'll be right back.
But I'm really okay.
Maybe I should have tried to eat it.
It would have made me more patient.
I'll tell him we're having only delivery foods from now on.
Why aren't you answering?
I'll pay you the ₩800 back. Let's meet.
Gosh. What's wrong with him?
Wait.
Is the reason why he's being so persistent...
because he hates to own someone?
You can wire the money here.
This is a hundred percent poop.
Calm down. The toilet is near you.
What?
Why won't it flush?
Is it clogged?
I'll give it to you in person. Let's meet.
No.
Why not?
I'm really busy now.
Why are you busy?
I'm unclogging the toilet.
Actually, do you know how to unclog it?
This is urgent.
This is not about my image.
This is about the privacy of my intestine and human dignity.
What did I put inside?
Maybe I should stop living.
No. Let's not give up hope.
Mr. Gumiho left thirty minutes ago
and it takes five minutes to the downtown,
so he should arrive in a minute.
So I will keep calm and flee the country.
This is ridiculous!
- Hey, Miss Dam.
- How long until you're home?
I'm almost there.
Already?
Right. I bought some pizza. Is that okay with you?
No, it's not.
I think greasy food like that can cause trouble
and diseases like obesity and esophagitis.
I should have asked you before buying it then.
Is there anything else you want to eat?
What's the food he can't get near here?
Something that takes a long time to get.
Yum woon sen.
(T/N: Thai Glass Noodle Salad)
Yum woon sen?
I'll see if I can find it.
Okay.
Yum woon sen?
Now, yum woon sen earned me some time, let's see what I can do.
I found a how-to.
As you said, I wrapped the toilet.
Now, try flushing it.
Then the plastic will be bloated.
Press it hard.
It worked! It's unclogged, Seon Woo!
Thank you!
From now on, I'll call you the Toilet Fairy.
You don't need to call me that.
You don't have to give me the ₩800 back either.
This doesn't make up for it.
- Let's go out and eat.
- Sure.
It's on me. It's totally on me.
Thank you so much, Sunbaenim.
(T/N: Sunbaenim -  formal way to call a senior)
Thank you!
Thank goodness.
That was horrible.
She was actually unclogging a toilet.
Now, the pressure is off, both my mind and stomach.
Especially, my stomach.
It feels like my stomach is totally empty.
Oh, no.
Oh, I have a problem.
I think the Bead came out.
Could you see if the Bead is still there?
The Bead is fine.
Really? Ah!
Thank goodness.
- Did something happen?
- It's just that
I had a serious stomachache and pooped so hard
I felt like all my organs came out.
I was worried that the Bead also...
But it's fine.
Anyway, I'm glad the Bead is fine.
Hey.
Can I have a slice of pizza?
Are you sure?
What about esophagitis and gastritis?
Actually, I gave it some thought.
You see, cars need oil to move.
I think humans need some oil too to move.
I love fat.
Sure. Help yourself.
Thank you.
It's so tasty.
I have one question.
For me? What is it?
Losing the Bead would be a good thing for you.
Right. That's what I want.
Then why were you so relieved when I said the Bead was still there?
I do wish the Bead is gone, but I wish it happens safely.
I don't want the Bead to go to the sewer.
I don't only care about my own life.
I care about the Bead and your dream, too.
What did you think of me, I'm not that selfish.
Why don't you have some too?
I don't appease my hunger with human food.
Human food is like some sort of snack I eat for pleasure from time to time.
Then why did you cook earlier?
I told you.
I made it because I felt bad that I put you through the pain.
Then did you get these...
I got them for you.
Oh, I see.
This goes to plastic and this goes to plastic bags. Right?
Yes.
From now on, I'll make sure to recycle trash.
Right. Can we talk about how we address each other?
I don't feel comfortable calling you Mr. Gumiho all the time.
Since I call you by your name, you can call my name too.
No, I can't do that.
You're 977 years older than me.
It's like I can't call the king of a country by his name.
I think it's disrespectful.
How about Mr. Landlord?
Well, maybe it sounds like you would push me to pay rent.
How about Mr. Ancestor?
Well, I guess it sounds like you would take food from an ancestral rite.
How about "Sir"?
How about Oldmiho? It's short for Old Gumiho.
"Sir" sounds good to me.
It's "Sir" then.
Let's get inside, Sir.
Sir.
"Sir"...
He's sweeter and more caring than I thought.
And...
How does it feel to live a long life?
Nothing. It doesn't feel like anything.
He looks a bit lonely too.
Sir.
Why haven't you gone to bed yet?
Well, I was doing my assignment and I got sleepy, so I came out to get some fresh air.
It's hard, right?
You seem tired, so I was worried.
Until now, I have been thinking only about my situation,
but earlier when I visited the basement,
I realized how long you have been living.
For such a long time, you had one dream.
And it can all go down the drain, so I can only imagine how hard it must be.
I feel a bit bad too, because it feels like it's my fault.
Why would you feel bad?
Just because.
You know what? How about we try to live through this day?
If we repeat that, I believe good days will come in the end.
Let's tough it out together.
I'll go inside now.
Don't think too much.
Anyway, there's something I would like to ask.
Do you even want to become a human?
To be honest, after what happened, I thought you gave up hope.
Who is she to turn you like this?
You already know how to take the Bead out.
- Miss Dam.
- Yes?
Let me check one thing.
You can go back now.
Just think all this was a dream.
I'll get going.
♫   Again tonight, I can’t sleep cuz I’m thinking of you. Oh every night  ♫
♫   What am I to you? I’m curious. Please tell me now  ♫
♫   Without even knowing, my feelings grow deeper   ♫
♫   I’m seeping into you   ♫
♫   The longer I wait, they'll get deeper. Ask the moon  ♫
♫   Tell me now, how are you doing it?   ♫
♫   My nights are filled with you   ♫
♫   Stare me now, I wanna be your moon   ♫
~ Preview ~
If I say I want to be your boyfriend, will you let me?
What do you think he's up to?
I think even Gye Seon Woo can't get Lee Dam.
You. Aren't you leaving?
How can I help you?
- Go on a date with me.
- A date?
It may be just a simulation, but I thought I should dress properly for a date.
He's enchanting me.
He's indeed a fox.
Hold it in and date her.
This might be the last chance you have.
♫   Again tonight, I can’t sleep cuz I’m thinking of you   ♫