A Cappella
I was twenty.
I will let no one say
it is the best time of life.
Everything threatens
a young man with ruin.
Paul Nizan
Anti-uniform Committee
Kyoko Noma and Julie Kanazawa.
Look at this old fashioned uniform.
It's meant to be respectable!
Dowdy Peter Pan collars and socks!
No perms, ribbons or headbands!
We have to follow these
silly rules.
Let's demand that uniforms
are abolished.
Yes!
With stylish clothes we'll
reclaim our rights!
Let's do it!
Yes!
We hereby organize
the Anti-uniform committee.
...never give in to
the authority's oppression.
This battle affects
every one of us.
I'm addressing
citizens, workers and students.
We need to unite.
The university administrators are
responsible
for pacifying students.
They're oppressive.
And we're not taking their
oppression any longer!
It is the embodiment of
Imperialism.
That's what schools are...
We organized an anti-uniform committee.
Go, Revolutionary Rosa!
- You can print flyers at our office.
- Thank you.
- The demonstration's on 6/15.
- OK!
Here. Use it for the cause.
Thank you.
- Want ramen?
- No, it's for the cause!
Kyoko, do you like classical music?
- Sure.
- Good.
Yes!
Julie should be the Chair.
I'd be lousy.
You do it, Kyoko.
I'd be lousy too!
Julie here will help you out.
Reiko and I'll support you.
It'll be fun.
Embers Poetry Collection  100 yen.
You love poetry...
Thank you.
Kyoko.
A Cappella...?
Just follow us.
A Cappella.
What's this?
3 coffees.
Well?
Not bad!
Look at those marks.
They're from people's heads.
Gross!
Coffee please.
Pachelbel's Canon.
Don't you get bored of that?
You bought those poems?
For 100 yen?
150. The extra 50 yen was
a donation.
You're strange.
He's just a spoilt street poet.
Why am I strange?
May I?
The poet and I go to the
same college.
At dawn I saw a wind being born.
It was forlorn
and without direction.
It made waves
and moved a ship.
Tossing leaves,
it hit a wall and died.
And went out
in a trash bag..
What's this?
He's just jerking off.
Give it back.
We're her friends.
I'm Reiko and this is Julie.
High school girls?
Seniors at Sendai All-girls' High.
Kyoko is our Revolutionary Rosa.
Nice to meet you.
Revolutionary Rosa? Wow.
It's just a nickname.
So your school has
an anti-war group now.
Nothing so organized.
We just oppose school uniforms.
You're the Chair?
Kind of.
You make speeches?
From now.
You must have fun every day...
You talk to me like I'm a child.
I didn't mean to.
Sorry.
Thank you.
You know this piece?
It's Pachelbel's Canon.
Should I?
It's beautiful.
...as a result 18 students
have been arrested so far.
Since barricading off Tokyo University
the student activists' struggle
is spreading
to high schools across Japan.
Many graduates are boycotting
commencements...
Arrest them and shoot them!
Parents paid tuition for that?
Kyoko is late.
Noma Family.
You're late!
I was studying with friends.
Honey...
Hi, Kyoko. I brought
some strawberries.
Thanks for letting me stay
with you.
Aunt Aiko came to eat with us.
Aiko, don't be too soft on her.
Yes, please.
Kyoko.
No political activities
or skipping class.
Kyoko, I won't spoil you.
Your curfew is 7 o'clock.
You forgot to pack this.
Where were you really, Sis?
At a baroque cafe
talking about the Security Treaty.
Abolish the Treaty!
Victory is ours!
Sis.
Don't give Birdie any spinach.
It'll give her diarrhea.
I'll take good care of her.
Auntie Aiko might give her spinach.
I'll make sure she won't.
Time to sleep.
Good night.
Night.
Dad's forced smile
lingers like a funeral photo.
A new life away from my parents.
Will it make any difference to me?
We're people, not a herd of sheep.
And people have the
freedom of speech!
Yes!
Why should we give it up?
Stop eating from the belt feeder!
We'll smash it!
Right!
Come down, girls!
You've been suspended?
Shame on you!
You embarrassed your aunt!
Shame?
You know nothing.
Don't get all preachy.
Here.
It's me. It must be a mistake.
I'll watch her.
I'm just copying.
I hate myself for that. I wonder
if Julie and Reiko feel the same.
It's easier if I think they do.
I feel calmer.
Kyoko.
Julie.
Reiko!
Reiko.
How's it going?
They cast long stripes of shadows.
All lined up in identical poses.
They all bow their heads but one.
Only one who
looks away indignantly.
That's me, the seal who
hates seals.
But a seal is still a seal.
I'm just looking the other way.
I don't really care about
the Vietnam or anything.
I'm just trying to stand
in the storm so I won't go mad.
Go away!
Go away, police!
Leave us alone!
Leave!
Run!
I was born with
emotions that bleed.
My flesh will never bleed...
The blue sky framed by
riot shields
wasn't the same sky I saw
at school with Julie and Reiko.
You alone?
Meeting someone?
Can we join you?
- Were you at the demonstration?
- Uh, yes...
Did you get hurt?
A badge of honor.
Hardly.
As a senior you must be... 18?
- 17.
- Like Emma.
- Emma?
- She was here that day.
Oh, your girlfriend.
And you are... Kyoko.
That's right.
My name was hard for kids when we
moved for dad's job.
Ah, the life of a bohemian!
- Domoto...
- Wataru.
And Yunosuke Seki.
We've been friends forever and we
go to the same college.
His family owns Sengendo,
the sweet shop.
That your family's?
It is but he's
crashing at my place.
Are you OK?
Yeah.
You sure?
I'll wash it for you.
Wataru's girl!
Nice to know you.
The movie will start soon.
Excuse us.
You can stick around with Wataru.
Is this out of rivalry?
How come?
You're here because
Yunosuke went out with Emma.
I can't just ask you
for sex straight out.
Try me.
Don't pretend....
I know you're sweet and innocent.
Wataru.
Is there anything worth
hanging onto in life?
Love between two people...?
Without love would revolutions happen?
Without love revolutions
wouldn't happen..
The next stop is Rinnoji Temple.
We'll stop here.
Hi.
Hello.
Let's go.
It's nice and quiet.
Where's Yunosuke?
At home.
He didn't go out?
He and Emma are listening to records.
Right.
We're here.
Go in.
Relax.
We won't do tea ceremony.
Know why the entrance's small?
When you enter,
you leave the ordinary world.
We're in the other world.
It's nice here.
- Did you want beer?
- No, this is OK.
Is Setsuko coming back for summer?
Dunno. She hasn't called.
Has Kyoko met Setsuko?
- Who is she?
- Wataru's sister.
Just wait!
She's like a movie star.
- Their story's so sad...
- Don't talk about that.
- Why?
- You're not entitled to.
Don't be mad.
You're no expert
on people's private lives.
You mock like a tabloid writer.
It's OK. Don't argue about it.
Kyoko, want to get cigarettes?
Can you get some beer too?
Wataru's mother killed herself.
She did?
Wataru and his sister were kids
when they found her hanging.
- Do you like Mick Jagger?
- Yes.
He'll be cool when he's middle-aged.
So will Yunosuke and Wataru.
Don't you think?
I can't imagine.
A middle-aged Wataru...
- We're back.
- Hey.
- Your beer.
- Thanks.
Emma.
Sorry I was angry.
I know Wataru is a sore point
with you.
That's not it.
I was just irritable.
Sorry.
Are you drunk?
We should leave them alone.
Let's go...
Aren't you going, Wataru?
See?
Emma's wet now.
Are you mad?
Why would I be mad?
This is yours.
I love you, Kyoko.
Oh, why is that?
Do I need a reason?
Paging Dr. Miyamoto.
Why'd you do it?
I was bored.
That's all.
What a big bag!
I'm supposed to
be at cram school.
Where do you two do it?
Sex! Yunosuke and I
use the teahouse.
Kyoko.
Do you love life?
You mean... living?
Life itself.
I don't know what you mean
but I guess so.
Summer mornings before
anybody's up.
Snow-covered evenings.
Stormy days...
I'm so heartsick I want to cry.
I feel present.
I'm right here.
That's all I need to know.
That's beautiful.
Wataru, you know that night...
We kissed under the moon.
There were no American
footsteps on it then.
Kyoko!
Wataru.
Can we meet alone next time?
Sure.
Wataru and Yunosuke look past
us girls into the distance.
Are you a virgin?
Maybe...
I'll leave it to your imagination.
Hey.
Do you still want to die?
All the time.
But you won't die
if you're thinking about death.
The danger is
when your mind goes blank.
Don't you dare!
You have a pink bomb
waiting inside you.
Set it off grandly so
it knocks men off their feet.
Sound good?
Not bad.
- So Yunosuke's in Tokyo?
- Yes.
Emma hated being left here.
Kyoko, there's someone
I want you to meet.
- My sister.
- Kyoko.
Hi, I'm Setsuko.
Hi.
She's pretty.
You're the first girlfriend
I've ever met.
So I'm pretty excited to
meet you.
I'm cold.
Don't you have a coat?
I feel cold because
I have my period.
You had a painkiller?
Let's go then.
Isn't she great?
Too good for you.
She is.
Setsuko is beautiful.
I felt like an
ugly high school girl.
I was miserable.
I'd have run and hid if I could.
I was jealous of Setsuko.
It brought out something in me.
Hello.
- Hi.
- How are you?
I better go.
Already?
Sit down.
Seeing you two makes me feel lonely.
I can walk you home.
It's OK. I just feel dizzy.
Wataru, you should
come home sometimes.
I will if you are there.
I'd better walk her home.
Why does he behave as if.
Setsuko is his girlfriend?
Is it possible that
Wataru and Setsuko
have made love?
Wataru!
Piano Lessons.
Why are you here?
To learn piano.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Kyoko, the neighbors can see us!
I don't care.
- Come in.
- What about your aunt?
She'll be at a recital until 8.
I'm like your lover.
- Help yourself.
- Thank you.
You can sit here.
Use this as an ashtray.
See this?
I thought about it and decided
to give you my favorite record.
I hope you like it.
Don't you like Tchaikovsky?
I love him.
Thank you.
Wataru.
You seem distracted...
Is that how I look?
Yes.
Even when we're laughing and
talking together
you aren't with me.
You're far away.
I'm more aware of it
the longer I know you.
It's as if half of you
is in a distant universe.
Sorry.
I don't know what it is.
Just forget it.
Stop!
It's Setsuko, isn't it?
I know Setsuko's the only
one you can love.
You don't have to hide it,
it's obvious.
I don't mind at all.
Siblings with unhappy pasts
must have a strong bond.
That's silly.
I don't love my sister.
Who do you love then?
I'll answer it.
Hello?
Is this Kyoko Noma?
Yunosuke?
It's your birthday, right?
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Is Wataru there?
Put him on.
Setsuko's in hospital.
She tried to kill herself.
Why did Setsuko do it...?
She had a boyfriend in Tokyo and
they broke up.
Is she OK?
Looks like she'll be OK.
Sorry, Kyoko.
We'll celebrate later.
You were out sick! Proof that
you're human!
You missed the consultation
about college.
I'm too tired.
Did you decide?
Not yet.
And you?
I want to go to a Tokyo art school.
No matter what.
What's this?
Mom's pickled garlic.
For stamina.
Oh, I feel horny...
Cut it out!
Julie.
Sorry.
What for?
For quitting the Committee...
No hurt feelings!
But let's sabotage
the graduation ceremony?
Application for Admission.
Stop it!
Kyoko.
Sit down.
You don't go to cram school.
And you skip classes at
high school too.
What do you want?
How about college?
Dad.
I want to stay another year.
And bother your aunt?
I don't mind...
Your aunt kindly let you
live here
and you return the favor by
embarrassing her.
When did I embarrass her?
This is my life.
Are you involved in activism?
It's not that.
Activism is risky.
You could die doing it!
You'd never understand!
You're just a
groveling office worker.
Your life is controlled.
How could you get it?
Get out.
No! Come back and make up.
Kyoko!
Pachelbel's Canon.
So silly.
What is?
You heard me?
Dad slapped me.
He's a good dad.
How come?
My father's never hit me.
He must be fair and gentle.
No. He's a coward.
I've never felt love
from my father. Not once.
Oh...
You had a nice upbringing.
A classy girl.
No. I'm ordinary.
- How's Wataru?
- He's down with a cold.
You can visit him.
Yes, I might do that.
Later.
- Say Hi to Emma.
- Okay, I will.
What's up?
I heard you had a cold.
Are you OK?
Mom gives me this
when I have a cold.
- Want some?
- Thanks.
I'll get a plate.
Wataru. Why did you decide
to go to college?
Me?
To become a poet.
Kidding.
I wanted a socially condoned
4-year vacation.
And you?
Well...
I want a wild life but I don't
want people to think I'm dumb.
How egocentric!
Right.
- Go ahead.
- Thank you.
So I have to study for
the college entrance exams.
You going to Tokyo?
I want to stay here.
Forever.
Why?
Can't you guess?
Forget it.
Because you don't
want to leave me?
Exactly.
I don't wanna leave you.
You're feverish.
I feel lightheaded and nice.
Please... This is my first time.
Okay.
Kyoko, I love you.
Kyoko.
Leave! Right now!
Was he watching us the whole time?
- Forget about him.
- No!
Why was he watching us?
What's wrong with him?
I didn't know Yunosuke was
like that.
No, you're wrong about him...
Thank you, Ma'am.
See you next week.
Bye-bye.
Feeling better?
I'm hungry.
Mr. Domoto called you many times.
He is very worried about
your fever.
Is he your boyfriend?
I won't tell your dad.
So please don't fight with him.
I won't.
I'll focus on the college
entrance exams.
Maybe the fever made you wiser!
Hello?
Hello.
Kyoko?
You've got the wrong number.
Promise me that we'll meet
when you're better.
I love you, Kyoko.
Me too.
I love you.
Sabotage the graduation ceremony!
Students, join the cause!
This school's archaic administration
mirrors the authority's tyranny!
The bourgeoisie uses education
to tame us!
Schools produce
an obedient labor force.
It should be condemned!
So we'll sabotage
the graduation ceremony!
We refuse to be a product
of oppression.
We don't want their education!
Yes!
Come down!
Stop this misconduct!
I could say things calmed down
but I don't know what that means.
I suspect there is no such
state as calm.
I'm left behind in time.
So what if I am...?
Abolish the Security Treaty!
Free Okinawa!
Okinawa! Treaty!
Your favorite writers.
Boris Vian, Camus
and Yumiko Kurahashi.
Favorite poets.
Mitsuharu Kaneko and Baudelaire.
Also Paul Eluard.
Musicians?
The Bee Gees.
Karl Marx?
I don't understand Marx.
Nor Kazumi Takahashi's poems.
I confess to loving Sagan.
I love Bonjour Tristesse, too.
Make a sad face.
Hello, Sadness.
Why don't the 4 of us go to the sea?
You know...
I don't understand why
you want Yunosuke for a friend.
I do feel uneasy with him.
I can't trust him completely.
He's just an eccentric voyeur.
He still bothers you.
Wataru, rent an apartment.
We can be together all night.
Promise?
I'm drowning in the real world.
It's amusing to think of myself
as a drowned body floating on waves.
It's fine.
To be a drowned body
is not bad at all.
The waves can be rough and cold.
But a drowned body feels nothing.
I bloat up purple
and wait to wash up somewhere.
Come to my place next Saturday.
My aunt's going away.
I'll come round 5.
Just us two, all night.
Kyoko, let me in!
Kyoko.
Kyoko, please!
I loved Yunosuke.
And he loved me.
How did it happen...
...I don't really know.
We couldn't be without one another.
For 2 years...
it wasn't quite like that.
Because we promised to end it.
When he met Emma.
I felt saved.
But I was wrong.
He made out with her
in front of me
and I felt lonely.
That's when I met you.
But I really love you.
Then it got out of control.
On that snowy day...
I was happy to see
Yunosuke jealous.
Tell me...
What should I do?
Only you can decide.
I loved you.
I loved you so much.
Platonic love isn't possible.
When we hold back on lust
we make love spiritually.
That's what they did.
I'm so jealous I could die.
Kyoko?
Hello!
- You look great.
- Thanks.
No one home?
Looks like Yunosuke's gone to Tokyo.
- Got a cigarette?
- Yes.
If I chew gum when I smoke
it feels less unhealthy.
- Too late to worry about health.
- I know but...
It's not just for me.
I'm pregnant.
Almost 5 months.
How about congratulating me?
- You'll have it?
- Of course.
- What's Yunosuke want?
- To abort but I won't!
What about him?
You don't have to worry.
We'll work it out.
- Will you get married?
- Not yet.
But we're having a baby!
I'll leave home when my tummy gets big.
And move in with Yunosuke.
I'll help you.
I guess that's life.
Sometimes you have to steal
the one you love
even if it's sinful.
I love you, Wataru.
I love you too.
A Cappella.
Kyoko!
A coffee.
The 4 of us haven't met in a while!
- How's it going?
- Perfect.
Congratulations.
You'll be a dad soon.
Sorry but we have to go.
See you.
Don't fall over!
I'm fine. I'm with him.
What's wrong?
I believe she doesn't know...?
No.
I wouldn't tell her.
You're strange.
I'm ordinary.
You know why I wouldn't tell her.
Don't you?
I do.
Besides Emma's happy now.
I can smell apples.
I want to name the baby Mick.
I prefer Giovanni.
No!
You're out late...
Going somewhere?
Yunosuke!
The Chiba residence.
Please hold.
A woman named Domoto.
Hello, Setsuko?
Kyoko? I'm at the police station.
You know Wataru's friend, Emma?
She was killed.
Hello?
Kyoko?
Emma...
Emma!
What's wrong?
Emma was murdered!
Wataru...
He's gone.
Oh, my God...
Yunosuke's gone.
Yunosuke!
Where were you?
I've been so worried.
I roamed the Iwate countryside
because the world is ending.
Wataru.
It was amazing!
I've never felt so free.
So...
Just for 2 days of freedom.
I committed a crime.
Yunosuke Seki?
No, he didn't do it!
I killed her!
Yunosuke, no!
No! Don't!
Yunosuke!
He didn't do it. I killed her!
Hello?
Is this Wataru?
Where are you?
The seaside? Tell me where.
Listen...
Yunosuke and I planned
to murder Emma.
I thought he was joking.
But he wasn't.
If not for me
he wouldn't have killed Emma.
So it's my crime too.
Yunosuke might have been saved if you'd
told the police about you two.
Because this is our fate.
Why...?
Why would you...?
Listen, Kyoko.
I have to tell you this.
Kyoko...
You're the first woman
I ever loved.
How clumsy I was...
Forgive me.
I'm out of money.
No!
I'll call you... Wataru!
There was no suicide note
except...
Here.
I can finally sleep well   Wataru.
The police told me that Wataru
tried to protect Yunosuke.
Why would he...?
I don't know.
Buy something to eat
on the train.
Thanks.
Good luck in Tokyo.
Call me sometimes.
Thank you for everything.
Bach cantata BWV140.
Wataru...
Pachelbel's Canon.
Based on the original novel MUBANSOU
by MARIKO KOIKE,
published by SHINCHOSHA Publishing Co., Ltd.
and SHUEISHA Inc.
Directed by Hitoshi Yazaki
c2015 A Cappella film partners.
English subtitles by Dean Shimauchi