[Episode 6]
Kneel!
My Lord.
Mao,
do you know why we're fighting for power?
Because the people are suffering.
Upright people can work with each other yet remain different.
As long as it's good for the country and the people,
what's the harm in making a deal with the devil?
Still kneeling?
Aren't you tired?
I always do as you say.
Yes, you're right.
Have you found the tally?
Probably...
Come on,
can you work harder?
The entanglement between Princess of Yandan and me
was cleverly resolved by me.
I, along with the kind lady, and...
Greetings, City Lord.
And Yuan Qingheng.
Sorry,
I really don't know how to describe Yuan Qingheng.
Anyway,
we pulled off a self-sacrifice trick together.
This narration is way too long.
Isn't this Princess Chun Yuzhi,
who swore she would marry no one but Sima Qi?
Where did this nobody come from? Get lost!
You talk rudely. Slap her!
Her Ladyship fell into the water!
Help!
My Lady!
City Lord!
Her Ladyship was pushed into the water by the Princess of Yandan!
What?
-What?
-Please go there and take a look.
Lead the way.
Over there.
Honey?
You...
Her Ladyship is of noble status,
yet you humiliated her!
The autumn water is cold.
If anything happens to Her Ladyship,
you'll be held accountable!
Yes!
I...
Yuzhi, apologize.
Brother,
she was the one who came to pick a fight.
How did my wife become like this?
Summon an imperial physician! Hurry!
City Lord,
you must seek justice for me.
The villain cries first.
Don't think that I'll be scared just because you're crying.
Shut up!
You pushed someone into the water and still don't repent.
Hurry up and take your good sister
and disappear from my sight.
I didn't expect you to be such a vicious woman.
Exactly!
I never thought that the Princess of Yandan could be so vicious.
I...
Let's go.
Brother, I...
Let's go!
Brother.
Qingheng, at this moment, the one who truly understands you is me.
The City Lord is becoming more and more ambitious.
He dares to play tricks behind my back.
Zhang Dequan.
I'm here.
Prepare things as you said.
Yes.
The chill in me hasn't worn off yet.
Get another cloak for me.
Yes.
The autumn water is cold.
My Lady, your health is very important.
You shouldn't have used yourself to lure the enemy.
I was sacrificing for my husband.
It was nothing.
Grand Tutor,
how long are you going to bow?
It's rare that you're free today.
The planting festival is coming.
Could you help me think of some activities
to celebrate with the people?
How about setting off river lanterns?
I've traveled outside for many years.
But I've never had a chance
to set off the blessing lanterns in the capital.
I bought one three years ago.
-But in the end...
-Qingheng.
I know.
It's all in the past.
Now you are the esteemed wife of the City Lord.
You should be in a happy marriage with him.
The past?
Then why do you still keep this blessing knot?
Do you want to push me to the City Lord this much?
On the day of our wedding,
you said we had no further ties.
Then why do you care?
I...
Qingheng,
three years ago, I wronged you.
No.
Honey.
I'm here. How long have you been waiting?
Have a seat.
Honey, are you alright?
Yes.
City Lord,
Her Ladyship has done so much for you.
You should cherish her more.
I know.
My wife is the most gentle and considerate.
Without you,
I wouldn't know what to do.
City Lord, I know you're wise.
Yandan has come on very aggressively this time.
It's not that simple.
Of course.
The City Lord's move is quite clever.
He no longer needs to enter into a political marriage,
and the blame has shifted to Yandan.
Yandan has no excuse,
so the war won't happen.
My Lord,
this stupid City Lord seems to have really changed a lot.
But when it comes to right and wrong, it's just petty cleverness.
Avoiding war is the true responsibility of an emperor.
Next,
it's our turn.
Is this the Seventh Princess who visited the mansion last time?
My Lord,
could it be you like her?
Mao,
don't be nosey.
So, it's one-sided love?
Mao.
Can't I just say?
I'll stop.
The Seventh Princess really looks like the City Lord.
No wonder they are siblings.
But My Lord,
if we're going to kill the City Lord,
then the Seventh Princess...
The Seventh Princess has nothing to do with it.
The purpose of Lady Dowager and Yandan forming an alliance
is to establish a trade market.
I can offer them the same thing.
But right now, there's a lack of trust between us.
Marriage is the best way to build trust.
I never intended to use this method
from the beginning.
But since you're willing...
Are you sure?
It's not too late to change your mind.
To escape this dog-eat-dog City Lord's Mansion
and to break free from the Lady Dowager's control,
I've been waiting for this opportunity for so long.
It's all my fault.
I failed to protect my sisters.
I'm useless.
It's all your fault.
It's your fault for starting to seize power only now.
If you had started it earlier,
the Lady Dowager wouldn't have had the energy to meddle with us.
Alright, alright.
Anyway,
the Young Lord Chun Yu of Yandan will appear at Chunting Pavilion.
By then, I'll arrange
a "hero saving the beauty" plan.
There will be kidnappers abducting you
and using the sachet as a token to...
Stop the carriage now.
What's wrong?
This trip concerns my life.
I value it more than you do.
Trust me.
Why do I feel something is wrong?
Help!
The people of Yandan are bullying us!
They broke my leg and are trying to escape!
It hurts so much!
You're slandering us!
You clearly staged an accident for compensation.
You want compensation, right?
Fine, I'll give you what you want.
Stop!
You Yandan people hit him and now want to kill him too?
You clearly have no respect for Fengyao.
Such malicious intent cannot be tolerated!
Exactly! Such malicious intent cannot be tolerated!
This person is escalating a personal grudge into a conflict between the two cities,
forcing us to swallow this loss.
Kill me! Kill me!
You staged an accident just for compensation.
Why did you say they have malicious intent?
Everyone knows that Yandan and our city have a friendly relationship
and are considering a marriage alliance.
Yet, at this critical moment, you are sowing discord between the two cities.
If a war truly breaks out, causing devastation and suffering,
can you bear the responsibility?
Nonsense!
Bah! Traitors!
Who sent you here?
It hurts! My leg is broken!
With such a petty trick,
you want to stir up conflict between the two cities?
Miss, you're a hero. May I know your name?
Wait a moment, Young Lord of Yandan,
are you sure you're acting out "love at first sight" here
and not "long-lost sisters reunited"?
Impressive, truly impressive.
Sima Qi?
What a coincidence.
Are you trying to kill me again?
You must be joking.
I'm loyal and devoted.
When have I ever tried to assassinate you?
You...
Stop!
You pointed your sword at my neck last time.
This time, we're even.