[Episode 8]
You just fell asleep.
The City Lord's Mansion is ahead.
I'll take you back.
Sima Qi,
are you really not going to usurp the throne?
My Lord,
I am willing to follow your lead.
[East Gate]
My Lord, where have you been?
I've finally found you.
Let's talk when we get back.
Okay. Let's go.
Mao.
My Lord.
Check where the City Lord was during the last Lantern Festival
and whether he was in the City Lord's Mansion or not.
Is this related to usurping the throne?
Just do it.
My Lord,
Sima Qi knows you're the benefactor behind the scenes now?
I think...
we both misunderstood Sima Qi.
He is completely loyal.
He's a good official.
My Lord, are you alright?
You weren't like this before you left.
What's wrong with you?
I'm fine.
I just think
Sima Qi is quite a good person.
Give Sima Qi an umbrella.
Don't let the sun fry his brain.
Don't tell him it's my order.
Let's talk when we get back.
City Lord,
you... you must prioritize the people of the city.
What exactly is he trying to say?
Be happy.
So it was you all along.
But why is it you?
I've finally found you.
But you're the City Lord.
What can I do?
My Lord!
Why are you dressed like this in my chambers?
My Lord, please forgive me.
I didn't mean to.
Get up.
You may leave.
My Lord.
Seriously?
Yuan Qingheng could really go this far?
My Lord,
I'm just concerned about you.
What is...
What is this pink powder?
My Lord.
My Lord,
I've been admiring you for a long time.
Please grant me your favor for once.
My Lord!
Feng Yi didn't expect that
the amount of exercise she did today would meet the standard in this way.
My Lord!
I was so scared.
I finally made it out.
Luckily, I had spare clothes at the palace gate.
Ms. Feng?
Ms. Feng, why are you here?
Jiyue?
Jiyue, help me.
I think I've been drugged.
Hurry and find me a doctor.
No need to find a doctor.
My family has been in the medical profession for generations.
I'll check you out.
What's wrong?
Do you mind if we come in to take your pulse?
A doctor smiling isn't terrifying,
but a doctor frowning is truly terrifying.
Physician Lin,
is there something wrong with me?
Open your mouth.
Has anyone tampered with your food recently?
Well…
At my place,
from the raw ingredients to the cooked dishes,
and finally to my mouth,
it passed through at least 20 people.
It was like a sieve, full of holes.
I don't know if anyone tampered with it.
Your house is that big?
Listen to me.
You've been poisoned by a chronic toxin called Zhiman.
Although you haven't been poisoned for long,
if it continues over a longer period,
you're certain to die in two years.
Certain to die?
Moreover, this toxin is very difficult for outsiders to diagnose.
What's worse is that
it can only be cured with a herbal bath.
A herbal bath?
Well, I'll go and prescribe the medicine for you.
Who poisoned me?
Say it again. What did you do?
Well, it was not entirely my fault.
I only found out about it last night.
Someone in the organization turned the head chef of the Imperial Kitchen,
and he immediately poisoned the City Lord.
He thought he had made a great contribution,
so he reported it to me.
Don't you oversee your people's actions?
When it comes to power...
I'm just a flag
they need.
So,
you're also just a puppet?
Why would a puppet make things hard for another puppet?
I'm already miserable enough.
How about having a cup of tea?
There's something worse.
This poison can only be cured with a herbal bath.
But there is no bath here.
Am I really going to die from this poison?
No need.
I have it. I have it.