[Return of the Queen]
[Episode 23]
The secret document
is hidden behind the painting.
Siyu is still missing.
Everything is going downhill
and turning more and more against us.
What should we
do next, Chairman?
Or maybe we could...
What's going on?
I'll go check it out.
Chairman.
W-What's happening here?
Could it be that the wind was too strong
and just blew it away?
Check the CCTV footage
and alert security.
This is the most critical moment.
We need to make sure
everything is secure,
both at home and at the company.
I'll go right away.
Got it.
Our insider just delivered this,
and nobody has opened it yet.
[To Ye Haimeng]
This is...
Lu Sinan left it for you?
Tan Xin,
open it.
Haimeng,
it's me.
Today, we just
completed our marriage registration.
The wedding ceremony
will be held the day after tomorrow.
After that,
we'll be heading to Monaco
for our honeymoon.
I'm leaving this video message
for you today
to admit
that I lied.
From the moment
I met you at the book café a year ago,
it was all a premeditated plan.
Six months ago,
my family faced
the worst credit crisis
in its history.
My father's
Changlu Capital Group,
suffered massive credit losses
following
the real estate industry's downfall.
My family is about to fall.
Actually,
I could have ignored them.
But if I
ran away on my own,
my father,
sister, and brother
would face the greatest crisis
of their lives.
They'd lose
everything they currently own—
property,
finances, education, and their future.
I can't even imagine
what they'd go through.
Also,
my father took my son away.
He is the child I had
with my college lover,
born overseas.
My father used him
as a leverage
to force me into a final choice:
choose my son,
or choose to deceive you.
In the end, I chose
you.
I know that no matter how many times
I say I'm sorry,
it can never make up
for what my family and I
did to you—
a fraudulent marriage,
tricking you out of
your Mare Nubium shares,
using marital co-ownership
to carve up
your family's vast fortune.
I have no right
to ask for your forgiveness.
But Haimeng,
I'm leaving this video message
to tell you that
I want to change the plan.
I won't follow my father's plan.
I've already made the arrangements.
Once my local friends
at the honeymoon hotel—
acting on my father's orders—
make you disappear,
I will secretly
get you out of the hotel.
My friends will take you away immediately
and make sure
you're safe.
I will return to China
and take, according to my father's plan,
some of your Mare Nubium shares.
After we use those shares
to obtain enough resources to support
Changlu Group
for its revival,
I will return to you
and personally explain
everything that happened.
This is already
the only solution I could come up with
under such extreme circumstances—
the only way
to protect my family,
my love,
and to avoid hurting you.
So Lu Sinan actually
had people at the hotel ready
to fake your death
and get you out.
I don't believe it.
If his plan was to take me away,
why did he push me
into the pool?
Why did someone rush into the room?
And why did we still get into
that car accident?
Was that accident...
really an accident?
There's one last thing.
If my plan fails,
if I stay in Monaco
and never return—
What is Lu Sinan saying?
Haimeng,
if I die in Monaco,
please,
do whatever it takes
to take back Mare Nubium completely.
I already sense that,
to prevent the Lu family
from being destroyed,
my father
would do anything,
even make you and me
disappear together.
What Lu Sinan meant was
that he was forced by his father
to marry you.
He wanted to use this sham marriage
to take over
your shared Mare Nubium shares.
But three days before departure,
he recorded this video.
In the video, he said
there was a good chance
that he and you would both be made
to disappear.
Lu Sinan said
he might stay in Monaco forever.
He had a feeling
that his father
would want him dead.
How could that be?
Lu Sinan is the eldest son
of the Lu family.
He's Lu Changdong's biological son.
Lu Changdong using Lu Sinan's son
to threaten him
is already unbelievable.
How could he possibly
want to kill Lu Sinan?
Could it be that,
besides Lu Sinan wanting to harm me
and make me fake my death in Monaco,
his father
wanted to kill us both?
[Mr. F]
The honeymoon hotel footage
you asked me to check—
I could only find one clip,
just a few dozen seconds long.
I've sent it to your phone.
Please take a look.
This is the CCTV footage
from the hotel back then.
So...
someone really did try
to kill Lu Sinan.
Today, I suddenly remembered
that Sinan once sent me
some unexpected photos
and a strange message
when you were overseas.
I don't know
[Bai Jingmin]
if it might help
with your equity case.
Are you safe these days?
When are you coming back?
[Lu Sinan]
[Someone is following us.]
[Four years ago, Monaco]
What happened?
Sir,
are you alright?
Haimeng!
What's going on?
Do you need help?
Excuse me?
Room service.
We didn't order room service.
It was your wife who ordered room service.
What are you doing?
You work for Mo.
My father wants me dead.
He wants to get rid of Haimeng and—
Only the dead can keep secrets.
Sinan?
Sinan!
Go!
Let's go!
Get in the car.
Sinan,
who are they?
Thieves or robbers?
Should we call the police?
I'll make the call.
If anything happens to us,
don't contact anyone.
Don't ask anyone for help.
Don't trust anyone!
What are you talking about?
Remember what I said.
Haimeng.
Haimeng, calm down.
Haimeng!
Haimeng.
That's impossible.
Lu Sinan and I
could never be like that.
No.
I have to find him.
I need to get to the bottom of everything.
Ms. Ye!
Haimeng!
Where is she going?
She's not going to Cloud Manor
to find Lu Changdong, is she?
Follow her.
That's roughly the situation.
I'll go check it out.
Ms. Ye,
it's so late. You—
Ms. Ye!
Dad!
Haimeng!
What are you doing?
If your intention in trying to kill me
was to gain control of Mare Nubium,
why did you kill Lu Sinan?
He was your son,
your own flesh and blood.
Today,
you're not here because of my younger son,
but because of my eldest son.
Even a tiger will not eat its own cub.
Why were you so cruel
to Lu Sinan?
He was the heir to Changlu Capital—
my own eldest son—
yet he never once sought
to seize the company
or enlarge our fortune.
He even went behind our backs
to get married and have a child.
Just because he lost his mother,
does that mean he also lost
the warmth of a family?
I let him grow up freely.
Was that my failure
as a father?
He was weak, timid,
and had no ambition.
How could he ever be worthy
of being my son?
How could he possibly
succeed me at Changlu Capital?
So you decided to kill him?
Being able to sacrifice for the family
is his glory.
To me,
other than Changlu Capital,
which I've built with
all my blood and sweat,
no one is exempt from sacrifice.
If anyone harms
the Lu family's interests
or stands in the way of Changlu Capital,
no matter who they are—
even my eldest
or my youngest son—
they must die.
That's all twisted logic.
In this world,
there's more—
far more precious—
than money, profit,
capital, and your desires.
Rubbish.
All that so-called
affection, love,
family, friendship—
nothing but trash.
Your trash can't be traded
for a single cent of gain.
It can't buy you
any means to survive.
In a world
this cruel and ruthless,
there's only fighting—
no compassion.
Why are you laughing?
I'm laughing
because you're truly pitiful.
What did you say?
In your world,
there's only darkness
and no light,
only malice
and no goodness.
You've never felt
a family's love,
You've never
been looked up to by your sons
or admired by your wife.
Your whole life is nothing
but money,
ruthlessness,
and murder.
You think
that by accumulating wealth,
you can control the world.
Let me tell you,
that's impossible.
Ye Haimeng.
Today,
I'll be your opponent.
I'll show you
that you're not the only strong one.
Men aren't the only ones
who can take control.
Evil isn't the only thing
that can prevail.
I'll defend Mare Nubium
and destroy your Changlu Capital.
Overseas reports indicate
that the Lu family and Changlu Group
have secured
backing from foreign investors.
Mare Nubium's
share price
[Mare Nubium]
has been heavily suppressed
in international markets,
and preliminary estimates
suggest it has lost
more than ten billion in assets
over the past week.
Several foreign chains
have cut ties with Mare Nubium.
The company is suffering
a massive blow in the capital market
and now teeters on the brink of collapse.
Bochen,
you're back.
Well,
your father
was forced to step down, right?
He hasn't been in a good mood lately.
I was thinking
the weather's been nice lately.
He might want to go out for a while.
I'm just
packing some extra supplies for him,
in case he goes hiking or travels far
and runs short—
Mom,
are you going with him?
Probably.
Mom,
I'm hungry.
Let me make you a bowl of noodles.
Thanks, Mom.
[Password is needed
after restarting the device]
[Wrong password]
[Message]
[Album]
[Recently deleted]
[Mare Nubium's Transfer Record]
What are you doing?
Dad.
Don't call me Dad.
I don't have
such an ungrateful son.
We raised you with such hardship,
yet this is how you repay me?
Did you take photos?
Give me your phone.
Give me your phone!
Dad.
Give it to me!
Dad!
This is all the evidence
of Mare Nubium's financial leaks.
If you don't want
to spend the rest of your life in prison,
you should confess.
Apologize to Haimeng,
to all Mare Nubium shareholders
and employees,
and accept your punishment.
You want me to confess?
We've already seen through
all your secrets.
If you repent now,
there's still a chance for you.
But if you keep going down
this path,
you won't just bring harm to Mom—
you'll ruin the Ye family.
Nonsense!
Rubbish!
Give me that phone!
Give it to me!
It's already been sent.
Haimeng and Ling Ke
have already received it.
You're rebelling against me?
I can't take it anymore!
You and Mom were the ones
who adopted me from the orphanage.
I've lived in fear,
at your feet, for twenty years.
I accepted your beatings and scoldings,
trying to please you.
All I wanted was
to gain your approval.
But Dad,
in these 20 years,
have you ever really looked me in the eye?
Have you ever let me finish
a single sentence?
You can't take out
your frustration about being infertile
on me alone.
I am a human being.
I'm not a pet.
I'm not someone who can survive
just because you feed me.
For over 20 years,
I've given everything
for this family.
I don't want to continue anymore.
What do you mean?
I don't want to be a Ye anymore.
From today on,
for the rest of my life,
I'll live only for myself.
Finally showing your true colors,
aren't you?
Have you always
wanted to seize my property
and then
get rid of your mother and me?
You ungrateful thing!
Give me that phone!
Give it to me!
I appreciate both of you
for raising me.
But
Dad,
one cannot let their desires
grow without limits.
Haimeng's family
once treated us
as their closest family.
But you and Mom
have given them
the most devastating blow.
I can't accept
such behavior.
I refuse to be a son
of this family any longer.
I hope that in the future,
we will never
see each other again.
W-What's going on here?
Get up now.
Bochen.
Wait,
Bochen,
where are you going?
[Mare Nubium]
Haimeng.
Two more branch offices
have submitted the decoupling agreement.
It seems this time, Lu Changdong
is going all out against us.
No need to respond.
But in this spiraling situation,
our headquarters
will only keep losing more and more.
Plus, our stock price
has nearly hit rock bottom.
The financial institutions
will withdraw all their investments.
We'll be in serious trouble then.
Don't worry.
It's going to be fine.
[Ye Bochen]
[Mare Nubium]
Go see him.
With the company in this state,
how can I leave?
Go see him.
I'll take care of things here.
If anything happens,
make sure you call me
right away.
[Mare Nubium]
From now on,
you can't call me "Kid" anymore.
Call me your boyfriend.
I'm willing
to keep standing by your side.
I'm willing to keep being with you,
loving you.
With me here,
you won't hurt anymore.
[Haicang Bridge]
Hello.
Excuse me,
are you the president of Mare Nubium,
Ms. Ye Haimeng?
Yes, I am.
What can I do for you?
Hello.
We're co-investors
in the archery club with Mr. Lu Siyu.
We're calling to inform you
that we have sold
Mr. Lu Siyu's stock share
in the archery club
to a new investor.
The total transfer amount
is 22 million.
Following Mr. Lu's authorization,
all the money, after tax deductions,
has been deposited
into your personal account.
You can use it
as you see fit.
What did you say?
The proceeds from Siyu's archery club sale
have been transferred to my account?
Why?
[Haicang Bridge]
We're simply acting
under Mr. Lu Siyu's authorization.
Authorization?
When did this happen?
Was it when Siyu
was still at the archery club?
Half a month ago, Siyu—
Besides the transfer notification,
we cannot disclose anything else.
[Haicang Bridge]
Haimeng.
♪ The wind blows softly ♪
♪ I chase closely ♪
♪ It rains all night ♪
It's me.
♪ Days pass by like this ♪
♪ Who am I to you? ♪
♪ I'm tired too ♪
♪ But tell me why ♪
♪ Why do I have to ♪
♪ Keep trapped in this cycle? ♪
[Haicang Bridge]
♪ I still can't let go of you ♪
♪ Carrying this weight inside ♪
♪ Even if I never hear from you again ♪
♪ Watch a movie ♪
♪ I'm here ♪
♪ Those sweet words were not
meant for me ♪
♪ I still can't let go of you ♪
♪ And it's not such a pity ♪
♪ Actually, I won't push myself too hard ♪
♪ Scrolling through the messages ♪
♪ Closing my eyes ♪
♪ Good morning ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ Carry on ♪
♪ Who am I to you? ♪
♪ I'm tired too ♪
♪ But tell me why ♪
♪ Why do I have to ♪
♪ Keep trapped in this cycle? ♪
♪ I still can't let go of you ♪
♪ Carrying this weight inside ♪
♪ Even if I never hear from you again ♪
♪ Watch a movie ♪
♪ I'm here ♪
♪ Those sweet words were not
meant for me ♪
♪ If this is all I can be in the end ♪
♪ Then let me be this way, in the end ♪
♪ But I still can't let you go ♪
♪ Covered in scars ♪
♪ I still can't let go of you ♪
♪ Such a pity ♪
♪ I'm powerless now ♪
♪ To keep on loving you ♪
♪ Delete the messages ♪
♪ Closing my eyes ♪
♪ Good night ♪