Hey, what the hell is going on?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why don't you get it?
I couldn't stand you.
I absolutely hated you.
You've always made a fool of me.
Do you have any idea what I went through
to become a hairstylist just to prove you all wrong?
Have you ever even considered it?!
And then you just waltz back into my life...
So that's what you thought...
- Then why did you go out with me?
- I figured I'd just mess around with you and dump you.
Revenge. It's revenge.
Look at that. That mark.
I was planning to do it in one month.
So... that's what that meant...
- I'm leaving.
- What?
Are you going to ruin my plan?
Hey, Natsuo.
Let's do it one last time.
- No!
- Isn't that what you want?
Stop it! Ugh...
Natsuo!
- Ugh...
- Don't move!
Hurry up and take it off!
- No!
- Shut up!
I said shut up! Natsuo...
- No...
- Take it off!
No...
- Mmm...
- Natsu... Take it off!
Ah, ah... I said no...
Natsuo!
- Stop it...
- Shut up!
No...
Natsuo!
This is it.
This is the look I wanted to see.
And yet...
"The Proper Way to Write Love"
(Episode 8: The Way to Write Proper Love)
Everyone, can I have a minute?
We're currently in talks with RaMu
about coming to our salon.
What, RaMu?
That's right. Apparently,
she sent a DM yesterday saying she'd love to get her hair cut here.
Wait, RaMu, as in "the" RaMu?
- The famous influencer.
- Yep.
It seems Haruyo-san's last post
went viral.
- Whoa.
- Wow.
- 100,000 followers?
- I heard she's actually a businesswoman.
No way!
So that's the deal, Hiro. I'm counting on you.
This is a big chance for both you
and the salon.
- Yes, I understand.
- Good.
Yes.
- Yes.
Let's do this!
- Good luck.
- I'm looking forward to it.
- Oh? Drinking a bit too much?
- Yeah.
- Had a gathering yesterday.
- I see.
But enough about me.
- Hmm?
- What's up with you?
- Huh?
- You're actually working seriously.
What's that supposed to mean? I'm always serious.
Right...
But, boss...
Have you ever hurt someone without realizing it?
- Huh?
- Well...
I've always been the one who gets dumped.
I've never even lasted a month with anyone.
Well, that's... kind of bad.
Really bad.
I always get made fun of
and then dumped. It's the same cycle...
I see.
But this time, it feels different somehow...
I bet it does.
Huh?
It's the first time I've ever seen it.
You, worrying about someone else like this.
So of course you're going to struggle.
It's the first time you've ever tried
to grow a relationship with someone.
- Ugh.
- That's a good sign, isn't it?
Grow...
Ahh...
Nope, I'm full...
- Huh? Hey, wait...
- Here you go.
- I can't eat that much either.
- It's fine.
- When you're worried, you just gotta eat.
- Seriously...
- Isn't this way too much macaroni salad?
- I said it's fine.
My wife made it, so it's delicious.
Huh?
- Mmm.
- Mmm?
It's good.
- Right?
- Yeah.
No way.
Does a guy this handsome really exist?
I'm Hiro, your stylist. It's a pleasure to meet you.
- I'm RaMu. Nice to meet you too.
- Right this way, please.
Look at the wall! It's so textured!
- That's our signature touch.
- Wow. A textured signature touch?
So, what are we doing today?
Today, um, let's see...
Do whatever you think looks best.
Let me see... Hmm.
Got it. You can count on me.
I'm counting on you.
Alright.
Hey!
Here we go.
Break time.
Yeah.
Alright.
Ugh...
Ah...
- Boss.
- Yeah?
Still hurts?
Yeah, a little...
You alright?
Ugh...
I hope this does the trick...
Oh, yeah. What time is it?
Don't you think they did a great job with the cut? Look.
So cute!
(Breaking News: Pedestrian struck by car in Tokyo.
The accident occurred near a construction site.)
Huh?
Hmm? Shiina...?
- Hiro-kun, one second...
- What?
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
This phone...
This has to be Natsuo's, right?
Apparently, he got hit by a car...
I'm going to go look for the hospital.
- Wait, what...?
- Hiro-kun, you just wait here.
I'll call you later.
Shiina! It's okay, I'll go.
RaMu-san. It seems a friend of mine was taken to the hospital.
What?! Is he okay?
Shiina will take over from here.
What?
Manager, I'm really sorry, but...
is that okay?
Can't be helped.
Shiina.
I'm sure you know this,
but this is being broadcast worldwide.
If you screw this up, I'll...
- Whoa!
- I'm leaving the rest to you.
Same here. Heh, you'll be fine!
- Okay.
- Right.
Good luck.
This is Shiina, I'll be taking over.
- Pleased to meet you.
- You too.
- Okay, I'm going to start cutting now.
- Okay.
Is it okay if I make the layers
a little shorter here?
- Mhm, yes. Please do.
- Okay, got it.
Natsuo...!
Hiro, what are you doing here?
The truth is... it's my first time cooking.
You need to have more faith in these hands.
And your heart, too.
Otherwise, your hands and your heart...
what a pathetic waste!
It's nice, having someone next to me.
Huh?
It's strangely comforting.
Hiro.
Hey, can you hear me?
Hiro!
Come on, get down here.
Natsuo... Natsuo...!
Natsuo... Natsuo... Natsuo...
Hiro.
Huh? A stomach exam?
Yeah. The boss.
I was at the hospital with him.
Then what about that phone?
I freaked out and dropped it.
A car suddenly came rushing right at me.
I'm glad you're here.
Oh, right.
I heard the victim only has minor injuries.
And by the way, the boss just has gastritis.
- I see.
- Yeah.
- What about you, Natsuo?
- Me?
I'm totally fine.
That's a relief.
I...
I really hated you back in high school...
No need to bring that up again.
You were always bugging me, and I was such a loser.
I always thought
you were making fun of me.
But...
you were the only one.
The only one who talked to me for all three years.
So...
the truth is, I wanted to talk to you more.
But I had no self-confidence...
I... I was always running away.
From facing myself.
You haven't changed at all.
Huh?
That earnest side of yours, Hiro...
I always really liked that about you.
You'd be out there all by yourself,
taking care of that filthy courtyard.
And you'd always listen to everything
I had to say until the very end.
You even wrote the furigana for me.
That's why I was so happy the other day.
When I realized that Hiro was that Suzuki.
Honestly, I couldn't tell at all just from your looks.
That's when I realized I'd fallen for Hiro all over again.
I'm sure of it.
No matter how much your looks or appearance might change,
I know I'd fall in love with Hiro over and over again.
Natsuo...!
I...
Without you,
nothing I eat tastes good,
and I always wake up at seven in the morning.
I was totally fine before,
but now it hurts so much not having Natsuo next to me...
Hiro...
I love you.
I...
Somewhere along the line, I seriously fell for you.
Don't I stink of sweat?
Should I go take a shower?
No. It's fine like this.
Huh...?
You can do what you did the other day.
I'll be still.
You like that, don't you? When it's rough.
No, I don't.
Of course I don't.
Natsuo.
- Hmm?
- Are you okay?
It might be a little heavy...
Oh, sorry.
Hiro.
Natsuo...
Hiro...
- Ah, it's a beautiful day.
- Yeah.
I hear Shiina's doing amazing.
Huh? In what way?
She's totally going viral. Look!
Her follower count has skyrocketed, too.
- That's all my doing.
- What are you going to do?
What if Shiina is chosen as
the representative for the next competition?
- I'm fine with it.
- You are?!
What should we do?
Hey, what about this spot?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Okay, okay.
Here.
- Okay. Gently.
- Right.
Okay, here.
- Slowly.
- Easy does it.
- Gently.
- Yeah.
Oh, looking good.
- Mission complete.
- Right.
- Your turn, Hiro.
- Mission complete.
Heh heh. All right, let's go.
What's next?
- I'm hungry.
- Oh.
We've applied first aid for now,
but we should probably
put it somewhere with good airflow.
Yeah.
What about outside?
Huh?
It might recover outside, right?
Out in the wide-open land.
The airflow is perfect, and it'll get
all the rain and sun it could want.
Natsuo.
- You're smart.
- Hmm?
You always know what's most important.
You think so?
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
Okay, but first.
- Huh? What?
- Up we go.
All right, I get it.
Mmm.
This is nice.
- Am I heavy?
- No, you're fine.
(This story is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to actual persons or groups is purely coincidental.)