Run!
- Hurry up! - Run!
- Run! - Come on!
Hurry up!
What are you doing? Run!
- Get them! - Stop there!
Stop!
Stop there!
- Run! - Hey!
Where is it coming from?
That's me.
Ryu Su Hyeon.
What is this?
Why is Hui Young's stuff with me?
(Chicago Typewriter)
That way!
Let's go.
- Get them! - Where is it coming from?
What is this?
Are we invisible?
We must be like ghosts here.
Look, they can't see us.
They're running away! Get them!
Over here!
(Episode 13)
Anastasia?
Are you okay?
Oh, it's you.
What are you doing here at this hour?
I heard gun shots on the way from my composer.
I was so terrified.
So I hid myself in the backstreet.
My heart is still pounding.
The terrorist attack has stopped for now,
but it's still dangerous around here.
You should hurry and go home.
Well...
I'm sorry to ask this,
but could you walk me to the main street?
I'm still very shocked.
Sure.
You're very kind.
Is that...
Mr. Baek?
His name is Heo Young Min here.
You already knew about this?
You knew Tae Min is related to our past lives?
I don't know the details yet.
I just know that he was a secret agent of Japan.
A secret agent?
Then isn't this too dangerous?
Su Hyeon doesn't seem to know that.
Let's follow them.
I can walk alone from here.
I can walk you to Carpe Diem.
If my boss finds me with a customer,
I'll get in trouble.
I'll never forget your kindness.
See you.
I'll follow Su Hyeon.
You follow Young Min.
Okay. Meet me here in an hour.
I gave you all the information.
How could you miss him?
I had no idea the sniper was there.
Where did the sniper go?
No one knows.
But according to some witnesses,
it's the same sniper from Min Hwan Shik's case.
There must be some traces left.
Find evidence by all means.
Yes, sir.
Your guest is here, sir.
You were aware that there would be an attack...
at the house of the vice-president of Siksan Bank.
And you still failed to arrest any Joseon Youth Alliance members.
Is that true?
I have nothing to say.
Why did you withdraw the troops?
We should not waste our military force...
over only a few people.
Shouldn't you still arrest them and get them to talk?
Joseon Youth Alliance...
operates under absolute secrecy.
They don't know themselves where they belong.
We better take our time and...
I believe I already gave you enough time!
I'll make sure...
to arrest the leading members of Joseon Youth Alliance soon.
A trap has already been set up.
A trap?
Who is he waiting for?
Have you been waiting long?
Oh, you're here.
Get in the car.
Let's talk on the way.
Sure.
What took you so long? Everyone's been worried.
I took a detour to ditch the tail.
Mom.
Thank you, Su Hyeon.
You saved my life.
Thank your parents instead.
They gave you a long life.
By the way, wasn't something...
fishy today?
What do you mean?
They showed up so early.
As if they were expecting us.
It seemed like they knew about our escape routes.
I hope it's just a coincidence.
And the streets of Kyungsung are not complicated.
I don't think so. It doesn't feel right.
There might be...
secret agents hiding within our organization.
Secret agents?
What are you doing here?
Su Hyeon is in there with her comrades.
They're suspecting there are secret agents in the organization.
Secret agents?
If you're going to shoot, shoot now.
If not, put it down.
It's the doctor guy.
How many are wounded?
Let's go in.
What happened?
Why were we brought back?
My apologies. I got distracted for a second.
Goodness, you should've taken us to a nice place.
Out of all places, you took us to a gunfight.
That's not under my control.
You must've gone to where your subconscious led you.
Are you saying I wanted to go there?
Not really.
That's where you and Seol's subconscious met.
Did you...
feel anything different from the last time?
Anything different?
Yes, there was.
Last time, other people could see me.
We even did things together in the past life.
But this time,
it seemed like they couldn't see me.
In the past,
you were confused because you didn't know you were in your past life.
But now you can distinguish between your present and past lives.
So...
did you find anything out?
- What? - What?
There was a secret agent in the organization.
Mom also said something.
I remember things from my past life.
Don't get involved with that man.
Don't meet him.
You guys must not cross paths.
Was Mom...
You must not let any of the ill-fated relationships repeat.
Was she the secret agent who betrayed the leader?
Young Min said he laid traps to catch the leaders...
of Joseon Youth Alliance.
Have you been waiting long?
And...
Oh, you're here.
No way.
Was Shin Yul the secret agent?
Seol said she shot someone next to the typewriter.
And...
Was the person who shot me...
Ryu Su Hyeon?
What's this?
Who are you looking at?
What is it? If you have something to say, say it.
Have you forgotten?
Until the novel is finished, we will share each other's memories.
And trust will be at the heart of that practice.
We shall not keep any secrets from each other...
nor betray each other.
We said that,
but we didn't sign any papers yet.
- Right. - Right.
More than anything, I'm very tired today.
Experiencing the past life is quite exhausting, isn't it?
- That's what I'm saying. It is. - It really is.
Then let's stop here today.
When we meet next time, we will sign the contract...
and resume writing my novel together. Okay?
- Okay. - Okay.
I was right.
What do you mean?
You were a great, confident, and brave sniper.
See?
Once you opened it up, there was nothing terrible in it.
In the end, I wasn't the one you killed.
I told you that you have nothing to lose when you listen to me.
Why don't you stop there? It's no fun if you go on.
The boss will personally take you home today.
All right, Boss.
Let's go.
Then...
who did I kill?
I still have the feeling in the tip of my fingers.
Whenever I thought about it, I become too sad.
It was painful.
It broke my heart so much...
that my hand used to tremble.
It looks like...
I killed the owner...
of this pocket watch.
Does it mean I'm the person Seol killed?
Why would Su Hyeon kill me?
What on earth happened between the three of us?
If Shin Yul...
was the secret agent who betrayed our organization...
If that was the reason why he had to wander as a ghost,
should I tell him?
Why don't we go get some beer?
(Send me back to Chicago)
Do you...
want to go back to Chicago?
What's the reason?
Is it because I was too hard on you?
All right.
I won't abuse you anymore,
so don't go...
to Chicago.
Why do you keep looking at me?
Do you hate feeding me that much?
Did it look like that?
My eyes are at fault.
I'm sorry. Keep eating.
I think I'm going to get indigestion.
You...
- Yes. - Chicago...
I mean, secret agent...
What is a Chicago secret agent?
I've heard of a Chicago gang,
but I've never heard of a Chicago secret agent.
I got the question messed up.
- What I'm trying to say is... - Se Ju!
Where's my Se Ju?
There you are.
What's all this?
Did you know that I'd be coming? I'm so hungry right now.
You read my mind.
What's wrong with this? It tastes so bland.
Everything tastes like that after ghosts eat it.
Just think that you're eating at a memorial service.
Is your personal chef from Andong?
- Se Ju. - Yes?
Don't you think it's about time you start spicing things up?
- Was it that bland? - Yes.
Throw in some hot chili powder or soybean paste. It can be anything.
Let's enrich it.
All right. I'll talk to my chef.
No, I'm talking about your novel, "Chicago Typewriter".
Is it a romance, fantasy, hard-boiled or action novel?
Let's be clear on the genre.
You won't be able to fix it later if you miss the right time.
What's your point?
To be honest with you,
this novel is too pure.
That's why the comments say that the story is too loose...
and old. People are even saying that you're a fanatic patriot.
Ji Seok.
With this novel,
I want to continue writing it in my own way.
Do that. You always wrote in the way you want.
You never worried about what those in the literary circle would say...
and kept writing novels that the public were craving.
That's exactly why I always had to worry about what people would think.
And I had to put what they wanted before what I wanted to write about.
Of course, you have to. We can earn money because of them.
I told you before.
I felt lost as to what to write about and why I had to write.
But I've found the answer.
I went through hoops to find it. I just want to write about that.
So you're insisting that you want to write something that won't sell.
I'll obviously do my best,
but if people don't like it,
I'll have to deal with it.
Hey, Se Ju.
You said we should never be jaded. How can you say such a thing?
I've said everything I had to say.
You should get back to work, Boss.
Fine! Do whatever you want.
You never listen to me anyway.
Are you mad at me?
Come on, Ji Seok. I won't feel good if you leave like this.
You're not about to cry, are you?
Ji Seok?
Why are you trying to sound so friendly?
Gosh, please don't.
I said, don't.
Because of what you said, I've been working like a money-making machine.
You wanted a clear line between work and personal matters, so I listened.
I've been catering to everything you wanted and needed.
But how can you do this to me?
I don't think I've done anything you should be this upset about.
Do you really not know what you've done wrong?
Gosh, don't talk like you're my girlfriend.
I didn't want to look petty, so I wasn't going to say this,
but let's be honest. You put out extra food because you're lonely,
yet you've never even invited me over for a meal.
Well, that's...
"That tender-hearted guy is just putting up a tough front."
"He'll open up to me eventually." I really tried to understand you.
But you putting up a wall like this hurts my feelings a lot.
When did I put up a wall?
No.
Mr. Han,
you have changed a lot.
Ms. Kang.
When I see you these days, I can't help but wonder...
if you actually need me.
Ms. Kang, why are you being like this?
Of course, you're always...
- indispensable to me. - Right.
I used to be.
But I'm only allowed to come in here at set times these days.
I used to know everything about your writing schedule...
and even checked whether you're out of dental floss or not.
Now, I have to ask around to know your schedule...
Gosh, these high-end brands sure know what they're doing.
Thanks, Se Ju.
Who says you're cold? You're so warm-hearted and generous.
I don't know if it's okay for me to accept this, but wearing this...
means that I must bear the weight of it,
so I'll do my best, Mr. Han.
I'm glad you like it.
By the way, I thought we wouldn't have to deal with crazy stalkers...
after that stalker committed suicide.
I guess people already forgot about it.
Speaking of which, I think we should have taken...
strong action towards the culprit of the motorcycle incident.
That's what I'm saying. Se Ju.
Let's talk to the police again and capture that jerk.
We should make sure the media covers it too.
That way, prospective terrorists will be careful.
My apologies.
Gosh, I'm so sorry. We'll give you a new one.
Sang Mi, what are you doing?
I'm sorry. She's new.
Your dessert will be on the house.
Oh, I'm assuming this 80-year-old weasel here won't have any.
You want to do what with Jin Oh?
Gosh, why are you being like this?
You promised me that you'd properly introduce me to Jin Oh.
When did I say that?
I asked you to arrange something for me to meet him.
Were you not listening to me at all or what?
How many times do I have to tell you? I can't introduce you to him...
even if I want to.
Why? Why on earth can't you introduce me to him?
Do you...
believe in supernatural beings?
What do you mean by "supernatural"?
For example,
things like ghosts.
You should just say that you're keeping him on the hook.
That'd be less cruel, you wench.
I was telling her the truth.
What is this crack?
(Sungsoocheong)
Let's see.
Darn it. I thought I should give it a try because I get no customers,
but no one is visiting this either.
Gosh, my eyes are blurry.
What just happened?
Is the window open?
It's not.
Who are you?
Someone is here, right?
Goodness.
Who... Who are you?
I'm sorry for visiting you again. I'd like your advice.
By any chance, are you that guy who came here with Bang Jin?
Yes, I am.
What is it? Why are you here again?
Random cracks are starting to appear on my body.
You're getting cracks?
How many years have you been wandering around as a ghost?
I've spent 80 years locked up in a typewriter.
What? You're locked up in an object?
How did Bang Jin get involved with this poor soul?
Please answer my question.
In short, it's a sign that you'll perish soon.
Perish?
In other words, you don't have much time left in the worldly realm.
Why all of a sudden...
Either the object you're in is at its life's end, or...
- That is not the case. - Then...
you probably got involved in people's affairs, played tricks,
and abused your power.
When such cracks appear, your power starts to disperse little by little.
If you continue to use your power and energy,
the cracks will spread and deepen.
Then one day, you'll perish completely.
You were supposed to quietly stay inside that object.
All of this is happening...
because you interfered in the worldly realm.
You should have just quietly stayed inside that thing.
Jin Oh!
You came.
I thought you'd never come here again.
Bang Jin.
You told me that we'd never see each other again,
and Mom kept telling me not to see you for no reason.
Then Seol spewed a load of nonsense...
about how she can't introduce me to you because you're a ghost.
Who are you, really?
Do you work for National Intelligence Service?
Just let him go.
Mom.
Let him go. You two aren't meant to be.
What? Why not?
What is it? Are we supposed to be incompatible?
It's because he's not human.
This guy is a ghost.
What's this nonsense now?
I can clearly see him.
I can touch him too.
Have you lost your ability to differentiate ghosts from humans?
You're the only one who can see him.
I don't even see anything, you wench.
You can't see him?
That's completely crazy.
Are you really...
You're not, right?
What your mother said is right.
- I wanted to tell you sooner but... - You're lying.
I'm sorry...
that I'm a ghost.
No way.
That can't be!
She said I'll perish.
Does that mean I'll cease to exist?
There are still so many things that I have to do.
My memories aren't back yet either.
You're a ghost, yet you act just like us humans.
You even opened the door with your hand.
I guess you only flaunt your tricks in front of other people.
Are they for bluffing?
I want to reserve my power.
Where are you coming from?
Pardon? Oh, I was... I had to take care of something.
Follow me.
You're hiding something from me, aren't you?
Me? What do you mean?
(Send me back to Chicago.)
Why do you want to go back to Chicago all of a sudden?
I was just bored.
I wanted to practice typing.
- Really? You were practicing? - Yes.
You're already so good though. You don't need to practice.
What a diligent ghost.
You seem very happy to hear...
that I'm not leaving.
Me?
Sorry, that was my mistake.
By the way, did you drink this much...
to ask me that?
Because you needed the courage?
Actually,
there's something else that's been on my mind.
Ask away, whatever it is.
Well...
On the day I experienced my past life thanks to you,
I saw you...
secretly meeting with Heo Young Min.
It was the day we robbed the house of Siksan Bank's vice-president.
- Su Hyeon was covering fire... - Oh, right.
I remember that day.
I met up with Heo Young Min that day because...
Here's the invitation you asked for.
My gosh, thank you.
I can get my hands on such a privileged invitation...
because you, my friend, are from a family of barons.
Many VIPs have been invited to this meaningful event...
for promoting donations towards war fund.
It's a perfect opportunity to build connections with powerful people.
I'm looking forward to meeting...
and leaving a lasting impression on those influential high-ups.
Oh, right. I got you two tickets so that Hui Young can come too.
Right. He'd love to come.
He won't say no to such a meaningful party.
He loves to drink and party.
Here. I got you the invitation.
Good work.
A party for promoting donations towards war fund...
I guess the rich who are blinded by power will be there.
And they'll exploit the commoners...
in a more cruel way.
All that money will smell putrid.
Important figures in the General Government, high-up officials,
and diplomats from various countries will be there,
so it's the perfect occasion for us to carry out the plan.
And the blind money they'll collect should be used...
for the rebel forces, not as war fund.
It'll also...
show the world how determined we are to fight for Joseon's independence.
But won't it be too dangerous?
Those high-up officials alone will bring a bunch of bodyguards.
We've been invited,
so accepting the invitation would be a polite thing to do.
You know that it's a trap Heo Young Min has set up to catch us.
They'll use all of their resources in order to make sure...
that not even a single rat could escape the trap.
That's right.
That's why we have to pretend that we've bitten the bait.
In order to make him believe that things are going as he planned,
we, at Joseon Youth Alliance,
will officially prepare for attending the party...
but get ready to carry out the operation.
It's because they might have planted secret agents in our organization.
On the day of the operation,
most of the police force will be at the party.
We'll use our agents to attack them from behind.
You and I will be the only ones who know the full picture...
until the day. No one else can know.
It was a feint operation where we acted like we had fallen...
into their trap while working on attacking them from elsewhere.
Then you're saying we knew it from the beginning...
that Heo Young Min was Japan's secret agent.
Joseon Youth Alliance had a lot of Intel.
And don't underestimate Boss' keen insight.
What's with you? Why are you flattering him all of a sudden?
He staged everything as a coincidence to approach us,
but the first time we met him was so memorable...
that we started digging up Intel on him right away.
So?
Did the operation succeed?
That... I don't know.
I only remember up to right before...
we carried out the operation.
Anyway, one thing puts my mind at ease.
What do you mean?
The fact that you didn't betray me.
I'm relieved to know that.
I've been betrayed so many times by those whom I once trusted.
If I was betrayed by a ghost whom I've finally befriended,
I'd be very hurt.
Oh, there's one more thing I'm curious about.
If all the pieces of memories come together...
and the novel gets completed,
what will happen to you?
Then you will have fulfilled your wish.
Will you ascend to the upper world...
You won't, right?
Why are you asking?
Well... I'm just curious.
Keeping you around...
won't be too bad.
You'll continue to age,
and I'll stay young like this.
Won't you get jealous?
That I envy.
It's a sign that you'll perish soon.
In other words, you don't have much time left in the worldly realm.
Then one day,
you'll perish completely.
Why aren't you drinking?
I will. Cheers.
Bottoms up.
You still have some left.
Okay.
There's still some left.
There are many definitions of novels that were published in the 90s.
I'd like to...
define them with the word "mixture".
This phenomenon arose from a crisis in the literary world.
The crisis of literature...
no longer being the center of culture.
The pressure of having to compete with visual media.
These issues led to a diversity in novels.
You really know how to surprise people.
I do?
You're the one who wanted to see me.
In that kind of situation,
normal people would first reply with a yes or no.
Then they'd talk about where and when to meet.
You can't just pop out of the blue...
Gosh, this is no fun.
I wouldn't have come if I knew you were going to lecture me on manners.
I wanted to meet because I had something to ask you.
Why did you tell me about...
your long-cherished plan?
You don't even know me that well.
What will you do if I tell...
Se Ju everything?
No way.
You can never do that.
Why do you think that way?
While my brother was busy researching about Han Se Ju,
I was busy collecting information about you.
That's when I found out...
that you're always hidden behind Han Se Ju's shadow.
"He must be miserable."
"He must want to die."
"Or maybe..."
"he wants to..."
"kill him instead."
I'm pretty sure you want Han Se Ju to be miserable as much as I do.
For me, it's about my brother's death.
But for you, it's about yourself.
Am I wrong?
Mr. Han.
They found a new video regarding...
the motorcycle terror incident. They sent it to us via email.
Would you like to see the video?
Let's just...
let go of that incident.
We already decided to end it.
Okay. Then I'll delete the file.
Wait.
They already sent it to us,
so let's just take a look.
Mr. Han.
What's wrong?
I...
wasn't the target.
Mr. Han, look at this.
I think that person is too small to be a man.
Why? Did you forget something again?
Yes, I know. You want the white cucumber, not the green one.
You want the thin one, right?
You're really taking full advantage of me.
Okay, I'll hurry up and get it for you.
Seol!
Did you get hurt? Are you okay?
Are you okay, Seol?
I guess I'm alive.
Are you saying that...
the target was me?
Unfortunately, yes.
That doesn't make sense.
Do you think what just happened makes sense?
That motorcycle...
didn't even have a license plate number.
That means it was all planned beforehand.
Then I guess it won't end...
with just one try.
You guys shouldn't worry too much.
If that person was really trying to hit me with his motorcycle,
he would've done so even before I sensed anything.
I'm sure he was only trying to scare me.
Anyway, I'll still be careful.
No. That won't be enough.
Stay here...
until the culprit gets caught.
- What? - This place is much safer...
than where you're living right now.
I'm the one who put you in danger,
so I should be the one to take responsibility.
But still...
I came out to shop for groceries.
And now, you want me to live with a guy and a ghost?
I'm not Madame Freedom.
Do as I say.
I'm going to find out who's behind this and why.
I'm going to catch the culprit with my own two hands.
So stay by my side until then.
You should do as he says, Seol.
Am I supposed to be happy or not?
I don't know. I don't know.
I brought you this. You can wear this to bed.
Here.
Okay.
Well,
I was in France when "Stalker" got published.
A designer I met was a fan of mine, and she gave it to me as a gift.
This T-shirt is one of a kind.
It sounds so precious. How can I wear it to sleep?
It's okay. Just wear it.
I'm the one who invited you here. You deserve this much.
Thank you.
Well, okay. You should rest.
I'll be off then. Goodnight.
Keep your door locked.
You never know.
What's wrong, Mr. Han?
I didn't know which color you'd prefer.
It's made of organic cotton, so the texture is very soft.
It does look soft. Thank you so much.
Okay.
Goodnight.
Okay. Goodnight.
You didn't forget to keep the door locked, did you?
Why do you keep telling me to lock the door?
You should be the one to stop visiting me.
Why are you getting annoyed?
It's always safe to be careful.
Why are you here again?
I brought you pajama pants. I thought you might need them.
Was this made by an Italian master artisan?
Bingo. How did you know that?
You have good eyes.
You must be tired. Go to sleep.
My gosh, you startled me.
I thought you might need this.
Are they competing against each other?
What's their problem?
My goodness.
Mr. Han, why are you doing this?
Mr. Han.
- Mr. Han. - What?
Gosh, what's wrong with...
What did I do?
I really can't trust you.
I want you to sleep here with me tonight.
What?
Are you asking me to sleep in the same bed?
Seol can't take a full rest because of you.
Because of me? Are you sure it's not because of you?
Anyway,
while she's staying here,
any kind of independent action after sunset will not be permitted.
You better keep that in mind.
What is this?
Must you take it this far?
Yes, I must.
I'm a ghost. What can I possibly do?
From what I know,
you're a ghost who can pretty much do everything.
Shut it and go to sleep.
You're really something.
Thanks to you, I've been eating all three meals. It's become a habit.
I'm so fulfilled.
Happiness isn't anything grand.
I felt so uneasy earlier because of both the terrorist...
and the unexpected happening of having to suddenly live here.
But right now, the only thing I can think of is that I'm really sleepy.
Now that I think of it, sleeping is really important,
although it seems like nothing.
You guys are so simple-minded.
I can't believe you guys are talking about happiness over noodles.
What about you? When was the happiest moment for you?
- Me? - I want to know too.
When was the happiest moment in your life?
It was when I got a call that my novel won the rookie award.
It sounded like a lie.
My heart was filled up with excitement.
"I guess all my efforts are paying off now."
"Someone must've recognized all the effort I've put in."
This is what you call happiness, right?
What a pity. If I knew you back then, I would've congratulated you.
I know it's too late, but congratulations, Mr. Han.
Hey, you. The ghost who's been living for 80 years.
When was your happiest moment?
Or will you feel the happiest when your soul rests in peace?
Mine...
is right now.
- Right now? - Yes, right now.
The moment where the three of us have gathered together again.
We don't have to worry about what might happen tomorrow.
We also don't have to worry about our country's independence.
This moment right now is as light as a feather.
This moment where we don't have to feel guilty about enjoying...
a bowl of noodles.
Even now, when I close my eyes, I can clearly remember my friends,
whom I miss very much.
I can remember the faces of my friends...
who had to smile for each other...
while hiding their fear and anxiety.
The big day...
is almost here.
It's time to show our thoughts through our actions.
On behalf of our leader who couldn't join us here today,
I will deliver his message to all of you.
"The pain and anger you've felt for Joseon as a colony..."
"will be a stepping stone to change this country's reality."
"The tears and blood you've shed..."
"will be a foundation for this country's future."
"The power that drives you to take action until the very end..."
"derives from the love you have for this country, Joseon."
"It is for our parents, brothers,"
"children,"
"precious friends, lovers,"
"and all of you who are in this together."
"We are doing this out of love and compassion for the country..."
"that our loved ones will be living in."
The fighting spirit and anger flame up easily,
but they also easily die out when faced with reality.
Idealism and passion are noble, but they also fade very easily.
However, the desire for my loved ones to be happy...
can never change.
I wish for a world where our kids don't have to starve.
A world where they can smile and run around freely.
A world where there is no persecution and discrimination.
My Joseon Youth Alliance friends, let us never give up.
"Let us greet the day when Joseon gets liberated!"
- Let us greet that day! - Let us greet that day!
- We can do it! - We can do it!
- Let us greet that day! - That's right.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
- Please give me more. - Here you go.
- Here. Enjoy. - My gosh.
Thank you.
Everyone, listen up.
Don't just fill yourselves with alcohol.
Make sure you eat some food.
You might get sick tomorrow and ruin everything.
She's right.
- Don't get too drunk. - Okay.
Now that everyone's here together,
let's take turns and talk about...
what we'd like to do once our country gets liberated.
To be honest,
I haven't planned anything grand.
I just want to retrieve my stolen rice paddy...
and live peacefully in the countryside with my mother.
That's all.
My son wants to become a police officer.
My dream is to see him become a police officer of Joseon, not Japan.
- That's great. - Applause.
My goal is to meet...
my first love and start dating her.
Wait a minute.
We should hear what Su Hyeon has in mind.
Me?
Yes. What would you like to do once Joseon gets liberated?
I don't know.
I haven't thought about it much.
But where's Mr. Jo?
His wife is giving birth today.
My goodness. I guess it's his way of showing patriotism.
But what should we do?
No one knows the way as well as Mr. Jo.
We'll have to find someone else to guide the way.
We can't ask him to come...
when his baby is just born.
I'm sorry for being late.
I heard your wife is giving birth. How did you get here?
She safely delivered our baby a while ago.
- It's a girl. She's beautiful. - It's a girl.
Look at him. He must've run all the way here to boast.
Now that I have a child,
I really couldn't stay still and do nothing.
I should help this country get liberated as soon as possible...
for the sake of my child.
I'll prescribe some medicinal herbs for your wife.
You should go to my cousin's pharmacy.
He'll give you what you need if you tell him that I sent you.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Here.
Why the long face?
But then again, you always had that face before an important day.
I think about this every time before a mission.
"How many of those men out there..."
"will survive in the end?"
It hurts to say this,
but sacrifice is inevitable.
I'm always responsible for putting them in danger.
I make those naive people...
hold guns in their hands.
They even sacrifice their lives at times.
I wonder what I'm doing.
I sometimes hate who I am.
What are you talking about?
If it wasn't for you, Joseon Youth Alliance wouldn't even exist.
This time,
even you could be in grave danger.
Heo Young Min set up a trap because of me.
He's obsessed with finding the leader.
You're probably on the top of his list of suspects.
So if anything happens,
take Su Hyeon and go to Manchuria.
I understand what you're worried about.
But right now, you're at Carpe Diem.
Just enjoy this moment.
Can't you hear the music?
Oh, right.
What about you?
What do you want to do...
once Joseon gets liberated?
I don't know.
Shall we go fishing?
Then what if...
you were born again after Joseon got liberated?
What would you like to be?
I just wanted to get some air.
Then come inside after you get some air.
It's okay.
You don't need to avoid me anymore.
I've settled my feelings now.
If I were Mae Hyang, the best kisaeng of Myeongwolgwan,
I would've given it a shot.
But I can't risk our country's independence.
But in our next life,
if we get to be born in Joseon again after it gets liberated,
promise me...
that you'll think of me as a woman.
Don't hesitate.
Don't reject me completely.
Don't lie.
Don't endure pain all by yourself.
I want you to be honest...
and tell me everything.
Promise me that you'll do everything you couldn't do in this life.
Why do you keep talking about the next life?
Hurry up and promise me.
Then I want you to promise me something.
Make sure you come back alive.
It's an order.
(Chicago Typewriter)
Shall I start the morning of a successful mania?
If you're reminded of something you have to do,
do it now.
If I were to be born in Joseon after it gets liberated,
I wish I'll be with you guys again.
He's not a nice ghost.
He's going to perish soon?
Seol is going to die because of you.
Where is she, you jerk?
What are you doing?
Let go of me!