(noonaspoiler.site)
You're back, Ms. Hong.
Pyo Jaehyun.
I told you to do nothing.
INCOMING CALL
KYOJIN
Jang Kyojin?
EPISODE 13
Kyojin, I made your favorite,
doraji-jeonggwa.
I have somewhere to be.
Where to? What's happened?
I think Taera found Sujeong.
I need to confirm it's her.
Don't go, Kyojin. It's dangerous.
All the more reason to go.
I can't leave Taera alone.
Taera?
Yes, Haesoo.
I can't reach Taera.
She's disappeared.
Microchip insertion isn't safe to do yet.
Let's halt Project Eraser for now,
Sujeong.
Go on.
It's too dangerous, Chairman.
You know her life will be at risk
if we insert the microchip.
She could have seizures,
and her memory distortion will get worse...
We'll give her meds.
That issue's unconfirmed.
Its effects vary.
Her brain could explode
like it did with Red...
I know, I know!
Even if it's just for a while,
I want to be happy with Taera,
like we were before.
Please... Please reconsider...
I can't keep living in this hell.
Let's erase Taera's memory.
We're connected. Begin.
DELETE MEMORIES?
YES, NO
Don't worry, Taera.
Everything will return
to its rightful place.
Let's go back to our happy days.
Trust me.
DELETE MEMORIES?
YES, NO
Taera!
What did you want with him?
None of your business.
What's going on?
I need to know to help you.
Help me with what?
Didn't you just threaten me
with divorce action?
I did it to buy time!
If we get divorced,
it'll really be over between us, no?
You'll never see me again, will you?
I'm not asking you to live with me.
I am ashamed, you know.
I know how cowardly and despicable I am.
But I'm worried sick about you.
I'm so worried you might get hurt
that it's affecting everything I do.
Can I…
at least for once…
be someone you need?
I'm dying here.
The least you can do is resent me!
I think Jaehyun…
did something to Taera.
Help me.
Who said I'd do this interview?
I've no interest in publicly endorsing
your campaign.
Thanks to me, Kumjo Group's stock
increased severalfold, no?
You'll be well received
at the shareholders' meeting.
Or do you not like that?
Out of anyone at Hatch,
the spotlight's on you.
The board is considering making you CEO.
Of course, I've agreed to it too.
Didn't you mock me
for how unqualified I was?
Hey, I don't want to be CEO.
Even if you hand it to me, I'll pass.
Why are you both so on edge?
We're friends, aren't we?
If you're so displeased with me,
off with my head already.
Except,
you better be prepared
to lose everything you have.
Is that what you want?
Kyojin is still looking for Sujeong.
Did you know that?
Say what we did gets exposed.
Then we're all screwed, for real.
I won't ask for your friendship.
I just want us to be accomplices.
A perfect partnership.
Take your pick.
Either we all die together
or we all survive together.
Currently, Hatch has been
conducting smart patch clinical trials
on critically ill patients.
Kumjo Group and Hatch
have a cordial business relationship.
The research I've conducted at Hatch
will be utilized by Kumjo Group's
Brain Sciences Research Lab.
My friends and I founded Hatch on passion,
so seeing it succeed truly moves my heart.
I'm happy and relieved
to be able to focus on the election.
SMART PATCH "CLOVER" LAUNCH
HATCH, VALUE HIKES
TO GLOBAL TOP 3!
POPULAR SEARCH TERMS
1. HATCH 2. SMART PATCH
KOO SUNGCHAN, CEO
Yes, Mr. CEO.
What'd you say?
Pardon, Mr. CEO?
Wh... What did you just call me?
Mr. CEO, of course, sir.
So, I... I'm...
The CE... CEO. Yes, that's me!
I am Hatch's CEO, Koo Sungchan! Me…
Haven't seen Taera much lately.
She not campaigning with you?
Election's coming up, no?
I haven't seen her in a while either.
Or Jiu.
Jiu's on a trip and Taera is unwell.
You know my wife's been having
memory problems. It's gotten worse again.
How could it get worse?
She's never remembered her past, no?
Perhaps it's the stress, but she's having
short-term memory issues.
She's in treatment,
so she'll get well soon.
I don't believe it. She was fine.
Why would she be sick now?
Jaehyun must have done something to her.
I'll go ask him myself.
Wait...
We haven't even located her yet.
If we mess with Jaehyun rashly,
Taera's safety may be compromised.
Then what do we do?
You want me to just sit back and wait?
I'll look into it.
Oh, right.
Just pretend you know nothing
for now, okay?
Go ahead.
- What's this?
- You can't go in, ma'am.
- Move.
- You're prohibited from entering, Ms. Ko.
You feel all right?
What happened?
You're here too, Dr. Kang.
You fell and hurt your head
at your sister's boutique.
Don't you remember?
I fell?
Oh, I remember.
How long was I out?
Quite a long time.
And?
Remember anything else?
No.
Nothing after the incident
at Yura's boutique.
You can take your time.
Don't stress over it.
I'm so relieved you're awake, Taera.
- Where's Jiu?
- She's on a trip.
She'll be back soon.
Wow, we're home!
Aren't you happy to be home, Uncle?
Yeah.
Shall we go home, Jiu?
Let's go, Uncle.
Mommy!
- Jiu, you're home.
- I'm home.
You don't know how much I missed you.
Didn't you miss me, Mommy?
Of course I missed you!
- Daddy, Jiu's home!
- Yes, my darling.
You've gotten prettier.
Daddy missed you so much.
Who did you go with? Auntie Yura?
Auntie?
Auntie Yura is dead.
What is she talking about?
I'll explain.
Why don't we go unpack first?
Ms. Yoo, could you help Jiu unpack?
Go on, Jiu.
Honey. W... Why? When?
I don't remember anything at all.
Yura committed suicide.
Suicide?
No way. She was such a cheerful person.
Tell me it's not true.
It's all right, Taera.
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you everything that happened…
to you.
You were traumatized by Yura's death.
Dr. Kang thinks your brain suppressed
those memories
as a protective mechanism.
I can't believe it.
It'll be hard to accept.
I'll be here if you need.
Don't suffer alone.
You can always lean on me.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
Dr. Kang earnestly requested
that you don't skip your medication.
Mommy!
I want to sleep here tonight.
I cried every night
because I wanted to sleep next to you.
MR. JO
You had to leave home
for Mommy's sake. Mommy's sorry.
One moment.
What of No. 105?
I'm talking to him now.
Pyo Jaehyun!
I'm going to kill you.
Don't you dare do anything to my sis...
How dare you, traitor.
We have a healthy sample for a change.
Take him to room six.
Yes, sir.
Bring him up. Quietly.
YBC NEWS
Is the election a joke to you, Mr. Pyo?
Candidate Pyo.
You acted like you'd resign immediately,
what with your devoted husband act.
But now that Hatch is on the rise,
you wag your tail back here
to take advantage of this favorable
atmosphere?
Even community leader elections
aren't so nonsensical!
Withdraw immediately!
Please don't make rash remarks
about Hatch.
Whether I become president or not,
I'm certain Hatch
will make this country flourish.
Please refrain from speaking
against national interest.
L... Look at this!
This is a clear violation
of the election law.
He dared show up at the Hatch presentation
to act like its owner.
A presidential candidate
can't be the largest shareholder
of a conglomerate company!
This is clearly a political collusion!
So what is it you wish to say?
Set up a blind trust
for your Hatch shares,
and draw the line with Hatch!
If you can't do that,
just give up on your candidacy!
You're being way too greedy,
Candidate Pyo!
You clearly haven't taken much interest
in me lately.
What did you say?
The shares my family and I own
are already taken care of.
I've yielded some to my employees
as a partial transfer.
The rest are up for sale to the public.
- Up for sale?
- Yes.
I wanted to share Hatch's success
with the people.
My fellow Koreans,
I, Pyo Jaehyun,
will take you to the future.
5 DAYS TO ELECTION DAY
Mommy!
Wow, Jiu. You look so pretty today.
We haven't been to a party in so long.
Let me introduce to you all:
this is my beloved wife, Hong Taera.
Been a while since I felt so stoked.
Don't you agree?
I'm getting wasted as hell today.
Shall we have a drink, President Pyo?
You're overdoing it again.
You're in the public's favor
for this election. Come on, admit it.
What? Am I the only one who thinks so?
What does our first lady think?
Your assessment sounds uplifting.
Right?
What'd I say, dude?
Hey, behave yourself.
You're the CEO of Hatch now.
- We have many eyes watching.
- Damn.
Being CEO sure is a pain in the ass.
By the way, where did Haesoo go?
I'll go bring Haesoo.
You're filthy rich,
practically conglomerate royalty.
Just give her the alimony
and call it quits.
Isn't it uncomfortable living
under one roof?
Hi, Leo.
Go play with Jiu.
Jiu!
What're you doing here alone?
Everyone's having a drink.
Taera, are you okay?
What do you mean? Of course I'm okay.
Such a great day. I'm so happy.
I couldn't be happier.
You're happy?
How can you be happy right now?
You forget all we talked about?
Haesoo.
Jaehyun did something to you. Didn't he?
What're you two talking about?
Oh, Haesoo just said something strange.
What? She say I did something bad to you?
Ms. Hong.
Could you select some photos
for the press release?
Sure.
Come along soon.
Shall we?
Did you hypnotize her or something?
What happened?
She can't remember anything from before.
What should she remember?
That she's a killer?
Or that you two plotted
to take revenge against me?
What?
Did you think I wouldn't know?
You dared to work with Taera
and pretend to help me?
Uhm died needlessly because of you.
His death is on you.
You've made a habit
of killing people you don't need.
So?
You going to kill Taera too?
Kill Taera?
I'm trying to save her from herself.
Would she be happy
if she knew the uncomfortable truth?
You should know.
You lived in misery for 15 years.
Pyo Jaehyun...
Taera's forgotten it all.
She knows none of that now.
So forget about tormenting her
by bringing up the past.
Right.
Judging by your friendly texts with Taera,
it seems you've forgiven her, no?
Who…
Who the hell are you?
Me?
I'm Jang Kummo's victim, just like you.
Which is why
I won't stop your revenge against him.
However, don't even think
about getting close to my wife.
Am I clear?
It's been so long
since we've heard laughter here.
It's time you forgot about the past.
Dojin must've been pretty sick of you
if he chose to leave you.
Son of a bitch.
What about this photo?
I think it's great.
Let's go with this one.
Yes, ma'am.
Yeah.
Kyojin!
Taera.
Goodness.
You look so healthy.
You haven't changed in seven years.
You okay?
I was so worried.
I couldn't reach you since that day.
That day?
We were supposed to meet at Dr. Yang's...
Don't you remember?
What are you talking about?
I think you're mistaken about something.
- Taera, that day...
- Kyojin, you came.
You okay, honey?
You went out of your way today.
I'm okay.
You look much better
than what Jaehyun said.
It's good to see you.
- Taera.
- Kyojin.
Don't push it.
You barely managed to revive yourself.
- What's so funny?
- The people earlier…
Is this what you wanted?
Dojin joined forces with Jaehyun
to take over Kumjo.
You know better than anyone
what kind of man Jaehyun he is!
What?
You want to criticize me too?
Fine. Mock me and say it served me right.
Call me an imbecile.
Attend the shareholders' meeting.
Then announce that
you're yielding your shares to me.
Have you gone mad?
Your mother stole them from me,
but Kumjo's chairman seat
is for Dojin's to take!
Do you really want me to destroy Kumjo?
See you on the day.
You think I'm the only one
who's done anything wrong?
Chairman.
UHM SANGBAE
Uhm, you traitor son of a bitch.
You're mocking me to the end.
I envy her.
What?
I envy Jiu.
Her parents are really close too.
But you always fight with Dad.
You're getting a divorce too.
All my friends at kindergarten
know about it.
Mom and Dad love you so much, Leo.
That will never change.
No, I want you to love Dad.
I don't want you to get divorced! Geez.
Leo! Jang Leo!
I take pretty good pictures, right?
Thank you
for taking such good pictures of me.
Who's this?
Uncle Pilseung, of course.
Uncle Pilseung?
Mommy, you really were sick, huh?
You even forgot Uncle Glued-to-me.
What're you two on about?
Mommy doesn't recognize
Uncle Pilseung, Daddy.
Oh, he was your bodyguard,
and Jiu took a liking to him too.
Jiu, I hear dessert is chocolate cake.
Mommy, bye!
Don't have too much of it.
He was my bodyguard?
You didn't really like him.
He was with us for a while,
but he quit shortly after.
Really?
He's no one of importance.
That aside, what did Kyojin tell you?
Oh, that he was worried about me.
Apparently we promised to meet,
but he couldn't reach me.
We were never that close.
It was a bit strange.
He was unconscious for seven years.
It must be tough for him to readjust.
Just bear with him
when he makes odd remarks.
But we won't be seeing him often anyway.
I hope he gets better soon.
If you're tired, you can go rest.
I'll wrap it up over here.
Shall I? Thank you.
Take your medication and get some sleep.
What should I do, Taera?
I don't know what to do.
How do I save you?
Dojin?
Do you have something to say?
Haesoo's very worried about you.
She hopes you'll regain your memory soon.
Jaehyun is taking good care of me,
so tell her she needn't worry.
Dr. Yang Sejin resigned? So suddenly?
She didn't say where she was going?
We wouldn't know.
She resigned due to personal reasons.
Ms. Eun, I need you
to find someone for me.
Find Dr. Yang Sejin of Hatch.
Jang Kyojin is looking
for Dr. Yang, Mr. Pyo.
He went to Hatch
and even to Dr. Yang's house.
I should've taken care of her sooner.
Keep an eye on him
so that he doesn't cause any trouble.
Did you check? Are you sure
she has a chip implanted in her?
I checked with the reader.
Jaehyun wiped her memories.
I'm sure of it.
Is that even possible?
My brother used to conduct
research on memory.
He implanted a chip
in a traumatized patient's brain
and erased a part of their memory.
Well, we stopped the clinical trials
due to severe side effects.
Was Jaehyun on the research team too?
Only Kyojin and Sujeong were involved
in that research.
But how could Jaehyun erase
Taera's memories without Sujeong?
He probably had help from Dr. Yang.
I think Dr. Yang and Jaehyun
have a special relationship.
It was Jaehyun
who brought Dr. Yang to Hatch.
They're the ones who concocted
the narrative about Red's death as well.
Dojin.
What if, by some extraordinary chance,
Dr. Yang is Sujeong?
NATIONAL ID
YANG SEJIN
Isn't that Dr. Yang Sejin?
Why does Jaehyun have this?
Isn't it odd that these are hidden here?
I found out Pyo Jaehyun
had hidden Dr. Yang's ID.
What if Yang Sejin is a fake identity?
If her face has been altered,
we wouldn't be able to recognize her.
I doubt it.
Jaehyun is more than capable
of doing such a thing.
Anything new from my wife's phone?
I'm constantly checking,
but there's nothing new.
Don't let her out of your sight.
Make sure no one comes near her.
Especially keep her away
from Jang Dojin and Ko Haesoo.
Got it?
Yes, Mr. Pyo.
No. 50, who assassinated
President Ko Taesun,
is Pyo Jaehyun's wife, Hong Taera.
Mr. Uhm.
I guess you did have
a sliver of conscience left in you.
Will you really be okay with that?
I really mean it.
I'll support you right by your side
until the election.
You want my support, no?
So much so that I feel guilty.
I sold off my Hatch shares,
and you've set up your blind trust.
When I asked Mr. Oh about it,
he didn't know what I meant.
Who did you entrust your shares to?
I have a friend who's managing it.
I couldn't tell you in advance
because you were ill.
I took care of it,
so you don't need to worry.
You must trust that person a lot.
Who could it be?
There's someone who will never betray me.
You're not upset because I didn't ask
for your consent, right?
I'm sure you took care of it well.
You're going to Haesoo's station
for the radio interview, right?
Yes.
I looked through
the materials you gave me.
If the implanted chip has already
attached itself to a cranial nerve,
it can't be removed.
The chip was implanted recently,
so there must be hope.
Please find a way
with all the data you have.
You know the odds are slim.
There hasn't been a successful case yet.
I've asked for cooperation
from neuroscientists abroad.
She's very important to me.
You must save her, Professor.
INCOMING CALL
MOTHER
This number is unavailable.
Please leave a message...
It's time, ma'am.
SHAREHOLDERS' MEETING
With Hatch's successful presentation,
Mr. Jang Dojin's
capabilities have been proven.
Also, as he is experienced in this field,
it's only right that
he takes over the neuroscience project.
KUMJO GROUP
Mr. Jang Dojin
sold Kumjo Pharmaceuticals for a song,
which also means that
he lacks business insight.
If he thought about
the future value of neuroscience,
he would've never merged
the two companies.
Kyojin would've never made such a choice.
He was bedridden for seven years.
Business insight?
He probably doesn't even know
what's going on in our company.
Sir!
Chairman.
- How...
- Oh, no.
Sit down.
I'm sure some of you are glad
that I came back alive.
And some of you
probably wished that I was dead.
And someone even acted on that wish.
But that's what gave me the strength
to stand here again,
so perhaps I should be thanking them.
What's happening?
That's a crime.
I can't believe it.
Mother, is this all true?
If this actually happened,
then the stock waiver is invalid.
That's... That's...
This is all my fault,
so there's no one else to blame.
There won't be any more dirty fights
for money at Kumjo.
It's just too embarrassing
to see us fight amongst family.
I, Jang Kummo,
will return as the chairman
and bring peace and order to the family.
So there is need to worry. Understood?
Yes, sir.
Give me a chance to explain.
And CEO Jang Dojin, you'll be
the vice chairman starting today.
He will work by my side,
so I can teach him.
So make sure you treat him well.
Yes, sir!
Reporter Jung.
Go to the KDP campaign office right now.
Mr. Park, you and I
will cover Candidate Pyo's campaign.
Mr. Pyo's next schedule
is a live radio show, so...
I'll cover Pyo, Mr. Song.
I'll report on Candidate Pyo Jaehyun.
But why?
I'm sincerely grateful to everyone
who's shown support
for my husband, Candidate Pyo.
He's always been a great husband
and an amazing father.
That is why I support and trust him
in this decision.
I'll do my best until the end. Thank you.
I'm Ko Haesoo from YBC.
I'm currently at the station
where candidate No. 7, Pyo's live
radio interview is taking place.
The presidential election is
in three days.
The candidate's wife, Hong Taera,
is actively campaigning with him,
drawing many people's attention.
Pyo Jaehyun! Pyo Jaehyun! Pyo Jaehyun!
Pyo Jaehyun! Pyo Jaehyun!
Ms. Hong. May I interview you?
You can't do this
without an appointment, Ms. Ko.
I'm sorry, but we have to run
to our next appointment.
This is the question your supporters
want to know the most.
Please spare us some time.
Will you really refuse?
It'll only take a minute.
Let's begin, Ms. Ko. What's the question?
Read the questionnaire first.
Taera, you know who this is, don't you?
Who on earth is she?
The real killer
of the late President Ko Taesun.
This is the assassin who killed my father.
The woman in this photo.
The suspect who assassinated
the former President Ko.
Is this you, Ms. Hong?
What is this?
Your memory that Jaehyun erased.
What on earth
are you talking about, Haesoo?
Jaehyun implanted a chip in you
to erase your memory
because you found out the truth about him.
He's the one who killed Yura.
You saw him on the night
of the thunderstorm.
He staged Yura's death as a suicide.
Stop helping Jaehyun.
How much more do you want to regret?
Stop it, Haesoo.
I'm quite happy right now.
I'm warning you.
Don't cross the line again.
If you talk that way about Jaehyun
one more time, we will never speak again.
Taera.
You have to believe me.
Stay away from Jaehyun.
There's no time!
I can't watch you become miserable.
No, Taera. Jaehyun gave that to you?
Don't take the pill.
Don't do anything he tells you to do!
Taera! Please believe me!
Are you okay, honey?
Let's go.
Taera, hold on!
Taera!
Where were you?
Didn't you know how important
today's shareholders' meeting was?
Kummo became the chairman again.
Kumjo Group is in their hands!
I'm sorry.
I had something important to do.
What is more important than Kumjo?
It's about Taera's chip removal surgery.
I found a doctor.
This isn't the time to cling on
to something so lousy!
Mother.
I'm not interested in taking over Kumjo.
What are you talking about?
I had bad blood with Dojin
because he refused to admit his fault.
It's not because I wanted to lead Kumjo.
I don't want to risk my life
to take over that blood-stained Kumjo.
How could you be so irresponsible?
Do you know what I sacrificed
to make sure you inherit Kumjo?
Who do you think I protected Kumjo for?
Don't you get it?
You're just like Father.
Or maybe even worse.
What?
Do you think I don't know?
Father bought me a bike
on my 13th birthday.
You broke it on purpose.
You hated Dojin for riding my bike,
so you wanted Father
to hate Dojin as well.
If you really care about me,
you should let go
of your ambition for Kumjo.
Stop hiding behind Buddha
and smiling like a saint.
Let go of your ambitions first!
None of us
deserve to have Kumjo.
Hong Taera!
Is it because of that wench?
She doesn't even remember you anymore.
Why are you doing this for her?
Don't tell me…
you have feelings for Hong Taera.
What are you talking about?
I pity her. I have to help her somehow!
Don't get the wrong idea.
How... How could you do this to me?
How... How could you?
30 YEARS AGO
How dare you ride my son's bike first?
You little bastard.
Kyojin.
You only deserve perfection.
I will make sure that happens.
Ultimately, Kumjo Group will be yours.
Do you think your father
will give it to Kyojin? Huh?
But what's with the long face?
You look like you ate shit. Huh?
You're such a buzzkill.
Besides, if I were you,
I would've gotten divorced already
and gotten married three more times.
This is between us, but frankly...
This is just between us.
What's so great about Haesoo?
She's mean as hell.
Daughter of the president, my foot.
That was ages ago.
You punk.
If I think about it,
you're such a pushover.
Shit.
Watch your mouth.
That woman doesn't deserve mockery
from your filthy mouth.
And she doesn't deserve to be miserable
because of a moron like me.
He must be out of his mind.
Does he want to face death
like his brother?
You worked so hard today.
You're the one who worked hard today.
You have to become the president
so that our efforts aren't in vain, okay?
Okay.
You need to take your medicine.
Right.
X
SAMPLE 2 MISSING
Oh, man.
Something came up at the camp.
I have to go.
Don't wait up for me, okay?
Even if it's just for a while,
I want to be happy with Taera,
like we were before.
Let's erase Taera's memory.
Your real name is Park Sujeong.
You were tricked by Jaehyun
just like I was.
You have to stop him.
Please help me.
Park Sujeong?
We're connected. Begin.
DELETE MEMORIES?
YES, NO
Dr. Yang?
DELETE MEMORIES?
YES, NO
Wait, what just happened?
Pyo Jaehyun.
Are you planning to make Taera like me?
I'm going to tell Kyojin everything.
I'm going to tell him
all about what you've done!
So you finally remembered?
- Take her to room two.
- Yes, sir.
Leave Taera alone!
Leave her alone!
DELETING MEMORIES
No.
Taera.
Let's go back home.
Check her vitals
and get ready to move her.
Yes, sir.
Where's No. 105?
We have a healthy sample for a change.
Take him to room six.
Room six?
I need to find his secret lab.
Dr. Yang and Hajun are there.
Have you not been keeping watch?
Check the security footage
and find her escape route.
Get her back before someone finds out.
Got it?
PAWNSHOP
Are you becoming senile?
I guess you are really busy.
You're hearing this news so late.
Returning as the chairman?
Did you forget about the cards
I have against you?
Perhaps I have been a decent man,
but I received a gift.
Your wife is something else.
No. 50, who assassinated
President Ko Taesun,
is Pyo Jaehyun's wife, Hong Taera.
Pyo Jaehyun, you're really something.
What prompted you
to make an assassin your wife?
Oh, my, how terrifying.
I could never do it.
I concede defeat, you punk.
Did you think Mr. Uhm was your man?
Don't fool yourself.
Do you know how hard it is
to win someone's heart?
You really think you have
what it takes be president?
Thanks to Mr. Uhm,
I got my position back.
I found him a nice burial ground.
Don't ever lay your hands on Kumjo again.
You and I are in the same boat.
Whether we're floating or sinking,
we're in this together.
You understand?
Mr. Jang Dojin.
I think Haesoo is up to something.
What do you mean?
She submitted her resignation.
Resignation?
Hello? Haesoo.
- Hey.
-Where are you?
Let's meet. I'll go to you.
I have nothing to say.
Wait. We should meet.
Let's talk in person.
Where are you right now?
I've given it some thought,
and I realized I've been cowardly.
What right did I have to criticize you
when I couldn't even sacrifice
my own life?
I can't forgive myself
for being incapable of hurting your father
only because I felt sorry for you
and I didn't want to see you fall apart.
My parents…
must be very disappointed in me.
You're not thinking
of doing anything weird, are you?
I'm going to end it.
Take good care of Leo.
That's all I ask of you.
What are you trying to end?
No, don't do anything.
Wait until I get there, okay?
Do you understand, Haesoo? He... Hello?
This number is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Shit.
You don't have to push yourself too hard.
You said they'll be
on your transition team.
I can't miss such an important meeting.
How should I repay you for all this work?
President Pyo Jaehyun.
That title is all I need.
I promise I'll make you the first lady.
Oh, right.
I packed a bottle of wine as a gift.
Hold on.
Take your time.
You still haven't found her?
Dr. Yang, that bitch.
Where the hell is she hiding?
Die, Pyo Jaehyun.
- No!
- Oh!
Taera?
No.
Taera!
No! Taera! No, Taera! Taera!
I'll show you what happens,
if you take Taera away from me.
Thought I followed Dr. Yang here,
but it's Sujeong.
Watch your mouth,
unless you want to die here.
You're under arrest
for embezzlement and breach of trust.
I found Jaehyun's co-conspirator.
I'm staking my life
to bring Kumjo down from this day forward.
I'm in a bad mood today.
Do your best to hang in there.
You're going to blow this place up?
Along with Jang Kyojin…
Forever.