The Long Ballad
Episode 16
The doctor said
he was dying of starvation.
I'm afraid he won't wake up again.
Sixth sister is gone.
His mother is dead.
He has no attachment to this world.
I want to be with him alone.
Let's go.
Sixth sister
Uncle.
I just found a letter
from Sixth uncle to the embroidery bureau.
But what's the use of just a letter?
He's gone.
You go out first.
Don't let anyone in.
Will Sixth brother wake up
if I stay here?
Xiuqu,
take care.
I'm going to go south today.
Xiuqu.
Yanzhou.
How can you fall asleep reading?
Isn't your boat...
What boat?
I'm fine.
I had a nightmare.
I dreamt
I would never see you again.
I thought you dreamed of marrying me
and having a happy life.
Happy and bitter.
Yanzhou,
I want to be with you.
I want to marry you.
Okay.
Then we will be together forever.
The end
People say
that a daughter can't be willful
when she's married.
But you're different.
As long as you have me,
you can do whatever you want.
In the next life,
I want to be your daughter.
You're such a silly child.
Now I'm leaving you to her.
You can finally become my bride.
Yanzhou,
after we get married,
we'll find a place
with a beautiful scenery
and plant flowers and pick oranges.
No one can ever
separate us.
I'm sorry, Xiuquan.
I'm going to break my promise.
I can't keep you.
You should wake up.
What do you mean, Yanzhou?
Yanzhou,
it's not a dream.
We're getting married soon.
If I keep keeping you,
you can't wake up.
I want...
I want to be with you.
Do you remember that tune?
It's me.
I'll be with you forever.
Yanzhou,
you don't even know.
I regretted it so much that day.
I shouldn't have said those words.
I shouldn't have let you go, Yanzhou.
I know.
The words you said to me
were all lies.
Xiaoqi,
I don't blame you.
No matter what,
I hope you can live well
and live your life
as you want.
Live your life with no fear.
I said that
doesn't mean we forget each other.
I just want to tell you
that we're the most beautiful
and the most beautiful couple in our lives.
We should spend our whole lives together.
But in our lives,
we shouldn't be the only one.
Xiaoqi,
there are many dreams
and dreams waiting for you to fulfill.
I can't
put you in this dream.
No.
Yanzhou,
I don't want you to go.
As long as you still have me in your heart,
I'll always be by your side.
I love you.
Xiaoqi,
goodbye.
Goodbye,
Yanzhou.
I wish you happiness
and happiness.
I can only let go
when I'm happy.
Yanzhou.
Master,
Madam
and Zhi Le
have tried their best
to make me live
for them
or for you and your mother.
I'm sorry
for what I did.
For you and your mother,
for myself,
I'll live well
and cheer up.
Yanzhou,
Master.
You seem to be so serious.
I didn't disturb you.
The orange juice is good recently.
You have worked hard.
Are you feeling better?
I can't think about those things when I'm busy.
I'm going to the city to search for shops.
You follow me to the desert to learn.
And have a walk.
Master, I...
Get ready.
I'll wait for you downstairs.
Okay.
Master,
you'll take me to the city every year to search for shops.
I don't know how long you can stay this time.
You can go and pack up some of my new clothes.
Oh, and put on some expensive jewelry.
I have to make sure you look good.
And bring some medicine to keep you hydrated.
After he comes to the city,
he'll drink and drink.
He'll feel sick then.
Okay.
Okay. Is this good?
Yes.
Let's go.
Don't keep him waiting.
Okay.
Master, I'm ready.
We can go.
Where's Master?
Madam,
Master told me to tell you to take Third Madam to the city.
She's already gone.
I see.
Yes.
Madam, this...
It's time to take Xiuju out to see the world.
After all, Xiuju is still young.
It's boring to stay in the countryside.
I should be happy.
This...
Xiuju has finally caught Master's heart.
I have hope.
Right?
Yes.
Madam, you're right.
Sir!
Here comes the water!
Perfume and wine!
Miss, sir.
I'm a
wine-drinker from the city of Falanxi.
Perfume and wine
are the scent of the soul.
Each one has its own unique
personality and smell.
This one has a light orange scent
and a clear and lively scent.
The middle one has a sweet scent.
The tail one has a strong fragrance
and the front one has a strong scent.
It smells sweet.
It's like walking in the rain.
There are flowers all around.
It seems that you like perfume.
I'll take all of these.
Okay.
Where is the boss?
Get in the car.
Excuse me.
Sir, please slow down.
Madam is here.
Excuse me.
Hello.
The orange jam from the first round is really good.
Yes, I've never had such a delicious food.
Give it to my wife.
Isn't this my orange jam?
Take a look at this.
This is our store's commercial product.
Why is it being sold in such a high-end store?
I promised
to help you sell the orange jam to the whole country.
But you created this business.
You should be seen.
So
I'm sorry.
It seems that the small-scale production
is a big hit.
I remember it.
It's called the first round.
The label
can be a unique orange flower.
See some orange and Sichuan citizen
who have never seen such a beautiful flower like this.
This canned grape is for you.
Why is this not the grape taste?
Great.
So
You work in this store?
This is the first store we opened together.
The orange jam can be sold here in the future.
I'm sorry.
Master.
Yu Qing, I like you.
I'm willing to sacrifice for you.
Yu Li, I'm your shareholder.
This is also my investment.
So don't mention
the return of the family.
Come on, we're arriving.
Come on.
Why isn't anybody picking me up?
Didn't tell Second Madam I'm back today?
Second Madam said it.
Maybe she's asleep.
Unruly.
Let me show you our house in the city.
Boss.
Welcome.
Brother Shen, I've been waiting for you.
During your absence,
Miss Liu has done a lot of business for you.
Yes.
I'm very proud of Brother Shen
for having such a good wife.
Yes.
Where is she?
Here.
Welcome home, Master.
I happen to take this opportunity
to introduce my Third Madam to you.
Xiuqu.
Please take care of her.
Okay.
Brother Shen, I have something to discuss with you.
Let's talk in private.
Okay.
I'll be back soon.
Please.
Today is the first time Third Madam has shown her face.
I suggest
she should dance the opening dance today.
Okay.
Good.
I don't want to dance.
You don't want to dance or you don't know how to dance?
I forgot to introduce.
Our Third Madam is a country girl.
It's her first time in the city.
She's never seen anything like this.
Please take care of her.
Don't leave, Third Madam.
So many people are watching.
You should have been more careful.
You're in a good mood today.
Can you invite a beautiful girl
to dance with you?
I can't.
Imagine you're a cloud
and I'm the wind.
You're the wind.
I'm a cloud.
Where you blow,
I'll float in that direction.
Okay.
You're not here
It's raining and snowing
You don't care
The sea is covered with clouds
in your ears
The flowers fall into the sky
The snowfall is blue
and the clouds are blue
There is a bright moon this morning
I'm not here
for the dead
The trees are still here
The more the day goes by, the more people go away
I'm not used to
you still not here
I don't understand
how much time has changed
I shouldn't have said that
I'm still in the dream
hoping you'll come back
The trees are still here
The more the day goes by, the more people go away
I'm not used to
you still not here
I don't understand
how much time has changed
I shouldn't have said that
I'm still in the dream
hoping you'll come back
The End
I'll teach you
the last song
Master, I don't know how to dance
You dance very well
very beautiful
Just follow the feeling
I'll take you
Master, I'm sorry
I stepped on your foot
It doesn't matter if you step on the wrong foot
You have to jump bravely
You will be lost
and start over
Master
You're very sick
My body is not as good as it is now
But Mrs. Dai told me
You have a fever
I have to be careful
Forget about it
She is not you
I never thought you would be like her
Master
Master, President Chen is talking to you
I'll be right there
If you don't mind
You can go around and see
Okay
Why don't you want to compete with me?
You're just pretending
to be a pure white flower
and you're so shameless
Whatever you want
I can't tell you
You're so shameless
You only know how to seduce men
You've killed the sixth child
You want to harm master
You dare to say it again
I said
You only know how to seduce men
Who will seduce men?
How did you become Mrs. Dai?
You're not a woman
You know how to seduce Mrs. Dai
Yes
Everyone looks down on me
In order to make a living
I was a dancer for a few days
And I'm a low-ranking dancer
Do I have to be watched by all of you for a lifetime?
No one is born a low-ranking dancer
You're blind, aren't you?
What are you?
Do you know who I am?
You dare to kill me
What's wrong, Shen Yi?
You're looking at her
Do you know
to fight for this kind of mess?
You'd better shut up
Today is the day of my show
I invited all the guests
You're too low-ranking to be a woman
What did you say?
Say it again
What did I say?
You can ask the Governor Zhao
If there's nothing else
Goodbye
Okay
All these years
I've suffered a lot
Only Shen Yi
is willing to look at me
and protect me
Thank you
I'm sorry
I've met a man
who dares to be a good man like you
Am I wrong
to love him?
I want to hold him tight
He's a man of high status
He's never been an excuse
to fight for his love
He even doesn't know how to do it
This is the reason
why people really like you
Is your love
really that pure?
I love him
I have money, status
and conflicts with him
I love him
Do you have conflicts?
I, Liu Ruyan
will not allow myself
to be a woman
who has no dignity
and no money
I will not allow that
So
no one can be my master
I love you