You
Brother.
Brother came here today.
There must be something special, right?
Xiaoju.
How old is your child?
Two months.
Good, good, good.
You were still in the Shen family at that time.
This...
This is the child of me and Xiuqu.
Xiuqu and I are now husband and wife.
This child came here justly.
No matter who wants to hurt my child,
don't blame me.
Don't worry.
I won't hurt this child.
On the contrary,
you must give birth to him.
But he must be alive.
But he must be the child of me and Xiuqu.
I will go back to the Shen family
to claim that Xiuqu was in great difficulty.
This child is raised by me.
It's my father.
The family property of the Shen family
and the family business I have,
will be all his.
Brother.
I don't understand what you are talking about.
This is the child of me and Xiuqu.
Do you want to take it away?
No, not take.
I'm asking you.
To claim that this is the child of me and Xiuqu.
Your relationship can only exist in secret.
Master.
This is ridiculous.
Brother.
We have gone through all the hardships
to get out of the Shen family.
Do you want us to go back
and steal love for a lifetime?
I...
I have a reason.
I, Shen Yaning, have never begged anyone in my life.
But this time I want to beg you.
Please fulfill the crime of a man.
And the reputation of the whole family.
For the so-called reputation,
you have to lose your personality, right?
Even hurting my child
and making him the victim of the Fengjian family
is a crime.
I beg you.
Please.
You want to make him the victim of the Fengjian family, right?
Master.
We can't accept it.
Please go back.
I knew it would be like this.
But I had to come.
Today you just pretend I didn't come.
Take good care of Xiuqu.
I'm responsible for myself
One said it without surprise
One is too confident to make a promise
I cried for happiness from the beginning
Then I smiled to end it
The tears that flowed
Can make people learn to be mature
Time is breaking through the beautiful
And the cruel
Love is not a constant temperature
I cried for happiness from the beginning
Then I smiled to end it
The tears that flowed
Can make people learn to be mature
Sometimes I can say hello politely
From a friend's angle
What's wrong with brother today?
What he said is so strange.
I think he seems to be in a lot of trouble.
Could something happen to the Shen family?
I also feel a little weird.
You say
Could the master encounter some difficulties?
Otherwise he had already helped us before.
Why suddenly
Suddenly changed again?
The god of heaven is in the house.
Sixth Lord and Third Madam are not dead.
Come
Go to the god's house
Watch it well
I dare not
Who gave you the right?
Where is my brother?
I want to see my brother
This is what your brother means.
How could the master?
He just clearly
Stop talking nonsense.
Hurry up and take it back to the Shen family.
Tianzhou
Xiaojue
You let him go
Let him go
Xiaojue
Who gave you the right?
I caught the sixth and the lord without permission.
Didn't I already ask you?
But the result
Still rejected
I came back with a nose.
This is to be painted.
Don't think we don't know the big guy.
This thing wants to drag to the end.
Impossible
We have already told the lord and the third wife.
This is what the big guy means.
What
You
How dare you
In the name of my name
This makes me have a face in the future.
Face the six and Xiaoju
The face of the big guy alone
How can it be compared to the face of the whole Shen family?
The king's death cannot be broken.
The Shen family cannot be destroyed in our generation.
I have to force it.
Don't come to the death again.
If the big guy doesn't obey
Then the three wives in the belly
The evil seed that is in the mess
Can't stay
What do you say
Only like this
Can make the six and the third wife
Can't be done
The face of the big guy
And the reputation of the Shen family
Only to be protected
Where does this kid go?
Big guy, you choose yourself.
Face
Name
Family
I anybody
How many
I do jumping
Lock
Did you pick up
That line
Erfolg and fortune in heaven...
The Communist Party single
the Tzu Chi of six emperors
and be …
...given a great honor
to lastn
their great strength.
And be加油!
Don't make any trouble!
Why did he do that?
It's the master's order.
We can only obey him.
Mrs. Jiang,
this is the young master's clothes
that we have prepared.
Look.
How cute!
Master.
Sit down.
Master,
what happened?
Do you have any reason to do this?
Master.
Yanzhou and I
will try our best to help you.
It's my idea.
You're a young man.
The most important thing now is this child.
Don't expect me to save you.
He was tied up in the pond.
Mike and my daughter
are livingleg Bakunade.
Their drums sound like a bell
hitting a피 ty issue
is Mikey's partner.
New find,
a surely good one.
There are 4 sticks.
And Ma Peiutar's
terrible technique!
So the rest is a joke!
They started to make shit.
We was бытьon fun.
Hes's Theme
I'm feeling relieved.
Brother,
why did you do all this?
Please tell me the truth.
Brother,
say something.
do you want to know why?
I'm telling you now.
I have a bad habit of being
like a family member
and betraying my ancestors.
I'm sorry.
I've never said
that I would be the last one
to be in my hands.
Brother,
is this true?
My father used to hold my hand
and say that
he had once cast a spell
and if he wanted to live forever,
he had to marry a good son
or he would have no hope.
He wanted me to be a teacher.
Family interests are the most important thing in life.
So since I was a child,
I've been living in the fate of the Shen Family.
Family,
family name,
Brother has been suffering from these for a lifetime.
But Brother,
the child is innocent.
So I have to keep this child.
I'm willing to pay for it.
Madam.
Xiaojue.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
It's all my fault.
It's all my selfishness that has caused you harm.
Because I wanted to keep Master
and keep him from talking about his selfishness,
I dragged you
into the Shen Family.
I'm sorry, Xiaojue.
I caused you harm.
I'm sorry to you and Master.
It's all my fault.
Madam,
why did you say that?
Let's get up first.
Get up and talk.
Xiaojue,
have you been sleeping for 20 years?
I know
you're still young.
You can't be like me.
You'll be trapped in this big house for the rest of your life.
I'll take you away.
Come with me.
I'll take you out.
Master.
You can't leave now.
Listen to me.
Go.
No, you can't go.
Madam.
Are you okay?
Shen Yanqing,
I want to divorce you.
Nothing.
In these 20 years,
I've had a dream.
In the past,
I would take all the responsibility
and leave it to myself.
But now,
I'm not afraid of anything.
I've lived in vain
for the first half of my life.
You
know it all.
I know it all.
I'm sorry for you.
Shen Yanqing,
I want to ask you
if you really cared about me
for the past decades.
Even if
your love
and your affectionate eyes
are nothing but a joke,
I said I didn't care.
But do you know
I felt so sad
from the bottom of my heart?
I've been waiting for that for my whole life.
I want to ask you one more thing.
Do you know what I'm called?
I'm called
Shen Yanqing.
Do you know what I'm called?
In this family,
I'm the only one who doesn't have a name.
I'm called Madam.
That decent, virtuous,
kind and kind Madam.
Who am I?
Zhuang Hui.
You're in the Shen family.
You're the father of the Shen family.
And you met me.
You're the only one who doesn't have a name.
I'm Zhuang Hui.
Master,
you called me Zhuang Hui.
I'm not Madam.
Let's go, Zhuang Hui.
Leave the Shen family.
You're free.
Let's go.
If you have no intention,
I'll stop.
Rather than relying on someone else's love,
it's better to break apart and re-birth.
And re-birth another side of the world.
I've been trapped in this house all my life.
It's time to go out
and see the outside world.
Madam, take care of yourself.
Go.
Take care.