ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCALES, AND EVENTS ARE USED
IN AN ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS MANNER
AND NOT BASED ON HISTORICAL FACTS
I'm not the only one with these feelings.
I like Lord Yi-eon,
and he likes me as well.
I think it's unfair for you
to only blame me for that.
Why, I never…
What in the world did she say to me?
A girl the size of a field mouse,
wide-eyed like some rabbit…
What did she say to me?
I shouldn't only blame her.
My grandson is the biggest…
fool, idiot, moron out there.
Nice.
-Grandmother.
-Were you in the kitchen again?
I heard that you were here,
so I made some gwapyeon for you.
I won't fall for it!
You need to add more honey.
More starch, too.
Come inside.
Okay.
What were you doing?
She barged in,
so there was no time to signal to you.
-Hurry.
-Put it on him.
She just came out of nowhere.
Bring out some tea.
I hope the madam hits him
with the switch again.
I'll have a sturdy one ready.
How can anyone sleep
with all this mess around?
Why does your room look like this?
I told you time and time again
that orderly surroundings
lead to a refined fate.
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
You've been coming by a lot.
When are you going to get married?
-All of a sudden?
-That's right, punk.
You have a job and you make a living now.
Your bachelor life needs to end
so that this messy room
can house a set of lovebird bedding.
Well…
You told me to choose
between marriage and the state exams,
so I took the exam.
Lord Kim and Lord Park's grandsons
got married ages ago
and have produced
strapping great-grandchildren.
What exactly is your plan?
But their grandsons did not get
the highest marks on their state exams.
The Inspector General's daughter
is wise, fair-complexioned,
and quite composed.
She enjoys eating,
so she'll suit you well.
Grandmother.
It hasn't been that long
since the Crown Prince returned
and there are things
I must assist him with--
You have no such duties.
Your Highness.
Don't use me as an excuse.
In my opinion,
he's the most handsome crown
prince in this nation's history.
I seriously think
they chose him because of his looks.
True.
Then who is more handsome?
Our lord or His Highness?
Me.
Don't do things like that.
You? No. Me.
Me…
It's me. Me!
He's being
such a terrible grandson, Your Highness.
The only son in a string of
only sons for five generations
refusing to marry means
the family name will end with him.
His Highness most certainly said
that there isn't anything worth
giving up one's life for in this world.
I did say that.
Did he?
Then,
what are you going to do
about the life I sacrificed to raise you?
Right.
Men drag in all sorts of customs and
rules to make women sacrifice everything
and they get to cherish
their sense of dignity?
Why don't you give us
your input, Your Highness?
You're wrong.
Every single word you spoke is wrong.
-Your Highness.
-Saying that marriage is
like giving up your life
is an exaggeration.
It's an excuse typical Joseon men make.
With the support of a wife,
you could achieve even greater successes.
Women
make more sacrifices.
My thoughts exactly.
Please call me over
when you set up his blind dates.
I would like to meet them, as well.
Will you do that for us?
Until then, I'll do what I can to quell…
this kid's persistent obstinacy.
We have a whole grove
of ash trees outside.
The branches make great switches.
What a great idea.
Would you like some help?
Go away.
Wait…
Do you pluck the eggplant at the top?
Can I just pluck it?
Come now.
How dare you turn your back
on your crown prince?
We shall see how long you can hold out
without talking to me.
Will you only be satisfied if I call
the guards over and teach you a lesson?
You're too old
to play tricks like some snot-nosed child…
So stop throwing a tantrum.
If a young noblewoman
is willing to marry you,
you should gratefully welcome her.
If you do not get married,
then how will I ever get
to see a nephew or a niece?
Nephew and niece, my foot.
What nephew? What niece?
We make a pact to never get married,
and then he runs off to get hitched.
Traitor.
What a hopeless fool…
How are you going to survive
if you only listen to me?
What would you do without me?
I bet you'll live
5,000 years more than me.
You eat so many tasty
and precious things at the palace.
Anyhow, Yi-eon,
keep what I tell you in mind.
Understood?
Don't just blindly follow what I say.
See how the world lives
and learn to be flexible.
Rely on people other than me.
That's all I'm saying.
Anyhow, what's for dinner tonight?
Why would you look for dinner at my place?
You should eat at the palace.
But your food tastes so much better.
Wait a second. How about
you take this chance
to become my taster maid?
Since you have
the most discrimination palate
in all of Joseon.
How can I enter the palace as a maid?
Yes. What a pity…
You'd be perfect.
Why don't you help me
with the red beans first?
I made sure to empty my schedule today.
When are you going back? You should soon.
I won't until I finish
every dish you've made today.
Nothing's been made yet, Your Highness.
Everything that damn rabbit said
is right.
Grandmother?
All the young women and men
in the country have gathered
to find their partners on Dano.
Why are you in your room?
Grandmother, can you just…
Stop idling at home
and go find someone to marry, punk!
-Grandmother!
-No matchmakers. No marriage.
You can't just live your life
doing the things you like.
You can't live your life
just doing the things you want to do!
Grandmother!
This isn't ladylike!
Let's talk this out
like sophisticated people would do.
I'm the only one
without a granddaughter-in-law.
All other noblewomen
have granddaughter-in-laws
except me, punk!
I told you to give it up.
Not everyone is cut out for marriage.
Then,
are you cut out to be a good-for-nothing
staying home all the time?
He has the tendency
to just dig his own grave.
His tolerance for a beating will grow.
Everyone has a granddaughter-in-law
except me, punk!
Grandmother, do you think this is going
to make me suddenly want to get married?
Fine.
Let's just beat you up
until you come across a woman you like!
Wait, Grandmother!
Grandmother!
It's not like I can just
meet a woman I like
because I want to.
Then go and bring some widow if you must!
I won't care as long
as you like her. I won't!
Grandmother!
Who knew he would
really bring a divorced woman?
Kkot-dan.
Are you outside, Kkot-dan?
Yes, my lady.
Did you call for me?
Go and find out all you can
about that girl, Kim Jo-yi.
Kim Jo-yi?
You know…
She was in Yi-eon's room…
The one sweet as honey with him…
Yes.
Anyhow,
find out where she lives
and what she does for a living.
Trace every step
and leave no stone unturned.
-Do you understand?
-Yes, my lady.
Did I say too much?
Maybe I should've just kept quiet.
Why did I have to keep talking back?
No.
Marriage is still…
Marriage is…
Kim Jo-yi!
Why don't you know how to hold back?
-This is why--
-People call you an audacious brat.
Would you like
to have a cup of tea, cute lady?
Sure, adorable lad.
Here.
I want this one.
Okay, it was more expensive, anyhow.
-Then I want that one.
-No.
My goodness!
Give it to me.
Is there one that you like?
Seung-yul.
If you want, I could buy you everything
from here to there.
Look at you.
Forget it. People like us
have no use for jade hairpins.
Why not?
People may discriminate
against other people, but not hairpins.
How much is this?
Come on now.
This is for a nobleman's wife.
Why don't you look at the cheaper stuff?
How embarrassing!
I knew you'd get turned down.
Once I pass the exam,
I'll buy you a cartload
of these ornaments…
I'll be a granny by then.
With you wandering around markets,
it'll take a lifetime.
If I really pass the exam
and get you this hairpin,
will you marry me?
If you pass it as you say,
then I'll consider it.
I'm leaving, punk.
What are you going to do if I really pass?
You just wait, Kim Jo-yi.
Come on now.
I said, it's for a nobleman's wife.
Go after her.
What are you going to do?
What?
You and Lord Yi-eon.
What do you mean?
It's an unwritten law
that a nobleman cannot marry
a divorced woman even in his next life.
You know that remarriage
is legally prohibited
in Gyeongguk Daejeon.
I'm sure if Lord Yi-eon says
he would like to marry you,
his grandmother will have to wait her turn
as the scholars of this nation
rise up to oppose it.
People from across the land
will submit appeals
and the scholars will protest against it
in front of the palace.
Appeals and protests?
Yes.
Listen, Seung-yul.
Lord Yi-eon and I are just--
Which is why I mobilized all the knowledge
I had as a lawyer to find a solution.
I analyzed all the laws
enforced in this nation,
and there's only one way
you and Lord Yi-eon can get
officially married.
To sue Lord Yi-eon
for the seubcheob.
Get people who saw you and
Lord Yi-eon enter a seubcheob to testify,
and sue Lord Yi-eon.
In accordance with the laws
based on the code of morality,
he must take you as his wife.
That way,
Lord Yi-eon and you
can officially get married.
Stop right there!
What the? Where is it?
Who is it? What is it?
The first man she comes across
must take her to be his wife.
That's the custom in Joseon.
It's called seubcheob.
There's no reason to abide by that custom.
How dare you! It's a serious crime!
If you want,
I could help you with the lawsuit.
However, that path
will inevitably be a thorny one.
I don't want you to walk on a thorny path.
Jo-yi.
How about only walking
on flowery paths with me?
Forget it, punk.
My goodness, Seung-yul.
You're so good at your job.
I didn't even ask you to,
but you prepared all this.
I can see now why you're the lawyer
with the highest success rate.
But I have no intention
of accepting a hairpin from you
or hiring you to sue Lord Yi-eon.
So look for clients elsewhere.
Do you understand?
That was completely fruitless.
The act of bravado was a bit too much.
It wasn't an act.
See.
I even packed my bags to leave
in case you rejected me.
Really?
I'm going on a business trip, brat.
It seems that word of me
has even spread across the sea.
I received a request.
That makes more sense. But I can
understand why after seeing how you work.
It may take a while.
Sure. Okay. Have a safe trip.
Don't skip meals.
Don't get sick.
Don't get angry so easily.
Don't cry.
You said it's just a business trip.
Why the long goodbye?
Get going.
You go on first.
Okay, goodbye.
Get a silk garment for me!
What is this bundle for?
I'll be making a short trip
to Gapbigocha for the investigation.
You only came back not too long ago.
Why are you leaving already?
You said that you were even demoted.
Can't you just
take your hands off this case?
I took on this case,
and I must close it.
I'll try my best to be careful.
All right.
As you've said,
I'll stay out of your affairs.
However,
the issue of marriage isn't yours alone.
So do as I say.
Don't complain.
Marry the girl that I choose
by the end of the year, no matter what.
-Do I make myself clear?
-Grandmother.
Marriage is my business.
If you don't want to get married
that badly, then stop seeing that girl.
If you're not even going to get married,
why in the world
are you seeing that girl, Jo-yi?
Even if I'm not sure about marriage,
Jo-yi…
I'm sure about her.
And are you sure
she's sure about you as well?
I hear that she's just been
spotted with another man earlier.
You didn't
have someone tail her, did you?
I did.
I need to know what kind of girl she is
for me to make a decision as well.
Well done.
I'm sure once you find out
what kind of girl she is,
you will get to like her.
Grandmother.
I know very well how much you care for me.
However,
my decision not to get married stands.
Despite that,
if you continue to push for marriage…
I will do it.
With Jo-yi.
I can only do one of two things
regarding the issue of marriage.
Either I don't get married,
or if I'm forced to, I will with Jo-yi.
There are no other
possible choices in my life.
Then, I'll leave for Gapbigocha now.
Let me know when you've made your mind.
You can take them now.
Good job. Be careful with them.
This place was finally
beginning to look like a home.
I'm getting a bit upset.
We're still people of this land.
First, for being captured
and dragged away,
and then for coming back,
they treat us like crap until the end…
Let's have no regrets
about leaving this place.
Go through the things
in the butcher's shop
and take what you can
to trade at the marketplace.
Try to get food if you can.
Okay, I will.
You should get some rest.
I can take care of this place.
I'll prepare food for the kids
and leave the rest to you.
Okay.
I'm glad you're here.
I was actually looking for you
because some work came in.
-Really?
-A minister's servant
just stopped by.
She said that money wasn't an issue
and asked for the best needlewoman
to make clothes for the young master.
So I've been waiting for you to come by.
Oh, thank you.
Go on and show them what you can do.
He tends to order by the cartload
if he likes what he sees.
Okay.
But if you accept the job,
you need to make
some socks for the lord, too. Look.
You just need to make
a pocket like this inside each sock.
You can do that, right?
A pocket inside a sock?
Yes. That's what she orders,
so you just need to make them like that.
But she said she was in a hurry
and asked for them to be made by tomorrow.
-Is that possible?
-Of course.
Then, choose the fabric.
The most expensive silks are there,
-so choose from there.
-Okay.
Excuse me,
can I ask you for some directions?
If I continue along this path,
will I find Sewoon Temple?
Yes, if you go down a bit more,
you'll see the first gate.
Okay, thank you.
What is this?
They asked for a pocket inside the sock.
It's odd, isn't it?
A pocket inside a sock?
Are they trying to hide
some sort of treasure?
I know, right?
And they asked for them
to be done by tomorrow.
Anyhow,
maybe Gwang-soon really is seeing a man.
Why is she late every night?
If only there was a man.
She's been looking a bit down recently.
I'm worried about her.
Actually… Me, too.
She keeps appearing in my dreams,
looking for shoes.
My dreams have been worrisome recently.
Shoes? Is such a dream a bad omen?
I'm not sure
if it's a bad omen or a good one.
Where have you been?
My goodness, it looks like
you even skipped dinner.
Wait here. I'll go set a table.
No.
It's fine. I had a bite to eat earlier.
Is something going on?
What's wrong with your face?
What? No, it's nothing. Nothing.
Come on, there's clearly
something going on.
What's the matter? What's going on?
-Tell us. We'll help if we can.
-Yes.
Well…
The truth is,
I'm also looking for someone.
-You are?
-Who?
My father.
Goodness.
Do you have any idea where he might be?
I heard that he moved
to a small temple near Hanyang.
But I'm not exactly sure which one.
Then we just need to search through
every small temple near Hanyang.
Yes, let's.
-Let's look together.
-Oh, no, that's fine.
Do you know how many small
temples there are around Hanyang?
-Come on.
-That's not that many.
-Not many at all.
And all of them are on top of mountains.
So you've been
climbing mountains every day…
Thanks for the gesture,
but I can do it by myself one by one.
This is nothing.
I bet we can do it in a day.
-Don't you think so, Bi-ryeong?
-Of course.
I use to live in the mountains.
I'm a master.
No, that's fine.
I'm not even sure he's there.
What if it's all for nothing?
What's the point
of worrying about it in advance?
And if he's not there,
we can look elsewhere.
Gwang-soon, I'll be by your side
until you find him.
Who knows?
I know it's unstable,
but my spiritual powers might be helpful.
Okay.
Let's do that. Whatever it may be,
let's do it together.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
How hard it must have been for you alone!
Jo-yi, your accent was like…
I am from Hanyang.
How many mountains do we need to climb?
This seems like the place.
GOKDU
TURUKSON, GUNPOWDER
Hey, kids.
Is this Tail Island?
Who are you?
Ma'am?
Ma'am!
It's you, isn't it?
Seung-yul, is that you?
Yes, ma'am. I'm Seung-yul
from Yeowul Valley.
Have you been well?
Yes, I have…
The air is quite clean here, ma'am.
We shouldn't do this out here.
We can go inside--
It's fine.
I'm perfectly fine with here as well.
Okay.
My goodness.
You haven't lost your touch at all.
So I hear you became a lawyer.
You knew.
Then, you must know
how Jo-yi is doing as well.
After I severed ties with her last time,
I haven't heard anything.
Severed ties?
Because I'm planning
to leave this place soon.
I'm nothing
but a burdensome mother to Jo-yi.
You don't have to worry about Jo-yi.
I'm sure she'll have no problems
taking care of herself.
She's already a famous needlewoman
and has customers lining up.
Now she even has friends by her side,
and above all else,
she has a lord that cares for her deeply
and protects her.
Yes. He's a busuchan at Hongmungwan,
and his name is Ra Yi-eon.
The two met when he was a secret
royal inspector in Chungcheong,
and I believe
he's been by her side ever since.
Why?
To live as Turukson?
The Uigeumbu is searching for this.
GUNPOWDER TRANSACTION RECORD
So that's why Jo-yi had that ledger book.
To tell the truth, that's the reason
why I came to see you today.
Lord Yi-eon is
pursuing a case involving
the traitor, Park Tae-seo, and his men.
Therefore,
I came to ask you for a favor.
Will you leaving like this
be better for Jo-yi's sake?
Or will staying by her side
to help with this investigation be better?
Please, reconsider it.
I may have lost the position
of Jo-yi's suitor to Lord Yi-eon,
but as her childhood friend,
I wanted to do something for her.
That's why I came to see you today.
Please reconsider, ma'am.
So you're saying he left nothing behind?
It doesn't matter what it is.
Anything connected to Ra Yong-gyun…
The only thing left
are the straw shoes he wore.
Then can we take a look at them?
But what for?
I don't know.
Let's just take them for now.
-Just a moment.
-Thank you.
I see it.
I felt something. I think he's here.
Here…
Let's hurry.
Excuse me, can I ask you something?
Wait, Gwang-soon?
Yook-chil?
Jo-yi?
Bi-ryeong?
Gu-pal?
What are you…
Lord Yi-eon sent us here
to collect some evidence.
But what are you doing here, Gwang-soon?
I'm here to look for my father.
What's wrong?
By any chance, is your father's name…
-Ra…
-Ra Yong-gyun?
Yes, it is.
But how do you know my father's name?
Back then…
I just thought my father
was just losing his mind.
One and a half don of seohyang,
two dons of baeggyeong,
four dons of aconite…
One and a half don of seohyang, two dons
of baeggyeong, four dons of aconite…
How long do you plan on keeping this up?
Father.
Pull yourself together now.
Please, stop now.
Gwang-soon, I gave the right prescription.
I put exactly one nyang of angelica root
-and the aconite…
-The Crown Prince…
His Highness has already passed.
So why do you keep digging up the past
and reliving that event?
What if the neighbors hear you?
My goodness, Father, you can't.
Father…
It wasn't me!
Someone must've poisoned the Crown Prince.
or such a substance
couldn't have been found in that tonic.
Watch what you say!
What if people think it's true?
Please, stop, Father.
Gwang-soon, you must leave this house.
You could end up in danger, too.
-Father…
-Get away now!
-Now!
-Pull yourself together.
-Go on!
-Where am I supposed to go?
Go on and leave!
-Father, it's going to be okay.
-Go…
It will be okay, Father.
Father, it will be okay.
But my father…
It turns out he was right.
So, who did it?
Who dared to do that to the Crown Prince…
and my father…
Who's the bastard?
It's Park Tae-seo.
-Gwang-soon.
-I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I'm okay.
What…
What do you mean?
I…
I've committed a grave sin, Young Master!
Young Master?
Why are you calling me that?
Mother.
I might have been very young,
but I still remember your face, Mother.
No.
No…
I'm not your mother, Young Master.
If you're feeling guilty
about leaving me as a child,
I…
do not resent you, Mother.
swapped the babies!
It's a son, my lord.
A son?
Thank you!
It's a son, my lord.
What does that lowly girl's baby
have to do with me?
A son? He's just an illegitimate child.
Does my son have ten fingers and toes?
Does he look like me?
Yes, my lord. Sincerest congratulations.
Thank you!
I'm sorry.
I could not
let my child…
live as an illegitimate child
and become an object of scorn.
Young Master!
Young Master.
Young Master…
GAPBIGOCHA
TAVERN
My goodness.
You look like you suffered
some serious seasickness.
Hey.
What's the most famous
and tastiest dish here?
The only food we have is rice and soup.
-Then, give me a bowl of it.
-Sure.
You'll feel better
once you have some warm soup.
Enjoy.
It's a bit bland.
This is the stuff.
-I'm so tired.
-I'm exhausted.
-Welcome!
-Hello.
-We'll take some rice and soup.
-Sure. Two rice and soups.
By the way,
did you hear about what happened at Gokdu?
It turns out that the leader of Gokdu
got caught partaking in treason,
so it was completely destroyed.
I was wondering why
there was no trading group left.
So that's why it was torn down.
But the royal forces weren't behind that.
Some nobleman from Hanyang,
the Chief State Councilor,
wanted to build a villa for his son
in that spot and had it knocked down.
My goodness.
That trading group was doing so well
but vanished overnight without a trace.
Life is all vanity.
Park Seung managed
to take control of Gapbigocha already?
GUNPOWDER TRANSACTION RECORD
KANG HAN-GI
TURUKSON
These bastards are just sickening.
They crossed the sea
to even strike deals in Gapbigocha.
TURUKSON
Someone in Gapbigocha
must have been working
with Park Tae-seo's group.
Park Tae-seo!
I must go.
I will drag you to Hanyang.
I need to go see my father.
I need to tell him something.
I must go!
I cannot just let you go.
Get out of my way!
Goodness.
Jo-yi.
Aren't they due today?
You can go.
I'll look after Gwang-soon.
Are you sure?
You said you made a promise.
You can't lose credibility.
Then, I'll be right back.
-Be careful.
-Okay.
I came to deliver some socks.
Come on in.
Please, wait here for a moment.
I'll bring the head servant.
Okay.
Do-soo, you might get hurt! Careful!
Father!
Do-soo, be careful! Careful!
-Father!
-My son, you'll get hurt.
Father.
I feel so good.
Seeing my son being so happy
makes me so happy.
Do-soo.
For all those years,
I've wanted to be accepted by my father.
But I'm the legitimate child.
Do-soo is not.
I am
the legitimate child.
The babies were switched.
I wonder what Father will say…
once he finds out we were switched.
That doesn't change the life you have led.
You can resent it, get angry,
and regret it all you want.
But it won't erase…
what you have done.
If you truly wish to change,
there is only one way.
You must properly pay for your crimes.
The last tonic…
was not delivered by me.
It was probably Do-soo.
Put that here and sit.
Feel free to come closer and take a look.
They say the lands and oceans have always
been joined together in a circular fashion
like this to create the shape of a ball.
If I have the chance,
I'd like to visit these other countries.
But I remain unwell like this…
Who knows?
There might be a nation
where everyone is equal
without discrimination.
Does…
Does such a nation
really exist?
I'm not sure.
But there must be one somewhere.
If it doesn't exist,
we could make this nation to be the first.
I'm sorry for making a silly joke.
Your Highness.
I apologize,
but I made a mistake
with the dosage in that tonic.
I'll make a fresh batch.
Please, don't drink that one.
It's fine.
Forgive me, Father.
I failed to follow your order
and made a mistake…
You damn coward.
Father, I took very good care of it.
He drank it so well.
What did I tell you?
Tae-seo can't do stuff like this.
I didn't want to get blood on your hands.
You stupid bastard.
You couldn't even take
care of a simple task
and had to make my Do-soo
get blood on his hands?
You useless bastard.
Get out of my house right now!
So…
Are you sure no one saw you?
Father, you had everything
set up perfectly.
I didn't even sign in and
just walked into the Naeuiwon.
My baby! I'm so proud of you.
You're so brave just like me.
-Of course.
-My goodness. My baby!
My goodness. My baby!
You're right.
I was wrong.
I've committed too many sins.
As you said,
I will pay for my crimes.
I will confess to everything.
I will take my friends
and head to Hanyang.
This is a written oath
containing Park Seung's seal.
This can't be…
Is this Lord Park Seung's house?
You are never to disclose
what you saw and heard
and to cooperate in letting the herbal
tonics into the Crown Prince's palace.
THE SAFETY OF THE CHILD ACTORS
IN THIS EPISODE WAS PROPERLY ENSURED
SPECIAL THANKS TO
LEE JUN-HYUK AND CHA HAK-YEON
The evidence that Lord Yi-eon
risked his life to acquire…
The first sponsor was
the late Crown Prince.
Are you Lord Ra Yi-eon?
This is a list of ingredients for a tonic.
To prove that the Crown Prince
was poisoned to death.
Wherever you are,
I hope you remain healthy, Mother. Father.
He told me this nonsense
about how this place was possessed
by the spirit of a son
born in this household.
You take lives as if they were meals,
so you have countless spirits
swarming all over you.
I'll make sure
Park Seung's arrest warrant gets issued.
Let's move out!