ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCALES, AND EVENTS ARE USED
IN AN ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS MANNER
AND NOT BASED ON HISTORICAL FACTS
Park Tae-seo was the fake physician?
Are you sure?
The scar that I saw on
the abscess specialist's wrist that day…
I saw that scar
on Park Tae-seo's wrist.
So it's true
Park Seung was involved in the death
of the Crown Prince.
But why?
Why would he partake
in such a horrendous act?
This is the pharmacy journal
Park Tae-seo has with him.
It contains a detailed account of
everything that happened in the pharmacy.
But
this is just a written record.
There's no entry
that directly mentions Park Seung's name.
This is not enough to prove that
he poisoned the Crown Prince to death.
On top of that,
the real abscess specialist is dead.
If this was a mere pharmacy journal,
why would Park Tae-seo go
all the way to Jinin Temple
to acquire it when he was on the run?
Park Seung used Park Tae-seo,
his illegitimate son,
to embezzle tax grains from Chungcheong
and flagrantly collude
with the government officials
to illegally gain personal profit.
He murdered the inspectors sent out
to Chungcheong without hesitation
and blocked all their reports
from entering the palace.
Could this have been possible
without help from the palace?
In exchange for poisoning
the Crown Prince to death,
someone gave
Chungcheong Province to Park Seung.
You don't mean…
That's where this case begins.
The last page of the ledger was burned,
but it's enough to prove
the embezzlement of tax grains.
My lord! The ledger!
And the ledgers acquired at
Soyang Trading Group and the mountain base
prove they colluded
with Chungcheong officials.
They are as corrupt as they can get.
Park Tae-seo illegally operated a mine
to produce silver
and also illegally
cultivated aconite there.
And Park Do-soo murdered
Chief Hong Seok-gi of Maritime Transport.
PHARMACY JOURNAL
I'm sure there is something
in the Pharmacy Journal.
We must prove that all of this
is connected to Park Seung
through the interrogation at all cost.
It's perfectly valid speculation.
But the issue is
much too grave to rely solely on that.
One wrong move, and we could
end up getting harmed, instead.
We need a proper investigation.
It's too dangerous.
Especially so if behind Park Seung is
the one you and I think it is.
Chief Scholar.
Let's not pursue the Crown Prince matter
at the upcoming interrogation.
I fully empathize with your impatience.
However, we must concentrate
on getting Park Seung imprisoned for now.
We must strip him of his power first
before we pursue anything else.
Or we won't stand a chance.
This is the most realistic option
at this point.
I know it's shameless,
but I'll accept this one last time.
What do you mean?
The benefactor has
no intention of stopping the support.
I'm aware.
If it's because the amount is not enough,
I could talk to them about it.
Thanks to their support,
we were able to settle down in Tail Island
when we had nowhere to go.
The benefactor gave us
the courage to fight for survival.
And we were able to farm
and raise livestock by ourselves,
and have made enough money
to be independent,
but that isn't the issue…
Most were kicked out of their homes,
have no parents,
or are fugitives.
That is to say, we're not
acknowledged as Joseon citizens.
We're not listed on a family registry,
so if you visit a physician
because you're sick,
you're most likely turned away.
And even if we offer
to pay many times the price,
medication is hard to come by.
Above all else,
government officials could raid
and disperse our village any moment,
so we must live in constant fear.
Which is why we're preparing to leave.
Leave?
I heard there are
many other countries in this world.
And I've seen some ships
from foreign lands dock in Gapbigocha.
As soon as we have enough money
to get us on one of those ships,
I'm planning to leave Joseon
with the women and children.
Must you do that?
Which is why
before we leave, I would
very much like to meet our benefactor.
I'd like to extend my gratitude in person.
Could you possibly tell me
who the benefactor is
and where I might find them?
I'm sorry.
I'm just the messenger.
I can't tell you anything about them.
Wait. Isn't that Tae-seo?
Tae-seo!
Tae-seo…
Did you really willingly give yourself up?
Were you
unable to get away?
I'm sorry.
We were caught thanks to
this idiot dawdling to buy some shoes.
You ate three bowls of noodles.
Because you were taking so long!
You fools.
What about Han-gi?
I'm not sure.
I doubt it's safe at Gokdu either.
GAPBIGOCHA
Ma'am!
What is it?
What is this fuss about?
Kang Han-gi…
Kang Han-gi's Gokdu Trading Group
is being ransacked right now!
What do you mean ransacked?
Officials from the mainland came in.
They're taking everything and everyone
they can get their hands on at Gokdu.
Ma'am.
What happened? What about the goods?
They took all the royal offerings
and the trade goods
that Kang Han-gi embezzled.
But
they didn't seem to know
about the gunpowder and weapons.
But
I can't find the ledger
containing our names.
To live as Turukson?
The Uigeumbu is searching for this.
This butterfly symbol.
It's your mark.
What about Kang Han-gi?
Did they take her, too?
GUNPOWDER TRANSACTION RECORD
TURUKSON
Why is your mark here?
What in the world is going on with you?
If that bothers you,
you can also commit a crime for my sake
or you can pursue justice for your sake.
You just need to choose.
Your plan isn't ruined
because of us, is it?
What is your plan anyhow?
Tae-seo, did you
give yourself up on purpose?
-Seriously?
-If you know, shut up.
Should I?
Hey, don't worry about us.
Just go on with your plan.
We're at the Uigeumbu. It's different
from the regional offices you frequented.
That's true.
I could have sent
Park Seung to hell by now.
If you two idiots hadn't been captured.
Were you going
to sacrifice yourself with that?
If I were alone,
I would've sacrificed, confessed,
taken my own life, whatever it took
to end Park Seung with this.
You should've told me if you had
something like that. I'm hurt.
Because it'd put us in danger, idiot.
Why are you so twisted?
I can't get a word out
without you jumping all over it.
Listen to me carefully.
The two of you must say
you were just following my orders
and get out
of the palace alive at all cost.
You might not be able to avoid punishment,
but if you say
I forced you to do all of it,
your lives should be spared.
What about you?
Once you're sentenced and taken away,
my interrogation will begin.
And that's when
I will accuse Park Seung with this.
Hey, even so, we can't
just leave you behind.
I won't gamble
with your lives.
So please…
Shut up and get out of here alive.
Fine.
I will.
I'll try my best.
You know I'm a pretty good actor, right?
Fine.
Maeng-su. You, too.
Okay.
Why is the gunpowder
transaction ledger missing?
Give this ledger to Yook-chil later.
I shall submit it as evidence
with my report.
Okay, I will.
My lord, I forgot to bring
one of the documents. I'll go retrieve it.
Go ahead.
And while you're at home,
why don't you take a nap and rest?
The interrogation will be held tomorrow.
Has it been postponed?
The royal forces that left for Gapbigocha
to arrest Kang Han-gi have yet to return.
Don't worry too much, and get some rest.
Then, I shall.
My lord.
My lord…
My lord, we're coming soon. Hang in there.
The source of Joseon's strength
is garlic, right?
Of course.
Without garlic and scallions,
you can't call it Joseon cuisine.
By the way, why are you crying so much?
-My eyes!
-Sorry!
I'm going blind…
I'm going blind. Am I dying?
I think I need to eat something.
My eyes… I think
I'm going blind because of you.
You haven't gone blind.
Seeing that you managed
to only pick out meat.
The meat is cooked perfectly.
Thanks to our lord,
our cooking skills have improved a lot.
-Of course. Pass me soybean paste.
-Yes, sir.
Who are you to order me around?
-Salt.
-Yes, sir.
Who are you to order me around?
-Is it seasoned right?
-Why are you--
Salty!
Salty? How could it be salty?
We're in big trouble.
I threw in all the meat we had.
My God! Our lord despises salty food.
Then we should eat it all up.
Yes, let's.
-I prefer salty anyhow.
-Me, too.
-Salty makes it tasty.
-It makes you eat a lot of rice.
You know how to eat.
We're not going to buy anything!
You can try next door.
Yes. The neighbors are
much more well off anyhow.
The master of this house
is incredibly stingy.
You should just move on.
I see.
So you have meat as your side dish
because your master
is incredibly stingy?
My lord, when did you get here?
I make the money, and you spend it.
Well.
We were making it for you
because you've been working so hard,
but it was much too salty.
How are things going at work?
I'm sure he did
everything perfectly. Right?
He even locked up Park Tae-seo.
It's game over, right?
Right.
Anyhow, bring me the gunpowder ledger
you received at the mountain base.
You should've brought it to me
as soon as you received it.
I didn't receive it.
What do you mean? You didn't get
the gunpowder transaction ledger?
My lord, Jo-yi has that ledger.
She still hasn't handed it over yet?
No.
You said Ojang-dong, right?
You're going to visit her?
Gwang-soon is there, too.
You're not going empty-handed, right?
I have no time. Lead the way.
My lord.
Why do you look so pale?
I apologize.
I should've given it to you sooner.
I made the wrong choice.
I can't tell you why,
but I tried to burn this ledger.
I am truly sorry.
It's fine.
You brought it to me right on time.
Do not worry.
My lord.
Whatever the truth may be,
please conduct a proper investigation.
I want a complete answer, the truth.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
Have you eaten?
I'm fine.
I have to take care of that.
-Yook-chil, Gu-pal.
-Yes, sir.
Get ready.
Did you find it?
No.
What's wrong?
You can't do that, my lord!
My lord.
You are so mean.
Wait!
Didn't you want to taste
Bo-ri's thick kimchi stew?
I did.
The truth is, I'm the one
who taught her the secret to her recipe.
Really?
Do you have
a mortar and pestle by any chance?
Men should do tasks like these.
Let me.
Don't you remember
what happened when we were held up
by those bandits?
Have a seat and wait.
It'll be done in no time.
Ta-da.
So this is the special seasoning
for Bo-ri's stew.
We'll soon arrive
at Chungcheong's most famous eatery,
Bo-ri's Thick Kimchi Stew.
They use a special minced seasoning
made out of dried chili powder.
Aren't you curious how good it tastes?
I get to taste Bo-ri's stew in Hanyang?
This is incredible, isn't it?
Does it make you that happy?
You must tell me the recipe.
No!
I might open a stew place of my own later.
Teach it to me.
Are you trying to score
a secret recipe for free?
You can't.
If you don't want to,
I guess you can come over
and cook it for me every day.
What?
I'd like to see you at my place every day
when I come home from work.
Well, I mean…
What a unique taste!
I've never tasted
anything like this before.
But it's something that you can't stop
eating once you've tasted it once.
How did you end up cooking like this?
I…
used to have a brother
with quite a finicky palate.
He was so picky that he used to
even reject meals with 12 side dishes.
You should go ahead and taste it, too.
Okay.
It's clean, not dry, yet deep in flavor.
How did you think
of making broth like this?
My mother used to cook it
for me often when I was younger.
My mother had such delicate hands.
But…
You should try it
after mixing the broth with rice.
You need a full stomach
to do your job well.
Okay.
You eat up, too.
When your stomach is empty,
so is your heart.
Even if it's just a single meal,
you must enjoy it to be happy.
Put the gunpowder
in the shed in the mountain.
And bury the rifles in the beach.
Except the ones we need,
-burn all of the ledgers.
-Yes, ma'am.
What do we do
if they come to raid us, too?
What do we do now?
There's no need for rash thoughts.
We just continue cooking and eating
with the other women and carry on.
Tail Island…
I'll do whatever it takes to protect it.
Tell me what you told me before.
I can help you get on an iyangseon.
IYANGSEON:
A SHIP HEADED FOR THE WEST
But to get on one,
you're going to need more than the fare.
My lord…
Do you see the Pleiades cluster,
towards the west?
"The Pleiades cluster"?
Are you talking about those?
That's toward the north.
That's the Big Dipper.
That's north.
Over there.
There! You mean those stars!
That's Cassiopeia.
"Cassiopeia"?
Over there.
That star! You're talking about that one.
That's the evening star!
It's the evening star?
Then, is it that star?
Which one do you mean?
The one right next to the evening star.
What star is next to the evening star?
Do you not see it?
That is
the moon.
Tie the criminal to the rack
and proceed with the interrogation!
Please, get the chief
state councilor for me.
I'm his only son.
Please, let me just talk to him. Please…
The chief state councilor… Please…
Remove the hoods.
Please get the chief
state councilor for me.
-Your Majesty…
-Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Such impertinence!
How dare you lift up your head?
Where is the other prisoner, Park Seung?
Chief Scholar.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Didn't you say
there was a female offender?
My deepest regrets, Your Majesty…
Gokdu Trading Group on Gapbigocha
was searched thoroughly,
but Kang Han-gi was nowhere to be found.
You couldn't even arrest a woman,
and now there's a setback.
Start the interrogation.
Park Tae-seo. Cha Mal-jong.
Ji Maeng-su. Park Do-soo.
They not only committed theft and robbery
but also kidnapped and sold people,
embezzled royal offerings and grain taxes
to rob the palace's assets
and violate principles of morality.
They even committed murder.
And these principal offenders
have been arrested.
Will you admit to your crimes and confess?
Cha Mal-jong will be interrogated first.
Why me…
Sir. My lord. Your Majesty.
I…
-Beat him 30 times.
-Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
Please, spare me.
What are you apologizing for?
You better confess your crime in detail.
I…
I stole precious royal offerings
and committed acts of high treason.
Are you referring
to bribing the provincial offices
of Chungcheong as the head of Soyang,
abducting and abusing civilians
to turn them into slaves,
murdering secret
royal inspectors in the field,
illegally mining silver
by conspiring with Park Tae-seo,
and hiring bandits to pillage?
Those acts of high treason?
What?
No!
I don't know anything about that!
I only desired riches
to dress nicely and eat well.
You dare resort to lies
when there's evidence?
Please, spare me!
I was born into
an unremarkable noble family,
but they were still nobles,
so they kicked me out
for being an illegitimate son.
I just tried to make a living
with people of similar backgrounds.
That's how I ended up
committing such foolish acts.
Beat him!
Everything I did…
Tae-seo…
Tae-seo ordered me to do it…
And that punk, Park Do-soo…
killed Hong Seok-gi,
the Chief of Maritime Transport.
You bastard!
How dare you lowly bastard
run that mouth of yours?
Your Majesty!
It's not true!
I've never seen
these bastards before in my life
and only just found out about
the atrocious acts they've committed!
Everyone, be quiet!
Please call the chief
state councilor for me!
Your Majesty!
I swear that I'm innocent!
Park Do-soo,
is it true you killed Hong Seok-gi,
the Chief of Maritime Transport?
I did not.
I did not kill him.
Bring in the witness!
I…
saw Park Do-soo kill the Chief
of Maritime Transport with my eyes.
That is a false testimony!
Furthermore, he kidnapped me
and took me to Park Tae-seo's hideout.
Are you claiming that Park Do-soo
and Park Tae-seo kept in contact?
Your Majesty! How can you believe her?
It's true that Park Tae-seo
is an illegitimate son of my father,
but he left home when he turned 15,
and I haven't even
heard from him until now!
I swear, I did not
keep in contact with Park Tae-seo!
On the day I witnessed the act,
Park Do-soo, Park Tae-seo
and Cha Mal-jong were together.
And while I was a slave
at Soyang Trading Group,
I saw Park Tae-seo and Ji Maeng-su
come by the group many times.
Even with her testimony,
you still refuse to confess.
-Look here!
-Prepare the press!
I'll confess!
Yes, I was ordered
to just meet with Tae-seo
and went to Chungcheong Province.
Who gave the order?
Was it Lord Park Seung?
Father…
Your Majesty.
I, Park Seung,
was released by the grace of Your Majesty
and present myself
as the judge of this case.
Your Majesty.
Park Seung was named as
the possible mastermind behind this case.
It's not right to release him like this.
On top of that, he's the judge?
Does any of that evidence
contain Lord Park's name?
Your Majesty. His name may
not be mentioned directly,
but if we compare
the many transaction ledgers,
his involvement will be proven.
How could we investigate
the Chief Councilor
without direct evidence?
However, Your Majesty,
having a suspect solely exempt
from the due process is unheard of.
How could we investigate him
without clear evidence?
Your Majesty.
Park Do-soo and Park Tae-seo are
Park Seung's sons.
Even if there's no evidence,
Park Seung's connection
to their crimes is undeniable.
Then,
I will remove Park Seung
from his position and demote him.
You can stop there, Chief Scholar.
You may continue with the interrogation.
Your Majesty…
Your Majesty!
I…
have offered so many bribes to Park Seung
that I have kept a distribution log
detailing the transactions.
I have hidden it
in a place that I only know of.
I can go and get it right now if you wish.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty. Please, immediately imprison
the suspects in separate cells
and let us interrogate them again
with additional evidence.
-You cannot--
-You may do so.
Bring them back to their cells!
Good. It's done.
If you're lying,
you will be beheaded on the spot.
Where is the distribution log?
I hid it in a tavern I know.
I would suggest you refrain
from pulling any tricks.
Even if I have to give it up,
I won't hand it over to you.
-Lock him up.
-Yes, sir.
Cha Mal-jong will never
hand over the distribution log to me.
I thought so as well.
I think we should send officials over
to find the evidence.
Is there anyone we can trust?
-Come over here.
-Yes, sir.
They served me for many years
during my time at Saheonbu.
Take Cha Mal-jong with you
to retrieve the distribution log.
-Thank you.
-Yes, sir.
Bi-ryeong!
Jo-yi.
My goodness. Well done.
How scary that must have been!
Not at all. Lord Yi-eon was there,
and I did so well without trembling.
Great. I'm glad to hear that.
-Let's hurry back home.
-Okay.
Here. Get on.
What?
Jo-yi, I'm not a child.
How badly your legs must
have been shaking in there!
I can't let you walk with them.
Get on.
Jo-yi.
I'm even taller than you.
You're right.
Then…
make sure not to let go of my hand, okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's hurry.
You hid it well, right?
I just couldn't trust
that old geezer, Park Seung.
So I hid it,
and then I forgot about it. My goodness.
I remember now.
So don't worry.
You must find it.
I'll run over and find it,
so just hang in there.
Let's go.
Tae-seo, don't worry.
I'm Mal-jong. Cha Mal-jong!
This is it. Over there.
It's at the end. Over there at the end.
It's on top of that.
Good. It remained safe and sound up there.
If you look inside,
you'll find Park Seung's seal.
Okay. It's going to be all right now.
Where is Cha Mal-jong?
Some guards just came by and took him.
Are there guards other than us
that were sent to transport him?
I don't think we came
through this way earlier.
Is there a way back
to the palace this way, too?
What are you doing?
I have to get back
to Tae-seo and Maeng-su!
What is this?
Damn it.
Cha Mal-jong is dead?
He's dead? What are you talking about?
When the guards we sent arrived,
other guards had already taken him away.
Other guards?
It seems that Park Seung intercepted.
According to the guards,
Cha Mal-jong lied, attempted to flee,
and ended up dead in the process…
Then, what about the distribution log?
They say it never existed
in the first place.
We don't know what's the truth though.
This is definitely Park Seung's doing.
We should do something about it.
Stop right there.
I can't just sit back
and watch this absurdity unfold.
Do you still not understand?
His Majesty
has taken Park Seung's side.
Do you still not understand?
Where are we going?
Where are you taking me?
Cha Mal-jong.
Where is he?
Cha Mal-jong is dead.
What do you mean, he's dead?
Why would Mal-jong die?
There's no way. That's impossible.
What did you do to him?
Cha Mal-jong!
Since the suspect has died,
the investigation cannot continue.
So the interrogation ends here.
The suspect, Park Do-soo,
has been proven guilty of murder
and shall be exiled
from the land of Korea.
Based on the compiled evidence,
Park Tae-seo and Ji Maeng-su
have committed too many crimes
to name individually.
I hereby order them to be executed.
Finally,
I'm done with you.
I'll do whatever it takes
to distract them, so you run.
This is the palace.
This is nothing
like the places we've lived at.
You're going to die like this?
Pull yourself together, punk.
Think of Mal-jong.
Mal-jong even died to save us.
The execution of Park Tae-seo and
Ji Maeng-su will commence soon.
You should attend.
If they die,
this investigation
will end like this.
Even though Park Seung
managed to get out unscathed.
This is the time to lie low
and wait for the right time.
I don't want to accept it,
but we have been defeated by Park Seung.
No, I cannot accept defeat.
Look here.
Look here, Busuchan.
Is he all right?
My son.
It's me, your father.
Where am I? Have I been exiled?
You're home.
Home?
I paid the restitution fees
to free you. Don't worry.
Father.
My goodness, my baby.
Why didn't you free me sooner?
I went through so much because of you!
It's okay. It's okay, my baby.
You must have been so scared, my son.
It's all right. You're all right now.
Sir, you can't. You can't, sir.
Do-soo is trying to get some rest!
How dare you barge in here like this?
I must hear
why you killed the Crown Prince.
If you wish to formally ask that question,
you must first
find evidence
that I poisoned the Crown Prince.
You used Park Tae-seo
to allow herbal tonics
containing aconite to enter his palace.
Is that the version
of the truth you believe?
So?
Were you able to catch me with that truth?
Did I run away? Did I hide?
I am standing right in front of you.
Back then and even now,
the one who failed
to catch or stop me was you.
I saw
what would happen.
Hold on!
CHUNGCHEONG PROVINCE
And
I knew it from the start.
Want to know what I think?
I think it'll be best
if you take the fall for everything,
let the inspector take you away,
and disappear from the world.
I knew
that you would do exactly as I expected.
The fools always blame the rock
after they fall over.
Father.
Yes, Do-soo.
I'm right here.
Do-soo!
So?
Were you able to catch me with that truth?
Did I run away? Did I hide?
I am standing right in front of you.
Back then and even now,
the one who failed
to catch or stop me was you.
Normally, after the first trial,
executions cannot take place
based on the law.
However, their crimes are heinous,
and there are flight risks.
So their executions
will be held immediately.
All right. Let's have some fun.
Stand guard of the area.
Make them step back.
Kill me or let me live,
you will be executed in the end.
You will not be able to
make it out of here alive.
Tae-seo.
Kill him.
Stop.
Attack the criminals now.
You cannot let them get away.
What are you doing?
Are you going to defy the royal command
to execute them?
Are you all right, my lord?
We must kill them.
Don't let them get away alive!
Go after them!
SPECIAL THANKS TO JO KWAN-WOO
So what if you fail?
So what if something goes wrong?
It's crap.
Father, I'm really scared.
The prisoners have escaped, so you will be
the first one they suspect, Leader Kang.
Mother.
What do you think you're doing?
Show some respect!
Some work hard to make the porridge
so another minister can gobble it up.
I'm sure you'll get back
on your feet, my lord.
Jo-yi, for you,
I will start over.