ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCALES, AND EVENTS ARE USED
IN AN ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS MANNER
AND NOT BASED ON HISTORICAL FACTS
Your Highness.
Brother!
Did you say
that you were scared and lonely?
Then having something sweet is the best!
You were right.
This makes me feel much better.
Then, what should we eat next?
Pick up the sword.
I don't want to.
Why don't you want to?
Brother,
it's been so long
since we last met in private.
Why would you waste
this precious time on training--
Brother, if I learn how to use a sword,
I'll end up using it against someone.
I don't want to use
a knife except for when I cook.
Has the world ever gone your way?
Has it ever gone our way?
In order to protect something precious,
you must be prepared
to do whatever it takes.
A day will come
when you will have to wield
a real sword instead of a wooden one
to protect yourself
and the things precious to you.
Even so,
I don't think I'll be
able to wield a real sword.
Your Highness…
Your Highness.
Why didn't you evacuate?
Safely escort him to Mount Gwanggyo.
-Your Highness!
-What do you mean?
Those barbarians don't know your face.
They could harm you
on your way back to the fortress.
I'll find my way back.
-But our duty is to escort--
-Did you not hear me?
Obey your Crown Prince!
You can't, Your Highness.
I cherish this man
more than my real brother.
Consider his life as important as mine.
Yes, Your Highness.
You can't, Your Highness.
Your Highness!
You can't!
Your Highness. No!
Your Highness!
Have you been well?
Please come back, Your Highness!
You feared that
your corruption would be exposed,
so you murdered Park Moo-kyung
who were inspecting the regional office.
And to cover up the murder,
you sunk the freighter.
Despite all that, his body was found.
So you attempted to get rid of it!
I swear I didn't kill him!
Even if you didn't do it yourself,
you must have aided or overlooked it.
This is my command.
Lock up the storehouse
and confiscate the seal immediately!
No, you can't!
You're the divorcee who slapped my mouth.
You're Bang-deuk!
-Royal Inspector!
-Mother!
You came at an opportune time, my lord!
We shall return home now.
You damn brat.
Your impudence knows no end.
Let her go.
How dare you use violence
in a government office?
I hope I'm not too late.
As of today, May 5th…
your divorce is approved.
The royal inspector's body was washed up?
It seems
that the inspector
dispatched to Chungcheong
raided the grain storehouse
and found out about the freighter.
To get rid of the evidence,
we had no choice
but to sink the freighter
and bury the inspector at sea.
Then you should've been thorough.
Why are you telling me this?
We gave you half of the taxes we embezzled
in exchange for protection.
No, you gave it to Park Tae-seo.
Why are you dragging me into this?
What are you trying to pull here?
You took everything you wanted using him!
How could you turn your back on us now?
Besides, Park Tae-seo
is your son, isn't he?
How could he be
when he's not even in the family registry?
Oh, my gosh!
-What?
-What's going on?
An assassin! Run after him!
Move aside!
Your mother is over there!
No!
You have to be the one
to protect her now, not me.
-Grow up already!
-Mother!
My lord!
The marketplace will be chaotic
because it's Dano today.
If your men crash in there
without warning, people might get hurt.
How about your men block
the streets leading to the marketplace
and just a few chase after him?
Listen up.
Block all the streets
leading to the marketplace
and surround the village walls
so the assassin cannot escape.
-No one is to get hurt. Understood?
-Yes, sir!
Yook-chil, Gu-pal.
-Yes, sir.
-We will go after the assassin.
-I'll lead the way if you need me to.
I know this town very well.
Lead the way.
How will you keep up with a horse?
Get up here.
You should've at least
stopped the dispatch of another inspector.
stopped it for your safety!
Did I sink the freighter?
Or did I kill the royal inspector?
What did I do for you
to dare voice your concern about my safety
and threaten me?
If you made a mess,
kill all the witnesses and those involved
or take your own life.
Take care of it on your own.
Please help me, my lord.
What has Tae-seo done to your face?
He should have just killed you.
Giddy up!
Halt.
This way.
Move!
Make way!
Yook-chil, Gu-pal.
Do not draw any attention.
We need to move cautiously.
Let's go.
Move quietly.
Did we lose him?
-We have to find him.
-How do we find him in this mess?
I told them to block all the streets,
so he couldn't have gone far.
Just a moment.
Watch out!
-What was that?
-Oh, my goodness.
My lord!
Get him!
That way!
Stop right there!
-Damn it. This way, Gu-pal.
-Yes, sir.
That way!
-Be careful!
-Move aside!
Gu-pal!
Stop. I want him alive.
My lord, over there.
-Get him!
Are you all right?
What?
Yes.
Thanks to your quick wit,
we captured the assassin
without anyone getting hurt.
I'm more grateful
that I could be of assistance.
Besides, I regained my life thanks to you.
Thank you very much.
No.
You regained it yourself
with your courage.
I wish to reward you,
so tell me if there's anything you desire.
Do you mean it?
If I really can,
there is a favor I'd like to ask.
Go on then.
I'd like to make
a grave for my friend, Bo-ri.
Do you mean the maiden who ran the tavern?
Yes.
Although there's no body
because it was burned,
I wish to at least
bury her spirit in a sunny spot
to let her rest in peace.
You are on your own
now that you're divorced.
I can submit a byeoldan to reward you.
How do you feel about a reward?
A reward?
As in prize money?
No, it's fine.
I'd regret it for the rest of my life.
I decided to get a divorce
because I didn't want
any more regrets in my life.
I'm going to stop
living a life with regret.
-My lord.
-The culprit is ready to be transported.
Let's go, my lord.
-Let go of me!
-Stay still!
I will not interrogate you.
The moment you were arrested,
you failed your mission.
The ones who hired you
will kill you anyway.
Or, since you have committed murder,
sentencing you to death
right now is also an option.
But if there are
extenuating circumstances,
I may show you
some form of mercy or another,
but I'm sure you won't
reveal the one behind this.
Am I wrong?
Think about it carefully.
Are those that you're
risking your life to protect
worth that much?
-Lock him up.
-Yes, sir.
They sent someone
who can't speak on purpose.
We don't know when they'll send
another assassin, so stay alert.
A report has been submitted,
so Hanyang will send instructions.
All of you must oversee
the district until then.
Pardon?
Will you not be doing that yourself?
I received a royal decree
to inspect all of Chungcheong Province.
I cannot stay here for much longer.
I know things are chaotic,
but you must do your duty
in your post.
Yes, my lord.
Oh, but my lord…
According to the ojagin,
the assassin's arrow
was made from an aconite root.
-Aconite?
-Yes, sir.
Aconite is used
for medicinal purposes in the palace.
Yes. It's known
as the best base for a tonic.
However, if misused,
it could be used as a base for poison.
The base for a poison?
What do you mean?
Many people know aconite
to be a medicinal herb,
but depending on the way it's used,
it can also be poisonous.
I have an abscess on my back.
What did you use to make the medicine?
I used aconite.
It's an herb civilians
are prohibited from cultivating.
If aconite was used,
those behind this are in no way ordinary.
Please, be careful.
My lord.
Let's quickly move on
to the next restaurant.
What are we having next?
It was aconite.
Aconite?
Is that the name of a dish?
Does it taste good?
What?
Me coming here was divine intervention.
We must hurry.
Before people hear about
a secret royal inspector digging around,
we'll trace the route the freighter took.
I shall get to the bottom of this case.
Gu-pal. It seems our restaurant tour
has been postponed.
Gosh.
They say that
even furniture harbors memories.
All of you should forget me.
What is all this you packed?
Being kicked out with nothing
wouldn't be good enough.
You dare collect alimony?
Not a chance.
Your jars of alcohol…
-I broke all of them yesterday.
-What?
Because I hate you.
That was the last act of revenge
as your daughter-in-law.
You little…
You're just going out of your way
to act like a dirtbag, aren't you?
How dare you break
those precious jars of herbal liquor!
Even if you get sick,
he has no money
because of his gambling debts.
So don't buy alcohol with this.
Make sure to save it
and use it for medicine later.
How dare you try
to lecture your mother-in-law?
You insolent brat!
The alcohol inspectors might come.
So don't make your own alcohol.
Why do you care?
You said that we're strangers now!
Damn it.
You said that we're strangers now.
You vicious brat!
Go back inside.
When did you ever see me out?
You…
You really can't do this.
I'll forgive everything.
I'll give you one field of barley.
A tenth of a patch.
Just come back!
Are you deaf?
Can she not hear me?
Where are you going?
This is quite a lot.
How did she save all this?
Pardon? He left already?
This case is a complete mess.
He must have a lot
to report back at Hanyang.
He left in a hurry.
Then did he, by any chance,
mention where he was heading next?
Don't be ridiculous.
He's a secret inspector so acts in secret.
So of course, he didn't tell me.
That makes sense.
Maybe I should've accepted
the reward when he offered it.
Before I forget,
he asked me to give you this.
What is this?
He said you should go there.
Hey, woman. Stop right there.
Did you think
we'd just let you go peacefully?
You think divorce is a joke?
Listen, a man and a woman--
That hurts!
-Hey!
-Watch it!
Goodness.
You're too tough for a woman!
You'll have a rough life!
Like mother, like daughter!
Her mother returned
after being dragged away to Qing,
but she didn't even end her life!
You are a disgrace to our village!
A disgrace!
My friend.
You've worked hard.
Well done.
Goodness.
Are you leaving now?
Child.
What is this?
They're trumpet creeper seeds.
They're precious flowers
that nobles plant in their yard.
Do you know what this flower symbolizes?
Honor.
They say that even the southern skies
could not stop this flower from blooming.
I'll be rooting for you.
Never bend to someone else's will
or give in.
Take care of yourself.
Thank you.
Of course.
Jo-yi!
You've worked hard!
Take care!
You made the right decision!
Don't ever come back here!
Fly away freely like a butterfly
and live a good life!
My lord.
-Hello, there.
-This way.
Make way.
I heard this scumbag
is going to hold a banquet.
Why make a fuss with banquets and whatnot?
We have a banquet every month.
It's different this time
because there's a reason.
A reason?
Tae-seo successfully
pulled off cupellation.
Cupellation?
Isn't that when you separate
pure silver from silver ores?
Is that true?
Congratulations!
How could the King look down
on that precious technology?
Isn't Tae-seo much better than the King?
Of course, he is.
Getting Joseon in your grasp
is just a matter of time.
Isn't the King
so pathetic?
He has no idea
what's going on in the world.
He just sits on his throne
trying to hold onto that position.
Father, I'm glad you are here--
Nobody move.
I need all of you here
to humiliate him.
-Father.
-Shut up!
If any of you were foolish enough to think
that you could gain scraps
by sticking around him,
remember what you just saw.
Father…
Father.
I was the fool
for putting a punk like you to work,
thinking you'd be useful.
I have no idea what you mean.
If I told you to steal something,
you shouldn't have left even
a trace of a breath behind.
Thanks to you, the idiot
that forgot to clean up after himself,
rumors about a warehouse
in the south being robbed
are running rampant.
It'll be better
if I bury you myself, don't you agree?
Father, I…
For you…
I did everything
you asked me to do.
I told you to do it with no loose ends!
I hear a secret royal inspector
was murdered
and the ledger is lost.
The next inspector from Hongmungwan
will be after you now.
Want to know what I think?
I think it'll be best
if you take the fall for everything,
let the inspector take you away,
and disappear from the world.
Tae-seo.
Don't disappoint your father.
My son.
Yes.
Father.
Get up!
Go and kill
the new secret royal inspector.
How can we find a secret royal inspector?
Just kill them all.
The secret royal inspector…
or someone that looks like one.
If I hear the inspector has returned
to Hanyang after fulfilling his duties,
all of you will be dead.
Why would you burn
these precious rice cakes?
Exactly. We should be
licking and sucking on them.
Come now. If you roast them like this,
they'll be crispy on the outside
and chewy on the inside.
It enhances the flavors.
That's roasted well.
Take out the soft persimmons
we got from Gaehwa Valley.
Soft persimmons?
Wait.
Here.
Why do that to the sweet persimmon?
See? You know how much
of a gourmet master I am.
It's good, isn't it?
Soft persimmons aid digestion
and are great for hangovers…
"Great for hangovers…"
He started another lecture.
No wonder he's a Hongmungwan official
who passed the state exam.
Doesn't every word
of the sentence sound annoying?
It has many benefits…
Go chew on some rocks,
you wicked bastards!
"Go chew on--"
Here.
Did the Crown Prince
enjoy soft persimmons as a snack, too?
What?
It's already been over a year
since the Crown Prince left us.
He's not gone.
I still see him often.
Every night, in my sleep.
Who else would I dream about
but the Crown Prince?
Brother!
You were always by my side.
He was the one
who saved my life in the war.
I cherish this man
more than my real brother.
Even when he returned to Joseon
after nine years
of being held hostage in Qing,
I was
the first person he asked for.
-He always…
-Your Highness.
put me first.
His Highness…
protected me.
But I…
wasn't able to protect him.
I'll be taking a nap.
Wake me up in a short while.
We need to pass that hill
before nightfall.
Have you decided on our next destination?
We'll be heading to Gongjinchang,
where the grain
from the freighter came from.
I'm sure this is the way to the dock…
But what are you going to do
after you get divorced?
I'll go to Hanyang.
I heard that at the dock,
there's a large ship that goes to Hanyang.
There must be a lot of nobles in Hanyang.
I will be able to make money
by making clothes for the ladies.
You know I'm pretty good
at making clothes.
Can't you just forget
about getting a divorce
and just put up with your husband?
No, I don't want to do that.
I don't want to live like this anymore.
And above all else,
I want to find my mother.
But Bo-ri,
before even beginning my fresh start,
I think I'm lost.
Giddy up!
My lord.
I don't think
this is the way.
How is this a path for people?
It clearly leads to the afterlife.
If we take the path that most people take,
we might come across a tiger.
Are you sure
you're going in the right direction?
Do not worry. Here.
Once we get past this hill,
we'll see a path.
Maybe this isn't the right way.
What?
Bo-ri.
There's a shrine here. Isn't that cool?
Someone even lit the candles.
Right.
It'd be better to rest here
than to wander around out there.
I'm sure the spirits will look after me
if I stay close to the shrine.
Excuse me for a moment.
These are all wishes made by people?
Everyone is desperate.
Fly away freely like a butterfly
and live a good life!
Never bend to someone else's will
or give in.
You regained your life yourself
with your courage.
Why…
Why did I think about Bang-deuk?
I must have gone crazy.
It's because I was in a weird position.
Let's lie down. That'll be better.
I must be losing it.
This isn't like me at all.
Found it!
I found it! Finally!
We almost died
because you have no sense of direction.
But we made it. We're alive!
If he wasn't our lord,
I would've killed him on the spot.
But we're alive!
We're alive!
What?
We're alive. That's all that matters.
-Gu-pal, run!
-Yes.
You punks. Stop right there!
You punks.
Stop right there!
-Gu-pal, run!
-Yes.
Stop right there!
What is it? Where is it? Who is it?
You're…
Bang-deuk…
Royal Inspector?
So…
you were sleeping here?
By yourself?
I was just taking a short break
because I didn't know where to go,
but I guess I fell asleep
because I was so tired.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
No matter how tired you are,
you can't fall asleep in the mountains.
You'd be in danger
if you ran into thieves or wild animals.
After all you've been through
to get a divorce,
how could you sleep
in front of a creepy shrine like this?
Right.
Thank you for making Bo-ri's--
Yes, it's a shrine!
So that's why.
Pardon?
Well…
Are you not aware?
What? What is it this time?
This is why I have no choice
but to lecture you all.
What? What did we do now?
Yes, my lord.
What do we not know this time?
If there's a divorced woman
standing in front of a shrine,
the first man she comes across
must take her to be his wife.
That's the custom in Joseon.
It's called seubcheob.
-Seubcheob?
If that man is not married,
he must marry the divorced woman.
If the man is already married,
the divorced woman becomes his concubine.
I had no idea.
That's right! I've heard of that before.
Then, were you waiting here,
hoping to find someone to remarry?
What?
No, of course not.
That's not it. I was just taking a break.
I didn't even think about seubcheob.
The ink on my divorce papers
hasn't even dried yet.
Then again,
there's no reason to abide by that custom.
How dare you! It's a serious crime!
If you break a custom,
you could be dragged
to the Uigeumbu and flogged.
Are they that strict?
I didn't know that.
-The law is really quite scary.
-Yes.
Flogging…
But thank goodness,
no one has passed by until now.
Hold on, if no one
has passed by until now,
-we're the first.
-Yes.
Lord Yi-eon was the first man?
Yes.
Wait.
The first man that she comes across
becomes her husband.
-That's what he said…
-That's not it. Listen, you punk.
Then what?
Are you saying Lord Yi-eon must…
marry her or something?
Is that what you mean?
-I see it now. I apologize.
-What nonsense is that?
Have you gone insane?
You're talking nonsense.
That's hilarious.
That's so funny.
What did I do wrong?
Seubcheob? Why is this happening?
No.
-This is…
-Please pretend you didn't see.
-Why out of all people…
-I can't.
-I can't remarry.
-No.
-Please pretend you didn't see.
-Maybe I'm not the first person.
-Maybe not.
-I can't do this.
-I'm not.
-I won't remarry.
-This is invalid.
-Please.
-Right.
-Hear my prayers.
This is invalid.
How many times is he going to repeat that?
Hear my prayers…
Let's pretend this never happened.
We never met here. What do you think?
We all saw it. How can we lie about that?
Earlier you were like,
"It's a serious crime!"
"You could be dragged to
the Uigeumbu and flogged!"
That's what you said.
Besides, he's a public official.
He can't break the law.
I was just talking to myself.
Why are you eavesdropping?
I can't.
Why me?
Why did you have to lie down there?
It's not like I wanted to be here.
I was lost and taking a short break.
And I didn't hear you coming
because I fell asleep.
Hold on.
Then why did you have to
walk in front of the shrine?
When there are a lot of other paths.
And why did you have to trip over my leg?
Who was the one who hurtled
screaming when I was sleeping?
Well, that's…
Fine.
I apologize for stepping on your leg.
But…
I have no intention of getting married!
I even forced myself
to take the difficult state exam
because I didn't want to get married.
My grandmother went
on a hunger strike for six days,
telling me to either
get married or take the exam.
That's why I had no choice
but to choose the lesser of two evils.
-That's true.
-Yes.
He did.
Do you understand now?
Do you understand now
what I despise the most in this world?
Then,
do you know what I despise
the most in this world?
It's not my forced marriage
or the divorce I barely got.
It's remarrying a man I'm not in the least
attracted to who's arrogant and selfish!
She called him arrogant.
And selfish.
Fine. I understand.
Let's never cross paths again.
Yes. Why would we ever meet again?
-My point exactly!
-My lord!
My lord!
Don't move. You'll be dead if you do.
Collect all their bags.
And tie them up with some ropes.
-Okay!
Who are you people?
My goodness, what a temper. Damn it.
How is a woman so strong?
She might be stronger than a man.
Do you know who this is?
This man is…
Who else could he be?
Your husband.
-No!
What?
What do you mean no?
We heard you talking
about seubcheob in front of the shrine.
-Was I the only one?
-We all heard it.
-We're the witnesses.
-I heard it, too.
All these people saw and heard it,
so stop lying!
Listen…
I'll bury you together
like the seubcheob couple you are.
Let's bury them quickly and leave.
-Okay!
-How dare you!
-Hold on.
-I didn't move.
-Let go of me!
Let go of me!
Can't you just tell them
you're a secret royal inspector?
No, I can't.
It'll set back the investigation.
Since when did you have a sense of duty?
We're all about to die!
Show them the horse plaque
and yell at them now.
I can't reveal my identity!
-To find the culprit--
-Reveal your identity first,
then you can look for the culprit.
Then why bother
hiding identities in the first place?
Hey.
Hey, Brother!
Did you eat?
Yes. How's your eldest?
He's growing up so well.
What are you doing down there?
We're digging a hole.
To bury them.
They were in front
of the shrine for seubcheob,
so we robbed them.
By the way, where are you going
in this pitch darkness?
Are you on your way to catch
an inspector like last time?
Watch your mouth
and make sure you bury them well.
Or the bodies will pop out when it rains.
And if you see anyone escaping
from the merchants, bring them to me.
Let's go.
Okay.
Good luck.
Why are you so heavy?
It's all done.
-Are you all right?
-Do I look okay?
I'm not okay, either.
It looks like they're really
going to bury us alive.
What do we do now? Do something!
My goodness!
Thanks to our unprepared lord,
I'm about to die as a bachelor!
Our lord? We're about to die.
Who cares about our lord?
I met the wrong lord.
You're still young.
-How is he a lord?
-I'll die as a bachelor!
Be quiet. Let me think.
Hello?
Hey!
What just happened?
Was my yelling that scary?
A tiger must have shown up.
-A tiger.
-No, it wasn't an animal.
Then what could it be?
You're scaring me even more.
We need to get out of here first.
Let's cut this rope first.
I need your help.
You need to do it.
If you reach inside my robe,
you should find a vernier. Hurry.
We don't have time. Just do it.
All right.
Excuse me for a moment.
I got it.
I modified it just in case.
-Now open it.
-Okay.
Good.
That's right. You punks.
You never need to worry
about our Lord Yi-eon, you punks!
Exactly. Our lord is fully prepared.
Right, my lord?
-Are you all right?
-Yes, I'm fine.
Let's go.
My lord.
What about us?
Why would I?
You said I wasn't your lord anymore.
It hurts.
Come on, my lord. Just this once.
I can't believe these guys.
Almost.
There we go!
Grab it.
Hurry up and grab it.
Climb up now.
Hurry.
How is your grip stronger than a man's?
Our lord's hands are delicate as ferns.
Try carrying around the water jug
and doing laundry and housework.
You end up with a strong grip.
Is housework that hard?
You punks. Stop blabbering.
Help me too!
-What's wrong?
-Look…
-Over there.
-Where?
You're about to be completely exposed
because he couldn't
take care of one inspector.
My mother is also a hwanhyangnyeo.
I want to help out in any way I can.
Ruffians working with the merchants
are controlling the village, and
are all armed with swords.
Those bastards are completely insane.
We must acquire concrete evidence.
Pretty Girl, where are you from?
We must teach a lesson to brats like her.
Do not insult my wife.
Who are you?
I don't think he is one of us.
Who are you? Tell me!