ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCALES, AND EVENTS ARE USED
IN AN ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS MANNER
AND NOT BASED ON HISTORICAL FACTS
He's putting on a show.
The inspector is putting on
a show with the traveling entertainers.
Bi-ryeong…
I apologize, my lord.
Bi-ryeong sometimes
gets possessed by spirits.
It's all right, Bi-ryeong.
Did you just say that he was putting on
a show with the entertainers?
Did I say that?
Do you remember
the date of the boss' birthday?
He was born in the year of the red dog,
the month of the blue horse,
on the day of the black tiger…
Oh, that's in two days.
-Traveling entertainers.
Let's sneak in pretending
to be traveling entertainers.
I had the same thought.
Then we'll go to the marketplace
and look for traveling entertainers.
-Now?
-Let's go.
-What?
In the meantime,
I'll go and arrest Hong Seok-gi.
I bet
you and the inspector must've had
a deep connection in a past life.
You think so?
Deep connection? Please.
Just find the traveling entertainers.
They should be here already.
Why not? You two seem to get along well.
Plus, didn't you meet him
for seubcheob at the shrine?
Seubcheob?
So you two are married by seubcheob?
No. We decided that never happened, so no.
You're lucky to have run
into an inspector at the shrine.
I heard some wait
for inspectors by their routes.
But it wasn't my intention--
Was it nice?
What?
They must be over there!
Here they are.
They're so popular
that we didn't even have to search.
You punk!
How dare you pretend
to be a relative of mine
and deceive the officials?
A horse plaque?
As if being a widower wasn't sad enough,
I now have to chase
after some useless brats.
How am I supposed to find
that Jo-yi, Jo-raeng, or whatever?
What?
My goodness.
Look at you all enjoying yourselves.
Hooray!
Coming through!
Hurrah!
Wait, that's…
I was wondering where I'd find that brat.
The deities are smiling upon me today.
Hey, you brat!
Where is the ledger?
Hand over the ledger!
Officer?
Come with me.
What's going on?
Bo-ri?
My goodness.
What? Are you Bo-ri?
Did he just say ledger?
Help!
I'll get straight to the point.
I looked over the records
of the grain tax transported
and saw an entry regarding the freighter
that sank off the coast of Gaehwa Valley.
According to the entry,
the freighter was sucked
into a storm before sinking.
Is it true that no one drowned
or went missing?
Luckily, a warship nearby found them,
and the sailors rescued everyone.
Is that so?
The navy vessel records
for the day the freighter sank
show that not a single warship
set sail that day.
Not a single warship set sail that day,
so how is it possible
that they were rescued by sailors?
Who is it?
Who destroyed the evidence,
aided the murder,
and is now trying to cover up
the truth behind this whole incident?
You are under arrest for embezzling
tributes and destroying evidence.
Tie him!
-Yes, sir.
Father was very worried about you.
But you should either find
the ledger or take care of the inspector
before you do if you want to face him.
Are you inside?
Let me do it for you.
Your Excellency.
Now that you've become an adult,
you should contribute something
to the family.
Therefore…
What is this?
It's a hat strap
with our family crest engraved.
I'm not worthy…
of such…
It signifies
that you have a duty and responsibility
to ensure our family's prosperity.
Do you understand?
My son.
Yes.
Father.
What about the brat?
We lost her.
That damn inspector
showed up out of the blue. Damn it.
I must catch the inspector myself.
Yourself?
Wait, you've never gotten
directly involved before.
I just changed my mind.
Is it because of that brat?
Or is it because of Do-soo?
No way.
Don't tell me you really
consider him your brother.
The nobles do not consider you
as one of their own at all.
They have children
with slaves only to enslave them.
So if this is because of the man
you believe to be your father,
don't do it.
I just think it'll be fun.
That's all.
My lord.
How about sending him
to the provincial office?
If you can't trust them either,
sending him to the station house
could be safer for protecting the witness.
My lord. I think you should at least
move somewhere protected by armed guards.
I will see this through myself this time.
Come on!
Turn! There you go.
No. With your arms.
Try again.
That's it. Nice.
Well done.
My lord.
These are the traveling entertainers
for the boss' birthday party.
I lured them here
by offering free lodging.
Well done.
I'm sure it wasn't easy to persuade them.
Is that Hong Seok-gi?
Then he must be involved in Bo-ri's death.
Involved? I didn't kill anyone!
Inspector.
You got the wrong person.
I admit that I pocketed
a bit of the tribute,
but I never murdered anyone.
If I could,
I would cut myself open
and show you my heart.
You want to show him?
That's good to hear.
Why don't we go inside?
I have to show you something.
Let's go.
You're here.
Officer?
He's the Gaehwa Valley Officer.
Why is he here?
He was also looking for the ledger.
Did you tie him up on your own?
We got help from the entertainers.
You're right on time.
It's time.
But all of you need to remain quiet.
What's with the bell
and what are the things on the box for?
That's a jewoong.
We're going to use that
to make him confess.
You little…
You are all much too superstitious.
This is why people need to study.
How could you have
blind faith in old folk beliefs--
Ask me anything.
It's working!
Ask him about the ledger.
The spirit asks you.
Tell us everything you know
about the ledger now.
The ledger…
I received orders from the boss
and went to Bo-ri's tavern
to look for the ledger.
Hey! Stop it right now!
I went…
I went there and came across a woman.
It was a big woman named Jang Pat-soon.
She lured me into her house.
I told her that I had
to return to the office,
but she tried to force me
to spend the night.
She stuck her lips out
and breathed hot air onto my nape…
This isn't going to work.
Change the question.
Just tell us everything you know!
Everything…
Tell you everything?
My family is from Chungcheong Province.
The year my father turned 20,
he married the daughter
of the station house and had me.
My surname is Mi and my name is An-hae.
Mi An-hae.
He really is telling us everything.
-Make him stop.
-Stop.
One long bar of rice cake
and two rice ball cakes…
-I said stop!
-The one in the middle…
Why isn't he stopping?
I don't really know how to stop them yet.
-So you can't stop him?
-A dream that predicted a son…
That's how, on July 7th,
when I turned 18,
I met the first woman I had ever loved,
but our relationship did not last.
To tell you the reason,
one day she came up to me
and said sorry
with a very serious look on her face.
I wasn't sure if she was apologizing
or calling out my name.
I thought I lost them all,
but here they are.
Goodness, these traveling performers
just do whatever they want.
-They're completely out of control.
-The rookies, too.
If we don't check on them again later,
it'll be a complete mess.
Just let them be.
We found a way to sneak
into the mountain base thanks to them.
Try to be understanding and generous.
Why is he so obsessed with being generous?
If we keep being generous like this,
we might end up sleeping on the streets.
You worry too much.
That won't ever happen.
Anyway, my lord,
is there really no other way
than to enter the mountain base?
I hear it's quite a scary place.
It's a place we must go through
to acquire evidence.
But they all know our faces.
Is that going to be okay?
That's why we're disguising ourselves
as entertainers.
If you're still so worried,
put on more makeup.
No.
Fine, let's say we'll manage
to get past the gatekeeper, then what?
With no backup forces and just performers.
My point exactly.
Please think it over once more, my lord.
If we end up getting caught…
Hence, I need one of you
to go to Hoehyeon-dong.
Hoehyeon-dong is where
the crown prince's home is.
Are you planning to call them here?
Then I'll go since I'm fast.
I'm faster than you. I'll go.
-I'm faster.
I'm older, so of course, I'm faster.
My lord.
My lord?
Since I'm going,
I'll go see what she needs.
My goodness.
Damn it.
You don't have a room to sleep in?
The entertainers took every single room,
so there's no room left for us.
Dozens of young men went into the rooms
and fell asleep, so there's no room left.
What do you mean?
I apologize, my lord.
I knew this would happen
when he kept going on about generosity.
Then let's give this room to the ladies.
-We should--
-No!
We should what?
Sleep out in the yard?
I can't do that.
You can do that if you want.
I'm going to sleep in this room.
You can sleep out in the yard if you wish.
I was going to say
we should go sleep at the tavern.
Forget it, then.
I was thinking about
buying you rice wine at the tavern.
Rice wine? Wait.
Then can we also get
the boiled meat you promised?
Don't bother.
We're here because
we already went and had no luck.
Maybe it's because we're near the dock,
but every tavern is full.
There's no room left.
Now what?
Well,
how about we share the room
as we do at taverns?
Nobles like you might find it unpleasant,
but it's something pretty common for us.
I apologize if I've offended you, my lord.
I didn't want you
to experience unnecessary trouble.
Our lord is slightly, very slightly picky.
But he's quick to accept things
if it seems reasonable.
He has the heart of a saint.
The noblest of all nobles.
Right, my lord?
Fine.
We shall do that.
If everyone else does it,
why can't I?
-Let's go inside.
-Yes.
Thank you.
By the way,
you have somewhere to go,
don't you Yook-chil?
Gu-pal. You're right.
You're much faster.
Hurry up.
Have a safe trip.
Thank you, Gu-pal.
I'll go and get some water then.
We'll have no choice but to stick together
because the room is small.
Therefore, you should stick to the wall.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Turn the lights off and lie down.
Tomorrow will be even busier than today.
You should go ahead and sleep.
I'm going to get some fresh air.
Wait
What are you doing right now?
Don't worry.
I'll make sure not to cross this line.
My lord.
Are you asleep, my lord?
My lord?
Unbelievable.
How could you be still in bed?
The sun is high up in the sky.
Put these on and come out quickly.
There you go.
Gu-pal, you're pretty good at that.
I can tell that you're a shaman
from the way you hop around.
Your spiritual powers
are a bit unstable though.
Gwang-soon.
Look.
Did you see how high that went up?
There are a total of 29 entertainers,
27 excluding the kids.
Three different colors per person,
that's 81.
If we include the 5 of us,
we're going to need 96.
There's one missing…
Oh, here it is.
"The five of us"?
Why are you going? It's dangerous.
No one knows Cha Mal-jong better
than I do, so I'm sure I'll be helpful.
This isn't about reading or calculating.
A sword fight might break out.
Stay out of it.
This is a chance to end Cha Mal-jong
and you're telling me to stay out of it?
If I was going to stay out of it,
I would've never gotten off the ship
when I saw the ledger.
Just go, Yook-chil!
Gosh.
Damn it, you scared me!
When did you get here?
It's your birthday today, Maeng-su.
Are the preparations
for the party going well?
-Where's Tae-seo?
-Tae-seo?
He's probably training somewhere.
There he is.
Hong Seok-gi was arrested.
That inspector even arrested Hong Seok-gi?
It's only a matter of time
before he opens his mouth.
Hold on.
How did he know
that Hong Seok-gi was involved?
That must mean
that the inspector found the ledger.
How did that punk find the ledger
when we couldn't
even after ransacking Gaehwa Valley?
The brat from Gaehwa Valley
must've had it.
I should've killed them
when I had the chance.
Wait.
Now that Hong Seok-gi's been caught,
this place isn't safe.
Goodness.
Let me do it.
This is quite difficult to tie by myself.
You can't even do this by yourself?
How did you…
First, take this strap.
Start from your right shoulder and wrap it
to the left side of your waist,
and then tie it here.
Then, you take this
and start from the left shoulder.
You wrap it
to the right side of your waist,
crossing them before tying it
in the middle of your waist.
Lastly,
you take this strap…
and wrap it around your waist once
before tying them together
in the center of your back.
Then, you just let them hang.
It's easy, isn't it?
Let me do yours.
-It's fine. I can do it by myself.
-Wait.
How do you know how to do this?
Commoners participate in Durepungjang,
a festivity held every spring.
They wear three different colored straps
and pray for a good harvest.
I saw it a lot then.
You only saw others do it,
yet you condescend to me.
Even if I want to,
they don't let women join the performance.
Only men are allowed
to wish for a good harvest.
That's what condescension is.
That's why I must join the entertainers
this time and go to the mountain base.
Don't you dare leave me out
just because I'm a woman.
I won't.
But do not get hurt.
That's an order.
Thank you.
What about the silver for Gapbigocha?
We're mining the last bit.
It'll be done by today.
We'll take the promised silver
to Gapbigocha once the party is over.
You're going there yourself?
Han-gi is at Gokdu.
No, I'll deal the gunpowder myself.
We need to fast-track the plan.
Sure. There's no point in stalling.
It might be better to get it done sooner.
Han-gi will be so happy to see you.
Or will she be happier if Maeng-su goes?
No, that's not right.
Han-gi will be the happiest if I go.
Is it necessary to fast-track the plan?
-Since it's come to this…
-Can you just not do it?
Think about it.
We can live good enough lives
with the silver we get from here.
We didn't start this to get rich.
Contact Gokdu.
Let them know I'll deliver it in person.
All right.
Are you telling me to wear this?
Yes, put it on.
It suits you well.
Multi-color is the way to go
if you want to disguise yourself.
Oh, my.
There's our nobleman.
It suits her well.
You look great.
A nobleman needs a beard.
Let's put on this beard.
Good.
My lord, hurry up and put it on.
Let's put this on top of your head.
Goodness, you look pretty.
It suits you well.
You should position your legs like this.
Swing right and left as you walk forward.
Like this.
Nobleman. Let's see you give it a go.
You didn't mean me.
Go on.
Nobleman, watch carefully.
You open your fan like this
and become bow-legged.
Come out and greet me!
-Well done.
-Thanks.
-You're set. You can go back.
-Okay.
My lord, come on out.
Fine.
Please do it right.
Like this.
Like this…
I think he needs to do more than that.
Oh, dear.
My lord. Like this.
How can you not do it?
Do you expect a nobleman
to do something so foolish?
This isn't going to work.
Why don't you just go in with a mask on?
Yes.
That sounds good.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Yes. Didn't you see what I did with this?
A ship from Gapbigocha is coming in today.
I'll go out to the marketplace
in the evening.
I'll feel at ease once the peddlers
confirm that the children arrived safely.
All right.
But make sure to be careful.
I'll be fine.
Don't worry too much.
The soldiers will be here soon.
I'm counting on you.
Sure.
AGRICULTURE IS THE BACKBONE
OF THE COUNTRY
Let's go.
Let's go!
Why do you keep submitting petitions
when you know they'll be turned down?
If Hongmungwan has time on their hands,
they should help out in the kitchens.
A very important petition
regarding Chungcheong's Chief
of Maritime Transport came up.
Reports from
the dispatched royal inspectors
have been coming in one by one.
I was going to suggest an investigation
into the grain tributes to His Majesty…
You should have me,
the Chief State Councilor, deliver such
an important petition to His Majesty.
I will discuss it
with Saheonbu and Saganwon
and submit a joint petition
to His Majesty.
To avoid rejection.
Hongmungwan doesn't just
study public sentiment.
Even when a sword is held to our neck,
it is our only honor to promote
what is right for the nation
before succumbing to death.
Also…
we do indeed have some time to spare.
My goodness. Have you been well, sir?
-You're here.
-Yes.
I didn't see them last year.
I thought that you might get bored
if you saw the same show every year,
so this year, I brought
some Durepungjang and masked performers.
We prepared a very fun show,
so I'm sure you won't be disappointed.
Great.
This is well-made.
Leave me one when you leave.
Yes, of course.
-Let them in!
-Thank you, sir.
Let's go in!
We got in more easily
than expected, right?
Yes.
They said it was a really scary place,
but it's not that bad.
But the base seems too empty.
You're right.
My goodness.
You really go all out.
Gosh.
Let's see.
I just think it'll be fun.
That's all.
But how are you going
to catch that rotten inspector?
That bastard is no joke.
Unless he came here voluntarily.
He wouldn't dare come here.
That's true.
Breaking into
the Great Jade Emperor's palace
would be easier
than breaking into this palace.
It's possible once a year.
On just one day.
Right.
Maeng-su, we should go all out
for your birthday this year.
I'll have Pebble tail them.
Even a royal inspector
who passed the state exams
doesn't make the right call
every single time.
That system is just fundamentally wrong.
Does it make any sense
that a smart punk like Tae-seo
isn't even allowed
to take the state exams?
Still, this world of ours
subtly shows that it can be fair at times.
Even a ten-year-old child knows
how precious human life is.
You, who have abused children
and maltreated human lives,
have no right to speak of fairness.
And one more thing.
I passed the state exams…
Well…
for a reason.
Attack!
Who are these punks?
The crown prince's guards.
The crown prince's guards?
If they really are…
Then we're doomed.
They're Joseon's human weapons.
I'll take this. You search for evidence!
Yes, my lord.
This way!
Hey!
Why is a woman so unbelievably strong?
What's wrong with a woman so strong?
I think this is it.
Ledger…
Cha Mal-jong most likely
just left it out in the open.
Take a look.
Something that doesn't look precious.
Something he put out
as if it wasn't important at all…
Stop getting in the way.
You're the one who needs
to stop being distracted!
All right. Just stand behind me.
Do not back down!
Do-soo, you're back.
Are you hurt anywhere?
The inspector I told them to kill
keeps sending in reports.
Why is he still alive?
What on earth is Tae-seo doing?
That's why you shouldn't
trust Tae-seo with anything.
The Chief of Maritime Transport.
We must take care of him first.
Goodness.
Do-soo.
You need to go there one more time.
Go and pressure Tae-seo once more.
If those rotten bastards
from the Three Offices join forces,
Saheonbu might break in here
and search our house.
Father, I just got back from Chungcheong.
You should leave immediately.
Go and tell him to take care
of the Chief of Maritime Transport first.
All you need to do
is relay my message to Tae-seo.
Do not get involved. Do you understand me?
Here.
Not this one. That one.
All right. Here.
Hear me! Get a horse ready immediately!
But I just got back.
It's urgent.
Go and eat something tasty
on your way, all right?
Fine.
-Darn it.
-There.
I'll tell him to take care
of the Chief of Maritime Transport.
-Wait, Father.
-Yes? What is it?
Do you want more money?
No.
Can I go look around
Tae-seo's mountain base?
Mountain base?
Are you talking about Tae-seo's minions'
hideout deep in the mountains?
What for?
You know, Father,
I've always been curious
how Tae-seo has all that money to spend.
All the alcohol, parties,
and his lavish lifestyle…
How is all of that possible?
That's because of the tributes--
Wait a minute.
Did you figure out the source
of his hidden income?
I feel like I might find it this time.
All right.
Anything I find
at the mountain base will be mine.
Okay?
-I'll get going.
-All right. Be careful.
What now?
I think we're losing.
Find the tax ledger
before they do and leave.
The ledger. Right.
Ledger…
Damn it!
Retreat!
Tae-seo.
Stop right there!
My lord. If we go after them now,
we'll most likely be ambushed
by the mountain trail.
They're wounded,
so they won't get too far.
My lord, please help.
Are you all right?
I'm fine, but these people…
Let's treat the wounded first.
They're all exhausted,
so we should feed them.
Let's start with the wounded first.
Yes, sir.
My lord!
The ledgers! We found all the ledgers!
We also found all the hostages!
But what is all this? Where did they go?
They're all gone.
They all ran away.
We won!
If it were not for these ledgers…
Gwang-soon.
Did they always exist in Joseon?
I heard they're the crown prince's guards.
They're in charge
of protecting the crown prince.
So it goes without saying.
Gosh. They're indeed
the guards who protect the royal family.
Their martial skills
are spectacular and beautiful.
Not just martial arts skills.
Exactly. Their solid physiques,
the confident look in their eyes…
-Yes.
-Shoulders as broad as rafters.
Yes.
Did you see them fight earlier?
They were like…
They must be tired.
We should prepare some food for them.
Is the kitchen this way? That way?
All right.
This way.
Come this way.
Thank you so much for your hard work.
This way, please.
Rafters?
Both of you. Look at my shoulders.
If these aren't rafters, what are they?
I think I should go prepare some food.
If these aren't ridgepoles, what are they?
What are you doing? Hurry up!
What about the ledgers?
This is all I could get.
They had already taken the rest.
We must get them
or my father will be in trouble.
It's too late!
Luckily, I was able to get the ledger
that has your old man's name in it.
So don't worry.
Go to Gokdu
and postpone the gunpowder deal.
All right.
Let's go. We need to get away first.
Let's see.
Both of you, step aside.
This is my turf.
All right.
The ingredients
are especially fresh today.
-Should we start with draining the blood?
-Cut the tail off first.
Wait. Don't cut too much into the flesh.
Yes, Chef.
What are you doing right now?
Whole chicken soup.
What? No…
That's not what I meant.
I meant, why are you in here?
To cook, of course…
What?
You've never met a perfect man like me
who's handsome, intelligent,
and even knows how to cook?
You should leave
the physically demanding tasks to men.
Have you gone insane?
We need to put them in whole.
Why did you crush them?
Then again,
an old bachelor should know
how to cook if he doesn't want to starve.
Well, that's…
Good luck then.
But will it be even edible?
Our lord has a nasty temper,
but he excels in cooking and studying.
I see.
It's a relief he's good at something.
We'll go assist the others then.
-Good luck!
-But Jo-yi, we should still…
-We can't just…
-Come on.
"An old bachelor…
with a nasty temper".
Me?
-Yes, sir!
I wasn't asking you two!
-Yes, sir.
You little…
Yes, sir.
How dare you!
Are you still trying to
do something foolish in this situation?
I'm watching your every move.
Every one of them.
Move an inch and I'll teach you a lesson.
My lord.
Right.
-Be careful.
-Yes, sir.
-It's ready.
-Give us some, too.
-Sure. Just a moment.
-Yes.
Coming right up.
It's coming right up.
-Here you go.
-Thank you for your patience.
-Thank you.
-No worries.
My lord.
This is the last one.
All right.
You two should eat, too.
Yes, sir.
-Let's go.
-Yes, sir.
It's getting cold. Hurry.
My goodness.
This meat just melts in your mouth.
This place has good chicken soup.
What a surprise.
The broth is the best
for restoring energy.
-Eat up.
-We will.
Enjoy your meal!
-Thank you, my lord.
It's delicious.
-You should eat first.
-No, I…
My goodness, but I can eat later.
Where did Jo-yi go?
Yook-chil.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you, my lord.
It's hot!
Are you all right?
It's not hot. Not at all.
It's not hot at all.
Here you go.
It must be hot.
Eat slowly, Gu-pal.
You'll get indigestion!
There's only one drumstick.
I can't eat this.
Don't worry. I can have this.
There must be mosquitoes
because we're in the mountains.
Enjoy the drumstick.
My lord.
Are you not eating?
This looks so good!
It's specially seasoned
with sesame seed oil and soy sauce…
It's even seasoned.
Her eating habits are rather rough.
I've never seen this much meat in my bowl.
What are these?
Taffy.
Taffy?
ALL SCENES INVOLVING ANIMALS
WERE SAFELY STAGED
The crown prince
beseeched us to protect you.
I must figure out where
the entrance to Baekgwiryeong is.
No, you can't.
Where do you think you're going alone?
You sound like his wife or something.
They did every bad thing they could
by colluding with government officials.
What's up there?
I heard there's something
that explodes when you step on it.
I could blow up something even bigger
to catch the inspector.
How many murder cases
have there been in just one month?
Please get to the bottom of this mystery,
my lord.
I promise I will at all costs.