ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCALES, AND EVENTS ARE USED
IN AN ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS MANNER
AND NOT BASED ON HISTORICAL FACTS
Back then and even now,
the one who failed
to catch or stop me was you.
I was able to acquire
this precious inkstone.
To gift this to Your Majesty,
I rushed over--
Your Highness.
Your Highness!
No… How did this happen?
Let me escort you to your royal chambers.
I'm fine.
My goodness. Please let me.
Careful.
Back then and even now,
I am
incompetent…
and unable to
protect anyone.
Let's go!
Oh, dear.
Fire.
-Fire!
OIL
-Oh, no!
-Fire!
Everything is burning!
Who's going to catch them?
What is happening?
Get some water!
Move him into a room and treat his wounds.
It seems he lost a lot of blood.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Come with me.
Yes.
Escort them.
Heat up the room and some water.
Yes, ma'am.
That's blood.
Seeing blood isn't anything special
for a butcher like me.
What about you? Are you all right?
Thank you for saving…
my friends.
I didn't do it to hear that.
Make sure you keep your word.
At the end of this month, a ship I do
business with will dock at Gapbigocha.
I'll help you get on that ship.
Okay. I'm counting on you.
You
kept your word and didn't take any lives.
Thank you.
The prisoners have escaped,
so you will be the first one they suspect.
They'll start chasing you soon.
Perhaps you should
get some sleep while you're here.
I don't have the slightest intention
of taking care of you for long.
You've been through so much.
Mother.
DISTRIBUTION LOG
I have kept a distribution log
of all the bribes
that I have given Lord Park Seung.
DISTRIBUTION LOG
My lord.
They say that Park Tae-seo
managed to escape the execution.
Father.
Yes.
Yes, my son?
Do-soo, you're awake. What is it?
Tae-seo…
Is he not dead yet?
You don't need to be concerned about that.
I will take care of everything.
You just have to worry
about getting better.
Don't worry about anything else.
Nothing else.
This will not do.
I'll pay a visit to Banchon.
BANCHON: A VILLAGE OF SLAVES,
IT HAS A BUTCHER'S SHOP
I'll go there myself
to buy that thing you like…
and some meat as well.
All right.
I guess our lord is working late again.
Let's bring him these treats
to cheer him up.
Let's hurry.
He'll probably be
working through the night.
Hello, sir.
What are you doing here?
We have something
to deliver to Lord Ra Yi-eon,
-a busuchan of Okdang.
-And this, too.
He left the palace earlier,
so I assumed he was headed home.
Earlier today,
some criminals escaped the execution.
So he must be preoccupied.
What…
Escaped?
Bi-ryeong, get some rest.
My goodness. I told you to get some rest.
Jo-yi, I told you, I'm really fine.
It just hasn't hit you yet.
How exhausted your body must be.
You testified at a royal interrogation.
In front of the king, no less.
Put that away. Don't do it.
Well? Are you feeling okay?
-What?
-Are you?
Yes. I'm perfectly fine.
Really? I don't think you are.
You should be lying down right now.
-Hurry up and lie down.
-I'm really fine.
You're not. No! Don't get up.
Lie down. Down. Just lie down.
Okay.
You have so many orders.
Yes.
But thank goodness I have quick hands.
You don't just have quick hands,
you have superior talent.
There are even some noblewomen
offering to pay extra
to come to them first.
A noblewoman has even asked me
to write up a talisman.
Wait… You don't mean
Lord Choi's wife, do you?
Yes, that's her! That's me!
Jo-yi, we might really end up
buying this house at this rate.
Yes, I think if we pinch
and scrape just a bit more, we can!
Where's Gwang-soon?
What?
I have no idea. She's not back yet.
She did say she had
something to take care of.
Really?
Maybe…
she found herself
a lover at the trading group?
That would be great.
Anyhow, lie down for a bit.
I'll go get some ox blood
and cook you soup.
Jo-yi. I'm really fine.
There's no need for that.
That's enough!
Lie down and don't even think
about moving until I get back. Got that?
Okay.
I'll be back.
Is anyone home?
Who are you?
I…
I came to see a man…
by the name of Ra Yong-gyun
that lives here.
Is he in?
Ra Yong-gyun?
-I don't know anyone by that name.
-Pardon?
He used to live in this house.
He used to work at the Naeuiwon.
Are you sure you don't know him?
That insane physician?
Just physician.
I heard he moved
to some temple near Hanyang.
What?
Do you know the name of the temple?
Come on, how would I know that?
I heard the rumor ages ago.
Is that so?
-Get out!
-Father!
Why did you come back?
I told you to leave!
Why are you doing this, Father?
Leave at once.
Leave this house at once!
You know I have nowhere to go.
I've just gotten back from Qing.
You can't stay at this house.
Go on.
Go on and leave now!
Father,
are you ashamed
that I was dragged away to Qing?
Do you know why
I tried so hard to stay alive?
Do you know why I've come back
after everything I've been through?
It's because of you.
Because I'm all you have.
And you're all that I have.
I really fought tooth and nail
to make it back here alive.
But…
you're ashamed
that your daughter returned alive?
Yes.
So don't come back here.
Don't ever come back here again.
I am not ashamed of myself.
I will go live my life…
and never return here.
Take care of yourself.
But he's still my father.
I should go and see him.
A temple near Hanyang?
Let's go find him.
Let's do that.
Hello, my lord.
Give me your best beef.
Don't worry about the price.
Of course, my lord.
Do you have any ox blood?
Just wait a moment.
I'm already with another customer.
We actually slaughtered a cow recently
for a Seonggyungwan ritual.
I'll be right back.
Where have I seen him before?
Do you by any chance have any of that?
My son is feeling a bit weak.
-Would you like that as well?
-Yes.
Here, my lord.
That will be ten yang in total.
What did that man just buy?
If it's good for restoring energy,
I'll take one, too.
Do you even know what that is?
It's called a poppy capsule.
It's a drug fed to cattle
to reduce pain when they're slaughtered.
It's best not to get started on it.
This will be one poon.
Boil that meat well and feed it to Do-soo.
Yes, sir.
Do-soo!
Jo-yi, is that you?
Yes, I bought some ox blood.
It won't take long to cook it.
Don't come out.
-Jo-yi.
Yook-chil? Gu-pal?
What are you doing here so late at night?
By any chance, did our lord stop by here?
No. Why would he come here at this hour?
He's not here, either.
Maybe he's still in the palace.
He must be so busy
with all those criminals.
Well, the truth is…
Park Tae-seo, that damn bastard,
escaped from the execution site.
What?
We ran into some officers
on our way to Okdang
to bring him food
because we thought he was on night duty.
They said he definitely left for the day,
but he hasn't come home yet.
Then where did he go?
You don't think…
he's still chasing after the criminals
by himself, do you?
So?
Were you able to catch me with that truth?
Back then and even now,
the one who failed
to catch or stop me was you.
I knew it from the start.
I knew
that you would do exactly as I expected.
We must find him.
Yes. We must find him immediately.
But you don't know where he is.
We must find him
even if we have to search everywhere.
Oh, right.
Cook this and have it with Bi-ryeong.
-Okay?
-Wait…
-This is…
-The perfect beef…
With a deep meaty aroma…
-This the best quality beef!
-This is for the young master.
-Okay.
What?
For letting the felons
escape their execution,
Chief Scholar Sim Tae-seon
shall be demoted two ranks
and Busuchan Ra Yi-eon
shall be removed from office.
Let's see.
So this is what a royal edict
of appointment looks like.
Hongmungwan is also called Okdang
because it's where precious
and elegant people work, right?
The most coveted government positions
appointed to the most distinguished…
Distinguished, my foot.
It's crap. Just crap.
As if a pathetic bastard like me
could ever…
So are you officially sacked now?
That's right.
I have been dismissed for good.
That's actually for the better.
Take this chance
to look after your health.
Or maybe this is my chance…
to open a dumpling place.
That sounds good to me.
I'll get to eat your dumplings every day.
Yes.
Sounds nice.
A life of making dumplings…
sounds so nice.
You run around like this all the time,
but you just end up
getting hurt more and more.
It's quite an unrewarding job.
Physical wounds will heal with time,
but what about the wounds in your heart?
Even if you work hard,
you achieve nothing.
Even when living isn't particularly fun,
you have no choice but to keep living.
How infuriating.
Sometimes,
I'm sick of it
the moment I wake up in the morning.
But it doesn't bring me
any closer to death.
I'd cry my eyes out,
but when the time came,
I would eat, sleep, and drink water.
I'm not sure…
if I can get back on my feet again.
My lord.
I'm sure you'll get back on your feet.
Would you like to make a bet?
So close.
Can you do it for me?
That was amazing. My lord!
It fell down!
How did you do it in one go?
My lord!
My lord, I made it this far.
It's your turn.
It seems that I have won.
That was too close.
Let's go for one more round.
I got you!
You're it, my lord!
You're it!
I'm going to get you, my lord!
I'm so tired.
Even if you tell me
you're going to grill me to eat,
I can't run anymore.
How out of shape you must be
to be so out of breath
when we didn't even run that much.
You're the one to talk.
What about you?
I can even see
the whites of your eyes right now.
That's impossible.
I'm perfectly fine.
Jo-yi.
Yes?
Today's competition…
I won all three rounds.
Do you know something?
You…
called me by my name
for the first time today.
I was only called a wretch,
a rotten brat, and a wench all the time…
but after meeting you,
I became Kim Jo-yi.
My lord!
I know that you're here, my lord!
Come on out, my lord!
Found you.
You're it now, my lord.
Why are you just standing there?
Have you never been it before?
You now have to chase me down.
You need to start over.
Can't I…
just remain in hiding?
just not come out?
You can't.
Didn't you say you were going to show me?
I will catch those bad guys
and show you
that not everything was in vain.
Show me that.
So what if you fail?
So what if something goes wrong?
I like you…
So what's there to be afraid of?
Okay.
For you…
I will start over.
The sky is so beautiful tonight.
Well, then…
Get back safely.
Okay. Go on inside.
Okay. I hope you have
sweet dreams tonight.
Okay.
Sweet dreams.
By any chance…
I'm just feeling a bit bloated.
Is there any walking trail around here?
It just so happens
that I'm also feeling indigestion
and want to take a walk.
-Would you like some company?
-Sure.
Then, I'll go on inside.
Okay. You should really go inside now.
Okay.
-By any chance…
-Yes?
Did you see our poster on the way here?
I think I didn't.
Did it fall off? Where did it go?
Should we go and check together?
Yes.
Go on inside now.
Okay.
-By any chance…
By any chance…
Then, I'll really, really go inside now.
Okay, go on inside now, really now.
Okay. I really hope you get home safely.
Noodles…
Do you want some before you go?
Noodles?
Noodles…
Noodles sound nice.
The fire in the furnace…
was just started,
so it'll get warm in no time.
Okay.
Make yourself at home.
Here.
Noodles…
I'll hurry up and make some.
Okay.
My lord.
Young Master.
Hey.
Why aren't you sleeping?
How could we sleep when you were
nowhere to be found? Are you okay?
We were absolutely worried sick
while looking for you.
I'm sorry about that.
Anyhow, thank goodness you're okay.
You should've let us know you were back.
You're right. I should have.
Oh, right. Did you meet Jo-yi?
She went out to look for you.
She hasn't come back home yet too,
so they're panicking as well.
I guess we just missed each other.
Anyhow, you're not hurt, right?
You're okay?
Yes. I'm really fine.
I'm not hurt at all.
That's good to hear.
So stop following me around
and go to sleep already!
The noodles at this hour?
Two bowls, at that.
I ended up making too much. That's all.
But why are there two sets of chopsticks?
My lord, don't tell me they are…
What?
They must be for us.
Your generosity knows no bounds.
I was actually getting hungry.
-What?
-Thank you for this.
Thank you.
-Let's go.
-Our Young Master is the best.
-I agree.
Damn annoying punks…
Well…
Let's have noodles some other time.
It's fine.
Young Master,
is someone in there with you?
Young Master?
He fell asleep already.
How tired he must have been.
Sleep well, Young Master. Let's go.
Enjoy.
Thank you for the food, my lord.
From the noodles,
-I can feel his love for us.
-Yes.
It's made with so much love.
He could have never made this
for someone else.
-Even for a woman.
-Of course not.
It'd never be this good.
His noodles are so good.
He's such a noodle enthusiast.
He really is.
What do we do now?
I wonder he ate some too.
Did you see him roll up
his sleeves to cook?
I think
you'll have to spend the night here.
So hot!
-It's hot!
-But it's so good.
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
Did you sleep well, my lord?
Waking up
together in the morning
like this is quite nice.
Yi-eon, are you inside?
I brought some honey…
Oh, no.
The honey has spilled…
-Grandmother?
-"Grandmother"?
Stop! Stop right there.
-My goodness.
-Catch me if you can!
Were you waiting there?
How is he?
He will live.
I'm the one who should suffer like that.
But that poor thing…
Who knew we would meet again like this?
We can't do anything
when it comes to destiny.
So,
what are you planning to do?
I don't know, either.
A part of me
doesn't see the point of telling him now.
But you're responsible for this twist,
so shouldn't you
be the one sorting it out?
It's a sin that I committed,
so I must wash it away myself.
That's retribution and fate.
The bastards that did this to you…
I'll make sure
to make them pay for it, so don't worry.
Father.
Yes? What is it?
Do you want to eat something tasty?
No, not something tasty.
Then, how about a new outfit?
I was actually planning
to get new socks made anyway.
Father.
I wasn't trying to rat you out
during the interrogation.
I know. I understand.
How scared you must have been to do that.
They took a sweet boy
and pushed him over the edge.
They're to blame.
There's no one
more despicable in this world
than a bastard who pushes one
to betray his own father.
I do not resent you, not one bit,
so don't worry.
But Father…
Yes?
What about Tae-seo?
Did they catch him?
They said the guards went after him,
but catching him isn't going to be easy.
Then what am I supposed to do?
I seriously can't sleep knowing
-that Tae-seo is alive.
-Yes. There, there.
I'll take care of that as well.
My son should be able to sleep well.
Then what about the inspector?
I think
he knows all about
what we did to the Crown Prince.
Father, I'm really scared.
I think he has evidence, too.
What if we really get caught?
Yes, yes. Stop crying. There, there.
Don't worry.
I have a plan in mind.
What's your plan?
They say that you should
keep your enemies closer.
Anyhow,
you don't worry about a thing.
Just focus on getting your health back.
When I was put in charge of this case,
I was also granted the authority
to oversee Gapbigocha.
I'll fix up Gokdu Trading Group's
buildings and let you use them.
I hear they have a spectacular view.
Then, is Gapbigocha ours now?
Instead of Chungcheong?
It's a bit smaller
than Chungcheong Province,
but it still has access to the sea,
so it should be quite lucrative.
That's my father for you.
The leader of the aristocracy,
the kingmaker,
and the true king
that controls the king like a puppet!
Oh, my baby.
My goodness. My baby. My sweet baby.
Sit down.
-Yes, ma'am!
What is your name?
It's Kim Jo-yi.
Miss.
Grandmother.
Great Madam?
My lady!
My lady.
Based on your attire,
I don't believe you are of noble birth.
That's correct. I am of the middle class.
Well…
Families are being torn apart by the war,
what does her class or family matter?
Do you wish to be kicked out?
You seem old enough.
Why haven't you gotten married yet?
Well…
You've just met her,
so asking
such personal questions is a bit…
I'm divorced.
What?
Divorced?
Are you saying you were kicked out?
She had her reasons.
Her ex-husband had huge gambling debts.
Are you the one that got a divorce?
I wasn't kicked out.
I filed a lawsuit to end my marriage.
Life with my in-law was difficult
and my husband was far from sweet.
Marriage isn't a child's play.
Of course, you come
across some difficulties.
It was beyond difficult.
It was closer to slavery.
What a novel sophistry.
Are you sure it wasn't due to
your lack of patience and tolerance?
That's also correct.
Yes, I'm quite hardheaded
and do not follow customs.
However, I also believe
the customs of this world are virtueless.
This world hates me
and calls me an audacious brat.
How could I have love for this country?
-Oh, that's…
-Yi-eon, you wait outside.
Did you not hear me? Go outside now.
If you have something to say,
you can say it to me.
-Jo-yi…
-My lord.
You should wait outside.
No.
I'll talk to Grandmother,
so you leave the room.
No.
I should be the one
who talks to her about this.
My lord!
You should come out for a second.
So, what do you plan on doing with Yi-eon?
I don't plan on doing anything.
I'm just staying by his side.
So what is your purpose
in staying by his side?
If you're hoping to marry him,
you may try so over my dead body.
I have no intention of marrying him.
When a woman gets married,
she is buried under customs and rules.
She loses her life and name.
I know that very well.
Therefore,
I want to live the rest of my life
as Kim Jo-yi and not as someone's wife.
I'm more than capable
of standing on my two feet.
I am looking after myself well
and making good money.
It's tough at times, but I'm very
much satisfied with my life now.
Such insolence…
Anyhow, what you're worried about
will never happen.
And above else,
I'm familiar with
our nation's rules of decorum.
I'm well aware of
how difficult a nobleman's life becomes
if he marries
a divorced middle-class woman.
I like Lord Yi-eon.
I do not wish to ruin his life.
If you knew that,
you should've kept your distance from him!
I'm not the only one with these feelings.
I like Lord Yi-eon,
and he likes me as well.
I think it's unfair for you
to only blame me for that.
My lord.
What is going on?
You were ordered to come to the court.
Come to the court?
But I have been dismissed.
Exactly.
What is this, some child's play?
It seems
there will be a special appointment.
What in the world is going on?
I'll make an announcement
on the king's behalf.
As punishment for mishandling the case
regarding Park Tae-seo and his mob,
Chief Scholar Sim Tae-seon
shall be demoted to Deputy Scholar,
and Busuchan Ra Yi-eon shall be
demoted to Scribe, Senior 8th Rank.
My lord.
I am appointed as Scribe?
I have been dismissed,
so I cannot be appointed.
Are you sure you're not mistaken?
You were reinstated
because His Majesty granted
the new chief scholar's plea.
The new chief scholar?
That will be all from me.
You can discuss the rest
with the new chief scholar.
My lord.
Heading to Western Xia
with my shadow as my friend…
This is paradise…
You can even feel
the touch of class in the air.
This is the great Okdang.
I have become the leader
of Hongmungwan as His Majesty wishes.
I, Park Seung, am the new chief scholar.
Such diligent public servants…
I see that your investigation
was quite thorough.
Well done.
Out of the six ministries and
three offices, this is where you end up?
There are 11 glorious positions
in Uijeongbu alone.
Why did it have to be here?
Show some respect!
I am your superior. How dare you!
What do you think you're doing?
This is what's interesting about life.
Some work hard to make the porridge,
and some other minister gobbles it up.
Wait.
Hey.
I know how you feel,
but you must not act rashly.
If you go after Park Seung now,
who knows what the repercussions will be?
We might end up getting executed!
He won't kill us.
Park Seung is having
so much fun toying with us.
Why would he kill us?
What are you planning to do?
I must find it.
I will start over.
Okay. Leave work early.
I'll cover for you.
Go.
Make sure you find it.
They collected so many useless things…
I should take them
to use as kindling at home.
-My lord.
-How did it go?
It was as I expected.
This is the best way
to get rid of all the evidence at once.
Lord Park Seung is smart.
Fortunately, Lord Yi-eon is smarter.
We almost lost all the evidence
that we've gathered.
PHARMACY JOURNAL
You two take this to Jinin Temple
and find out about the dead physician.
Yes, my lord.
I'll go to Gapbigocha and see
if I can trace Park Tae-seo's whereabouts.
It's time to counterattack.
THE SAFETY OF THE CHILD ACTORS
IN THIS EPISODE WAS PROPERLY ENSURED
SPECIAL THANKS TO
LEE JUN-HYUK AND JO KWAN-WOO
Can't you just
take your hands off this case?
I must close this case.
She said the socks are urgent
and asked for them to be made.
Is this Lord Park Seung's house?
I'm also looking for someone. My father.
I'll be by your side until you find him.
Jo-yi, I don't want you
to walk on a thorny path.
It's up to me
to decide to get married or not.
If you don't want to get married,
stop seeing that girl.
You can resent and regret it all you want.
That doesn't change the life you led.
Get out of my way!