He's here. He's here. He's here.
Duan Zhigang. Du Bin.
Hello. Hello.
Your dad? Yes.
He went out that night.
he never came back.
He died at the leopard beach
he died at the leopard beach.
Mom
Is there something you want to tell me? What is it?
I don't understand. I'm not sure. I'm not sure.
How did he know
how did my dad know
the three of them were at the leopard beach?
Yeah.
How did Tang Haojun know
you were at the leopard beach?
I was also confused.
But I thought about it.
Except the three of us and Director Yang,
only one
knows we're going to the leopard beach.
Not me
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Can you fool yourself?
I guess that night,
you not only told them where they were.
Yuzhen.
I'm going out.
Tang,
I heard Xu Chengliang
in the financial office today.
Du Bin and others
at the leopard beach tonight.
Go to bed early.
You went there with my dad's camera.
and took pictures of my dad's murder.
Linlin!
No.
You hurt my daughter.
is my life.
Tang!
Xu Chengliang.
What are you doing?
Do it!
Let go of me!
Not long after my dad left,
I found that photo at home.
The three of them were on it.
and my dad.
I can't remember.
That photo was...
Then I called the police with that photo.
It was pouring that day.
I couldn't see the road ahead.
I can't remember.
Let me think about it.
Mom.
I saw you that night.
You know Heo Chengliang so well.
Have you ever thought that my dad and the others
they won't come back?
Or is it because
because you were afraid
So you want to use Heo Chengliang to silence him.
Then you use the evidence of Heo Chengyeong’s murder
to force him to divorce.
you can be the wife
the wife of the chairman.
That photo
is more important than your daughter's life.
right?
No!
Linlin, no!
That's not what I thought.
No.
I guess you didn’t use it to force Heo Chengliang.
Otherwise, he wouldn’t let you live till now.
That day when I woke up at the beach,
I cried for the last time.
Since then,
there was only one thing left in my life.
is to avenge my dad.
It's been 15 years.
Every year on my dad's death anniversary,
on my dad's death anniversary.
It says "Return to Lost".
Turn yourself in and you'll be lenient.
I've been waiting for you for 15 years.
You never did that.
After I came back to Yujiang,
you know I live in danger every day.
You can stand up and end everything.
You didn’t do that.
After Du Bin died,
I was going to tell you the truth.
Are you pretending to be crazy?
That's when I knew
I would never
your path.
Linlin!
I'm sorry.
I really had no choice last night.
so I called you.
Please give me the photo.
I’ll use it to force him
to save Uncle Wang’s son.
I think a daughter
wants to see her for the last time.
It's not too much, is it?
It seems
to you.
Mom.
I do have one more ticket,
but it's not for you.
Because you have to stay here.
and pay back what you owe my dad.
Before Heo Chengliang finishes his confession,
before Heo Chengliang finished.
I've been wrong all my life.
Don't make mistakes again.
Mom!
Linlin!
We thought about
how to choose ourselves.
There was a typhoon that night.
We thought
there might be no evidence left at the scene.
So I rushed back immediately
to collaborate with Director Yang.
and destroyed all the accounts.
and blamed everything on that typhoon.
And then,
you knew everything.
Is there any letter from Qin Kaihui?
Almost.
Don't move.
Stay still.
What are you doing?
I'm telling you, there's someone up there.
I'll arrest you if there's no one.
Handcuff him.
Get him! Get him!
Don't move.
One more question.
You buried three bodies.
Why are they in the ground?
Why is Tang Haojun's body in the sea?
I really don't know.
I did bury all three of them.
Maybe it was washed away by the flood.
Or he didn't die.
crawling out of the pit,
and was pushed into the sea as a ghost.
Maybe.
What happened in the end?
What did you do with her?
I gave her some money
to get her off work.
Anyway,
we're on the same boat.
It's not easy to push him too hard.
You keep a close eye on her.
she won't call the police and get herself into trouble.
Forget it.
Master.
I need to answer a call.
What’s wrong, Liu?
Captain Li.
Qin Kaixuan is imprisoned by Xu Chengliang.
We found the place.
But he's not here anymore.
The man in charge told me
Xu Chengliang ordered Qin Kaihui to go this morning.
Okay.
I got it.
Shi, let's go. Let's go.
If I knew this would happen, I would've listened to you. I should've listened to you.
I should have listened to you.
At least my son can...
What did you do earlier?
Now you regret it.
Alright.
Tell me about Su Ran.
Su Ran.
She is the daughter of Tang Haojun.
Xu Chengliang.
Where is Qin Kaixuan?
You kidnapped him
and let him go.
What are you doing?
Ask two people to continue the trial.
Let's go.
What's wrong, master?
Hurry up.
Hey!
Linlin!
Where are you?
We're leaving soon.
I'll wait for you at the dock.
Do you know
Got it?
Linlin.
Tell me.
not to kill innocent people.
But none of the people I killed
are innocent.
You can't do it.
I'll play for you.
I told her to turn herself in.
Come to the dock now.
and get on the boat.
and leave.
everything will be over.
If she turns herself in,
would she have waited until today?
I understand that you didn't tell me about this.
But I have no right
to forgive any murderer for my dad.
I've done so much for you.
This time,
for my dad.
Don't blame me.
Return in triumph.
It's been 15 years.
Every year on my dad's death anniversary,
on my dad's death anniversary.
It says "Return to Lost".
Turn yourself in and you'll be lenient.
I've been waiting for you for 15 years.
You never did that.
I do have one more ticket,
but it's not for you.
Because you have to stay here.
and pay my dad back.
I've been wrong for a lifetime.
Don't make mistakes again.
Mom.
When did she disappear?
The hospital said
in the park across the street every afternoon.
Change the dressing before dinner.
She's not here today.
I've asked Liu to look for her at her house.
Captain Li.
Is he home?
No.
But Yuzhen Song has a burning object.
She didn't go far from the temperature.
One kilometre.
Split the film and find someone.
Hurry.
Hurry up.
Aunt Song.
Who is it?
Do you still know me?
You are...
I am Max.
Wang Wenqiang's son.
How much?
You've grown up.
I can't recognize you.
But I know you.
Back then,
killed my father and the others.
I have to pay
this debt.
Max.
Listen to me.
It's not what you think.
At that time...
It doesn't matter.
Auntie Song.
Ling Ling said you're going to turn yourself in.
This way...
No.
The direction.
Yes.
This way.
Don't move.
Qin Kaixuan.
Put down the knife.
Don't come over.
Qin Kaixuan.
What can we discuss?
Don't move.
Come closer.
Boss.
On the east side of 13 Alley,
We found the murderer Qin Kaixuan.
Hello.
The subscriber you dialed is powered off.
Sir, can you hurry up?
Okay.
Qin Kaixuan, put down the knife.
Don't move.
Put the knife down.
Qin Kaixuan, put down the knife.
Put the knife down!
Mr. Shi.
I'm sorry.
I can't listen to you this time.
Stop talking nonsense.
Put it down.
Do you think your dad can rest in peace?
He can't live in peace.
Qin.
Don't move.
Calm down.
Qin.
When your dad was in the Security Department,
he was a security slogan in the factory for years.
All workers in the factory
to live next to your house.
Why?
Because it's closer to your dad.
everyone will feel at ease.
Look at you now.
Do you deserve to be his son?
I know all these years,
You...
You are
Zhang Yixing: Tang Linlin. Zhang Yixing: Yes.
and Zhao Lun.
must have suffered a lot.
But this is not the reason for you to punish her.
What does Su Ran have to do with Linlin?
She's already missing.
If you really wanted to help her,
you should have persuaded her to trust the police.
to come this far.
It's meaningless for you to do this.
Qin Kaixuan.
Why are you still here?
Why did you come back?
Why did we
become like this?
Max.
Put the knife down.
I...
I can't watch my mom die.
I can't watch you die either.
Put the knife down.
Qin Kaixuan.
Think about it.
Why did Heo Seong-liang let you go?
This is what he wants to see.
Are you still breathing?
If you want to kill me,
kill me.
Don't worry.
I won't kill you,
I have one more thing to tell you.
Actually, there was another murderer.
If he didn't die,
You'll pay for it. You'll pay for it.
Who?
Yuzhen Song.
Put down the knife.
Put the knife down.
Seok Soo.
You're a good cop.
All these years,
you haven't given up on the investigation.
I can see
for this case.
All these years,
Thank you.
Captain Li.
You're indeed Shi's disciple.
We've known each other for so many years.
for so many years.
This time,
Sorry for the trouble.
Sorry.
Don't cry.
What are you doing?
Get lost.
I thought my life
was a joke from God.
Now I know
why I'm alive.
When I recover,
I'll go to Yujiang to set things up for you.
I'll wait for you to come back.
Because I want to try.
Is life
Is it possible?
Yes.
I'm crazy.
But I know why I'm back.
It doesn't matter if he betrays me.
What if he betrays you one day?
Just like Zhao Lun,
I have a thorn in my heart.
You want me to leave too.
But...
But I can't wash it clean.
Take my ticket and leave here.
Live a clean life for me.
I committed a crime.
How will you sentence me?
I have nothing to say.
I thought
even without us,
Heo Chengliang and the three of them
will explode one by one.
Their ending will be the same.
I just don't want to wait any longer.
to light the fire for them.
But I didn't expect
this fire
will ignite us
until the end.
We can't even recognize ourselves.
Captain Li.
Please apologize
for me.
He's right.
We should trust the police.
You shouldn't apologize to us.
You should apologize to your dad.
He wanted to see you live well.
and finish his unfinished life
his unfinished life.
Captain Li.
I have another question.
Go ahead.
You have done a DNA test
for me and my mom.
Why didn't you arrest me?
I just finished my job.
It's not like I'm not coming back.
Alright.
Go back.
Go back to work.
Master.
Come visit us often.
You said that.
What?
Am I still reckless?
No.
Do I still act on my own?
Absolutely not.
Am I still on the edge of the law?
Just don't attack the police.
I almost...
You punk.
I have to pick up my wife.
She brought my fat grandson home today.
Let's go.
Master, wait a minute.
Ready, go.
Golden Shield.
With passion
Show yourself when you're in danger.
Enough.
Don't be so emotional if you don't know how.
When you're on a mission,
when you're on a mission.
For family,
For the sake of society,
you must take care of yourself.
This is important.
Good work, everyone.
Let's go.
Everyone.
Salute.
Thank you.
Bye.
In fact,
is quite cute.
Leader Li.
What do you mean?
We found this at her house.
She also told us
your father, Tang Haojun,
has no ability to give birth.
Brother.
I want to go to the toilet ahead.
Can you give me a hug?
I'll be back soon.
Okay, go ahead.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Slow down.
Listen to me.
Sister, I'll wait for you here.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Your dad waited until the sun set,
no one came to find this child.
Later, in that fur,
he found this note.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Kid,
We are destined to meet.
How about
we can
once in a lifetime.
Don't worry.
I'll protect you.
Linlin!
Yes.
It's Linlin.
Let's go.
Let's go home. Okay.
Okay.
Xiao Cong as Li Hao.
Liu Weifeng as Yan Xiaobo.
Lou Ga Yeon as the staff
Lee Sun-shin as Fisherman A
Chai Chang Hui as Doctor.
Li Sirui,
XIN Zheng, Liu Boyue, Zhang Shuhui, Wang Yilin.
Li, Na, Shao Jiawei, Chi Yixuan, Chen Jiapeng.
Yu Zhe, Cheng Zhige, Tiantian, Xu Xiner.
Zou Zitong, Zhou Ziye, Zhang Jiale, Xia Mengjie.
The production team.
Lighting Team.
Props team.
The venue team.
Driver team.
beat Tae-jung and...
Producer Yaya
Video technical instructor Chen Xiaoguang
Voice production.
Music copyright provided sesame music
Special effects production.
Directed by Liu Shiyang.
Tracker Zhang Xiaotong Wang Zhe
Exclusive data strategy.
Zhejiang Honglang Movie and Culture Co., Ltd.
Taihe Wealth (Beijing) Investment management Co., Ltd.
Gansu Cultivation Film Co., Ltd.
Beijing Time Co., Ltd. Ltd.