[English subtitles are available]
[Men in Love]
[Episode 22]
I'm already here. Where are you?
Is your girlfriend here yet?
I have something to do later.
I need to go to my friend.
Tell your girlfriend for me.
Auntie.
Why did you assume that I had something to do with him?
Don't say that.
This is a famous model.
Tong Yiwen!
I can't believe
I can see the woman here.
Why are you looking at me?
Who are you?
Jialin.
You're here.
Brother.
My girlfriend.
My sister, Jialin.
Do you know each other?
Of course.
Aren't you…
the model I saw on TV that day,
Tong Yiwen?
Have a seat.
Hi, Jiacheng's sister.
I'm Yiwen.
Nice to meet you.
Hello, I'm Xu Jialin.
You must try their steak.
Their steak is very good.
Here.
Brother.
That piece is too fat.
Aren't you on a diet?
You need to eat lean meat.
This piece is perfect for you.
Eat it while it's hot.
I need to take a call.
Enjoy your meal.
I let you go.
You know that, right?
It won't do you any good if my brother knows
you're a girl who loves bars.
I appreciate your kindness.
But…
I don't care.
I don't think your brother cares, either.
You don't care?
Then why did you put up a show just now?
You thought you could be the best female lead?
Your brother knows
I'm not a dutiful stay-at-home wife and mother.
So,
you must be afraid he'll find out you were out at a bar.
That's why you put up the show with me.
I knew my first impression was right.
Tong Yiwen, you're such a jinx.
Talk nicely.
If you want me to keep your secret,
shut up.
Why is it my brother?
You don't lack for pursuers, do you?
Why don't you find a young and handsome man?
Do you want our family's money?
I advise you not to talk.
Shut up.
Otherwise, I won't keep your secret.
What can you do?
I can't do anything.
I just hope that you can put on a smile
when your brother comes back
so that I can buy you a cup of coffee.
Okay.
I'll reject you politely.
Anyway, I don't want to spend another second with you
just like you.
I have an appointment with my friend. I'm leaving.
Have some more fat.
I hope you'll get fat!
When Jialin came, she told me
she had something to do and had to go early.
Don't take it to heart.
She has always been like that.
She's spoiled by our family.
I didn't.
How could I be so petty?
I saw you two…
I think she has a good personality.
I prefer to be with someone like her,
compared to those
who hide everything in their heart.
Do you really think so?
Yes.
That's good.
Do you want anything else?
I'm full.
I'll pay the bill first.
Take your time.
Tong Yiwen.
Hello.
I wanted to say hello
at the party that day.
I didn't expect you to leave early.
Your dress
is beautiful.
Very unique.
Thank you.
Have a seat.
You're a popular model now.
Why are you still worried?
Models are supposed to be young.
Look at Tong Yiwen now.
I heard that Tong Yiwen was going to terminate the contract
and quit being a model.
Who knows?
I don't know if she can afford
the penalty.
I don't understand
why she wants to terminate the contract with the company.
The company treats her well.
Yeah.
The restroom is over here.
Let's go.
Back then,
I was pissed off.
I designed it,
but he included it in his work of the season.
And my name
wasn't even mentioned.
I was little known.
He went too far.
His inspiration was exhausted at that time.
He could only exploit the designers of his company.
And
he wouldn't give anyone a chance to get promoted.
Why wouldn't you quit?
So, I cut all three of
my elaborately designed outfits
at the backstage of the show.
Then, I was fired.
Awesome.
What are you talking about?
Let me introduce you two.
I know him.
Eric.
Your work has been very popular recently.
I'm flattered.
I'm Xu Jiacheng.
Hello.
The boss of "Declaration."
I read your magazine a lot.
I'm a loyal reader.
It's an honor.
We didn't meet at the party last time.
I didn't expect to meet you here.
What a coincidence.
I had an appointment with some friends
and ran into Yiwen.
You had a good chat.
We've only met for the second time,
but it feels like we're old friends.
Actually, we...
Sorry, I called a designated driver.
I won't bother you, then.
See you later.
Okay.
President Xu.
There's a long way to go.
I hope we can work together someday.
Of course.
Why are you here again?
Don't you like the place you live now?
A little…
depressing.
Depressing?
Jiacheng's family is like a manor. Is it still depressing?
It seems that Jialin is torturing you.
How could that be?
I think
it's me
who's torturing Jiacheng.
Did something happen between you two?
It didn't feel right just now.
You can tell it?
If I couldn't even see this,
do you think our relationship
would be so harmonious?
Really?
Normally,
when two people have conflicts,
the third person will come out to play the peacemaker.
I'm different.
I'm a weathercock.
I turn to you when I'm in front of you,
and I turn to Jiacheng when I'm in front of him.
So, both of you will think
I'm on the same side as you.
And our relationship will be better.
So,
whose side are you on?
I...
I'm on my side.
And I think my judgment is always right.
I'm the smartest among us, after all.
For so many years,
it's the first time
that I think you're the smartest.
So,
as the smart guy,
I have a sincere suggestion for you.
Love is the most important thing.
I hope you can ask yourself
what you think,
not what Jiacheng thinks.
I'm serious.
Sometimes, being selfish is not a bad thing.
At least you can be happier.
As a friend,
I hope you can be happy.
Rest early.
I'm going back.
Don't take Jialin's matter to heart.
Are you jealous?
No.
Who am I jealous of?
Why would I be jealous of him?
So funny.
How do you know who I'm talking about?
And you said you weren't jealous.
He just praised me for my beautiful dress.
I did, too.
I also praised you for being pretty.
But you never praised
the dress I designed.
The dress designed by Miss Tong Yiwen
is unique.
Xu Jiacheng likes it very much.
Happy?
I like it.
I gotta go.
Bye.
Look.
February 9, 2022,
17:35.
Look, it's here.
Right?
This is the time
when you found the payment on my phone.
Look.
I was going to check in.
Not yet.
Ye Han kicked you first.
Then, you patted Ye Han's shoulder.
How...
How did you know?
If I didn't love you,
I wouldn't have gone to the hotel owner
and asked for the surveillance footage.
People might think
I keep an eye on my husband every day
and may gossip about me.
But
it must have taken you a lot
to get the video, right?
My wife is the best.
Xu Yan,
time for breakfast.
[Clouds Cafe]
For the past ten years,
I've only liked you.
But no matter what I did,
I couldn't get close to you,
not even a little bit.
Can you be sick of me more than I am?
[Clouds Cafe]
Uncle.
Thank you.
Your dad and I have been friends for years.
It's nothing.
Don't mention it.
Let me treat you to a meal next time.
Okay.
Bring the girl
with you next time.
Sure.
By the way,
don't tell my family
about this.
You know my mom…
Don't worry.
Here.
-Let me see you off.
-Okay.
[IN WORK]
Handsome boy.
How dare you respond to "Handsome boy"?
Do you think you're young
or you're handsome?
[IN WORK]
Why are you acting
like a hooligan?
Bingo.
Right.
I almost forgot.
[IN WORK]
Say cheese.
Cheese.
Give me your phone.
Unlock it.
[IN WORK]
What?
What do you think?
People will know
we're a sweet couple.
Did you plan this?
I've been dreaming about it.
They say
setting a couple's photo as the screensaver
is the first thing a couple should do.
[IN WORK]
What's the second?
Change your nickname.
Nickname?
[IN WORK]
The cute nicknames
used by the female and male leads in a drama.
For example,
Chubby, Silly.
These two names both suit you.
Annoying!
You're so strong.
Why don't I call you Popeye?
What's your name, then?
I can be called Oliver.
We're destined to be together, after all.
Popeye.
I think there's one thing missing.
What is the third one?
There are only these two online.
This is the third one.
Alright.
Let's go eat.
I'm hungry.
What do you want to eat today, Popeye?
Spinach?
Okay.
Welcome.
Xiaoxiao.
It's you.
Long time no see.
Do you work here?
Yes, what a coincidence.
How have you been?
I was thinking
of inviting you to dinner sometime.
I'm fine.
How about you?
How is it?
Same as usual.
Please come in.
Please.
Let's sit here.
The view here is so nice.
Is he your old friend?
We met on a blind date.
Blind date?
How far did you go?
Did you get intimate?
Look how nervous you are.
Am I nervous?
No, no.
Ms. Zhang introduced me to him.
She insisted that I meet him.
We just had a meal.
Is…
Is that all?
That's all.
Impossible.
The way he looked at you is not that simple.
Are you jealous?
No.
He just looks weird.
He doesn't look like a good person.
He
liked me for a while.
But I didn't like him.
I knew it.
What?
I made it clear to him.
We are just friends.
Beside, it's been 3 or 4 years.
Excuse me, we're ready to order.
Alright.
Calm down.
Don't be so petty.
[IN WORK]
I'm so mad.
What now?
You haven't gone mad for a long time.
I went out with Xiaoxiao just now.
A previous blind date of her
said hello to her,
and she responded.
Of course.
He said hello to her.
How could she pretend not to see him?
He was just a blind date,
not ex-boyfriend.
Why are you so worked up?
Yes.
Although they've never been together,
he had liked her
for a long time.
So what?
Can't others like Xiaoxiao?
It doesn't matter.
No.
Don't you think there is something wrong?
You don't trust Xiaoxiao?
Of course, I trust her.
Tell me
what's wrong.
I'm all ears.
Look.
He and her are just friends at most.
Right?
I'm her boyfriend.
Isn't it natural
for her to introduce me to him
and tell him I'm her boyfriend
when we met each other?
I was standing right next to her.
Why didn't she introduce me?
He didn't ask.
Why would she introduce you?
The man said
he wanted to ask her out for dinner.
Why?
How old is he?
He looks
a little less than 30.
I remember.
Xiaoxiao mentioned
she had a blind date who was 2 years younger than her.
She had a blind date with him 2 years ago.
She said it was 3 or 4 years ago.
Then, it was the one who was 4 years younger than her.
There's more than one blind date. Look.
The one who was 2 years younger was not enough. She still needed someone who was 4 years younger.
Could there be more
blind dates who are even younger?
How many blind dates did she have?
Does she like young boys only?
So shallow. I'm so pissed off.
Bro,
if she liked young boys, why would she date you?
You're so old.
Yes.
I'm a few years older than her.
It's too unfair for her.
Yes.
It's so unfair for Xiaoxiao.
Crazy.
This is great.
They saw Ye Han and I
holding hands together.
[Clouds Cafe]
You won't be able to clear your name
since you dressed like that.
Are you a bystander?
Are you having fun?
[Clouds Cafe]
I can't help it.
You were caught by so many people at the same time.
It's so exciting just thinking about it.
[Clouds Cafe]
By the way,
do you know who my brother is with?
Yiwen.
[Clouds Cafe]
How did you know?
Are you close to that Auntie?
Don't say that.
She's my best friend
[Clouds Cafe]
and roommate.
The best friend and roommate you mentioned
is Tong Yiwen?
Yes.
[Clouds Cafe]
So many questions will follow up
if I tell others about it.
She's too famous,
so I don't usually talk about her.
The plot
has become more dramatic.
Your best friend stole your beloved man.
[Clouds Cafe]
So, you gave up on my brother because of her?
It's intolerable if that's the case.
What are you talking about?
How can you treat your sister-in-law like that?
Did you have an unpleasant chat?
They love each other
and have gone through a lot to get together.
Don't be willful.
You should support them.
Support?
It's good that I don't object.
Besides,
how can I support others now?
Mr. Xu may be out for work.
Just put it on his desk.
Okay, thank you.
It's okay.
♫I'll be heartbroken no matter how careful I am♫
♫We could only blame that we didn't have time to prepare for it♫
♫If missing is a misunderstanding♫
♫The contradictory emotions are also shaky♫
♫The traffic lights are like tears♫
♫Twinkling in my heart♫
♫Time has stolen blossoms♫
Xu Yan.
You don't eat shrimp,
♫Like a silent monologue♫
so I ate the shrimp sushi.
♫But my heartbeats♫
♫Turn the past pages♫
Have dinner before you continue to work.
I'm going home today.
♫We met by chance and missed each other; I look forward to seeing you again♫
So don't sleep out.
Go home.
♫I don't dare to love even if I long to♫
♫But how can I forget your tenderness?♫
Xu Yan,
I'm sorry.
I like you.
♫Distance makes people retreat♫
♫Can I still face it if I turn around?♫
♫I want to hug you 'cause you're precious♫
♫I always doubt myself and take myself as a humble person♫
♫The denial hit my sore point♫
♫How embarrassing it's for me when I'm heartbroken♫
♫Turns out the future is beyond reach♫
[IN WORK]
♫I've been looking forward to it♫
♫I just found that you're irreplaceable♫
Didn't we just meet during the day?
Are you on duty again?
Stop laughing.
Stand still.
Let me ask you a question.
Go ahead.
Does the man we met at noon
still like you?
Which man?
Your blind date.
The one at the restaurant?
How long has it been?
How could he still like me?
But he said he wanted to ask you out for dinner.
That's just courtesies.
Do you want to have dinner with him?
Of course…
I don't.
Of course not.
Then why didn't you introduce me to him?
It's not important.
I mean him.
Are you jealous?
Jealous?
How is that possible?
Being jealous
is an act of very childish men.
A mature man like me
has seen all kinds of hardships.
How could I be jealous?
Fine.
So, you're here...
To see you, of course.
Now that we've met,
I'm going back to work.
Why are you still here?
The company has agreed to terminate the contract.
You just need to sign the termination contract,
and you'll be free.
Okay.
Have you decided what to do next?
After this, it's my own life.
I'll make a good plan
and be responsible for myself.
I wish you a smooth journey ahead.
Thank you.
Bei.
Actually,
we've been working together for so many years.
I've brought you a lot of trouble.
I sincerely want to
thank you.
You've worked hard these years.
I hope you can continue to be so lucky.
Go now.
My car is downstairs.
The driver is waiting for you inside.
Don't try to run away again.
Do you think you can hide
the fact that you asked Mr. Sun for help?
Can you hide it from your mother?
All these years,
you've always wanted to be independent.
You didn't even want our family to help you
when you had so much trouble
starting your own business.
How could you beg others for a woman?
What about your pride?
What about your principle?
She drags you down all the time
Is she really a match for you?
Let me tell you.
You have to
go to the blind date today
whether you want it
or not.
Auntie.
Actually,
Jiacheng is...
Shut up.
I'm teaching my son a lesson.
I'll go, okay?
That's right.
Because you're not good enough,
I have to beg
all my friends
to choose these girls for you.
Alright, Mom, stop it.
I'll go now.
What's that attitude?
Who did he learn it from?
Probably
from the other two.
Auntie,
it occurred to me that I had something to do.
I gotta go.
Wait a minute.
Don't leave.
Listen.
You should just sit here
before Jiacheng comes back.
You can't go anywhere.
I've been practicing piano since I was a kid.
But I liked jazz in middle school.
I remember my mom found out
when I practiced jazz secretly
and got beaten up.
It's fine that she didn't hit me.
But the fact that she hit me
made me more rebellious.
So, later,
I played Chopin's Etude
in the style of jazz at a competition.
The 25th Etude.
And then?
One word.
Terrible.
At least you won spiritually.
So,
you lost?
What do you mean?
Judging from your look,
you must have lost the fight with your mom.
That's why you came on a blind date, right?
Don't feel sorry.
I was forced here, too.
Here's the thing.
I like my girlfriend very much,
but my family is against it.
That's great.
Let's just say
I don't like you on this blind date.
In my experience,
you'll have no future trouble
if I don't like you at this time.
Thank you.
I won't forget
your kindness today.
I had a good chat with you today.
Well,
I'm leaving.
Bye.
-Sorry, I'm late today.
-You scared me.
This meal is on me.
Thank you.
By the way,
I went to
AU's show,
but I didn't get to say hello to you.
It's okay.
Everyone knows you're busy.
What project have you been busy with recently?
Are you still working as a career woman?
Don't mention it.
My mom has been nagging me lately.
She told me
if I didn't get married,
I shouldn't come to the company anymore.
She's threatening you?
Now, I'm being urged to go on blind dates every day.
I'm going crazy right now.
I just finished a blind date before I came.
What do you think of him?
You can think about him if he's not bad.
He's not bad.
But
I don't feel anything.
And I heard
that his mother seemed to be anxious, too.
But she's also very demanding.
Now,
she's looking for a girlfriend for his son.
It sounds like your moms get along.
You're right!
My mom
has spas, coffee, and tea
at their hotel every day.
And what?
Now, she is
a good friend of his mother's.
And
they asked us to go on a blind date.
Why does your mom always go to the hotel?
Because they run a hotel.
Zeus Hotel.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It sounds like you two are a good match.
It's all right.
There is no chemistry between us, so what can I do about it,
right?
Hello?
Hello? Where are you?
I'm at home.
I'll go pick you up.
I'm going over there now at the right time.
Don't worry.
It's too much trouble.
I'll go with my friend later.
Your friend?
Didn't you say you wanted to introduce a girlfriend to Xu Yan?
I'll bring her there later.
Okay.
See you later.
You haven't done yet?
You're half the star today.
Don't be late for your boyfriend's birthday.
Okay.
Chop chop.
I'll go now.
[Happy birthday]
Put it on.
It's your 80th birthday.
Bro.
I...
I'm eighteen, okay?
Don't mess around.
Where is Xiaoxiao?
She's coming.
Where's Yiwen?
She's on her way.
What about Yiwen's friend?
Yiwen's friend is a date for Xu Yan.
Why are you so excited?
Yun is not here. Don't be cocky.
Set up the wine.
We're here.
Xiaoxiao.
Happy birthday, Jiacheng.
Thank you.
You even brought me a gift.
Why are you here, too?
Can't I come to your birthday party?
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Have a seat.
Why are you two here together?
Do you know each other?
We know each other very well.
But I know Shengyun better.
We know each other well, right?
Sit down.
Don't wait for them.
Let's have a drink.
Cheers.
Happy birthday to Jiacheng.
Happy birthday.
Thank you, guys.
Jialin.
Don't drink too much.
I made an exception for you today.
Go home soon.
I'll leave early even if you don't tell me.
I just want to
say happy birthday to you.
Sorry.
We're late because of the traffic.
You're here.
Sit here.
You sit.
I'll sit here.
Let me introduce you guys.
This is the owner of a beauty shop,
my best friend, Yang Xue'er.
-Hello, everyone.
-Hello.
This is my best friend, Xiaoxiao,
and her boyfriend, Ye Han.
-Hello.
This is Jiacheng, the birthday boy.
Hello.
Happy birthday.
And his sister.
This is...
Lu Zheng.
My wife is not here.
This is your main goal today,
Xu Yan.
Hello, nice to meet you. My name is Xue'er.
Hello, nice to meet you. My name is Xu Yan.
It's a couple's gathering today.
You two, and you two.
Whose girlfriend is she?
You have a bad memory
because of your age, right?
She just introduced me.
I'm the birthday boy's sister.
Sister?
Hello.
Isn't today my brother's birthday party?
Why is a stranger here?
Isn't that what friends are like? You get familiar little by little.
What's wrong with that?
It's okay
if you're here to make friends.
But if you're here for a blind date...
Jialin.
What?
Am I wrong?
Go home first.
Why should I go home?
Didn't you hear me?
I told you to go home now.
I won't leave.
Are you going to kick me out
just because I like Xu Yan
and I'm in the way of their blind date?
-Jiacheng.
Let go of me.
I'm not leaving.
Let go.
You can talk to me.
I'll listen on behalf of Jialin.
Enough.
It's your birthday.
What are you doing?
Jialin.
Let's go.
Go.
I'm sorry, today...
-We're leaving.
-It's a bit sudden.
Let me see you off.
-Jiacheng.
-I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
Xiaoxiao.
You brought me here for fun,
but I ruined the birthday party.
You've grown up.
You are already so sad,
but you still worry about others.
Am I ugly now?
My eyeliner is messed up.
The ingredients of tears are not only water.
Of course your makeup would be messed up.
What else is there?
Sadness, longing, grievances,
and so on.
No matter how good the cosmetics are, they can't resist them.
Stop talking nonsense.
Just
comfort her.
Let me take her home.
I can comfort her with my actions.
I don't want to go home.
I don't want to see that jerk, Xu Jiacheng.
Don't say that about your brother.
How about this?
Come to my place today.
I'll take care of her.
Is that okay?
I'll listen to my girlfriend.
Here.
Sorry.
Jiacheng.
I should say sorry, too.
But I can only say this.
Xu Yan, I trust you.
Please understand me.
I understand you.
But...
Do you understand me?
I fell in love with Jialin.
I don't want to lie to you.
So,
don't blame Jialin anymore.
It's enough
that I'm the one who hurt her.
Don't be sad.
Have some water.
You're back.
I'm back.
Why are you here?
Now I even have to
take care of Jiacheng's sister?
I'll take care of her.
Shanghai is so big.
Why can't I escape my brother's grip?
I finally found a place to hide.
But it's my brother's girlfriend's house.
Why is she my brother's girlfriend
instead of her?
Stop talking nonsense.
Use water
to shut your mouth.
If I knew you like Mr. Xu,
I wouldn't have introduced him to a girlfriend.
Do you think
you can repair the damage by saying so?
You're just like my brother.
You're all in this.
What's wrong with you?
His sister likes a man
who is ten years older than her and was once married.
Which big brother would
leave his sister to this kind of man
and wish them happiness?
He doesn't like the person I like.
I don't like the person he likes, either!
What did I say?
Enough.
Stop it.
She's been
working out.
Do you want a beating?
Xiaoxiao.
All right.
Don't be sad.
I sent Jialin to Xiaoxiao's house.
She'll stay there tonight.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
Yiwen and her friends
should be sent back by Lu Zheng.
Okay, I got it.
Are you home?
What
did you talk about?
Nothing.
Xu Yan has nowhere to go tonight.
I don't know where he'll stay.
Go ask him.
Don't worry about that.
He's a grown man.
He can find a place to stay.
Leave him alone.
Ye Han.
I've never seen Xu Yan like that.
You know
he is the calmest among the four of us.
I can feel that Jialin is interested in him.
But the way he looked at me today...
I was worried.
He also fell in love with Jialin.
It's hard for him not to fall
when Jialin is so determined.