[English subtitles are available]
[Men in Love]
[Episode 20]
Xu Yan.
Let's go.
Let me take you home.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sorry, Jie.
Xu Yan still cannot get over Jie.
Should I give up?
Hello, Mr. Wang.
Lin Jia.
Lin Jia!
Are you zoning out?
Have you printed the file I sent to you?
Here, Mr. Wang.
You were really zoning out.
You printed the wrong file!
What are these?
Did I ask you to print this?
Besides,
you printed so many copies of one file.
What a waste of paper!
Sorry. It's my fault.
You're new here,
but you can't even
finish a job as simple as printing a file?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have wasted paper.
I don't mean to pick on you.
But young workers nowadays,
have no ambition at all.
You are just killing time.
You're always zoning out.
You don't have to be so harsh.
I'm also working for my future.
[Xu Yan]
Oh gosh.
I got rejected?
I must have been rejected.
Are you home?
Yes, I am.
I'm home. What's up?
Ye Han.
Well...
What is it?
Say it.
Well...
Yiwen and I have decided to be together.
I hope you can allow this.
I fell in love with Jiacheng first.
It has nothing to do with Jiacheng. It's all my fault.
No, it has nothing to do with you.
Yiwen did nothing wrong.
She just came to the world and we met.
It's all my fault.
Should I get a ticket for this first?
Is this a drama?
You're being so dramatic.
I'm really sorry.
I know
this news
will make you feel uncomfortable.
But I...
Yes.
I feel so uncomfortable.
Am I your mother-in-law?
Am I your mother?
Or do you think
I still have feelings for Jiacheng?
No, no, no.
I didn't mean that.
It's a good thing that you are a couple now.
I'm not troubled by this but by something else.
Jiacheng,
do you know where Ye Han is?
He's leaving for a business trip today.
A business trip?
How long will he be away?
Three days. What's wrong?
So long.
Is he leaving now?
He's in the office but will go to the airport very soon.
Why?
By the way,
you two will make a good couple.
I sincerely wish
you both
a long-lasting love.
May you have a baby soon.
Although I don't have time
to prepare gifts for you,
I sincerely wish you all the best.
I have something urgent to do.
I have to go now.
Wish you a long-lasting love.
The subscriber you dialed
is busy now.
Please try again later.
The subscriber you dialed is busy now.
Please...
I have to go somewhere else.
Please wait a few moments here.
Okay.
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
Have you read the letter
I gave to you?
Yes.
Then why didn't you give me a reply?
Do you
like me or not?
You should say something.
Say something?
I'm happy.
That's it?
Besides,
I was a little touched.
I kind of
like this feeling.
What?
Are you a freak?
Since I gave you the letter,
for every minute and every second,
I've been very anxious.
I've been looking at my phone all the time.
People might think
I'm in love with my phone.
You like to see me being anxious?
If we really start to date,
I cannot imagine how terrible my life will be.
Do you really think so?
No.
I was just testing you.
I was just kidding.
Can't you tell?
No.
Forget it.
I've decided.
You've decided what?
I will love you though my love is unrequited.
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
No need.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
I got it.
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
My unrequited love is still there.
I was always trying to win your love.
Now I succeeded.
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
So will you be my boyfriend?
Will you answer yes?
Tell me.
I dare not say no.
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
Go catch your plane.
Ye Han.
Work hard.
Take care.
Wish you a happy journey.
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
Xiaoxiao.
Thank you for coming to me.
Thank you for coming to me, too.
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
Why are you standing here?
Why didn't you go in?
Why didn't you answer my call?
You called me?
I muted my phone when I was working.
I didn't notice you called.
Yesterday...
What's wrong?
Was it you yesterday?
What?
The person in my old house.
Was it you?
I think it was my brother.
He said he would go there.
You mistook him for me.
Ye Han said
you had called him.
Although I was drunk,
I think I saw you there.
What can you recall about yesterday?
I didn't do anything rude to you, did I?
You saw me as your friend's sister.
You did nothing rude to me.
Jialin.
Even if I had been there yesterday,
please pretend it wasn't me.
I'm fine.
I hope you're fine, too.
Come in ten minutes later.
This is a newly added condition by me.
His love is so sweet.
My unrequited love is still there.
I was always trying to win your love.
Now I succeeded.
Li Xiaoxiao,
you have a boyfriend now.
you're amazing.
You're charming.
From today, I'm a girl with a boyfriend.
My boyfriend is calling.
It's not him.
Hello.
[Qidao Street]
[Office of Auxiliary Police]
Zhong Zixuan.
What happened?
Miss Li.
How did you hurt your face?
Did you
hurt any other part of your body?
Miss Li, I'm sorry.
Didn't I tell you not to cause any trouble?
Sorry, officer.
I'm his teacher.
You're his teacher.
I couldn't get in touch with his guardian,
so I called you.
Officer,
what happened?
Here's the story.
Give it to me.
What's wrong with you?
Let go.
What are you doing?
Give it back.
None of your business.
You guys, let go of him.
Boss!
Run!
Sir.
-Are you okay?
-Thank you.
Are you okay?
Thank you, sir.
It's okay. It's okay.
Wait a moment.
Later...
Where are your parents?
It's okay now.
Are you robbing him?
Are you crazy? What are you doing?
You misunderstood.
Are you robbing him? I've called the police.
Let go of me!
That's what happened.
It's just a misunderstanding.
They were both trying to help the boy.
They were doing a good thing.
But they were
being too impulsive.
They resorted to violence before knowing what was going on.
It's wrong to use violence.
So I criticized them.
You're right. I'll do the same thing when we go back.
You are adults.
Think about the consequences before taking action.
Don't be impulsive.
Which school are you in?
I'm not a student.
I'm a migrant worker in Shanghai.
Do you have any family members
or relatives in Shanghai?
My family are not in this city.
Even if they know I'm in the police station,
they will do nothing about it.
Just like me.
Give me your number.
You two, add each other on your WeChat contacts.
Why?
When the police catch the robber,
you need to come back and help with the investigation.
So you should keep in touch.
Is it delicious?
You caused trouble again.
This time, you got hit.
Don't make any trouble again.
How is your training?
After our last conversation on the phone,
did you do any training?
Something happened in my family recently.
So I didn't do any training.
What happened?
Is there anything I can help with?
I'm not a kid anymore.
I can take care of myself.
You are still my student.
So before you graduate,
the school and I are responsible for you.
I need to take care of you.
Will you do that after I graduate?
After you graduate...
By then,
you might have forgotten who your teacher is.
No, I won't.
Even after graduation,
I'll visit you and bring you flowers and fruit.
It sounds weird.
You don't like it?
I can bring you something you like.
How about wine?
You brat.
Eat your food.
♫The sky is getting dark♫
♫Moonlight is the monologue of my heart♫
♫It's always there♫
Let's go back together.
♫It makes my heart race♫
♫I wasn't waiting for anyone♫
♫You happened to come following the light♫
♫But the conversation was pleasant♫
♫I'm a little overjoyed♫
♫At the places where you can't see♫
♫My love keeps increasing♫
♫It accumulated into the most beautiful surprise♫
♫Can you hear me?♫
♫The first time I feel that I miss you every night♫
♫Can you see me?♫
♫Come to me; hold me tight♫
♫Will you love me more?♫
♫At times of sadness or joy♫
♫Let's go though together♫
♫Every moment of it♫
Take the medicine and go to bed early.
♫Because you're with me♫
♫I'm a little overjoyed♫
♫Because love♫
Xu Yan still cares about me.
♫My steps slow down♫
♫Because love♫
Should I wait for some more time?
Keep waiting for him, Xu Jialin.
♫Is the most beautiful accident♫
How are you?
Is your foot better?
Yes.
I'm here
to check my schedule for next month.
I've made some arrangements for you.
It's not a hectic schedule.
Take a look.
This is the opening
of a new store of a famous brand.
Many young and popular actresses will go there, too.
This is the 20th anniversary celebration of a mall.
It's a big occasion.
And there are two campaigns for big brands.
These are all commercial activities.
I'm not interested in any of them.
Now, short videos
are very popular.
Our company has contacted some top livestreamers.
You can be a guest
in the most popular livestreamings.
You can also help the brands you worked with
increase their livestreaming sales.
I don't want to do livestreaming marketing, either.
I'm a model, Bei.
I'm not a saleswoman.
Right.
Yiwen.
The company is doing its best for you.
If you can't do the catwalk show,
and you don't want to do commercial activities,
or the livesteaming sales campaigns,
what else can you do?
Were these outfits
those displayed on the Fashion Week show?
Yes.
You
came here from Shanghai just to see me?
Even if you were in Antarctica,
I would go find you.
Why do you want to see me?
My outfits didn't draw much attention
after the show.
Don't say that.
They draw my attention.
Don't you think my design
is not experimental?
Most new designers
try to make something experimental.
That's why there are so many
bizarre designs in the market.
Your design is different.
The clothes you design are comfortable to wear
and do not mean to attract people's attention first.
Good.
But only when you combine practical elements with artistic ones
can you make your design classic.
You have potential.
But others haven't noticed it yet.
That's what I have in mind.
Thank you for saying it for me.
This model is quite special.
I bought this doll
and made the jacket by myself.
Mr. Editor.
You like it?
My girlfriend should like it.
You have a girlfriend?
If you want it,
I'll give it to you.
Thanks.
[Clouds Cafe]
Xu Yan is not here.
[Garden Bridge of Shanghai]
Who said I'm waiting for him?
Maybe...
So what are you doing here?
I'm waiting for you.
It's a nice day.
[Garden Bridge of Shanghai]
I want to go home with you.
I see.
You want to go home with your brother,
but you didn't tell me in advance.
So you're here to give me a surprise.
Let's go home.
Let's go.
[Garden Bridge of Shanghai]
He's so annoying.
My humidifier is in Xu Yan's room.
His room is drier.
And he's a guest.
Stop liking him.
It's none of your business.
None of my business?
How could you say that?
I'm your brother.
You're being ridiculous.
When mom interfered with your relationship, you hated it.
But now,
you are interfering with mine.
This is about you, not me.
You're young and beautiful. I don't want you
to waste your time on someone who will never love you.
Who said he would never love me?
I said it.
Xu Yan won't see you as a woman.
If he doesn't see me as a woman,
what am I? A man?
He sees you as his sister.
You're my sister.
So what?
Let me tell you.
Xu Yan is one of my best friends.
He watched you grow up like your brother.
Of course this is my business.
If you can't do the catwalk show,
and you don't want to do commercial activities,
or the livesteaming sales campaigns,
what else can you do?
Hello?
Are you free now?
Are you okay?
I want your hug.
In the past, I didn't know what happiness was.
And
when I had a goal,
I just tried my best to achieve it.
When I got what I wanted,
I would feel happy.
So whenever I felt unhappy,
I told myself
to hang in there
and keep going.
Everything would be fine eventually.
Yes, everything would be fine.
No, I was wrong.
In my childhood, when my mom got sick,
my dad would do nothing about it.
I did everything by myself.
Everyone said I was such a strong girl.
Actually, no one knew
I had no choice but to be strong.
I had no one to rely on.
After I grew up,
I made some achievements
through my hard work.
But then I got injured.
You know what?
The modeling industry is incredibly competitive.
When I recovered,
I found that there was no place for me.
But I wasn't that frustrated.
I told myself
if I kept working harder,
I would be able to stand on the catwalk again.
But after this injury,
I have no chance at all.
Even so,
I don't want to be the pretty girl pleasing the guests at a celebration.
I don't want to be the hostess for a ribbon-cutting ceremony.
I don't want to do livestreaming.
I don't like any of them.
Those are meaningless.
I hate making concessions.
I know.
You did your best.
You really did.
But this is life.
We cannot always get
what we want.
So,
I've been thinking about it.
I think...
I think it's time for me to give up.
Working as a model brought me a lot of happiness.
I enjoyed it.
Although this is not a happy ending,
I have no regrets.
Yiwen, you're strong.
You really are.
But sometimes, you don't have to be that strong.
At least when you are with me,
you can be sad
or vulnerable.
If you are tired,
you can choose to let it go.
If you feel a pain in your foot,
you can cry in front of me.
You don't need to be a perfect Tong Yiwen.
Just be yourself.
No matter where you want to go,
or where you want to stay,
you won't be alone anymore.
I'm with you.
Trust yourself.
There will be many choices for you in the future.
They are waiting to be discovered by you.
This is destiny.
Take a careful look at the contract.
Call me when you make up your mind.
Okay.
Bye.
Yiwen.
Come here.
Have a seat.
I reconsidered it.
I can understand
why you don't want to do those jobs.
I'm sorry for what I said yesterday.
I made some adjustments to your schedule.
Bei.
You've done so much for me and my career.
What's wrong?
Before I graduated from college,
you noticed me.
You were a talent scout at that time.
You helped me start my career.
You let me join the company
and you were with me when I was on those shows.
You've been there for me all the time.
You were there for every show.
So I think
if you hadn't been with me,
I wouldn't
have made so many achievements.
Later, I hurt my foot,
but you were still there with me,
telling me everything would be fine.
I'm really grateful to you.
It's been a difficult journey for both of us.
You
have gone through so many difficulties.
You're really strong.
Thank you.
You asked me
what I can be if I'm not a model.
I've thought it through.
I decided not to be a model anymore.
I want to terminate my contract with the company.
I just went to the police station.
The robber has been caught.
That's good. Miss Li.
Sorry for the trouble this time.
It won't happen again.
Don't forget your promise.
How are things in your family?
Zixuan.
I have something to do right now.
I'll call you later. Bye.
[Change to voice call] [Hang up] [Switch]
Hello.
What is this?
This is the new friend I found for you in Beijing.
[Change to voice call] [Hang up] [Switch]
I haven't seen you for only a few days.
Why do you look thinner?
Really?
Are your arms sore?
I'm fine.
I didn't know playing basketball had such benefits.
My triceps can be used that way.
Now I know.
It's not too late.
Have you arrived at your station?
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
[Yuanzhuang South Gate]
Isn't this the doll I saw just now?
I knew it.
You look prettier when I see you in person.
Why are you here?
Shouldn't you be back tomorrow?
I missed you.
My dear sheep, you went to Beijing
and got this nice outfit.
Good for you.
It's made by a young designer.
It may be valuable three years later.
Remember to return it to me when it happens.
By the way,
what happened at the police station? Is everything solved?
Yes.
Zixuan
got into a fight
because of a misunderstanding.
He fought with others again?
This time, he was helping others.
Zixuan is from a single-parent family.
Maybe he didn't receive much care when he was a kid.
So I usually pay more attention to him.
He's a bit impulsive.
But
he's also a poor boy.
These children are lucky
to have a teacher like you.
I have a boyfriend like you.
I am also lucky.
Don't you feel tired, holding the doll?
How about we throw a party tomorrow?
What party?
At the party,
we will announce we're in a relationship.
I have good wine at home.
Go to your home so soon?
You've been to my home before.
You forgot about the Hawaii thing?
I was so drunk at that time.
I don't remember anything about it.
Xu Yan.
Mr. Xu.
Shouldn't you be in another city on business?
I came back early.
Why are you walking together?
It's not what you think.
We met by chance.
How do you know what I am thinking?
She said they had met by chance.
But
Ye Han was holding a sheep doll.
A sheep doll?
He said a designer had given it to him.
I asked if they were in a relationship.
Xiaoxiao said no.
They're in a relationship?
It can't happen so fast.
Two days ago,
when I met Xiaoxiao,
I also mentioned Ye Han to her.
She was flustered.
There must be something going on between them.
Let me help you.
I'm closer to it.
Thank you.
By the way, Jialin,
I'm going to attend a wedding tomorrow.
I'm flying to Dalian tomorrow morning.
I might not be able to come back tomorrow night.
Go back to our parents' home tomorrow night.
I'm not going.
I have something to do.
You can go back after you get your things done.
Mom and dad said they missed you.
I'm leaving for a business trip tomorrow.
Where are you going?
When will you be back?
I'm not sure yet.
Let's eat.
Xu Yan.
It's not what you think.
We met by chance.
[Chinese Agricultural Bank]
Who is it? It's so early.
Hey.
It's almost noon.
Have you got up?
You woke me up.
Why did you do that yesterday?
Yesterday?
What did I do?
When we met Xu Yan yesterday,
why did you deny that we were in a relationship?
You called me because of this?
It's not a big deal.
It is a big deal.
It made me sleepless last night.
Yesterday, I thought
you were too nervous.
But it's just my guess.
So I need to call you and find out.
We ran into him yesterday.
I panicked.
If you do not panic next time,
will you tell him we are together?
We've been together for only a few days.
What do you mean?
You mean we might break up soon?
I didn't mean that.
Why do you think so?
Will you never
tell our friends that we are together?
I didn't say that.
I think
we can find a better time
to tell everyone.
Do you think so?
I respect your choice.
Let's not tell anyone for now.
We are having a secret relationship.
Thank you for your understanding.
Anyway,
you woke up your girlfriend.
Shouldn't you ask
if I slept well?
Right?
I didn't sleep well.
If you slept well,
that's unfair.
All right.
I'm hanging up.
Don't hang up.
Hello.
Dear Sheep.
Your owner
is a strange person, right?
But he's my boyfriend.
Forget it. I forgive him.