[English subtitles are available]
It's 2022.
I'm one year older.
I'm thirty-three now.
Uncle Fei.
Am I handsome?
Yes.
How old do I look like?
Thirty-three.
Hey, homie.
Brother Fei, what about this time?
Still thirty-three.
Okay, I'll leave you be.
Today is my birthday.
It's just that different from yesterday,
I'm one year older now.
The age of 33 attacked me
like a bandit.
To be honest,
I was caught by surprise.
You can sit down.
Are you talking to me?
Do I look like I need a seat?
Do you need to offer your seat to me?
Bro.
I'm getting off at the next stop. You can sit.
Why were you
staring at me?
I just thought your suit was good,
so I couldn't help looking at you.
I bought it from an offline store on Nanjing West Road.
I think this one is better.
-Put this on top of that.
-This one.
Come in.
This is the new intern of the Content Department.
He's the author of
the Christmas restaurant tryout article.
I remember that article.
It's well written.
How old are you?
Twenty.
Judging from the way you said it,
you are proud of your age.
Yeah, is that something you should be proud of?
Right.
The age of twenty isn't something you can get
by working hard.
Do you think we grow old
because we don't work hard?
Mr. Ye, Mr. Xu.
I didn't follow you.
Everyone was once, is, or will be twenty, right?
Young man,
I'll give you my first piece of advice.
No one,
no one can be 20 forever.
In this world,
there's nothing that can last forever other than the word forever.
Okay, I got it, Mr. Ye.
I'll show you around somewhere else.
-Okay. -We're leaving.
Mr. Xu. Mr. Ye.
Twenty years old?
He lied about his age.
Our company can't hire
such a dishonest person.
If that's the case,
people will believe me even if I tell them I'm 20.
Right?
I can say I'm 18.
When we're over 30,
we get angry all the time.
In fact, getting older than 30 years old
has no effect on us at all.
It is we
who make our thirties unluckier.
Today,
I was out of control.
I can't do this again.
We still need to
stay elegant and graceful.
Our previous life experience
will make our life
in the future better.
This is the unique charm
men at our age can have.
I'm happy
about my age.
We are professionals
in our own fields.
We are more charismatic.
Also,
we still have energy.
That's right.
Men
should be like wine.
The older we get, the more valuable we are.
Right.
Just like
George Clooney and Colin Firth.
They are over 60 now
but they are still sexy
and admired by girls.
Cheers.
Tasty.
Excuse me.
We're doing
a customer satisfaction survey.
Can I ask you a few questions?
No problem.
Of course.
May I know your age?
28.
25.
23.
20.
What's wrong?
You are all older than me.
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
[Men in Love]
[Episode 13 Watcher and Guardian]
♫The contradictory emotions are also shaky♫
♫The traffic lights are like tears♫
I think
every time I had a game,
♫Twinkling in my heart♫
you were the one who put on protective gear for me.
♫Time has stolen blossoms♫
There's a game today.
Don't go.
Why?
♫Like a silent monologue♫
♫But my heartbeats♫
I don't want you to see Jiacheng.
♫Turn the past pages♫
♫We met by chance and missed each other; I look forward to seeing you again♫
What do I want?
♫I don't dare to love even if I long to♫
I don't want you to stay there
like a fool.
♫But how can I forget your tenderness?♫
But yesterday he asked me
if you like him.
Jiacheng didn't let me tell you.
He said he wanted to solve it himself.
♫Distance makes people retreat♫
You're the person I like
and he's my friend.
♫Can I still face it if I turn around?♫
♫I want to hug you 'cause you're precious♫
♫I always doubt myself and take myself as a humble person♫
♫The denial hit my sore point♫
♫How embarrassing it's for me when I'm heartbroken♫
♫Time has stolen blossoms♫
♫Like a silent monologue♫
♫But my heartbeats♫
♫Turn the past pages♫
♫We met by chance and missed each other; I look forward to seeing you again♫
♫I don't dare to love even if I long to♫
Remember.
♫But how can I forget your tenderness?♫
Coincidences
are never coincidental.
♫We drifeted apart in the crowd♫
Xiaoxiao.
Jiacheng.
♫I'm lingering in the same spot♫
What a coincidence.
You run here too?
♫I can't let go no matter how hard I try♫
Yes.
No.
Jiacheng?
♫Dust of constraints♫
Xiaoxiao?
Are you buying books here too?
♫When will the sunshine return?♫
What a coincidence. Yes.
-Jiacheng. -We met again.
How many times have we met this week?
It's fate.
When did it start?
♫I've never really understood♫
♫The future beyond my reach♫
♫I've been looking forward to it♫
♫I just found that you're irreplaceable♫
[Mr. Ye]
I really want you to do it.
Don't you think
she looks a little
weird today?
Does she?
How should I put it?
She looks quite
gloomy.
Well, women are always fickle.
-Let's go.
Xiaoxiao, are you free today?
[CLOUDS CAFE]
Why do you have my lipstick?
I heard you ran into Eily at the restaurant last week
and left your lipstick there.
But you didn't just come to me today
to return my lipstick, right?
No.
Your lipstick
is just an excuse.
Well?
How is Xiaoxiao?
She went straight back to her room yesterday.
She left without having breakfast this morning.
I am going to ask her
what happened after I go back tonight.
So I'm here to ask for a favor.
No matter what happens next,
please comfort her.
Why would you ask me to do this?
Because I like her.
Xiaoxiao.
Why are you here?
I am waiting for you.
There's something
I want to tell you.
Xiaoxiao,
you are a very important friend
to me.
Sometimes when people are too close,
they get along very casually.
If I have done...
I have something to do.
Xiaoxiao,
I wanted to pretend not to know.
I hope we can get along like we used to.
But if I'm going to lie to you
by pretending that I don't know anything,
I think it's too despicable.
It's not your fault.
I messed everything up.
I'm responsible.
I should apologize to you.
You don't have to apologize to me.
I won't apologize to you
because I liked you.
I don't regret liking you.
Jiacheng,
I don't like you anymore.
I really hope you and Yiwen can be happy together.
I'm not worried about that.
I just hope you won't be sad.
At the same time, I don't want to lose you as a friend.
I cherish my friendship with you guys.
Without this,
everyone would be happy
and I wouldn't have messed up
everybody's life.
I don't know how to face you,
and how to face Yiwen.
I ruined everything.
I'll keep this a secret for you.
I was about to ask you to keep the secret for me.
Thank you.
I'm very observant, right?
Yes.
I now understand
why Jiacheng likes you so much.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Come with me.
I want to go home.
What's wrong with you two?
What happened?
Yiwen.
I'm sorry.
I will
explain everything to you.
Why can't you tell me now?
I can share your burden.
It's not that I don't want to tell you.
I am in a mess today.
Leave me alone.
I'll tell you later.
I went to return Yiwen's lipstick.
I know. No need to explain.
But I need your explanation.
What did you say to Xiaoxiao?
I can't pretend to know nothing.
I don't want to lie to her.
You knew she liked me, didn't you?
That's why you came to play basketball that day
and you went to the restaurant with us.
Why didn't you tell me?
How should I tell you?
Li Xiaoxiao likes you
while you like her best friend
and I like her?
What?
You heard it right.
The person I like likes you.
Her name is Li Xiaoxiao.
Why didn't you tell me?
How should I tell you?
Should I tell you
the girl I like is sad
because she likes you
and how sad it makes me because I like her?
Or should I tell you how upset I am
caught between you two?
Sorry, Ye Han.
I didn't know.
Now you know.
You must feel bad.
She feels even worse now.
Because you left all the problems to her.
I just don't want to embarrass everyone.
I want to make things clear
so that we can let it go.
Yes.
You did let it go.
How about Xiaoxiao?
She has liked you secretly for so long
just because she was afraid that you would be affected.
And you only care about yourself.
You're too selfish.
I'm sorry.
My last sentence was too harsh.
You are friends.
♫Even the air is silent♫
Are you close?
♫There's no place for my heart to hide♫
Will you consider accepting him?
Xiaoxiao?
♫The world stops, like an illusion♫
We met again.
Yes.
What a coincidence.
Again?
Yeah, this is the third or the fourth time this week.
♫I thought you were calling me♫
Jiacheng likes you for real.
♫The hand I reached out touches nothing again♫
Are you tricking him
all along?
He's my valued friend.
You shouldn't hurt him like this.
♫I want to say something♫
♫But I just stand there and stare for a long time♫
♫Maybe I don't want to leave♫
♫It still hurts♫
♫Looking back♫
♫I feel so much warmth again♫
♫I'll be with you♫
♫You know it's true♫
♫Memories are endless♫
♫But why♫
♫We've been with each other♫
♫But why can't we have each other?♫
♫I'll be with you♫
♫I'll see this through♫
♫If we can notice all the considerations♫
♫At the intersection of time♫
♫Let's not lose each other again♫
[Southeast Institute of Physical Education]
♫On the snowy streets♫
♫I'm wandering alone again♫
Who rang the bell?
Who else's getting off?
♫If we can meet♫
Hurry up.
♫And change our destiny♫
♫I'll go far away with you♫
♫In the future I've been dreaming of♫
♫Love is like a lost ark♫
♫Where can I go into the dream?♫
♫I don't know what to do♫
[Southeast Institute of Physical Education]
♫I'll be with you♫
♫I'll see this through♫
♫Let's greet with a smile♫
♫At every intersection♫
♫I'll be with you♫
If there are obvious disagreements
as we just started our communication,
I think we should reconsider
whether we should work together.
We have our own persistence.
Just say no.
Tell them
we can cooperate if there are other opportunities.
Anything else?
If not, the meeting is dismissed.
[Do you have time for a meeting this noon?]
Let's go.
Didn't you invite me to lunch?
If I'm still alive in ten minutes,
let's go eat.
What's wrong?
Try clenching your fist like this.
If you hit any of these dots on me,
I'll die.
Hit me hard.
Go ahead.
What happened?
I'm the one who's going to die.
Why do you want to die?
My brother
knows you like him.
Yes, he knows.
Did he tell you?
It seems that
this
has something to do with you, Xu Jialin.
Xiaoxiao, please spare me.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean to.
What happened?
I put the photo in your wallet
to give you a keepsake
so that you can see and think about him more often.
How would I know
he would open your wallet?
He told me after he saw the photo.
I begged him not to tell you.
I remember now.
I think he found out the truth
at the restaurant.
Yes, Xu Jialin.
I haven't settled with you about the restaurant.
You're behind that too, aren't you?
Xu Jialin.
You can hit me.
There's an acupoint here. I'll become a mute if you hit it.
Take it back.
For the sake of your honesty,
I'll spare you this time.
You are really a good person, Xiaoxiao.
Why don't you just date my brother
since things are already like this?
I don't need to lose my job as Cupid.
Which acupoint did you say
can shut you up?
Come back.
[CLOUDS CAFE]
What brings you here?
I like your store.
I think your store can bring me good luck.
Miss.
I really have no more information to tell you.
Stop torturing me, okay?
Besides, do you have nothing to do all day long?
Who told you that?
I do important things every day.
Americano, large, please.
Send it to my table.
The car will arrive in three minutes.
Okay.
["Architecture was the great book of humanity written in stone." By Hugo]
What are you doing?
You scared me. Keep your voice down.
Who is that woman?
That's Ms. Huang.
Xu Yan's colleague?
The prettiest
in his law firm.
Well,
who's prettier?
She or I?
Of course it's...
I think you two have different styles.
This one?
Yes.
["Architecture was the great book of humanity written in stone." By Hugo]
What are you looking at? They're gone.
Why don't you ask me anything?
I'm just here to be your driver.
But here's a friendly reminder.
Your driver may be distracted when driving.
Because he has a crush on someone
and is thinking about that person.
Your eyes are swollen.
You cried after you went back yesterday.
Are you going to cry until you're blind
for Jiacheng?
It's not for Jiacheng.
Not for Jiacheng?
Is it because of me?
It's all my fault.
I ruined our relationship.
If you want me to turn around,
we can turn around right away.
No need.
I'll get off.
Have you made up your mind?
Not yet.
But I need to face
what I have to face.
Let me go with you.
I can't help much,
but I want to be on your side.
How did you two meet?
I waited for her in front of her house this morning.
Then waited for her at the bus station.
In the afternoon,
I held my phone while working and waited for her reply.
Then I waited at her school gate for three hours.
So, I got the chance to drive her home.
That's how important she is to me.
Xiaoxiao.
I...
I know why you came to me.
I'm sorry.
I haven't
replied to your messages the whole day.
I can't joke and tease with you
like we used to.
I...
I'm not ready yet.
I just came to see you.
I was worried because you didn't reply to my message.
I'm afraid something might happen to you.
I'm fine.
I just
need time to sort things out.
You can understand, right?
Yes.
I'm sorry
for making you two worry.
I'm here to apologize.
Yesterday someone said
I was too selfish.
I think he's right.
I am too selfish.
So I should be the one
who apologizes.
Don't say that.
Xiaoxiao, let's talk
when you're ready.
See you.
Ye Han.
Thank you
for today.
You were on the bus this morning, weren't you?
It wasn't me.
Anyway, thank you.
Give me some time.
Come on.
Put your work aside.
This is the new assistant.
Please introduce yourself.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Lin Jia.
Nice to meet you all at Zeus Hotel.
I look forward to working with you.
I will study hard
and work hard.
Thank you.
How's work?
Not bad.
The case of Jia Group was convicted.
You won again.
Not bad.
If I remember correctly,
this is your third case this month, right?
It happened these three cases came to trial this month.
Mr. Xu,
how is the house thing going?
It's settled.
Actually, I made the decision very quickly.
I need to thank you for introducing me to the agent.
They're really reliable.
I heard that
your girlfriend went to see the houses with you
and she checked every house very carefully.
Mr. Xu.
You have a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
She's just a girl I know.
That young and pretty girl
was holding your arm while viewing the houses.
You call that a girl you know?
I don't think so.
We were just joking that day.
Look.
Mr. Xu is shy.
[CLOUDS CAFE]
Bring her to see us next time.
Yes.
She's really not my girlfriend.
Hey,
come to me if you want to buy a house.
My agent is very reliable.
Of course.
Listen to me. The case today...
Bei,
I heard Ayu is recruiting
models for Fashion Week.
I want to go for an interview.
Actually, I've asked around for you.
But the models
who open and close the show
have been decided.
I'm talking about their public interview.
Public interview?
That's for those unknown models.
It's not appropriate for you to go.
Yiwen.
I know you want to go on the runway.
I've reached out to some other brands.
I'll let you know
if they contact me.
I understand, Bei.
But I haven't been on a show for years.
They won't directly book me.
Instead of asking you to mobilize your connections,
I'd rather go directly.
Have you thought it through?
This means you need to start all over.
Do you know
how many eyes will be on you?
They will say harsh things behind your back.
I don't care what others think anymore.
After all, it has been so many years.
Trust me.
I have confidence in myself.
OK.
It's just an interview.
How many interviews did you go through before?
Yeah.
If you want to start over,
I'll do it with you.
Fighting!
That's all for our last training
before the holiday.
It's holiday!
I didn't say you were dismissed.
After the holiday,
you'll have your first single game.
Crueler training is waiting for you.
If you don't want to suffer after the holiday,
you'd better practice during the holiday.
No less than three hours a day.
Three hours?
The whole school has high expectations for you.
Don't make me lose face then.
Miss,
don't worry.
We are so good. We'll make you proud.
I'm most worried about you.
Don't overeat
during the holiday.
Pay attention to your weight.
You're the fattest among them.
Zhong Zixuan.
How dare you laugh at others?
Don't spend all your time playing games.
Don't make trouble.
All right, I won't talk more.
Lastly,
I hope you can spend more time with your family
during the holiday.
Take care of yourselves.
Don't get sick.
Okay.
Alright.
You are dismissed.
Let's go.
-Goodbye.
Take care. Bye.
Miss.
What do you plan to do during the holiday?
Nothing.
It's tiring to train you.
During the holiday,
I just want to have a good rest.
You should go out more during the holidays
to relax.
You'll feel better
when you are on the outside.
Don't worry about me.
Worry about yourself.
When you come back,
you must make it into the top three
in the qualifier.
Of course.
Have a good holiday, Miss.
-Take care.
-I'm leaving.
Xu Yan.
You're still here?
None of your business.
What's the attitude?
Have you had dinner?
No.
Let's go and eat.
Why are you so weird today?
I'm leaving.
Xu Yan.
I'm here.
Why are you here again?
You didn't reply to my messages.
You didn't answer my calls.
I think
you may not like to use your phone,
so I came in person.
It's more sincere to talk in person.
Have you ever thought
it's not the phone that I don't like,
but you?
It doesn't matter.
You can like whatever you like.
Can you drive me home?
Your brother hasn't gone far.
Go find him.
I don't want to go home with him.
I have someone else with whom I want to go home.
Don't drag me.
Xu Yan.
Don't you think
I'm different today?
No.
This is my first day at work.
I'm a professional woman now.
You found a job.
Where do you work?
Well...
Just a regular white-collar job.
On the first day of work,
you should have dinner with your family
and talk about your work.
My family don't know I found a job.
I don't want them to know it either.
To me, you are my family.
I really want to talk with you
about my first day at work.
It will be better if you can treat me to dinner.
Answer the phone.
He might buy you dinner.
I don't want to have dinner with him.
Hey, what?
Where are you?
None of your business.
I'm warning you.
It does you no good
to talk to me like this.
Don't threaten me.
I've turned myself in to Xiaoxiao.
She pardoned me.
What did she say?
She said she wanted to die.
Bye.
So annoying.
I'll just block him.
Why didn't you tell him
you were with me?
Am I with you?
You were avoiding him
at the gate, right?
So, you know
why you did that, right?
Because you know
your unrequited love
won't have a happy ending.
I don't think
it's because of my brother.
That's also one reason.
So, there are two.
Hey, your store is still open.
It's still early. I'll close the store later.
Chinese New Year is coming.
Xiaoxiao will be on holiday.
When will she come back?
She should be back soon.
Can she
bring home your grandson-in-law this time?
This time,
I...
I really don't know.
You're still so funny.
I remember
Xiaoxiao
and my grandson Kun are the same age.
Then she'll be 30 next year.
You have to urge her.
What's the rush?
Fate is unpredictable.
As long as Xiaoxiao is happy,
it's better than anything.
It doesn't matter if she gets married.
That's very progressive of you.
You can't take all the burdens yourself.
Although I live far away
and I may not be able to help you,
I can try to
come up with some ideas.
Right?
I need to answer the phone.
Hello?
Hello, Grandma.
Speak of the devil.
Xiaoxiao.
My dear granddaughter.
Why did you call me?
I miss you.
Do you miss me?
I have to run the store.
I have to talk with customers.
I'm very busy.
I don't have time to miss you.
I don't miss you.
Liar.
Let's be serious.
Chinese New Year is coming.
When will you come back?
When do you want me to go back?
Whatever.
Whose granddaughter was that?
She said she missed her grandmother.
And now you're acting cute.
Fine.
I'll go back tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
She'll be back tomorrow.
Okay.
I'll buy a fish.
What else do you want to eat?
I'll buy whatever you want.
No need.
Is there anything
you want me to bring home from Shanghai?
No, nothing.
There's everything here.
You
just come back safely.
Okay.
Then stay home
at home.
See you tomorrow.