[English subtitles are available]
Ten years.
I've waited for ten years.
I put all my youth into it.
My sweat, tears,
fervent waiting, and anticipation
will finally receive
a real answer today.
We're over 30 years old.
We're still posing like this.
Aren't you embarrassed?
No one saw us, right?
Do you think this pose is embarrassing?
This has been our team spirit for over ten years.
I can't change a habit that I've built up over ten years.
It's my problem.
Thirty years of life
and the accumulation of time
have made us more determined
on the way forward.
[Justice Online]
Because
at thirty, a man should be able to think for himself.
Of course,
there are also times
when you're 30 and you feel like you can't do what you set out to do.
Because at this in-between age,
there are two souls in our bodies.
One
is a boy who hasn't grown up yet.
And the other is the same.
[Justice Online]
He dodged.
Come and heal me.
Hurry up.
I'm healing you right now.
Little Shrimp, go to your position.
I got it.
I got the "Peerless with the Wind" item!
Impressive, bro.
Not bad.
Let's go.
Why are we still playing?
The monster-killing, level-gaining, and gear burst
have all become outdated.
It's for college students.
Childish.
We're adults.
Who cares about the game equipment?
Childish.
[Justice Online]
Handsome,
can you sell me the equipment that you gained earlier?
I'll pay 500.
There must be three offers
before you set a market price.
Currently, the highest offer in the market is 600.
I'm offering 600.
Buddy.
800, sell it to me.
Cash. Think about it.
What are you three doing?
Shameless!
Your ages combined are almost 100 years already.
You're still doing this?
Move.
Brother.
How much did he give you?
800, right?
I'll give you another 200.
1,000 yuan. Let's round it up.
Give me the equipment.
Don't you care about your dignity?
Who wants that?
My ID is...
What ID?
It's "Innocent Man".
I think 500 is pretty good.
I'll send it over now.
No need.
600, 600, stop it.
First come, first served, understand?
I'm offering 1,000.
I'll pay 1,500 yuan.
Okay?
Stop!
My account has been deleted.
Be careful next time.
Take care of this. I need to make a call.
Hello, it's me.
I'm sorry.
[Let's celebrate the public beta version of the popular game Justice Online]
Keep fighting.
Why don't you guys keep fighting for the equipment anymore?
His account got deleted.
You three are really something.
You're leaving just like that?
I left some money for him.
You even gave him money?
Can I leave without leaving something?
Do you think it'd be appropriate?
I have to go.
I'm going back to look after the cafe.
I'm leaving, too.
I have an appointment with a witness at 3 p.m.
As a lawyer,
I can't be late.
Yes.
I have a meeting this afternoon, too.
Why don't I remember you having a meeting?
I have to write a draft.
Aren't we going to print soon?
Wait.
We've been friends for more than ten years.
We all know what we are thinking.
How about this?
Let's go together this time.
Xu Jiacheng.
What do you mean?
Yeah, you don't trust us.
Do you think
we'll sneak back in to keep playing?
Of course.
Fine. Let's go together.
But my car is here. I can't leave.
My car is also here. I can't leave.
My car is also… parked there.
We'll take a taxi.
We'll take the same taxi.
I'll pay for the parking fees.
Let's go.
Okay.
He's ruthless.
Alright, you pay.
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
[Men in Love]
[Episode 11: I'm going to have a crush on you]
Good news.
BM Company called.
They're running an event starting on the 6th of next month.
We have first dibs on the shoot.
Okay.
Bye.
Don't you want to go with me?
No.
Why not?
You've been too handsome lately.
I don't want to be near you. Alright?
Right?
Thank you. I think so, too.
I'm leaving. Bye.
Jiacheng.
The method Xiaoxiao told you about…
Does it work?
Her method
is kind of silly.
If you think it's silly, why are you using it?
It's love.
Love makes people silly anyway.
I'm leaving.
It's snowing outside.
It's snowing.
It's just snow.
Not anything we've never seen before.
Why are you so happy?
Don't you watch idol dramas?
The first snowfall.
You have to watch it with the person you like.
So, what about the person you like?
Does she care about you?
I'll go find her and give her a surprise.
Bye.
♫The footsteps follow the second hand♫
♫I'm willing to be in your story♫
♫I keep a perfect distance from you♫
♫I'm waiting for you to turn around♫
♫No matter how long♫
♫No matter how far♫
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
♫I will write down the fairy tale you wish♫
♫There's something I haven't told you♫
♫For even only once♫
♫Let me say it fearlessly♫
♫No matter how hard♫
♫No matter how rough♫
♫No matter how far away the place is, I'll go and find you there♫
♫I've met countless people♫
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
♫You're still♫
♫The only answer♫
Yiwen.
You don't have to do this.
I won't give up.
I finally met you today.
As long as I can see you, it'll be fine.
Even if you reject me 100 times,
I'll look for you one more time.
This is my determination.
[Hi, Shanghai]
Compared to yesterday,
December 31
is a very normal day.
But people give this day a special meaning.
The last day of the year
is also the easiest day to remember.
♫Even the air is silent♫
♫There's no place for my heart to hide♫
♫The world stops, like an illusion♫
♫I thought you were calling me♫
♫The hand I reached out touches nothing again♫
♫I want to say something♫
♫But I just stand there and stare for a long time♫
♫Maybe I don't want to leave♫
What's your plan for New Year's Eve?
♫It still hurts♫
On December 31 every year,
I go to the Bund to countdown.
♫Looking back♫
♫I feel so much warmth again♫
♫I'll be with you♫
Liking someone
is tough.
♫You know it's true♫
Sometimes, you'll be missed.
Sometimes,
♫Memories are endless♫
you'll be ignored.
Other times,
you can never get the answer you want.
But even if it's hard,
♫But why♫
you still like the person.
You still want to bump into that person.
♫We've been with each other♫
That is love.
So,
♫But why can't we have each other?♫
you must hold on.
One, I'll get dumped by her again.
♫I'll be with you♫
Two, she'll hate me more.
Three, I'll never be able to see her again.
♫I'll see this through♫
Four, even the first three scenarios could happen,
♫If we can notice all the considerations♫
I still want to be with her.
Five.
Four.
♫At the intersection of time♫
Three.
Two.
One.
♫Let's not lose each other again♫
Happy New Year.
Is this a chance encounter?
No.
How did you find me?
Because I didn't hesitate.
Don't hesitate.
That's the wish I made under the wishing tree.
I know you've thought about it for a long time
and rejected me.
But now,
I still want to say my first new year's resolution.
From now on,
I'm going to start a secret crush on someone.
That person is you,
Li Xiaoxiao.
I'll assume you
heard that.
I must have heard it wrong.
You didn't.
You said
you wanted to love me secretly?
But secret loves
should be kept in your heart, shouldn't they?
That's your way of loving secretly.
My way is different from yours.
You know
you're a weirdo, right?
I know.
But you don't have to do anything.
Just support me.
Support you?
Support you
to love me secretly?
Yes.
Cheer me on
sometimes.
Happy New Year.
Happy New Year!
How have you been?
I'm fine.
I'm not very good.
I've been thinking a lot lately.
Tong Yiwen.
I'm serious.
I like you.
I like your directness
and your candor.
I even like every moment
that you find embarrassing.
I think about you every day.
I never doubted you about that.
You never thought about getting married, right?
Why do you ask?
I met two girls
who were talking about you at the drinking session.
One of the girls' friends
dated you before.
She said
you broke up with her
once she brought up marriage.
I admit that
at this stage,
I've never considered marriage.
But I'm not someone
who would break up with someone
just because they brought up marriage.
Then let me ask you now.
Will you marry me?
I'm sorry. I can't answer you.
I don't want to make empty promises
just because I want you to be with me.
And I don't want to lie to you.
I also like your honesty.
This is your life.
You have your own views.
I won't force my views onto you
like your mother.
Actually,
I used to think the same way.
I don't understand why
people have to date with a purpose.
But I don't think that way anymore.
Because
I've had enough of the joys and sorrows of love
and its uncertainty.
I don't want to waste our time
because I know
we will eventually break up
because of our different goals.
I can see the pain.
I like how things are now.
I like you taking me to the aquarium.
I like the hairy crabs you gave me.
Maybe it's related to my family.
I'm too afraid of loss.
So,
I'd rather not have it in the first place.
Jiacheng,
I liked you.
Happy New Year.
Yiwen.
Why are you sitting here?
Did you celebrate New Year's Eve together?
We bumped into each other.
Thank you for sending me home.
Go home first.
Take care.
I'm going back.
Ye Han.
Can I ask you for a favor?
This "appearance" will erase the pain of your breakup.
Because your brothers
will always stand by you.
This is a box of fireworks.
It will take away all your sorrows.
Take my Sugar-coated haws.
From now on,
your life will be all but sweet.
A bunch of idiots.
Who are you calling idiots?
I didn't expect
that you'd come to the internet cafe after you broke up.
Are you playing alone?
Hero Xu.
Little Shrimp
will be mad.
It's the new year.
You can't be alone.
Right.
You're playing alone?
-Enough.
-Are you playing alone?
What's going on?
I suddenly feel like
I'm really an adult.
Just now,
I went through an adult breakup.
It was a clean and decisive breakup.
Really decisive.
Neither of you is wrong.
You both have your own convictions.
It's good to be decisive.
In the adult world,
you can't afford to be otherwise.
Yes.
I'm not the only one in the world who broke up anyway.
There are so many people with me.
Why should I be hurt?
But knowing that everyone has experienced a breakup
doesn't comfort me.
Every breakup
makes you feel the pain again.
Happy New Year,
guys.
Right.
Today is the first day of the new year.
What are we doing?
Let's leave all the unhappiness behind.
Today is the new year's day.
A new day.
Happy New Year.
They all look like traitors.
What are you looking at?
Looking at my sons.
Our first dawn as 33-year-olds is approaching.
But we're still at such a loss
on how to deal with our friend's pain.
We'll remember this morning forever.
Some people finished something
while some others just started something.
What are you doing here so early in the morning?
I'm loving you secretly.
You can ignore me.
Why don't you look at me?
Why are you acting like a little girl?
Did you draw this line?
Yes.
This is a line
I can't cross.
That's what having a crush is like.
You can only observe your crush from afar.
You can't approach them at will.
You want to love me secretly, yet you told me about it.
Now, you're even acting.
You're the one being loved.
How can you understand my feelings?
I got hurt by you again just now.
I'm sure you didn't know.
But it can't be helped.
That's how low one stoops to when having a crush.
Your acting
is getting better.
Check your phone.
What did you send?
[Coffee Coupon for all our products]
A coffee coupon?
Yes.
You can use it on cold or hot drinks.
You can drink whatever you want after exercising.
Normally in this situation,
you should have bought it and sent it to me.
If I bought it and sent it here to you,
you would feel embarrassed.
Loving someone secretly
requires such deep consideration.
Interesting.
Actually,
I have a lot more
that I'd like to say to you.
But I have to leave.
Because secret love
should be so silent.
Consultation?
What do you need to consult me about?
Well,
you are an absolute authority in this aspect.
What aspect?
Having a secret crush on someone.
It's the first time
I was loved secretly by someone.
You mean
your friend?
Yes.
My friend
has been
troubled by this.
I want to consult you on her behalf.
Because
you are an absolute authority on this issue.
In the past ten years,
Jialin has had a crush on you.
But why do you want to ask about that?
Because I
have a crush on someone, too.
You're over 30, and you still have a crush?
I don't know if I can help you.
What do you want to consult about?
I want to ask
if someone has a secret crush on you,
shouldn't he keep it a secret?
You should let her know.
If you don't let her know,
she will never know.
Your first step was right.
Good job.
Great.
Well,
What about the second step?
You should
chase her for a while and then, rest for a while.
At first,
be extremely gentle and considerate.
Act like you would die without her.
Then,
stop contacting her suddenly.
She hasn't contacted me these few days.
I feel that it's good.
She needs space to think about
what she really wants.
Yes.
I...
My friend thinks so, too.
I didn't do this
to get him to contact me.
After all, I'm the one who has a crush on him.
When you love someone,
you feel really inferior.
If you put all your energy
on the other person,
you'll gradually lose yourself.
They'll feel stressed, too.
When I'm with my friends,
I find myself again.
When I return to Xu Yan later,
I can feel like we are equal.
All of us should figure out
whether the person we like
is the person in our imagination
or the real him.
Do you think
I can never leave Xu Yan,
and I pursue Xu Yan crazily?
Yes.
You like him so much
that he could call the police on you.
I wonder how Xu Yan became a lawyer.
I haven't contacted Xu Yan for three days.
He must miss me a little now.
Your friend
must be having a hard time lately.
Yes.
What do you think
she should do?
Don't let that person
affect your normal life.
Well,
it's not like I don't like it.
It's a bit complicated.
Then...
There's only one move left.
What?
Live your life.
As for the rest,
let it be.
[WeChat]
Who should I consult?
Today's fortune.
Four stars.
Lucky color.
Yellow.
You'll meet interesting people
and interesting things today.
You'll also hear good news about people around you.
With someone who likes you,
you should…
just stay calm and act normal.
You're closer
than you were yesterday.
Yes.
Because today is the second day of my crush.
We should be closer.
Then, on the third day,
will you wait for me at my door?
You never know.
We're getting closer like this every day.
What if in the end,
we end up in the same coffin?
Do you plan to
come here every day?
Not really.
I won't come if it rains.
Because this thing
is water-soluble.
It'll get washed away when it rains.
What are you looking at?
Your scarf.
I always thought
that you have great taste in dressing.
Yellow
is my lucky color.
I brought it
not for warmth
or fashion.
I just want to have more luck.
Give me your hand.
Okay.
Are these for me?
I'm afraid you'll get cold.
Besides,
these gloves are yellow, too.
Double luck.
Actually,
my lucky color today
is also yellow.
In order to repay you,
I'll take you to work today, then.
Let's go.
Can I ask you
something
as someone
you're having a crush on?
Go ahead.
Why do you like me?
I mean,
what do you like about me?
There are many things.
Your expression when you talk,
your smiling eyes,
your figure when you're angry,
your rough voice,
your strong biceps,
and your unrestrained brain.
Enough.
You are upright and don't like to trouble others.
You have a healthy mindset, and you're kind of funny.
That's about it.
This looks nice
hanging here.
I almost forgot.
And the way you talk nonsense
whenever you're nervous.
I'm not doing that.
Bye.
He proposed?
Is it beautiful?
Not bad.
I told him
I didn't want him to propose to me
after I turned 30.
So he proposed to me
on my last day of being 29.
But
are you really going to marry him?
You've only known each other
for less than two months.
Why do you care so much?
Hurry and congratulate me.
Okay.
Congratulations.
May you grow old together
and have a baby soon.
When will you hold the wedding banquet?
We'll see.
If you're in a hurry to give me wedding cash,
you can transfer the money now.
-Miss Li.
-No problem.
There is a package for you.
I brought it in for you.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
What did you buy?
Take a look.
I don't remember.
The necklace is high-end.
Open it.
What is this?
A whistle?
To celebrate your first day at work in the new year,
here's a whistle.
Interesting.
How is it interesting?
It's a whistle in a luxury necklace box.
This box is probably more expensive than the whistle.
Why are you so happy?
Yeah.
Why am I so happy?
I really don't understand you.
I'm going to class.
[IN WORK]
You go first.
Okay, I'm leaving.
[IN WORK]
Honey, you're still up?
You want me to go to bed early so badly?
What are you talking about?
Was it fun?
What was fun?
Your elementary school reunion.
What reunion?
Elementary school reunion.
I'll have dinner
with my high school classmates tomorrow night.
I heard the pretty belle is coming, too.
I must go.
What are you talking about?
Why didn't I know
that we were having a high school reunion?
Oh, they're… my elementary school classmates.
Yes.
My elementary school reunion.
Looks like none of the pretty girls were there.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have come back so early.
I'm here
to see my beautiful wife.
That's why I came home early.
Stop lying.
I'm so old.
Elementary school reunion.
Okay.
I have something to do.
I'll be back soon.
Where are you going?
Looking for my high school classmates.
High school classmates?
Today will be a romantic day.
Today's fortune.
Five stars.
Lucky color.
Gray.
Grayish blue.
Grayish dark blue.
Did I come down too early?
No.
What lucky color?
It's not accurate at all.
Don't ask anything.
I'll stay at your place for two days.
Also,
I didn't sleep all night. I need to sleep.
Please be quiet.
Mom, why are you here?
Why didn't you tell me?
I guess you haven't moved in together yet.
What are you talking about?
Aren't you in a relationship with Tong Yiwen?
I know all about it.
You know
I don't approve of the two of you.
You have to go against me, right?
I'm not dating her.
Someone saw you two dating.
I'll pack up and go to work.
What are you talking about?
I said you won.
You won.
I can't go to her anymore.
Are you satisfied?
Shut up, Mom.
Why won't you let me sleep?
Why do you wake up so late?
You've gone too far.
I've gone too far?
Go find a child who's not gone too far then.
How could you say that to your mom?
Listen.
Wash your face and come with me.
Don't stay with your brother.
No.
What do you mean no?
Pack up and go home with me. Okay?
In my opinion,
Xu Jiacheng is old.
Leave his love life alone.
What are you talking about?
Who's old?
You're not young yourself.
You're always dreaming anyway.
I am
young and beautiful now.
When I really get old,
you'll be listening to kids call you uncle.
Don't forget
whose place this is.
If you don't want to live here, move out.
Don't forget
who begged me to stay here.
I had already found a place at that time.
Then move out now.
No problem. I'll...
Stop arguing, okay?
Jialin,
at your age,
I had already married your dad.
And Jiacheng.
You
are already at this age,
yet you're still not sensible.
My life
has always been steady.
But because of you two, it's getting disrupted.
I'm old enough to have a grandchild.
But I don't see any signs of a grandchild.
-Hello.
Hello.
Good morning.
Are you done with warm-up exercises?
Yes.
Start the functional training.
-Okay.
Okay.
Sorry, miss.
That's mine.
Why are you checking your phone during class?
Yeah!
Sorry, I turned it off.
Don't you think our teacher is
weird today?
Yeah.
Coming.
Who are you?
Hello, Auntie.
I'm Xu Yan's girlfriend.
My name is Xu Jialin.
Xu Yan has a girlfriend?
This is for you.
Thank you.
Please come in.
Where's the USB?
I heard from Xu Yan
that he lives with his mom.
I came uninvited,
but I've been wanting to visit you.
It's okay.
I've been asking him if he has a girlfriend,
but he always said no.
I'm quite worried.
I'm really happy
to see you.
Auntie, you're so nice.
I was so nervous before I came today.
But I can tell
you must be Xu Yan's mother.
Xu Yan is so handsome.
He takes after you.
Really?
But actually,
I'm not Xu Yan's girlfriend yet.
He keeps rejecting me.
But I've always liked him.
Really?
How could he refuse such a beautiful girl?
I don't know.
Jie has been gone for years,
but he's still very sad.
My brother and I have always wanted to help him
get out of it.
I agree with you.
So we're on the same page, Auntie.
You left something behind?
Why are you here?
I'm here to see Auntie,
not you.
Let's talk outside.
Didn't you hear that?
She said she came to see me.
Why are you so rude to her?
Besides,
it's not her fault that she doesn't know.
I'm really happy
she's here to see me.
Actually,
I'm not Xu Yan's mother.
I'm Jie's mother.