[English subtitles are available]
[Men in Love]
[Episode 40]
I hope the end of your journey
is happiness.
It will be.
Are you ready?
So handsome, Brother.
Way to go!
I'll wait for your good news.
["Shooting Stars" Suzhou Embroidery-Themed Fashion Show]
[Shooting Stars]
Did you say hello?
Not yet.
She must have seen me.
I was showing
my concentrated and handsome side.
She must have seen it.
Mr. Ye, long time no see.
Long time no see.
President Xu.
Hello.
-Thank you.
-You guys talk.
Add some more red.
I didn't expect
Tong Yiwen would squat on the floor
and help me sort out my clothes.
Why not?
Aren't you upset?
You went from
a top international model to this.
Why would I be upset?
This is my job.
Besides, an international model
is wearing the clothes I designed.
I'm more than happy.
If I knew you designed it,
I wouldn't wear it.
Take it off, then.
You dare not?
Then, be serious.
After all, I'm your Party A today.
Guys, hurry up.
Only 15 minutes left.
Take bigger steps
when you walk on stage.
Be careful not to fall.
Yiwen.
Bei.
This is for you.
I'm really happy for you.
Thank you for coming today.
I'm not so nervous now that you came.
After all, you've been to every show
I've done before.
Tonight
is meant to be your moment to shine.
Good luck.
Can I help you with anything?
Just go and watch.
I'll start later.
[Shooting Stars]
Let's go.
You go first.
Just go.
Come on.
All right.
Now
you can have a good sleep.
It's like I'm free.
But
you can't rest for too long,
because there are more important tasks.
I know.
This is the starting point for me.
Keep it up.
Congratulations.
You made it.
Thank you for coming.
Yiwen.
I think…
There are so many people here.
I have many people waiting for me.
Let's talk later.
No.
I want to say it now.
I don't want to wait anymore.
Tong Yiwen.
Last fall,
I met you.
When we first met,
♫The footsteps follow the second hand♫
you said I was a fraud.
Now that I think about it,
♫I'm willing to be in your story♫
you're the fraud.
♫I keep a perfect distance from you♫
Otherwise, why is my heart stolen?
♫I'm waiting for you to turn around♫
I remember
every word you said,
♫I want to cross the timeline♫
every smile of yours,
and every thing we've done together.
♫And embrace you from behind for a while♫
On the last day of last year,
♫I confirm it to myself repeatedly♫
you asked me
if I wanted to marry you.
♫You're my next journey♫
I want to tell you today
♫No matter how long♫
♫No matter how far♫
that
♫I will write down the fairy tale you wish♫
I do.
♫There's something I haven't told you♫
♫For even only once♫
♫Let me say it fearlessly♫
♫No matter how hard♫
♫No matter how rough♫
♫No matter how far away the place is, I'll go and find you there♫
♫I've met countless people♫
You wrote to me in the capsule toy
that you hoped the end of my journey was happiness.
♫You're still♫
♫The only answer♫
My happiness
can only be you.
Your heart
is my destiny.
♫The wind is still on the clouds♫
Tong Yiwen.
♫Your words are still in my ears♫
I love you.
I want to be with you forever.
♫If I miss the chance to be brave♫
♫Can we still reach the destination?♫
Will you marry me?
♫No matter how long♫
♫No matter how far♫
♫I will write down the fairy tale you wish♫
Yes!
♫There's something I haven't told you♫
♫For even only once♫
♫Let me say it fearlessly♫
♫No matter how hard♫
♫No matter how rough♫
♫No matter how far away the place is, I'll go and find you there♫
♫I've met countless people♫
♫You're still♫
♫The only answer♫
♫In the small world♫
Your heart is my destiny.
♫What else can be achieved?♫
How could Xu Jiacheng say such words?
♫I can only close my eyes quietly♫
Men…
♫Praying for you♫
Are all liars.
No, no.
How could it be?
♫No matter how hard♫
Tell me the truth.
Did you once lie to me?
♫No matter how rough♫
No.
I'm not getting married.
♫No matter how far away the place is, I'll go and find you there♫
Jiacheng is quite handsome.
♫I've met countless people♫
Yeah.
I wonder where he copied the lines.
It's quite touching.
♫You're still♫
Xu Jiacheng.
♫The only answer♫
I'm telling you.
From now on,
I'll make you lose everything.
What do you mean?
You said you'd make me lose everything.
From now on,
I'll be on my own.
Come back!
Do you want to drive me crazy?
Look at him.
Discipline him.
Why are you getting so angry?
Sit down.
Why bother?
Didn't I do it for his good?
Why does he always go against me?
Don't you know your own kids?
Jiacheng and Jialin have grown up.
They're not children anymore.
They have their ideas
and want to live their lives.
It's okay.
Mom.
Don't be so mad.
He's already proposed.
There's no turning back.
Did I allow it?
Did I approve it?
He wants to marry her?
In his dreams!
Mom.
My brother,
aka your son,
will turn 40 in a couple of years,
and 50 in 10 years.
He's not a hot shot.
Just let him get married.
Even though he's not in a hurry,
aren't you in a hurry to have a grandson?
That's right.
Jialin is right.
Jiacheng has the same temper as you.
The more you push him out, the farther away he is from you.
Mom.
Think about your grandson.
Chubby grandson.
A pair of Aces.
Like this?
No, no.
Grandma, it's like this.
I played a pair.
So at this time, you have to
play a pair of Twos.
The pair of Twos is the biggest among all the pairs.
Thank you for playing with her for so long.
It's my pleasure.
Thank you for visiting her often.
She hasn't been so happy for a long time.
Grandma has always been nice to me.
Besides,
she is your grandma.
I'm sorry, Xiaoxiao.
If I knew Grandma was sick,
I wouldn't have gone to Beijing.
No need to be sorry.
You didn't know it.
Things will eventually pass.
Don't mention it again.
I should go.
I have to catch the bullet train.
Let me see you off.
No need.
I've bought the ticket.
Xiaoxiao.
You know
my feelings, right?
It's okay if you haven't decided.
I'll wait for you.
Tell me
when you have an answer, okay?
I'm leaving.
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
[Store for Transfer, Clearance Sale]
You're here.
Are you
transferring the place?
I'm not doing this business anymore.
Choose your flowers.
And leave a message for me.
[All the goodness in the world can't compare to being just right]
[And a moment in time with you]
[In the vastness of space and the infinity of time, it's my honor to share the same star]
[Ye Han]
[All the goodness in the world can't compare to being just right]
[Store for Transfer, Clearance Sale]
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
[Ye Han]
The red light for a left turn is 40 seconds.
The green light is 32 seconds.
The red light for straight ahead is 45 seconds.
The green light is 50 seconds.
The red light of the pedestrian is 53 seconds.
The green light is 48 seconds.
Those numbers you wrote in the florist's guestbook
are the times of the traffic lights, right?
You've been there?
I never
paid attention to the traffic lights
because I never
waited for you there.
So our encounter was never by chance.
Every time,
you waited for me there.
You've been loving me so much,
but I was never able to see it.
I used to be
passive.
♫The footsteps follow the second hand♫
I was a coward,
even when it came to the person I like.
I was afraid that everything would be ruined
♫I'm willing to be in your story♫
and the tragedy would repeat.
But only after I parted with you did I realize
♫I keep a perfect distance from you♫
that the greatest tragedy
was losing you.
♫I'm waiting for you to turn around♫
So I want to tell you
♫I want to cross the timeline♫
that I want to love you
♫And embrace you from behind for a while♫
the way you love me.
♫I confirm it to myself repeatedly♫
♫You're my next journey♫
Is that your answer?
♫No matter how long♫
Yes.
♫No matter how far♫
You're not gonna change it?
♫I will write down the fairy tale you wish♫
♫There's something I haven't told you♫
♫For even only once♫
♫Let me say it fearlessly♫
♫No matter how hard♫
♫No matter how rough♫
I sent you a bouquet of sunflowers
when I was in Beijing.
♫No matter how far away the place is, I'll go and find you there♫
Why didn't you reply to me after receiving it?
What bouquet of sunflowers?
♫I've met countless people♫
That was from you?
Yeah.
You didn't know?
I thought someone gave it to Yiwen.
♫You're still♫
♫The only answer♫
I read the words on the back of the photo
and sent it to you.
I love you, too.
What do you mean?
Of course.
It's 3:2 now.
It's pretty much the same.
Sorry.
Hello.
Why don't you go on?
We...
We're leaving.
I'll leave the things for you.
No, no.
I'll go.
You guys go on.
Be careful.
What's going on?
Let's continue.
Thanks a lot.
Why are you here?
What's going on?
Didn't we agree to watch the game today?
You didn't have to come at this time.
Didn't you break up?
-What happened?
-Yeah.
Anyway,
it's just what you saw.
We would have knocked
if you told us earlier.
Yeah.
Don't even get me started with that.
Have you ever knocked once all these years?
I'll change my password later.
Ye Han, you value love more than friendship.
I can change your password, too.
My password…
I'll get the wine.
Tell us the truth.
What happened?
How did it become
like this?
And how could you do it in broad daylight?
That's right.
What do you have to say today?
It's my wedding tomorrow.
I want to get married.
Go ahead.
He has to propose first.
That's right.
You're the only one who's far away from marriage now.
It's hard for you to catch up with
excellent people like us.
Don't show off.
In my opinion,
Xu Yan and Jialin's wedding
can be a good time to do that.
Think about it.
It's easy for girls to be moved
on an occasion like that.
Make use of the opportunity
and you will succeed.
And she can even put on the wedding dress directly
and get married.
Most importantly,
you can share the venue fee with me.
And the photographer can take photos for you, too.
Everything is solved.
Have you watched TV series?
This is called repetitive shooting.
Repetitive shooting.
I mean…
Is that necessary?
Do I have to mooch your wedding like that?
[Clouds Cafe]
Then, let's go back to the proposal scene.
Proposal…
Jialin and I
will go on a honeymoon
after the wedding ceremoney.
Our luggage will be taken
to the airport.
Oh, we can say that
Jialin has no clothes to change into.
If they swap their clothes,
Xiaoxiao will wear the wedding dress.
This is good.
Wait.
Why does
Xiaoxiao have to wear Jialin's wedding dress?
Because once a woman wears the wedding dress,
she'll have an urge to get married,
so that your success rate
can be higher.
Really?
Of course.
But
even if she has nothing to change into,
you can just buy anything.
Don't mind
those useless details.
It's all about creating
the feeling of being caught off guard.
You know?
The feeling is everything.
You just don't understand.
A Moment of Romance.
You've watched it, right?
The classic of classics.
Your proposal
should pay tribute to the classic.
Xu Yan,
take your motorcycle there.
No problem.
Let Ye Han take Xiaoxiao.
Ye Han will sit in the front,
and Xiaoxiao will hug him gently.
When the wind blows…
Yes.
Her wedding dress will flutter.
♫Your hair is blown by youth♫
Let him lead you … What is it?
Let him lead you to your dreams!
Oh. Let him lead you to your dreams.
That's great.
-♫Lead you to your dreams♫
-Wait!
Listen.
I don't even know how to ride a bike.
Do you expect me to ride a motorcycle?
Can you teach him in a day?
I can, but…
He'll fall off the wagon
when it counts.
In my opinion, these details don't matter.
I'll lend you my car.
When the convertible top is open,
the wind can still come in.
It's also romantic.
Yeah, you can take Xiaoxiao
for a ride.
But it's better to
find a place where you share memories.
Darling,
will you marry me?
You scared me.
Fine, thank you. And you?
I'm fine, too. Good morning, teacher.
That's it.
I'll discuss it
with Jialin later.
If he can't understand,
I'll make him a mind map.
Yes, make a slide for him.
No problem.
You're so lucky
to have the three of us.
Excuse me.
You guys were kidding,
right?
No.
We mean it.
It's pretty good.
♫The sky is getting dark♫
♫Moonlight is the monologue of my heart♫
♫It's always there♫
Xu Yan looks handsome.
♫It makes my heart race♫
♫I wasn't waiting for anyone♫
♫You happened to come following the light♫
So beautiful.
♫But the conversation was pleasant♫
♫I'm a little overjoyed♫
The groom is so handsome.
♫At the places where you can't see♫
♫My love keeps increasing♫
[Xu Yan, Xu Jialin]
♫It accumulated into the most beautiful surprise♫
♫Can you hear me?♫
♫The first time I feel that I miss you every night♫
[Xu Yan, Xu Jialin]
♫Can you see me?♫
In order not to have a generation gap
♫Come to me; hold me tight♫
with Jialin,
I'll learn popular phrases carefully.
♫Will you love me more?♫
♫At times of sadness or joy♫
I won't bully Xu Yan
♫Let's go through together♫
just because he's older.
♫Every moment of it♫
♫Because you're with me♫
In order not to have a beer belly,
[Xu Yan, Xu Jialin]
I'll work out hard.
♫The uniqueness you prepared specially♫
I'm not going to ask you
♫Is extremely precious♫
boring questions like,
♫Memories are left in my heart♫
"Is the game more important than me";
"Is basketball more important than me"?
♫They bloom into different colors♫
I will respect your hobbies.
♫The story is recorded by smiles♫
♫We name it "Love"♫
[Xu Yan, Xu Jialin]
♫This journey is repeated once and again♫
I'll share the housework
with Jialin.
♫I'm used to relying on you♫
To make Mr. Xu retire without any worried,
♫You appeared unexpectedly♫
I will
work hard
and make money to support our family.
♫We call it "Love"♫
In the end,
♫Can you hear me?♫
♫The first time I feel that I miss you every night♫
we will love each other…
♫Can you see me?♫
Until the last moment of our lives.
♫Come to me; hold me tight♫
[Xu Yan, Xu Jialin]
♫Will you love me more?♫
♫At times of sadness or joy♫
♫Let's go through together♫
♫All the images♫
♫Will be frozen by warmth♫
♫The promise was made from the heart♫
[Xu Yan, Xu Jialin]
♫Is so meaningful♫
I'm so tired after such a long day.
I didn't expect the wedding to be so tiring.
That's right.
Marriage is the most tiring thing.
My heels hurt at the end.
Of course, it was harder for Shengyun.
Where are you going for your honeymoon?
Shangri-La.
Jialin has always wanted to go there.
I'll post you a lot of photos.
Remember to give me a like.
Okay.
Let's go.
Are you all ready?
Jialin.
Where's the bag of the clothes to be changed into?
Why couldn't I find it?
I think it's right in the dressing room.
I forgot about it because I was too busy.
I didn't bring my bag.
Well…
I forgot I was going to the airport
and came in this.
What should we do?
Where did you put your clothes?
I…
I was afraid we couldn't make it, so I asked someone
to send it to the airport.
Why are both of your clothes at the airport?
What should you change into?
Yeah.
What should we do?
How would I know?
Why are you looking at me?
Her dress is pretty.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
Anyway, you're going home
in Ye Han's car.
Why don't we switch?
Jialin, look at you.
Xiaoxiao.
Just lend it to her.
They have no choice.
Xiaoxiao,
my happiness
depends on you.
Lend it.
Thank you for coming.
We're leaving.
Bye. Bye.
Bye, Xiaoxiao.
You're so beautiful today.
Have fun.
-Bye.
Let's go, Jiacheng.
We're leaving.
Ye Han.
Bye.
It's all Jialin's fault.
I'm so embarrassed.
How come?
I think it's pretty.
Really?
Yes.
And think about it.
You're not a bride,
and you get to stand in the street in a wedding dress.
You don't get many chances like that.
Do you think so?
Tell me.
Now that you're wearing a wedding dress,
is there anything you want to do?
It's a pity to go back directly.
Is it because
I'm wearing a wedding dress?
Maybe.
Maybe he thinks we're married,
seeing us dressed like this.
Maybe
he thinks you kidnapped the bride.
Speaking of which,
this is the second time
we've attended someone else's wedding.
Yes.
How about making it ours
next time?
What's wrong, honey?
Are you feeling unwell?
No.
What's wrong?
I...
I want to eat waxberries.
Honey.
It's 2 a.m.
Where should I go to buy waxberries?
Actually, it's not that I want to eat it
but him.
Okay.
Dad will buy it for you.
Waxberries.
[Zeus Hotel]
President Xu.
It's just a simple proposal,
and you can't make it.
How many chances do I have to give you?
I'm talking to you.
What are you looking at?
Lin Jia.
Why are you here?
I don't think you informed me
when you left the company.
Hello, everyone.
From today onwards,
I'll take over the marketing department
and work with you.
Lin Jia, what's wrong with you?
The new boss of our department
is Chairman Xu's daughter, Xu Jialin.
I am Xu Jialin.
Welcome.
President Xu.
Lin Jia.
Are you Xu Jialin?
I'm sorry
for keeping it from you.
But I do need basic work experience.
Besides,
I have learned a lot during these days.
During the time
I'm leading the work,
I'll make sure
you can say no to unreasonable things
even if you don't have a backer.
I'll create such a working environment.
I'll make you feel your efforts acknowledged
and your skills respected.
I still need your help,
just like before.
I'll listen to all of you,
whether it's accusations or advice.
I'll try my best
to take responsibility.
I look forward to working with you.
Mr. Wang.
Yes, President Xu.
You've been in the business department
for some years, right?
Yes.
Thank you for your contribution to the company.
That's what I should do.
It's not worth mentioning.
You're fired.
Wait, President Xu.
Why are you doing this?
Let's not talk about your ability
to deceive and flatter;
you turned a blind eye
to what had happened to Zhou before.
How can a person like you
stay
in my company?
President Xu.
This way, please.
I'm gonna send you another "I love you"
that didn't make it last time.
Xiaoxiao
quarreled with me again.
She was the one who was late,
but she blamed me for being early.
She didn't even say sorry to me.
But I like
that she doesn't feel guilty about it,
whether she's alone or not.
I just love
how she shines
now.
In fact, I don't know
if there is that kind of unchanging love
in this world.
But she always tells me…
"Let our love
last forever."
You can still make me smile like this today.
Thank you. I'm replying to you this time.
What are you laughing at?
You come so early
when you're up to no good.
Why are you holding such a big shovel?
We're over 30.
Of course our equipment is upgraded.
How long will it take to dig with a little shovel?
Do you think we'll get caught?
I'm still a little afraid of the teacher.
Are you afraid because you've dated a female teacher?
What are you doing? My brother is here.
Brother-in-law.
You adress each other so confusingly.
I called the principal.
He has agreed.
We buried another Time Box,
just like 16 years ago.
The Time Box contains what we want to say to each other
in the future.
I
still want to say the same thing:
Keep in touch.
I'll say the same thing, too.
You are my breath.
You are my heartbeats.
Wait. Enough.
We know.
Disgusting.
Anyway,
I think it's very meaningful.
Who knows
what we'll be like in 16 years?
You're right.
I just dug for a while.
But my waist...
My waist feels sore.
We haven't played games for a long time.
Jialin told me
today was my bachelor party.
I can go back at any time.
Tong Yiwen
doesn't care what time I go home.
Xiaoxiao is fine with it, too.
Shengyun knows I'm with you.
I'll tell Shengyun
that you won't let me go.
Okay, that's it.
Did you say the same before?
Don't wrong me.
No wonder.
Case solved.
That's why Yun always blamed us.
No wonder.
After he remarried,
we didn't even mess with him, did we?
Do you want a beating?
I was thinking
that we were going to
the Internet cafe later anyway.
We can compete in the cyber world.
You all charged money in the game.
But I upgraded by only my skills.
Let's
see who is better, okay?
I think he has a point.
If we take off our equipment in the game,
we may not be able to defeat him.
That makes sense.
But adults
don't do things they're not sure of.
Let's just do it here. How is that?
Just beat him.
Come on, guys.
At 50,
how will Ye Han, Xu Jiacheng,
Xu Yan, and Lu Zheng
live their lives?
But clearly,
just like the past years,
♫We used to stand side by side♫
we'll tell each other
what we want to say
♫Chasing the light♫
in every moment of the future,
♫The distant place that we were sure of♫
because no matter how many years pass by,
♫We've finally arrived♫
the aging teenagers
♫In a bustling sea of people♫
will still be friends.
[Store for Transfer]
♫We set out willfully♫
Why did the owner
suddenly close the store?
♫Forgetting to look back♫
Don't you know?
♫You're in my life and you never left♫
The owner and his wife
opened a dessert shop.
It's good.
Really?
It's not far up the road.
[International Florist]
Do you want to try it?
♫We protect each other's wishes♫
Sure.
♫And embrace the world♫
But the rain
won't stop for a while.
♫Let's keep each other company and be stubborn♫
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
Yeah.
I thought it was a shower.
♫We'll go through all the dark nights♫
I didn't expect it to last so long.
♫We grow up bravely♫
Shall we
♫We have no regrets because we have all the burning moments♫
go there in the rain?
Don't you like it?
♫In the future♫
♫We meet again♫
Getting wet
when you're sad
will make you feel worse.
But getting wet when you're happy
is romantic.
♫Hide your edges and corners once in a while♫
Let's go.
[International Florist]
Wait.
♫Be a bird that flies towards the colorful world♫
Before we go into the rain,
how about a little warm-up?
♫On a new runway♫
♫Still proudly together♫
♫Rushing towards the next wave of the unknown♫
Let's go.
[International Florist]
♫Facing the wind, holding up the vast sea and sky♫
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
Are you ready?
Three.
Two.
One.
Go!
♫We protect each other's wishes♫
[FLORA DE NEW ART]
♫And embrace the world♫
♫Let's keep each other company and be stubborn♫
That's the whole story,
♫We'll go through all the dark nights♫
but it's not over yet.
♫We grow up bravely♫
♫We have no regrets because we have all the burning moments♫
By the way,
I've figured out the title of the book.
♫So dazzling♫
It's called
♫Draped in dreams and journeys♫
"Men in Love."
♫Lighting up each day♫
♫Watering the promises we made♫
♫By each other's side♫
♫We grow up bravely♫
♫I have no regrets in every burning moment♫
♫In the future♫
♫We meet again♫
[FLORA DE NEW ART]