[English subtitles are available]
[Men in Love]
[Episode 6]
Actually,
I do have something.
Is it troubling you?
Do you have beer at home?
Yes.
Go get two bottles.
I brought your favorite dishes.
Let's drink and talk.
The advertiser you mentioned last time.
Send me his needs.
I'll write the script.
He's very nice.
He helped me a lot.
But I hurt him.
Do you remember
we had a neighbor when you were young?
The small, short, and chubby kid.
He was so chubby.
Of course I remember.
The snotty chubby kid
who followed me around every day.
We are still friends now.
You were very close when you were little.
You always played together.
One time, the two of you quarreled for some reason.
You sat on the ground and cried.
I watched as you
slowly stood up in the midst of crying.
You cried and said, "Fatty, I am sorry."
I looked at you calmly
and thought, my granddaughter
is great.
The phrase "I am sorry"
may appear simple,
but it's really effective.
The difficult part is saying these three words.
It's not easy.
I watched you grow up.
I trust that
you have the courage.
What if he doesn't forgive me?
You haven't tried yet.
How do you know he won't forgive you?
Besides, as long as you are sincere,
they will definitely feel it.
Take Fatty for example.
Hasn't he always been your good friend?
Didn't you say you still keep in touch?
I wish it were as simple as when I was a kid.
Why do we have more troubles when we grow up?
Silly girl.
This is the trouble of growing up.
Life has
always been a mix of different emotions and experiences.
All right.
Keep tomorrow's work for tomorrow.
Now,
we need to enjoy ourselves.
Here.
Cheers.
Grandma.
Grandma?
Xiaoxiao, I'm going back.
I have a lot of things to do in the shop.
Breakfast is ready.
I made porridge.
Have it with Yiwen.
Also, you have to pay attention to your waist injury.
It takes 100 days for bone and nerve injuries to heal.
Don't be careless.
Remember,
if you encounter any problem again,
go home and have a drink with your grandma.
If you can't solve it,
let's have two more drinks.
[Art is life, IN WORK]
How is it?
Are you satisfied with my work result of staying up all night?
Are you really a genius?
I've been called a genius too many times.
It's not a compliment for me anymore.
Sorry, I forgot.
You don't need a compliment.
Then what do I need?
You need a blow to your confidence,
so you won't be arrogant.
Save it.
I've been struck enough lately.
Please let me go.
What’s wrong?
Did Bai Sha mock you again?
You overestimated him.
He has no impact
on me at all.
Then what struck you?
Forget it.
I'm off work.
From now on,
don't call me.
Don't text me, either.
Why don't you leave after lunch?
I invited Xiaoxiao as well. Let's go together.
She agreed to have dinner with you?
There's a basketball winter camp next week.
We have to confirm the schedule.
If you're not tired,
eat before you go back.
I'm tired.
So tired.
Bye.
The phrase "I am sorry"
may appear simple.
The difficult part is saying these three words.
It's not easy.
[Art is life, IN WORK]
[IN WORK]
Xiaoxiao, you’re here. Wait for a sec.
Okay.
What are you looking for?
Nothing.
Isn't Ye Han here?
Mr. Ye is not here.
He's out. What's up?
Nothing.
We'll leave after I send an email.
Okay.
[Enhance] [Inlay] [Combine]
[Tang Zhu]
[Young Master Yibai]
Log out?
Out of all the questions I received today,
this is the perfect one.
It can be simply,
clearly, and specifically
answered.
Some questions
are harder to answer than we thought.
Most of such questions
are very complicated.
Due to the difference in context,
the meaning of the questions differs too.
So we must be more cautious
when we answer.
But,
sometimes,
unbelievable things may happen.
No questions are asked,
but answers are everywhere.
Other times,
there are no questions.
Only answers.
[CLOUDS CAFE]
[Shooting Incident at LA Bar]
What are you looking at? You're so focused.
Shooting Incident at LA Bar?
LA?
Isn't Jialin in LA?
How is it?
She's not answering.
[CLOUDS CAFE]
Jiacheng.
Did you see the news?
Yes. Don't worry.
I've contacted Jia Lin. She's fine.
Get me a cup of coffee.
I got so dizzy because of this.
Hello?
Ye Han, can't you handle it yourself?
Don't worry.
I'll go back later.
Send the coffee to my office.
I'm leaving. Bye.
[CLOUDS CAFE]
Hello, Jialin.
Xu Yan!
This was the first time I saw a notification
of your missed call on my phone.
I even took a screenshot.
I was so shocked.
I'm the one who had a real shock.
I'm so touched.
Let me tell you.
If it had happened at a library,
I wouldn't have been worried.
But it happened to be at the bar.
Don't you know?
I was thinking of you at the bar, too.
But you didn't answer my calls.
You only remembered to call me
after seeing this kind of news.
I can tell.
You only care about me after something big happened, right?
Okay, I'll keep in touch.
I'm glad you're fine.
I'm hanging up.
[CLOUDS CAFE]
Where's the coffee?
The coffee is ready.
What?
Where is your ring?
My ring is right here...
Put it on.
Otherwise, Yun will come to me again.
The ring is gone.
Don't joke about this.
Hurry up and look for it.
Who dares to joke about this?
I don't have a death wish.
I think I really lost it.
Help me find it.
I'm speechless.
Can you be more careful?
Can you not take it off?
I've been wearing it all along.
I don't know how I lost it.
Help me find it.
I don't care. I'll talk to Yun first.
Why are you telling her?
You're so annoying.
[CLOUDS CAFE]
Xiaoxiao,
I didn't want you to worry about me after seeing the news,
so I left you a message.
I'm fine in LA.
That's good.
Miss Li.
You scared me.
When did you come in?
Why do you walk so quietly?
Miss Li, I'm here to pick up the entry form for the competition.
You were in such a rush.
Did something happen?
Nothing.
You've been quite active lately.
Keep it up.
Miss Li.
Your waist injury must have healed.
You were running pretty fast just now.
How did you hurt your waist in the first place?
Mind your own business.
Go to class.
My waist doesn't hurt anymore.
[Ye Han]
It was my fault that day.
I said...
My waist is fine now.
I'm back.
You're early today.
Did Ye Han send you home?
Why didn't you invite him up?
Why should I invite him?
My waist has almost recovered,
so I didn't ask him to send me.
I think he's much easier to get along with than before.
He was famous for being a weirdo.
The first time I met him is
because he wanted to interview me.
I prepared for it all night.
When I saw him,
he had draft papers,
a voice recorder, and a computer on his desk.
Even the handle of the mug was facing the same direction.
Back then, I thought,
he must be abnormal.
He's almost the same now.
He even saw the thinnest strand of hair
that fell on my shoulder.
So when we heard he was getting married,
we were all very curious.
We wondered which girl managed to change him.
The one you mentioned last time?
She's pretty.
When I first met her,
I thought she was a celebrity.
I see.
I thought people like him
would never consider marriage.
What kind of person is he?
He is
a little childish sometimes.
But sometimes,
I think he has many secrets in his heart.
Other times,
he's good at taking care of others.
But most of the time,
he's a little selfish.
In short,
he is a man who yearns for
romance and freedom.
So, it must have been someone he really loved.
Otherwise,
he wouldn't have considered getting married.
What?
Am I wrong?
You're absolutely right.
But you haven't known him for long.
How do you know him so well?
Unless
you like him,
and you want to be with him?
How is that possible?
What are you talking about?
I'm a person
who's always meticulous.
We've been together for so long, didn't you realize it?
I did.
You're indeed a meticulous person.
Did you not feel any discomfort today?
I left in a hurry and forgot to take it off.
This doesn't discount the fact that
I'm a very meticulous person.
Yes.
[Closed]
It can't be helped.
You just go and buy another one.
It's custom-made. There isn't another one.
Your wife still has the other one.
You can use that to order another one.
Yes.
How? She wears it every day.
24/365?
All the time?
She doesn't take it off even when showering or washing her face?
No.
No way, there isn't enough time.
It'll be over if he gets caught.
We need at least an hour.
The 90 minutes bundle.
Hello, Jiacheng.
Hello, Xiaoxiao.
Do you have time for a drink?
I'm near your house.
Now?
[No smoking]
Stop drinking.
Come on, eat some food.
Here.
Thank you.
Xiaoxiao.
Here! Come on.
Coming.
Sit.
-Hello.
-Have a seat.
Waiter, one more beer.
Let's get drunk tonight.
Hold on. She doesn't even have her drink yet.
Waiter.
Hurry up, waiter.
How much did you drink?
[Ryuuginn Izakaya]
Slow down.
Listen.
I asked her last time if there was something between Ye Han and her.
She got so worked up that she jumped.
Who jumped?
You.
That's not the point.
The point is there's nothing between us.
Then, who do you have something with?
No one.
My crush is over.
Why?
The person I like doesn't like me back.
That person has no taste.
Eat up.
So,
stop showing affection in front of me.
Who's doing that?
We're not together.
I plan
not to see him again after today.
Stop kidding. Are you drunk?
I'm not kidding.
Are we breaking up?
Why, Yiwen?
Because you're too dangerous.
You're like a flame.
But a flame can be immediately extinguished by cold water.
What makes you think it'll be extinguished?
In this world,
there's no love that's passionate forever.
How would you know if you don't try?
Why should I waste time on trying?
I might as well
live a happy day today
and end it here.
I never thought being with you
was a waste of time.
But you think
we're just wasting time being together?
That's not what I meant.
I've enjoyed our time together too.
Jiacheng,
Yiwen is drunk.
Don't take it seriously.
Stop drinking.
I understand.
It's not happy for me to be with someone
when we have no future together.
I'm leaving, Xiaoxiao.
Jiacheng.
Are you crazy?
Do you know what you're doing?
You're just gonna let him go like that?
He's right.
How can you be happy when there isn't a future?
Sorry for letting you see this.
Jiacheng is serious about you.
Have you been toying with his feelings this entire time?
Who said I was toying with his feelings?
I pushed him away precisely because
I started to like him.
You like him but you pushed him away?
Yes.
Xiaoxiao,
love is too extravagant for me.
I cannot afford to disregard
the sacrifices and my future
just to love someone again.
Jiacheng is serious about you.
He is also a precious friend of mine.
You shouldn't have hurt him like that.
I'm sorry.
It must be him. I can't be wrong.
Xu Jiacheng is famous in the circle.
Do you mean... the magazine producer?
Yes, that's him.
I have a friend who dated him before.
But for some reason,
they broke up very soon.
What other reason could there be?
Your friend is over 30 years old, right?
She must have pushed him too hard for marriage
and scared him away.
Listen.
Men are different from women.
He's handsome and rich.
Of course he won't get married.
[Perfect]
I want whiskey. Bring me the whole bottle.
What's wrong?
[Perfect]
That's the look of a heartbroken man.
He got dumped.
Quit being the editor-in-chief.
You should be a fortune teller instead.
Who dumped you?
Where's the wine?
There's only coffee but no wine.
[Perfect]
Tong Yiwen.
And it was in front of Li Xiaoxiao.
This name sounds familiar.
Who is Li Xiaoxiao?
Why was Xiaoxiao there?
We had dinner near her house,
so I invited her, too.
Just because you had dinner near her house, you had to invite her?
Yes.
I really...
I haven't been this upset in a long time.
I'm leaving.
Are you not going to comfort me?
There's someone who needs comfort more than you.
Sir! Your sandwich!
Sir, that sandwich...
Let him have it.
Come back.
Put it in the fridge.
[Mr. Ye]
♫I'll be heartbroken no matter how careful I am♫
♫Maybe you have nothing to say♫
♫Our love takes a roundabout route♫
♫We could only blame that we didn't have time to prepare for it♫
♫If missing is a misunderstanding♫
♫The contradictory emotions are also shaky♫
♫The traffic lights are like tears♫
♫Twinkling in my heart♫
[Mr. Ye]
♫Time has stolen blossoms♫
♫Like a silent monologue♫
♫But my heartbeats♫
♫Turn the past pages♫
♫We met by chance and missed each other; I look forward to seeing you again♫
No one asked me any questions.
♫I don't dare to love even if I long to♫
Neither did I.
♫But how can I forget your tenderness?♫
No questions are asked,
but answers are everywhere.
♫Distance makes people retreat♫
♫Can I still face it if I turn around?♫
♫I want to hug you 'cause you're precious♫
♫I always doubt myself and take myself as a humble person♫
♫The denial hit my sore point♫
♫How embarrassing it's for me when I'm heartbroken♫
♫Turns out the future is beyond reach♫
♫I've been looking forward to it♫
Hello, Mr. Ye.
♫I just found that you're irreplaceable♫
You're drunk again.
I've merged with the wine
and we become one.
Why are you here?
Actually, those answers...
I found…
were all found by me.
What did you find?
I had no doubt,
so I never asked.
I found you.
Didn't you say
not to see each other again?
I don't know why I came to you.
I've retrieved the magazine with the typo,
shot the photos for the poster,
and even signed the settlement agreement.
Do you know what that means?
You told me.
It means that we don't have to see each other again.
No.
It means I have exhausted all the excuses
I have made up to meet you.
There's only one reason left.
I miss you.
When the answer appears,
the question you forgot will also emerge.
But when you realize the question,
the answer will become more certain.
I never doubted it.
Not even once.
Then I'll let you take a good look at me.
Li Xiaoxiao.
Wait.
Where am I?
Why am I in a tent?
What is this?
Aloha.
What are you doing?
I'm sunbathing.
Where are you sunbathing?
In Hawaii.
What Hawaii is this?
You don't remember?
Where am I?
This is my home.
You're in my bed.
I'll go down in a minute.
You can sleep here.
No.
How can I sleep at a man's place?
I'm not that kind of person.
No.
Li Xiaoxiao, I'm tired.
Can you shut up
and go to bed?
No.
I can't sleep in a man's place.
Never.
Let's go out and play then.
Let's go to Hawaii.
Aloha!
Aloha, aloha.
Hawaii. Hawaii.
The plane is a bit bumpy.
We'll be in Hawaii soon.
Seeing you again…
really made me happy.
I thought I'd never see you again.
It's not easy for me
to meet you.
Ye Han.
I...
I want to vomit.
No!
Congratulations. You finally remember.
What have I done?
How embarrassing!
Why did you drink so much alone?
That was a farewell wine.
Forget it.
Since we're in Hawaii,
let me tell you about it.
At first,
I thought Yiwen didn't like Jiacheng.
That's why I pretended to meet Jiacheng by accident.
But today, I found out that
Yiwen really likes Jiacheng.
They like each other.
It's my fault.
No one is at fault here.
You are kind.
You're just a little dumb.
No.
That's not kindness.
I blame myself.
Yiwen is my best friend.
She told me everything,
but I kept things from her.
It's time
to end these painful
and complicated feelings.
When I'm sad,
I like to drink alone
to vent some frustration.
I guess I was trying to clear my mind with wine.
Be it a crush or a relationship,
this bit remains the same,
and only this bit is the same.
Why are you looking at me like that?
What's that look?
You're very cool right now.
Li Xiaoxiao.
What time is it now?
Three o'clock.
I thought you would sleep until dawn.
It's three o'clock?
I have to go.
Are you okay? Do you need a ride?
No.
I can go by myself.
I can go on my own.
I'm sober.
I'm very sober.
I saw the lights on.
I thought you were home.
You didn't go home
because you thought
I was at home?
Where have you been?
It's three o'clock.
Hawaii.
What?
Just kidding.
I want to apologize to you.
Thank you
for reminding me when I was willful.
Is this an apology?
Yes.
Without you,
I would never understand
what self-reflection means.
So don't leave me again.
Don't leave me.
Okay.
I won't leave you anymore.
But
I did something wrong too.
I'll apologize to you another day.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I was wrong today.
Don't you really like Jiacheng?
Then be with him.
If it were Tong Yiwen five years ago,
I would choose to be with him.
But now,
I won't choose that path anymore.
What path is that?
A bitter and sweet path.
At the age of 30,
I just want a stable relationship.
I just want to go to work with someone hand in hand.
We can go to the park together
and stand under the starry sky together.
That's all I want right now.
I don't want anything else.
I slept all night.
My head still hurts.
As the saying goes,
coffee is the best cure for hangover.
Thank you.
Again, as the saying goes,
a woman with a hangover
must have drunk wine with a man.
All these sayings must come from you.
If you didn't drink with a man,
who did you drink with?
As the saying goes,
it's easier to get drunk
when drinking alone.
What happened?
No, wait.
Hold it first. I'm going to class.
Talk later.
Sorry.
I accidentally smeared something on you.
In my opinion,
the one that best suits our style is...
the second one.
The third one.
We're done!
Thank you.
We're done.
While everyone is working hard,
I have good news
to share with you.
Our "Declaration" magazine
has been nominated for the
Best Writing Award
at the China Publishing Culture Award.
We all worked hard to get this honor.
Congratulations, Mr. Ye.
Give us a raise!
There's a raise and a company trip!
Oh, right. We need to attend the award ceremony.
Are they giving us the award?
We won't know until we get there.
Is that ceremony held in Zhejiang every year?
If the time is near the time
of the basketball winter camp,
you can go for me.
I think they are about the same time.
But the editor-in-chief
should attend the award ceremony in person.
By the way,
"His Story" was nominated too.
Really.
How long haven't you seen Bai Sha?
You should go and say hi.
You think it's fun, right?
Yes.
I really like the way you compete
and look down on each other.
Stop.
The word "compete"
doesn't apply to the two of us.
Our capabilities have to be neck-to-neck
for you to call us competitors.
People like Lin Dan and Lee Chongwei are competitors.
You have a point.
"His Story" is the best in our field.
We are indeed no match for them.
You...
I see.
You keep attacking me
to relieve your pain
of being dumped, right?
You didn't have to bring that up.
You can attack me as much as you want.
But only for today.
Straighten your backs.
Go lower.
I think you have the team's fund card.
I can't leave today.
If you have the time,
please bring the card to my office.
Gosh.
Are you telling me to sneak into the enemy's camp?
[Mr. Ye]
What are you looking at?
Are you done with your 50 sets?
The national competition is about to begin.
Focus on your state!
You're so lazy.
Zhong Zixuan.
Squat lower.
Keep your back straight.
Hurry up. Faster!
[IN WORK]
[Chief Lawyer's Office]
Why are you dressed like this?
I heard
as long as a dog's mouth is warm,
its entire body will be warm as well.
I don't mean I'm a dog.
I've paid for
the uniform.
Thank you.
I've booked
the hotel
and the train tickets.
All that's left to do is leave.
Xu Yan.
Does the magazine office
end work on time?
Jiacheng should be off work by now.
Others
should be off work too, right?
Not necessarily.
It seems to be their deadline lately.
They'll probably work overtime.
Are you looking for someone?
No.
I was just asking.
You scared me.