You're here.
Have a seat.
I'm sorry
for keeping you waiting.
No.
I just got here too.
Let's order first.
Let's get this straight.
It's my treat.
To thank you
for taking me to your school museum.
Then I'll order the whole menu.
You can order the entire menu if you want.
Waiter, we'd like to order.
Coming.
Here is your water.
Pizza.
And a tiramisu.
Okay.
Some popcorn chicken.
That's it.
Okay, please wait a moment.
Didn't you say you'd order the whole menu?
I want to save the rest for next time.
See how nice you look when you smile.
You should smile more.
When I saw you at the Imperial Kiln Museum last time,
you were sitting there all alone looking so down.
What happened?
Is something on your mind?
Are you sure you want to know?
It'll be a long story.
So,
you have a friend helping you
set you up with another guy.
But there is a girl
who got in your friend's way.
Right.
Then your friend
went to blame this girl.
Right.
And you spoke up for this girl.
So,
your friend turned around and blamed you.
I don't mean to judge your situation.
Believe me.
If you ran into the same thing as me,
you'd be very troubled too.
Trust me.
I would never run into something like this.
True.
Sometimes I really envy you.
You seem to be able
to handle everything with ease.
Not really.
I have my own troubles too.
And lately, I've been so anxious about it
that I can't sleep.
What's wrong?
My job at the Imperial Kiln Museum is temporary.
So I've always wanted to become a full-time employee.
But the previous two times,
I failed at the final interview.
I've qualified for the interview again this time.
But when I think about the previous failures,
I get really nervous.
I'm so anxious that I can't sleep.
I didn't expect
you to have a side like this.
So I want to thank you.
Every time I see you,
I feel a lot more relaxed.
This is how to do this move, right?
Like this.
Students,
starting from today,
we will begin
the study and research of the Kintsugi restoration technique.
The first step of the Kintsugi technique
is to use raw lacquer to consolidate the base.
This involves brushing raw lacquer
onto the cross-sections of the ceramics,
joining them together,
and then placing them in a kiln to dry.
This raw lacquer,
as the name suggests,
is a substance formed after collecting the raw sap
from the lacquer tree.
After this substance dries,
it is corrosion-resistant
and heat-resistant,
with a beautiful color and luster.
When applied to ceramics,
it is not only practical,
but also enhances
the color and luster of the object.
Class is over.
Want to eat together?
I have something to do.
I'm leaving now. Bye.
Bye.
What are you doing?
In class.
How's your interview prep going?
You're replying to messages in class?
Go focus on your class.
Mind your own business.
Class dismissed.
Xiaocen,
have you thought about it?
About what?
Helping out at Fang Xiaqing's studio.
Is it appropriate?
Yes, of course it is.
Besides, we can finish our homework there.
Let's have dinner with them tonight.
Dinner?
There you go again.
I just feel like
maybe they
only want you to go.
If I go, I won't be of much help.
Of course not.
But I...
Xu Xiao.
I think you're a talent.
When you graduate,
you don't even need to look for a job.
Just join Banlan Studio directly.
We cover food, accommodation, and getting rich.
How about it?
Actually, my skills
are still in the learning process.
I can give it a try.
Xiao Cen,
what do you think?
I...
Yeah.
Xiaocen,
we
also really hope you can join us.
But
I'm not as good as Xu Xiao.
I'm afraid I won't be of much help.
Who said that?
Your drawing skills are great.
Yeah, Xiaocen.
Don't be modest.
Stay and join us
to create better works together,
okay?
Yeah, stay.
Alright.
I think that's a yes.
Then come on, let's have a drink.
Come on, cheers.
Let's have a drink.
Come on.
Cheers.
No need to see us out.
From today on,
you are employees of Banlan.
Then you'll start working tomorrow.
Just come over when you don't have classes.
Okay.
Tell me what you want to eat.
I'll make it for you.
Okay.
All right, stop talking.
Or it'll be tomorrow.
Bye.
Then we are leaving.
Be safe on your way.
Bye.
Everyone is so friendly.
Yeah.
Actually...
What's wrong?
Actually, I was thinking,
Sister Xia Qing wants your skills.
I might not be able to help.
That's not true.
I'm used to working with you.
From Mr. Yue's class to the antique shop,
I've always worked with you,
haven't I?
Don't worry.
You can do it.
Let's go.
Okay.
Where are we?
My friend's exhibition hall.
It happens to be vacant for the next couple of days.
Why did you bring me here?
Aren't you having your interview soon?
I figured these couple of days
would be when you're the most nervous.
So I came up with an idea.
Look.
This is...
This is the map of the museum.
Yes.
Did I draw it accurately?
Why did you draw this?
Now,
pretend this is the Imperial Kiln Museum.
It's filled with countless
extremely beautiful treasures.
And I am your first visitor.
Now, you need to use the lines at your feet
and your memory
to explain all the collections here to me.
Now.
I have paid for a human guide.
All right.
Please.
Welcome to Jingdezhen Imperial Kiln Museum.
I am your guide, Qi Yi.
The first thing we see
is our most treasured piece, the Suisui Duck.
From the Chenghua period of the Ming Dynasty,
a plain sancai duck-shaped incense burner.
Due to the extreme difficulty of the craftsmanship
and the strict selection system of the imperial kiln back then,
it was smashed and buried deep in Zhushan for over 500 years.
Unearthed by archaeologists in 1987,
it is unique to the imperial kiln
and has not been handed down.
What we are looking at now
is the blue-and-white vat with cloud and dragon patterns.
Its main function is to store water.
Next, we will see
the three-pot communicating vessel.
Alright.
That's all for today's tour.
I hope you enjoyed it.
Look at you.
You don't even need to be in a real museum
to know all the collections like the back of your hand.
You explained them so well blindly.
One hundred points.
During the real interview,
if only I could be as relaxed as I am with you.
The reason you get nervous
is because whenever
the words 'Imperial Kiln Museum' are mentioned,
it brings back your bad memories.
So I came up with a way.
I want to create a new memory for you
to erase those bad ones from before.
A new memory?
Yeah.
I hope you remember today.
In this imaginary museum,
you fluently
and smoothly explained all the collections to me.
This way, during your interview,
if you get nervous,
you can think of today,
this very moment,
and think of me.
So,
did today's memory
overwrite the shadows of the past?
Thank you.
Its name is Xiaoguai.
It used to be a stray cat around here.
But everyone in our studio often fed it,
so it came here a lot.
Then we also bathed it, clipped its nails,
and gave it delicious food.
So it just stayed here and wouldn't leave.
It really likes being pet on the head like this.
Xiaoguai.
You are all here.
Let's go.
Come here. I have something to announce.
Let me tell you two something.
Before you two joined Banlan,
Xiaqing and I had been working on her solo exhibition.
And while doing this exhibition,
we hope more people
can see Xiaqing's works
and notice our brand, Banlan.
Most importantly,
there is a Boss Qin.
If he sees Banlan's potential
and invests heavily,
he can help our brand grow.
Um,
who is Boss Qin?
A boss Jingjing is currently in contact with.
He is an investor
our studio is trying to win over now.
We were originally supposed to start this exhibition
next week.
But Xiaqing told me
she wanted more time
for you guys to help her
polish the final product.
So this exhibition might be postponed.
Understood.
Then knock the two ends of the staple we made earlier
into the holes.
This way, the broken pieces can be connected.
Let me try.
Sure.
Start with this one.
Here.
Be
careful.
Okay.
The finished product is roughly like this.
Try to cut it a bit smaller.
We still need to knock
and polish it later.
You edit very well.
I find that I learn quite fast.
You're smart.
You learn it as soon as you are taught.
Xiaoguai is barking.
Did Jingjing forget to feed it?
I'll go.
Thanks, Xiaocen.
No problem.
Xiaoguai.
What are you barking at?
What's wrong?
Xu Xiao.
Do you like Xiaocen?
W-What?
You're blushing.
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
No.
We're just ordinary classmates.
You're not just ordinary classmates.
You clearly care a lot.
Care?
No, I don't.
Xiaocen just got up to leave,
and you were already looking for her.
If that's not caring, what is?
Don't talk nonsense.
And don't say anything crazy to Xiaocen.
Xiaoguai is indeed hungry.
Sit.
Let's continue.
Why did she kill him?
They were enemies in their past life.
So in this life,
this woman wants to seek revenge on this man.
Then why didn't the man hide?
This man has no memory of his past life.
He loves this woman in this life.
When did he fall in love with her?
Sis.
Can't you just watch the show properly?
You watch the show for a bit, then do chores.
You can't even follow the plot.
I wouldn't be able to follow it if I didn't ask you.
Tell me quickly.
Then don't ask me. Ask Xiaocen.
You're distracting me from the show.
Xiaocen, tell your mom about it.
Xiaocen.
What's wrong?
You don't look well.
Is something wrong?
What's wrong? Are you feeling unwell?
It's nothing.
Really?
What's going on at your school recently?
You used to come straight home after school,
but now you leave early and come back late every day.
She said she was going to Taoxichuan.
What are you doing in Taoxichuan?
There was an...
an older girl from outside the school,
who asked me to help her make pottery.
No.
Schoolwork is heavy enough.
Things outside of school,
just don't get involved.
Okay?
We don't need you to earn tuition money.
I'm not doing it for money.
If not for money, then what for?
I don't know what for either.
You don't know why, yet you're just messing around?
Are you doing this on purpose to make me mad?
No, Mom.
Sis, keep your voice down.
Look how you scared her.
We need to keep Xiaocen happy.
A broad mind makes a healthy body.
First of all, she needs a broad mind.
Yes.
Okay.
I was speaking too loudly just now.
I'm telling you, things outside of school,
just don't get involved.
Look at this period of time,
it wasn't easy to get your health back on track.
The doctor even said you can stop taking Chinese medicine.
Don't mess around and get sick again.
Got it?
I got it.
Alright, it's late.
Hurry up and go to sleep.
Go ahead.
Go to bed early.
With Xu Xiao's help,
Xia Qing made rapid progress
and soon found a new approach to her work.
The two of them worked together
with great chemistry.
I even felt that in just a few days,
she had gotten closer to Xu Xiao
than I ever was.
I am always like this,
doing everything a few steps slower than others.
The world runs
just like the TV series my aunt and mom are watching.
The fast pace leaves me breathless.
How I wish the time Xu Xiao and I spent together
could be like the bus that took us home,
moving forward slowly, stop by stop.
But I feel like I'm still left on the platform,
not knowing if the last bus hasn't arrived yet
or has already left.
Xiaocen.
What are you doing here?
I've finished the hand drawings Xiaoyu and Tian Yuan gave me.
Xiaqing.
I have nothing to do right now.
Do you need any help?
No need.
Everything is going smoothly.
This is a cake I made.
Jingjing and Xu Xiao both said it was delicious.
I hope you like it too.
Thank you.
Enjoy it. I'll get going.
This is so delicious.
Xiaocen,
Did you notice
if there's anything different
between Wang Lin and Li Zhuoting today?
Sorry, Wu Jing.
I didn't catch a word you said.
Wang Lin, Wang Lin.
They are not sitting together.
Keep it down.
Yes.
Let me tell you.
You have no idea.
Xiaoyi.
The three of them are in a complicated situation now.
Why?
Xiaoyi and Wang Lin used to be together, right?
After they broke up,
Xiaoyi started flirting with Li Zhuoting.
So now Wang Lin and Li Zhuoting
are not sitting together anymore.
Look at how they are sitting,
like they're at the ends of the earth.
They're forming a triangle.
Yeah.
It really is a triangle.
Look how awkward they are now.
Look.
Class monitor, is everyone here?
Everyone is here.
Then,
let's start the class.
Xiaocen.
Are you going to the antique shop today?
Xia Qing and the others went to collect porcelain shards this afternoon.
You don't need to go to the studio so early.
I won't go this afternoon.
Yuexin is treating me to milk tea.
Let's go.
Milk tea.
Xiao Xu.
I have something to share with you.
Do you remember my pair of large chicken-heart walnuts?
What about them?
A couple of mornings ago,
as soon as I arrived at the shop,
I found one was suddenly missing.
I was so anxious that I searched in the shop,
upstairs and downstairs.
It's been with me for about ten years.
I'm attached to it, you know?
Most importantly,
it's called Big Chicken Heart.
Missing one, wouldn't that mean missing a heart?
This is not the strangest thing.
The strangest thing is,
in the afternoon,
it suddenly appeared on my desk,
in the most obvious place.
Right here,
right in the middle.
Don't you think it's too weird?
How come when I share something with you,
I get no reaction at all?
Didn't I ask you to come with Xiaocen?
There's a bunch of cups in the shop waiting for her to write on.
You can't just grab her
the moment she takes a break.
She needs to rest too.
From what you're saying,
something seems wrong.
What's up?
Nothing.
Did you two fight?
We didn't.
Then what's wrong?
It's just...
I feel like lately
she's suddenly become a different person.
Did you make her mad?
Mad about what?
How would I know?
Let me tell you, stop overthinking.
When it comes to women,
even if you pay 120 percent attention,
you can't dodge a single landmine you're meant to step on.
When I was young,
I suffered a lot because of this.
Stop overthinking.
Women...
I didn't understand when I was young.
I don't understand it now either.
And as for the future,
I probably won't either.
Xu Xiao.
Reply to him. Hurry.
Xiaocen.
You asked me to come today to...
I want to sincerely
apologize to you.
Apologize?
Have you been
unhappy lately?
No.
I know you haven't been very happy lately.
And I know
you're not someone who gets angry easily.
When I interact with others,
I can be a bit slow.
Sometimes I upset people.
So,
is it my fault
that you're unhappy?
It's not your fault.
It's me.
Young man,
buy a balloon for your girlfriend.
Sorry.
We are not in that kind of relationship.
It doesn't look like it.
Then what can I do to make you a little happier?
Young man.
Buy a balloon for your girlfriend and she'll be happy.
You can cheer her up.
Buy one.
Do you want one?
No, thanks.
You really don't want it? I'm leaving.
Sir.
Xu Xiao.
How much?
Five yuan.
I'll scan your code.
Okay.
Thank you.
Do you
want this?
Is this...
Is this for me?
If it makes you happy,
here you go.
Thank you.
Young man.
Did you cheer up your girlfriend?
If not, get another one.
No need.
One is enough.
Are you sure?
Then I'm really leaving.
Thank you.
Let's go.