Xiaoxing.
Stop watching TV.
Do your Chinese homework in a while.
Got it.
Let's go.
Auntie,
let me watch a little longer.
I really just want to watch a little longer.
Talking is useless. Let's go.
Auntie.
Sis, only you can handle this.
Just like you when you were little.
This poem is a Han Yuefu folk song.
'He' means 'how'.
'Tiantian' refers to
the lush growth of lotus leaves.
I know what you're saying.
But the teacher asked us to write a 100-word reflection.
And I can't write a single word.
Then let's imagine
what kind of person would write this poem.
'Lotus can be picked in Jiangnan.'
So it's the lotus pickers watching the fish.
As for the lotus pickers,
it describes young men and women.
And the picking time
is right in midsummer.
It's the time when young men and women work together,
and express their love for each other.
You know, the 'lian' in lotus
is a homophone for tender love.
It symbolizes romance.
So when he saw the fish
playing around,
he thought of himself
picking lotuses and laughing with his beloved.
Got it?
So it's a love poem after all.
That's easy.
I know all about love.
What do you know?
Like you and that older guy.
Don't talk nonsense. What older guy?
He walks you home every day.
You pick lotuses together.
Who told you to talk nonsense?
I'm not talking nonsense.
Don't you look at him on your phone every day?
Give it back.
No.
Give me my phone.
I won't.
Give it back. Give it back.
No.
Give it back
to me.
No.
Hurry up.
Xiaocen, how old are you?
Still playing around with Xiaoxing.
Auntie, my sister picked a lotus.
You.
What lotus picking?
Xiaoxing, what did you say?
My sister is teaching me to recite 'Picking Lotus'.
Xiaoxing, have you finished your homework?
Let's go do your homework.
Good morning.
Morning.
Let me help you.
No need.
It's fine.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Why is it that the more I talk to you,
the more you avoid me?
I'm not.
You're not?
No.
You call this not avoiding me?
I'm not.
I'm not avoiding you.
Good morning.
Why are you two crouching so low?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
You guys go ahead and talk.
I'm rooting for you.
In the Mo'e Xiaolu from the late Yuan and early Ming dynasties,
there is such a record.
Craftsmen made an adhesive by mixing gluten with lime
to glue those broken ceramics.
What is its disadvantage?
It cannot be soaked in water for a long time.
This means it is afraid of water.
Shortly after,
the technique of porcelain riveting appeared.
This small bowl
was repaired using the porcelain riveting technique.
The saying, 'Without a diamond drill,
don't take on porcelain work,'
refers to this technique.
Later on,
there emerged a technique that focuses more on artistry
and the aesthetics of the objects, known as gold repair.
To be exact,
the gold repair technique
should actually be called lacquer repair.
It involves applying raw lacquer to the broken porcelain pieces,
and then bonding them together.
Then on the surface of the object,
gold powder or gold leaf is applied
to form this appearance.
What's wrong?
Xu Xiao asked me to go to Taoxichuan this weekend.
Don't overthink it.
He usually comes to me
to talk about business.
What else did you expect?
Then go with me this weekend.
Sorry.
I have plans this weekend.
Is it too deliberate?
Xiaocen.
Xu Xiao.
Why did you ask me out to Taoxichuan?
Didn't I tell you?
There's a youth creative market here on weekends.
Many young artists will set up stalls here.
So I wanted to ask you to come and see.
I see.
Yeah.
Isn't it interesting?
Let's go then.
Okay.
Come on, take a look.
Imitation Ru ware.
Imitation Ru ware, one of the five great kilns of the Southern Song Dynasty.
Come and see.
Our main product is the Flora Cup.
All underglaze color.
Safe, hygienic, and durable.
Take a look.
How much is this, boss?
Does it have a theme?
The theme of this porcelain piece
is rebirth and repair.
Boss, how much is this?
Two hundred and eighty.
Two hundred and eighty, huh.
These are works of art restored from ceramics.
These works of yours
are not restoration.
Your works
are just piecing together broken porcelain shards.
They should be considered cultural and creative products.
Kid, are you buying something?
Excuse me.
Stop right there.
What's wrong?
Come, come here.
Take a look at our works.
Isn't our work pieced together?
Hasn't it been brought back to life?
Then how does it not count as restoration?
First of all,
restoration is a very rigorous matter.
On these works of yours,
there is still leftover glue.
Moreover,
these are all imitation antique porcelain pieces.
You've been scammed.
Have you seen ancient porcelain shards?
Jingjing.
Sorry.
That's just her temper.
She meant no harm.
All right.
Everyone has the right to speak.
I'm sorry too.
I was a bit reckless with my words just now.
Let's go.
I'm so mad.
It's fine.
Class,
to master porcelain repair,
we must first learn to make staples.
Today,
we'll learn how to make them.
The purpose of the staples
is to bind broken porcelain
tightly together.
As for the staples,
there are traditional shuttle-shaped ones,
as well as various decorative styles.
Porcelain repair uses staples to bind broken objects
tightly together.
We call this binding objects with iron.
It tightly binds broken porcelain together.
This is transforming broken pieces into a whole.
It's mealtime already.
But there isn't a single student from our class in the cafeteria.
What's going on?
Is Mr. Yue's assignment too difficult?
Yeah.
Don't mention it.
He asked us to hammer staples.
My hands are blistered.
We can't eat, Mr. Liang.
But you still have to eat when it's mealtime.
I ruined a bunch of them.
I have to start over again.
Then let me help you.
Mr. Liang.
Did Xu Xiao make these staples?
Mr. Liang, how could you tell?
This kind of technique
isn't something newly learned.
I heard Xu Xiao works at an antique shop.
He must be exposed to ceramic mending and kintsugi often.
He's already a master.
So,
the assignment Mr. Yue gave this time
in such a short period,
only Xu Xiao could finish it.
Look.
No wonder he looked so familiar.
That boy from before.
The one who broke the antique
and then cleared up the misunderstanding.
He's quite popular now.
Got some fame.
I'll be leaving first then.
Okay.
I'll finish this up
and head back too.
Drive safe.
Okay. Bye.
Bye.
You're the girl from the market that day.
Zhao Xiaocen.
Hello.
Did you make all these cups?
I didn't make them.
I just write on them.
That's also very impressive.
They look really nice.
Thank you.
By the way, I'm looking for Xu Xiao.
Is he here?
He's inside.
Thank you.
Hello, Xu Xiao.
You are the one from Taoxichuan.
What's up? Anything I can help you with?
I heard from a friend
that you appraise treasures here.
I have something I want you to look at.
Okay.
Please have a seat.
This is it.
Why are you back?
I left something behind.
It's
at Boss Wang's place.
Do you know where
these porcelain pieces were found?
Xianghu Village, Fuliang County.
That explains it.
The pieces I saw at your stall a couple of days ago
were probably made
by the same person.
I found it.
Okay.
Drive safe.
Bye,
Xiaocen.
You can tell that?
These broken pieces
were obviously picked up
from the ceramic dump in Xianghu Village.
They are defective fragments of pottery,
glued together.
It seems like turning waste into treasure,
very valuable,
but there is no real technique involved.
This item
is fine to play with,
but in my opinion,
it's not worth collecting.
Then do you think a work like this
can still be saved?
From what I can see right now,
it's about combining more complex techniques
in ceramic restoration
with the imagination of the ceramic artist.
What techniques?
Like porcelain stapling and Kintsugi.
Porcelain stapling can be applied
to more complex shapes
to make the work sturdier.
Kintsugi can enhance the artistic value
and create more possibilities.
I know a bit about what you're saying.
Were you just doing
porcelain stapling restoration?
Yes.
Do you also know Kintsugi
or other cultural relic restoration techniques?
Can you do them all?
I've just done some research on them.
How is it?
My little pavilion has some style, right?
Recently,
our Jingdezhen
will have a large number of tourists coming.
So let's take out these nice-looking, fun,
and reasonably priced little plates and bowls
to sell.
You two sit here
and do a good job selling.
Be a good front for the shop,
got it?
The girl is pretty, and the boy is handsome.
Alright, I won't be an eyesore here.
Don't just focus on romance, you know?
Get this month's sales performance up for me.
We used to go to the market,
but I didn't expect
that we would end up being vendors today.
How much for these small cups with characters?
Thirty yuan each.
Do you have the characters 'Zhuge' and 'Ran'?
I don't see them.
Found them. Here.
Please wrap them up for me.
Okay, thanks.
Found them.
Here you go.
You can scan there.
It's sixty yuan in total.
Thank you.
Okay, take care.
How is it?
It doesn't seem too hard, right?
It's quite interesting.
How about
you try it with the next customer?
I'll be right beside you. Don't worry.
You do it.
Feel free to look around.
You're deciding between these two, right?
How did you know?
For these small animal ornaments,
we have a buy one, get one free offer.
If you like both of them,
you can take them both
for thirty yuan.
Then I'll take both.
Please wrap them up for me.
Okay.
Here you go.
Take care.
Relax.
You did great.
I'm just like this.
Every time I see strangers,
I get nervous easily.
But when you talk to me,
aren't you fine?
Because we're familiar.
Look,
I told you.
We still need to do mid-to-high-end.
The way you do things,
this time we came to Taoxichuan
and sold the studio's stuff,
but it didn't even cover our travel
and meal expenses.
Once we run this studio and exhibition
properly,
and get investments,
I'll open a showroom like this for you
and make you the chief ceramic artist.
Let's go.
Jingjing,
I have something to discuss with you.
I want to delay
the opening time a bit.
And we also need more hands.
Do you have
any candidates in mind?
Just take your time polishing it.
Sorry to bother you again.
I didn't introduce myself last time, did I?
My name is Fang Xiaqing.
The works you saw at Taoxichuan before,
and the one I showed you last time,
were all made by me.
So you're here this time to...
I
am here to recruit you.
I hope you can join my studio.
I'm sorry.
I might be a bit abrupt today.
I wonder if you have time
to visit my studio.
My partner might be able to explain in more detail.
This is it.
We're here.
Come in.
These two rooms are our studios.
Here is the tearoom,
and inside is the main workspace.
This is our studio,
and also the place we rent to live.
Come, this way.
This is Tian Yuan, and this is Xiao Yu.
Hello.
They are our roommates,
and also our studio partners.
Hello.
We're busy.
Just pretend we've already stood up
and hugged you.
Welcome.
You guys go ahead.
Okay.
If you want it,
you can note down the artwork number.
Then,
you can send me a direct message.
Today's live stream
ends here.
Bye-bye.
Are you just ending the stream like this?
I streamed for an hour,
and had only five viewers.
Let me introduce you.
This is Jingjing,
the boss of Banlan.
You've met before.
You are...
Xu Xiao.
You're the one from Taoxichuan that day.
Yes, that's right.
Here for a visit?
Yes.
Okay, take a look around.
Come.
These are the works of Banlan.
Look at these flowers.
They are scrap pieces I collected from a kiln.
I used broken porcelain pieces of different colors and textures
and pieced them together.
Are the basic materials of all your works
discarded porcelain pieces?
Yes.
Then why did you think of
using these discarded porcelain pieces?
Because it's cheap.
That's true.
How is it?
After seeing these works,
do you like them?
They're quite distinctive.
Here.
Thank you.
You haven't answered me yet.
Do you want to work with me?
It's okay.
Take your time.
Contact me when you've decided.
Okay.
So what do you think?
This Fang Xiaqing...
What
about her?
I criticized her work.
Not only was she not angry,
but she also invited me to collaborate.
Instead of being a sculpture teacher,
she came to Jingdezhen for cultural creations.
Actually, I also want to explore
whether artifact restoration can
be combined with ceramic art.
Maybe.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I
think Fang Xiaqing's studio is pretty good.