What do you think?
Yeah, it looks good.
Now for the lipstick...
This is the one I usually use.
Do you want to try it?
Huh? You're not a germaphobe, are you?
No, that's not it... Um...
That's not what I meant.
But it's probably better
to have your own lipstick, right?
Want to go buy one?
- Ooh, it's a new release...
- This one over here looks nice.
- I'm interested.
- Mmm.
This shade is pretty natural.
It's not exactly "cute,"
but it's a very flattering color.
Oh... Sorry, Yuki.
Can I use the restroom real quick?
Sure, I'll just look around here.
(If I had something like this,
maybe I could be a little better?)
(I ended up buying it...
I'll just give it to him as a thank-you gift for today.)
(Wh-what?!
Who... Who is that?!)
(Could it be... Yuki's girlfriend?!)