(theme music)
DR. ROMANTIC SEASON 3
THE CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS, AND
EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE WORKS OF FICTION
EPISODE 6
(whimsical music)
(phone vibrates)
MOM
JEONGSEON BUS TERMINAL
Excuse me, sir.
Who are you?
Do you happen
to know a Doldam Hospital here?
Well, of course.
In Jeongseon,
everyone knows Doldam Hospital.
Why are you asking?
Are you sick?
Where's your mother?
I came to see my dad.
My dad is a doctor at Doldam Hospital.
Oh, really?
I have a nephew who works there too.
So which doctor is he?
Do you want me to call your dad?
No, you can't do that.
My dad can't know that I came here.
Oh, I see.
Okay, let's see.
If you go over there,
there will be a bus stop.
Take Bus Number 15 or 36 from there.
They'll take you
straight to Doldam Hospital.
(chuckles)
Okay, thank you.
You're welcome.
By the way,
does the doctor called Master Kim
still work at the hospital?
DOLDAM HOSPITAL
TRAUMA BAY 1
(tense music)
(clicks)
INSU (crying):
I forgot about that patient.
That's why he died.
It's my fault.
Master Kim.
(sighs)
FRONT 2 & FRONT 3
POLICE
FRONT 2
INTENSIVE OBSERVATION AREA 3
TRAUMA BAY 1
INTENSIVE OBSERVATION AREA 2
(phone vibrates)
WIFE
(phone continues vibrating)
(sighs)
(crosswalk beeps)
Be careful, miss!
CHILD: Be careful!
It's dangerous!
(intense music)
CHILD: Be careful, miss!
It's dangerous!
Miss, be careful!
(tires squeal)
(upbeat music)
VOLUME 6
PARAMEDIC 1: Patient incoming!
At the crosswalk
in front of Jeongseon Terminal, a truck--
Wait, we didn't receive any calls
about a patient. What's going on?
Oh, I forgot! That way.
The Trauma Center is that way.
No, not that way!
-HYEONJEONG: This way is faster!
-This way, hurry!
-PARAMEDIC 1: Quickly!
-PARAMEDIC 2: Let's go!
-Hurry!
-Go quickly!
HYEONJEONG: Hurry.
(breathes heavily)
(whimsical music)
DOLDAM HOSPITAL
How are the patient's vitals?
PARAMEDIC 1: Vitals are 100/70.
Heart rate 110.
However, her saturation level
is too low. It's only 75%.
Ma'am, can you hear me?
We gave her plenty of oxygen
through a non-rebreather mask,
but her breathing's been odd.
Her lung sounds are abnormal.
Are her lungs injured?
I think she has asthma.
Nurse Choi, prepare for an ultrasound
-and page Pulmonology.
-NURSE CHOI: Yes.
-Let's start with intubation.
-Okay.
Have you contacted the guardian?
PARAMEDIC 1: Not yet.
Here's her phone, Doctor.
EUNJAE: Her medical information
is written here.
She has asthma and pulmonary fibrosis.
EUNJAE: She even has
pulmonary hypertension.
INSU: Tube, please.
Take it out.
I'll take a look at her stomach.
(Insu sighs)
Her spleen is completely ruptured.
Could you go lower?
INSU: Yes, like that.
Looks like there is bleeding
in the kidney too.
The left side is filled with blood.
Isn't surgery too risky
since she has pulmonary hypertension?
Let's first run some blood tests
and take a look
at her ABG analysis results.
Quickly page Dr. Nam.
Okay.
(whimsical music continues)
CHILD: Gosh, that scared me.
Who are you?
How did you get here?
Are you hurt somewhere?
No, I came to see someone.
Who did you come to see?
Do you happen
to know someone called Master Kim?
What?
(phone vibrates)
What's this?
Hello?
Uncle-in-law?
Yes, it's me.
It's just… The more I think about it,
the more it bothers me.
What is it?
Yes.
Wait, what?
Daughter?
What?
Yes, apparently.
Apparently.
Yes, I'm almost sure of it.
That's ridiculous!
I said the same thing,
that it's complete nonsense.
However, all the circumstances
say otherwise.
Her dad is a doctor at Doldam Hospital,
but it's a secret she can't tell.
Plus, she's looking for Master Kim.
Isn't it mysterious and heartrending
like something out of
a narrative structure?
No, Chief Jang.
It can't be, right?
It's definitely not true, Nurse Oh.
I may not know everything,
but I know about his familial relations.
-It's not true.
-(phone vibrates)
It's another patient. Goodness.
I'll be going now.
It's most definitely not true!
(shouts)
See?
What did I say? I told you it's not true.
I wasted my time on this. Gosh.
I believe what my uncle-in-law told me.
He may talk a lot,
but he doesn't make things up.
Then…
(Doil groans)
The patient's condition is really bad.
Shouldn't we
at least open her up to stop the bleeding?
Surgery is really risky
for someone with pulmonary hypertension.
Even if it's a success,
there could be a lot
of serious complications afterward.
Most importantly,
we don't know
if she'll make it through the surgery.
Would it really be that hard?
For now, I will open an operating room.
Because despite the risk,
surgery is our only option.
-Let's get ready.
-Okay.
Hold on, everyone.
Due to pulmonary hypertension,
this patient is in a state of RV failure.
If the bleeding
causes a reduction in preload,
you won't be able
to maintain pulmonary circulation.
JINMAN: That could result in
not hypervolemia,
but hypoxia,
which you won't be able to control.
JINMAN: Dr. Seo Woojin,
reconsider…
this operation.
WOOJIN: Professor Cha.
If we keep a blood transfusion going
while we stop the bleeding,
wouldn't that work?
If we don't do anything,
this patient will die within an hour.
I heard that you have some experience
working with trauma,
so you should know what will happen
as soon as you operate
on someone in that condition.
You won't be able to focus on the bleeding
because of the adhesions,
and she'll die on the table.
Is it really necessary
to operate on a patient
who has less than a 20% chance to live?
A 20% chance to live
is more than enough reason
for me to operate.
I've saved patients with even worse odds.
But in most cases,
it didn't go well, did it?
You've probably received hate
and been sued by the patients' guardians.
You've probably been to the police station
and questioned countless times too.
Even so,
am I supposed to give up on a patient?
Yes, give up.
(tense music)
-What?
-Excuse me, Professor Cha Jinman.
From what I can see, there is…
no hope for this patient.
(sighs)
WOMAN: What do you mean?
What do you mean by "there is no hope"?
Why would there be
no hope for my daughter?
Are you saying
she's going to die?
WOMAN: Well?
(breathes shakily)
SABU: Here.
Drink this. It's barley tea.
If you drink that,
it will warm you right up.
But why did you come looking for me?
I have something important
to discuss with you.
What would that be?
But…
are you sure you're Master Kim?
(chuckles)
Well, of course, I am.
See? Look here.
It says, "Master Kim."
Right?
(chuckles)
What is it?
It's just…
you look a lot different
from what I imagined.
What do you mean by different?
It's just…
I don't know.
(laughs softly)
(playful music)
(whispering)
See that? A dad's smile.
Are you sure it's a dad's smile?
Yes, of course.
There's so much affection in his gaze.
What do we do? Do you think he saw us?
We were a little faster. Don't worry.
Okay.
What are you two doing here?
My shoelaces were untied, so…
(phone vibrates)
Hello, Eunjae.
-That seemed natural, right?
-Yes.
He didn't notice
that there were no shoelaces.
(in English)
Okay.
(in Korean)
Hi.
Master Kim, I think you should
come over here right now.
Why? Did something happen?
It's just…
An emergency patient can't
get into an operating room.
Is Seo Woojin not there?
He's here, but…
(sighs)
Professor Cha
isn't allowing him to operate.
What?
(tense music)
Please tell me.
What about my daughter?
WOMAN (voice breaking):
What's wrong with her?
Is something bad going to happen to her?
There's severe bleeding
in the abdominal cavity,
but if we operate--
JINMAN: Yes.
The patient is in a very bad condition.
JINMAN: There's a lot of bleeding
in the abdomen so we need to operate.
However, your daughter
has pulmonary hypertension,
so even operating will be difficult.
-Professor Cha--
-It's unfortunate,
but there isn't much we can do
in her current condition.
JINMAN: The operation
will be meaningless as well.
(cries)
HEAD OF TRAUMA CENTER, CHA JINMAN
WOOJIN: But if you insist,
-I'll do my best and operate--
-JINMAN: Dr. Seo Woojin.
There are many risks,
but there's still a chance, so…
Professor Cha Jinman?
Are you Professor Cha Jinman
of Hanguk University's
Department of Cardiothoracic Surgery?
Yes, that's right.
(breathes shakily)
Oh!
(all gasp)
WOMAN: Why are you here?
"There is no hope"?
How dare you say something like that
to my daughter again?
WOOJIN: Ma'am, please.
You can't do this here.
Get away from my daughter immediately!
You terrible doctor!
You demonic man!
WOMAN (crying): This is all your fault!
Because of you,
my daughter
didn't get proper treatment on time
and never got compensated either.
You made my daughter like this.
Do you know that?
(yells)
Do you?
(wails loudly)
WOOJIN: Ma'am, please calm down.
(woman continues crying)
(machines beep frantically)
Doctor,
the patient's saturation level is falling!
Come on, Dr. Seo Woojin.
-Dr. Jung.
-Yes.
(crying)
Yurim.
What are you doing?
Take the guardian outside.
(tense music)
Woojin.
-How is she?
-Nurse Joo.
WOOJIN: The patient has asthma.
And due to pulmonary fibrosis
and pulmonary hypertension,
she's practically
in a state of RV failure.
There's severe hemorrhaging in the abdomen
and her spleen is completely ruptured.
DOIL: With her medical history,
we don't know how much adhesion there is,
so it'll be dangerous.
Master Kim…
SABU: Ma'am.
We will try to save Yurim.
Can she live?
You may have heard this already,
but she's in a very bad condition.
(cries)
It will be hard to access
the bleeding areas due to adhesion,
and because of her underlying disease,
she may not make it through the surgery.
(sobs)
SABU: Even after surgery,
there could be respiratory failure.
We can temporarily
keep her alive with ECMO,
but besides a lung transplant,
there may not be any other options.
(cries)
However, ma'am,
we should
still do everything we can, right?
Yurim…
SABU: She did her best to get this far.
Right?
(sobs)
Please save her.
Please save Yurim, Doctor.
YURIM'S MOM: Please save my daughter.
Okay, let's give it a shot.
All right.
Ma'am, you need
to sign the consent form first.
INSU: This way.
(continues crying)
SABU: Let's go, Doil.
Okay, I'll open up a room.
We'll move the patient.
SABU: Eunjae, put in a call to KONOS.
Tell them she's been waiting two years
for a lung transplant and it's urgent.
Even if we stop the bleeding,
if she doesn't get a lung transplant,
she won't make it past a week.
Yes, Master Kim.
Mm.
What are you doing?
How is this a trauma center
when everything moves so slowly?
I gave you the fast lane,
so why do you keep hitting the brakes?
Don't you know that every second counts
when it comes to a severe trauma case?
It's not because I don't know that!
It's because the patient
can't be operated on.
You're operating on a patient
with an obvious outcome.
What are you trying to do?
(yelling) Do you only see the patient,
and not the doctor?
Just how many doctors
did you screw over like this?
JINMAN: Last year's records alone
show 20 cases of Doldam Hospital's doctors
called in for investigation.
And 11 of those cases were Dr. Seo's.
JINMAN: But you.
You said he's your most cherished pupil
so why do you keep
making him perform ridiculous operations?
JINMAN: Why do you keep
putting that kind of risk
on the doctors? Just why?
Because that's
a doctor's job.
He's doing what a doctor should.
Should there be another reason?
(scoffs)
(sighs)
You're a lunatic.
(upbeat music)
Let's move the patient.
Yes, we're currently
moving the patient to the OR,
but the patient won't be able
to make it past a week.
That's why you, Bu Yongju,
even with your skills
will forever be known
as a third-rate doctor.
Do you know that?
Is that so?
Then so be it.
You lunatic.
SABU: By the way,
did you know...
that the patient on her way
to the OR, Bae Yurim,
is a humidifier victim?
She came to me as a patient two years ago,
but she started
being sick over 12 years ago.
She was only eight years old then.
She endured 12 years
without being able to breathe properly.
(sighs)
Can you even imagine
the pain she went through?
Even if I am a third-rate doctor,
if I can do anything to help,
I'm willing to do my best.
Got it?
(sighs)
EUNJAE: Put this against your head.
Just what happened?
Are you not going to tell me?
(sighs)
Around 12 years ago,
there was a compensation lawsuit
for an issue with a humidifier.
The court asked me
to issue a written opinion.
So the patient
in the lawsuit was Bae Yurim?
I could not clearly establish
whether the cause of her asthma
was because of an underlying disease
or a humidifier.
I wrote and submitted my opinion
according to my conscience
and medical views.
And this time, you were against
that patient's emergency surgery?
Do you know when I feel most disillusioned
with my job as a doctor?
It's when I have to deal with
impersonal individuals like them.
They have little to no courtesy
or respect for human beings.
They question and criticize the opinions
of experts however they want.
They endlessly tear others down,
turning their achievements
and dignity into their shame overnight.
They mock and condemn them
and call it justice.
(sighs)
I've had it up to here
with those kinds of people.
I'm also sick and tired
of that punk, Bu Yongju,
who defends those kinds of people.
Master Kim spends every moment
trying to do his best for his patients.
He helped me find pride
in being a doctor too.
The world doesn't care
about something like your pride, Eunjae.
JINMAN: Understand?
(door opens)
Dr. Cha, could you come out for a moment?
Let's talk later, Dad.
POLICE: Hello.
We have additional information
regarding Bae Yurim's accident.
WOOJIN: Since there was a lot of delay,
I'll try to stop the bleeding first.
SABU: Don't rush. Do as you always have,
at your own pace. Okay?
WOOJIN: Scalpel.
(tense music)
WOOJIN: Metz.
WOOJIN: Give me a lot of gauze, please.
More.
Dr. Nam,
will the patient be able to hold on?
DOIL: Just focus on the operation,
I'll try to keep her stable.
Add five units of packed RBC and FFP each.
-NURSE: Okay.
-DOIL: I'm starting the RIS.
SABU: All right.
-Three.
-Two.
-One.
-AREUM: Done!
Ah!
This is the best time to eat this.
Is this a Friday tradition
at Doldam Hospital as well?
No, it's not a tradition.
It just tastes the best at this hour.
You get hungry
right after the first wave of patients.
First wave?
So is there a second wave?
Well, on some days,
there's a third wave or a fourth wave too.
Doesn't that make you tired?
Of course, it does.
I'm always exhausted and past my limits.
Oh, I couldn't tell.
You're always smiling.
Well, it's very exhausting
but I'm also very proud.
I, Yoon Areum,
am a boring and insignificant person,
but as Dr. Yoon Areum,
I'm a pretty decent person.
I feel like I'm helping someone too.
You have a great mindset.
I think I know that feeling.
I came to Doldam
so I could know that feeling too.
That's my Dr. Ung.
You know what I'm talking about.
-(in English) Cheers.
(in Korean) "Dr. Ung?" What is that?
It's a nickname Dr. Cha made for him.
Everyone here calls him Dr. Ung.
What about me? Do I have one?
Should I make you one?
Hmm…
How about "Dr. Dong"?
Well, that's…
Ah…
Isn't that a little dangerous though?
If you don't say it carefully,
it can sound like Dr. Dung…
Then he'll be Dr. Dung.
Hey!
(phone vibrates)
Oh, I'll be leaving first,
so enjoy the rest of your meal.
(door closes)
SEONUNG: She said she had a boyfriend.
DONGHWA: What?
Dr. Yoon Areum.
She has a boyfriend
she's been dating for about three years.
How do you know this?
By coincidence.
I overheard it.
Dang it.
PATIENT: It hurts.
(groans)
Mix five doses of dextrose-saline
with two doses of thiamine.
-A brain CT too.
-Yes, Doctor.
Where is Nurse Eom?
She's on her 10-minute break.
I see.
Have you taken a break, Dr. Areum?
(gasps)
You won't believe this.
I went to take a break,
but I ended up giving ultrasound lessons
to Dr. Ung and Dr. Dong.
I see.
The two of them were practicing
with the ultrasound in the dark.
AREUM: It was so funny.
You should have seen them, Nurse Euntak.
-I don't really want to.
-AREUM: Why not?
(Donghwa clears throat)
What about the patient?
We're taking him to get a brain CT.
I see.
Oh! What's with your hand?
My hand? What about it?
No, the other hand.
There's nothing here either.
-Right. There really isn't anything.
-What?
I heard that you had a boyfriend
you've been dating for three years.
DONGHWA: But you don't seem to have
a couple's ring
and there are no signs
of you having worn a ring.
That must mean
it's not that serious, right?
-What?
-(chuckles softly)
(door opens)
Oh! What are you all doing out here?
Did a patient come in?
WOMAN 2: Doctor, over here!
-Please take a look at my husband!
-Nurse Eom.
This way, please!
PATIENT 2: Oh, my stomach!
AREUM: Sir.
I'll take the patient to get a CT.
Young man. Can you examine me?
(woman 3 belches)
(burps)
Okay.
(whimsical music)
(approaching footsteps)
NURSE KOO
(gasps)
GITAE: They look similar.
Really similar.
There's no doubt about it.
That little kid and Master Kim?
No, not Master Kim.
Those friendly eyes and sharp nose…
(yells)
I'm certain she looks like someone.
But I can't remember whom.
MUNJEONG: She's asking you to call back.
Who, me?
Your wife called me just now,
and she said
you wouldn't pick up the phone.
I was busy. That's why I didn't pick up.
Well, it's not that.
You should call her back.
I think it's about Byeol.
What about Byeol?
Is she sick?
She hasn't been able to contact Byeol
since this afternoon.
What?
Do you want to eat this?
How come whenever adults see little kids,
they always try to give them
something to eat?
Especially sweets
like candies, jelly, and chocolate?
They're the things that make moms mad
if you eat them.
So you don't want the lollipop?
By the way, this hospital is really big.
Right. Especially
since the Trauma Center was built,
this place became even bigger.
You'll keep this a secret
from my dad, right?
Don't worry. I'm good at keeping secrets.
(Mr. Koo laughs)
INSU: What are you saying?
Where is Byeol?
You're supposed to look after the kid.
You had one job!
You don't even know when she disappeared
or where she went.
Do you think that makes sense?
What did you say?
Hey.
Besides living expenses,
all the money I make goes home.
Why is nothing ever enough for you?
What else do you want from me?
I'm lonely too.
I'm worn out too, honey.
You're not the only one
having a hard time, all right?
Forget it.
I don't want to fight with you.
I'm tired of it.
Let's just stop! I'll look for Byeol here.
(sighs deeply)
(Insu sniffles)
(cries)
(tense music)
WOOJIN: Taking out the spleen.
WOOJIN: Suture, please.
-WOOJIN: Cut.
-SABU: Cut.
WOOJIN: I'll be moving on to the SMV.
-SABU: Doil?
-DOIL: Yes.
She's holding on well.
I'm doing my best too.
WOOJIN: Clamp.
Suture, please.
(Woojin grunts)
MYEONGSIM: Dr. Seo, are you okay?
WOOJIN: I'm sorry.
I'll go change my gloves real quick.
SABU: Suture, please.
-SABU: Cut.
-MYEONGSIM: Cut.
SABU: Irrigation.
WOOJIN: Give it to me, please.
WOOJIN: Richardson retractor.
There seems to only be a hematoma
in the retroperitoneum
and no active bleeding.
SABU: Okay. Let's finish up.
WOOJIN: We'll start closing up now.
What do mean my daughter
tried to commit suicide?
According to the driver, Ms. Bae Yurim
was standing in the middle of the road
even though the walk signal wasn't on.
POLICE: Even when there was a car coming,
she didn't try to move out of the way,
like she was standing there on purpose.
It also seems that way from the footage
on the driver's dashcam.
That's ridiculous.
Why would my daughter--
POLICE: By any chance,
did she have depression?
While investigating,
we found this
on her social media account.
BAE_YURIM_
#SENDING #CONDOLENCES #TO_MYSELF
What do you mean it wasn't an accident?
They say she walked into the road herself.
It looks like
she was trying to commit suicide.
(sighs)
I heard about Bae Yurim.
If it comes out
that she really did try to commit suicide,
she won't be able
to receive a lung transplant.
One of KONOS' principles is
to not give transplants
to patients with suicide risks.
JINMAN: Do you know what that means?
It means that the emergency surgery
you risked performing
was for nothing.
Now the patient's family
will receive a huge surgery bill
and the patient won't even survive a week
and die.
When your moments of hope go awry,
only this
harsh reality remains.
JINMAN: Do you know that?
Hello?
This is Byeol's father
who just made a report.
Have you still not heard anything?
No. Right now,
I'm on duty at the hospital…
(breathes shakily)
(voice breaking)
I'm on duty right now,
so please find her quickly.
She's only nine years old.
It's late at night and cold out.
I beg you, please.
Okay, thank you. Bye.
(sighs)
MR. KOO: Dr. Jung Insu.
CONSULTATION ROOM 2
Master Kim.
(inhales)
(whimpers)
SABU: Hey, Insu. Let her sleep.
It seems like
she went on a great adventure today.
-I'm sorry, Master Kim.
-What?
It seems she suddenly
wanted to see her dad.
She only left a note for her mom
and ran away from home.
INSU: Since she's only nine years old,
I doubted she would come here by herself.
I'm sorry.
(Insu sniffles)
Insu, are you…
estranged from your wife?
(soft music)
Do you know what "estranged" is?
"Estranged" is just "estranged."
Why?
My mom and dad
have been estranged for a year now.
They're not divorced,
but it's pretty similar.
I see.
Mom said it was
because of you, Master Kim.
She said you're holding on to him
and wouldn't let him go,
so he couldn't leave this place.
So if I'm being honest…
I came here to ask you to let him go, but…
But?
(sighs)
I think my mom and dad
just don't get along.
I heard them fighting earlier.
BYEOL: Even at my age,
I don't yell and fight like they do.
Gosh…
(sighs)
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm embarrassed.
It's not something
you should be worrying about.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
Stay with Byeol for a bit.
I'm going to go take a walk, okay?
(sniffles)
(somber music)
JINMAN: Just how many doctors
did you screw over like this?
It's my fault.
I will…
I will take full responsibility.
My mom and dad
have been estranged for a year now.
Do you only see the patient,
and not the doctor?
(Woojin grunts)
(sighs)
All right, sir, please show me your butt.
WOOJIN: What?
Okay, fine. Give me your arm then.
And they say
even monkeys fall from trees sometimes.
The surgery genius
stabbed his own finger during surgery.
EUNJAE: Hold it down, please.
How come you haven't gotten
better at giving shots?
As if. I have many years
of experience giving shots.
Anyway, it does seem a little futile
if she can't get a lung transplant.
Because I worked really hard.
We don't know that yet.
It's not conclusive yet.
Which finger was stabbed with the needle?
It's fine that you work hard,
but please don't hurt yourself.
Your blood is my blood
and your delicate bones are also mine.
-(snorts)
-EUNJAE: Okay?
Are you going home now?
Yes, since my strict father
is staying with me.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
(soft music)
(laughs softly)
WJ, EJ
(soft music continues)
EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
Master Kim.
WOOJIN: Master Kim?
Oh, hey.
What is it? Why aren't you going home?
I'm staying here for the time being.
(grunts)
Did you dress the wound properly?
-Yes, you don't have to worry about that.
-Mm.
The patient's viral markers
came back negative as well.
What happened earlier?
You've never made such mistakes before.
(laughs softly)
I think it's because I was anxious.
I wanted to reduce
the surgery time somehow,
so as to lessen the strain on the patient.
Also,
I wanted to show Professor Cha Jinman
that I could save the patient.
(chuckles)
Well, you're not the type of person
to perform an operation just to show off.
(laughs softly)
See?
I told you.
You're the only one who knows me best.
(chuckles)
For the time being, we'll keep
the Trauma Center in a dispatch format.
Whenever you need urgent trauma surgery,
I'll go over and conduct it.
However, I won't
be changing my affiliation.
At least let me decide that for myself.
WOOJIN: And please stop
making a Plan B for everything.
-(laughs)
-WOOJIN: You'll put me in a tough spot.
(laughs)
Okay, I won't.
All right. Keep up the good work.
Okay.
(exhales)
SOONYOUNG'S RESTAURANT
BREAKFAST AVAILABLE
Woojin, you're here.
Yes, I'm hungry. Please give me some food.
SOONYOUNG'S MOM: Okay, take a seat.
What about Eunjae?
I haven't seen her around lately.
Her father is here from Seoul,
so she's been busy.
I see.
So are you making a formal introduction?
-(coughs)
-And choosing a wedding date?
Hey, if you need
a stand-in mom, let me know.
I'll get my hair done at the nearby salon,
wear my best clothes,
and be your stand-in mom, okay?
Okay, please do.
I'll bring your food out soon.
WOOJIN: Okay.
(whimsical music)
Woojin, are you
getting married?
Woojin, are you getting married?
Well, I…
EUNJAE: Dad,
have you heard from real estate yet?
Yes, there are a few houses,
but they're a little far from here.
Oh, I see.
Why?
Is your roommate complaining?
Asking me to leave faster?
No, that's not it.
My roommate says it's okay,
but I just feel bad.
About Seo Woojin…
Seo Woojin?
What about Seo Woojin?
Pick a day next week
so we can eat together.
JINMAN: I'll do the dishes,
so just leave them.
I disapprove.
You see,
marriage isn't something you do just
because you have feelings for them.
INSU: When you have feelings for someone,
the furthest you should go is dating.
Marriage
is like one of the pillars
in the multi-universe of chaos.
Why are you trying so hard
to go into that chaotic universe?
Just live comfortably by yourself.
Dad, you know I can hear you, right?
Of course, there is an upside to marriage.
Like having a beautiful daughter like her.
Having Byeol
was my greatest accomplishment in life.
However,
you…
You need to think
about this more carefully.
And who's going to be your father-in-law?
Professor Cha Jinman?
Seriously?
Are you crazy?
Should I tell Eunjae
what you said just now?
Hey!
Why tell her something
that was said between two men?
But I'm not a man.
Of course.
You're a girl, Byeol.
You're a child.
INSU: And my daughter, right?
I want to get married if Eunjae wants to.
Here.
I want to have
a pretty daughter like Byeol too.
WOOJIN: And exercise with her
in the mornings too.
(snorts loudly)
INSU: What?
In your dreams.
Just waking up every morning
to send your kid off
to kindergarten is a war.
It's such a hassle.
Dad!
Of course, it's not like that anymore,
right?
By the way,
was that lady's surgery a success?
-Who?
-Ms. Bae Yurim.
The one who got into an accident
in front of the terminal yesterday.
Byeol, how do you know about her?
I witnessed the whole thing.
I called 911 too.
I even took the ambulance
with her to Doldam Hospital.
What?
But how did you know
her name was Bae Yurim?
She told me in the ambulance.
(crosswalk beeping)
(grunts)
(Yurim chokes)
Be careful, miss!
-(chokes)
-BYEOL: Be careful!
It's dangerous!
A car is coming!
YURIM: I should have waited.
I should have crossed at the next light.
I knew I would only be able
to take a few steps
before getting winded.
Why did I do it?
(exhales)
So…
what happens now?
Can Yurim get a transplant now?
Yes. I believe so, ma'am.
(sighs in relief)
The little girl who witnessed
what happened and called 911
testified to it all.
SABU: The paramedics who were
in the ambulance also gave statements
about everything that they heard.
(exhales)
(Yurim's mom cries)
(light, hopeful music)
(laughs softly)
When you get to Seoul,
Mom will be waiting for you.
I'll be in big trouble, right?
Well, of course.
You ran away without saying anything.
Can I come again next time?
With your mom's permission.
I wish I lived with you.
BYEOL: But…
I think you're really cool
for working here.
(laughs emotionally)
Thank you, Byeol.
BYEOL: But…
Woojin is a little cooler.
-What?
-(playful music)
Hurry up and go.
The bus is leaving soon.
I love you, Dad!
I…
I love you too.
(mouthing silently)
See you next time.
I'm against this surgery.
What exactly are you against?
We already got KONOS' approval for it.
I do not wish
for Master Kim to perform it.
But what do you mean by that?
The patient is under Master Kim's care,
so if not him,
then who can perform this surgery?
Professor Cha Jinman.
-What?
-Cha Jinman?
Why should I
perform that surgery?
MINGUK: You want the Trauma Center,
don't you?
If you want it that badly,
you need to earn the staff's favor.
And in order to do that,
you need to perform this surgery.
Are you
asking me to put
on a performance, Director Park?
If you believe that will shift the tides,
then you must.
(phone vibrates)
What are you going to do?
Do you want to perform this surgery?
What's the real reason for you doing this?
As you said, I only know one thing.
So in one person's eyes, I seem reckless.
In another's, I seem dangerous.
And in someone else's,
I may seem like a lunatic.
SABU: But I
was okay with that.
I didn't care.
SABU: However…
(Sabu sighs)
…now I'm not sure
if it's okay with the others.
So show me.
How you would do it,
what solution you have in mind.
First, help Yurim get her life back,
the one that stopped 12 years ago.
Then, your time here
will begin anew.
MYEONGSIM: Did you know?
I don't like the way
you conduct your business at all,
Professor Park Minguk.
Did you know, Nurse Oh?
For the last three years,
you've never called me Director.
(chuckles)
I guess I haven't.
You have the title
of Doldam Hospital's Director,
but I suppose it can't be helped
that I'm still wary of you.
I hope you get over it soon.
I don't really feel the need
to put in the effort to.
SABU: Please don't worry too much, ma'am.
Professor Cha Jinman performs
lung surgeries very well.
He has much more experience
than me in that field as well.
That man
never said he was sorry.
I still don't believe
what I did was wrong.
All I did 12 years ago
was my opinion as a doctor,
and my thoughts on the matter
still haven't changed.
JINMAN: I never sided with anyone
and did not make it personal.
Your daughter's surgery today
will also be that way.
As a doctor, I will do the best that I can
without any prejudice
or personal feelings.
You can count on that.
(sobs)
Please take care of her.
YURIM'S MOM: I was furious
but there was nothing else I could do
because saving my daughter comes first.
(cries)
EUNJAE (sighing): I'm nervous.
You can't make a mistake, Cha Eunjae.
WOOJIN: Is this your first operation
with Professor Cha?
EUNJAE: Yes, it's my first time,
so I'm super nervous.
Right, when's your next day off?
WOOJIN: Why?
EUNJAE: Professor Cha wants
to eat together, so make some time for it.
(tense music)
(door opens)
-DOIL: Please lower the ECMO flow rate.
-NURSE 2: Okay.
WOOJIN: What's going on?
MYEONGSIM: Apparently,
Professor Cha Jinman called everyone here.
I guess he's planning
to put on a performance.
INFORMATION
JINMAN: Patient's name, Bae Yurim.
Age, 20 years old.
She has pulmonary fibrosis
and secondary pulmonary hypertension.
We will begin
the lung transplant surgery now.
Dr. Nam Doil?
DOIL: The patient's vitals
and saturation level are stable.
You may begin.
JINMAN: Dr. Cha Eunjae?
EUNJAE: Yes, I'm ready.
JINMAN: Scalpel.
(upbeat rock music)
WOOJIN: At that time, I didn't realize
that the more solid your heart is,
the more
difficult and meticulous
the trials become.
That the more solid it is,
even the smallest of cracks
can leave a mark.
(upbeat rock music continues)
You seem to be studying very hard.
Yes, whenever I get the chance.
(inhales)
Uh...
By the way, about Dr. Areum,
have you ever
seen the person she's dating?
(playful music)
She said
they've been dating for three years,
so I thought maybe you've seen him before.
DONGHWA: What kind of man is he?
(turns page)
Why are you asking?
I'm just curious
about how he looks.
(sighs)
He looks like this.
I'm the man dating Areum.
(sighs)
Damn it.
(upbeat music)
DR. ROMANTIC SEASON 3
MYEONGSIM: There was a shooting incident
at the nearby military base.
GITAE: He's still on the run.
WOOJIN: One bullet is still
in the abdomen.
DOIL: Cardiac arrest!
EUNJAE: I failed this patient.
DOIL: The blood transport vehicle
is stuck in traffic?
MINGUK: Run!
INSU: The shooter who is on the run
seems to be inside the hospital.
JINMAN: You should get out too. Evacuate.
What about Seo Woojin?
AREUM: I looked everywhere
in the hospital, but I couldn't find him.
SABU: Seo Woojin!