(theme music)
DR. ROMANTIC SEASON 3
THE CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS AND
EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE WORKS OF FICTION
(breathes heavily)
(woodboard creaking)
(gun cocks)
(panting)
KOREA-JAPAN EEZ INTERMEDIATE AREA,
DAEHWATOE, EAST SEA, CURRENT TIME 23:18
(suspenseful music)
(horn honking)
COAST GUARD
What's going on?
There's a doubtful vessel on the radar.
Operator, report detections.
Radar one, reporting detections.
OPERATOR: Heading 30 degrees,
3,000km away.
The vessel seems to immobile.
Attempting to contact the small target.
-Search for a signal for the ship.
-OFFICER 1: Yes, sir.
Contacting the immobile vessel.
This is Coast Guard ship P-3008.
Do you read?
OFFICER 1 (in English, on intercom):
This is Korea Coast Guard.
Vessel heading 30 degrees.
Do you read me? Over.
This is Korea Coast Guard.
Vessel heading 30 degrees.
Do you read me? Over.
(in Mandarin) This is Korea Coast Guard.
Vessel heading 30 degrees.
Do you read me? Over.
This is Korea Coast Guard.
Vessel heading 30 degrees.
Do you read me? Over.
(in Korean)
There's no response.
This is the captain of 3008.
We've found a doubtful vessel.
Please provide information.
Grant permission for inspection as well.
OFFICER 2: Upon inquiring with the navy,
there is no information.
Granting permission for inspection.
Chief, carry out the inspection.
Gather the inspection team.
Yes, sir.
(alarm honking)
(honking continues)
Team One, take the wheelhouse.
Team Two, search the deck and engine room.
There could be an ambush,
so keep your guard up.
CHIEF: If they open fire,
fire back right away and gain control.
Got it?
ALL: Yes, sir!
Let's move.
(action music)
Dolphin One, this is Alpha Ship.
LEADER: Alpha, this is Dolphin One.
Check the vessel's condition
and report back if it's possible to board.
LEADER: Checking.
Alpha, this is Dolphin One.
Suspicious vessel not showing resistance.
No obstacles in the way of boarding.
Able to board with our numbers
and equipment. Awaiting orders.
Captain, should we board and take control?
Okay, board. Take control.
Dolphin, inspection team leader,
board and take control.
LEADER: Boarding. We will take control.
(tense music)
(tense music continues)
(object clatters)
(gun clicks)
(coughs)
(man panting)
(grunts)
(door clanks)
(tense music)
LEADER (in Mandarin):
Drop your weapons. Hands in the air.
(in Mandarin)
Where are we?
Where are you from?
LEADER (in Korean):
We are the Korean Coast Guard.
Where are you from?
(knife clanks)
Help us.
We are from North Korea.
(shaky breathing)
PRESENTER 1:
The traffic congestion heading to Seoul…
PRESENTER 2: Today, six representatives
from North Korea…
EPISODE 1
…crossed the DMZ
in order to attend the summit--
PRESENTER 3: It's four degrees
in Seoul and the surrounding area,
but Gwangju is--
PRESENTER 4: This song was requested
by one of our listeners.
We'll be back with part 3 after the song.
(soft music playing)
(man clears throat)
(whistles)
(whistling continues)
(cell phone buzzing)
(medic breathes shakily)
(coughs)
(medical equipments clatter)
When are the other doctors coming?
MEDIC: They'll be here soon. Please wait
just a little longer.
(medic breathes shakily)
(helicopter blades whirring)
Do you hear that?
They're coming now.
(helicopter whirring continues)
CURRENT TIME: 12:08 A.M.
PILOT: P-3008, we're returning home.
Report current weather status.
COAST GUARD
What's this?
They're kids.
They're the team that saved former
Defense Minister Ryu Woongil's life.
(sighs)
Lieutenant Ko Eunho.
Hello, we're from Doldam Hospital.
I'm emergency physician Jung Insu.
This is surgeon Seo Woojin.
And this is
nurse practitioner Park Euntak.
Let's see the patient first.
We heard it was a gunshot.
-Before that, you must sign some forms.
-INSU: What?
As of this moment, everything that occurs
on this ship is strictly confidential.
LIEUTENANT KO: You may only ask
the minimum information required
about the patient for treatment.
If you do not comply,
you may be court-martialed
for violation of national security laws.
National security…
There. Can we see the patient now?
This way.
Where's Master Kim?
Eunjae went to find him.
We'll hear from her soon.
Wait up, Euntak.
(tense music)
EUNJAE: You know,
there are three things
I never do after sundown.
One of them is driving at night.
Does this make any sense right now?
I don't even drive on an eight-lane road
in Seoul at nighttime.
But at this time of night,
and on a bumpy unpaved road at that?
Gosh.
-Oh, dear.
-My goodness.
What are you doing, Dr. Jang?
You still can't reach Master Kim?
I keep calling, but he's not picking up.
Gosh, Master Kim. Please pick up.
SABU (singing):
♪ The world is lonely and melancholy ♪
♪ At times, you need a friend too ♪
♪ Even if you leave ♪
♪ For somewhere far away ♪
(song continues on radio)
This way.
LIEUTENANT KO: You may go inside.
How are the patient's vitals?
MEDIC: What? Oh, right.
BP 100/70, heart rate 120.
WOOJIN: Blood loss?
MEDIC: He had already lost a lot of blood
when I got here.
I'm not sure exactly…
We'll take charge from now on. Step back.
MEDIC: Okay.
Step back.
Sir? Can you hear me?
(groans in pain)
He's in a stupor.
When did he lose consciousness?
MEDIC: I'm not sure about that either.
He was like this when I got here.
Scissors, please.
Let's check his back.
One, two, three.
No exit wounds.
It means both bullets are still inside.
Let's see the ultrasound.
(suspenseful music)
(woman coughs)
(Insu sighs)
He has severe hemoperitoneum.
INSU: It's a liver injury, right?
Yes, it looks that way.
But there's too much blood,
even up to the spleen.
Right? There could more bleeding.
Can we do general anesthesia?
MEDIC: Here, in the treatment room?
That might be hard.
We don't have an anesthesiologist--
Dr. Jung, can you handle sedation?
Can we take him to a hospital?
I don't think he'll last.
He's lost a lot of blood,
but he's in bad shape in general.
Also, he might be…
Why? What is it?
Is something else wrong?
There is a possibility of an IVC injury.
(tense music)
Where is the treatment room?
Let's see your equipment first.
MEDIC: This is it.
This is the only place
you can treat patients
on this ship.
SEO WOOJIN
It's Dr. Seo Woojin.
-Answer it.
-Okay.
SEO WOOJIN
-DONGHWA: Here.
-Hey.
Hey, Eunjae.
What's going on? What about Master Kim?
I don't know yet. He won't even pick up.
You still haven't found him?
Cha Eunjae!
That's why I'm doing my best!
But I can't find him anywhere.
We've been circling this area
for an hour already.
(Eunjae pants)
Wait, over there!
Where? Is he here?
-There.
-Where?
Did you find him? Did you find Master Kim?
Stay on the line. Darn it.
(gasps)
EUNJAE: Master!
Gosh, Master Kim!
Were you here the whole time?
Why didn't you answer your phone?
Do you know how many times I called you?
(Eunjae pants)
Hey, I'm on my precious vacation.
Don't you know that?
EUNJAE: Of course I do.
I do,
but it's a gunshot wound patient.
We got an emergency call
from the Coast Guard.
EUNJAE: For now, Dr. Seo Woojin, Insu,
and Euntak went to the site.
But the patient seems to be in bad shape.
Hey, give me your phone.
-Here.
-Okay.
Hey, Woojin. What's the situation?
It's an unidentified middle-aged man.
He's had three gunshot wounds.
One of them nicked
the left brachial plexus,
and the other two don't have exit wounds.
They're lodged inside.
WOOJIN: We suspect a liver injury,
so we plan to open him up
and stop bleeding first.
Then why not just do it?
But,
there's also a chance of an IVC injury.
How much blood loss?
He was rescued
when he had already lost a lot.
We're not sure exactly--
WOMAN: It should be
about 800cc.
WOMAN: Since he was first shot,
he has lost about 800 up to 1,000cc.
Since about 10 minutes after he was shot,
he's been in a stupor.
(coughs)
Who's that?
It's the person who was with the patient.
The patient is very malnourished.
It's not looking good overall.
I'm not sure how much longer
he can hold out in this state.
Please save him.
He's my father.
WOMAN (over phone): We escaped…
(woman sobbing)
We escaped and risked our lives
in order to survive.
Please save him, doctor.
(rods creaking)
(helicopter blades whirring)
Open him up now.
Open him up and find the bleeding!
Are you coming?
Just hang on for 30 minutes!
SABU: Got it?
(exhales in relief)
Yes, sir.
(opening theme music)
VOLUME 1
BREAK LINE:
WHERE THE WATER SUDDENLY GETS DEEPER
NEGOTIATIONS FOR PEACE
ON THE KOREAN PENINSULA BEGIN
(soft music playing)
He's running pretty late.
Looks like he won't be showing up.
I told you it wouldn't be easy.
We're talking about a trauma center
in Gangwon Province, not even Seoul.
And Dr. Bu Yongju is there too.
It's not easy.
So, should I try calling Dr. Oh again?
If he's not showing up
after making an appointment,
it must mean he isn't interested.
Still, I'll call one last time--
Forget it. There's no need.
Let's get going.
(grunts)
Isn't that Dr. Cha Jinman?
You're right.
MAN: I went to see him once recently.
Actually, Shinseong Hospital has been
trying to recruit him.
Is he planning to leave his position?
Gosh, he won't go there, though.
All the major hospitals in Seoul
are fighting to recruit him.
I was one of them. And I still am.
There are always variables at play.
And where there is a will, there is a way.
Will you really meet with him?
(sighs)
MAN: Excuse me, sir.
Fancy meeting you here.
Surgery? Here?
He has bullets lodged inside
and is losing a lot of blood.
It seems they'll perform emergency surgery
to stop the bleeding.
They say they have
more people coming for backup.
WOOJIN: There's a lot of blood
in the peritoneum,
so we're going in
without a clear idea of the injury site.
If it's an IVC injury, his vitals
will drop as soon as we open him.
You're a cardiothoracic surgeon?
MEDIC: Yes, but I enlisted
as soon as I passed the exam.
I don't have a lot of experience.
WOOJIN: Do you have experience with
general or combined operations?
MEDIC: I've worked on an abdominal
aortic injury, a diaphragm injury,
and a cancer vessel invasion case.
WOOJIN: There will be much more blood
than you think.
Don't get flustered
and follow along when I ask for help.
MEDIC: Yes, I'll do my best.
-WOOJIN: Insu.
-INSU: Yes.
The patient is stable.
WOOJIN: Scalpel, please.
(tense music)
Bovie.
INSU: Hey, his BP is dropping.
-WOOJIN: Kelly.
-MEDIC: Yes, sir.
(clattering)
WOOJIN: Gauze.
MEDIC: Gauze!
Gauze.
(beeping)
INSU: Cardiac arrest. PEA.
Start chest compressions.
MEDIC: Cardiac arrest.
INSU: Get up there now!
MEDIC: Yes, sir!
(breathes shakily)
WOOJIN: Kelly.
Bovie.
Tie.
(medic pants)
-WOOJIN: Okay. Cut.
-EUNTAK: Cut.
(Woojin grunts)
-WOOJIN: Cut.
-EUNTAK: Cut.
WOOJIN: There's no one to take over
for you. Hang in there.
MEDIC: Yes, sir!
WOOJIN: Gauze.
(coughs)
(helicopter blades whirring)
(continues coughing)
(hopeful music)
Gosh.
(hopeful music rises)
-LIEUTENANT KO: This is the medical room.
-Okay.
I heard there was another patient.
Pardon?
(coughs)
She's coughing, and it doesn't sound good.
WOOJIN: She has pale conjunctiva,
and I hear rales and wheezing too.
You must be mistaken.
The gunshot wound patient
is the only one on this ship who needs
emergency medical care.
Lieutenant.
(woman coughs)
(heaves)
Ma'am, are you okay?
What are you doing? Get in there.
But I'm a general surgeon.
-And?
-Yes, sir.
Oh, darn you…
Where is the captain of this ship?
The Captain is on the bridge.
Run over there and tell him
that we need to get
the helicopter back up.
As soon as we finish emergency care,
we need to move them to a hospital.
Wait, but that's not--
Go and report to him now! Or else,
you'll have a dead man on your hands!
Cha Eunjae, how is she?
Her BP and heart rate are okay,
but oxygen saturation is at 93%.
She seems to have chest pain
on the right side.
It's dyspnea due to massive hemoptysis.
Can you get it under control?
Yes, I'll try.
Okay. Hey, Jang Donghwa.
-Yes?
-Help Dr. Cha.
Then what about the emergency surgery?
The ship is too small,
so we can't all fit in the room anyway.
I'll call you if we need you.
Just stay here.
EUNJAE: Give her 10 L of O2 reservoir.
Okay.
(medic bag zipper rasps)
(monitor beeping)
INSU: Master!
Hey.
How long have you been at CPR?
-INSU: Ten minutes.
-SABU: Is that so?
INSU: Let's check the rhythm.
(medic pants)
INSU: PEA. Continue compressions.
(medic grunts and pants)
SABU: Okay, how far along are we?
WOOJIN: We're stitching above
the injury site.
Okay, cut.
-WOOJIN: Suction.
-SABU: Suction.
(squishing)
WOOJIN: Tie.
-WOOJIN: Cut.
-EUNTAK: Cut.
WOOJIN: We've got it all.
SABU: Good. Euntak, irrigation.
(medic pants)
SABU: Okay.
I think you tied it off well.
The bleeding seems to be under control.
Dr. Jung?
INSU: Yes. We'll check the rhythm.
INSU: ROSC.
He's back.
(medic sighs)
WOOJIN: We stitched him up in a rush
because he went into arrest.
But the venous return
isn't all there as expected.
What do we do now?
(Sabu grunts)
SABU: It's above the renal vein.
If we delay too much,
we'll lose the kidneys too.
WOOJIN: About a third of the liver
is damaged too.
MEDIC: This is checkmate.
Even I can tell
without any real firsthand experience.
This patient will soon…
die.
SABU: We're going to pass the injury site.
Change positions.
MEDIC: What does that mean?
EUNTAK: Will a foley tube work?
SABU: No, let's use an endotracheal tube.
The biggest one.
INSU: Yes, sir.
MEDIC: Does everyone understand
what he's saying?
(suspenseful music)
SABU: Blade number 11.
Stick in the side with the balloon first.
Put the side without towards the heart
and fix it in place.
As soon as I put this tube in,
tie it immediately. Are you ready?
-WOOJIN: Yes, sir.
-SABU: Let's begin.
SABU: There.
Okay.
SABU: All right, tie this side.
WOOJIN: There, cut.
SABU: And the right side.
Tie.
-WOOJIN: Cut.
-EUNTAK: Cut.
MEDIC: I have never seen
anything like this before.
SABU: Euntak.
MEDIC: No way.
Is that really going to work?
WOOJIN: It's working, Doctor.
(Euntak sighs in relief)
(breathes heavily)
INSU: The patient is hanging in there.
-His vitals are holding steady too.
-SABU: Okay.
Cover it with film first,
and let's move him to Doldam Hospital.
We'll go straight into secondary surgery.
Get ready.
WOOJIN: Yes, sir.
(door opens)
OFFICER: That's not going to be possible.
For the next 18 hours,
this patient cannot leave this ship.
(tense music)
(gloves rustling)
(coughs)
DONGHWA: What?
Dr. Cha, blood keeps coming up the tube.
How many of the smallest tubes are there?
(plastic rustling)
There are two 4.5 mm tubes.
(squishing)
Give me one now.
(exclaims)
Isn't that too deep?
Another.
Use 3 cc for each ballooning.
You can do that much, right?
General surgeons can handle ballooning.
(hissing)
(coughs)
-(exclaims)
-Gauze.
This side is bleeding.
Did you put that in her lungs?
Yes, one tube is deep in one of the lungs.
The other one is positioned above.
That maintains respiration
from the lung that isn't bleeding.
(soft grunt)
If you were a cardiothoracic surgeon,
you'd know how sensational and fantastic
this treatment was.
Oh, okay.
It would've been nice to have
a double lumen tube, but we don't.
That's 98%. Good.
Suction both sides
and use half the force with the Ambu bag.
You can do that much, right?
Why do you keep asking me that?
There are plenty of residents
who don't even know how to do this much.
I can do it.
(scoffs)
Is your arm okay?
I'm fine.
The bullet only grazed me.
Okay.
Are you okay?
What's your name?
(sighs)
We don't have time for this, Captain.
If we don't move and operate right away,
the patient will die.
Orders from above are
just as serious as human life.
That patient will stay on this ship
until 6 p.m. tomorrow evening.
As a dead man?
You said that he's past the crisis.
At this rate,
he'll keep facing more crises.
He'll keep going into cardiac arrest,
and there's only so much
we can do with CPR.
I heard you were a talented doctor.
If we can't operate on time,
talented or not, it doesn't matter.
You must've caught on by now,
but those people…
are North Korean defectors.
Yes, and?
You do know that there is a summit
going on in Seoul, right?
So what?
The process to discuss peace policies
in the Korean peninsula
is happening in Seoul of all places.
If an issue regarding
North Korean defectors occurs,
what do you think will happen?
Does a doctor
need to consider all of that?
Anyway, there is a political situation
Korea is facing at the moment.
Even on the battlefield,
it's human nature to treat the injured,
no matter what side they are from.
Moreover,
these people risked their lives
to come down south to survive.
Also, they're civilians.
Tacking on all that
political situation nonsense to this,
isn't that foul play?
You should watch what you're saying.
I'm just saying
we should stick to our jobs!
(clicks tongue)
(tense music)
Captain.
You and I both work
our butts off day and night
so we can save people's lives.
SABU: Then we should save
the man's life first.
The political situation is
for the politicians to deal with.
Isn't that right?
Isn't it?
CAPTAIN: Yes, this is the captain.
Yes, sir.
Well… Please give us your order.
I spoke to the higher-ups just now.
Until the North Korean representatives
return to Pyongyang,
those people cannot be allowed
onto South Korean soil.
Darn it…
CAPTAIN: However,
that's how it is
on an official level.
(pensive music)
(sighs)
Then what about on an unofficial level?
How much can we do?
My shift ended a long time ago.
Go home then.
Are you joking?
How am I supposed to get off this ship?
I know.
This is exactly what they mean
by being on the same boat, Dr. Jang.
Just because you want to leave
doesn't mean you can get off alone.
How do I put it…
that we share a common destiny?
I want to live as an individual
without a destiny.
(inhales sharply)
(door opens)
(approaching footsteps)
(tense music)
(monitor beeping)
I guess even Master Kim can't fix this…
(approaching footsteps)
(door opens)
The helicopter will take off
in five minutes.
You may prepare to leave, doctors.
You're sending us back?
What about the patient?
What will happen to him?
He'll be transferred with you.
(sighs in relief)
Where are you taking her?
We're transferring her to a hospital.
You should get treated too.
You mean you're taking us to South Korea?
Saving lives comes first.
Don't worry.
We're going to Doldam Hospital.
EUNJAE: It's this place.
A very nice hospital in Jeongseon.
(helicopter blades whirring)
(pensive music)
We'll be there soon.
Look.
DOLDAM HOSPITAL
DOLDAM HOSPITAL, EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
(grunts)
Where is everyone? Oh, wait…
Which way is it…
Oh, gosh.
HOPE, LOVE, SERVICE
(pants)
Darn it.
Why did they want me in such a hurry?
Hey, what on earth is this
all of a sudden?
A gunshot wound trauma patient?
Master Kim isn't even here.
What on earth--
Master Kim is on his way too.
Master Kim?
But he's on vacation right now.
Looks like
Dr. Seo Woojin called him urgently.
Dr. Cha went to find him herself.
Does anyone need caffeine?
I'm fine.
I'll take a double shot
with double the cream and sugar.
(Gitae sighs)
Gosh, that Dr. Seo. I mean,
Master Kim barely managed
to take a vacation in years,
but they just couldn't let him be.
There was a gunshot wound patient.
He had no choice in
such an urgent situation.
Anyway, that gunshot wound patient
is coming here with Master Kim.
We should come up with a plan too.
What plan?
Officially speaking,
this patient is someone
who can't be on South Korean soil
until 6 p.m. tomorrow evening.
(quirky dramatic music)
Other than the minimum number
of staff for surgery,
don't let anyone know.
And until 6 p.m. tomorrow,
make sure this information
doesn't get leaked.
Those are the conditions
for transferring this patient.
What on earth…
How is that possible?
You know how many staff come and go
from Doldam Hospital.
So it has to be a place
where we can keep this secret
and treat the patient with minimal staff.
It cannot be leaked.
That's what I mean, Ms. Oh.
In this tiny little hospital,
where can we treat a patient
without anyone knowing
with the bare minimum staff?
There is one place.
No way, Ms. Oh.
Could it be…
SABU (over phone): Yes, that's right.
The trauma center.
Let's open it up for now.
DOLDAM HOSPITAL
EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
DOLDAM HOSPITAL TRAUMA CENTER
That can't be done, Ms. Oh.
We haven't even gotten approval
for completion of the building yet!
Didn't I tell you to hurry it up?
The building was finished ages ago.
Yet, you haven't been able
to get the approval for months.
We're getting government funding.
The process is complicated, that's all.
I hear a new government employee is
in charge.
That's what I mean.
Since there's a new person in charge,
we don't know when he might barge in.
How could we keep a patient there?
We can't do this, Ms. Oh.
This would be like ruining
the whole project at the very end.
Officially speaking,
until 6 p.m. tomorrow evening,
we're not admitting a patient.
We haven't done anything officially,
so why would it be a problem?
Come on, you can't say that!
Why are you being like this as well?
If this goes wrong and we can't use
that perfectly fine trauma center,
will you hold responsibility?
Well, Master Kim is bringing the patient
via helicopter as we speak.
Anyway, not there.
We can not put him there!
(helicopter blades whirring)
(exclaims)
What can we do?
They seem to be here already.
MYEONGSIM: Let's get ready, everyone.
Wait, no…
Seriously!
Ms. Oh!
CURRENT TIME: 3:09 A.M.
PILOT: Should I land
on the helicopter pad on the roof?
No, we haven't gotten approval
for the building completion yet.
Behind the building,
there's another helicopter pad.
Let's land there.
(in English)
Roger.
PILOT (in Korean): Bravo 517.
Bravo 518 will be landing first.
Bravo 517, standby in the air.
(epic music)
DOLDAM HOSPITAL TRAUMA CENTER
(machine beeps)
Over here. Come this way.
MYEONGSIM: Dr. Nam is waiting
in Operating Room One.
WOOJIN: Okay.
We'll move the patient to Room One.
Nurse.
Run an operation lab test first
and have plenty of packed RBCs ready.
As soon as we start anesthesia,
we'll start the operation.
-NURSE: Yes, Doctor.
-I'll get things ready.
Ms. Oh, more patients are coming.
I got the call. It's a CS case, right?
I'll get things ready.
(exhales loudly)
So this is how we open this place.
EUNJAE: Dr. Jung!
INSU: Hey.
-Dr. Jang.
-DONGHWA: Yes?
Get ready and come to OR One, quick.
-DONGHWAN: Right now?
-Hurry, it's urgent.
Darn it!
(sighs)
She's a massive hemoptysis patient.
She's been coughing and has chest pains.
-What about an echocardiogram?
-EUNJAE: Will do.
Can we get a CT scan here?
We've got it all.
Then can we get a sputum test
and run an OP lab too?
Why not just ask
if we can teleport in here?
Dr. Jang, let's get a sputum test
and run an OP lab--
Dr. Jang. Where did he go?
Dr. Seo called him into the OR.
Ms. Choi, let's get a sputum test
and run an OP lab.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Jang Donghwa is so out of it.
He was complaining about working
after hours in front of the patient,
and he doesn't even respect his seniors.
I don't think you respected me
that much either, Dr. Cha.
Still, I wasn't that bad.
Ms. Oh, can we get a portable chest x-ray?
MYEONGSIM: Yes, Doctor.
You're here, Master Kim.
SABU: Hey, Ms. Oh.
You couldn't even rest
on your long awaited vacation.
I guess it's just my fate.
By the way, you got Mr. Jang
to open up the doors somehow.
GITAE: This isn't right.
(sighs)
This can't be.
MYEONGSIM: But where did
these patients come from?
They're North Korean defectors.
Because of the South-North talks
in Seoul right now,
they're trying to keep this under wraps.
Still, we couldn't keep them on that ship
without operating on them.
I had them brought here unofficially.
I see.
SABU: That little boy's father expired
on the boat.
EXPIRE: TO DIE
The kid doesn't seem to be
physically hurt,
but he's too quiet.
I'll keep a close watch.
Okay.
Right, then let's get started.
Let's do that, Master Kim.
(lively music)
(both chuckle)
(sighs)
WOOJIN: Nurse.
Could you call Dr. Jang Donghwa?
Yes, Doctor.
DOLDAM HOSPITAL
OUTPATIENT CARE
(car beeps)
(cell phone buzzing)
(monitor beeping)
(sighs)
DOIL: Finally, this is the first surgery
at the Doldam Hospital Trauma Center.
Although, it's unofficial.
-SABU: Dr. Seo Woojin.
-WOOJIN: Yes, Doctor?
SABU: This is
our trauma center's first patient.
Let's save him no matter what. Got it?
WOOJIN: Of course.
DOIL: Okay.
The patient's vitals are stable.
SABU: Right. Let's get started.
Scalpel.
WOOJIN: Bovie.
DOLDAM HOSPITAL TRAUMA CENTER
Sorry to ask you to meet here.
MINGUK: It's quite all right.
It didn't take long getting here.
So, how is it…
living in the countryside?
There's no difference in saving lives
in Seoul or elsewhere.
I just do my best for my patients.
You sound like
you've reached enlightenment.
(chuckles)
Well…
I've heard rumors that you will be moving
to another hospital. Is this true?
Why do you ask?
Actually, Doldam Hospital
has newly built a trauma center.
You already have Bu Yongju there.
I know that
you're both Keosan University alumni.
That you two were undergrad rivals.
I don't know about rivals.
I'm a cardiothoracic surgeon,
and he's a general surgeon.
(Minguk chuckles)
If you come to our hospital,
you would be of tremendous help.
By the way, Dr. Park,
why did you go there?
I wanted to test myself.
Master Kim can do it, so why can't I?
(Minguk chuckles)
MINGUK: But then,
I came to my senses one day,
and I found myself here.
You've gone off the deep end.
I guess you could say
that my respect for Dr. Bu Yongju
played a part in it.
Anyway, thank you for making time for me.
If you can,
please stop by the hospital sometime.
DOLDAM HOSPITAL
DIRECTOR PARK MINGUK
How about today?
Pardon?
I happen to be off today.
How are his vitals and urine output?
His BP is holding at 100/70.
EUNTAK: And his urine output is
70 to 80 cc per hour, which is good.
(exhales in relief)
I honestly thought he wouldn't make it.
You did a good job.
I didn't know
you'd get the IVC injury as well.
I wouldn't have been able
to do it without you.
Go and get some shut-eye.
We need to observe him until this evening
with the minimum number of staff.
Let's take turns and save our energy.
Have you not heard
from Dr. Jang Donghwa yet?
No, I think he went home.
I'll stay here. Go and get some rest.
Then I'll be back soon after I wash up.
(Euntak sighs)
(gentle music)
EUNTAK: Where are you now?
WHERE ARE YOU NOW?
When will you be back?
WHEN WILL YOU BE BACK?
I miss you.
(approaching footsteps)
Euntak.
Yes, Dr. Cha?
Where is Seo Woojin?
He went to get some sleep.
We're going to take turns observing
until this evening.
What about Jang Donghwa? What's he doing?
I think he went home.
Why, that little punk. I knew it.
What's Seo Woojin doing?
He's supposed to be his mentor.
Will he leave him to do whatever he wants?
I'm sure he'll deal with it.
(sighs)
Seriously.
By the way, did you finish moving?
I heard from Dr. Eom
that you moved over the weekend.
(chuckling awkwardly)
Oh, well, yes.
When will you have a housewarming party?
I'm so curious what your house is like.
Well, it's just a small house.
I haven't gotten settled in yet.
I think it will take some time
to get organized.
(Eunjae laughs awkwardly)
I'll be going first.
NURSE: Mm.
She should just get married instead.
Dr. Cha and Dr. Seo, I mean.
They're in the same place in
their relationship for over three years.
There's no progress
and it's getting awkward.
(nurse inhales sharply)
Being in a long-term relationship
isn't necessarily a good thing.
I'm sure they'll figure it out themselves.
How is Areum?
Is she doing well?
Yes, I'm sure she is.
What's this?
This couple is kind of awkward too.
I MISS YOU…
(phone clicks shut)
(gentle music playing)
(man exhales softly)
MAN: Goodness…
There you go.
(door opens)
(door closes)
Where is he?
Wait…
(door opens)
What are you doing?
I couldn't find you, so…
What? Did you miss me already?
The surgery must've gone well today.
You seem to be in a good mood.
I fixed an IVC injury.
What? An IVC injury
that's supposed to be super hard?
Goodness, congratulations, Dr. Seo Woojin.
Is that it?
Then what else do you want?
Beer? Or wine?
Something like this.
Gosh, Dr. Seo!
What are you doing in broad daylight?
Euntak told you to get some sleep,
but you're making moves on me?
Isn't this why we moved in together?
(Eunjae sighs)
Right. I'll explain it once more,
so listen carefully.
The reason why we decided
to move in together is, first,
to reduce our expenses
since we've spent so much
on monthly rent over the past three years.
-That's the first reason.
-And?
You and I are both so busy,
so it's a hassle to go into town
every weekend to go on dates.
So reducing the time and distance to be
more efficient is the second reason.
Is that it?
So let's stop messing around
and unpack our stuff, Dr. Seo Woojin.
Where's the memo I gave you
before we moved?
You remember that, right?
I cook and you do the dishes.
Recycling, me. Food waste, you.
Living room and bedroom, me.
Bathroom and yard, you.
Just as we agreed. Nice and neat. Okay?
I have a question, Dr. Cha.
Then when do we get to kiss?
Well, that's…
Just whenever the mood is right.
Then when do we sleep?
That's also…
when you're tired.
Sleep on your own time.
"On your own time?"
Of course, on our own.
How else would it be?
What? What are you imagining?
The same thing you just imagined.
Gosh. Dr. Seo!
Will you really make things rated-R
at every chance?
I totally will.
Hey!
EUNJAE: No.
Dr. Seo!
There are so many boxes to unpack!
-Go away.
-Okay.
-Okay!
-Wait!
Hey, hang on! Okay, wait.
EUNJAE: Wait a second.
-No, wait--
-No waiting.
(Eunjae squeals, giggles)
WOOJIN: What should we do now?
(rhythmic tapping)
(tapping continues)
Why, those little punks.
Are Seo Woojin and Cha Eunjae
still not here?
Oh, they're both off this morning.
They'll come to work in the afternoon.
There was a gunshot wound patient
on a military base last night.
They were called out urgently
and worked all night.
Where is that gunshot wound patient?
I'm not sure. Maybe the military hospital?
I don't know either.
What?
Wait…
(Hojun sighs)
(phone buzzes)
(groans)
INSU: Hey.
(pensive music)
TRAUMA CENTER
(groans)
MYEONGSIM: Dr. Yang?
(chuckles awkwardly)
What are you doing there?
Oh, I just thought
I saw people in there.
I was wondering what it was.
I thought the trauma center
wasn't open yet.
(sighs)
I know, right?
Why is there so much
to prepare and check to get approval
for completion of the building?
I couldn't do it all myself,
so I asked a few people
to take care of it.
Will you help me out too?
-There's so much work to do.
-(groans)
Goodness.
(chuckles, sucks teeth)
I'm a bit busy right now.
I have a lot of papers to read.
Can't you spare some time?
Well, not right now.
Maybe next time.
Bye then.
(mutters)
(quirky music)
Goodness.
(laughs awkwardly)
(exclaims)
(sighs)
That's weird.
Something is definitely up.
(in English)
Mr. Koo?
They're from
the National Intelligence Service.
AGENT: Does it hurt anywhere?
This must've hurt.
Do you want to go eat something?
What do you like?
(sighs)
(male agent murmuring)
AGENT 2: Could you tell us why
you came here?
DOLDAM HOSPITAL
The trauma center is this way.
(panicked breathing)
(cell phone buzzing)
(gasps)
DIRECTOR PARK MINGUK
(exhales deeply)
Yes, Director Park?
MINGUK: Where are you right now?
Right now? I stepped out for a while.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
My gosh!
What are you doing here?
Oh, well, that's…
I was just about to step out for a bit!
(laughs awkwardly)
What is it this time?
Tell me.
(suspenseful music)
(monitor beeping)
(mellow music)
Dr. Kim.
Oh, hey.
How is the patient?
He's stable so far.
His urine output is good too.
Mm.
Have you been taking your medicine?
Haven't skipped a day.
If I'm to keep this job for a long time,
I need to be prompt with my meds.
(chuckles)
Thank you for coming during your vacation.
You would've been fine without me.
You should go ahead and take care
of things you can do on your own, Dr. Seo.
I still have a lot to learn, Master.
And with you around,
I feel like my surgeries go better.
And I feel more confident too.
Gosh, Seo Woojin.
You're becoming good at flattery.
Where did you learn
to say stuff like that?
I'm not trying to flatter you.
It's the truth.
Okay.
It really is the truth, sir.
(laughing)
Gosh, okay. I get it.
GITAE: Master Kim!
Master Kim!
Do you have any idea what's happening now?
(Gitae pants)
GITAE: Right now…
Director Park.
-You're here.
-MINGUK: Master Kim.
-Yes?
-What is this situation?
(sighs)
I was going to explain when you got here.
Let's head to your office for now.
(sighs)
(tense music)
SABU: What's going on?
I offered him a position here.
He wanted to see the trauma center first.
Right.
That's why he's here.
It's been a while.
Mm.
(footsteps echoing)
(tense music intensifies)
(scoffs)
It's been a while, Eunjae.
Dad.
(mouths)
Dad?
(mellow music)
(closing theme music)
DR. ROMANTIC SEASON 3
-WOOJIN: It's a PEA arrest.
-JINMAN: You're not…
receiving patients here, are you?
SABU: Those people are
critically ill patients.
Where are you trying
to send these dying people?
Don't move!
MAN: If you do anything…
Surgery?
SABU: No matter how the world moves,
let's keep it "world and peace"
for us, Director Park.
JINMAN: Your nonsense hasn't changed.
MAN: Die!
GITAE: They're in the middle of surgery!
JINMAN: You're going to find it
only with your sense of touch?
SABU: If I weren't confident,
would I have started this fight?