(theme music)
DR. ROMANTIC SEASON 3
THE CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA
ARE WORKS OF FICTION
(light music)
-SABU: Ms. Ha Yoonkyung?
-Yes.
Why did you apply to Doldam Hospital?
I watched your video from seven years ago
about the artificial heart surgery.
As a doctor myself, it was so inspiring...
(in emotional voice)
One moment, please.
Here.
I've heard a lot
about the water and air being good,
as well as the mountains.
By the way, I'm a really big fan of yours.
Really. A real big fan.
-APPLICANT 1: I like you.
-(chuckles)
What makes a good doctor?
-Do you provide food?
-How much is
the annual salary
for someone of my status?
(voice breaking)
For me to get this far...
-(sighs)
-APPLICANT 2: Let's be honest.
General surgeons and CT surgeons
don't really get paid a lot
and they're extreme jobs.
If you look there, you'll see
that I have overseas training experience.
For a week?
It's plenty of time
for a life-changing experience.
Is food delivery available out here?
Having you, Dr. Bu Yongju,
as a mentor would really...
boost my recognition
when I open my own hospital...
I cried a lot, didn't I?
(soft chuckle)
-May I shake your hand?
-Sure.
(squeals, giggles)
-Nurse!
Nurse!
Nurse, please bring us some water.
APPLICANT 3: I...
was curious.
Curious?
About what?
APPLICANT 3: You.
Also, the people at Doldam Hospital.
(papers rustle)
Hold on...
(inhales deeply)
Aren't you...
LEE SEONUNG, R.O.K. NAVY
(soft grunt)
Ah!
Ah...
There's a lounge over there.
You can rest there if you'd like.
Okay... No, it's okay.
(grunts, sighs)
EUNJAE'S MOM: Eunho.
His doctor's license is suspended
for a year.
Is this what you meant
by fairness and justice?
Do you feel better now?
It was Eunho's fault.
There's even a victim.
Even now, you care more
about the victim than your own family?
Just because you're family...
does it mean you're supposed
to cover for them no matter what?
Of course. That's what family is.
It's common sense.
What about Dad?
(breathes shakily)
Does Dad...
see it that way too?
It's been a long time, Eunjae.
Have you been well?
Dad.
What brings you here?
I just had some business to attend to.
The hospital building is nice.
JINMAN: But...
I heard there hasn't been
a final building inspection yet.
You're not...
receiving patients, are you?
(tense music)
(mouthing)
The final building inspection is
for the building itself.
As doctors,
our job is to receive patients.
Also, as a visitor,
if you're done with your business,
you should be on your way.
Dr. Park.
Didn't you say you would show me
the Trauma Center today?
Yes, well, I was planning on it.
However,
it seems a few issues
I wasn't aware of have occurred.
I'm sorry.
Isn't a hospital's chief decision-maker
the hospital director?
JINMAN: But how is it
that the unopened Trauma Center
is being used
without the Director's
knowledge or permission?
How is that possible, Director Park?
(breathes deeply)
(phones buzz)
You should go.
There's nothing to worry about here.
You too, Dr. Cha Eunjae.
Go.
Let's go, Cha Eunjae.
INTENSIVE CARE UNIT
As of today, the Trauma Center
is temporarily closed to the public.
Also, everything that occurs in here
is a security matter.
Please escort him out, Director Park.
Your nonsense hasn't changed.
(tense music continues)
(whispering)
Those two...
What's with them?
They were well-known for their rivalry
ever since their undergrad years.
It's a "dragon versus tiger" situation,
or as they say nowadays, "TVPG."
"TVPG?"
It means "Two Very Proud Geniuses."
To make a comparison,
they were the Ronaldo and Messi
of Keosan Medical School.
I see.
Who was Messi?
Excuse me,
Dr. Cha Jinman?
Master Kim.
(chuckles)
(upbeat music)
VOLUME 2
BETWEEN ETHICS AND REALITY
EPISODE 2
(camera shutters clicking)
REPORTER 1: Here he comes.
REPORTER 2: He's here.
(camera shutters clicking)
REPORTER 3:
Are the negotiations going well?
REPORTER 4: Is it true
the agreed inter-Korean exchange will have
over 40 trillion won of economic value?
REPORTER 5:
Is it true that there are negotiations
for demolishing
the DMZ military facilities?
Is that why
the former Secretary of Defense
is present on the council?
For the first time in a long time,
the South and North have come together
to establish many agreements.
WOONGIL:
Everything seems to be going well.
Please send your support
so that we may yield good results.
REPORTER 6: Is there any chance
of restarting business with the North?
REPORTER 7: Do you have any suggestions
-for alleviating military tension?
-(reporters clamoring)
(tense music)
Something's come up, sir.
The officials from the North
are not departing from the hotel.
Why? What's happened?
Yesterday, our Coast Guard found
a boat stranded in the East Sea.
Apparently, there were
North Korean defectors on it.
SECRETARY: It seems
this info was relayed to the officials.
Here you go, sir.
If we don't implement this,
they say they'll overturn
all their decisions from this summit
and return to Pyongyang tomorrow morning.
Where are the defectors now?
Are you really going to be like this,
Master Kim?
You left it up to me
to organize the Trauma Center.
Well, I told you not him.
He wouldn't come down
to a place like this anyway.
Was I a person who would come down
to a place like this then?
Director Park, you're different.
You were moderately pure
with some serious craziness.
You were our guy from the beginning.
Anyway, we would be lucky to have someone
as overqualified as Dr. Cha.
Sometimes, being overqualified
isn't everything.
I admit that he is a talented person,
but that doesn't necessarily mean
he's dedicated to his patients.
I'm telling you,
he's completely different from us.
JINMAN: As I expected.
I heard that everything at Doldam Hospital
starts and stops at Bu Yongju's word.
I suppose the rumors were true,
Dr. Park Minguk.
Not in the slightest.
I am the Director of Doldam Hospital.
I make the final decisions.
SABU: So what?
Did he say he'd come if we tell him to?
I'm going to try and convince him.
If you have any objections, tell me now.
Otherwise, just keep your mouth shut.
You...
JINMAN: To be honest,
Bu Yongju isn't at a level
to raise any objections about me.
In that case, you can finish looking
around the Trauma Center as planned.
MINGUK: I will guide you.
(door opens)
Director Park Minguk,
may we speak with you for a second?
EUNJAE: Take this to Labs.
EUNTAK: How much blood should I take?
EUNJAE: Just one liter.
Please run an ABGA as well.
SABU: How is she?
EUNJAE: Her fever keeps rising,
and her RR is fast.
And she still has hemoptysis.
SABU: You can't hear anything on one side.
What about the Xpert results?
EUNTAK: They came back TB-positive.
It is confirmed
to be resistant to rifampin.
(Eunjae sighs)
EUNJAE: I'm sure it's MDR...
What should we do?
The condition of her lungs is very bad.
SABU: When will Pulmonologist Dr. Na
be back from the conference?
EUNTAK: Dr. Na should be back
next week on Monday.
SABU: Send her the photos, videos,
and test results for now.
Ask Dr. Na to contact us
after taking a look.
EUNTAK: Yes, sir.
(door opens)
(alarm beeping)
(tense music)
WOOJIN: It's a PEA arrest.
-Nurse Euntak!
-NURSE: He's in the ICU next door.
WOOJIN: In the meantime, give one ampule
of epinephrine every three minutes.
-Can you help me with the ambu bag?
-NURSE: Okay.
SABU: I can do that.
Can you bring the ultrasound?
NURSE: Yes, Doctor.
WOOJIN: Please page Dr. Jang Donghwa.
NURSE: About that...
We've been paging him this whole time,
but he hasn't been responding.
SABU: Since this is an emergency,
call Dr. Jung Insu and Dr. Nam Doil.
NURSE: Yes, Doctor.
I sent the files to Dr. Na
and left a message.
EUNJAE: The patient next door
seems to have gone into arrest.
(Woojin panting)
(panting continues)
WOOJIN: I'll check his rhythm now.
There's no pulse. Continuing CPR.
I'll take over.
(Woojin panting)
EUNJAE (sighs):
Where the hell is Jang Donghwa?
Did he scram again?
DONGHWA: Let's check together.
We have to move together.
We can't die, you guys.
You can't die. Think of this as real life.
Slowly.
Come quickly, everyone!
This is a warzone! Hurry!
-(gunshot in video game)
-(man groans in video game)
-(exhales loudly)
-(keyboard clacking)
Pay attention! This is a warzone!
(laughs)
(tense music)
INSU: I'll do it.
SABU: Dr. Jung Insu, run an echo.
INSU: Yes, sir.
-EUNTAK: Let's switch.
-WOOJIN: Checking rhythm.
PEA arrest. Continuing CPR!
INSU: Ah...
It's cardiac tamponade, Master Kim.
SABU:
Get me a c-line for a pericardiocentesis.
(Woojin panting)
SABU: Don't stop the compressions.
WOOJIN (panting): Yes, sir.
(panting continues)
Wasn't he a general surgeon?
How does he know
how to deal with a cardiac tamponade?
-(door opens)
-(footsteps approaching)
INSU: I'm going to check his rhythm.
ROSC. His pulse is back.
-(Euntak sighs)
-(Woojin exhales in relief)
SABU: Good job, everyone.
Keep this pericardial catheter in
and keep an eye on the patient.
-The LV contractility is too low.
-(Woojin panting)
There's a chance
of another cardiac arrest.
WOOJIN: The patient's nutritional status
and health are very bad.
I'm worried that the patient
may not be able to endure it.
SABU: Double the amount of norepinephrine.
WOOJIN:
Should we give Vasopressin as well?
SABU: Yes. Let's do that.
-EUNTAK: Master Kim.
-SABU: Yeah?
(Woojin panting)
SABU: What nonsense is this?
What do you mean by repatriation?
Director Park.
Where are you trying to send
these dying people?
There seems to be a major figure
among the defectors.
If we don't return all the people
that were on that boat by midnight,
the summit in Seoul
will be suspended immediately.
Listen here.
Those people are critically ill patients.
One of them went into cardiac arrest,
and we just barely brought him back.
SABU: Also, those people clearly expressed
their intention to become naturalized
in the Republic of Korea.
The Republic of Korea is obligated
to protect those people.
We're not obligated to do that yet.
SABU: Hmm?
As you know, they haven't officially
entered our territory yet.
AGENT: At stake is 40 trillion won,
depending on the outcome
of the summit meeting.
Should we lose out on 40 trillion won
because of a few defectors?
Are you asking me, a doctor,
to decide what is more important?
A human's life or 40 trillion won?
AGENT: I'm just informing you
about the current circumstances.
The fishing boat stranded in the East Sea
was a North Korean vessel.
Both the boat and its passengers
will be sent back to North Korea.
Before midnight.
(Sabu sighs)
Damn it...
Have you heard from Dr. Jang Donghwa yet?
No, not yet.
NURSE: We're still paging him,
but no response at all.
Dr. Seo, this...
DONGHWA.JJANG
DONGHWA: Emergency overtime again today.
Staying up all night,
and getting off work at dawn.
Current time, 3:49 a.m.
Is this for real?
(sighs, scoffs)
(Donghwa exhales deeply)
(phone buzzes)
What's this?
EUNJAE: Hey, Dr. Jang Donghwa!
Where are you?
Come to the hospital right now.
Whatever.
-(keyboard clacking)
-(phone buzzes)
EUNJAE: Seo Woojin is totally pissed.
(clacking continues)
(breathes deeply)
EUNJAE: Come immediately.
I'll give you ten seconds.
(clacking continues)
(phone buzzes)
(annoyed groan)
EUNJAE: Are you ignoring me?
You're confident you can handle
the consequences, right?
-(gunshots in video game)
-Oh!
Oh!
Wait!
-(exclaims, yelling)
-(man groans in video game)
Damn it!
(sighs)
IT HAPPENS. SOME DAYS ARE LIKE THAT.
Dr. Jang Donghwa!
What time is it?
It's 3:00 in the afternoon.
You!
I heard you didn't come
to the OR last night and ran away.
EUNJAE: There was a patient
whose life was on the balance.
How could you just leave?
Would you leave the battlefield
during an enemy invasion
just because your time was up?
I worked the morning shift
and overtime yesterday.
Hey, are you the only one?
Everyone here worked overtime.
We are legally protected
to work only 80 hours a week.
Plus eight hours
for educational purposes
or emergency cases.
In other words, 88 hours in total.
Why are you leaving that out?
Residents aren't allowed
to work 36 hours straight.
What?
You worked 20 hours straight,
including both day and night shifts.
Even if you included the surgery time,
that's still approximately 24 hours.
There was an emergency patient
who required surgery.
It was a surgery
you needed to be here for,
but you left.
Even though you didn't work
over the legal amount of hours.
Got anything to say?
Sure, work-life balance.
I also think that's important.
But you wanted to be a doctor.
Then do what you must.
(sighs)
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize to me.
If you don't practice properly,
your patients deal with the repercussions.
Unless told otherwise,
the patient in ICU Room No.1
is your responsibility.
He went into cardiac arrest this morning,
so if he seems unstable,
call someone immediately.
Get it together, Jang Donghwa.
You're lucky this is Dr. Seo Woojin.
If it was Dr. Yang Hojun,
you would have taken a beating.
(sighs)
Stop it. I can see you giggling.
(both snicker)
CAFE AU LAIT
MILK COFFEE
Let's just try to be understanding.
We were residents
and the third year of residency
is the hardest, most sensitive time.
He's going into fellowship next year,
and he can't even perform first-aid.
Fine.
It isn't a crime to not be able to do it.
But he doesn't even try,
nor is he diligent.
Is there any hope for him?
Dr. Insu said we were the same way.
Not me.
Well, I guess you were good at everything
from the start.
(laughs softly)
(Eunjae slurps)
Did your father leave?
Hmm?
Oh, I'm not sure. Did he?
(soft chuckle)
It's been a while since you last saw him.
Yeah.
I saw him briefly
on his birthday last year.
Is he still upset...
about your brother?
I don't know.
JINMAN: What are you doing here?
(soft music)
Actually,
I have to operate,
so I'll talk to you later.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, DAD
I don't regret what I did.
Don't I look cool?
(soft chuckle)
Now wouldn't be the right time
to introduce myself, would it?
I guess not. Let's do that later.
Is that all right?
Yeah.
(phone buzzes)
Master Kim is calling for me.
-Thanks for the coffee.
-Wait.
-What is it?
-Stay like that just a moment.
-Why?
-Turn your head this way.
Is there something on my face? Where?
EUNJAE: Here?
Or is it here?
There's something...
Hey!
In the middle of the hospital!
(soft chuckle)
Hurry up and go. Master Kim is waiting.
EMPLOYEE LOUNGE
(soft chuckle)
(tense music)
Nobody cares. Not a single one of you!
Using facilities that aren't even ready!
Darn it.
What are they going to do
if a new official suddenly comes in?
GITAE: Darn it.
Hold on.
Which is stronger?
The Ministry of Health and Welfare?
Or National Intelligence Service?
Damn it! I've been so distracted
by the final building inspection.
Hold on.
Come to think of it,
there was something going on today.
MY SCHEDULE
GITAE: At 4 p.m.?
What's at 4 p.m.?
-Here's your helmet.
-Thank you.
EMPLOYEE: You're here!
Hello!
Did you receive the notice
for the electrical inspection today?
Yes, of course.
For 30 minutes, from 4 p.m.,
power in the new trauma center
will be shut off.
Is there anything else
we need to know before that?
Actually, we weren't able
to install the UPS battery yet.
EMPLOYEE: There was a problem
in the bidding process
and the company was changed,
so it was delayed.
It'll come within the week.
I understand.
Where is the electrical room?
EMPLOYEE:
It's on the second basement level.
If you turn left around that building,
you'll see the entrance to the basement.
ELECTRICIAN: Let's move.
-Let's go down together.
-Yes, let's go.
-This way.
-ELECTRICIAN: Okay.
(door opens)
Master Kim,
I just received an email from Dr. Na.
EUNTAK: Dr. Na suggests kanamycin.
If that doesn't work,
prothionamide and cycloserine,
since we don't know if it is XDR-TB.
Did you tell her about the BUN levels?
Yes, I told her that creatinine levels
and urea output are decreasing.
I also mentioned
that the ABGA indicated
a PaCO2 value of 60 mmHg.
(sighs)
Master Kim, I'm here.
Did Dr. Na send an opinion?
Here you go, Dr. Cha.
As expected,
Dr. Na says to go with medicine.
At this rate,
it would take another week or two.
What are your thoughts then, Eunjae?
Mm...
I think it's better
to remove the lesion site with surgery.
EUNJAE: The patient's BUN levels are bad
and there's constant hemorrhaging,
meaning that the lungs
are still being destroyed locally.
Have you ever performed a lung lobectomy?
No, not for the lung.
You can give it a try this time then.
(phone ringing)
This is the Trauma Center.
Yes, Nurse Euntak.
What?
Okay.
Master Kim says to prepare for surgery.
ANESTHESIOLOGIST NAM DOIL
Surgery?
What surgery are you talking about?
A lung lobecto--
(splutters)
Where is Master Kim?
No, tell him not to do anything
until I get there.
(breathes deeply)
(sighs deeply)
Master Kim.
Master Kim!
Your name?
My name is Seo Woojin.
JINMAN: Eunjae is
my precious daughter
whether you knew that or not.
When she chose to go into CT surgery,
I was so proud of her.
I almost cried.
Her brother Eunho was also happy
when she made her choice.
And so,
we respected and supported each other.
Our family didn't have any problems
until you showed up,
Dr. Seo Woojin.
(soft tense music)
I'm just saying.
(door closes)
(door sliding open)
Master Kim,
you're operating on patient Ri Bokyoung?
SABU: Yes, that's what we've decided.
What is it?
Now, why are you doing this?
Why are you trying to open up someone
who'll be repatriated by midnight tonight?
(breathes deeply)
Master Kim!
-(clanks)
-SABU: That's why I'm doing it.
So what about politics
and economic whatever
-of 40 trillion won?
-(sighs)
It's none of my business.
The least I can do
is to make sure they can live.
In any case, they're our patients.
My gosh.
Do you really have to do this surgery?
SABU: It's our job and ethos
to save people, Director Park.
No matter how the world moves,
let's keep it "world and peace" for us,
Director Park.
Okay?
(clanks)
(water running)
(Sabu breathes deeply)
SABU: Dr. Nam?
DOIL: Vitals are good. You may begin.
SABU: Scalpel.
(Sabu grunts)
Bovie.
(sizzling)
Lift it a little.
Rib shears.
CURRENT TIME
OPERATION TIME, ANESTHESIA TIME
GITAE: 4 p.m.?
What was at 4 p.m.?
I swear there was something then.
EMPLOYEE: This way.
The electrical room is this way.
It's dark here, so please be careful.
Watch your head.
ELECTRICIAN: Ah, yes.
AGENT: Okay, I will relay the message.
(phone beeps)
(whispering)
I need to go to the bathroom.
-(man clears throat)
-(ominous sting)
(squelches)
EUNJAE: I'm sorry.
SABU: Gauze.
EUNTAK: Are you okay, Dr. Cha?
EUNJAE: I'm okay, just a little nervous
since it's my first time performing this.
SABU: Be careful of the bronchial artery
when you remove the adhesion.
EUNJAE: Okay.
SABU: All right, we're going to separate
the pulmonary ligament.
(exhales deeply)
JINMAN:
Our family didn't have any problems
until you showed up,
Dr. Seo Woojin.
(sighs)
WOOJIN: What are you doing here?
I was just watching the patient
who went into cardiac arrest earlier.
Did you see the resident
who was watching the patient?
He left to go to the bathroom, it seems.
How long has it been?
About 20 or 30 minutes, I would say?
(exhales sharply)
(scoffs)
(door opens)
(foreboding music)
(grunts)
(tense music)
(agent groans, grunts)
(both grunting)
-(agent grunts)
-(man groans)
(shouts)
(yells)
(grunts)
(agent groans in pain)
(softly)
Oh, my gosh!
(grunts)
(phone buzzes)
-(suspenseful music)
-(gasps)
(nervous, soft breath)
-(banging on door)
-DONGHWA: Sir, what's the matter?
Sir!
(screaming)
I'm sorry! Sir!
(whimpering, screams)
No, don't go in.
The man in there killed my dad
and shot a doctor.
He said he would kill us all.
Don't go in.
(Donghwa yelling)
-(man yells)
-(Donghwa pants)
(both grunting)
DONGHWA: Dr. Seo,
please save me.
Please, help me.
(sobs)
(Donghwa sobbing)
HOPE, LOVE, SERVICE
DOCTOR'S OFFICE 2
MASTER KIM
ON VACATION
(soft music playing)
(phone buzzing)
-(buzzing continues)
-(music stops)
DIRECTOR PARK MINGUK
JINMAN: It's me, Cha Jinman.
Hello, Dr. Cha Jinman.
My apologies for making you wait.
No, it's okay. I have been looking around.
Actually, Master Kim
just went into surgery just now.
MINGUK: A lobectomy of the right lung.
MINGUK (over phone):
You haven't seen him operate in a while.
How about it?
Would like to come and observe?
Where should I go?
EUNJAE: There's no adhesion
and less bleeding than I thought.
DOIL: The patient's vitals are fine too.
SABU: Hold this.
Right angle.
A 5-0 black silk suture, please.
(bright music)
(Sabu grunts softly)
-SABU: Cut.
-EUNTAK: Cut.
SABU: One more.
This is the reason why
I stay at Doldam Hospital.
Master Kim is a different person
when he's in the operating room.
MINGUK: When he's in his zone,
there is nothing else I can think of.
I only have respect for him.
SABU: Metzenbaum.
SABU:
We're removing the right upper lobe now.
-Bovie.
-(snaps)
CURRENT TIME
May I turn off the power now?
Are we ready?
ELECTRICIAN:
I'm going to turn off the transformer.
DOLDAM HOSPITAL, TRAUMA CENTER
ELECTRICIAN: The transformer is now off.
All right, turning off the ACB.
-Turning off the ACB.
-(tense music)
What are you doing?
This is a hospital.
Put down those tweezers.
MAN (shouts): Don't play with me!
This isn't a hospital.
Why don't I see any other patients?
That's because this place was just built.
(breathing nervously)
It hasn't been--
I don't want to hear it!
Give me back my boat!
I'm going back to North Korea.
If you don't, I'll kill everyone!
Dr. Seo!
(chokes)
-(exhales softly)
-(Donghwa grunting)
Turn off the VCB.
Okay, turning off the VCB.
GITAE: At 4 p.m....
Just what was it?
(breathes deeply)
At 4 p.m....
What was it?
(music intensifies)
Oh, 4 p.m.!
No!
CURRENT TIME
Main VCB off.
(suspenseful music)
-(man grunting)
-(Donghwa groans)
MAN: What?
Lastly, turning off the LBS!
DOIL: What? What's going on?
It's a relief though,
the monitor and ventilators
are rechargeable so...
Oh...
(sighs)
It wasn't charging properly.
Ambu bag. Where is it?
(tense music)
(phone beeps)
Chief Jang, what is going on?
Why is the power out?
So about that,
there was an electrical inspection today.
I'm sorry, I should have given you
another notice this morning.
There was a sudden issue
at the trauma center,
so I completely forgot.
I'm really sorry.
Do you know that the emergency power
is not running in the OR right now?
The OR? There's an operation
going on right now?
Hurry downstairs
and turn the power back on!
Yes, sir. Please wait a moment.
-(phone beeps)
-Manager Lee...
Manager Lee! Where are you?
SABU: For now, use cellphone flashlights.
Here.
(squelching)
EUNJAE (gasps): Oh, no.
I think I touched a vein
when the lights went out.
SABU: It's okay.
We can control the bleeding.
EUNJAE: I'm sorry.
SABU: Relax. It's okay.
It's not the worst situation ever.
Don't get flustered.
Give me a lot of gauzes.
(phone buzzes)
DOIL: It's Director Park.
MINGUK (over phone): Master Kim.
It's me, Park Minguk.
DOIL: What is going on right now?
MINGUK: There was an inspection
for the electrical equipment.
They didn't realize anyone was inside.
The administration staff didn't know
what was going on at the Trauma Center.
MINGUK (breathes deeply): Chief Jang
is heading down to the electrical room,
but I don't know how long it will take.
What should I do?
DOIL: Could you send me
a portable ventilator and a monitor first?
Okay. Anything else?
SABU: Are you saying
the whole building is without power?
Yes, I'm afraid so.
(Sabu sighs)
Then, quickly go to the ICU
and check it out.
There's a patient that went
into cardiac arrest in the morning.
We're going to have
to go check him quickly.
Okay, I'll take care of the ICU.
What kind of game are you guys playing at?
MAN: Turn the lights back on!
(Donghwa breathes heavily)
(Donghwa groans)
(suspenseful music)
(Donghwa pants)
MAN: Stay still, you bastard.
(Donghwa breathes shakily)
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
MYEONGSIM: What should we do, Master Kim?
Are we just going to keep using gauze
until the power comes back?
(Sabu sighs)
(Sabu breathes deeply)
SABU: Shine a light where my forceps are.
Here, Doil.
DOIL: Okay.
SABU: Dr. Kim, over here.
Nurse Choi, here.
SABU: It would be better
if there were two more lights.
MYEONGSIM: I'll do it.
Nurse Euntak and Dr. Cha,
give me your phones.
EUNJAE: I didn't bring mine.
EUNTAK: It's in my pocket.
SABU: Okay, this way.
-A little higher.
-MYEONGSIM: Yes, Doctor.
SABU: Mm.
MYEONGSIM: It's still a little weak.
And the shadows get in the way.
Is this okay, Master Kim?
SABU: Well...
Let's do what we can.
Cha Eunjae, press here.
-Nurse Euntak?
-EUNTAK: Don't worry.
I'll cover you two.
SABU: Okay.
All right.
Focus.
(intense music)
(huffs)
You're going to find it
only with your sense of touch?
GITAE: Turn on the power, please! Hurry!
They're in the middle of a surgery!
Please!
(Sabu gasps softly)
-SABU: Okay.
-EUNJAE: Did you find it?
SABU: I think so.
(light music)
MYEONGSIM: Nurse Euntak.
EUNTAK: Here's a hemoclip.
SABU: Right here.
EUNJAE: One more, please.
SABU: You have to clip it twice.
EUNJAE: I got it.
Is it the bronchial artery?
SABU: Yes, it seems that way. Suture.
(hopeful music)
-SABU: Cut.
-EUNTAK: Cut.
GITAE (shouts): Flip the switch! Now!
(wheezes)
Turn on the power. Hurry!
Right now!
CONTINUE BATTLE
(gunshots in video game)
-(suspenseful music)
-(both grunting)
(grunts)
-(devices whir)
-(all exclaim)
(all sigh in relief)
(Eunjae and Sabu sigh)
(Sabu and Myeongsim sigh)
(Sabu chuckles softly)
-(both grunting)
-(suspenseful music continues)
-(shouts)
-(grunts)
-(clattering)
-AGENT: Sergeant Kim!
-(man shouts)
-(Woojin grunts)
Die, you son of a bitch!
(breathing heavily, rapidly)
-(whimpers)
-(grunts)
-(guns click)
-Put your hands up!
(Woojin breathing heavily, rapidly)
(wailing)
-Let go of me, you bastard!
-(boy continues wailing)
MAN: You damn bastards!
Why are you doing this to me?
Let go of me, you bastards!
MAN: Let go of me, you bastards!
(wailing)
I'm sorry.
(footsteps approaching)
(sighs)
(grunts)
One moment, please.
I think he's only fainted.
(Donghwa pants)
His pulse was fine when I last checked.
But just in case,
you can have a brain CT taken.
(sighs)
Who are you?
SEONUNG: Oh.
I'm a military doctor from the Navy
and the first to treat the patients
while out at sea.
Is this your doing, Captain?
SEONUNG:
I'm sorry I did this without permission.
Everyone seemed distracted, so...
But I have a professional license
so don't worry.
You did well.
Thank you.
(soft chuckle)
How did you know his pulse was stable?
His arm happened to fall near me
when he collapsed.
(clattering)
Good job, everyone.
Good job.
-Good job, you guys.
-Good job.
You did a good job.
Dad?
(pensive music)
Cha Eunjae...
She's very special to me too.
Whether you knew that or not.
I'm just saying.
DOLDAM HOSPITAL TRAUMA CENTER
DOIL: Careful.
Care...
(Myeongsim sighs)
The aftereffects seem to be severe.
Why wouldn't they be?
A power outage during surgery
is the worst accident
that can happen in a hospital.
What's he doing?
(scoffs)
(groans)
What was I thinking...
(somber music)
What are you doing here alone?
What? Oh, hey.
Just thinking over a few things.
Those people...
Hmm?
Was it really right for us...
to send them back?
Was there no way for us...
to protect them?
(sighs)
Woojin,
it's enough that we did what we could.
Oftentimes, between ethics and reality...
(inhales deeply)
...what is right and what the solution is
is hard to balance.
It's just better for us
to do our best as doctors.
Okay?
MYEONGSIM: I wonder what happened.
To what?
MYEONGSIM: Master Kim.
He's not one to give up
on his patients that easily.
Even Master Kim wouldn't have
the ability to do anything.
The higher-ups made the decision.
By any chance,
could he be involved in something?
Politics is what determines
the balance between ethics and reality.
And Master Kim is a man
who absolutely hates such politics.
You know that, Ms. Oh.
It's strange for him to do nothing
and send away surgical patients.
And that young child as well.
He's not the type to just send them away.
(smacks lips)
We just did our job,
so let's just say that was enough. Here.
REPORTER (on TV): Early this morning,
in the East Sea,
a stranded North Korean fishing boat
was rescued
by the South Korean Coast Guard.
A total of five sailors were rescued
from the North Korean ship
that had been drifting in the East Sea
for ten days due to engine failure.
Unfortunately, four of the sailors
died of extreme malnourishment,
dehydration, and injuries.
Only one engineer survived
and was repatriated
to North Korea this evening.
As a result, the inter-Korean summit
that was scheduled for this afternoon
was delayed for about two hours.
Many voiced their concerns
about how this could potentially
cause the summit to fall apart.
-(scoffs)
-REPORTER: However,
around 4 p.m.,
two hours after the scheduled meeting,
the North Korean representatives
appeared at the meeting,
seemingly ending
the concerns of the involved officials.
We cautiously await the results
of the summit,
in hopes that it will pave the way
for practical inter-Korean
economic cooperation.
With that, we end our broadcast.
This was Park Jonghyun from SBC.
(soft music)
(soft music playing)
(sighs)
DOLDAM HOSPITAL
MEDICAL RECORDS SEARCH
(exhales deeply)
RI BOKYOUNG
OPERATIVE REPORT
(mouse scrolling)
(mouse clicks)
FILE DELETION
FILE DELETED
WOULD YOU LIKE TO DELETE THE FILE?
THE FILE HAS BEEN DELETED
RI SANGTAE
MEDICAL RECORD
WOULD YOU LIKE TO DELETE THE FILE?
THE FILE HAS BEEN DELETED
DEFENSE MINISTER RYU WOONGIL
WOONGIL: Since I granted you this favor,
I no longer owe you anything.
(soft chuckle)
(poignant music)
DELETE MESSAGE
DELETE ALL
All right. I guess that's that.
MASTER KIM
DELETE MESSAGE
DELETE ALL
WOONGIL: All right. Let's go in.
-(epic music)
-(camera shutters clicking)
DOLDAM HOSPITAL
Wow, we're finally back.
Man, I actually missed this place.
AREUM: I know.
You brought the present, right?
Of course.
MUNJEONG: Thank you, sir.
Goodbye.
It's safely packed away in this bag.
-It's cold. Let's go in.
-Okay.
Oh, by the way!
The hospital's been pretty quiet,
even though it's Friday.
(gasps)
(stammers)
Dr. Yoon Areum...
(gasps)
(phone ringing)
RECEPTION INFORMATION
This is Doldam Hospital's Emergency Room.
(phones buzzing)
(Insu groans)
-INSU: I had a feeling.
-Let's go, sir.
Okay.
Aren't you coming, Woojin?
On my way.
(bright music)
What kind of patients do we have?
There was a collision at a ski resort.
-Four in total, one with a fracture.
-Okay.
Is Dr. Bae Munjeong
not here yet?
I'm here.
SABU: Hurry up now.
Dr. Bae Munjeong. Welcome back!
-INSU: It's been awhile.
-(groans)
-(Insu yells)
-(Munjeong laughs)
Nice to see you all again.
I'm here too!
INSU: Dr. Yoon Areum!
I'm glad you made it.
Welcome back.
-(Eunjae squeals)
-(Areum giggles)
(bright music continues)
-It's been awhile.
-Hello!
MUNJEONG: Have you been busy?
INSU: Yes.
EUNJAE: Gloves.
TREAT PATIENTS LIKE FAMILY
(chuckles)
(siren blaring)
(ominous music)
RESTRICTED AREA
OPERATING ROOM
-(door slams)
-PARAMEDIC: We have a patient!
(suspenseful music)
-MAN 1: Doctor!
-This way.
Take the emergency patient
to the hybrid room!
MUNJEONG: This way!
-SABU: Slowly.
-(patient groans in pain)
Move him to that bed over there.
-NURSE: Patient, where does it hurt?
-MAN 2: Two, three.
NURSE: Where are you most uncomfortable?
To the treatment room over there,
Nurse Euntak.
Carefully now.
PARAMEDIC
(uplifting music)
I'm going to press down for a bit.
EUNJAE: I'll slowly raise this leg too.
-SABU: ...raise it slowly.
-Jang Donghwa!
-MUNJEONG: Leave it here.
-NURSE: Yes?
Please give me a portable quickly!
-MAN: The left leg...
-EUNJAE: ...lower this leg too.
SABU: Hold on. Are you...?
It's you, right? The one from before?
SEONUNG: Yes, it's me.
I'm the military doctor from that day,
Lee Seonung.
Hmm.
(soft chuckle)
Lee Seonung, you say...
(phone buzzing)
Hello, this is Park Minguk
from Doldam Hospital.
JINMAN (over phone): It's me, Cha Jinman.
Hello, Dr. Cha. It's been awhile.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
I'm calling about the position
at Doldam Trauma Center that you offered.
I have a condition
if you want me to work there.
(tense music)
Yes, what is it?
Bu Yongju...
I want you to remove him
from the Trauma Center.
The Trauma Center without Bu Yongju,
then I'll consider it.
(tense music continues)
(closing theme music)
DR. ROMANTIC SEASON 3
SABU: This will be a test for us too.
You're the only one
who can evaluate me as a doctor.
What kind of plot are you hiding
behind this ridiculous
personnel appointment?
(in childish voice)
Open the lid for me too. Please?
-Your roommate is a doctor?
-What?
JINMAN: To be honest, it's obvious
how they'd be if they learned from you.
DONGHWA:
Look at what happened to that patient.
That patient was the patient I sent away.
Do you think that's a surgery
to save a person's life?
Are you trying to get someone killed?