That day, it was the end of the world for
some, but a new world began for others.
I can't accept this.
My wife just appeared
after years as a corpse,
and now you want me to adopt the children
she had with another man?
How about you being so quick
to transfer Su-hyeon's assets to yourself?
How about you
having not divorced her for years?
Ji-han, go sit over there.
You have no place here.
Among the hostile looks,
-I realized something.
-Look.
Listen carefully...
I'm Lee Ji-han.
Are you my grandfather from today?
That if there's no place for me here,
I should just make one myself.
LEE JI-HAN, AGE 8
YEAR 2007 GRADUATION CEREMONY
I'm sorry I'm not who you were expecting.
Don't say that, Mr. Kim.
I was waiting for you.
For me?
"A triple salary raise coupon,
promotion coupon,
forgiving-a-mistake coupon."
What is...
I've graduated from elementary school now.
I know what's going on at home.
Put in a good word
for me and Do-han with Grandpa.
If we succeed later on,
I'll let you use those coupons.
If there's no one on my side,
I'll make them be.
LEE JI-HAN, AGE 14
Ji-han.
Let's stop now, please?
We pulled three all-nighters.
Only three?
My exam's soon.
Okay.
Go and wash your face,
then explain this question to me.
I don't get this.
Even without hope...
LEE JI-HAN, AGE 18
Whenever I see you
Three, two, one
Be mine, LJ
I love you, LJ
They were hired
through blind screening this year.
I'll always protect you
-Blind screening?
-Be mine, LJ
I'll take care of you until the end
Be mine, LJ
You know me
Even without faith,
if I worked harder,
I thought I could have it all.
And after all those years of effort,
when I just had one step left...
Just one single step left...
Where the hell did she come from?
A-jung.
Would you like to marry me?
And why didn't I know this?
No,
what angers me the most right now...
Please, will you marry me?
No!
Why now?
Why?
Why did she suddenly appear now,
at this crucial time?
CHAIRMAN HYUN'S BIRTHDAY PARTY
LJ FOR A BRIGHT FUTURE
He called Do-han.
He's just standing there alone.
Someone has to help him.
Hello.
I'm Yoon Chae-won from Taeyang Products.
Well...
What is she doing up there?
Is Grandpa announcing it?
What are you doing? Send someone
to cut the power or something.
I can't.
I sent them to find something.
The woman
Do-han's dating is here, right now.
-What?
-She's here now.
Before Mr. Hyun makes a big announcement,
I would like you
to spare some time for me.
Do-han.
What's going on?
I have to know what's going on
to play along.
Go and stay in my car.
Okay.
-You had a car?
-I'll explain.
Just wait for me.
Hurry.
He should've told me
where he parked his car at least.
There's a range to this key.
He's gotten a bit weird.
Excuse me.
Were you with Mr. Lee Do-han earlier?
Who are you?
Please come with us.
Mr. Choi Min-woong wants to see you.
Who's he?
Tell him to come himself.
-Why...
-You can get
-an explanation later.
-What are you doing?
I'm not talking to strangers.
What? I can scream pretty loudly.
You shouldn't do this here.
Give me the key.
Give it to me! Or want to follow them?
EPISODE 2
My head hurts so much.
So it wasn't a dream.
Do-han?
Oh, my God!
You're the one who invaded my space,
so why are you startled?
Where am I?
You don't remember yesterday?
I do.
I ran away with some weirdo
from some strange people.
You popped up
looking like some shabby ninja.
Because I couldn't be seen with you.
Just out of curiosity,
are you not going to thank me at all?
I get to ask questions first.
Where am I?
I guess Do-han's never
even invited you here?
This is
really Do-han's house?
Why would he live here?
You hurt your head hard.
Right, my head...
What happened to my head?
I wanted to ask that.
What's wrong with you?
You jumped out of a moving car yesterday.
Give me my contract.
What's happening today?
Everyone's ordering me around all day.
Give it. You said you'd bring it.
Happy?
Drop me off at the street over there.
One more thing.
Promise me you'll ignore what Do-han said.
What do you mean?
That thing
Do-han asked you.
Oh, marriage?
To be honest,
I can't believe he said that.
I'll talk it over with him.
Talking doesn't seem to work with him.
I'll be the judge of that.
Promise you won't do it.
Approaching school zone.
Observe the speed limit.
Let me tell you this.
I learned Hapkido and Taekwondo and
attended action school for three years.
Threatening to hit me?
No. I mean that if I was less pretty,
you'd have seen me at the Olympics.
And I know how to jump and fall
safely from a car
if the driver won't let me off.
-You're kidding.
-No.
Is she crazy?
Oh, right. I remember.
But I'm sure I calculated
the speed and angle before I jumped.
Ms. Na. Hey.
Ms. Na!
Is she alive or dead?
I hit my head. Shouldn't you
have taken me to the hospital?
We're not that close, you know.
Don't worry.
They said your head was fine.
By the way, Do-han's brother...
I mean, Mr. Lee.
You asked if I was fake yesterday.
You're right.
I lied to Do-han.
I already know that.
But it seems Do-han lied to me too,
for 15 years.
That's a long time.
Everything I know about Do-han
might be all fake.
That's what I'm worried about most.
So
if you tell me honestly about him,
I'd be grateful.
Is he scamming people?
Yes, Professor.
Thank you so much
for coming over late last night.
Yes.
I'll relay the message.
All right.
JEONGAK PHARMACY
FOR: NA A-JUNG
I know he's not that kind of person.
But it's easy
for those who look really kind
to do shady things behind people's backs.
To be honest,
him staying in New York was strange.
He could do art here.
I mean, he loves noodles and chicken feet.
So why does he even stay
where he can't get any of them?
Don't you agree?
But
it makes sense if he's in hiding.
The man who was looking for me
was Choi Min-woong, right?
He had Do-han followed.
But if he was a victim,
it all makes sense.
Then it all fits.
I was mistaken.
Go get changed.
Let's go get your head checked.
No, I'm completely fine.
An arranged marriage?
A successor? Living in a house like this?
It doesn't make sense at all.
It's either
scamming,
or...
Are his parents rich or something?
Our grandpa is.
He is Chairman Hyun Dae-ho.
And Choi Min-woong is my half-brother.
So what you heard yesterday
is Do-han being announced
as LJ's successor.
LJ? LJ Group?
But he wants to throw it away.
Why?
Because of you.
I think I gave you
a kind and honest reply.
So it's your turn.
You really didn't know any of this?
For real?
Stock prices are unstable.
You must be feeling uneasy.
Everyone's talking
about the risks of the change.
And he totally embarrassed you.
Min-woong cried all night
because of what happened.
Scars from your family never really heal.
He got calls from reporters
asking about Do-han's parents.
Darn it. I'm a man of pride.
I've been pushed out
by someone who's not even family.
He's not a part of our family, Grandpa.
Our family's under fire because of him,
but there's no sight of him.
He should be apologizing,
but where is he?
He's not qualified,
and he's not even interested.
And about yesterday,
if he was in his right mind,
he wouldn't have brought her.
Right.
"Her"?
Who do you mean?
Oh, you don't know the real reason
why he refused to marry Chae-won.
No.
He has a long-term girlfriend.
He even brought her
to the party yesterday!
CHAIRMAN HYUN ANNOUNCES SUCCESSOR...
So you're the grandson
of LJ Group's chairman?
And you want to fool him?
By marrying me?
You said you wanted to play
a role like this.
And I'm casting you.
Act as my wife. Just for three years.
Then I'll divorce you.
Are you crazy?
You're the only one I can ask to do this.
At this rate, I'll be forced to marry her,
or they'll find out.
Do-han.
I think you're using your courage
for something weird.
A warm family show where you come out
and be understood is better
than a soap opera about a fake marriage.
A family show about a gay child
born out of wedlock?
The same thing happened five years ago.
I almost got married.
Not at all.
I was going to reveal everything then.
I couldn't bring myself
to deceive someone like that.
DAE-HYEON
Hello?
What's wrong? Did something happen?
When I saw him,
I came to my senses.
I wasn't worried,
I was scared.
I actually felt relieved
it happened while I was gone.
All I could think of next
was to just flee
from everything.
If I have to get married,
I want to do it with you.
I need someone to help me
flee from the company, not succeed it.
Flee? For real?
Are you James Dean?
Like Rebel Without a Cause?
Just accept it.
It's LJ Group of all things.
I can finally understand
why your brother made such a fuss.
A-jung.
I'm not joking.
You're good at acting.
You can keep acting, and I can avoid this.
So you mean
you need a Joan of Arc, not a princess.
But you know what?
Princesses get forgiven for anything,
but Joan of Arc was burned to death
even after saving her country.
Get it?
And you think I'd commit fraud
or jump into fire pits if I got cast?
You think I'd do anything for money?
I have work ethics too, you know.
And a family register isn't
some ending credit.
I promise it won't harm you in any way.
What if...
we're caught?
What will LJ Group's legal team do to me?
Look.
If your grandpa gets angry and sues me,
I could end up
paying them 20 billion instead.
Are you not scared of ruining my life?
That's nonsense.
A-jung...
And you think I know you the best?
You've been hiding so many things from me.
For all those 15 years.
You feel like a stranger to me.
I'm leaving.
Things wouldn't have gotten so complicated
if Mr. Choi were the successor.
The chairman's sudden announcement
is causing a lot of trouble for us too.
That's why I believe everyone here
should make the right decision.
You want the new shopping mall in Myeongju
to be stopped again?
The city is pressuring LJ
to sell the land if it'll get postponed.
We can't do that.
It's easier to make
a justifiable reason.
I have another half-brother.
What if
that other brother is actually
the one in charge of that project?
Wouldn't it cause more trouble later?
I want it so badly.
Maybe this is
a trick.
You know,
in The Honest Woodcutter, he rejects
the axes at first, then gets them all.
Maybe he's after something bigger.
I'm not sure.
The biggest thing he seems to want
is that woman right now.
-Mr. Eun.
-Yes?
Can't you see I'm trying to have hope?
What's with all the facts?
Sorry, sir.
I don't want
to hear
Na A-jung's name.
But neither the chairman nor your brother
are picking up.
What else can you do?
This is so unfair.
A small leak might sink my great ship!
I worked so hard.
Calm down. Breathe.
And sit, please.
Calm down.
Try to be hopeful again.
How can I do that?
If there's a leak,
you should get rid of the cause first.
Then it'll be easy to fix the leak.
The cause?
Na A-jung?
What is it? Why are you so down?
Why else?
The stocks they bought the other day
have plummeted.
You said the prices
were going to soar.
I told you I wouldn't buy them!
That was my severance pay!
But honestly,
even the gods couldn't have guessed
such a surprise announcement.
Right.
Dad! Why are you blaming him?
Go take it up with the chairman of LJ.
It was all because of his grandson.
-Jeez.
-Good job!
My eldest daughter is the best!
I don't care about his grandson!
I just care about my stocks!
If the stock price doesn't go up,
you're dead!
Stop it already!
Enough with those stocks.
And I thought I had your bankbook...
Honey.
Follow me.
Come on!
Are you okay?
I lost my appetite.
Honey!
Darn it.
This won't do.
Dad will really kill him.
A-jung,
let's put it forward.
What?
Dad's turning 60 next month.
You suggested a hair transplant for him.
Let's do that early.
Did I really say that?
Hey!
You skipped
so many birthday gifts for that.
Don't you dare back out now.
I'm not saying I won't do it.
Dad's looking forward to it.
I found a good hospital,
so send the money.
Honey!
I didn't mean to deceive you,
but I'm sorry I did.
I never meant to hurt you.
And my offer's still valid,
so think about it. I hope you say yes.
-Is it good?
-Yes.
I just got
proposed to.
And by my best friend.
-What?
-Hang on.
The guy
who came from New York?
He suddenly wants to marry you? Not date?
-He had a crush on you?
-Hey.
There's no such thing as friends
between men and women,
especially after sex.
No wonder.
She was singing,
"let's go to my house"
all the time these days.
Oh, shut up.
You guys are so vulgar.
Okay, fine.
Let's be sophisticated.
Does he even have money saved?
-You don't.
-He's rich.
He has a house, a car,
and even a company.
You actually believe that?
He could scam you.
Hey, I'm serious.
But you said he's a decent guy.
He's the only guy you complimented.
Right.
Do-han's a really good friend to me.
I'll never do this again.
People tried to stop me for a reason.
I told you so.
You even dragged me into this.
But the pay was good.
I'm investing this money
in my show. It'll succeed, right?
Of course.
God,
please let my first show
have a huge audience.
Please...
Send lots of guests.
-Please.
Amen.
What about you?
Well...
I'm going to invest it in you.
-In me?
-Yes.
Hey, watch your hair.
Don't look so down. You did nothing wrong.
I did.
You invested that hard-earned money,
but my show flopped.
I used my hard-earned money
for something meaningful.
A-jung.
Friends are about giving,
not just receiving.
I have no regrets.
What's with that look? Are you grateful?
Then pay me back later
with your acting.
Still, how could he want
marriage for that?
You get along, and you're single.
What's the problem?
Right. If he's rich,
ask him to help
with your dad's hair transplant too.
You're telling me
to sell myself for his hair?
Come on. Your father may have failed
with his children,
but his hair might succeed.
You're so annoying.
I got to go.
I'm late for my part-time job.
You got a job?
Of course, I did.
I have to earn money for my dad's hair.
Bye.
Hey, clean this up.
It's your job to clean up,
and my job to eat.
Jeez.
Exploring the jungle!
You guys, we have to run!
Everyone, you can't tell the hunter
where we are, okay?
-Okay!
Did you see a monkey?
-Over there!
Thank you, everyone!
We survived thanks to you.
We prepared candies
as a token of our gratitude.
Are you ready for them?
-Yes!
You can't run from me.
I'm going to end this.
You fell from a horse and became a monkey.
Yes, since I need money.
I'm sorry about that day.
I pressed you too much.
Why are you apologizing?
Are you using a different method?
Yes.
A consolation fee.
Not as much as you asked, but it's enough
to make you live comfortably.
I see.
But
from my experience,
eating something in a hurry
never ended well.
Food, men, or money for that matter.
Guess you experienced it a lot.
I'm old enough to know that I should think
about the consequences.
This is money
that I saved up myself from work.
This is clean money,
so just use it freely for your happiness.
You know by now
that Do-han will find his place
if you're gone.
You two are on opposite sides right now.
He asks me to marry him,
and you ask me not to.
Who should I listen to?
Do the right thing.
The right thing?
What Do-han asks?
No, what I ask.
What would you like?
Two iced Americanos
to go please.
Sure.
You're from LJ, right?
Do you remember me?
You come every day
and always get iced coffee.
Oh, yes. That's me.
My heart's actually really warm,
so I need to cool it down
with a cold drink...
That was a joke.
I see.
What's your number?
What?
Sir,
will you enter it yourself?
Excuse me?
Your number for the stamps.
Oh, right.
My fingernails are short,
so I need this.
It's 010-0613-8593, Eun Taek.
Right.
It's Taek, like the famous character.
Two syllables.
Just like Eunhyuk from Super Junior.
What took you so long?
She's really unpredictable.
She's not meeting Do-han that often,
but she took the money straight away.
Very strange.
Right?
That was really weird.
You agree?
And the accident happened right then.
Like some insurance scam.
Why did I keep rambling?
What?
You scammed me!
What do we do?
The chairman knows about Na A-jung.
You said Lee Ji-han was so promising.
I dedicated myself to Ji-han's success,
and this is the result?
Total failure?
Taek.
It's not over yet.
The position
is still open,
and you can still win.
When Ji-han graduated
from elementary school,
do you know what I saw in him?
That again?
A tiger with its claws hidden?
What?
When he and his brother start competing,
he'll even stab Do-han
to ascend the throne.
Then he should sit there right now.
Why's he trying to get Do-han
to sit on the throne?
Because of the accident.
The one that killed Hyun Su-hyeon.
He thinks he caused his parents' death.
He can't take that throne.
This is a rough sketch.
The amount changes
depending on the design.
Lowering the hairline like this
would cost more,
but it'll have more volume.
I like this shape, but my daughters
are paying...
-I see.
-Jeez, Dad. Don't worry.
Just pick the design you want.
Go on.
Give him lots of hair.
-All right.
-Make it thick.
Lots of hair.
We'll harvest them through an incision,
and it'll be 6.3 million won in cash.
We're paying in advance.
Is there no discount?
-Sorry, there isn't.
-All right.
This is money
that I saved up myself from work.
Hey.
-What?
-What's up?
Nothing. I'm sending it.
This is clean money.
Right. He said it was clean.
I should use it.
So just use it freely for your happiness.
I'm sorry.
We'll be back next time.
-Pardon?
-I'm sorry.
-Hey.
-Dad.
I'll get twice the amount
transplanted for you next time.
I promise.
-What...
-Come on.
Wait a moment.
A-jung.
What are you saying?
I feel like I'll stain
my conscience doing this.
Let's just go.
I'm sorry.
We'll come back.
Sorry.
Dad, let's go.
He should really plant some hair.
NA A-JUNG
I thought we were done talking.
Did you have a change of heart?
You should never take back
what you gave.
I never said I'd take that money back.
You said things
like you saved it from work yourself.
Why did you tell me that?
They say
you should never touch money
that's in your savings account.
So?
You want Do-han instead?
You're so crazy about your brother.
I get that you love him.
-Have a drink.
-No thanks.
I never drink with strangers.
Fine, then I'll call Do-han to join me.
Let me ask,
why are you so nosy about his business?
The only thing I want
is his happiness.
Right.
But that's really weird.
Younger brothers never think that.
Normally, they'd only think
about taking their older brother's stuff.
But "happiness"?
That's creepy.
Shouldn't you say "touching" instead?
Do you owe him your life or something?
Yes.
I lived thanks to him.
His happiness is my happiness.
So I always want the best for him.
That really is creepy.
That's normal to me. Is that so wrong?
No, there's nothing wrong with that.
But it sounds kind of suffocating.
Are you saying I'm suffocating him?
No, I mean it must be suffocating for you.
You look anxious and uneasy somehow
when you say you want him to be happy.
For a split second,
I wondered if Do-han would really be happy
seeing that face on you.
No thanks.
I don't drink more than one glass
with someone I hate.
I've decided
not to be Do-han's girlfriend.
But you don't have to drink.
Since I gave your money back,
I was going to make you pay for this.
But I should call Do-han.
Keep your word.
She's Do-han's high school friend.
And they met as soon as he landed here.
I've confirmed
that she was at your birthday party too.
I think Do-han's trying
to introduce her to you, sir.
He's quite late.
I guess we should come back next time...
What...
Over there.
Is that her?
Do-han's girlfriend?
I think so.
What?
Sir.
Wait, that's...
-Ms. Na.
-Yes?
I'll walk you home.
It's fine.
I can go by myself.
I just have to keep going straight.
Who knows if you'll turn around
and go to Do-han's house?
Do you follow girls to their homes
when you're drunk?
Hey, you're talking
as if I'm some kind of wolf.
Hey,
I'm a 32-year-old fox
who's scarier than a wolf.
I'm scared! Go away, old fox...
You're totally wasted.
I should take you home.
I'll take you home.
Taxi!
-Taxi.
-It's here.
What?
-Where should I go, driver?
Sir?
Drive us to his house.
No,
go to hers first.
we should go to yours first.
Go to his house.
Please drive safely.
All right...
His grandfather's
the chairman of LJ Group.
He's a very precious man!
Don't go around telling people that.
My grandfather will hate it.
Why?
I don't know.
My grandfather hates me.
Why?
Do-han hates me,
and you hate me.
Everyone does.
No!
I like you.
I like anyone who buys me drinks.
-Really?
-Yes!
-Then I'll buy again.
-Really?
-Yes!
-Oh, my!
You're the best!
-Yes!
-You're awesome!
Amazing!
We're getting along when we're drunk.
I'll tell you what.
Call your grandfather and bring him here.
I'll scold him for you.
How?
"Grandfather."
"Why would you hate someone like him?"
"Please like him."
"Please love him."
Hey, he's really scary.
You'll freeze in front of him.
Hey, don't worry about that.
You know my nickname?
It's "Princess."
Princess?
I can make anyone listen.
I mean, the fact that he's the chairman
doesn't mean he can hate his grandsons
or force them to marry someone
and succeed a company
when they don't want to.
He can't do that.
Do-han's refusing it all
because of you. To marry you.
Hey.
Do you know why he wants to marry me?
I don't.
By the way, do you think I'm cute?
Do-han
has no one to talk to but me.
I'm the only one
he can be honest with.
He has no one but me.
Even if I'm cute,
you can't
keep liking Do-han.
Oh, no.
Sir.
Yes?
Is this Olympic Expressway?
Yes, it is.
No, we're making a detour.
No, we're not.
We're almost there.
You have deviated from the route.
-Make sure to tell them that.
-Okay.
What?
Where's A-jung?
Is she dating someone?
She's staying out often.
Whatever.
I don't care.
-Mom.
-Yes?
Maybe she had a drink.
She sleeps over at her friend's
when she's drunk.
Maybe.
I don't care.
Aren't you worried about her?
You've always treated A-jung
as though she was
a stray cat you picked up.
Why did you follow them to the hospital?
You know she got fired
and doesn't have any money.
You're terrible.
It's not that.
I can tell
something's going on with her.
MR. KIM
Hello?
What is...
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
I woke up, and I was here.
Come on.
Tell him what happened.
I don't know either.
What?
Would I be here if I remember?
Sit down and eat.
Set the table for Do-han too.
Yes, sir.
What will you do if I say no?
Tell me.
If I oppose to you marrying her like I did
with your parents, what will you do?
Will you give up everything
like your mother
and choose her?
Yes.
Even when she received money
from your brother?
And why can't you be honest
with everyone except her?
Do you know why he wants to marry me?
Do-han has no one to talk to but me.
I'm the only one he can be honest with.
Why can't you answer?
What are you hiding from me?
I'll break up.
A-jung.
You'll break up?
Yes,
I will.
I'm not that stupid.
You called me here
to make me say this myself.
Was your relationship
that easy to give up on?
We can remain...
What?
I guess we can't be friends either.
I understand.
So you don't need to go this far
to oppose us.
Please give Do-han
what you were planning on giving.
I don't want Do-han to give up anything
because of me.
Hey.
A-jung.
You said I seemed like a stranger.
That's what I feel about you. Who are you?
I was shocked when I got the call.
How did you end up drinking with Ji-han?
Why did you sleep there? And the money...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do all that.
It just happened, I guess.
I'm really sorry.
Is talking about me
something that "just happens"?
Are you worried I told him?
I remember that.
I never said a word about it.
-I mean it.
-You did.
You said you'd break up with me
and told him to give me the company.
Wait.
This is ridiculous.
What should I have said, then?
He was even mentioning your parents.
Should I have taken your hand
and run away with you?
You don't even care why I lied, do you?
You and I
seem to think differently
about what friendship is.
To me, a good friend is someone
who tells you
that you can overcome anything,
not runs away with you
when you face trouble.
A-jung.
Telling someone
to overcome something can be cruel.
And saying you trust them
could be the heaviest burden.
I thought you of all people would know.
I overestimated our friendship.
Hey!
You're looking down these days. What's up?
It's been chaos
ever since Do-han came.
So just stop.
Deciding to marry is so hard.
You did it once.
Right.
Why did you decide it?
I don't know,
it was too long ago.
Well,
my ideal type
was someone
who could make anything special.
That's me.
What?
This is ordinary food,
and the river's always the same.
But this is nice.
Yes, it is.
I knew it.
You're perfect
for my brother.
Do-han's the same.
You're using every chance you have.
-Of course.
-Jeez.
I just can't relax
when it comes to you two.
I have to make extra sure
you get married...
Right, making...
extra sure.
Hey, your friend is
in the entertainment business, right?
Yes?
Can I ask a favor?
The role of the female lead's friend?
That's awesome!
Tell me about it.
We've felt so bad since you got fired.
Right.
Writer Hong Bo-ra,
Director Park Tae-pil?
It'll be a masterpiece!
But how did you get cast?
The director saw her acting
in an indie film.
Ji-ae, Jong-hee. I'm going to think
this is my last chance and do my best.
You know I learned
so many things just in case?
I can shoot in water
or fall from the sky if I have to.
I'll show them
that I'm ready for anything.
You need a bigger dream.
Just earning a living is too humble.
Get your dad new hair!
Yes!
-Buy your mom a gift!
-Yes!
-Buy a building!
Thanks.
I'm here.
What kind of grownup does she want to be?
-Dad.
-Yes?
Is Auntie not a grownup yet?
Ji-oh.
Getting old doesn't make you a grownup.
She's just an old child.
Old child...
Oh, my gosh!
Dad, let's go
get that transplant tomorrow.
Mom!
My mom.
Let's buy that massage chair you wanted.
You little brat. Be quiet and go inside.
We should really marry her off
and get rid of her.
I won't get married.
I'm going to live as a baby forever here.
You have to take care of me until I'm 50!
Does she need a whipping to wake up?
-Honey! Wait!
-No!
-Mom!
-Honey!
-Honey, stop!
-You little...
You're a terrible mom
if you can't take care of me until I'm 60!
-Shut up!
-Mom.
You stepped on me.
Director! Hello.
Oh, you're here.
I prepared a lot for the shoot.
I'll do my best so I won't disappoint you.
-Sure.
-Great.
As I told you,
the most important thing
is not to have scandals
regarding your personal life.
Be careful.
Yes, of course.
I'll keep in mind that you don't want
-any scandals.
-Yes.
Just go and get ready.
Okay. I'll get ready.
-Tell the team.
-Okay.
Let's start shooting.
Mr. Lee?
It's really you.
What are you doing here?
To see me?
Why would I come for you?
I work here. LJ Department Store.
I see. But why are you so grumpy?
What are you doing here, then?
Me?
I'm shooting here.
Where's my mirror?
How do I look?
How's my makeup?
Not too much?
It doesn't show much with so much light,
so I put some on.
Is it okay?
My lips.
What are you doing?
I'm asking you to check if it's okay.
Your heart pounded.
-What?
-Yes.
-What, my heart?
-Yes, because of me.
Because of you?
It did!
Awesome.
I'm going to make everyone fall for me.
Thanks for the coffee.
And good luck with work.
My heart never pounded.
Hey, I mean it.
That little...
What are you smiling at?
When did I smile?
Just now.
Like this.
What?
Isn't that Na A-jung?
Is it?
Who cares? Let's go.
Everyone's working really hard.
The actors are doing great.
Especially the friend role.
She got in through her connections, right?
She was all excited, not even knowing
that it was chaos here because of her.
I guess you have to
be so shameless to steal roles.
I just feel sorry
for the actress who had her role stolen.
She took so many auditions.
The director liked her.
I know, right?
Hello.
Was that
about me?
Using my connections?
When?
Ji-oh, say bye.
-Bye.
I'll talk to him.
Okay. Bye.
Let's go.
Ji-oh.
Did you say you ate kimchi
when you didn't?
I told you, lying is bad.
Being honest and getting scolded
will make you a good adult.
It wasn't just me.
Si-hyun and Hae-bom lied about it too.
They did it yesterday too,
but no one knew.
Right, no one might have known,
but one person would have.
Who?
Yourself.
No one may know,
but you know that it's wrong.
Ms. Na, stand at the T-bar here.
Okay.
Walk from there to here.
If you're ready, let's go.
Roll camera.
All right.
Ms. Na, what...
What's wrong?
What is it?
Excuse me.
Where's the actress Na A-jung?
Na A-jung?
Who's that?
The lead's friend.
Oh, her.
She went home.
What? Why?
I'm curious too.
She suddenly apologized
and said she couldn't do it.
Did she think this was some playground?
I heard you passed an audition
and got a good role.
I don't need a massage chair.
I'm so happy for you.
I know you can do it! Good luck!
I knew you would succeed.
I need that hair transplant. Great job!
Get in.
Come on.
Are you crazy?
Why would you suddenly quit?
You're going to miss
such a good opportunity?
I heard somewhere
there are three steps
between two people.
One less step makes a misunderstanding
and one more makes an understanding.
Just three steps.
And you know what it is if you take more?
What is it?
What do you think?
Meddling without knowing your place.
Why did I suddenly quit?
You dare to ask me that?
Did you just punch me? Seriously?
What upsets me the most
isn't that you got me a role
I didn't ask for,
but that
I want to call the director and beg him
to just give me a chance.
I know that it's wrong to pretend
I don't know anything,
but I just want to do my best.
That angers me the most.
Do you even get it?
If I hadn't gone to the bathroom...
No, if I hadn't come out at that time...
Then I would have just thought
that I really got a good opportunity.
Who are you...
to make me have such regrets?
I get it, so get in the car.
Cabs don't stop here.
What makes you really awful
is that you made me hate myself, not you.
You know that?
The logic of life
is that you can't always be happy.
You suffer at one point in your life.
When that moment comes, think of me.
Because that's when my wish has come true.
You asked if I'll miss the opportunity.
I won't.
Do-han.
No,
nothing's up.
I'll do it.
I'll marry you.
Choose.
Is it me or her?
I'll get exploited
and abandoned if I marry.
It's not a baby, right?
-Here.
-You won't regret it?
I'm getting married.
What?
An elopement. That's what we'll do.
I just became a cupid for them.
Who are you?
Are you both frauds?
Do you like Ji-han?
I thought it was always him.
There seems to be only one way
to fix this problem with Na A-jung.
Translated by Juyoung Park