The day when someone's death
was the start of a new life for someone else.
I absolutely cannot.
It's absurd that my wife, whom I never had contact with, only appeared after her death.
Now, you want me to raise the children she had with another guy as my own?
Is that why you were so quick to liquidate Soo Hyeon's stocks and real estate and add it to your account?
Was that the reason you didn't divorce her and were separated?
Ji Han, go over there and sit.
There is no place for you to sit in this house.
I realized one thing in the midst of the unfriendly stares.
Son-in-law Choi.
Listen to me carefully—
I'm Lee Ji Han.
Are you my grandfather starting today?
If there is no place for me,
I can just create space for me.
I'm sorry I'm not the one you're waiting for.
Why would you say such a thing?
I was waiting for you, Secretary Kim.
For me?
Tripling your salary coupon,
special promotion coupon,
overlooking a major mistake coupon.
This is...
I graduated from elementary school now.
I've finished assessing the situation somewhat.
Please put in a good word for me and Do Han to Grandfather.
If you support us well, I'll make sure you can use those coupons.
Even if nobody's on my side,
I just have to pull them to my side.
Ji Han.
Let's please stop now.
We pulled three straight all-nighters!
It's only been three days?
We only have two days until the exam.
Okay.
If you're sleepy, go wash your face.
When you come back, explain to me why you got this answer.
I keep getting it wrong.
Even when there seems to be no hope.
♫  Every time I see you  ♫
♫  Three, two, one! Be mine, LJ!  ♫
♫  I love you, oh, LJ!  ♫
They're the new employees we hired through blind recruitment.
♫  I will protect you to the end  ♫
Blind?
♫  LJ, I'll take responsibility for you to the end  ♫
♫  Be mine, LJ! You know me  ♫
Even though I couldn't see what I hoped for,
I thought I could attain all of it if I just tried harder.
After running tirelessly all these years,
I was just one step away from obtaining everything.
It was really just one more step...
So, where did that woman suddenly come from?
Hey, Na A Jeong. By chance, would you be willing to marry me?
And why hadn't I known all this time? No, never mind.
More than all this, the thing that drives me crazy the most...
Please, marry me.
No!
Why now of all times...
Why at this extremely important timing
did that woman appear?
He called for Do Han.
Grandfather is waiting there like that. Is there any other option?
Someone should go and fix the situation.
Hello, I'm Yoon Chae Won of Taeyang Corporation.
What? Why is she over there?
Did Grandfather decide to go through with announcing the marriage?
Oppa, what are you doing?
You should order someone to cut the power or something.
I don't have anyone to give orders to.
I sent them somewhere else to look for something urgent.
That woman. The one Lee Do Han is supposedly dating.
I heard she's here.
- What?
- She's here.
Before the chairman makes an important announcement,
I'd appreciate it if you could spare me some of your time.
Hey, Lee Do Han, what is this situation?
I'd need to know the situation for me to go along with you.
Go to my car in the parking lot for now.
Okay.
- You had a car?
- I'll explain everything later.
Wait for me a bit. Hurry up and go.
I mean, he should at least tell me where he parked.
Even if I try to just guess, I need to know the range.
He's gotten weird since I last saw him.
Excuse me.
By chance, were you with Lee Do Han just now?
- Who are you?
- Please come with us for a moment.
Executive Director Choi Min Woong wants to see you.
And who is that?
If he wants to see me, he should come himself. Why tell me to come?
You can hear the explanation later when you get there.
Why are you doing this?
I'm uncomfortable around strangers. I don't need to hear anything from you people.
Hey! I have a very loud voice.
If you do this here, things will get messy for everyone.
Give me the key.
I said, give me the key!
Or will you go with them?
Gosh, that really hurts.
It doesn't seem like it's a dream.
Lee Do Han?
You're the one trespassing.
Why are you sneaking around like a thief and getting scared?
- Where is this place?
- I guess you don't remember what happened yesterday.
I do remember.
I ran away from very suspicious people with a less suspicious you.
You suddenly showed up looking like some low-quality ninja turtle.
That was because I was afraid people might see me with you.
I'm only asking because I'm curious,
but aren't you going to thank me for helping you?
Questions are answered on a first-come, first-serve, and I asked first.
I asked where this is.
You said you loved him and whatnot, but I guess Brother never brought you home.
This is...
really Lee Do Han's house?
Why does he live in a place like this?
You must've really hurt your head badly.
Oh, right! My head...
Why is my head like this?
That's what I want to ask you.
Why are you like that?
You jumped out of a moving car.
Give me my contract.
Gosh, what's with my luck today?
Today is full of people telling me what to do.
Give it to me. You said you would bring my contract.
Happy?
I'll get off, so stop at that major road up ahead.
One more thing. Promise me to forget everything my brother said.
About what?
You know, about...
what he asked you to do earlier.
Oh, marrying him?
Honestly, I'm also confused about what I just heard earlier.
But I'll discuss that with him in person.
I'm saying this because I can't seem to get through to him.
And that decision is for him to decide.
Until you promise, you can't get off.
You are entering the children's safety zone.
Follow the speed limit.
To explain a bit about myself,
I'm second-degree in hapkido and taekwondo,
and I've attended action school for three years.
Are you saying you will hit me or something?
No. I'm saying if I was just a little less pretty, you would've seen me at the Olympics.
It also means if the driver doesn't let me off,
I know the landing techniques to jump out safely.
- You're joking, right?
- No.
This woman must be crazy!
Right, right. I remembered.
But I'm sure I jumped out after calculating the speed and angle...
Na A Jeong. Na A Jeong, wake up!
Na A Jeong!
What? Is she dead or alive?
Shouldn't you have taken someone who might have a concussion to a hospital first?
We're not that close for me to act as your guardian twice.
Don't worry.
Paramedics said nothing was wrong with your brain.
But Do Han's younger brother, no—
Lee Ji Han,
you asked me yesterday if I was a fake, right?
You're right.
I lied to Do Han.
You don't need to tell me what I already know.
But I think Lee Do Han lied to me, too.
I have known him for 15 years.
That's a long time.
To think that everything about him for the past 15 years might be fake...
That is what I'm most worried about right now.
So, I'd really appreciate it if you could tell me everything
you know, honestly.
Does Lee Do Han go around committing fraud?
Yes, Professor. Yes, yes.
Thank you so much for yesterday.
It mustn't have been easy for you to come to my house at that late hour.
Yes. Yes, I'll pass that on. Yes, yes.
Okay.
Of course, I know. He would never do that.
But usually, it's easier for people who look so nice
to do something devious in secret.
Honestly, I thought it was strange that he was in New York.
He could do art here.
He loves banquet noodles and chicken feet.
So, why would he live where there are no Korean street food vendors?
Don't you think so?
But when you add the word "Flee," everything makes sense.
The one who ordered his secretary to search for me yesterday.
His name was Choi Min Woong, right?
I remembered he was the one following Do Han.
But what if he was also a victim?
I'm getting goosebumps. Everything makes sense.
I didn't think this through.
Hurry inside and get changed so we can get your head examined.
No, no. My head is perfectly fine.
The arranged marriage, being a successor,
and living in a house like this. None of this makes sense.
How do you explain any of this?
I mean...
fraud...
or...
are you saying he's a second-generation chaebol?
Not second-generation. Third generation.
Our grandfather is Chairman Hyeon Dae Ho.
And the man who was looking for you viciously was my half-brother.
So, what you heard yesterday
was my brother's name being officially announced as the successor of LJ.
Did you just say LJ Group?
But he says he will blow off that incredible opportunity.
For what?
All because of you.
I think I answered you pretty honestly and helpfully.
So you should answer me now.
You really didn't know any of this?
And you're not acting like you didn't know it?
With our stocks tumultuous at the moment,
you also must feel tumultuous, Grandfather.
There is so much talk in and out of the company about owner risk
and you lost face, Grandfather.
He cried all night last night, so upset.
Even if you're an adult, family issues hurt you for life.
He got so many calls from people and reporters about the illegitimate child controversy.
- Nice shot!
- Good shot!
I also have pride.
It's upsetting that I got pushed out as your eldest grandson.
But the one who pushed me out isn't even on the family registry.
That guy isn't part of our family, Grandfather.
Look at what's going on now. Our entire family is on the chopping board because of him.
He should be begging for forgiveness.
But where is he? Where is he?
He's nowhere to be seen.
It shows that he lacks basic character and he doesn't care.
Just look at yesterday!
If he had any thoughts at all,
would he have brought that woman?
What do you mean by a woman?
What do you mean by that?
You don't know about that, right?
The real reason Lee Do Han refuses to marry Chae Won.
What?
He has a girlfriend he's been dating for a long time.
Not only that, he brought that woman with him yesterday!
So, you're really the grandson of LJ Group's chairman?
And you're saying we should deceive the chairman by getting married?
You told me before you wanted to act in a drama with this kind of story.
I'll cast you, A Jeong.
Please act as my wife for just three years.
After that, I'll make sure we get divorced.
Are you crazy?
No matter how much I think about it, you're the only one I can talk to about this.
At this rate, I'll either get married or get found out about my sexual orientation.
Do Han, I think you're trying to use your courage in a weird way.
Rather than a melodrama where you're forced into a fake marriage,
isn't a family drama where you confess your secret and everyone understands you better?
Is there a family drama with an illegitimate gay son?
The same thing happened five years ago.
I almost got married then, too.
Don't mention it.
I was going to reveal everything then.
I couldn't spend the rest of my life deceiving an innocent person.
Hello?
What's wrong? Is something the matter?
When I saw that, I suddenly came to my senses.
Rather than worried, I got scared.
I was actually grateful
that it happened while I wasn't there.
After that, all I could think was one thing.
I wanted to run from this situation.
If I must get married anyway, I want to marry you since you know my situation.
What I need is not someone to help me inherit the company
but someone to help me escape from the company.
Escape, my foot.
Who are you, James Dean?
Are you supposed to be a rebel without a cause?
If he gives it to you, take it.
Of course, you should take it. It's LJ.
I finally understand why your younger brother was making such a fuss.
A Jeong,
I'm not joking right now.
You're good at acting.
You can do all the acting you love, and I can escape this situation.
So, you're saying you don't need a princess but Joan of Arc.
But did you know that
a princess is forgiven for whatever sins she commits,
but Joan of Arc was burned at the stake despite saving her country?
Burned at the stake!
And did you think I'd deceive people and throw myself into flames as long as I'm cast?
Did you think I'd get excited and say okay if you just paid me?
I also have a sense of my professional calling.
And is a family register some kind of ending credit
that you'd add to it and take it off like that?
I promise it won't cause you any harm.
What if we get caught?
What will you do if we get caught?
Is the legal team at a major corporation like LJ only there for show?
Look here.
If your grandfather decides to hold a grudge against me,
I may have to pay 20 billion won while trying to earn 2 billion!
Screwing over some other guy's life is scary,
but screwing over my life is fine?
What kind of contradiction is that?
A Jeong...
And you say I know your situation?
Didn't you hide too much from me for you to say that?
Seriously, 15 years of friendship is meaningless.
Now that my trust in you is broken, you seem like a stranger.
I want to leave.
If Executive Director Choi inherited the management rights as planned,
things wouldn't have gotten this complicated.
Because the chairman suddenly announced his successor,
we're also facing a headache.
That's why those of you here at least need to make the right choice.
Are you asking us to suspend the construction of the
new shopping mall complex in Myeongju again?
Even the city is nagging us to sell it to a competitor
if we're going to delay any longer. So we can't suspend it.
It's better to come up with a reason rather than to create another headache.
I have one more younger brother besides Lee Do Han.
If the real person in charge of that project is that younger brother,
wouldn't it become an even bigger headache later?
I want it so badly.
Is it something like that?
A foundational change?
You know, even the woodcutter acted like he refused the golden and silver axes,
before taking it all home in the end.
Do you think my brother is after something bigger?
I don't know.
Right now, the only thing bigger to your brother is that woman.
- Team Leader Eun.
- Yes?
Can't you see I'm taking copium right now?
(Lying to oneself to cope)
Did I say I wanted to hear facts right now?
I'm sorry.
What I need to hear are sweet things.
Not the name, Na A Jeong.
The angry chairman and your brother who angered him are not picking up their phones,
so what else can you do?
I'm the one who's most pissed off.
My precious tower is about to collapse because of an ant hole!
- Do you know how I climbed up here?
- Now, now.
First, calm down and breathe deeply.
Over here.
Let's get back to some copium.
How! How!
If an ant hole appeared,
you should squash the ant coming through the hole.
Then, filling up the hole would be an easy task.
Ant?
Na A Jeong.
What's going on? What's with the mood?
What do you think?
The stocks that the small investors here bought a couple of days ago dropped steeply.
You said it was trustworthy information.
You said it will rise like crazy.
That's why I said I wouldn't buy it!
What are you going to do about my severance pay!
But honestly, a surprise successor announcement like this...
Even God or Buddha can't predict that.
Hey, Dad! Why are you being so hard on him only?
If you have something to say, say it to LJ's chairman.
Their stocks fell because he revealed he had an illegitimate grandson—
- Gosh, seriously.
- All right!
I could only count on my eldest daughter.
I don't care about some illegitimate grandson or successor! My stocks better rise!
You already got water sprayed on your face. Blood will be spilled in this family!
Gosh, stop it! Seriously.
Talking about the stocks from the morning, geez.
Also, that severance pay account—
Honey, come inside for a moment.
Hurry!
Are you okay?
I don't have much of an appetite...
Honey!
This won't do.
At this rate, my husband will die of stress.
Hey, Sis, let's move up our plan.
- What plan?
- It's Dad's 60th birthday next month.
You said we should get him hair implants.
Let's bring that up a bit sooner.
Did I say such a commendable thing?
What's this? You skipped on Dad's birthday gifts for several years to save up for that.
You're not going to say otherwise now. Are you?
No, it's not that, but...
Dad is totally looking forward to it.
I've looked into a hospital for it,
so you just send the money.
Honey!
I didn't do it intentionally,
but I'm sorry for hiding it all this time.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
Also, my offer is still on the table,
so I'd appreciate it if you'd consider it positively again.
- Is it good?
- Yeah.
I... I received a proposal.
From my best friend of 32 years, at that.
- What!
- Wait, wait.
From that guy who came from New York?
He's not even asking you out. Go directly to marriage from being friends suddenly?
He liked you? Since when?
Hey, there's no such a thing as "suddenly" between a man and a woman.
You just switch modes after sleeping together.
Wow, no wonder you've been singing
"Let's go to my house" all the time lately.
Gosh, seriously... Shut up! Shut up!
Why am I trying to talk to such low-class people?
Okay, okay, let's talk about something more classy.
Did he say that with some money saved up? You don't have money.
He says he's rich.
He also has a car, a house, and his own company.
He didn't say he had a jade mat?
He didn't try to sell it to you?
I'm being serious. Don't be like this.
But you said he was an okay guy.
Wasn't he the only guy you've ever praised like that?
You're right, Unni. Lee Do Han is a really good friend to me.
I won't ever do this part-time job again.
There was a reason why people said not to do it.
I told you this job was hard.
Why did you have to drag me into it when I said no?
Come on! At least we earned a lot of money.
My performance won't be a failure after investing all of my hard-earned money, right?
Of course not.
God, may many people come to my first-ever performance.
In Jesus' name—
Please let many people come!
- Please let many people come.
- Yes.
Amen.
What are you going to do with this money?
I will invest it in you.
- In me?
- Yeah.
Hey, your hair is going to fall into your noodles.
Hey, lift your head! Why are hanging your head like you're some criminal?
It is a crime.
You invested your hard-earned money into my performance, but it was a complete failure.
Okay, okay! It was hard-earned money.
I just spent my hard-earned money where I wanted to.
A Jeong, it's better to give than to receive. That's what friends are for.
I'm happy! I don't regret it.
What's with your expression? I guess you're really grateful.
Then, just pay me back in the future with great acting.
Still, how could he think of getting it back with marriage?
You guys get along, and you guys aren't seeing anyone. So what's the problem?
Unni, why don't you ask him to help your father get hair implants if he's that rich?
Hey, am I Simcheong that I'd get sold off to get my dad's hair implants?
(Korean folktale)
Why not? Though your father may not have raised his children well,
he may be successful in growing his hair.
So annoying. Forget it.
I'm going to my part-time job. I'm late.
You got a part-time job?
Of course! Would I just loaf around?
I need to work hard and earn money to get my dad's hair implants.
I'm leaving.
You should clean up before you go!
Cleaning is your job, and eating is my job.
Jungle expedition!
Friends, we have to run away quickly!
Kids, you can't tell that hunter where we are. Okay?
Okay!
Did you see a monkey?
Over there, over there!
There, there!
Everyone, thank you so much!
Thanks to your help, we were able to survive.
To thank all of you, we prepared candy for you guys.
Are you ready to receive your candy?
Yes!
There is no use in running away.
I will end you for sure.
After you fell off the horse, you became a monkey chased by a hunter, I see.
Yes, since I'm short on money.
I was too discourteous that day.
I pushed you too much, right?
Why are you suddenly apologizing to me?
Have you decided to use a different method now?
Yes.
It's an appropriate amount of compensation money.
It's not the amount you mentioned, but I prepared it sincerely.
Enough so that you won't be short on money for a while.
I see.
But based on my statistics,
I always got indigestion whenever I ate what was around in a hurry.
Whether it's food, men, or even this money.
Sounds like you've eaten badly many times before.
I'm old enough to know that I should watch what I eat before it becomes an issue.
This isn't our family money.
It's my money I saved up every month once I got hired.
It won't become a problem,
so just think about your happiness while spending that money, Na A Jeong.
By now, you should know
that if Brother would naturally go back to his place once you go away.
When I think about it, you brothers are like an umbrella and salt vendor.
One asks me to marry him, and the other asks me not to.
Who should I listen to?
Listen to the umbrella vendor.
If it's the umbrella vendor...
Do Han?
I'm the umbrella vendor.
What can I get for you?
Please give me two cold iced Americanos to go.
Okay.
You're an LJ employee, right?
By chance, do you remember me?
You come in every day. You drink iced even in winter.
Yes. That's me.
I'm actually a warmhearted guy inside, so I always need to cool off with a cold drink.
Otherwise, people say they'll get burned.
Oh, it's just a joke.
- Oh, I see.
- Yes...
Could you give me your number?
Pardon?
Sir, could you input your number yourself?
The number to collect your stamps.
Yes. My nails are a bit short... I was going to input it.
It's 010-0613-8593, Eun Taek!
Oh, I see.
It's Taek. Like Taek from the Reply series.
It's two syllables like Super Junior's Eun Hyuk.
What took you so long?
I keep getting it wrong with my predictions.
She doesn't interact with Young Master Do Han often.
But she accepted the money as if she was waiting for it?
Very strange.
Right?
It was too weird, huh?
You feel that way, too?
She got in the accident as if she was timing it.
Just like insurance fraud.
I should have just stopped at Taek. Taek!
You're the one who committed fraud! What will you do now?
You said the chairman found out about that woman Na A Jeong.
You said Lee Ji Han is a skyrocketing stock.
Is this what I get for serving Lee Ji Han night and day?
Is it? Freefall?
Taek.
The market hasn't closed yet.
The successor position is still open,
and if we hang in there, we will be victorious one day.
On Young Master Ji Han's elementary school graduation,
do you know who I saw in him?
Again, again...
Who? Yi Bang Won with his hidden claws?
(Third king of Joseon Dynasty)
Hey, once the feud between brothers gets underway,
he's the type who will slaughter everyone to rise to the throne.
Then, he should just hurry up and do so.
Why is he trying to get a Jeongjong like Lee Do Han on the throne?
(Second king of Joseon Dynasty)
Of course, because of that accident.
The accident that led to President Hyeon Soo Yeon's death.
How could he sit on that throne
when he thinks his parents died because of him.
All right. This is the basic sketch.
The amount of hair follicle implants will be different based on the design.
Though lowering the hairline like this is more expensive,
it will make your hair look much fuller.
I do like this design,
but my daughters are paying for it.
Gosh, Dad. Don't worry.
Go with whichever one you like, Dad.
Oh, yes. Fill in his hairline tightly.
So, it looks like he has a lot of hair.
Full and abundant.
We're going to collect your hair through incisions,
and it will cost you 6.3 million won in cash today.
We'll pay it in one advance payment. Is there any discount?
No, there isn't.
I see, okay.
This isn't our family money.
It's my money I saved up every month once I got hired.
Hey.
- Yeah?
- What are you doing?
No, it's nothing. I should send the money.
It won't become a problem...
Yeah, he said this money won't become a problem. Let's just use it.
So, just think about your happiness while spending that money, Na A Jeong.
I'm sorry.
We'll just come back next time.
- Pardon?
- I'm sorry.
- Hey.
- Dad,
I'll let you get double the implants next time with your hair all the way down here.
Really, I promise. Let's just go home for today.
Just a moment.
Hey, Sis. What are you saying after we've come all this way?
I feel like I'll lose my conscience trying to help Dad grow some hair.
Let's just go.
I'm sorry.
We'll come back next time. We're sorry. Dad...
Oh, oh, oh... I think you should get your hair implants, though...
I don't think there's anything more to talk about.
I guess you had an unnecessary change of heart?
Do you know what the meanest thing in the world is?
To give something and take it back.
I said to spend it. I never said I'd take it back.
You added extra comments. You told me to spend it.
So, why did you say how you saved up that money every month since you got hired?
You know, I was told it was okay to touch lottery money
but you shouldn't touch maturity savings.
So? You won't take this money but take my brother's instead?
That damn brother, brother, brother talk.
People without a brother must be so sad.
- Have a drink first.
- No, thank you.
As a rule, I don't drink with people I don't know.
Since it'll be boring to drink by myself, I guess I'll just call Do Han.
Let me ask you something.
Why are you getting so involved in Do Han's business?
I only want one thing.
For Brother to be happy.
I'm saying that's really weird.
That's not the mindset of someone who is younger.
Typically, it's normal for younger brothers to think about how they can take
their brother's clothes, things, and food.
But wanting his happiness?
That gives me goosebumps.
Don't people say it's brotherly love instead of giving goosebumps?
Do you owe your life to Do Han for something?
Yes.
I was able to live thanks to my brother.
My happiness is Brother's happiness.
So, if Brother is supposed to have something, I want that to be the very best.
Still gives me goosebumps.
In my world, this is normal. Do you have a problem with that?
No. That won't be a problem,
but I feel like it will be suffocating.
Are you saying I'm choking my brother or something?
No. I'm saying it must be suffocating for you, Lee Ji Han.
Your facial expression as you say you want your brothers happiness
seems very anxious and nervous for some reason.
I briefly wondered if Do Han can truly become happy when he sees that expression
for a split second.
No thank you.
I don't drink more than one glass with someone I don't like as a rule.
I made up my mind not to be Do Han's lover anymore.
If you still say no, oh well.
I didn't accept your money,
so I was going to tell you to pay for these drinks.
I guess I should call Lee Do Han now.
You better not change your mind later.
She's Do Han's high school classmate.
She was the first person he met after returning to South Korea.
After looking into it,
it's also true she came to your birthday banquet, Chairman.
It seems to me that Do Han was going to introduce that young lady to you, Chairman.
She's quite late in coming home.
I don't think you'll get to meet her today. Should we come back next time—
Well...
It's that young lady?
The one Do Han is supposedly dating?
I think so...
Chairman.
That's...
- Na A Jeong.
- Yes?
I said I'll walk you home.
I said, I'm fine!
I can go by myself.
I just have to go straight from here. Straight.
Gosh, how do I know if you will go straight home or make a U-turn toward my brother's house?
Were you the type who follows a girl you don't know home when you get drunk?
Yeah! What if I follow you home?
You talk as if I'm a wolf or something.
No.
I'm a 32-year-old fox who's more dangerous than a wolf.
Oh, you're so scary! I am going to go home—
You're way too drunk.
I'll have to take you to your house.
I should take you to your house.
Taxi.
- Taxi.
- A taxi came.
Taxi! It's a taxi.
♫  Where should I go?  ♫
♫  Ahjussi!  ♫
Ahjussi, please take us to his house.
Gosh, no, please take us to her house first.
Gosh, we should go to your house first, Young Master.
Please take us to his house first.
Please drive safely.
Okay.
His grandfather is LJ Group's chairman.
He's a really important person!
I told you not to tell people that!
My grandfather won't like it!
- But why?
- I don't know.
My grandfather never liked me.
Why?
Brother also doesn't like me, and you don't like me, either.
- Everyone hates me!
- That's not true!
I like you!
I like anyone who buys me drinks!
- Really?
- Yeah!
- Then I'll buy you drinks again!
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- Whoa!
You're the best! The absolute best!
You're the best!
I can actually talk to you now that you're drunk.
I feel great. Bring your grandfather here.
I'll teach him a lesson.
How?
Grandfather...
Why don't you like such a good boy like him?
Please like him!
Please show him some love!
Hey, my grandfather is really scary.
If you meet him, you can't say anything.
Hey. Don't even worry about stuff like that.
Do you know what my nickname is?
- It's Princess, Princess.
- Princess!
The mouth of terror.
To be blunt, is being a chairman all that?
If he's the chairman, does that make it all right
to hate someone, marry someone off to a girl he doesn't like,
and force someone to sit and inherit a company he doesn't want?
Hey, why do you think Brother is saying no to all of that?
It's because of you, so he can marry you.
Hey.
Do you know why Lee Do Han is trying to marry me?
I don't know.
But do you find me cute?
I'm the only one Lee Do Han can speak to about stuff like that.
I'm the only one he can be honest with!
But don't find me cute.
You can't keep liking my brother just because I'm cute. Okay?
Okay.
Mr. Driver.
Yes?
Are you sure this is the Olympic Highway?
Yes, it is.
We're going back right now.
Oh, no, that's not true. The IC, the IC is up ahead.
You are off course.
Make sure to tell the teacher.
Where's Sis?
Did Na A Jeong get a boyfriend?
She's been sleeping out often these days.
Whether she does or not, whatever.
Whether she comes home or not, whatever.
- Mom.
- Yeah?
You sure Auntie isn't drinking?
Auntie usually sleeps over at her friend's house when she drinks.
Maybe?
Whether she drinks or not, whatever.
Aren't you even worried about her?
How could you treat A Jeong like you've been raising some stray cat since her childhood?
So why did you follow them to the hospital?
You knew she had no money because she got cut from work.
Goodness, how could you be like that?
I don't think so...
I feel like something's up with her.
Hello?
What is going on?
A Jeong, why are you here?
I know, right?
I opened my eyes, and here I am.
What are you doing?
Say something since I don't remember.
- Do you think I remember anything?
- What?
If I remembered, do you think I would be like this right now?
What are you doing? Eat if you're here.
Ahjumma, prepare some food for Do Han, too.
Yes, Chairman.
So, what will you do if I can't give you my permission?
What if I also oppose it this time, like I did to your mom and dad?
What will you do?
Will you also give up everything I've given you
and choose this young lady here?
Yes.
Even though she accepted the money your brother gave her without hesitation?
Also, what is it that you can't be honest about to others except for her?
Do you know why Lee Do Han is trying to marry me?
I'm the only one Lee Do Han can speak to about stuff like that.
I'm the only one he can be honest with!
Why can't you answer me?
I'm asking what you're hiding from me, your grandfather!
I'll break up with him.
Hey, Na A Jeong!
You will break up with him?
Yes. I will break up with him.
I'm not that oblivious.
You had me sit here while you talked about this, hoping I'd say this first.
Your relationship with him was this easy to give up on?
Being friends—
What?
You wouldn't want that, right?
Then, I'll do what you want.
So, don't waste your energy opposing us.
Just give him what you intended to give him, Sir.
So, Do Han doesn't give up on anything while being compared to his parents because of me.
Hey.
Hey, Na A Jeong, you said I seemed like a stranger to you, right?
That's how I feel right now. Who are you? Are you my friend?
Do you know how shocked I was when I picked up the phone this morning?
How did you and Ji Han end up getting drunk like that?
Why did you sleep at my grandfather's house, and what money?
I'm sorry.
I really didn't mean to, but I guess it just happened that way. I'm really sorry.
Is my story that easy for you to tell if things happened to go that way?
Do you think I may have told your grandfather?
I do remember that. No matter how drunk I was, I never mentioned that.
- I mean it.
- But you did.
You said you'd break up with me.
So, he should pass on the company to me.
I mean...
This is ridiculous the more I listen.
What should I have said in that situation, then?
When he started bringing up your parents, whom I know nothing about,
should I have grabbed your hand and run away or something?
You're not even interested in knowing why I lied, right?
It seems like you and I
have such a different idea of what friendship is while we were apart.
My idea of a good friend
isn't someone who takes my hand and runs off when I'm in trouble,
but someone who tells me I can do this to the end. That's a good friend.
Na A Jeong, in some situations,
telling someone they can do it is the cruelest thing to say.
Telling them you believe in them could become the heaviest burden.
I thought you would at least know that.
I guess I overestimated our friendship.
Hey!
Your face looks so bad these days.
Is something bothering you?
I've always got something going on.
Every day without fail since Lee Do Han came.
So, stop it now.
Do you know how hard it is to decide on getting married?
But you got married once, CEO Yoon.
Yeah. How did you end up getting married then?
I don't know...
It was such a long time ago.
It was just that my ideal type was
someone who made mundane things special for me.
That's me.
- What?
- We're eating mundane food like this
at the Han River, which is nothing out of the ordinary.
But isn't it really nice?
Yeah. It's nice.
As I thought.
My brother is a perfect match for you.
We're brothers. My brother also likes things like this.
You really try to score a goal whenever you get the chance.
Of course.
Even if I score a goal like this, I can't ever let down my guard with you and Brother.
I need to score an extra goal and a final nail-in-the-coffin goal to feel at ease—
Right, an extra goal.
The nail-in-the-coffin goal.
CEO Yoon, you said you knew someone in the entertainment business, right?
- Yeah.
- Let me ask you a favor.
I can't believe you got the female lead's friend role. That's great, Unni!
I know!
- We felt really bad when you got cut last time.
- I know.
You know it's a trustworthy hit drama with the Writer Hong Bo Ra and Director Park Dae Pil!
But how did they end up calling you first?
That director saw A Jeong's acting in an indie film.
Unni, Jong Hye, I'll really try my best, thinking this is my last chance.
You know I got many certifications just for this moment, right?
If they tell me to go in the water, I will.
If they tell me to drop out of the sky, I can!
I will show them I've been ready for a long time.
Unni, you should reset your dream.
Your dream of earning a living through acting is a bit too small now.
- Give your father hair implants through your acting.
- Yeah!
- Buy your mother a massage chair.
- That's right!
- And buy coffee over there!
- Yeah!
Thanks.
I make an entrance.
Seriously, what kind of an adult does she want to become?
- Dad.
- Yeah?
Auntie isn't an adult yet?
Ji Ho, just because you're older doesn't mean you become an adult.
She is an adult who aged incorrectly.
An adult who aged incorrectly...
Dad? You should go get your hair implants tomorrow.
Mom! My mom...
Go buy the massage chair you've wanted right away!
Gosh, you troublemaker! If you're drunk, go inside and stay quiet!
Gosh, I really need to marry her off if I want to get her out of my sight.
I'm not getting married, Dad.
I'll live in this house forever as a baby.
You have to support me until I'm at least 50!
She needs a taste of slaps before coming to her senses.
- Honey, Honey, Honey, Honey!
- No, no! Why are you doing this?
- Come here!
- Honey, Honey!
You little, come over here!
Why did you give birth to me if you can't take care of me until I'm 60?
You're not a mother! You're not!
Be quiet! Mom, Mom.
- Gosh. Goodness.
- Honey, Honey.
Director! Hello.
Oh, you're here, Na A Jeong?
Yes, I really prepared a lot for today.
I'll work hard so I don't disappoint you.
Oh, okay, sure.
Forget about everything else.
As I mentioned before, just be careful not to have
any personal issues that can become controversial.
Yes, yes, yes. I'll take it to heart that you don't want your drama to cause a stir due to external factors.
That's enough. Go over there and get ready to shoot.
Yes. I'll be back after getting ready.
- Let the others know, too.
- Okay.
All right, we are going to start filming.
Lee Ji Han?
Lee Ji Han? Oh, it is you, Lee Ji Han.
What brings you here?
- Did you come to see me?
- Why would I come to see you?
This is my workplace, LJ Department Store.
If it's not, it's not. Why are you getting mad?
Then, what brings you here, Na A Jeong?
Me? I came to shoot a drama.
Where did my mirror go?
Lee Ji Han, how do I look?
How does my makeup look?
It's not too excessive?
I put some on because the lighting makes my face look flatter.
Does it look okay?
My lips.
W-What are you doing right now?
What would I be doing? I'm asking for your feedback.
Your heart fluttered, right?
- F-Flutter?
- Yeah.
- Who? Me?
- With me.
- Who? With you?
You did!
Nice.
I'll go with this momentum and make everyone fall for me.
Thank you for the coffee.
Take care of whatever business you have to handle here.
Goodness, my heart didn't flutter! Hey! I seriously didn't!
Gosh, that woman...
Wait! What were you looking at smiling like that?
When did I smile?
Just now.
You were smiling like this.
Isn't that Na A Jeong?
Really? Who cares.
Let's get going.
Maybe it's because it's the first shoot. Everyone seems to be so energetic.
The actors are full of spirit.
Especially that female lead's friend.
She is that actress, right? The one who got in through nepotism.
She has no idea the director, broadcasting company, and production company suffered because of her.
You saw how she went around all happy, right?
I guess you need to be that shameless to overturn a finished casting and join a drama.
I feel sorry for the original actress who suddenly got replaced.
She was a rookie actress who got the role after several auditions.
The director really liked her.
I know.
Hello.
By chance, were you talking about me?
I got in through nepotism?
When?
- Ji Ho, say goodbye!
- Goodbye!
I'll talk to him.
Yes, goodbye. Let's go.
Son, did you tell the teacher you ate the kimchi when you didn't?
Hey, I told you lying is bad.
I told you it's way better to tell the truth and get in trouble.
I'm not the only one who did that.
Si Yeon and Hye Bin also didn't eat it but said they ate it.
They did the same thing yesterday, too, but nobody knew.
Yeah, it's possible nobody knew.
But at least one person knows.
Who?
Yourself.
Even if nobody else knows, you know what you did was wrong.
Na A Jeong, please stand at this tea bar.
Okay.
Just come walking out this way.
If everyone's ready, we'll start shooting.
Ready, camera roll.
All right.
Ready,
action!
Cut, cut.
Na A Jeong, w-what's wrong? What is it?
By chance, could you tell me where Actress Na A Jeong is?
Na A Jeong? Who is that?
The role of the female lead's friend.
Oh, that woman? She went home earlier.
Pardon? Why?
We're also curious why she apologized and left like a different person.
Gosh, it's not like this is a playground for kids.
Daughter, I heard you landed a good role after passing an audition.
I don't actually need a massage chair.
In any case, this is such good news.
Fighting! My daughter, you can do it!
I knew you'd be successful.
I do need my hair. Fighting!
Get in.
I said, get in.
Are you crazy?
Why did you quit suddenly when you were so happy and boasting before?
You said it was a good opportunity.
Will you miss out like this?
I heard somewhere
that there exist three steps between people.
Misunderstandings from not stepping close enough,
and understanding that comes from stepping a bit closer. Exactly three steps.
But do you know what you get when you get closer than those three steps?
- What is it?
- What do you think?
It's sticking your nose where you don't belong.
Why did I suddenly quit?
You dare ask me that right now?
Did you just hit me? Are you crazy?
Do you know why I'm so furious right now?
That you got me a role through nepotism when I didn't ask for it?
No, it's the fact that I want to call the director and beg even now.
The fact that I still want to try my best
pretending I don't know anything, even though I know it's wrong...
That's what pisses me off the most.
Do you how that feels?
Gosh, I shouldn't have gone to the restroom then.
No, even if I did go, if only I hadn't come out then.
If I did, I could have lived in flowery dreamland
mistakenly believing that I had finally caught my break.
But who the hell are you?
Who the hell are you to make me have nasty regrets?
I got it. Let's go to the car.
You can't catch a taxi here.
The reason you're so screwed up
is because you made me hate myself, not you.
You know that?
The logic of life
is that you can't always be happy.
One day, there will come a day when you will fall.
Lee Ji Han, please remember my face when that day comes.
That would mean my prayers were finally answered.
You asked if I would miss out on a good opportunity, right?
I'll seize it, then.
Hey, Do Han.
No, it's nothing big.
I'll do it.
Getting married.
♫  I fly with you  ♫
♫  Azure feelings come blowing  ♫
♫  What do we do?  ♫
♫  A night filled with dreams  ♫
♫  Only you and I  ♫
♫  In all the days and scenes containing you  ♫
♫  Butterflies are flying around  ♫
♫  Butterflies are you and I, yeah  ♫
Stand there and make your choice. Is it me or that woman?
If we get married, I'll just be taken advantage of and abandoned.
- It's not a child, right?
- Take my hand.
Are you sure you won't regret it?
- I'm getting married.
- Hey, what is she saying?
Eloping for love.
That is our concept.
I ended up being a matchmaker.
Who are you guys? A two-man racketeering scammer?
Do you like Ji Han, by chance?
I feel like you were always into Ji Han.
No matter how much I think about it, there's only one answer to taking care of Na A Jeong.
♫  A scent that fills the air  ♫
♫  Over the skyline  ♫