Since it's over, just be honest.
You came to ruin it, didn't you?
I think I can see
the right path for me now.
Attending the meeting
meant I'd accept it.
Accept what?
You and Do-han.
I hope you live happily
with my brother.
You know, they say
that wishing someone happiness
comes from the heart.
And I couldn't feel his sincerity at all,
so it bothered me so much.
It felt like he actually
wanted to say something else.
Why do I feel like
I can get the answer from you?
You're torn.
Then I'll think about
whether I should tell Ji-ae
that you approached her
just to get info about me.
So how's Ji-han doing?
Something bothering you again?
Want to go to the temple? Or the church?
I'm worried about our sales.
It's a mess right now.
By the way,
I don't have any religions now.
Are you serious?
No more confusion.
I only believe in myself now.
Isn't it great?
A life without any concern
about Satan or karma.
2023 LJ GROUP
MODEL EMPLOYEE LEE JI-HAN
Okay, Do-han.
Don't worry. Enjoy your time with A-jung.
You're serious?
No more stress.
I'm going to focus on recovering.
Isn't it great?
A simple life where I no longer
have to be curious about
what she and Do-han are doing.
How do I put it?
He seems like he's finally
at peace after experiencing a huge storm.
No hidden schemes,
and doing well?
What could it be?
Maybe he's finally realized
that he no longer needs
to worry about you.
The chairman accepted you, and
the family meeting's over. It's game over.
He probably wants to stop
wasting his time opposing
and focus on work again.
What?
Oh, wow.
Did you change your car?
Yes, I did.
But why?
You said you had no plans
to change your car yet.
I wanted to start afresh
with a new car and a new heart.
Bye, then.
What kind of new life could it be?
How is he so cool?
A life with debts, for sure.
He's obviously car poor.
That's too expensive for his salary.
Is he going on a date? With that girl?
You're right. It must be her.
You reached your answer
sooner than I thought.
No, it took longer than I thought.
I should've answered right away,
but I had too many thoughts on my mind.
So? What's your answer?
I will
put in my effort.
Effort?
To get everything to find its place.
Including my feelings.
That's vague.
You're keeping me on the hook?
Fine, I'll stay on that hook, then.
A vague reply is
better than a firm rejection.
Just like business.
It's easier to dig in if there's a crack.
Keep making an effort.
I'll do the same.
I hope you live happily
with my brother.
Right.
Let's be happy.
It's nothing special.
He told me to.
He's finally accepting us.
His happiness is my happiness.
So I always want the best for him.
That's normal to me.
Is that so wrong?
Congratulations, A-jung.
You finally stole Do-han from Ji-han.
EPISODE 7
I want to go home.
The family meeting's over,
so you've cleared a big hurdle.
The chairman's helping, so don't worry.
-Mr. Kim.
-Yes?
I've been wondering,
why does Grandpa care so much
about my marriage?
Honestly, I thought he'd oppose A-jung.
But he accepted her,
and he's even helping us now.
I don't understand.
I believe
he wants to atone for what he did.
Opposing the late Ms. Hyun
and your father.
He may look fine,
but his scars haven't healed yet.
I'm not my mom's replacement,
and I can't ever be.
Of course not.
Still, you can give him a chance.
And maybe
to everyone who was hurt by that incident.
What is it?
Gosh, you startled me.
-What?
-Jeez.
Come here.
-Why?
-Come on.
You wanted to have dinner with Grandpa.
Why are we going home?
We supported Na A-jung
so she'd stop Do-han
from getting the company,
but she's helping him.
Do-han and Grandfather
are just getting closer now.
Honey, let's set off a bomb.
A bomb?
We'll reveal a huge scandal.
Boom!
Aren't your teeth cold?
-They are.
-They are?
Excuse me, can I ask you something?
Oh, sure.
I'm looking for this house.
Do you know where it is?
Who are you?
Oh, I'm...
-I'm a reporter for Jekook Daily.
-I see.
I was told the future wife of LJ Group's
third grandson lives nearby.
Have you seen...
That's our house.
-Your house?
-Hey.
The houses all look similar around here.
He was mistaken.
She doesn't live there.
I mean, it's not our house.
Let's go. Come on.
Let's go.
-Hello?
-Yes?
-Can I ask you something?
-What is it?
Hello, I'm a reporter for...
Are you the one marrying
the grandson of LJ Group?
I wanted a comment about your marriage.
Can you open this?
No, we can't.
I don't know what you're talking about.
-We...
-LJ? Don't be ridiculous.
She doesn't live here.
She's right.
-She's mine.
-Yes.
She's not marrying someone from LJ.
She's the mother
of my child.
Anyways, it's not our house.
Check somewhere else.
-Right. I'm sorry.
-Bye.
Honey, he left.
He's looking for A-jung!
-What's going on?
-Hurry.
There are reporters
looking for A-jung around here...
-Be quiet.
-What?
-Go inside.
Is someone looking for me?
-Hey! Go back inside!
-No!
-Go inside!
-Get inside!
-What's going on?
-Hurry!
My foot!
I heard from secretary team that the
chairman's grandson is getting married.
They're trying to stop the press.
I'm sure they made
preparations for that beforehand.
The woman's an ordinary person,
so they prepared fake info on her,
but real info got leaked.
It must be tiring
marrying into that family.
She'll get harassed by reporters.
We're the victims here.
Stock prices fluctuated because of
that grandson, and there was chaos.
This might cause more trouble at work.
Don't you agree?
You're right.
You're not married yet.
Is it okay to live there?
There are more reporters outside now.
I can't stay cooped up in here forever.
If I stay here, you'll keep suffering.
Can you trust that family?
He said, "We want to protect her."
But look at what's happening.
-Take this too.
-What?
I didn't get to make a lot, though.
-Eat it with Do-han.
-What is this?
Come back anytime
if it's uncomfortable there.
Don't make such a fuss, Mom.
The secretary says
he'll make sure things get quiet.
I'll only stay there until then.
-I can't believe this.
-My goodness.
Hey. Get there safely, okay?
-Text me if you're bored.
-Okay.
Mom.
-I'll drive you.
-It's fine.
-It's okay.
-Stop it.
-Be safe.
-Bye.
Bye, Ji-oh.
Hey.
-Do you like me?
-What?
I mean, I want to make things clear.
If you like me,
then say it now.
Well, I...
I didn't prepare anything to say yet.
Right.
Ji-ae.
Ever since this cafe opened
in front of our company,
I've always
-liked...
-I have to hear it
to decide whether to turn you down.
What? Whether or not to turn me down?
So, you do like me?
I can answer you now, right?
I'm not interested in you at all--
There was something in my ear.
If I don't tell you that I like you,
then I won't get turned down, right?
You just started to say you liked me.
No, I was going to say
that I like your coffee.
Your coffee is the best around here.
I like this coffee.
What did he say? Did he say it?
Yes.
-He said he liked...
-Wow.
my coffee.
-What?
-I can't believe it.
I'm not interested in him at all,
but if he asked me out sincerely,
I might've said yes...
Who is he
to make me feel like I was turned down?
Taek.
The chairman keeps asking
how the info was leaked.
This coffee is my only
method for relaxation.
Really?
This coffee is
my sadness right now.
You're suffering a lot
because of Ji-han too.
You call yourselves family?
How could you
go around spilling family matters
to the reporters?
That wasn't us.
We got that article released, but...
But?
But we didn't call that reporter
at the memorial.
Right. And the public has
the right to know the truth.
The truth?
All right. I may not know about the truth,
but I can tell you how I feel.
I have no intention
of giving the company to you two,
so don't even dream about it.
That's how I feel.
Hey.
Hey!
You... Are you crazy?
You did this, didn't you?
-Do what?
-"Do what?"
Look at her playing dumb.
I saw it, Seung-a.
You were smirking in there.
Are you framing us for what you did?
You bitch, how dare you!
What? Can't I do that?
You framed me for drunk driving.
Choi Seung-a!
So you know my name.
Then stop calling me a bitch.
Seung-a.
You're making a big mistake.
If Father finds out--
Yes. If he hears
he fell out of favor with Grandpa,
he'll make a different choice.
I told you, didn't I?
I said there was no need to worry
and that we should
get rid of both of them.
I warned you.
You're the one who didn't get it.
You idiot.
You think it'll be you
who gets the company then?
It will be me. Wait and see.
And keep quiet.
Honey.
What do we do now?
-Are we really done for? Is that it?
-Let go of me!
Say something! Damn it!
I must have underestimated
this marriage.
Marriage is easy.
The fame makes it hard.
Should I just do
-the interview?
-What?
I mean,
I don't get why I have to hide.
People are curious too.
I'll just show them who I am
without being all mysterious.
It's a waste to hide this face.
I keep ending up bothering you with stuff
like this and the family meeting.
Sorry.
It's fine. Stop apologizing.
Besides, your brother helped us out.
It's a relief that Ji-han finally
accepted you.
I'm not sure if he accepted me
or just gave up opposing me.
I'm still not sure
if it's right to stay here.
You're not living here alone.
I can stay at your studio--
No, I can't let you do that.
Just make yourself at home.
What's this, though?
-My mom packed some side dishes.
-Oh, okay.
How are you, Terry?
I'm home.
Is no one here?
NA A-JUNG
NO RESULTS
LJ GRANDSON MARRIAGE
WHO WILL INHERIT LJ?
There's nothing yet.
Lee Ji-han.
After everything you said,
what are you doing?
You accepted her. It's over.
You shouldn't worry about her anymore.
My eyesight is really bad.
And I wasn't wearing my glasses,
so don't worry.
Didn't you get LASEK last year?
So why did you
come into the house so quietly?
Oh, so it's my fault?
I came into my own house too quietly?
I didn't mean that.
I mean, you should've gotten dressed.
Oh, so that's my fault too.
I was naked in my own house.
I mean...
It's my fault. I'm at fault.
I should've told him I was here.
I'm sorry.
No, you're my sister-in-law.
It's my fault for not being careful.
Just yell if you're angry.
You being like that makes me feel uneasy.
Angry? I'm not angry at all.
Of course, I should
keep my sister-in-law safe here.
Hang on.
Since when was she your sister-in-law?
Since now.
Anyway, enjoy a comfortable stay here.
Bye, then.
Hang on,
you're not sharing a room, are you?
He's ridiculous.
Why's he suddenly
calling me his sister-in-law?
Sister-in-law...
Don't you agree?
He's ridiculous.
I can sleep in the living room.
-You're going out?
-I have something to do.
Ji-han.
Thanks for accepting A-jung.
Come on. That's cringey.
Go to bed. See you later.
Don't stay out too late.
You should've gotten dressed.
You should've worked out.
Whether they share a room or not,
you shouldn't have said that!
She might feel uncomfortable
sharing a room with you.
Plus, you're not married yet.
Do you have any sleeping habits?
He has really bad ones. He could hit you.
Darn it.
It's fine.
I can do it.
She is my sister-in-law.
I can live with her
under the same roof!
I'm not opposing you sharing a bed.
It's just strange
to do that in this huge house.
It was a good purchase.
All right.
Once she's out, it's final.
This is Ji-oh's room from now on.
Of course. And you and I
can make a sibling for Ji-oh.
Honey!
-You pervert.
-Hey.
-But honey...
-Yes?
Didn't you move here when
-when A-jung entered college?
-Yes.
How is an elementary textbook here?
A-jung's like that.
Look. She still has all the scripts
from her past roles,
even when she barely had any lines.
These look like her contracts.
Jeez. Couldn't she have organized them?
I always have to clean up after her.
"Employment contract."
And...
What? "Marriage contract"?
"Lee Do-han and Na A-jung."
"Three-year-contract."
"Client and actress"?
Who are you?
Where's Na A-jung?
Did Do-han leave first?
Rolled omelet?
I love rolled omelet.
That looks amazing.
It's yours, sister-in-law.
I heard you always have breakfast.
This way, please.
You didn't have to.
Why is there only one bowl?
I don't eat breakfast, sister-in-law.
Still, I feel sorry eating by myself
in your house.
"Sorry"?
I should do this much
for my sister-in-law.
Why do you keep calling me sister-in-law?
Dear brother-in-law?
Because you're my sister-in-law.
Enjoy your meal.
Well, then.
Hey, just eat with me!
Hey, brother-in-law!
Great.
I made her breakfast, and I was polite.
I was a good brother-in-law.
Brother-in-law.
I'll do it.
No, I'll do it. Go and rest.
No, let me do it. It's fine.
No, really.
I'm sorry.
It was refreshing.
It's fine.
Excuse me.
How do I do the laundry?
Oh, and do you have a dryer?
Listen. I'll do it.
Please just go and rest.
Being a good brother-in-law is tough.
Please just sit still
so I don't have to see you.
Why would he try to act
in front of an actress?
Accepting me?
Calling me "sister-in-law"
when he doesn't even mean it.
With this, it's 1,000.
You folded these yourself, right?
You do this
when you make a wish.
You've acted weird since that day.
Don't play dumb.
It was about me, right?
Tell me what the wish was.
You don't need to know.
You were lying when you told me
to be happy with Do-han, right?
Tell me. What wish did you make?
Did you wish for me to leave Do-han?
No.
The opposite.
For myself to leave you alone.
I really meant
what I said that day.
And when I accepted you
as my sister-in-law, I felt so at ease.
The time I spent opposing you
felt like a waste.
But why are you saying that
as if you're pushing me away, Ji-han?
No matter what,
it means this is my place.
So, let's keep our places as in-laws.
Barging into my room
and digging through my trash.
You're crossing the line, aren't you?
Yes, I met him.
He knew you.
He knew you changed your lock too.
And that we're getting married.
He's your ex,
isn't he?
It was nice meeting you.
See you next time.
No wonder. His tone was weird.
But how did he know we're getting married?
And how did he know it was me?
A-jung, I might be late today.
Don't wait for me and just rest.
What is it?
Is it broken again?
You met A-jung.
Well...
I did.
By coincidence.
Coincidence?
Yes, by coincidence.
How odd.
There are a lot of coincidences around me.
Someone keeps
secretly taking photos of me,
and the power keeps shutting down
in my studio.
The person I'm marrying
coincidentally meets someone I know?
Don't you dare touch A-jung.
That's crossing the line.
You're upset.
As if you actually like her.
What you said about hurting me,
is this what you meant? Revenge?
By threatening me?
Do-han.
You're the one crossing the line.
Don't you feel sorry toward me at all?
I don't.
No, I used to,
but you got rid of that just now.
So stop this now.
Stay out of my life.
Lee Do-han barely has
any connection to that man.
They only have one or two
mutual acquaintances.
Then there's nothing between them.
Oh, you seem to be clueless.
Such relationships are more interesting.
A conflict when they have no connection?
That means there's something going on.
What I want to know is what's going on
between Do-han, A-jung,
and Ji-han. Those three.
So wouldn't I get irritated
if you suddenly
bring up someone unrelated?
No, this means he's connected
in some way too.
Who knows?
He might be related to Na A-jung as well.
Then contact me when you find something.
Hang on.
Then
what would I get?
It might be a useful card for you,
but for me, releasing this
won't even have much of an impact.
I get what's in it for you,
but I don't get what's in it for me.
Just tell me what you want.
I hate beating around the bush.
Your mother's accident.
I want to stop being blamed.
Then it'll be a win-win situation.
Mr. Kang.
You know that sitting here with you
and drinking tea
doesn't mean I like you, right?
Even though she abandoned her family,
she was still my mother.
And you caused
the accident that killed her.
I haven't forgotten it.
That's why
I need to clear my name.
Aren't you curious
what truth will be revealed
once I do?
What's on your mind?
What?
It's nothing.
We should've gone to an aquarium
to celebrate me being on your hook.
I can show you my fish friends.
I'm getting introduced
to a lot of friends.
Fish friends, bird friends...
Bird friends?
Yes,
a thousand birds stuck in my house.
They're a huge pain in the neck,
making me
unable to do anything.
So how long is Ms. Na staying there?
I don't know.
Forever, I guess.
What?
They'll live together
once they get married.
They'll nest
in my house.
That's awful.
You should find your place.
Wouldn't it be uncomfortable
being with newlyweds?
It'll be better for you to come to me.
Don't worry.
I'm trying my best right now.
-Ji-ae.
-Oh, my!
It's me, let's go inside.
Ji-ae.
Do you
know that guy?
He's not, right?
Did he follow me here?
He's a regular.
Is he?
Darn it. This is so exhausting.
You should rethink about getting famous.
This is a huge pain.
It's not easy.
She thinks she's some celebrity now.
So how is it
living in your future husband's house?
Is his brother still bullying you?
No, he's not.
Wow, I guess he really did accept her.
He's finally on her side now.
But why do I feel more uneasy?
I preferred it when he just opposed me.
I understand.
You defeated him,
so you'd feel sorry for the loser.
Well, right.
But whenever he calls me "sister-in-law,"
I feel something heavy
in my chest.
It should be the opposite.
You should feel much lighter.
There's no one opposing you now.
All you have to do
is focus on your wedding.
Right, you're worrying for no reason.
Everything's going well. Why would you?
Right.
You think so?
Are you free after work today?
Why do you ask?
Go on.
Are you trying to start
that productive life project again?
No, it's not that.
How about some drinks?
That sounds great.
Drinks?
Is something wrong?
No, it's not that.
I just want to go home late.
I'll see you later.
-Honey, wait!
-Let go.
I have to tell her this is wrong.
But still...
Does she think marriage is a joke?
-I'm going to kill her.
-Honey.
-But...
-Na A-jung!
Honey, lower your voice...
The neighbors will hear you!
Su-jung? Tae-min?
A-jung! Run! I'll hold her back.
-Are you crazy?
-What's wrong?
-You lunatic.
-What is it?
-Have you lost your mind?
-What?
-Hey!
-What's with you?
What's with me? Seriously?
Here.
What is this?
A marriage contract?
I knew you were a fraud
ever since you pretended to be Mom
when your school called home.
A fake marriage? That's crazy!
-It's just acting.
-Hey!
Getting married as an act?
Do you want to go to jail as an act too?
Honey, let's hear her out.
I'm sure she had plans...
when she signed it.
It's my first lead role.
What?
I mean,
my career wasn't getting anywhere,
and my dream seemed impossible to achieve.
And just as I felt that,
Do-han begged me so desperately.
Of course, I refused at first.
But once we talked,
the payment wasn't bad,
and it seemed like an okay job.
But I'm not sure anymore.
I thought I'd just be acting
in everyday life,
but I keep having to lie.
I thought it'd be a great role,
but I'm becoming a nuisance.
That's how I feel.
How could you say that right now?
Didn't you even think that through?
Hey. Did you think everything through
before getting pregnant with Tae-min
when you weren't married?
But what can I do?
I made my choice.
I have to stick with it until the end.
You idiot.
Do you have any idea
what'll happen at the end?
Su-jung!
You can't just leave like that. Come on.
Don't worry, I'll talk to her.
I support you, A-jung.
Knives rust if you don't use them,
and your body stiffens if you don't move.
Acting is the same.
You can use this chance
to keep acting.
You're doing great.
I support you.
Fine, keep going with it.
It's your life.
Then keep my secret.
But don't get caught by anyone.
Especially Mom and Dad.
They already bragged about it
to our aunts who looked down on you.
They were so happy
you were getting married.
They'll feel hurt even if you break it up.
So get divorced quietly after three years.
Do you get what I mean?
Yes, Su-jung.
I'm sorry.
This is so annoying.
That bigmouth would've had a hard time
keeping this all to herself.
By the way,
with that much money,
you could get Father's head
to be as hairy as Bigfoot.
Bigfoot!
Hurry up!
Okay.
A-jung.
Drink up.
One more glass.
I had a lot to say to you,
but first,
let me tell you about a dream I had once.
It's still vivid in my mind.
In my dream, I grew a peach tree
in my front yard.
And the big, pretty peaches
suddenly
began to fall.
Was it before you had A-jung?
This is where she appears.
A huge dog suddenly ran in
and ate all those peaches.
It was terrifying.
And ten months later, A-jung was born.
Maybe because of that dream,
she was gluttonous and greedy.
She lunged at everyone
whenever she was upset, like a mad dog.
She was my child,
but it was so tough raising her.
It must've been tough.
I was happy
raising her.
Sometimes, I wondered
if she was literally sucking me dry,
and I got angry
when she wouldn't listen to me.
But strangely, I still felt
proud of her and grateful toward her.
I just want to ask you one single favor.
Of course, Father.
Don't
make her walk on eggshells.
Let her do what she wants
and express her feelings when she's upset.
That's how I raised her.
I will, Father.
Don't worry. I'll take care of her.
-Let's drink.
-Sure.
You know,
today's actually the first time
you've asked me to have a drink with you.
Congratulations.
You've seen a new side of me.
That's right.
By the way, why don't you want to go home?
My brother and A-jung
are nesting in my house.
I can relate to
the story of Hong Gil-dong now.
I don't want to call them at all.
That's different.
Hong Gil-dong didn't really have a choice.
Is that important?
The point is that I'm making an effort.
And with time, I'll get used to it,
then I'll feel more at ease, right?
That's a great way of thinking.
I've heard the expression,
"Fake it till you make it."
That's what people say.
That sounds nice.
I'm great at faking things.
Cheers.
My gosh.
-Hello.
-Hi.
How much did he drink?
Three glasses of soju.
-Three?
-Yes.
That's too much!
Tae-min, carry him. Come on.
Oh, my gosh.
He's wasted.
Jeez.
Is there something you want to tell me?
Keep in mind that I'm watching you.
Me too.
What are you two saying?
Stop the nonsense and go inside.
-Thanks.
-No problem.
Hurry home before A-jung worries.
Get home safely.
We're watching you.
What?
Hey, A-jung.
What are you doing out in the cold?
You called me
and said you had something to tell me.
Oh, right. I did.
Sorry.
You're drunk.
Go to bed. We can talk tomorrow.
No, I'll say it now. I want to say it now.
A-jung.
I know this will sound selfish,
but I'm so happy right now.
For the first time, I don't feel anxious,
thanks to you.
So I'll make you feel the same.
I'll be a really great husband.
I'll let you do anything you want,
and I'll take care of everything for you.
Okay?
Go to bed.
Why?
I want to sit here a little longer.
Okay, I'll head inside first.
Don't stay out too long.
But don't get caught by anyone.
Especially Mom and Dad.
They were so happy
you were getting married.
They'll feel hurt even if you break it up.
So get divorced quietly after three years.
I know this will sound selfish,
but I'm so happy right now.
For the first time, I don't feel anxious,
thanks to you.
Don't worry.
Just trust your decision.
I think you made the right choice, A-jung.
You're not calling me "sister-in-law" now?
No.
Well, whatever I call you,
you'll be my sister-in-law.
That's good.
At least you're consistent.
But how are you so sure
when you don't know
what I was thinking?
I just don't want you
to be wavered about your decision.
It's the first time
hearing Do-han say he's not anxious.
But you'll be anxious instead.
I've thought about
everything that made me uneasy
about this marriage.
I can ignore everything except one thing.
I keep feeling uneasy about you.
I don't know why,
but I do.
I'm wavering.
So I want to ask you this
for the last time.
Are you really okay
with me marrying Do-han?
You really don't mind
if we become in-laws?
Yes.
I'll trust
my choice too.
Right.
If I keep faking it, I'll make it someday.
Your wish won't come true without this.
Keep it and fulfill your wish.
I guess you were right.
I'm so jealous of A-jung.
What?
This is why lottery tickets
don't matter much.
Even without it,
A-jung won the lottery
with a husband from a rich family.
Don't be ridiculous.
You have to win the lottery
with your own hands to enjoy it.
There's no fun in winning it
through someone else.
Why? I'd love that.
I'm sure A-jung's jealous of us right now.
What?
A-jung did all those part-time jobs
so she could keep acting.
She doesn't have to worry about money,
but she's told to stop working.
Would she feel happy?
Of course.
Don't you know the FIRE movement?
Young people these days
want to retire early.
You always go on about "young people"
when you're in a tight spot.
And if she really feels uncomfortable,
would she go for a wedding dress fitting?
Wow, it's prettier than I thought.
It's so hard to choose.
Let's just pick anything.
We can't do that. It's your wedding dress.
Hey, I used to wear a wedding dress
every weekend.
And I had dozens of grooms.
Let's get this over with.
We can take our time choosing.
You're the lead at this wedding.
I've thought about
everything that made me uneasy
about this marriage.
I can ignore everything except one thing.
I keep feeling uneasy about you.
Get a grip, A-jung.
Are you really okay
with me marrying Do-han?
You really don't mind
if we become in-laws?
What? Ji-han.
Come with me.
EPILOGUE
I won't send you back to Do-han.
I don't know what happened,
but I'll just trust A-jung and let it go.
What's the point of telling the truth now?
Do you really like Do-han?
You should stop popping up
here and there and meddling in my life.
Aren't you ashamed of living like that?
Would that be really protecting me?
It'd be locking myself up.
Because I like you, A-jung.
So I can't do it anymore.
Translated by Juyoung Park