(Flourished Peony)
(Episode 19)
I've never seen a play that uses flowers
to depict Zhu Rong striking stones to create fire.
Miss Mu Dan,
this is such an excellent idea.
You flatter me.
The flower in the middle must be the Moutan peony.
It does look like a raging fire. It's very captivating.
Moutan peony is extremely delicate.
One must devote a lot of effort to it.
I've written down the instructions.
San, she's reminding you to pay up.
- That's not true. - I almost forgot about it.
I won't stand on ceremony, then.
Chuan Yu.
Thank you.
Your spouse's birthday is nearing.
This is the perfect time to give her this as a gift.
All women love flowers after all.
Shopkeeper, I want one pot as well.
I want the one with the crimson hue.
The top courtesan of Huanyun Pavilion will surely be happy to have this.
I want two pots so that my spouses won't get jealous.
Unfortunately,
Lord Jiang has bought the last batch.
Miss Mu Dan, you're so biased.
This variety is very popular. Why does he get to choose first?
Lord Jiang frequents our shop.
Naturally, we have to prioritize our regulars.
Please visit Blooming Abode when you're free.
We have plenty of rare varieties there.
No matter if you buy them as gifts for your mother, wife, or mistress,
they'll definitely be happy with them.
If so, do you still sell this variety there?
What she meant was,
if you guys visit her shop and become regulars,
you guys get to buy all kinds of varieties.
I've already divided and preserved the Moutan peony's seedlings beforehand.
They'll bloom in the coming spring.
If anyone desires them,
please reserve them in advance.
All right! I'll head to your shop tomorrow.
All right.
Seems like you do frequent her shop.
You even understood
what she was implying.
It's the same thing when it comes to making money, you know?
I saw what you did just now.
It's not like the dance started a real fire.
Why were you avoiding it?
That flower of yours has a strong scent.
If it's too near, I won't be able to savor the liquor.
No wonder you were egging me on.
You hired a performing troupe and set up a banquet.
You did everything to promote your flowers.
You mustn't put it that way.
Lord Jiang, you get a share of the profit from the flowers I sell.
This is a win-win situation.
But you filled up my courtyard with your flowers without telling me.
How could you force me to do this deal?
Lord Jiang, you said this yourself.
The flowers in Jiang Residence will be supplied by Blooming Abode.
Back then, with a grand gesture, you spent money like water.
It was charming and elegant.
That was an unforgettable sight.
No thanks. My hand is injured. I cannot take alcohol.
Come and take a look!
I want two pots of this.
It smells great.
I want a bottle of that.
- I want a bottle too. - Let's check out the flowers.
Over here.
Are all of these fragrant powders?
I want ten sets of this.
All right.
Xiao Chun, I misunderstood you.
Sorry about that.
Please forgive me.
But the deed was done by someone from the flower trade indeed.
Da Fu, I don't blame you at all.
I'm sure you've swallowed a lot of grievances.
What about this? You should punch me twice.
Da Fu, it's fine.
It's fine. Just vent it out. It'll be fine after that.
What about this? Stab me with your needles.
I'd rather punch you instead.
Sure.
You're forgiven.
Is that all?
All right! You're straightforward as well.
From now on, we're a family.
Anyone who tries to bully you will have to get through me first!
Luckily, she only said that she wanted you to punch her.
I was afraid she might stab herself with a knife.
I won't do that.
Mu Dan, speaking of cut wounds,
a patient of mine got his leg cut.
I've tried several dressings on him.
However, his wound kept festering without getting better.
I've written down all of the symptoms.
Mu Dan, can you help me pass it to Physician Fu?
(To Physician Fu)
No problem.
Take care.
Shopkeeper, how much is this?
Xiao Chun!
Please give me a moment.
This is a fragrant powder I specially crafted for you.
It has an elegant scent.
It suits you perfectly.
I hope you can forgive me for what I said before.
It's fine. It's all in the past now.
Moreover, I don't use fragrant powder often.
It'll affect my diagnosis if I put on fragrant powder.
Therefore, you can keep it with you first.
Two of my patients are still waiting for me. Farewell.
She shouldn't just refuse my good intentions like this.
She's pretty dense. She can't take a hint at all.
Don't hold it against her.
This is the hand cream from Youshi Hall.
You have to manage the shop and tend to the plants every day.
I'm sure it's tough.
This cream can moisturize your hands.
You're being overly attentive without any reason.
What are you doing here out of the blue?
I reflected deeply on my actions after you reprimanded me last time.
I spent a lot of time on it.
I did treat you badly in the past.
Now, I've quit drinking. I'm no longer the scoundrel I was.
I'm here to ask you this.
Wu Niang, have you found someone you fancy?
What has that got to do with you?
Do you still remember the blind old lady who lived behind our tavern?
- When she was young... - Excuse me.
She also did business when she was young.
She showed her face in public and was despised by people.
She never got married.
She had no children, and she was lonely all her life.
She passed away last month, and there was no one to see her off.
Why did you mention her all of a sudden?
Because she reminded me of you.
I don't want you to end up like her.
Wu Niang, can you please give me another chance?
We once had good days as well...
Back then, you stirred up trouble for no reason.
You almost caused us to lose our business.
Now, our shop is operating well.
You came here to tell me this when I'm leading a good life?
Do you think I'll believe you?
That's because Mu Dan took you away from me.
I only did so out of spite.
I suppose I was abrupt today.
It's just that I've been missing you ever since you left me.
Wu Niang,
have you never thought of me even once all this while?
Have you never felt lonely even for a moment?
This is the lily essence. It has a fragrant smell.
It costs 240 coins.
Come. Great timing.
All right.
Where's Sheng Yi?
She went out.
Here you go. Take care.
Now that you're leading a good life,
I can rest at ease.
If you follow me, you have to suffer again.
Did you owe gambling debts again?
No.
I've already repaid all of my previous debt.
I didn't come to you because of money.
I just miss you.
In the future, I'll treat you well.
Is that Sheng Yi's ex-husband?
You shouldn't waste your money on such items in the future.
- As for other things... - You scoundrel!
How dare you come and ask Sheng Yi for money?
Da Fu! He's not here to ask me for money!
He's here to deliver a present to me.
This doesn't cost much.
You're the second shopkeeper of Blooming Abode!
You can buy whatever you want yourself!
Why would you need him to buy it?
He's trying to trick you with these trinkets.
I'm sincere in rekindling our old flame.
Stop lying! The legends say
that the words of a heartless lover can never be trusted!
Today, I shall uphold justice!
I'll beat you up!
You can beat me up if that'll prove my sincerity!
Just look. He'll surely avoid my punch.
Are you hurt?
It's fine even if I'm hurt.
Wu Niang, it's fine as long as you're fine.
Excellent!
I don't understand at all.
How did that scoundrel manage to bewitch Sheng Yi?
A person like Wang Qing should be taught a lesson.
There's no need to waste your breath on him.
Did you beat Wang Qing up because he offended you?
I don't know him.
I did so because I didn't want Sheng Yi to be deceived.
So, you beat up Wang Qing for the sake of Sheng Yi.
But in the end, you hurt her by accident, huh?
If so, what should you tell Sheng Yi?
Sheng Yi,
I was too impulsive today.
I'm sorry.
What else should you say
besides that?
You should say
that you'll teach Wang Qing another lesson if you see him again.
People like him need to be taught a lesson every time we see them!
That's right! That's what I thought as well!
I know you guys are worried about me.
But Da Fu, you don't understand the intricacies of a relationship.
This time, Wang Qing isn't here to stir up trouble.
He's only here to care for me.
Maybe he has realized the error of his ways.
Wang Qing has committed a lot of evil deeds.
Can a person like him truly be able to turn over a new leaf?
I know that Wang Qing isn't a good person.
But we show ourselves in public often.
No good men are willing to marry women like us.
Now, we're still young. We still have the privilege to choose our mate.
But once we grow old,
and when we're no longer able to operate our business,
won't that make us old and lonely?
How could that be?
You still have us, you know?
That's right.
My mother raised me by herself as well.
We still led a good life without a man in the family.
But how could you exist without men?
How could your mother give birth to you if she was alone from the start?
To you guys,
is it enough to make a fortune
with our business
without getting a husband and children?
Sheng Yi,
people change.
If other people provide you with happiness,
they can take it away as well.
The only thing that'll last is the thing that you strive for yourself.
Excellent!
Some like to drink mutton soup by itself.
But I don't think it's good enough
without a flatbread.
Maybe I'm too greedy.
I want to lead a good life
and get a husband
and children.
You're not greedy.
There's nothing wrong about desiring them.
It's reasonable.
It's not that I'm stopping you from getting married.
However, it mustn't be Wang Qing.
Did you forget how he treated you in the past?
You've only escaped from this hellhole not long ago.
Sheng Yi, you must think twice.
Now, you're the second shopkeeper of Blooming Abode.
You're beautiful and wealthy.
You'll definitely be able to get a good husband.
Compared to getting married,
it's more important to find a mate
who understands you well.
Shopkeeper, get us two flatbreads.
Coming, miss.
Thank you.
Please enjoy your meal.
Excellent!
Your Highness, I heard that you were coming.
I made these snacks myself.
I made them with top-quality ingredients.
Your Highness, please try them.
I've also prepared a gift for my visit.
This is purple bamboo shoot tea from Mt. Guzhu, Huzhou.
It's known as the celestial nectar of the imperial garden.
Her Highness and Lord Xu will get married soon.
Esteemed guests will visit your residence eventually.
Only this tea is worthy of serving to match the status of the Liu family.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Time is essential when it comes to the purple bamboo shoot tea.
It'll only retain its fragrance if you consume it within two months.
It won't taste as good after that.
Your Highness, you have a point.
Such fine tea should not be stored for long.
Master and I have hired someone to come up with the best date.
The sixth day of the upcoming month
is a rare auspicious day.
It's suitable for marriage.
Mother,
many personnel of the Ministry of Revenue have applied for leave lately.
I'm busy with work.
Let's put it aside for now.
State affairs aren't as important as our wedding.
Since it's important, we have to prepare for it meticulously.
We mustn't rush things.
Now, I finally have something substantial to do at the Ministry of Revenue.
Why don't we hold our wedding later?
We can discuss the wedding date later.
The flowers in the garden are blooming.
Zi Shu, why don't you admire them together with Her Highness?
All right now. Stop being angry.
I'll heed your will.
We can get married after you're done with work.
Thank you.
Besides that, you have to thank me for one more thing.
Do you know why the officials of the Ministry of Revenue applied for leave?
They disrespected you.
Therefore, I sent my men there to teach them a lesson.
After this incident,
they'll surely reflect upon their actions.
They won't show you the cold shoulder again.
Why did you act on your own initiative
without asking for my opinion?
You were the one who told me that you had nothing to do.
I merely wanted to give you a surprise.
Now, they're gone. Isn't that what you want?
I did so for your own good.
Why aren't you appreciating my intention? Why are you angry at me instead?
Qiu Shi!
Your Highness, His Lordship granted them this dog.
Master was grateful to His Lordship's grace.
He has spoiled it utterly.
That's why it was allowed to roam free in the residence.
But it scared you.
Your Highness, please forgive it.
So, Father granted the dog to them, huh?
Bring it here. Let me take a look.
Come.
A dog does rely on its master indeed.
Since this dog was granted by King Ning,
it's fine even if it offends Your Highness.
If this dog belonged to someone else,
I suppose it would've been beaten to death by now.
What's wrong with you today?
You just have to pick a fight with me, huh?
I just feel that I'm no different from a dog.
My value
depends on my master.
Zi Shu, you're belittling yourself by saying so.
You're also looking down on Father's effort in nurturing you.
I know.
You're upset that I'm urging us to get married.
But how long do I have to wait?
I've done so much for you. I never expected you to be moved by my actions.
But at least you shouldn't say such hurtful words.
Could it be that you still have feelings for Lady He?
Impossible.
She's just a commoner.
What's there to miss about her?
Moreover, she's already dead.
Do you truly think that I don't know how she died?
Didn't she die after falling off a cliff?
Since you want to be married to me,
she has no choice but to die.
Although you didn't do it yourself,
she died because of your desire.
She slipped and fell off the cliff. What has that got to do with me?
Zi Shu, you're arguing with me because of a woman.
You were the one who promised me that you would marry me.
Now, you're blaming me for it.
I'm not blaming you. I'm blaming myself.
I blame myself for being inept.
I can't hold onto anything at all.
You influence all of my emotions.
You're the only person who can hold onto me.
Why are you pushing me away time and time again?
You Zhen, how could you still not understand?
It's not that I don't appreciate the things you've done for me.
It's just that your actions are suffocating me.
Everyone fears me and stays away from me because of what you did.
I won't have any peers or friends in the future.
You don't need anyone else. I'm the only person you need.
Zi Shu, don't you understand?
Without me, there was no way you could join the Ministry of Revenue.
You just need to cherish me and love me.
If so, Father will give you all the positions you desire.
Are you saying that my career is built upon a woman?
How could you say something like that?
By being my husband, you won't need to get involved in political trifles.
What's so bad about that?
Pleasing me
is much easier than doing tedious paperwork.
This is a blessing that others seek but cannot obtain.
Why are you avoiding it as if it's the plague?
So, to you, my dreams and aspirations are cheap, huh?
They're insignificant to you, huh?
Blessing?
Do you expect me to kneel and thank you for that?
Mu Dan never saw me in this light
when she was still in the Liu Residence.
However, I didn't know how to cherish her.
I knew you still couldn't get over He Wei Fang.
Do you think she's better than me?
- She's just a wretch... - She's innocent!
You shouldn't insult her like that.
Innocent?
Back then, in Shuiyu Pavilion, Luoyang,
she was the one who requested me to stage an act with her
so that we could use the momentum to be engaged.
He Wei Fang wanted to divorce you long ago.
She even resorted to such a plot.
Do you still think that she's innocent?
Impossible.
He Wei Fang isn't someone like that.
Both of you are women.
Why would she sacrifice your reputation in order to get her way?
That's right.
As a woman,
I'm willing to cast away my reputation in order to be with you.
But when you heard that, the only thing you were thinking
was that He Wei Fang wasn't someone like that.
What about me?
How could Father agree to our marriage
if I didn't do so?
Zi Shu,
for your sake, I'm willing to join hands with that wretch.
I even plotted against my own father.
Do you still not understand my feelings for you?
You must've lost your mind.
So, you deceived me from the start.
You stood idly by as people looked at me as if I was a circus clown.
I was called an adulterer because of you.
I felt guilty to you because of that.
Due to the scandal, my family couldn't reject the marriage.
And now, you want me to pretend to be ignorant
and proceed with our marriage?
What do you mean by that?
Liu Zi Shu,
I've already swallowed a lot of grievances for your sake.
Now, you're pushing me away?
I'm the county princess, yet I'm willing to coax you and please you.
Do you truly think I don't have a temper?
I was the one who went out of my league.
Your Highness,
there are already plenty of unhappy couples in the world.
There's no need to add one more pair to the count.
Excellent!
Miss Yun is truly a great businesswoman.
She organized the selection for the top courtesan
with such great excitement.
Your trip wasn't in vain, huh?
Yeah.
Today, only VIPs may enter Huanyun Pavilion.
Lord Jiang, thank you for taking me here.
There's no need to thank me.
I'm willing to take you here
because you said you wanted to learn her business strategies.
As long as you apply what you've learned and make more money for me,
I'll be happy about it.
Lord Jiang, don't worry.
I've already committed this strategy to my memory.
I'll definitely apply it to our shop in the future.
Huanyun Pavilion started today's event
with a grand and dramatic performance.
And, they even distributed different masks to the guests.
This is interesting indeed.
My Lord,
that's not our liquor.
Change the drinking set.
Yes, My Lord.
What's wrong?
I'm afraid the waiter served us with the wrong set.
Or,
someone might have placed this on my table amidst the commotion.
Even so, you don't need to pour it away.
It's such a waste.
We have to be wary.
Miss He, you might not know,
but people have tried to poison Lord Jiang more than once.
A few years ago, he fell for their trick.
He even threw up blood.
It was that serious?
I'm notorious after all. I have to be extra careful.
When we were in Luoyang,
you encountered assassins.
Even so, you acted nonchalantly, just like how you're acting now.
It's as if you're already used to being in danger.
If one encounters the same situation time and time again,
everyone will get used to it.
Lord Jiang, seems like it's tough
being a corrupt official as well.
You don't need to worry about me.
Excellent!
Today is a rare event.
Why don't we enjoy ourselves?
Excellent!
All right.
Zi Shu, don't you understand?
Without me, there was no way you could join the Ministry of Revenue.
You just need to cherish me and love me.
If so, Father will give you all the positions you desire.
Pleasing me
is much easier than doing tedious paperwork.
This is a blessing that others seek but cannot obtain.
Why are you avoiding it as if it's the plague?
The slanderers boast loudly,
while the virtuous remain nameless.
Alas, in silence,
who knows of my integrity and steadfastness?
Liu Zi Shu, just look at you right now.
Lonely and standing alone, my shadow and I keep each other company.
Drinking alone beneath the moon.
What a tragic sight.
What a tragic sight!
Mister,
are you okay?
I'll retrieve it for you.
Thank you.
To address the flood issue, start with the people's livelihood.
The homes and farmlands of the common people should be the top priority.
There are even ideas of building fields by enclosing water
and controlling water to combat sand.
This is a long-term solution
for the flood issues the state is facing.
This is an excellent approach to water management.
I suppose he has devoted a lot of effort to it.
Every day, officials send over flattering articles and poems.
His Lordship ordered us to burn them periodically to make space.
Mister, here's your policy proposal.
Thank you.
In the vast world with high mountains and flowing rivers,
a bosom friend is hard to find.
Are you okay?
Mu Dan?
Mu Dan.
- Mu Dan. - Liu Chang?
You are the wife I wish to honor, cherish, and love!
What nonsense are you spouting?
Mu Dan,
I've already found out about the act
you staged together with Her Highness.
So?
The Liu family and I had let you down in the past.
I don't blame you for what you did.
Now, can you please give me another chance?
Let's rekindle our old flame.
I'll definitely...
I didn't know that you were behind the mask.
Secondly, there was no old flame between you and I.
Fine.
Fine. Let's drop the past, then.
Let's not bring it up.
At this moment...
At this moment, this should be considered our first encounter.
You and I are getting to know each other for the first time again.
I've already requested Her Highness to cancel our engagement.
I'm willing to give up on my title and fame for you.
Okay?
Liu Chang,
I suggest you hire a physician to check your brain
before it's too late.
So, do you look down on me just like the others?
That's right.
I'm just a pitiful dog that follows King Ning and Her Highness.
Why would anyone respect a dog?
But even dogs can bark and bare their teeth.
Why must I restrain myself?
When have you ever restrained yourself in front of me?
Don't you think you're the one who landed yourself in this plight?
You pestered me time and time again
not because you had feelings for me.
You just wish to derive a sense of existence from me
so that you won't feel as terrible.
You want to make your family honorable and have a great career,
but you can't let go of your prideful self.
You complain about your plight endlessly,
pushing all the blame
to your parents and your surroundings.
But what about you?
You've never changed at all.
You kept feeling that everyone was looking down on you.
To me,
you're the person who looks down on you the most.
You don't even know what you're seeking.
No.
That's not true.
Even if I do desire something else,
the honor of the Liu family
falls upon my shoulders.
How could I cast that away?
If you wish to be aloof and prideful, then follow the path of poverty.
If you decide to submit,
then you must bear the shame of kneeling.
But you insist on seeking both.
In the end,
it'll only lead to mutual sabotage.
It'll ruin you.
Liu Chang,
first, become a person.
After that, you can bear the burden of your surname.
First, become a person?
Become a person, huh?
Is it fun to eavesdrop on us?
You could recognize me even with this disguise?
It's hard not to recognize you when you're sticking out like a sore thumb.
Moreover, I can see your cunning eyes behind the mask.
Did you forget who brought you here?
I was wrong.
I mean, behind the mask,
I can tell how knowledgeable,
talented,
wise,
virtuous,
- cool... - Seems like I'll never get
to hear something truthful from you in this lifetime.
It's cold outside at night.
You shouldn't be too engrossed in your conversation with your old flame.
Did you come out and eavesdrop on us just so you could help me put this on?
And, the hour of Hai has already passed.
We cannot leave the building.
I'm afraid you have to spend the night here.
It's the second watch already?
There's only one room left.
Due to the top courtesan selection, we have plenty of guests tonight.
There's no extra guest room.
This is the only room left.
And, it's meant for Lord Jiang when he wishes to take a break here.
Lord Jiang is very resourceful.
He's not confined to the curfew.
Even if he leaves the building and heads home now,
no one will dare to stop him.
Why don't you let me have the room?
What if I insist on being a law-abiding citizen tonight?
What will you do, then?
Since that's the case,
I suppose there's only one way left.
No wonder the business of Huanyun Pavilion is always good.
The bed is so comfortable.
Actually, tonight,
I've been wanting to find an opportunity
to have a good chat with you.