[A Dream Within A Dream]
[Episode 24]
♪ The mortal world entangles,
so much sorrow and chill in the mist ♪
♪ Our fates intertwine and weave
into a story ♪
♪ Listening to the wind whispering
by my ear ♪
♪ The schemes of the dark night ♪
♪ Eyes guarding a single sunrise ♪
It really is you,
♪ When will there be a way home? ♪
Nan Heng.
♪ Time brings life and death, binding life
but not the heart ♪
♪ Stepping into the ranks of fate,
each pain a prelude ♪
♪ Transformed in a fleeting moment,
like a dream, elusive and near ♪
I can explain it. I...
♪ How can love and hate be hidden? ♪
♪ Time brings life and death, binding life
but not the heart ♪
Fine.
Explain it then.
♪ Making all moves in life cautiously,
joy and sorrow already destined ♪
Go ahead.
I'll hear you out.
♪ If one dares oppose Heaven,
how can the ending be rewritten? ♪
♪ So close yet still, we part ways ♪
You can barely say a word.
What explanation can you give me?
I'm sorry.
I...
Song Yimeng!
You approached me with a purpose.
You used me.
You watched me act silly
as you played me like a fool.
Are you satisfied now?
I really am a fool.
I thought I was the reason
for all your suffering.
I was constantly worried
that Nan Heng would hurt you.
I was worried about you the entire time.
But meanwhile,
what did you do?
You never stopped lying to me.
You never stopped using me.
No.
Please hear me out.
Stop it.
Don't bother telling me anything.
Nan Heng,
you had so many chances
to tell me the truth,
but you seized none of them.
Not even one.
It wasn't like that.
I didn't mean to lie to you.
Can you believe me?
Can you just believe me once?
What should I believe?
That you're not Nan Heng?
Or that Li Shiliu
has never lied to me?
♪ I leave the book aside,
though I haven't finished reading it ♪
Say something.
♪ I know one day I can have
a glimpse of the ending ♪
Say something now!
♪ Life is unpredictable ♪
♪ Who can get rid of perplexity ♪
Song Yimeng, I...
Let go of me.
♪ And find the answer he yearns for? ♪
Song Yimeng,
what do I have to do
to have your forgiveness?
I told you to let go of me!
I asked you to let go.
Did you hear that?
♪ Let the wind flip through
the past chapters of my life ♪
Fine.
You won't let go, will you?
♪ Let brush and ink
depict my adventures ♪
♪ Let's see how many ways
fate can shape my life in ♪
♪ Let moonlight shine on
the lines about love and hate ♪
♪ Let me bang my head
against a brick wall ♪
Nan Heng,
♪ If this is my destiny,
I'll accept it ♪
I'll say this one last time.
I'm done being a fool.
Stop acting
like you love me dearly.
That will only make me
hate you more.
Do you understand?
♪ Setting sun, help me
weather through the big snow ♪
♪ I'll wait till the next chapter
to get sorrowful ♪
♪ Every word resonates with me
like dancing notes on the paper ♪
♪ Wind, be with me
in the quest for an ideal ♪
♪ Brush and ink,
stand with me on the cliff ♪
♪ My heart measures
the waves I've cleaved ♪
♪ Setting sun, help me
weather through the big snow ♪
♪ I'll wait till the next chapter
to get sorrowful ♪
Did you find them?
General,
we searched this place, but found no one.
Search the lower floors with me.
♪ Every word resonates with me
like dancing notes on the paper ♪
-Yes!
Miss Song?
Where is Li Shiliu?
I have nothing
to do with him.
Miss Song.
What do you mean by this?
Can the capital prefecture's office arrest
innocent civilians when it
carries out its duties?
You'll have to excuse me, Miss Song.
This matter is about a major criminal.
You should
explain to General Chu in person.
Fugui.
Song Yimeng was taken away by Rong Hua.
I need you to go to
Chu Guihong's residence
and keep an eye on the situation there.
Report to me if anything happens.
Did you not hear...
Your Highness, when do you
plan to tell me the truth?
Uncle,
are you here to denounce me?
You're a counsellor of mine.
I don't owe you any
explanation on anything.
You sheltered
Shangguan Baihe for three years.
Don't you owe me
an explanation on this matter?
When you embezzled
disaster relief funds years ago,
I already informed you of its severity.
For the sake of my mother,
I cut you some slack for one last time.
Even the most ignorant peasants
know to protect their families.
Your Highness, are you going
to thrust your own uncle
into adversity?
Your Highness, are you
really a heartless man?
Heartless?
You call me "heartless"?
I've always turned a blind eye
to all the evil deeds
you've done over these years.
Our kinship is the only reason
that I haven't disclosed
your illegal acts.
You should've been
executed a thousand times!
Now that we're being honest,
you might as well
answer my question candidly.
When Pingrong Battle happened,
did you do anything out of bounds?
Absolutely not.
Okay.
I'll believe you then.
However, if one day
I find out you've committed treason,
I won't let you get away with it
even though you're my uncle.
I get it now.
Your Highness thinks I'm old
and useless.
You can't wait to get rid of me.
I don't want to talk about that.
Chu Guihong is targeting
the Waning River Crescent now.
He'll discover the truth sooner or later.
You have to kill Shangguan Baihe,
or your life,
my life,
your mother's life
and all the lives of
the Gao family will be taken!
The one dragging the Gao family down
is not me,
but you.
[A long journey starts from the vicinity]
[Qianyu Mansion]
General.
Yimeng,
Li Shiliu is a key offender
of Shangguan He's case.
Why did you go meet him?
What did you two talk about?
Chu Guihong,
Shangguan He might be guilty,
but the other Nightwalkers are innocent.
Don't try to defend them.
They're all on Nan Heng's side.
None of them are innocent.
What are you saying?
When have you become like this?
You made an oath
before your aunt's
memorial tablet in childhood.
Have you forgotten it?
I have never forgotten it.
I made a vow to prevent innocent people
from being wrongfully killed.
It's a principle I've always upheld.
Everything I've done is
in accordance with the law,
fair and square.
But by shutting down
the Waning River Crescent
and going after the Nightwalkers,
you're embroiling innocent people.
The Nightwalkers once saved my life
and lent a helping hand
to you and Qianyu Army.
But now, you are
driving them into a corner.
You're just feeling sorry
for Li Shiliu, aren't you?
Yimeng,
I'm not suffocating them.
You are suffocating me!
I'm suffocating you?
How come?
You're turning me into
someone like Nan Heng!
He's a villain in your eyes,
so you're not surprised when he tricks
and deceives you.
By contrast,
you consider me as
a good person from Qianyu Army.
You question me when I
take slightly harsh measures.
Why?
Why does a good person
have to lose to a bad person?
Why can't a good person do something
as he watches the girl he likes
being drawn to a bad person?
Just in order to prove himself
to be a good person?
Chu Guihong,
being a good person
isn't about proving anything to others,
but about keeping a clear conscience.
Your father spent
20-odd years nurturing you.
If he saw what you're doing now...
If I hadn't chosen to be
a good person years ago,
perhaps my father wouldn't have died.
If being a good person means
not to fight back
when his next of kin dies,
or to lose the love of his life
to someone else again and again,
then I'd rather be
a more brutal and despicable man
than Nan Heng.
Long live Your Majesty!
[Calm, Respectful, and Sincere]
All rise.
Thank Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
I have a report to make.
The capital prefecture's office
is said to be making big moves lately.
Speak up.
Recently,
I've caught a man
from the martial arts world,
named Shangguan Baihe.
Investigation results
prove him to be
the absconding culprit
of the theft case in Jiangnan
Province three years ago.
Now, he has adopted a new identity
as the second master of the Nightwalkers,
an organization in the martial arts world.
The theft case in Jiangnan Province...
It was handled by Heng, wasn't it?
I remember
all the offenders were
executed at that time.
Your Majesty is correct.
I suspect
that the Seventh Prince proceeded with
the case unjustly,
and that he is now in collusion
with the Nightwalkers.
I humbly request Your Majesty's
authorization for me to lead Qianyu Army
to search and seize his  residence
for an investigation.
In view of your concerns,
I hereby...
Think twice, Your Majesty.
General Chu has exhibited no evidence.
If Your Majesty is to make a ruling,
please at least hear what
the Seventh Prince has to say.
What can Heng say?
When Guihong completes the investigation,
he will present all the evidence
before your eyes, Chancellor Gao.
How can a prince's residence
be searched and seized
based on a false allegation?
Minister Song,
as head of the six ministries,
would you care
to share your insights?
Mr. Song?
Mr. Song!
He's asking you.
About what?
Did you doze off?
About Heng.
The Seventh Prince?
A family member of mine has
connections with His Highness.
So, it's appropriate for me to
comment on matters
concerning His Highness.
It is me that General Chu
finds suspicious.
I'd like to prove my innocence on my own.
Others shouldn't be involved.
What a coincidence.
I also have a report to make today.
Your Majesty,
the one colluding
with those from the martial arts world
and stirring up trouble non-stop recently
is not me, but the general of Qianyu Army
and the capital prefect
who is falsely accusing me,
Chu Guihong.
Nonsense!
This is slander!
Heng,
anyone who falsely
charges against an official
will be punished for
inciting factional fights.
Your Majesty is right.
But the fact is,
despite the heavy protection
provided by General Chu's Qianyu Army,
I was nearly assassinated
at the Lantern Festival.
Now that I think of it,
I still feel frightened.
Today, General Chu
is confusing the officials
and fabricating charges against me.
So, I feel the need
to make a statement.
Go ahead.
That assassination case has been closed.
Some people from the martial arts world
attacked me in the disguise of Nightwalkers.
But I'm puzzled
by two things.
First,
the security arrangements for the festival
were made by Qianyu Army.
Yet an injured man
from the martial arts world
managed to escape
in the presence of General Chu
and dozens of Qianyu soldiers.
Something must've gone wrong.
I contend that this man
was assisted by someone in Qianyu Army.
Second,
the assassin showed up
and retreated without cause.
Besides, he was instructed by no one.
At that time, I already had many doubts.
But Your Majesty didn't want
to pursue the matter further,
so, to maintain political stability,
I had to set it aside.
A few days ago,
General Chu made me go to
the capital prefecture's prison
for Shangguan Baihe's case.
Coincidentally,
some thugs broke in,
trying to rescue the prisoner.
I was wounded in the course.
What bewilders me is
that General Chu
shifted all the blame to the Nightwalkers
before catching
the mastermind.
Are you saying
that neither the assassin
nor the prisoner's rescuers
are members of the Waning River Crescent?
Yes. It is wise of Your Majesty.
I suspect
that General Chu hired people
from the martial arts world
to assassinate me and rescue the prisoner.
Then, he framed the Waning
River Crescent for the crimes.
Your Highness,
if a man can be convicted without proof,
then what is the use of the law?
Did you hear that, Heng?
Convictions can't be made without proof.
If you're just venturing a speculation...
I have proof.
Bring it in.
[Calm, Respectful, and Sincere]
Bring it in!
Mr. Chu, do you recognize this mask?
If Mr. Chu can't recall,
I believe the Eighteen Prince
must know the origins of this mask.
I...
Heng,
don't keep me in suspense.
Just tell the truth.
Your Majesty,
several days before I was attacked
at the Lantern Festival,
General Chu caused a disturbance
in the Waning River Crescent
with this mask on,
and antagonized the Nightwalkers.
There were many witnesses at the scene,
including the Eighteenth Prince.
What else do you have to say, General Chu?
Chu Guihong,
how do you explain this?
I impersonated Li Shiliu
only to figure out
if the Seventh Prince was
in collusion with the Nightwalkers.
Collusion?
General Chu, did you start taking me
and the Nightwalkers as outlaws long ago?
Anyone who falsely
charges against an official
will be punished for
inciting factional fights.
Your Majesty,
it is my belief
that the assassination and
the attempted prison break
were done by Chu Guihong
out of spite and revenge,
for the purposes of harming me
and incriminating the Nightwalkers.
As the capital prefect, Chu
Guihong abused his power
for personal vendettas
and knowingly broke the law.
He should be executed.
Nan Heng,
you're committing the crime
of deceiving the sovereign
by distorting the truth!
Stop bickering!
A prince and the capital prefect
are hurling accusations at each other.
What a disgrace!
A nobody from the martial arts world
has caused such chaos in the court.
In my opinion,
Shangguan Baihe
must be killed.
Why not
behead him in public
tomorrow?
Your Majesty,
the truth of the case
is yet to be revealed.
Please don't make a rash decision.
Your Highness is merciful.
I understand that.
But this case will never be resolved
until Shangguan Baihe is dead.
To prove your innocence,
Your Highness should
oversee the execution.
If the Seventh Prince
truly executes that criminal,
General Chu, you must pay for
falsely accusing His Highness,
confess that you colluded
with outlaws to plan an
assassination against a prince,
resign from your position
as the capital prefect,
and be demoted to be a commoner.
Don't try to intimidate anyone!
What if Heng sides with Shangguan Baihe
and can't bring himself
to kill that criminal?
If so,
I'll take my own life in the court
to atone for falsely accusing General Chu
today!
You crossed the line today, Uncle.
Your Highness,
you almost gave yourself away
in the court just now.
I thought that move was
the last chance to deter Chu Guihong.
Hesitation could only
lead to a giant failure.
What stands between
you and success is mercy.
Nan Heng,
I told Shangguan He yesterday
that trusting you
would cost him his life.
What you did today proves me right.
Thank you.
Now,
I'm free of moral restraints
when I do anything.
Guihong, why even bother talking to him?
Breathing the same air
as a vile person like him
really disgusts me!
Let's go.
My Lady!
Please eat something.
My Lady,
you've locked yourself inside
for a day and night.
What happened to you?
You can tell us about it!
My Lady!
Yimeng!
[Laiyi House]
My Lady!
Yimeng!
An imperial edict was made today.
Shangguan He will be executed tomorrow.
I beg you to save his life!
Your Highness,
Chancellor Gao has destroyed
all the clothes of Li Shiliu
in the mansion.
As for Shangguan He...
Now,
the capital prefecture's prison
is guarded by Qianyu Army
and
some elite calvary forces
borrowed by Chancellor Gao
from the Emperor.
My uncle truly
is a scheming man.
He's trying to cut
all my ties with the Nightwalkers,
so he will be
the only one I can rely on.
Your Highness,
will you really
kill Shangguan He tomorrow?
The Emperor is forcing
me to depart for my fiefdom.
Chu Guihong is forcing me to plead guilty.
Even my uncle
is forcing me to kill.
Everyone is trying
to manipulate me.
But even if I'm in a dead end,
I'll fight my way through.
[Laiyi House]
There is only one way
to save Shangguan He.
What is it?
To clear his name by finding out
the truth of the case he was involved in.
I'm afraid we can't
make it in just one night.
Yiting,
don't fret.
The situation is not desperate yet.
We can turn things around.
But we don't have helpers now.
We can't turn to Nan Heng or Chu Guihong.
Nor can we let Dad know about this.
We can turn to
the Nightwalkers
and try postponing the execution.
Shanhu!
Spill it.
What did you find?
Chancellor Gao has sent 200
more elite calvary troopers
to guard the capital prefecture's prison.
200?
That'll make tonight's
rescue mission even harder.
How can we save him?
Yeah.
The prison is heavily guarded.
So what if it's difficult?
Have we Nightwalkers
been afraid of anything?
At worst,
we'll die before Second Master does.
We can be brothers again in hell.
If you're scared,
then don't follow me!
Yunlong,
what do you mean by this?
There are many guards.
You'll all die if you go.
Let me do it.
If I survive,
meet me outside the city.
If I die,
leave me there.
No!
The masters' women are here.
Who?
The Song sisters.
Open the door.
Nan Heng took off his mask
in front of you guys?
He threatened us,
saying that we had to leave the capital,
or
he would kill us.
He addressed those harsh words
only to persuade you
not to risk your lives.
What a model of probity
at this critical moment.
That is what Li Shiliu
would normally say.
But he is Nan Heng,
Great Jing's brutal God of Death.
What are the odds of him being our chief?
Li Shiliu and the Seventh Prince...
Which identity represents Nan Heng best?
Mrs. Li,
don't be upset.
Nan...
Chief really loves you.
Though the way he treats us...
Cut it out.
I don't want to talk about that now.
Li Shiliu
on longer exists in this world.
Chief is still with us.
We need to rescue
Second Master as well.
You're planning to rescue him from prison?
-Don't!
But Second Master will
be executed tomorrow.
What else
option do we have?
There is one, of course.
We'll stall the execution
and clear his name.
Mrs. Shangguan,
can we really save
Second Master this way?
Don't call me that,
or I'll make you regret it.
Shangguan He's conviction
comes from
stealing disaster relief funds.
If this charge drops,
he won't be executed.
Think it through, Yimeng.
By revealing the truth of this theft case,
you'll make
an enemy of Nan Heng.
Even Li Shiliu is a fake identity.
You think I'd care about
Nan Heng's opinion?
I'm helping Shangguan He
for friends
and everyone.
It has nothing to do with Nan Heng.
You know you're lying.
Mrs. Li,
you're wrong about Chief.
Don't call me that.
What's between us is more
complicated than you think.
You don't understand.
I do.
How do I not?
You like Li Shiliu,
and Li Shiliu likes you too.
You're mad because Chief lied to you.
But
that's just the way Chief is.
He just can't bring himself
to say nice things.
Beneath that poker face of his,
there is a warm heart.
He is usually indifferent
when he sees women.
But whenever he sees you,
he is especially happy.
He always has a mask on.
How do you know if he is happy or not?
I...
Mrs. Shangguan,
whose side are you on?
Don't call me that!
Stop looking for trouble
where none exists.
It's not easy to find
someone you love
amidst so many men, is it?
Yiting,
if Shangguan He deceives you like this,
will you believe he loves you?
Has he not deceived me the same way?
Well...
It's different.
Yes.
It is different.
My situation is worse than yours.
He runs away when he sees me.
Even when I catch up, he runs again.
But does it matter?
Nan Heng did lie to you.
But you lied to him too, didn't you?
Aren't you clear if Nan Heng
is in love with you or not?
I saw something.
Chief secretly drew
portraits of you in his room.
He stashed the files
about your information
and read them several times a day.
Oh right,
do you remember
those two fish?
When you two argue,
Chief would
separate them with a stick.
Blatant abuse, isn't it?
That's abuse.
I don't know
what Nan Heng is like.
But the Nightwalkers
all trust Li Shiliu.
If he says he likes you,
then he must mean it.
We respect you as Mrs. Li.
You have
that respect now
and forever.
How magnificent.
So many people are bidding me farewell.
It's worth dying.
You look sad. Why?
Are you friends with
Shangguan Baihe?
Do I look sad?
I'm bursting with impatience.
I'm ecstatic.
People mourn the passing
of those of their kind.
Your Highness.
All the eyes of Qianyu
Army are on you today.
No slip is allowed.
Your Highness,
Shangguan Baihe must die,
or I'll be the one to die
tomorrow in the imperial court.
Your Highness,
sort out your priorities.
You're an important official
with immense power and influence.
You must be kidding.
[Yongde Gate]
Shangguan Baihe, a leader of thugs,
shall be executed for committing
numerous atrocities.
The Emperor has granted
a written approval,
appointing the Seventh Prince
to supervise the execution,
which will be carried out in no time.
Your Highness,
please order to proceed.
Verify his identity.
Verify his identity?
Why the unnecessary move, Your Highness?
I'd hate to give you the satisfaction
by executing the wrong criminal
and being punished by the Emperor.
What are you doing?
Does my face look like clay to you?
Now is the wrong time
to joke around, isn't it?
Can't you let me have a quick death?
What's the point of all this?
You want to die?
It won't be that easy.
What do you mean?
Execute!
[Approved]
There's a secret passage.
The exit is on the right.
To the right side!
I've resigned myself to being killed.
Don't take risks for me.
Your Highness,
the criminal's identity has been
verified and confirmed.
Execute!
[Approved]
Wait!
I have something to say.
His Highness,
I know I committed appalling crimes.
All I want is a quick death.
But before that,
I'd like to have a drink to quench
my sudden thirst for alcohol
and to brace myself.
I beg for Your Highness's permission.
You're about to die.
Just cut the crap!
Calm, Your Highness.
I'll atone for my wrongs with my life
after my one last drink.
What if my real identity is exposed?
Atone for your wrongs with your life then.
It's already noon.
The criminal must be executed now.
I am the supervisor here.
Chancellor Gao,
aren't you overstepping your bounds?
The token has been thrown out.
Why are you delaying the execution?
Your Highness,
are you just stalling for time?
If there's a change of situation,
ignite the explosives
create chaos,
and seek a chance to save the target.
Phantom dragon lurks in the black market.
Radiant lanterns
illuminate the Nightwalkers.
[Yongde Gate]
I'm a Nightwalker.
Nobody can hurt this man!
It's Shanhu.
What are you waiting for?
Catch the intruder now!
♪ Phantom dragon
lurks in the black market ♪
Here come the Nightwalkers.
Don't you dare hurt Shangguan Baihe!
♪ Radiant lanterns
illuminate the Nightwalkers ♪
Yunlong?
♪ In the dark of night,
pure dreams run deep and wide ♪
Nan Heng,
now I understand why
you were stalling for time.
♪ Who dares to join the game?
This isn't child's play ♪
You were waiting for these outlaws
♪ Footsteps that shake the sky,
fear refuses to fade ♪
to rescue the criminal.
Now, can you still deny being
♪ Every punch lands
hard on this wild melody ♪
connected to the Nightwalkers?
[Yongde Gate]
General Chu,
don't you want to wipe out
the entire Waning River Crescent?
I suggest you carefully consider
if you have what it takes.
Phantom dragon lurks in the black market,
♪ I ride on the wind
of the waning river crescent ♪
Radiant lanterns
illuminate the Nightwalkers
♪ Hate the injustice in the world ♪
♪ Loyalty and righteousness
weigh on both sides of the scale ♪
We're Nightwalkers.
Greetings, officers.
♪ Wield the knife
to carve a rift in the hell ♪
♪ Phantom dragon
lurks in the black market ♪
The Nightwalker of Waning River Crescent,
Greetings, officers.
♪ Radiant lanterns
illuminate the Nightwalkers ♪