♪In cool weather♪
♪I fly over the sea to see you♪
♪As fast as I can♪
♪I don't know why♪
♪But I've had my heart set on it♪
♪I've been eager to meet you♪
♪I keep practicing with trembling hands♪
♪Learning to embrace you♪
♪The brilliant roses are withering♪
♪Sunshine is sprinkled on the earth♪
♪Passing through
the splendid four seasons♪
♪I must see you♪
♪I will see you at any cost♪
♪While I am young♪
♪I will hold you tightly♪
♪And tell you♪
♪How important you are to me♪
♪I will see you at any cost♪
♪Whatever we said when parting♪
♪No matter how far apart we may be♪
♪I will grasp your hands♪
♪And take you with me♪
=Sweet Games =
(I used to be helpless
when faced with problems,)
(thinking that leaving this city
was protecting her)
(and giving up this relationship
was fulfilling her dream.)
(I didn't understand
until I saw her again)
(that she was more determined
than I had imagined.)
(No matter how long I'd been gone,)
(she'd always be here, waiting for me.)
=Episode 20=
(The Truth Is Near)
What's up with you?
You won the lottery?
Five million.
Yan Yue is back.
I thought you won the lottery.
Pardon?
Yan Yue is back.
Oh my,
the sun is rising from the west today.
Are you okay?
Alright,
get in now.
Wait.
You came to pick me up?
Don't be verbose.
Get in or not?
I will.
Stop.
Go.
Seat belt.
When the people
from Southern Lights come later,
what should I say?
Did you hear me?
I'm listening. Go on.
You seem a bit off today.
Your love life...
I-I-I don't want to hear it.
I know.
Just think about
the Southern Lights matter.
Don't be as impulsive as last time.
Okay?
Roger.
I know.
But I've been to those few companies.
There's no useful information.
Right now,
I'm near the Gaishi building.
You're funny.
You can't expect me
to go duel with Zhao Qian, can you?
(Gaishi)
Chen Rui.
Wait.
Changfeng, I'm hanging up.
Chen...
(Gaishi)
How can she be with Zhao Qian?
It's not time yet. Just wait.
(Miss An, I ran into
Chen Rui at the Gaishi Group.)
Chen Rui?
What's it?
Tian Xin said she ran into
Chen Rui at the Gaishi Group.
Gaishi.
Tian Xin, are you sure?
(Miss An, I'm sure.)
Don't tell anyone for now.
I'll handle this matter.
Thanks to Wu this time,
we found a breakthrough
and even managed
to set up a meeting with him.
We must get some information.
Hello, my name is An Ran.
This is Hu Yingjun.
We're the heads of Gaishi Unparalleled.
Hello,
my name is Chen Jiaxi.
I've heard from Wu
that you are old friends.
Yes.
Were you guys
attacked by hackers too?
Our game has been shut down.
I know
your company and ours
had the same experience.
Let me give you some advice.
If I were you,
I would stick it out to the end.
Never think about relying on others.
Otherwise...
Back then,
our team worked hard for five years.
Just when we were attacked by hackers,
we felt too weak,
so we chose to join a big company,
hoping that it'd save
the company and the game.
But then...
Is it the Gaishi Group?
Do you think our terms will be accepted
by Gaishi Unparalleled?
Mr. Zhao, your terms are too harsh.
They care a lot about
Time Boyfriend.
I don't think
they will accept your terms.
Mr. Chen, may I ask the details
of your company being acquired
by the Gaishi Group?
Mr. Chen,
Wu told me some
about Jiaxi Technology.
I also know
how hard it has been
for you to sustain till now.
I can tell you
our company is under attack now,
and that I absolutely won't compromise.
If I tell you,
do you have the confidence
to find out who the mastermind is?
I didn't expect Time Boyfriend
to end up like this.
Two months ago,
I was still discussing
cooperation with Miss An.
Who would have thought of today?
She made it harder
for herself, didn't she?
My previous company
was called Xinyang Culture.
I spent three years
carefully making a game.
But only three days after going online,
it was attacked,
and I was blackmailed by a hacker.
The hacker gave me
an account number
and threatened that if I didn't pay,
he would keep attacking my server.
I paid the first time,
but I didn't expect him
to take it too far.
When I realized
it was a bottomless pit,
my company's cash flow
could not hold up.
Just when I felt desperate,
a friend introduced me
to Mr. Zhao of the Gaishi Group.
Mr. Zhao?
Which Zhao?
The investment director of Gaishi,
Zhao Qian.
Alright,
my condition
is to get a stake in Time Boyfriend.
I'll cover
the publishing and server costs
in exchange for 40% equity.
After it's successful,
you can get the part you deserve.
Mr. Zhao,
I have already decided to resign.
Zhao Qian proposed
to invest in my company.
We felt like we had grabbed
a lifeline at that time,
but we didn't expect
the investment turned
into an acquisition later.
All of us and the games we developed
were acquired by the Gaishi Group.
We were unwilling,
but we had no choices.
But more unexpectedly,
we were all kicked out
in less than a month.
I know Gaishi Unparalleled is a startup.
But your achievements
are well-recognized.
That's why I came here
to propose
a collaboration.
What do you think about it?
I was desperate at the time,
but I persisted and established
Jiaxi Technology,
yet to really take off.
I have replayed it
in my mind countless times.
From being attacked,
extorted
and acquired
to being kicked out
by the Gaishi Group in the end.
All this is absolutely not
a coincidence.
Mr. Chen, thank you for your honesty.
Your words
really help us a lot.
Are you really sure to expose
all the bad things Zhao Qian did?
We will do our best,
but we're still too weak.
If we need you to stand up
and join us at that time,
would you be willing?
Mr. Chen, may I ask
how your game is now?
After the Gaishi Group
acquired the game,
the subsidiary Tiansheng messed it up.
World of Imagination
is completely unrecognizable now.
You're finally back.
We haven't seen you for so long,
and that's what you said?
Stop joking.
Go in and prepare.
Those from Southern Lights
will be here soon.
Alright, drop the act.
Who asked when Yan Yue
would come back every other day?
I just wanted him to hurry back
to deal with this matter.
Losing weight?
Not much.
And you?
Don't be so impulsive anymore.
Got it.
World of Imagination
was actually made by them,
but it was completely messed up
by Zhao Qian and Wang.
It's lucky we didn't agree
to their acquisition at the time.
It's really scary to think about it.
Chen Jiaxi's words
basically confirmed
our previous thoughts.
The hacker incident
was done by Zhao Qian.
But we still
don't have clear evidence.
But at least one thing
we can be sure of
is that we absolutely cannot compromise.
Agreed.
I'm going to meet Chen Rui.
Then,
I'll go work on Mr. Chen again.
Bye.
Hello, everyone.
I am Song Yi, the proxy lawyer
for Southern Lights.
Why did only you come?
How about the person in charge?
Well,
I can represent
all affairs of Southern Lights.
Let's start.
Okay.
Our current demand is very simple.
Southern Lights publicly apologizes
and admits that it concealed from us
the fact that the author
didn't grant the right
to produce the audiobook
and compensates JS Sound Art Studio
and Mr. Yan Yue for all the losses
in the copyright dispute
about Lovely Moonlight.
Our attitude is very clear.
We refuse to negotiate.
Negotiation is to prevent
the situation from escalating.
Are you sure
you have thought it through?
I'm sorry.
But then what are you here for?
I just represent
Southern Lights to express a stance.
Hey, what's with the attitude?
This is my task.
If you have other demands,
we can talk about them in court.
Goodbye.
Hey, what do you mean?
We haven't even taken you to court yet,
and you've already decided it?
Calm down.
I would like to know
why you want to join our company.
I really like the concept of
Fragment Time Boyfriend.
I believe
this romantic game truly understands
contemporary women.
I also did some research
and truly admired your staff's passion
for this game.
I can feel consideration
for the female customers in the game.
(From character design to art style,)
(it's all quite unconventional.)
I believe
your company has a real passion
for developing games.
Thank you, Miss An.
You're welcome.
What have you been doing?
I've been packing up for a move.
You're really going home?
Yes.
Miss An, what can I do for you?
You're doing quite well
at Gaishi Unparalleled.
Why do you want to leave suddenly?
Is it because
the environment is not good enough
or the salary is not high,
or perhaps you want
to go to a better company,
like
the Gaishi Group?
No, Miss An.
Chen Rui,
do you know
what impressed me most about you
after you came to our company?
You are meticulous
and organized in your work.
You are not a creator,
but I can see
your love for games.
With your personality,
I don't think you would easily
leave this industry.
Unless
you have some unspeakable secret.
After it's successful,
you can get
the part you deserve.
Mr. Zhao,
I have already decided to resign.
Miss An,
I'm sorry.
Miss An, please believe me.
I really didn't do
anything bad to the company.
I believe you,
and I also believe my own choice.
But
if there's anything
I must know,
I hope you can tell me.
I will be very grateful to you.
I know
perhaps making this decision
requires a lot of courage,
but I sincerely hope
you can think about it carefully.
Thank you.
How was today?
We met Wu's friend
and got some useful information.
But just their company alone
can't form a chain of evidence.
We still need to gather some
other materials.
And you?
How was your studio today?
We planned to negotiate
with Southern Lights.
But they clearly know
they were in the wrong, yet they insist
on going to court
and don't want to reconcile.
This kind of lawsuit
is very hard to fight,
and they are an old copyright company.
I think they know
that it's hard for you.
The longer it drags on,
the more advantageous it is for them.
Yeah.
It's getting more and more complicated.
But we're getting
closer and closer to the truth.
Then why aren't you happy?
The closer you get to the answer,
the more you see
some dirty, ugly things.
I find it very annoying.
On the way back, I kept thinking.
Would it be better
if I didn't seek answers?
But with you by my side,
I have the strength
to fight all of this.
You fool.
Can you do me a favor?
What is it?
I'm starving.
Then
give me some strength.
Just like that?
This is the down payment.
If you want more,
you have to perform well.
Chef Yan, thank you.
Mengyao.
What's wrong?
Could you please go ask Mr. Hu
if he resolved the issue
with Miss An yesterday?
We dare not ask.
What's there to be afraid of?
Of course we are.
And they're too busy to tell us.
Can't we be anxious?
Right, Wu
and Peng?
Alright, I'll go.
Okay, thanks for the time.
I will convey
Lansheng's thoughts to An Ran.
On a call?
We've found the evidence.
The rest is only a matter of time.
Understood.
Thank you for the time, Mr. Pei.
Mr. Hu.
What's it?
How was your investigation
with An Ran yesterday?
We're getting closer to the truth
and getting more annoyed.
And there's no direct evidence.
So what do we do now?
I guess An Ran will find it.
Lansheng wants us to hurry
to ride on the Gaishi Group's coattails.
I'll be bearing
the pressure and holding on.
We have to persist
especially at this time.
I believe in An Ran
and you.
Keep up.
We haven't had a date for a long time.
After work today,
let's go eat something good.
Eating something good?
Do your job.
Still thinking about eating.
Yes, sir.
Be good.
How is it going, Mengyao?
Give them some more time.
We have to believe in them.
When will Miss An be back?
Yeah,
without Miss An,
we're leaderless.
There's so much work on hand.
Everyone, let's first do
the work in our hands.
Alright.
Dear,
when are you going
to start the show again?
It's already shut down. Start what?
I don't want to.
Bluebird was dubbed
by you, right?
How did you know?
How can't I recognize it?
I feel
the people on the internet
are not so radical anymore.
And your real fans have been waiting
for you for a long time.
Would there be?
Of course, dear.
You are a soul-soothing expert.
If your show doesn't start,
those souls will wither.
Besides,
would you give up and abandon your fans
who've followed you
for years
because of those criticisms online?
Of course, I won't care
about those people's comments.
But
I'm afraid my audience
won't want to listen to my show anymore.
How could it be?
They will want to.
The first impatient one
is me.
The tree at the door
was planted by Shan, right?
Who else could it be?
It's his taste.
My treasure.
Can't believe you'll share it.
I don't drink.
This is to welcome you.
Have a sense of ritual, okay?
Just a little.
A little bit.
Okay.
I'll do it, sir.
I couldn't stop you when you left.
How come you're back with just a push?
I missed you guys.
You missed me?
You didn't miss us.
You were just eager to get home.
You've had enough.
Know when to stop.
While I was gone,
the studio couldn't survive, could it?
The studio is fine.
But your manager
couldn't survive.
Hurry back
to let Nan make some more money,
okay?
Should I reconsider?
Please don't.
Yan Yue,
she's an independent woman.
You have to aspire
to be an independent man.
If you don't,
how can I be independent?
Fine, I'll go home and think about it.
Don't think about it.
When we
clear up the Southern Lights project
and this guy returns,
our studio,
well,
will go up
to the next level.
Cheers.
How's the wine?
So-so.
So-so?
I can't really tell.
I haven't drunk before.
Hello.
Chen Rui.
Miss An, I want to meet you.
(Work Plan)
Miss An.
Chen Rui.
Let's talk.
Sit.
Zhao Qian asked me to join your company
mainly for the acquisition.
He hopes that after the acquisition,
there can be his own people on the team.
What does he want you to do then?
Mainly to be responsible
for the operation
of Time Boyfriend after it goes live.
But I thought
he was planning
to make a normal acquisition.
I didn't expect him
to have hackers attack the game.
Hello,
Mr. Zhao.
Hasn't it already been acquired?
Why did you get people
to attack Time Boyfriend?
This isn't something
you should be worrying about, right?
Focus on your own work.
By the way,
when can I get the internal information
of Time Boyfriend?
I...
I don't have the information you want.
This sounds very outrageous,
but
it can't serve as direct evidence.
Miss An,
I'm sorry.
Is there anything else I can do?
I'm already very grateful
that you came to tell me.
Then, do you have any countermeasures?
I'm still working on it.
I have to think of a plan anyway.
Chen Rui, if I need you to stand up,
would you be willing to help me?
I know this is not a small decision.
But if you're willing to help me,
I will do my best
to protect your career.
Think about it.
Don't feel burdened.
In any case,
our door
is always open to you.
May I know
why you were willing to come today
to tell me these things?
Actually, before I joined
the Gaishi Group,
what I wanted to do was game planning.
My dream was to make
the best mobile game in my mind.
So I joined the Gaishi Group
with great expectations.
But after that,
I never had the chance to get
to the core content positions.
I'd been looking for many opportunities.
Although my colleagues
didn't say it outright...
They just didn't see it.
But after I joined Gaishi Unparalleled,
I found your company was different
and you were different from Zhao Qian.
Miss An, you are one
of the few people in the gaming industry
who are persistent
and have a love for games.
I really felt it
when I worked with you.
So
I really want you to be back.
Don't be nervous. Have some tea.
(Chen Jiaxi agreed
to cooperate with us.)
Is there any good news?
(Why do you have to leave?)
(You said before)
(no matter what others said,)
(you wouldn't leave.)
(If I didn't come back today...)
Mr. Jiang,
you already come to our company
every day,
and today you even want
to stay here until we get off work?
There's so much fun here.
I just like staying here.
Bluebird
seems to be quite popular recently.
Was it dubbed by Mr. Heisha?
I really have no idea.
You must know.
I really don't know.
Tian Xin, are you off work?
Okay, wait a minute.
Do you have any activities after work?
No?
Then I...
We're leaving.
Wait.
Goodbye, Mr. Jiang.
Goodbye.
Okay, goodbye.
Bye.
Aren't you leaving?
We're waiting to lock the door.
♪A movie, full of twists and turns
multiple plots♪
♪But you and I have only
one possibility♪
♪Our relationship is complicated
separated by thousands of miles♪
♪What are you thinking about♪
♪Where should I stand♪
♪From the strange to the familiar♪
♪From the familiar to the strange,
it's an inevitable part of love♪
♪Become a silent sentence♪
♪I look at your back♪
♪But I'm powerless♪
♪It seems you're going to give up on me♪
♪I'm behind you, slowly following you♪
♪Until the sun sets♪
♪When will you stop♪
♪To admire the scenery with me♪
♪Do you know it all doesn't come easy♪
♪I'm behind you, slowly following you♪
♪Following until the moon
wakes up the dawn♪
♪If you can't remember♪
♪I can help you recall♪
♪Reviewing on the one hand♪
♪Picking up on the other♪
♪A movie, full of twists and turns
multiple plots♪
♪But you and I have only
one possibility♪
♪Our relationship is complicated
separated by thousands of miles♪
♪What are you thinking about♪
♪Where should I stand♪
♪From the strange to the familiar♪
♪From the familiar to the strange,
it's an inevitable part of love♪
♪Become a silent sentence♪
♪I look at your back♪
♪But I'm powerless♪
♪It seems you're going to give up on me♪
♪I'm behind you, slowly following you♪
♪Until the sun sets♪
♪When will you stop♪
♪To admire the scenery with me♪
♪Do you know it all doesn't come easy♪
♪I'm behind you, slowly following you♪
♪Following until the moon
wakes up the dawn♪
♪If you can't remember♪
♪I can help you recall♪
♪Reviewing on the one hand♪
♪Picking up on the other♪