♪In cool weather♪
♪I fly over the sea to see you♪
♪As fast as I can♪
♪I don't know why♪
♪But I've had my heart set on it♪
♪I've been eager to meet you♪
♪I keep practicing with trembling hands♪
♪Learning to embrace you♪
♪The brilliant roses are withering♪
♪Sunshine is sprinkled on the earth♪
♪Passing through
the splendid four seasons♪
♪I must see you♪
♪I will see you at any cost♪
♪While I am young♪
♪I will hold you tightly♪
♪And tell you♪
♪How important you are to me♪
♪I will see you at any cost♪
♪Whatever we said when parting♪
♪No matter how far apart we may be♪
♪I will grasp your hands♪
♪And take you with me♪
=Sweet Games =
(Have you thought
about what life will be like in years?)
(From being in love to living together,)
(an ordinary couple will start)
(to grow tired of each other.)
(Two people
who know each other well begin)
(to be worried.)
(Why did they try so hard)
(to understand each other?)
♪I miss you more and more♪
♪It grows with each passing day♪
♪Wondering how we get here this time♪
♪I swear I tried, I tried♪
♪Darling, I tried♪
♪If everything just fell apart♪
♪I'll still have you in my heart♪
An Ran, what did my mother say to you?
Have you considered
what your mother told you?
I haven't.
I don't think that's an issue.
Yan Yue, we should think about it.
♪It isn't all beautiful memories♪
♪Sometimes with laughter and cry♪
♪Sometimes we hold on♪
♪We've been here before♪
♪So many times♪
♪It's never got easier♪
♪No matter how hard we tried♪
♪Wondering how we get here this time♪
♪I swear I tried, I tried♪
♪Darling, I tried♪
♪If everything just fell apart♪
♪I'll still have you in my heart♪
=Episode 14=
(Take the Initiative)
A business trip?
A last-minute notice.
When will you be back?
Not sure yet.
Well,
be careful on the road.
Hello.
Okay.
I'm coming down right away.
Go ahead.
What's with everyone?
You all look so tired.
We're debugging program.
I feel like
my brain is deprived of oxygen.
Have some tea to refresh yourself.
I feel alive again.
Why do I
sense a bit of anger here?
What anger?
Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
- Hi, Mr. Hu.
Mr. Hu.
Hi, why did you come almost at noon?
You look gorgeous today.
Thanks.
You're working so hard.
Let's have lunch together.
And we can talk about the plan.
My treat.
Peng, I need
to discuss art issues with you.
You guys determine the color.
And we also need to talk about the plot.
Everyone needs to be there.
Shouldn't I also join you?
That's not your job.
We'll report to you
about our conclusion.
Come on. Let's have lunch.
I've known Mr. Liu from Mingyang Corp
for many years.
Lansheng wants
to deepen cooperation with them
through Fragment Time Boyfriend.
If successful,
they will invest a lot in it.
That's great.
So, we must strike
while the iron is hot.
Let's seize this chance.
(September 6th, Yan Yue's birthday)
Miss Lan, how many days will we stay?
If all goes well,
we will return tomorrow.
What time?
You have something else to do?
I-I just remembered.
I have a meeting tomorrow night.
If I have to, I'll do it online.
So, let's finish this as fast as we can.
(September 6th, Yan Yue's birthday)
(Dongchuan)
Hello, what's up?
I got something big to tell you.
Bai Mengyao got mad at me.
What did you do?
Just do whatever she wants.
In a while, we will
- I gotta go.
- tell you our thoughts on this project.
Alright.
Let me introduce Mr. Liu
from Mingyang Corp.
This is Miss An
from Gaishi Unparalleled.
Hello, Mr. Liu.
An Ran, nice to meet you.
Fragment Time Boyfriend
has always been our key project.
We are committed to creating a game
that reflects modern love relationships.
It's a healing game for urbanites,
aiming at women longing for love.
We have conducted a beta version.
The results were very good.
(RECORDING)
I thought being in love
was a remarkable thing.
I can walk across the hills.
But, until today,
I just realized it.
After eating the flesh of Monk Tang...
People can become immortal.
The difference
between love and being loved
is probably...
We say goodnight to each other.
You start sleeping,
and I start missing you.
To be, or not to be...
That is the question.
Many years later,
if we are both not married,
it's really a pity.
It's really a pity.
It's too pitiful.
Our children will surely succeed.
Alright, everyone, let's call it a day.
Thank you all. Have a break.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please rest in the lounge.
- That's it for the meeting.
- Okay.
Miss Lan.
We barely ever meet.
Why don't we have a dinner?
It is my treat.
You can taste our Dongchuan cuisine.
My pleasure.
But here's one thing.
(Dongchuan, flight at 5:50 p.m.)
Since we're here,
when can we sign this letter of intent?
Miss Lan.
You still don't like to wait.
Don't worry.
I'll let my legal team draft it later.
We can go over it tomorrow morning.
That's great.
I hope we can work well together.
- Let's work well together.
Miss An, let's work well together.
(An Ran)
(Is the recording going smoothly?)
Mr. Heisha.
This is the script
for the next competition.
Let's go over it now.
Why are the voting results
already written in here?
This was decided
by the program team beforehand.
But I haven't even
seen the performances
of the contestants.
Why can they vote before that?
Mr. Heisha,
please don't make it difficult for us.
I don't.
I must be responsible
for the competition.
It is unfair to other contestants.
How about this?
You read the script first
and prepare for the program recording.
I'll go back and discuss it.
The car is here.
Here it is.
See you then.
See you, Mr. Liu.
See you tomorrow morning.
Alright.
We'll be there.
See you.
Are you drunk?
I'm fine.
Miss Lan, your car is here.
Okay, I have another appointment.
I'll go first.
You go back to the hotel.
Be careful.
We have a meeting tomorrow.
Don't worry.
No problem.
Alright.
Bye.
Be safe.
♪Lay your body near mine♪
(An Ran: I'm home. Auntie is here.
I won't go over today.)
♪With colors of morning light♪
(An Ran, is everything going well?)
♪They brighter with you in my life♪
♪Can I write your name on my heart♪
(WeChat message notification)
♪Can I be the only one,
to kiss you goodnight ooh♪
♪It's better with you♪
♪ in my life♪
♪We drove through the night
till we found♪
♪A place with nobody around♪
♪Sharing this life all with you♪
(An Ran, is everything going well?)
♪Can I write your name on my heart♪
♪Can I sing to you when times get dark♪
♪Can I be the only one,
to kiss you goodnight ooh♪
(An Ran, are you asleep?)
(Perhaps you're happy)
(with her now,)
but have you thought about the future?
If she has any problems at work,
can you stand in her shoes,
and understand her?
Have you considered
what your mother told you?
I haven't.
I don't think that's an issue.
Yan Yue, we should think about it.
♪Can I be the only one
to kiss you before sleeping♪
♪My life is better♪
♪You fill in my life♪
(You got one year older.)
(Happy birthday, buddy.)
(Happy birthday.)
(Happy birthday, Mr. Heisha.)
(Buddy, may you be happy.)
(I was tired from work yesterday,
so I went to bed early.)
Hello?
Hello, Miss An.
I want to confirm with you.
You booked a table at our restaurant
for two persons at 7 p.m.
Is there any change in time
or number of people?
No changes.
Alright, see you tonight.
Okay.
Hello.
I ordered a cake earlier.
Can you have it delivered
at 7 p.m. today?
Okay, thank you.
I have a meeting at 9 a.m.
The atmosphere in our company
is definitely better than
that of others.
Our colleagues are very nice.
You don't need to worry.
Attention, please.
Let me introduce our new colleague.
Chen Rui. She's responsible
for market research.
Let's welcome her.
Our company
has finally had a new colleague.
We've been expecting you.
Welcome.
My name is Peng.
He's an art specialist.
I'm Changfeng, a technician.
My name is Tian Xin, a planner.
We can order take-out together.
Hello, everyone. My name is Chen Rui.
Alright.
That's your desk over there.
I'll take you to see it.
Good morning, have some milk tea.
Come on.
Mr. Hu.
Where's Bai Mengyao?
She hasn't come yet.
A new colleague, right?
Hello, I'm Hu...
Hello, Mr. Hu. I'm Chen Rui.
Hello.
Mengyao is here.
Good morning, beauty.
Let me
introduce a new colleague, Chen Rui.
Hello.
I'm a concept artist.
Just call me Mengyao.
Hello, Mengyao.
I'm Chen Rui,
mainly responsible for the marketing.
Beauty, have some milk tea.
Sorry. Mr. Hu doesn't care
about manners.
Don't mind him.
Have some milk tea.
Thank you.
Not at all.
Have some milk tea.
Come on.
Smells good.
Mr. Hu.
Let's talk at the meeting room.
What is it?
Are you hungry?
How about I order some food?
Please confirm the character design.
It's okay.
I've given my revision suggestions.
Alright.
When does the promotional film team
need the final draft?
Mr. Hu, please be serious.
I forgot.
Well,
I'll confirm it later.
Alright.
If there are no comments,
I'll go for revision.
Mengyao.
Can we be clear on something?
Of course.
I just made my point about my work.
Miss Lan has always had a good taste.
We haven't met for many years,
but now when we meet again,
you have brought us such a good project.
Thank you so much.
I also want to take this opportunity
to cooperate with you again.
To be honest,
the project Fragment Time Boyfriend
is Lansheng's top priority this year.
I'm personally optimistic about this.
As you can see,
these young people
are creative and energetic.
They can create innovative stuff.
This is how we can precisely tap
into the young market.
Yes.
You have a good taste.
Why don't you
reconfirm this letter of intent?
My legal team has revised it.
If there are no problems,
we can sign it directly.
Okay.
I hope we work well together.
Miss Lan.
Is there anything else?
I want to leave first.
I have some important things to do.
Go ahead.
You do your things.
Thank you, Miss Lan.
See you.
Take care.
Okay, we're about to start recording.
Field staff,
please mute your phones.
Okay, please get ready.
We're about to start.
(An Ran, when will you return?)
(Passengers heading to Bowen,)
(we regret to inform)
(your flight AY1314 has been delayed)
(due to weather conditions.)
(We sincerely apologize for this.)
Hello?
Hello, Miss An.
You haven't arrived
at the restaurant yet.
Do you still need us
to hold your reservation?
Yes, please.
We'll be there soon.
Could you please wait a bit longer?
Okay.
Your birthday cake has also arrived.
See you later.
Thank you.
Mr. Heisha, you haven't left yet?
I'm about to leave.
- Thank you.
- You've worked hard.
(Yan Yue)
Hello, An Ran.
Yan Yue.
I'm sorry.
First of all, I remember your birthday.
And I planned
to come back
this afternoon to surprise you.
I know it's pointless
to say anything now.
I was indeed delayed this afternoon.
I'm at the airport now.
But the flight has been delayed.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
When will you arrive? I'll pick you up.
How about this?
I've booked a table.
Could you go to the restaurant first?
I should be boarding soon.
I should arrive around 10 p.m.
Let's meet at the restaurant.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
Okay.
Mr. Heisha.
I'm glad you're here.
We need an additional recording
for a backup interview.
Didn't we finish recording?
Yes, we did.
But you didn't follow the script,
so it doesn't match
with our live voting results.
It's difficult
for the post-production team.
Could you please record a few more?
Please do me a favor.
Xiaoting, come here.
Please redo Mr. Heisha's hair.
Hold on.
I remember I've told you many times.
I only say what I want to say.
The contestant you want me
to evaluate is less capable.
His vocal conditions
are far worse than his opponent's.
Even if you let me repeat it
a million times,
my words will still be the same.
Mr. Heisha,
contestants have their strengths
and weaknesses.
Why don't you bring up his strengths
and talk more about them?
Then problem is solved.
I'm sorry.
I have important things to do.
Today's recording has already ended.
I have to go.
Mr. Heisha,
if you leave now,
I can see this as a breach of contract.
According to our contract,
you invited me as a voice judge,
not an actor.
(Flight AY1314 passengers)
(heading to Bowen,)
(your flight is about to take off.)
(Hello, the phone
you dialed is turned off.)
♪In cool weather♪
♪I fly over the sea to see you♪
♪As fast as I can♪
♪I don't know why♪
♪But I've had my heart set on it♪
♪I've been eager to meet you♪
Excuse me, sir.
We're already closed.
Okay, got it.
Alright.
♪Sunshine is sprinkled on the earth♪
♪Passing through
the splendid four seasons♪
♪I must see you♪
♪I will see you at any cost♪
♪While I am young♪
Welcome.
Hello.
Can I
store this cake in your refrigerator?
I'm sorry, but you can't.
This cake is really important to me.
Can you do me a favor?
You put it
in the freezer.
Okay.
Thank you.
♪In cool weather♪
♪I fly over the sea to see you♪
♪As fast as I can♪
♪I don't know why♪
♪But I've had my heart set on it♪
♪I've been eager to meet you♪
♪I keep practicing with trembling hands♪
♪Learning to embrace you♪
♪The brilliant roses are shiny♪
♪Sunshine is sprinkled on the earth♪
♪Passing through
the splendid four seasons♪
♪I must see you♪
♪I will see you at any cost♪
♪While I am young♪
♪I will hold you tightly♪
♪And tell you♪
Hello?
Hello.
Has the flight
from Dongchuan to Bowen arrived?
It has arrived for a long time.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
♪Whatever we said when parting♪
Sir, do you have a charger?
I'm sorry, but I don't have it.
Can you speed up then?
I can't.
We're almost speeding.
♪And take you with me♪
♪I will see you at any cost♪
♪Whatever we said when parting♪
♪And take you with me♪
An Ran.
Yan Yue.
You're back.
I'm sorry.
I really wanted to surprise you.
Sorry I'm late.
I'm sorry.
I didn't make it.
It's okay. I'm glad you're back.
But today is your birthday.
And our dinner is ruined.
Wait for me.
Where are you going?
Wait here for me.
I'll be right back.
Thank you.
Isn't this what I prepared for you?
Thank you for the surprise.
I was afraid it would melt,
so I put it in the convenience store.
An Ran,
while you were on a business trip,
I thought about
what you said to me that day.
I want to tell you
I'm determined
to be with you.
No matter when we get married
and have children,
I respect your decision.
I want to be with you for nothing else.
I just want
to have you for as long as I can.
Thank you for saying this to me.
Actually, for a couple, it's hard
to take a step forward,
yet it's so easy to take a step back.
In fact, before this,
I had no expectations
about love at all.
Now, I've met you,
and I've made up my mind
to fall in love again.
I understand
what your mother said before,
but what I want to say is
I...
I want to be with you
for the rest of my life.
Thank you, An Ran.
Let's blow out the candles.
Make a wish.
Okay.
♪Since the moment you looked at me♪
My first wish.
I hope An Ran's game can be successful
and released soon.
My second wish.
I hope to be with An Ran forever.
My third wish.
What is it?
♪Since the moment you walked towards me♪
I can't let others
hear my third wish.
♪Past events are as heavy as♪
♪A nostalgic movie♪
♪Tonight it's rerun for past lovers♪
♪I kept you waiting for too long♪
♪Like the galaxy rushing
to the universe♪
♪The string in the dark
is never loosened♪
♪Always in my hands♪
♪I kept you waiting for too long♪
♪The belated evening wind is gentler♪
♪In the hustle and bustle of the world,
you are taking me♪
♪To kiss the clear sky♪
♪And the broad sea♪
Yueyue, you want
to talk about An Ran, right?
Mother, I've thought it through.
An Ran is the right girl for me.
Because of her,
I was able to come out of a closed world
and became a whole self.
I don't care where she's from,
how old she is,
whether she's successful,
or whether she's a good homemaker.
Those are not problems for me.
I like her.
Actually, no matter who I choose,
or what kind of life I live,
I think
I should make my own decisions.
This is what you've always taught me.
So,
I hope you can understand me.
I'm afraid you'll regret it
in the future.
If I give up on An Ran,
I'll regret it the next second.
An Ran
has talked to me.
She told me
she has confidence in herself
and in you.
So...
So I won't stop you.
However,
An Ran didn't want me to tell you
she came to see me.
Okay, I get it.
I'll keep it a secret.
You silly boy.
An Ran.
Does it sound good?
Yes.
Look, does it look like me?
Exactly the same.
I think
if the bad sounds can't be eliminated,
we can create some beautiful sounds.
(From being in love to living together,)
(don't worry too much
about things before they happen.)
(It took Jesse and Celine a decade)
(to get there.)
(You have to fight time.)
Look, your skin is so good.
No need for retouching.
Auntie, your smile is beautiful.
Really?
You look so young.
If only I had a daughter.
When I go out with Yan Yue,
he's so quiet and boring.
That's him.
Please understand him.
If you don't mind,
I'll go shopping
and visit different places
with you.
That would be great!
If you have nothing else to do,
let's do a facial together.
Okay.
Could you send me these pictures?
Okay, I'll send them to you right away.
Looks good.
I'll send it all to you.
Okay, Yan Yue looks so much like you
when he smiles.
So beautiful.
♪A movie, full of twists and turns
multiple plots♪
♪But you and I have only
one possibility♪
♪Our relationship is complicated
separated by thousands of miles♪
♪What are you thinking about♪
♪Where should I stand♪
♪From the strange to the familiar♪
♪From the familiar to the strange,
it's an inevitable part of love♪
♪Become a silent sentence♪
♪I look at your back♪
♪But I'm powerless♪
♪It seems you're going to give up on me♪
♪I'm behind you, slowly following you♪
♪Until the sun sets♪
♪When will you stop♪
♪To admire the scenery with me♪
♪Do you know it all doesn't come easy♪
♪I'm behind you, slowly following you♪
♪Following until the moon
wakes up the dawn♪
♪If you can't remember♪
♪I can help you recall♪
♪Reviewing on the one hand♪
♪Picking up on the other♪
♪A movie, full of twists and turns
multiple plots♪
♪But you and I have only
one possibility♪
♪Our relationship is complicated
separated by thousands of miles♪
♪What are you thinking about♪
♪Where should I stand♪
♪From the strange to the familiar♪
♪From the familiar to the strange,
it's an inevitable part of love♪
♪Become a silent sentence♪
♪I look at your back♪
♪But I'm powerless♪
♪It seems you're going to give up on me♪
♪I'm behind you, slowly following you♪
♪Until the sun sets♪
♪When will you stop♪
♪To admire the scenery with me♪
♪Do you know it all doesn't come easy♪
♪I'm behind you, slowly following you♪
♪Following until the moon
wakes up the dawn♪
♪If you can't remember♪
♪I can help you recall♪
♪Reviewing on the one hand♪
♪Picking up on the other♪