♪In cool weather♪
♪I fly over the sea to see you♪
♪As fast as I can♪
♪I don't know why♪
♪But I've had my heart set on it♪
♪I've been eager to meet you♪
♪I keep practicing with trembling hands♪
♪Learning to embrace you♪
♪The brilliant roses are withering♪
♪Sunshine is sprinkled on the earth♪
♪Passing through
the splendid four seasons♪
♪I must see you♪
♪I will see you at any cost♪
♪While I am young♪
♪I will hold you tightly♪
♪And tell you♪
♪How important you are to me♪
♪I will see you at any cost♪
♪Whatever we said when parting♪
♪No matter how far apart we may be♪
♪I will grasp your hands♪
♪And take you with me♪
=Sweet Games =
(We are often)
(reluctant to start a new relationship)
(not because we
can't get over the past,)
(but because we're scared
of getting hurt once again.)
=Episode 7=
(An Ran, You're Exposed)
He looks good.
So handsome.
He's really tall.
Yeah, tall and handsome.
Really?
Excuse me, it's taken.
It's taken.
It's me.
Who?
Little Princess.
Why are you wearing this?
Why are you dressed like this?
I just think that
Mr. Jiang has seen
so many pretty girls.
I can attract his attention
if I wear the sunglasses like his.
Good idea.
I just got this for you.
Thank you so much.
Testing.
Dear fans, welcome
to Mr. Jiang's reading club to celebrate
the tenth anniversary of his debut.
Is anyone else coming
apart from Mr. Jiang?
We were just saying
that No.22 just came out of the bathroom
and saw Mr. Jiang and Heisha.
Yeah.
Who?
Heisha.
I happened to hear them talking
and realized that it was Heisha.
Heisha rarely shows up in public,
but he's so handsome.
A rising dubbing actor, Mr. Heisha.
Welcome them.
Where are you going?
Sit down. It's starting.
Sit.
So handsome.
Hello, everyone. I'm Jiang Shan.
Welcome to my reading club
to celebrate
the tenth anniversary of my debut.
Meanwhile, I'd like to show my gratitude
to my buddy, Mr. Heisha,
for coming to support me.
Hello, I'm Heisha.
So handsome.
By the time I heard my mom calling me
with her suppressed voice,
I had already reached
the window outside the door.
The rainwater
streaming down the eaves...
I saw someone in a cap approaching
a common trash can by the road.
I recognized her.
I knew it was her.
What's wrong? Feeling sick?
To thank you for your constant support,
we're picking two lucky fans
to come on stage
for a group photo.
Group photo.
The first lucky fan is...
Green, No.28.
It's me. I'm No.28.
Go ahead.
Come on.
Just like that?
Three, two, one.
Okay, Mr. Heisha will draw
the second lucky number.
Come on.
Red, No.81.
Aren't yours red? Let me see.
No.81.
Here.
Little Princess.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Go, Little Princess.
Go.
Hurry up.
She's quite mysterious.
Isn't it a pity
to take a photo with your idol
without showing your face?
Please rest assured.
This event is
only for internal purposes.
Nothing will be posted online.
Please rest assured.
Or maybe you're hiding
a secret or something.
Take off your mask, okay?
Take it off, Little Princess.
Cheer for her.
Come on, Little Princess
Take off your mask.
It's you?
An...
An Ran?
What a coincidence.
Let me introduce her.
She is
a hard-core fan of Mr. Heisha.
What a coincidence.
Come on, give her a clap
Alright.
Let's take a photo.
Three, two, one.
Way to go, Little Princess.
So you've switched to another fan club.
Tell us the truth,
when did you betray Mr. Jiang?
I didn't.
Stop denying it.
My love for Mr. Jiang can withstand
the test of heaven and earth.
I'm just fooling around with Heisha.
So you know each other for real.
Don't tell me
he's the neighbor
who's six years younger than you.
- Six years?
- Neighbor?
It's really him?
You...
Way to go, Little Princess.
I didn't expect that.
What a coincidence.
Thanks to me, you finally
took a photo with your idol.
Thank you so much.
Want an autograph?
No, thanks.
Your bag is heavy?
Not really.
Let me help you.
What did I do to you? What do you want?
Didn't you tell me that
you like Heisha
instead of Jiang Shan?
Could it be that you like both?
Well.
Only kids make choices.
I just pretended to be a fan.
Why is he so jealous?
I like Jiang Shan, so what?
Why can't I like him?
(JS Sound Art Studio)
Thanks for the hard work.
Thanks.
Hello.
Hi, there.
M-Mr. Jiang. Please take a seat.
Lately...
I want bubble tea.
I'll get a takeout.
It's too slow.
Go get it on hand.
What would you like to drink?
No sugar. Same for him.
No sugar. The same.
Why did you come today?
Why can't I come?
I heard that someone
has been nesting in the studio.
It's so rare.
I have to see it with my own eyes.
Shan.
There's a new hotpot restaurant nearby.
Shall we try it?
I'm avoiding spice these days.
Avoiding spice.
Nice sunglasses you've got there.
What are you trying to say?
Come on. Sit here.
I have a friend.
Yeah, you have a friend.
Be serious.
Okay.
You have a friend. Go on.
I have a friend.
He asked me some questions.
I'm consulting you because you're
more experienced.
My friend
ran into his goddess in college,
but this goddess
has changed a lot.
And she doesn't remember him at all.
Do you think
he should tell her
that he's been into her?
Of course not.
Why not?
Manipulation, get it?
Manipulation?
You know why
I'm always wearing sunglasses?
To be mysterious.
To be mysterious?
Being mysterious
has the power of making people curious.
- Curious.
- Such curiosity somehow brings
the dull and stagnant relationship
between men and women
to a high level called love.
Look.
That girl doesn't remember you.
S-S-Sorry.
She doesn't remember t-that guy.
Right?
And
she's changed a lot.
First, we must figure out
why she has changed so much.
Knowing your enemy and yourself
is the key to winning.
If you don't get to know...
It's not me.
Sorry.
Y-Your friend
shouldn't rush to confess
before he figures out
anything about this girl.
Then...
Mr. Jiang.
I-I'm thirsty.
Thank you.
Mine is too sweet.
I'll get this one.
Slim chance of winning.
Alright, I will stop being
a thorn in the flesh here.
Go ahead. Bye.
My "friend".
This one is fine.
But they are sugar-free.
(JS Sound Art Studio)
That's it for today.
Thank you.
Bye.
You did well today.
Get some rest tomorrow.
Rest well.
See you around.
Be careful.
Knowing your enemy and yourself
is the key to winning.
Why are you phasing out? We're losing!
Go ahead. I'm done.
Come on, I came to your place
just to play.
Don't do this to your teammate.
Associate captain.
Pei Jun came to see An Ran.
Pei Jun came to see her?
How did you know?
An Ran told me.
Right, you're next-door neighbors now.
Back then,
she was such a sweet girl,
going out with him all the time
in her pretty high heels.
(Where do I start?)
Were they really so close
back then?
Yeah.
But she wasn't so mature back then.
She just liked older guys.
Pei Jun was
quite decent and mature.
How did they break up?
Why do you care?
Could it be that you...
Need material for the show?
Yeah.
Well,
she didn't want to mention it,
so I didn't ask.
She didn't mention it.
Why didn't you ask to show concern?
You're being narrow-minded, buddy.
You don't have to
ask about it to show concern.
Let's try another round.
Forget it. You can play alone.
(Why do I feel bored
in the office rather than the studio?)
Tian Xin, I have a proposal
that I'd like to consult with you.
What is it?
We're used to having Miss An
out of the office,
supervising the dubbing.
I'm a bit uneasy
with her here today.
I bet you're used to slacking off work.
What are we having for lunch?
Tian Xin.
I read your proposal.
Shall we discuss it?
Coming.
Take a look at it.
This page. You see the problem?
First, you forgot the basic.
All the titles should adopt
the same font and be aligned.
Otherwise, the PPT
would look unprofessional.
BP showcases the project.
Sorry, Miss An, I was careless.
I'll correct them.
Okay, take your time.
You rascal.
You harassed my employee
and stole my proposal.
I'm gonna beat you up!
(He's quite handsome when he's serious.)
Mr. Hu.
Come in.
We're working hard,
but you're playing games.
Mr. Hu, do you find it appropriate?
You only see me playing games.
It's because we're on different levels.
And the enemy got the first kill.
You're so lame.
You only see
the enemy getting the first kill.
But you don't see me
cultivating myself in the process.
Over there.
You're losing.
I'm losing all the battles,
but I won't give up.
That's how I overcome difficulties
and guide Gaishi Unparalleled
to its prime in the battles of business.
Noob. Let me do this.
Check out the character sketch.
I'll proceed if it's confirmed.
Someone's coming.
Here. I see him.
Here.
Not bad.
You're quite something.
I haven't played much,
but I'm better than you.
Here. Listen.
Use these two. And...
Upgrade this over there.
There you go.
Okay.
(Pei Jun: Mengyao, can you
ask An Ran out for me again?)
An Ran.
I thought about it.
I think I should inform you.
Look.
I shouldn't have helped Pei Jun
without informing you.
But he's been texting me all the time.
I think
even if I don't help,
he will figure something out.
That's why I'm telling you this.
I'm done as a messenger.
You'll know what to do.
Alright, I see.
Tell him that I'll decide
where to meet.
Okay.
Boss, same old. Two servings.
I'll pay you on WeChat.
Alright.
Why did you choose such a place?
It took me so much effort
to book that French restaurant.
The ingredients
are flown in from France today.
Mr. Pei, you haven't changed at all.
Ran.
I often recall the days
when we were together.
Stop calling me that.
I meant to apologize to you
in person today.
But look at the place you chose.
What about it?
You never visited places like this.
You didn't have to
make yourself suffer
just to show resentment toward me.
Mr. Pei, you're too self-centered.
Your taste could change. Why can't mine?
I know.
I hurt you back then.
I'm sorry.
But I'm back now.
Let me make it up to you
and give you the best life.
What is the best life?
We only know
what's best for us through experience.
I used to be so naive.
I really believed that
whatever you showed me
would be something I liked.
I'm actually grateful to you.
Because after we broke up,
I finally realized
what I truly want in life.
So, what you want in life
is to dine at dirty and cheap places
and mess around
with that immature young man.
I think we have
different definitions of maturity.
In my opinion,
it's quite childish
for you to keep pestering me.
I really hate to see you
end up like this.
First,
we're like from two different worlds.
Our paths don't cross.
Second, it's none of your business
what I end up being.
In fact, I asked you out today
to make things clear.
I don't need your apology.
Because I became a better person
after we broke up.
I have my dreams.
I have my friends.
My life may seem
tacky to you.
But this is what I like.
I'm so cozy in this environment.
I'm at ease.
Also, stop asking
Bai Mengyao to be the messenger.
I know you're just saying those
because you're upset.
I've said what I had to say.
Stop bothering me.
(The beauty of having a crush)
(made us look back)
(over our youthful years,)
(again and again.)
(Remember what Sanae Oikawa said)
(to Male Itsuki
after she got rejected by him?)
(The stories between boys and girls
keep repeating.)
(Visit Otaru when you're free.)
(Look for that person called Itsuki.)
(That's it for today.)
(Good night, everyone.)
Great show today.
Of course.
I'm an expert
on soothing souls of the city dwellers.
What a starry night.
You didn't finish what you said.
You said you got tired
of dating someone.
Tell me more.
Okay.
Let me provide the soul-soothing expert
with some materials.
I was young back then.
I was eager to devote everything I had
to the man I loved.
Just like a desperate gambler.
And what happened?
I lost everything.
It's not that I'm scared of failure.
It turned out that
it was easy for me to fall in love
but hard for me to snap out of it.
I've over 30.
I've been through so much.
I don't think I can accept
another person in my life
or wait to be accepted.
It's tiring to even think about it.
I don't have the strength to deal with
those twists and turns
or another utter failure.
Just like you said,
it's just fine to be alone.
I think so too.
It's not like we're failing
just because we're not with anyone.
You're not exactly successful.
Has anyone told you that
you're really bad at conversations?
So,
stop telling women older than you
to be brave and go seek love.
They didn't choose to be single
because they were not brave enough.
Then why is that?
Love is heavy.
It's tiring to carry it.
Fragment Time Boyfriend
is a project we've been planning.
With the change
in the target customers' aesthetics
and trending topics,
we've made countless modifications
to the drafts.
Very soon, Fragment Time Boyfriend
will go public
as we submit
the business proposal to be approved.
To be honest, I'm a bit nervous.
But we've come so far.
We have to pull it through
with confidence.
That's about it.
Let's try to make the case perfect.
Of course.
Miss An, I'll come up
with a new version of the sketches.
I promise, it's going to
surprise everyone.
Peng and I got two boxes of supplies
for us to work overtime.
Rest assured.
Let me make some
newly-invented refreshing tea
for all of you.
Alright.
My turn! I'll follow up
on the player's feedback
and the information
integrated by big data
to please the players.
Okay.
Miss An, I...
I-I...
I forgot.
Root for Fragment Time Boyfriend.
We got this!
Come on, won't you cheer?
Miss An,
I want the color lighter here.
It's a bit too bright right now.
No problem.
Miss An, please sign
the financial statement.
Let me see.
Miss An, is the drawing fine?
Nice face.
It's a bit complicated here.
The demo of Chapter One is out.
Want to try it?
Come on.
The demo is out. Get online.
Where is it?
Peng, the visual effect is good.
Check it out.
Let's see.
Wu, come and see.
- Here.
- Nice hues, huh?
It's amazing.
Great boot-up animation.
Who sent all these?
So generous.
If I'm not mistaken,
the graphics card must be for me.
Two graphics tablets.
Peng, how come
there happens to be two of these?
There must be something for me.
You got the desserts I bought?
These are desserts?
You bought these?
Miss An, you got these for us?
You really think so?
- No.
- Not really.
Really?
Who got these?
Hello?
Miss An, you got the delivery?
These are the gifts for proposals
from innovative startups.
It's our new regulation.
Wish you success.
Please thank Miss Lan
and the shareholders for us.
We will do our best.
Bye.
These are from Lansheng Investment.
Open them.
Here we go.
Graphics tablets. My goodness.
A whole box of tea leaves.
I'll take it.
The biggest one is gone.
Let me help. It's so heavy.
Sure.
Peng.
It paints better scenes with that.
Try it.
(Everything will go well.)
Hello?
Got the delivery?
I was about to call you.
I made myself clear last time.
Why are you still pestering me?
I just want to help your company.
Mr. Pei, our proposal
will be approved anyway.
Please stop sending us things
in the name of Miss Lan.
Bai Mengyao.
What's wrong?
It's yours now.
A fountain pen?
Doesn't it look nice?
Pei Jun gave it to you?
Return it if you don't like it.
Why would I?
He can give me gifts all he wants.
I can decide what to do with them.
Think twice. I'll leave it here.
Why are you here?
I thought we'd meet at the studio.
I came to tell you that
I'm sick today and won't go to work.
What's wrong?
Do you want a ride?
Let's get some medicine.
We'll carry on with work
once you're better.
No.
Why are you so willful?
Deal with that fountain pen
first, Miss An.
I'm sick. I'm leaving.
You could have just called me.
Just give me a break.
(Cefixime Capsules)
Little brat.
Why are you staring?
Mr. Heisha certainly looks cool
when he's at work.
What's wrong? Blushing?
Are you going to stay there?
Are you better today?
Kind of.
These are letters from your audience?
Yeah. And they're handwritten.
Handwritten?
That's rare nowadays.
What did they write?
Mostly their feedback on Heisha Time
and the dubbing I worked on.
Some of them are their love stories.
I would pick from those stories
and share them in the show.
This is one way for us to communicate.
These are the read ones?
These are unread?
That's right.
What about that?
It's also unread. Want to read it?
I can read it?
(Sir Heisha, your voice is awful.)
What's wrong?
It turns out your audience
is people of all ages.
Sir Heisha, your voice is awful.
So awful.
Are we gonna dub?
Of course.
Let's go.
(Please don't be sad.)
(You don't have to hide your old wounds)
(and swallow your sorrow alone.)
(I will stand by you)
(and create new memories with you.)
(I know you're working hard
to achieve your dream.)
(I support you no matter what.)
(For me, you're always the best.)
♪The movie told an undulating
and complicated story♪
♪And there is only one possibility
between us♪
♪We entangle ourselves in love♪
♪What are you thinking about♪
♪Where should I stand♪
♪From the strange to the familiar♪
♪From the familiar to the strange,
it's an inevitable part of love♪
♪I keep silent♪
♪Watching you leave♪
♪But there's nothing I can do♪
♪You seem to be giving up on me♪
♪I'm chasing after you♪
♪Until the sun sets♪
♪When will you stop♪
♪To admire the scenery with me♪
♪Do you know it all doesn't come easy♪
♪I'm chasing after you♪
♪Until the dawn♪
♪If you don't remember♪
♪I can help you recall it♪
♪Refresh your memory♪
♪And recall it♪
♪The movie told an undulating
and complicated story♪
♪And there is only one possibility
between us♪
♪We entangle ourselves in love♪
♪What are you thinking about♪
♪Where should I stand♪
♪From the strange to the familiar♪
♪From the familiar to the strange,
it's an inevitable part of love♪
♪I keep silent♪
♪Watching you leave♪
♪But there's nothing I can do♪
♪You seem to be giving up on me♪
♪I'm chasing after you♪
♪Until the sun sets♪
♪When will you stop♪
♪To admire the scenery with me♪
♪Do you know it all doesn't come easy♪
♪I'm chasing after you♪
♪Until the dawn♪
♪If you don't remember♪
♪I can help you recall it♪
♪Refresh your memory♪
♪And recall it♪