=Phoenix's Homecoming=
=Episode 12=
Your Majesty.
I wouldn't dare.
With me here,
you can do anything.
Your Majesty.
Having watched the show you organized,
I suddenly recall an urgent matter.
Speak.
This concerns state secrets.
Unrelated personnel should...
Understood.
I thought you had lost all interest
in court affairs.
You worthless fool.
Had you not neglected me, Father,
why would I ask
Jia Cheng to forge
officials' handwriting
to gain leverage
and secure my position?
You took in Jia Cheng
and Lu Chengfeng
to threaten me
when you're cornered.
Did you think you could deceive me?
Plotting to betray me?
Do you remember
that you bear the Huo name?
The Huo name?
Ever since I became Empress,
have you helped me the slightest?
Search your conscience, Father.
Do you see me as your daughter?
I'm nothing but a pawn to you.
A pawn?
Have I ever held a useless pawn?
I've always been sharp.
How did my daughter end up being a fool?
If you could conceive an imperial heir,
why would I need
to support that idiot Prince Mu?
If Yuan were still here...
That's right!
I'm no match for my brother, anyway.
His death serves me well.
Now I'm the only pawn you have left.
What can you do to me?
Jia Cheng is still
locked up at the academy.
Find a way to kill him.
This isn't a negotiation.
I'm giving you an order.
Fail me again,
and you'll cease
to be Empress.
Oh, Father.
Never forget I'm your daughter.
I inherited your cruelty.
(Lu Chengfeng lost.)
(Jia Cheng defected.)
When the Sheng army's name is cleared,
Jia Cheng will face his doom.
I've informed His Majesty
of Chancellor Huo's treason.
His Majesty will feign ignorance
and let me gather evidence first.
For convenience,
he reinstated me as Grand Tutor.
Is something wrong?
He still can't let you go
and wants you back at the palace.
This aligns with our plan.
Don't worry about it.
But after tomorrow,
you'll walk on thin ice every day.
I truly can't bear...
My decision is final.
Say no more.
I made this fan for you.
Fiddle with it at leisure,
or wield it
as a weapon in danger.
The palace is fraught with danger.
I won't be there...
Take care.
Alright.
I'll be careful.
Take care.
Tracking the explosives is critical.
I'm sure it's going to be risky.
We'll fight separately
once we part ways.
Huaiyong.
Take good care.
What did you call me?
Huaiyong.
(By the Mandate of Heaven,
the Emperor decrees.)
(I sorely miss my sister,
the Grand Princess,)
(and summon Sheng Yunfei,
the third daughter of the Sheng family,)
(to the palace.)
(She shall chant sutras
for the Grand Princess's blessings)
(and reside in the Weiyang Palace,
the Grand Princess's former abode.)
(By Imperial Decree.)
Set my sovereign above Yao and Shun,
and restore customs to purity.
Upon my ascension today,
I appoint Princess Changyi
as Grand Princess of the Chen State.
She shall act as regent.
(Chancellor Huo plots treason.)
(So the traitor)
(is him.)
(He framed the Sheng army of treason.)
(Now, I shall settle)
(all scores together.)
I am guilty.
(Since Heaven has granted me
a second chance at life,)
(I will uncover the truth on my own.)
(With my own hands,)
(I shall drag every last one of them)
(down to the underworld
to suffer for eternity.)
Go away.
Get lost.
(For ten years,
fire burned unceasingly.)
(Red walls and golden tiles
remain the same.)
(I'll make you repay a hundredfold)
(of the bone-deep agony
from those flames.)
(I, Sheng Yunlin,)
(have returned.)
What brings you here?
I have sinned and hereby
present my plea for death.
Your Majesty.
(Plea for Death)
Please grant me death.
The world praises you for your virtue
and benevolence.
How have you sinned?
I didn't save the Grand Princess
from the fire at the Weiyang Palace.
Though I copy scriptures and pray,
I can't free myself
from the insufferable guilt.
Rest assured.
During the Weiyang Palace fire,
you broke three ribs
trying to save the Grand Princess.
Had I suspected you,
the Huo family wouldn't have remained.
If you're still haunted by guilt,
pray more often for the Grand Princess.
Thank you for your compassion,
Your Majesty.
I shall copy Buddhist scriptures
five hundred times
for the Grand Princess.
Yunfei.
The hairpin you wear bears a resemblance
to one belonging
to the late Grand Princess.
What a pity.
She passed away long ago.
Those who look like her
are nothing but substitutes.
You remind me of my sister.
So that's why.
Thank you for your affection.
I bet your sister
must have loved you dearly.
Indeed.
When I was young,
she sheltered me beneath her wings.
I thought ascending the throne
would ease her burdens.
I aspire to be the great ruler
she had in mind.
You are a great ruler.
No doubt, you are now everything
your sister hoped you would become.
But my sister
is gone forever.
It's all my fault.
I caused her death.
Sister.
Do you know
how much I miss you?
♪The wind rises, snow falls♪
♪To stain endless remorse with red♪
♪No regrets in moves made.
Let the game unfold♪
♪Sorrow and joy intertwined♪
♪Yet we can't escape karma♪
♪Lament this fleeting life♪
♪So elusive♪
♪So indistinct♪
♪Resent farewells♪
♪Remembering each other♪
♪Love can't be extinguished♪
♪Unwilling to accept♪
♪Rewriting the story♪
♪And praying♪
♪A long-cherished wish♪
♪In a daze♪
♪Suddenly it's those years again♪
♪How I wish to relive my old dreams♪
♪Rewrite those torn pages♪