It's all over.
­
Where did Jeong Hui Yeong go?
What?
Huh?
­
Is this all you've been doing?
I'm already dead anyway.
I already died in that park!
What's the point of living like this?
My life is completely ruined!
So, if you die,
what will that solve?
If you die and disappear,
it means nothing.
You are alive, Jeong Hui Yeong.
You're not dead.
­
What is it? Did you get possessed by a spirit guide?
With what's happening right now, and also the fact that you knew that Sin Jeong Sook would go to KSH Cosmetic Surgery.
I asked you to find photos
of the acid attack on the district office employee two years ago. Right?
I am indebted to that person.
...after ruining her model face like this,
What are you going to do about it?
She was flustered when she saw the photos of other acid attack victims.
Is this woman the victim?
Perhaps Sin Jeong Sook probably didn't know Jeong Hui Yeong well.
So she must have needed to confirm if she did her job properly.
Madam, it's me.
Could you please open the door?
She must have thought she needed to prove it
to the person who ordered her to do that.
You are impressive as always.
Yes, I know.
Because it seemed different from the victim's photo shown at the police station,
you went to the hospital yourself?
I was worried I made a mistake.
Goodness, you are so naive.
The articles are everywhere.
Anyway, well done.
But did you have to come at such a late hour?
You could have come later.
I'm sorry.
I was in such a hurry for money.
Have you already spent the advance you received?
In just a week?
Oh, Madam Sin.
I didn't know you were interested in that sort of thing.
I guess
that would make you desperate for money.
The smell of leather is so nice.
That's right.
It doesn't seem to suit you.
The remaining payment is one thousand.
With this, the payment is all settled.
Aren't you leaving?
What are you doing, Ajumma?
Please leave now.
Ajumma.
A-Ajumma!
What are you doing?
I pretended to be crazy and splashed hydrochloric acid once,
and it stripped away the fear.
It's thrilling, isn't it?
The fact that you can ruin someone's life with just a flick of the wrist.
Don't look at me that way.
It's not like I am a bug.
So annoying.
Ajumma!
No, Madam Sin,
you must have had a tough time yesterday and today.
First, go home and rest.
How could I possibly sleep comfortably?
Look...
at what we did to that Jeong Hui Yeong girl.
Us, you say?
That's right, us…
Jeong Hui Yeong had an affair with my husband.
And just to take revenge,
I had to pretend to be crazy later on.
Then, I got a lawyer.
Somehow, claiming mental and physical weakness got me out.
Yes, right here, your voice is all recorded, you see?
Seriously, Ajumma, how could you?
Madam.
You're as beautiful as Jeong Hui Yeong, Madam.
Huh?
Compensation for the mental harm from my guilt.
Please do that for me a bit longer.
Sir, that black box,
could you just…
Seo Yoon Ha.
Wife of Kim Ji Hyeok, president of JH Model Agency.
Ms. Jeong Hui Yeong was a model under that agency until last year.
The fact of giving a large sum of cash
to the person who splashed hydrochloric acid...
means there was some sort of transaction between Seo Yoon Ha and Sin Jeong Sook.
On social media and personal broadcasts,
the reason Jeong Hui Yeong appeared at that modeling agency last year
is rumored to be because of a scandal with the agency's president.
So, due to that kind of relationship
between Jeong Hui Yeong and Kim Ji Hyeok,
Seo Yoon Ha, the wife, harbored ill feelings and just asked Sin Jeong Sook—
I should stitch those lips shut.
Who told you to investigate based on rumors?
It's a matter that can cause secondary harm to the victim.
Moreover, Kim Ji Hyeok is currently incarcerated due to a sexual harassment case last year.
Be careful with your words.
I apologize.
But securing evidence is the key.
If they brush it off as if that cash is a bonus
given to the housekeeper, there's nothing we can do.
That woman must be hiding something.
Looking at the card statements, her spending is no joke.
I wonder if she stashed something away in case she ever ran low on funds.
We can't even search and seize it since it's still a vague conjecture.
Seeing her coming out with money tonight,
it seems she has an urgent need for it.
Start by looking into her recent movements.
There must be something to dig into.
Yes, Ma'am.
Yes, hello?
Dr. Cha Jeong Woo?
Is Jeong Hui Yeong okay?
En garde!  (On your guard)
Êtes prêts?  (Are you ready?)
Allez!  (Let's go!)
À droite.  (The right)
Prêts?  (Ready?)
Allez!  (Let's go!)
Halte!  (Halt)
Attention!
Salut!  (Salute)
He let you off easy again.
I did not.
Are you kidding?
With your skills, you could have easily avoided this.
Sometimes it seems like you parry just to get stabbed.
- Want a drink?
- Next time.
Then, we'll go ahead.
♫  I can't forget the first day I saw you  ♫
♫  The wind was so cold. After your awkward hello  ♫
You worked hard today, too.
♫  Frozen, you were all I could see  ♫
♫  Every night when I missed you  ♫
♫  We would spend all night on the phone  ♫
♫  Time passed too quickly  ♫
♫  While we talked and kept sipping our drinks
♫  We've seen our last sunset  ♫
♫  I wish I could go back to those times with you  ♫
♫  When I saw you  ♫
♫  I want to go back to that dream  ♫
♫  When you were sitting there in that chair  ♫
♫  I'm walking outside of your thousand miles  ♫
♫  To the place where I saw you   ♫
I told you to stop drinking.
And why don't you answer the phone?
Yeah, here.
Goodness.
Yes, this is the customer's phone.
All right, you did a great job today, so consider this a reward.
Why are you so anxious? Like a puppy that needs to poop.
The detective gave him a lift herself.
Was there another unfortunate incident with Jeong Woo at the hospital?
Maybe?
What else happened besides yesterday's event?
It's been particularly bad these past few days.
Then why didn't you stay a bit with him? Why bother so much about a silly blind date?
S-Silly?
Excuse me!
I'm trying to communicate with these various people.
One shouldn't belittle this open-mindedness, especially a lawyer.
Right.
You've been devoted to just one guy since your school days. What would you know
about my feelings?
- Darn, just like that!
- Here it is, right on time! Jeong Woo's car.
Oh, my! Sorry for the trouble.
Catching criminals by day, running as a substitute driver by night.
How did you end up driving Director Cha's car, too?
Did you two drink together?
Of course not.
I called him because of work, by coincidence.
- Hurry and take care of him for me.
- Okay.
Jeong Woo, how much did you drink?
Jeong Woo, come to your senses. Jeong Woo!
Be careful.
Come here.
We meet again like this.
The three of you are friends, I see.
Yes, take care.
Taking care of crime victims,
Jeong Woo…
No. How long does Director Cha have to do this?
That's not something I can confirm.
Why do you ask?
It seems there were some issues with a victim under treatment.
It's not that there were problems,
but rather that the existing problems were resolved, no?
Whatever the case,
dealing with crime victims won't be easy for Director Cha.
Director Cha, too,
is a crime victim.
He lost his fiancée...
to a criminal case seven years ago.
Meeting with crime victims
must be constantly reopening old wounds he thought he had dealt with.
Isn't it about time to forget now?
- Why?
- About Sin Jeong Sook.
There's something unusual about her recent movements.
Unusual? Like what?
She frequently visited the hospital.
A plastic surgery clinic.
We found records of an appointment, too.
Really?
­
You want your eyes done like this?
Yes, I would like to have slightly thicker double eyelids.
You don't have drooping eyelids,
and it seems like you don't have any discomfort in terms of shape or function.
Also, such a flamboyant outline is not in trend these days either.
Well, I don't really know about trends or anything.
Can't you just do it like this for me?
What is the reason you want the surgery?
No, I…
Do I have to explain even that to get plastic surgery?
I-It's my first time coming to a place like this.
I need to know what kind of problem you want to improve, whether it's function or form,
so I can proceed with the surgery more effectively.
Well, just…
I just need to look like this person.
The wife's lover.
From the husband's point of view,
by having surgery to look like the lover his wife fell in love with,
doesn't it mean he wants to win back his wife?
A little while ago, I heard it also happened at the hospital where my friend works.
A woman showed a picture of his mistress and asked to be made similar.
Can you really bring back someone who has left by doing that?
Of course not!
You can't bring them back.
If you could capture a departed heart by changing the face,
I would have had that plastic surgery hundreds of times.
I wonder who?
Who would you have wanted to catch so badly?
Did you have such a pure-hearted love, Director Han?
First love?
What?
Why are you all so serious about other people's love affairs?
Anyway, this plastic surgery clinic never has a calm day.
And come to think of it, that patient Jeong Hui Yeong, the one with the affair…
Hey!
That's not a confirmed fact yet.
Please let me know when the facts come out.
Are you planning to just leave again today?
Perhaps, do you have
any connection to the patient?
Seeing that you came here twice, it seems
like you have something you must want to talk about.
She is a friend of our daughter.
But for what…
Do you know Kim Ji Hyeok by any chance?
The CEO of JH Model Agency.
Yes, what about that person?
It's just my own thought, however,
perhaps this
might be related to Kim Ji Hyeok.
Why do you think so?
Our daughter, too,
was a model in his company.
The person who splashed me with hydrochloric acid...
is the woman who works at Kim Ji Hyeok's house?
She's been working as a housekeeper for quite a long time.
Last night,
the place the suspect visited after leaving this hospital
was the house of CEO Kim Ji Hyeok.
That person… is in prison now.
I heard that the model who died by suicide
after the sexual harassment scandal with Kim Ji Hyeok last year
was very close to you.
She is related to that case too, right? You too…
Enough.
Please leave now.
You can tell us everything now.
We'll catch the real criminal.
But that's not the real end, is it?
Both you and your friend...
shouldn't be misunderstood anymore. Right?
­
Excluding the deposit of 300,000 won,
you need to pay the surgery fee of 7.5 million won.
I've seen that before?
Yeah, that's right.
Even the bundles tied with new bill bands in the envelope.
Look at this. It's the same money, isn't it?
You received it from Seo Yoon Ha, right?
Of course.
The madam just gave it to me as a bonus.
You didn't receive it after showing photos of the victim?
That… Going to the hospital yesterday was…
to apologize to the victim because I was feeling sorry.
First, let's go to the station together.
I request your voluntary accompaniment regarding the supplementary investigation.
Ah, no way.
I-I-I can't go.
I must have the surgery no matter what.
After the surgery, you'll see how much I've changed.
I mean, to show off to that person.
So you must cooperate even more with the investigation.
That way, you can get the surgery as soon as possible.
No, the date is…
If you resolve it quickly and let us know,
we'll make arrangements for you to have the surgery immediately.
Yes.
Money…
Ms. Seo Yoon Ha,
you are under emergency arrest on charges of instigating special bodily harm against Jeong Hui Yeong.
Sin Jeong Sook spilled everything.
That crazy b*tch is really…
Over there… right here.
The deal with the madam has all been recorded.
Uh… And this.
It's a letter sent to the madam
from her husband in prison.
It has the whole crime plan written down.
If I cooperate with the investigation, I can get the surgery. Right?
Right?
Jeong Hui Yeong, that girl.
Do you know how shameless and audacious that woman is?
When a man does big things in society, he can make mistakes.
But to report it so quickly?
After all we'd done to support her.
The fact that Mr. Kim Ji Hyeok sexually harassed Ms. Jeong Hui Yeong.
Are you admitting it?
What are you talking about?
That's what Jeong Hui Yeong said?
She's a victim, too?
No, it's not her!
She reported it even though she wasn't a victim!
My husband is also exploding with anger in prison—
So, because Ms. Jeong Hui Yeong is a whistleblower,
you're saying she committed the crime?
And you planned the crime in advance with Mr. Kim Ji Hyeok?
You might as well just keep your mouth shut.
Thank you for detailing everything from the motive to the process of the crime.
It's being recorded well, isn't it?
Ms. Seo Yoon Ha,
this time, you won't be able to get out.
The terrible thing you did, I'll make sure you receive proper punishment.
It's Kim Ji Hyeok!
Don't you have anything to say to the victim?
Is there another accomplice?
A case that was thought to be a crime of someone with mental disability
turned out to be a meticulously planned revenge crime.
Kim, who was in prison last year for charges
of sexual harassment, harbored a grudge.
While exchanging letters with his wife, while in prison,
he is known to have meticulously planned the crime.
In the process, he used the housemaid Ms. Sin
to abet the crime, and
it is known that he even attempted to destroy evidence.
Please don't do this, Boss.
Please!
Sir, I have something to say about that contract issue.
Why? What's the matter?
That is…
We can talk about it later.
I'll apply some peripheral vasodilators for you.
Wow, this is crazy.
For someone who detests meddling in others' affairs.
Exchanging letters with his wife,
it was revealed that the crime was meticulously planned.
Manager Yang, could you please look at this?
What is it? Why?
Have you seen the news?
What news?
About patient Jeong Hui Yeong.
They say she is a whistleblower. A whistleblower.
Pardon?
Oh, dear.
Spreading rumors without even verifying the facts.
Who goes around blabbering rumors as if they are true?
Do you know who it is?
Oh, my.
Just really bad people.
Director Cha.
What kind of surgery are you preparing for that is making you look so serious?
Mind your own business. It's not your patient.
Right, just take care of your own patients.
Why bother caring about someone else's patient, right?
Pay some attention to your patients.
Still, as a doctor specializing in victims, you should know at least this much.
It's not important information for the patient's treatment.
Some people never really change.
Right?
It's Jeong Hui Yeong.
I guess he was paying attention.
Are you going to the police station?
They say the person who ordered the crime is in the police station near here.
Are you going to chase after them and stab them with that?
Don't worry about it.
Even if you stabbed them with that, you probably couldn't kill them.
That's ring forceps for holding gauze during dressing.
Instead of wasting your time on nonsense, get a consultation for your scars.
Will that make this go away?
Of course...
We can't get rid of it completely.
Even if it's covered with a graft.
A graft?
A skin graft.
That's what I came to talk about.
If you're going to get revenge, make it a real revenge.
Don't think about giving up your life like the assailants want.
We can schedule a time for surgery consultation immediately.
Ah, hello?
This is the beauty model selection committee.
Are you feeling all right?
Yes.
What's the matter?
Well… I'm contacting you regarding the final recording of the audition.
I guess… it would be difficult for you to participate, right?
Let's see…
KSH Plastic Surgery.
The article about Director Cha Jeong Woo's reconstructive surgery for a crime victim…
There's none.
Why isn't it here?
Why is this missing?
Oh, Manager Yang!
Has our article not been published yet?
Ah, I talked a lot to Reporter Kim about it.
Why hasn't this been turned into an article?
She's the final candidate for the model contest.
It seems like it would be quite an issue.
It's too early, the surgery is today.
We should at least have an interview with the patient after the surgery
for it to be meaningful, don't you think?
Then, to make sure we can nail down the before-and-after photo materials,
get the pictures or interview before the surgery. Understood?
Why?
Director Cha isn't performing the surgery for that reason, is he?
What is this? Am I doing this just for my own benefit?
I also want to quickly clear the disgrace concerning Director Cha.
I know.
But you don't have to worry about that.
Because sincerity has a way of getting through.
What do you mean by sincerity?
I'm talking about compassion for the patient.
Whether in the emergency room before,
or here at the plastic surgery clinic,
doesn't it seem Director Cha's sincerity toward patients remains unchanged?
Beginning the patient Jeong Hui Yeong's autologous skin graft surgery.
We don't need any more debridement.
Give me the local anesthesia.
I will do the skin harvest.
Thank you for your hard work.
Are you here to get the surgery records?
If you give them to me, I'll be thankful.
They'll be useful for corroborating the victim's damages.
I'll mention it, please take them.
Thank you.
No matter how much we solve cases and arrest criminals,
the police can't directly help the victims recover.
But when a dedicated doctor steps in to assist in the recovery—
I'm just doing what we do in plastic surgery.
Come on, that can't be all it is.
Not only are there scars on the face,
but wouldn't it have contributed to the healing of Jeong Hui Yeong's heart, too?
While treating external wounds, it also helps heal the internal wounds.
That's why they call plastic surgery "psychosurgery," right?
Huh? You seem embarrassed.
Ah, wait a minute!
The face of someone who did a good thing is really…
Smile.
Get your sugar refill, too.
He is embarrassed.
I got a call from Sergeant Choi.
They say Jeong Hui Yeong will be discharged tomorrow.
The surgery went well.
Of course, they must have taken good care of her.
That Dr. Cha Jeong Woo.
I heard that when Ms. Jeong Hui Yeong went up to the rooftop,
he had left work but then suddenly turned his car around to come back.
It's like he knew Ms. Jeong Hui Yeong's situation perfectly.
He must have empathized with the victim's feeling of emptiness.
Emptiness?
The police investigate to solve cases.
When you see it directly from the side,
it can feel futile from the victim's perspective.
What's going to change by doing that?
You can't turn it back to before the crime, anyway.
But how would Doctor Cha Jeong Woo know that feeling?
Because what you see in a person isn't everything.
Oh, it seems like you know something.
There's something I want to know.
What is it? What?
How's the video of the car thief in Yeoksam-dong coming along?
I said I'd look into it.
That's right.
That, too, needs to be checked quickly as cases pour in like a flood.
On your way home, take a look around the theft location.
I'll try to check the video footage near Mr. Nam Gi Taek's house.
Yes.
But if the two really are the same person,
and if it's someone who holds a grudge against Mr. Cha Jeong Woo,
he might appear around him again.
That's worrying.
If they're not the same person,
I hope it was just my misunderstanding.
I'll eat well.
You've worked hard.
­
Hello, did you make a reservation?
I don't have a reservation, but could I possibly have a consultation for surgery?
Hmm… What kind of surgery are you considering?
My eyes.
I'm not sure if it's possible.
- Yes.
- Operating room number 2 is ready.
Understood.
Starting anesthesia, please give the midazolam.
Patient, do you feel a bit dizzy?
Yes…
Please give the local anesthesia.
Corneal shield, please.
Number 15.
You want to remove the double eyelids?
Yes, I want to have monolids.
Is that kind of operation not possible?
By making an incision right above the eyelashes,
some people do get it removed, occasionally.
However, depending on the height or thickness of the double eyelid,
the possibility and method of surgery may vary.
So, it might not be possible?
You would have to consult with the director to know for sure.
Do you have a particular eye shape in mind?
Something like a sample photo.
You can show it to me.
Yes, here it is.
This person…
The surgery went well.
Swelling may worsen for about 2 to 3 days,
but it will gradually subside, so please don't worry too much.
Yes, thank you.
It turned out well like the photo I showed you, right?
Now, you should look a bit more like your son.
Excuse me?
No, how did you…
Min-Min Seong! How did you get here?
Darn, what's this? Your eyes are all swollen!
Ah, why are you here?
What? Where are you trying to get surgery?
I don't know!
I'm sorry.
I thought I was the only one having a hard time.
Doctor!
Since my son came all this way,
how about some surgery to make his nose just like mine?
No, my nose is better!
Ah, what do you mean, your nose is better? Dad's nose is better.
- I'm telling you my nose is better.
- No, my nose is prettier.
Geez, really, you brat.
Are you okay?
Ever since he found out about the adoption a while ago,
I've heard the good father-son relationship became strained.
They both went their separate ways.
He is not even his real dad, so "why interfere? Mind your own business."
But how did you know?
That the two of them were father and son?
The hand around the shoulder in the photo
turned out to be Kim Hyeon Seok's.
I just need to look like this person.
A photo taken together is still a photo, but
who else but family would look at you with such a gaze?
You're still the same.
Still?
Something like that.
Anyway, you've worked hard.
The unspoken feelings between the father and son
were clearly conveyed by you through the surgery.
Oh, my…
God!
It turned out so well!
A real jackpot!
It is definitely different from being a former model.
Exactly. What do we do?
What are you doing?
What are you all looking at so intently?
Manager, take a look at this.
I think this is all because of Director Cha.
Huh? Oh, that person!
She's so pretty, isn't she?
Oh, my, what's going on?
Although I received a skin graft,
I can't go back to exactly how I was before.
I was about to give up, however
someone told me that
if I gave up like this,
I would be letting the assailants decide my life.
So I challenged myself.
My life. These scars, too.
I decided not to hide them and to show them as they are.
New face, new dream!
This is it! This is what I was aiming for.
What a touching story this is.
Touching stories like this don't come along every day.
Director,
did you gather everyone here to talk about that?
Now, just wait a second.
If Jeong Hui Yeong receives the award,
and we continue to take care of the aftermath,
where else in the world can you find such promotional effects?
So, let's all come together with one heart,
and support Jeong Hui Yeong.
Got it? Let's watch it.
The rankings have finally been decided.
It's the result of combining the audience votes and the judges' scores.
We will now announce
K Beauty Model Contest's honorable 3rd place.
The prestigious 3rd place goes to
contestant number 13! Choi Mi Soon! Congratulations.
Congratulatory applause, everyone.
I will now continue with the announcement of 2nd place.
Second place,
number 23! Go Hui Jin!
Congratulations!
I will go out first.
Uh, hey!
First place… Only the first place remains.
Nobody can leave.
Would she ever take first place?
There's no rule saying she can't!
But there's no rule saying she will either.
Challenge! K Beauty Model Contest!
The final and most honorable first place,
number 29, Choi Soo Ah! Congratulations!
I told you, didn't I? This?
That becoming first place isn't easy, you know?
In the end, everything is just about appearance.
She must have fallen behind in the public vote because of the early rumors.
Ah, this can't just end like this! Right?
Lastly, Ms. Jeong Hui Yeong,
who had the courage to stand up against injustice despite all disadvantages,
and who did not yield in the face of unfortunate circumstances,
showing a spirit of challenge,
and embodying what Château Cornell pursues,
the true essence of a woman.
Therefore, Château Cornell has decided to select Ms. Jeong Hui Yeong
as the representative model for the East Asia region.
We just received the information from our headquarters!
Congratulations, Ms. Jeong Hui Yeong!
- You said it couldn't be done.
- What's with that face?
It's done!
It's settled!
The plastic surgery, superbly done, changed everything, including the heart.
The face of someone who did a good thing is really…
Smile.
Get your sugar refill, too.
­
Beautiful!
Such a beautiful fragrance!
Good.
Hey, Jeong Woo, won't you try a bit more?
- What?
- The victim's dedicated doctor, I mean.
It strangely seems to suit you, even though it doesn't look like it will.
No, I mean, the partner doctor in Bintan is still on hold.
It's just that I didn't want you to feel disappointed.
It's because I have a surgery.
Is he doing it?
Or is he not?
Ugh, I sprayed too much.
Where have you been?
You were nowhere to be seen all night.
It's the guy who stole a car in Yeoksam-dong recently.
Did anything new come out?
I heard a video came out, so I brought it.
Is there anything that could identify the person?
They didn't wear a mask here.
The quality is good, too…
It's hard to recognize the face accurately since he's wearing a pressed-down cap.
Do you have anyone in mind?
What?
No, I'm not sure.
But somehow, it feels familiar.
Really? Who?
Among those you've caught before, is there anyone who looks similar?
Well… I'll have to think about it.
I think I need to go somewhere.
Send me this video.
Yes.
Good work!
Who are you?
Lee Min Hyeong!
It's been a while.
You've become prettier since I last saw you.
♫  I can't forget the first day I saw you  ♫
♫  The wind was so cold  ♫
♫  After your awkward hello  ♫
♫  Frozen, you were all I could see  ♫
Do you have any idea who it might be after watching this?
Don't you have anything to talk to me about?
Please help!
I'm a police officer. What's the matter?
The delivery person who just ran out…
You are under arrest for trespassing.
So, are you saying the wound wasn't caused by a falling fragment embedding itself?
Judging only by the shape of the wound, that's correct.
What the heck is this jerk doing?
You've been investigating assuming, I was the culprit from the beginning, haven't you?
Is Detective Lee Min Hyeong with you now?
Are you there?
Are you crazy?
Lee Min Hyeong.
♫  I'm walking outside of your...  ♫