Previous Episode
I looked up the news from twenty years ago.
One boy made it out alive then as well.
Previous Episode
You’re that boy.
Please give me another chance.
Previous Episode
If I sleep with you,
will you stay?
Previous Episode
What’s going on between you and Jean?
Are you leaving us to be with him?
I haven’t…
If I sleep with you,
will you stay?
Oh, Boss.
You don’t have to go that far.
What?
Does this mean you’re not leaving us to be with Jean?
Even though I’m dating Jean,
I’m not going to leave Sweet Day.
I still want to be with everyone here.
Besides,
I haven’t found you your first love yet.
I was scared you were going to leave us.
Do you know how stressed out I was?
That’s why I would even sleep with you.
I mean trade my body.
I’m so honored that you would trade your body for me.
You’re the cutest, Boss.’
On second thought,
I should kiss you once and take my gain.
Go away.
It’s your gain but my loss.
Thanat Lowkhunsombat
Prachaya Ruangrod
Purim Rattanaruangwattana
Patara Eksangkul
Juthapich Indrajundra
DIRECTED BY PANNARES RUCHIRANANTA
SUCRÉ MEANS SWEET, FAMILLE MEANS FAMILY
I’m late, Pooh Bear!
Don’t run in the house, Baby Pig.
I’ll wear these later in the car.
Just a minute.
Piglet, you can share this with your friends at school.
Thanks, Weir.
Let’s go, Pooh Bear.
Baby Pig, you need to wear your socks.
I’ll put them on in the car.
The car key!
Where’s the car key?
Here it is.
Thank you so much.
Run, Baby Pig!
This dad and daughter started making noise since early morning.
Darling, could you pass me the salt?
Here you are.
What does that couple think my house is?
Jean, I know how to do it.
Should we, Uncle?
Good idea.
What do you think?
Still as yummy as ever.
Both the pasta and your feelings are still the same, right?
I feel the same as well.
You’re amazed at my skills?
I’m annoyed.
You have your own house.
I don’t get why you came here.
I came because of this cutie.
Is everyone in France this lame?
If you want to know,
why don’t you go live there?
Actually, that’s why I invited Jean here today.
Huh?
What’s this about?
Why didn’t you discuss it with me first?
Krating is my guy.
Come on, Boss.
I’ve seen how talented Krating is at making desserts
and Jean agrees
that if Krating gets the opportunity to learn and practice, he’ll go far.
That’s why he wants to send Krating to a dessert school in France.
Don’t worry.
I’ll pay for all your expenses.
What?
You really have talent.
Ever since I started making desserts,
you’re the only person after Weir that I see potential in.
That won’t be necessary.
I can pay for Krating’s expenses myself.
But I don’t want…
Really?
You’re so kind, Boss. I knew it.
But it will be expensive.
Are you sure it’s not unaffordable for you?
The word ‘unaffordable’ is not in my dictionary.
Then I’ll contact the school in France
and let you know about the expenses later.
Hold on.
Do I really have to go study abroad?
Krating,
my lessons and their lessons are very different.
If you go there,
I guarantee you will learn so much more.
But I don’t want to…
You said you wanted to become a good pastry chef, didn’t you?
Trust me.
Krating,
come here.
What’s going on, Uncle?
This is Mr. Pierre,
your French tutor.
Do I have to take a lesson now?
Yes.
Weir and I want you to learn the language first
so you won’t struggle when you get there.
But I don’t want to.
Bonjour.
My name is Pierre.
No, Uncle. I don’t want to learn.
You have to.
I’ve already paid for it.
Then ask for a refund.
Hey, you can’t talk like that to someone who supports your study.
Krating,
don’t be stubborn.
I thought you said you wanted to become the best pastry chef.
But I…
No buts.
I will support you to become a very good chef.
You will become even better than that golden-haired, small-eyed Jean.
Boss,
did you say that because you’re jealous?
I said that because I hate your boyfriend.
I don’t know why you keep doing this when you already have a boyfriend.
Boss.
Ah, beh, seh, deh, eh, eff, jheh.
Ah, beh, seh, deh, e, f, g.
No, I didn’t pronounce them that way.
Let’s try again.
Ah, beh, seh, deh, eh, eff, jheh.
It’s difficult.
No one can remember them in such a short time.
[Saying French alphabets]
You can go on until Z, can’t you?
What’s up, Krating?
Is it okay if I don’t go to France?
Krating,
I told you that if you wanted to become a talented chef,
you have to study there
and you have to take it very seriously.
But I don’t…
Hello, Jean.
I’m home.
No, I haven’t eaten anything.
Okay, I can leave right away.
Sorry.
It’s always hard at first, Krating.
Keep going.
I know you can do it.
If you have any problems or don’t understand something,
you can ask me,
okay?
Please close the door for me.
What’s up?
I don’t understand anything in my lessons.
Can I stop taking French?
Pay more attention.
I’m not smart.
I’m stupid.
Krating,
there are no stupid people in this world,
only people who don’t try.
But I…
You have to stop with the buts.
Stop with the excuses.
And you’ll become better than that golden-haired, small-eyed Jean.
I want to see you become better than him.
I feel satisfied just thinking about it.
You only care about Jean.
What?
He’s not the only one I think about.
Hey! Krating!
If this is about learning French,
I understand.
Young Master once told me that sometimes humans can be unbelievably smart.
We can understand difficult things easily.
But for some people, it’s not always the case.
I think maybe you and I are one of those people.
Actually, that’s not the only thing I’m worried about.
I just don’t want to go anywhere anymore.
I could explain
but no one would understand.
No one is like me.
Baby Pig is calling.
Please excuse me.
Baby Pig!
I’m the only one in this house who’s never had a family.
I’m hungry.
Me too.
Hello.
Can I take your order?
Hey, Piglet. What are you doing here?
I’m helping Dad work.
Dad?
This is my dad.
Pooh Bear,
this is Ms. Im-Aim, my class teacher.
Hello, Ms. Im-Aim.
I’m Baby Pig’s parent.
I mean Piglet’s.
Hello, Piglet’s dad.
What would you guys like to order?
I’ll quickly get them for you.
Oh, okay, can I have the afternoon tea set?
I’d like a glass of peach tea, please.
Okay.
Let’s go get the desserts ready, Pooh Bear.
I didn’t know Mr. Pooh had a daughter.
They look so different from each other,
True.
Mr. Tinnapop.
Hi.
Sorry I’m late.
Have you been waiting long?
Not at all.	We just arrived.
Mone, this is Mr. Tinnapop, the new science teacher.
He’ll be helping me teach.
You can call me Toomtam.
Alright, feel free to order anything you’d like.
Think of this as a welcome treat.
Okay. These all look so good.
Here’s your order.
Wow, this looks so good.
This looks so good.
Are you okay?
Oh, Piglet, this is Mr. Toomtam.
He’s going to help me teach soon.
Hello, teacher.
Please try the canelé.
It’s our best seller.
Let’s eat, shall we?
Yes.
It’s really good.
I’ve never had a canelé this good anywhere.
Did Chef Weir make this?
No, Krating did.
Really? Krating?
Wow.
It’s yummy.
It’s good, isn’t it?
I think Krating will go far.
That’s good.
When you return from France, you can be our other chef,
alright, Krating?
If you want to ask people what they do for work,
you have to say “Quelle est votre profession?”
Could you repeat after me?
Quelle est votre pro…
pro fession?
Try again.
You have to pronounce it this way:
Quelle est votre profession?
Je suis pâtissier.
I’m a pastry chef.
Quelle… quelle est votre profession?
Why can’t you remember it?
It’s hard.
More like you’re not trying hard,
Ting Nong Noy. (silly words)
If you can’t even remember an easy phrase like this,
how are you going to learn everything else?
You’ll never be a pastry chef, Ting Nong Noy.
How much longer are you going to call me Ting Nong Noy?
I said my name is Krating.
You’re Ting Nong Noy.
Krating, calm down!
Fight me.
Krating, stop!
Mr. Krating.
He won’t stop calling me Ting Nong Noy.
I said my name is Krating.
Krating!
Calm down.
Stop.
You’re supposed to be learning, not being a thug.
He’s right, Krating.
You can’t do this to other people.
He’s rude!
How could he say that?
Because you act like this,
he’s right to criticize you.
Yes! I suck!
I don’t have parents.
This has nothing to do with that, Krating.
Pierre is your tutor.
If you’re still like this, how can you go to France?
Why is everyone sending me away?
I don’t want to go to France.
Don’t you understand?
I’m not going.
Hey! Ting!
Calm down, Young Master.
What is wrong with him?
Where is Krating?
It’s late. Why isn’t he back yet?
Weir,
please call him.
Okay.
His phone is off. I can’t get hold of him.
I’ll go look for him.
I’ll drive you, Young Master.
No,
you stay with Weir.
Alright.
Here.
Did you think you’re a lead guy in a Korean series?
I was scared you’d be grazed by that car. By the way,
why won’t you go home?
I don’t have a home to go back to.
Hey, I was just asking.
Do you really have to be dramatic?
I’ve never had a home.
Never had a family.
No one wants me.
Don’t be sad.
You’re a grown man, aren’t you?
You can take care of yourself.
Besides, everyone at the café takes care of you like family.
But they’re not my real family, are they?
All my life,
I’ve never understood the meaning of family.
The closest thing to that was the boxing academy.
But now I can’t box anymore.
I couldn’t stay there forever.
Why not?
Coach Choke seems to love you.
But he has his real family.
I’m just a boxer in the academy.
Ever since I came to Sweet Day,
I feel like it’s my other home.
Like it’s my family.
But I’m probably the only one who feels that way.
In the end,
I’m an outsider, as always.
What makes you think that?
Everyone keeps trying to send me away.
They want to send me abroad to study.
Oh.
You’re so s and s.
What do you mean?
Stupid and silly.
Hey, you’re supposed to be comforting me in a situation like this,
not laughing at me.
I’m laughing at your silliness.
Look, do you really think that
people who want to get rid of you or think of you as an outsider
would invest in your study abroad?
Listen.
People who don’t really love or care for you wouldn’t want good things for you like they do.
Same with Coach Choke.
Everyone thinks of you as family.
Only you are too silly to see it.
You misunderstood what family is.
Can I help you?
Do you want to apply for our course? We’re closed now.
No, Coach.
I’m the owner of the café Krating is working at.
Oh.
Sweet Day?
Is something the matter?
Why did you come here so late?
Has Krating come here at all?
I haven’t seen him.
Did he stir up trouble?
No,
but we’re in a fight.
So Krating didn’t go home.
No.
I just want to send Krating to a dessert school in France
but it seems like he doesn’t want to go
even though this opportunity could help him become a talented pastry chef.
I really don’t understand him.
He said he wanted to become a world class chef
but why is he acting like this?
He probably thinks you want to get rid of him.
Get rid of him?
How am I getting rid of him?
Krating might be a fighter and a strong man,
but he’s a sensitive soul.
He likes to think he’s an orphan who’s loved and wanted by no one.
He probably thinks of you guys as family
and thinks you’re sending him away because you want to get rid of him.
Don’t worry.
When he comes to his senses, he will come back.
He’s like a son to me.
Please take care of him.
Of course.
Krating.
Guys,
I’m sorry.
I canceled your French tutoring sessions
and if you don’t want to study in France,
you don’t have to go.
I’m sorry for forcing you to do this without asking what you want.
I want you to go not because I want to get rid of you.
I just want my first and only student to become successful and get the best thing.
Why are you crying?
You’re important to us, Krating.
Our café can’t do without you.
You’re a part of Sweet Day.
You’re a part of our family.
From now on, you don’t have to feel bad
and run anywhere.
Understand?
Hey.
You don’t have to hug me.
Fine, just this once.
I’ve made my decision.
I’m going to study in France.
I will become a talented chef like you.
Young Master!
Krating!
Hey.What’s wrong with you?
Why are you crying?
I can’t breathe.
Krating, from now on, if there’s anything you feel uncomfortable with,
be honest with us.
We’re family now.
We help each other.
Got it.
Ouch!
That’s for making me worried.
And now I have to go to trouble to find you a new tutor.
You don’t have to.
I found one myself.
Who?
Okay.
This word, sucré, means sweet.
For example, le gâteau est très sucré.
This sentence means the cake is very sweet.
Repeat after me.
Sucré.
Correct.
Very good, Ting Nong Noy.
Actually, Ting Nong Noy sounds kind of cute.
Right? I told you so.
Then I’ll keep calling you that.
Some people just look cute no matter what they do.
But cute people are usually taken.
Hey, are you here to tutor me or do what?
Did you get it?
How do we pronounce that word?
I need your advice on something.
What is it?
It’s about	Krating.
Actually, we could pass as Krating’s parents.
Krating is our son. You’re the father.
And I’m the mother.
Your imagination has run wild.
What’s it about then?
I’m going to invite a special guest to our café soon.
Who’s this special guest?
You don’t have to know yet.
Just know that he really wants to try Krating’s desserts.
What do you think Krating should make him?
He actually makes very yummy French toast.
but if he has to make a special dish for a special person,
why don’t we make him come up with his own recipe?
Good idea.
Can you guide him then?
Sure.
Ms. Nuan.
Madam!
This way!
Wait a minute, Ms. Nuan.
You guys.
Can we speak to Mr. Tert?
No.
Why do you want to speak to him now?
Look,
we’re so sorry we abandoned your son’s case back then.
But now we just want to know if Mr. Tert kidnapped the kids 21 years ago?
What are you talking about?
The boy Mr. Tert kidnapped looked like your son.
[The Return of the Children Kidnapper, A 10-Year-Old Boy is Missing]
Get out!
Or I’ll call the police you’re trespassing in my house.
Leave!
Ms. Nuan.
Ms. Nuan, wait.
Tert and Nuan must be involved in the children’s kidnapping.
Yes. I think so too.
What do we do next?
We have to follow this to the end.
Otherwise, worse things will surely follow.
Do you remember my lesson on how to make French toast?
That’s the basics.
Today I want you to create your own recipe for French toast.
Why do I have to?
Because it’ll be a special recipe for a special guest.
I really want to know who this special guest is.
Alright, let’s not waste time.
Alright, let’s not waste time.We should get started.
We should get started.
Remember, Krating.
It’s good to follow the original recipe
but it’s also important to create a new one.
You have to be able to add your own personality to the dish.
Just like artists who have their own signatures and styles,
chefs like us have our own tastes and ingredients.
Okay, let’s get started.
Why are we having this crazy guy teach him?
Krating, hold that tight.
Krating, hold that tight.That’s it.
That’s it.
Focus.
Try it.
I think it’s still too simple.
That one looks burnt.
Not bad.
I think it could be even better.
So good.
The milk is so rich.
Who’s this special guest, Uncle?
You’ll know soon enough.
Is it a movie star?
Tell me please.
Is it a man or a woman?
There he is.
Coach.
Our special guest today is Coach Choke.
Do your best, Krating.
We all want him to try your dessert
before you leave to study in France.
Where’s the dessert you’re making me?
I prepared my stomach for it.
I haven’t eaten anything since morning.
Give me a few minutes.
I’ll go get it ready.
This way, please.
Here you are.
Wow.
This is a French toast pudding.
Whoa.
I didn’t know you speak such good English.
It’s only normal
for a soon-to-be top pastry chef
for a soon-to-be top pastry chefto speak good English.
to speak good English.
But I think I saw you practicing in the kitchen earlier.
Please have a bite, Coach.
I came up with this dish myself.
Let me see if it’s any good.
What do you think, Coach?
Mm.
Mm?
Why are you crying?
Is it that bad?
I’m so proud.
Proud?
Your dessert is very much to my taste.
I’m really proud of you.
I believe you’re going to become the most talented pastry chef in the world.
I’m sure of it.
I have one more thing to tell you.
You are not alone.
You have people around you
who love and worry about you all the time
both at the boxing academy and this café.
To everyone,
you’re family.
And family has nothing to do with blood.
It has to do with bond.
Understand?
Coach.
You can do it.
I believe in you.
Why did you come here again?
Ms. Nuan, please let us speak to Mr. Tert.
You should leave.
Leave us alone.
But if you let this go on,
bad things could happen to the kids again.
How dare you talk about this again?
Twenty-one years ago, you were the ones who made things turn out this way.
You chose to sit by and do nothing.
That’s why my son is dead.
Where are you going?
Stay with Daddy.
Stay with Daddy.There’s a kid inside.
There’s a kid inside.
Stop!
I said stop!
I said stop!Get out of my house!
Get out of my house!
Stop!
Open your mouth, son,
so I can feed you.
You don’t want to eat it?
I’ll eat it then.
It’s good.
Next Episode
Sorry.
View.
Next Episode
This is my younger sister View.
Next EpisodeMom wants to see you.
Next Episode
Mom wants to see you.
My mom is the reason I’m afraid of women.
Next Episode
Weir.
Mom.
Next Episode
-I can’t keep Tert under control anymore.
Next Episode-What did he do?
Next Episode
-What did he do?
-You were the one who kidnapped the kids to our house, right?
Next Episode