Why are there so many people?
Previous Episode
Are you Chef Weir?
Chef Weir, can we interview you?
Previous Episode
How do you feel that the Old Butter unfairly stole your victory?
The Old Butter is owned by Nim.
Previous Episode
You think that this competition is fishy, isn’t it?
Phueak Nae page exposed that the Old butter gave a bribe to the producer.
Previous Episode
Our Sweet Day café. We won.
Hey, why are you here?
Why did you come outside late at night?
Hey, what’s wrong?
What happened?
Did someone hurt you?
Dessert.
Help me.
That person gave me a dessert to eat.
Who gave it to you?
What dessert?
Thanat Lowkhunsombat
Prachaya Ruangroj
Purim Rattanaruangwattana
Patara Eksangkul
Juthapich Indrajundra
DIRECTED BY PANNARES RUCHIRANANTA
[BITTERSWEET LOVE]
Lieutenant, why did the girl walk around here alone?
The reason is still unknown.
When I ran into her,
her condition was not quite good.
How is she now?
She’s safe.
She’s under the care of the doctor now.
There’s nothing to worry about.
Did she see the face of the kidnapper?
Come on.
Please tell us a bit.
Alright.
I’ll answer your question.
When it happened,
the kid was drugged,
so she didn’t have much consciousness.
Let alone recognized the kidnapper’s face,
the girl couldn’t even remember how she escaped.
Alright. Please leave now.
Your whole family, please leave already.
I will continue to inspect the scene.
We’ve just arrived.
Please.
Leaving or not?
Not leaving, right?
Fine.
I’m leaving first.
See you later.
Goodbye.
We even came here.
Did we get any information, huh?
Here you are.
This is your order and your change.
But I guess it’s better if the change is converted into love.
If you take a photo with me and check-in at our café on social media,
you’ll get a special discount.
Here you are.
This is Crème Brûlée
Pooh Bear!
Baby Pig!
Wow.
This is so yummy.
It is, right?
It’s freshly baked.
You’re the first person to try it.PL
Really?
Can I have one more?
Sure.
Why didn’t you tell me that you’re working at a dessert café?
You know I like desserts, don’t you?
I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean to do it.
Chef,
Since when did that uncle bodyguard have a girlfriend?
I don’t know either.
But she is still too young.
Isn’t it illegal?
So, Pooh actually likes high school girls, doesn’t he?
Pooh, can you please send me off to school?
I told my teacher that
I had to do an errand with my family in the morning.
I came here just to see you.
Baby Pig,
I told you already that lying is bad.
Don’t do this again.
Alright.
I won’t do it again.
Young master, can I send Baby Pig off to school?
I will hurry back here.
Sure.
Let’s go now.
Please carry the bag for me.
Boss,
since when did Pooh have a girlfriend?
Why didn’t I know about it?
He’s dating a girl.
Wicked.
Piglet is not in high school.
She’s only in grade 8.
What?
Grade 8?
Well,
we ran out of cookies.
What a teen.
Pooh.
Boss told us that you love that student so much. Right?
Yes.
I do love my Baby Pig so much.
But that’s not appropriate, is it?
She’s only in grade 8.
Why?
Why can’t I love a grade 8 student?
You will be sent to jail.
But Baby Pig…
I mean Piglet is my daughter.
What?
Your daughter?
I’m her dad.
You mean a daughter by blood?
Yes.
That’s right.
She’s his daughter for real.
He gave birth to her.
What’s going on here?
I’m totally confused now.
Does this mean you’re already married?
No, I’m not.
I’m not married.
So your girlfriend got pregnant before marriage?
Pooh donated his sperm to Piglet’s mother.
Her name is Tiwa.
Why did you end up donating your sperm to her?
Well…
Are you alright?
I am.
But can you help me with one thing?
What is it?
Please have a baby with me.
Huh?
Please.
I’m begging you.
I really want to become a mother.
If that’s what you want…
Alright.
Well, Tiwa has been haunted by her past memory.
Her dad abused her.
She doesn’t want a husband,
and she doesn’t want to spend her life with any man either.
But she still wanted to have a baby.
I understood her suffering,
so I agreed to help.
You’re such a good man.
You’d better stop being silly.
I agreed with Uncle Bodyguard.
So, your daughter was born by an artificial insemination?
No.
It was a natural process.
How can a person like him know how to ‘do’ it?
Yes.
You mean natural for real?
Only once.
Mom, on your upcoming birthday,
let’s go celebrate at a cake café, shall we?
Alright.
Is there any gift that you want?
Anything will do.
But I…
Piglet.
Don’t you see that I’m working?
Can we talk later?
Alright.
Mom,
I want to ask for your permission.
What’s that?
Who’s that?
Who?
Baby Pig?!
From today, I’ll stay here with you.
Piglet, what are you thinking?
Well, I just came here to stay with Pooh and Uncle Punn,
but I didn’t expect that there would be lots of people like this.
This is so warm.
Won’t your mom scold you for this?
I told my mom
that I would be going on a school’s field trip for 3 days and 2 nights.
My mom helped me pack herself.
Baby Pig, I told you that lying is bad, didn’t I?
But mom already allowed me to come,
though it’s a different story.
Tiwa must be super angry, Young Master.
True.
We will all be in trouble for sure.
So you two mustn’t let mom find out.
Or else, she will hit me for sure.
Won’t you feel sorry for me?
It’s just for three days.
I promise I will behave.
I won’t be naughty at all.
Please.
Actually, I came here because I want to bake a birthday cake for my mom.
I want her to be happy.
But Pooh and Uncle Poon don’t agree to help,
I will learn it from somewhere else instead.
But now I can’t go back home anyway.
If I do, mom will find out that I lied to her.
I guess I must sleep under a pedestrian bridge.
Under the pedestrian bride?
You feel sorry for me, right?
Nope.
It’s obvious you said this to make us feel sorry for you.
You’re completely different from your dad.
How?
I resemble him.
You guys are similar in height.
But I guess your intelligence level resembles that of your mom.
So… I can stay here, right?
No!
Please let me stay here.
I really want to bake a birthday cake for my mom.
Mom is always busy with her work.
She doesn’t pay attention to me at all.
I just want to grab her attention.
Do you want to bake a cake for your mom that much?
Yes.
Sweet Day’s cakes are the most delicious ones I’ve ever had.
If I can bake such a delicious cake,
mom will be so surprised.
Mom rarely gets to eat good food.
Please help me.
I’m begging you.
It’s just for three days.
It seems she came with a good intention.
Fine.
Well then, let’s start learning, shall we?
Good.
I’ll join.
I’ll also help with the cake turntable.
Uncle Poon?
Let’s go.
I don’t understand why the kidnapper changed the target.
According to previous cases, the kidnapper usually chose marginal kids
who rarely receives attention from others.
But this time, the kidnapper decided to kidnap the kid that has a family.
What is the reason?
Is that because the wanted to change the kidnap pattern.
in order to confuse to police team?
Probably, there’s more than one kidnapper.
Plus, the kidnapper chose to kidnap Lert Anan School’s student.
This change in pattern is suspicious.
Though I still can’t figure out why the kidnapper did so,
I’m certain that the murder must be living near the exercise ground.
That’s because it’s impossible for a little kid who was drugged
to walk by foot for more than 3 kilometers.
That includes the Sweet Day Café.
Is it possible that it’s the same kidnapper from the previous case?
That café’s dessert bag was found at the scene.
That café is not very far from the scene.
[Sweet Day Café’]
You let them do it on their own like this.
Do you think they will make it, Chef?
That uncle seems lame,
and Piglet is…
I think you put too much force.
But that dad and his daughter want to succeed by themselves.
But now I guess they will ruin it themselves.
They’ve unsuccessfully cracked so many eggs already.
But it seems they really put a lot effort in it.
Look at them.
Looking at how they’re doing now,
I guess it will take two days.
To be able to bake a cake?
To destroy our café.
Whose turn is it today to clean the kitchen?
It’s your turn, Chef.
Mesa, younger sister of Meena, a student in my class?
Yes. She was kidnapped.
I think the kidnapper is that desserts murderer.
because Mesa mentioned that she was forced to eat a dessert.
But nobody in this school knows about this.
I guess they want to conceal it
because if it becomes the news,
school’s reputation will be totally ruined.
Is this a school or what?
School officials are more concerned about reputation than students’ safety.
I guess I must do something.
Hey, I need your help.
What is it?
Please arrange Mesa and her family to meet me.
If I get to talk to them,
I may get new information
apart from what the police have been gathering so far.
Well, I’m not sure whether they will agree to talk.
But I’ll try.
Thanks a lot.
If we let it continues,
more students could be kidnapped.
How is it?
It’s super delicious.
Are you interested in opening a restaurant at my school?
So, I can eat the dish you cook every day.
I’m glad you like it,
but I need to work for this café.
Or else, you won’t get to eat delicious desserts.
What a regret.
Meena and I always discuss that school’s food is not delicious at all.
I’ll complain about it at school,
accusing them for cooking such tasteless food for Baby Pig.
Uncle, chill out.
Don’t exaggerate.
Baby Pig, apart from food,
do you face any other problems?
When I’m with Meena,
others like to believe that I’m her older sister.
They think that I’m already in grade 12,
while I’m actually half a year younger than Meena.
It’s just that I’m a bit taller than her.
I think it’s not just a bit.
Uncle Punn!
My friends also told me that I’m weird once.
How?
Well, I have been growing up differently.
I’m not living with my dad.
Mom rarely drops me off at school and picks me up
like other parents do.
But I think Tiwa loves you a lot.
I know that she loves me.
She’s just trying to teach me how to be independent.
But recently,
mom has been so busy with her work.
She doesn’t play with me.
She doesn’t pay attention to me at all.
I start to think that
she probably doesn’t love anymore.
She doesn’t want to play with me.
Nobody wants to play with me.
People think I’m no longer a kid,
but I actually am!
Don’t cry.
Eat this.
No!
Piglet, look here.
Piglet, don’t cry.
For your three days living with us here,
be happiest.
Alright?
Get under the blanket.
Is the temperature too cold?
Nope. It’s just right.
Alright. Sleep now.
If you need anything, let me know.
Sweet dreams.
Can you sleep in this room with me tonight?
Sure.
If I can have you sleep here every night,
it will be so good.
Wow.
Are these the same cookies I had the other day?
Yes.
These are French butter cookies called Sablé Breton.
But in this recipe, I will add dried longan
to add some Thai flavor to the cookies.
So I name this, Golden Longan Sablé Breton.
That’s all?
That would be all for its general recipe.
But for our café, we have a secret recipe.
What is it?
Just use this a little. Our cookies will be delicious, mellow,
with a nice touch of milky aroma.
Have a bite.
Wow, it’s really good.
When I get to taste a delicious thing like this,
I would like to become a great baker like you soon.
I want my mother to see what I can do.
Go ahead. Call Pooh to learn too.
Pooh Bear, come learn baking together.
Actually, Uncle Pooh looks like a good father.
I know,
right? He looks so warm.
Pooh looks happy when he is with his daughter.
Young Master,
may I ask you to look after my Baby Pig for a second.
I need to take a shower.
Why do you need to ask?
She’s not going anywhere.
I won’t run away.
I will come back and play with you right away.
Wait.
Can I have your phone? I would like to play a game.
Sure.
Thank you.
I’ll be right back.
Uncle Punn.
How to make two people fall for each other?
Why are you asking me?
Are you into someone?
No. No.
I want my father and my mother to love each other like other parents.
But I think…
Here, Uncle Punn.
Can you pretend to be Pooh Bear and send a sweet chat to my mother?
He told me you are flirty.
I’m sure you are a pro at this.
Well, Piglet.
I think love is a matter between two people.
Uncle Punn.
Didn’t you tell me you would do what I wanted during these 3 days?
Are you a liar?
I am not.
Then, text my mother.
Should I?
Go ahead. This must be pretty easy for you.
(I may have nothing to enchant you,
but I’ll do what it takes to make you fall for me.)
(No matter how vast the sky is, my small heart belongs to you.)
(My face may look cool, but my heart for you is warm.)
(From Pooh Bear)
What has gotten into him?
Pooh Bear?
Is it him?
Ma’am. They are from the Phuak Nae news page.
Nice to meet you.
Hi, ma’am.
Thank you so much for allowing us to see you today.
Ms. Im-aim told me about your searching for the kidnapper who abducted my daughter.
We would like to ask both Mesa and you.
We may get some info that leads to the kidnapper.
Would you mind if we ask you?
May I?
Do you remember the day that Mesa disappeared?
What happened that day?
Normally, Mesa waits with her older sister to go home together.
But that day, Mesa disappeared.
She was not at the pick-up point like usual.
Before we realized that Mesa was gone,
several hours had passed.
Where is your usual pick-up point?
It depends.
Mostly, it’s around this waiting area here.
Mesa.
May I ask you something?
You don’t need to speak to answer me.
Just nodding or shaking your head will do.
Okay?
Do you remember what happened that day?
Where did the kidnapper take you to?
Did you see the kidnapper before?
Did he give you some sweets?
Mesa.
Do you happen to remember the face of the kidnapper?
His hair is grey.
What do you mean?
He’s an old man.
An old man?
I’ll cook your favorite food.
Then we’ll have cake together.
Tert.
I think you should stop.
Don’t do this.
Leave me alone.
Our son must be happiest.
It’ll be done soon.
My cake is done.
Give her a big hand.
I’ll put it in a box for you.
It’ll be in good condition when you show this to your mother.
Thank you, Weir.
Let me help, Chef.
Thank you, my handsome Krating.
Piglet, how about we take a photo together?
No, thank you, Uncle Punn.
Why am I the only person who is an uncle here?
Pooh Bear said I must pay respect to his Young Master.
At first, I would like to call you lord.
But Pooh Bear said it was a bit too much.
So I call you Uncle Punn.
Pooh Bear, let’s celebrate mom’s birthday together this year.
So we are all together, you, mom, and me.
Uh…
Please join us. So we are together as a whole family.
Please.
Don’t you want to be with mom and me?
No. It’s not that. I just…
Piglet.
Mom.
Please calm down first, Tiwa.
How can I keep calm?
My daughter lied to me that she was on a school field trip.
Instead, she is living in a house full of men?
I find those messages suspicious, that’s how I know.
What messages?
The tacky messages you sent to flirt with me.
But I never do anything to flirt with you.
I know it’s not you.
But it’s this man and Piglet.
I know that it’s you.
because Pooh has never called himself “Pooh Bear” with me.
I’m sorry.
It’s all my fault.
Tiwa, listen. Baby Pig is...
Don’t try to defend her.
What kind of a grown man are you?
How could you let her lie to me?
Is this the right thing to do?
You cannot be a good father if you support your daughter on something like this.
Piglet, go home.
No. I’m not going.
You never care about me when I’m with you there.
Piglet.
I just made a cake for you as a birthday present.
I want you to be proud and look at me.
Is it so wrong if I want to have a father.
and a mother just like everybody else.
Baby Pig.
Do you know,
during these past 3 days,
I feel so happy that I get to be with you.
Honestly, I wish I could be with you every day.
I would like to drive you to school.
I would like to cook for you.
I would like to tuck you in every night.
I would like to be a good father to you.
But…
I’m not ready right now.
Why, Pooh Bear?
I don’t know if I could really be a good father to you,
or if I could be good enough to be in your life,
and Tiwa’s life.
Please understand me, Baby Pig.
But I want us to be together.
I want a complete family
with a father, a mother,
and me.
Can’t you do this for me?
Baby Pig.
A complete family doesn’t always consist of a father, a mother, and a child.
Some families do not have everyone living together.
But they can still be complete families.
Do you know why?
Why?
Because of love.
The love everyone has for other members of the family.
I don’t understand.
Do you think I love you?
Do you think that your mother loves you?
Do you love me and Tiwa?
I do.
Very much.
Then you already have a complete family.
Though we cannot be together,
we can always have love for each other.
The meaning of family,
doesn’t mean the number of members in the family.
It’s the feeling and bond we have.
In the old days,
I lived with my father and mother.
But you know what?
I didn’t feel like I belonged in the family.
My father liked to hit me and my mother.
I understand now.
You are the best father I could ever have.
I love you, Baby Pig.
Stop crying.
You stop crying too.
Ms. Tiwa.
Yes?
This is the cake that Baby Pig and I made together.
(Love Mommy Tiwa, from Piglet and Pooh Bear)
Thanks.
I’m sorry that I let Baby Pig lie to you.
I’m truly sorry.
Enough. Stop bowing to me.
I’m sorry for bowing too long.
You’re still the same.
I’m sorry for being the same.
I’ve been really busy lately.
If Piglet wants to stay over at your place later on,
you must tell me in advance. Understood?
Can I, Mom?
But we must have a video call every time.
Thank you so much.
I will take good care of her.
And I will make a video call to you every time.
I mean Piglet, not you.
I don’t need you to do that.
I’m sorry.
Enough. Let’s go, dear.
Ms. Tiwa.
Happy birthday in advance.
Bye-bye.
Keep going, bro.
I will.
You must become the best dad of the year.
I will try. Thank you.
If you feel like crying, you can lean on my chest.
No, thanks.
I don’t feel like crying at all.
Don’t be in denial.
It’s obvious that you are being emotional right now.
I’m not.
Young Master is tight-lipped.
Found it!
(10-years-old boy murdered ruthlessly and left sideway. Murderer at large.)
Do you think that this case might be related to the recent murders?
21 years ago, your dad and I followed this case.
Kids got kidnapped and murdered.
The murderer left desserts near the bodies.
The murderer is still at large until now.
Maybe, it’s this same murderer who is responsible for the recent crimes.
And a year after that,
a boy got kidnapped.
But he survived.
Honey.
If we can find this boy,
we may get some leads.
The surviving kid is named Punnapat Dechrachatanan.
Why do I find this name familiar?
Could it be…
The owner of Sweet Day café!
Hello.
Welcome to our café.
Bonjour.
Kid,
is Chef Weir here?
Weir?
Mon amour.
It’s been a while, honey.
I’ve been missing you.
What is all this?
Weir, who is this man?
I’m the owner of this café.
Who are you?
Me?
I’m the owner of Weir.
You? Weir’s boss?
So?
What does it have anything to do with you?
Everything about Weir is my matter.
I don’t want Weir to waste his time in a café that…
doesn’t deserve Weir.
Hey, Mister.
What do you mean?
Jean, please go.
This is not a good time. I need to work.
Please go.
Fine. See you later, honey.
I miss you.
Bye.
I don’t like him.
Me too.
Who is he, Weir?
Jean is my pastry mentor.
He owns l'oeuf ou la poule that I worked for in France.
And…
he’s also my ex.
What?
Your ex?