=Snow Fall=
=Episode 3=
(This drama is purely fictional.)
Mr. Shen.
I am...
Mr. Li.
I remember you.
It's been at least half a month
since we last saw each other, hasn't it?
Did you miss me?
I was ill.
What did you have?
Was it serious?
I almost died.
I wonder which hospital you go to.
The doctor's skill sure is remarkable.
Well, it's not the doctor's skills
that was remarkable.
I was just lucky.
They say that good fortune follows
after escaping death, Mr. Shen.
I wonder if I might have the honor
of sharing a meal with you, Mr. Shen.
Sure.
That's great.
I've long admired you, Mr. Shen.
I've always wanted
to be friends with you,
but you never gave me the opportunity.
I'm truly honored
that you're giving me
this opportunity today.
How about this?
I'll buy you a meal.
There's a restaurant called
Dongya Restaurant.
It's not too crowded and quiet.
How does that sound?
When?
How about tomorrow?
Sure.
That's great.
Tomorrow night at Dongya Restaurant,
I'll be waiting for you.
Mr. Li, go home and get a good rest
to be well-prepared.
Tomorrow night is a big night for you.
You probably won't be able
to sleep tonight.
- Splendid!
- Marvelous!
Mr. Situ,
how can you dance so well?
Miss Jin,
are we considered acquainted now?
Of course.
From now on, you're my friend.
I saw you with Li Yingliang
a moment ago.
Are you crazy?
He's out for your blood
and you still want to meet him?
What's there to be afraid of?
Besides, you're overthinking it.
We had a good chat and even made plans
to have dinner together.
Dinner?
What could you possibly talk about?
If he tries to kill me,
I'll kill him back.
If he wants to talk,
I'm open to it.
So if he kills you once,
you'll kill him once in return?
Is that too much?
Not at all.
Your dancing is quite impressive.
You saw me dance?
I thought you were indifferent to me.
Tell you what.
I had a chat with Jingxue
and we danced to quite a few songs.
Jingxue?
Yes.
Her name is Jingxue.
What's wrong with calling her
by her name?
Is that too much?
Not at all.
But to be with Jingxue
costs a lot.
Well, you are my savior.
I owe you this.
(Tomorrow night is a big night for you.)
You probably won't be able
to sleep tonight.
(Yongjia Li)
Mr. Shen won't keep hiring you
or me forever.
But I assure you
that you won't find a better employer
in Haidong.
- Yes.
- Mr. Wang.
He's very generous.
A day's work for him is worth
a month's work for someone else.
I understand.
Don't speak so softly.
Mr. Shen prefers us
to speak confidently.
This is the living room.
You're not allowed to stay
in the Shen Mansion after dark.
You must leave before nightfall.
Although the house doesn't have
many things,
it's filled with valuable antiques.
Be careful while you're working.
This is Mr. Shen's bedroom
and his study room,
which is a restricted area.
There is a dedicated person
for cleaning it.
You're not allowed to enter.
Also,
stay away from the locked rooms.
Mr. Shen is quite unusual.
Doesn't he feel scared living
in such a large place alone?
Don't gossip about Mr. Shen
behind his back.
Yes.
Good morning, Mr. Shen.
Good morning.
Stop staring.
From now on, you'll be responsible
for cleaning the ground floor
and maintaining the garden.
Since it's been snowing,
remember to clear the snow
from the garden.
Go along now.
(Series of Wild Animal Attacks
on Locals)
Youwen,
come to the house.
I need to talk to you.
(Report from Haidong Radio Station.)
(Yesterday, a severe incident occurred
where a wild animal attacked)
(hikers on the rocky hills
near the city outskirts.)
(By the time the police arrived,)
(the scene was only left
with a pool of blood)
(and no bodies.)
(We would like to remind the city's residents
that climbing mountains carries risks...)
Miss Mi,
Mr. Mi had someone send
these new clothes to you
for the winter.
Madam Zhang, fetch me some water.
I want to water this plant.
Here you go.
Miss Mi,
these new clothes are
beautiful and warm.
Mr. Mi still cares about you.
Mr. Shen,
there have been two incidents of
a wild animal attacking locals this month.
It's just outside the city
on the rocky hills.
The people who were attacked
were all hikers.
I went to check it out
right after hearing the news.
I happened to meet the police
who were searching the mountain.
But after a long search,
they found nothing.
After the newspaper reported it,
the wild animal seemed
to have disappeared
and hasn't appeared again.
The police think that since
the wild animal has disappeared,
there's no need to continue
the investigation
or cause unnecessary panic.
They've just let the matter drop.
But I believe
the truth is out there.
They just don't want to find it.
What has become of the victims?
All of them had died.
There are three of them.
They all died from severe blood loss.
One, who was in good health,
developed a high fever for several days
and was delirious.
He died in the end.
What did he say?
He kept shouting for help
and saying that a ghost was going
to eat him.
Excessive blood loss
and trying to eat them.
Trying to eat them?
(Could it be him?)
Mr. Shen,
look at this.
I took these in secret.
Could this wild animal be a leopard?
Is it possible
that it started attacking humans
because it was starving
in the cold winter?
But that doesn't add up.
If it were a leopard,
the bodies wouldn't be intact.
We need to publish more warnings
so people stay indoors.
The weather's too cold.
They should avoid deserted places.
Okay, don't worry.
I'll make sure it's handled properly.
Go.
I'll get going now, Mr. Shen.
Okay.
(If it really is him,)
(I must find a way to stop him.)
(I can't let him harm the innocent.)
You're a worthless burden.
You still have the nerve
to grow plants?
Madam Zhang, you should leave.
My mother is about to give me a beating.
But...
Madam.
This plant sure is beautiful.
It's a pity
that you can't see it.
Tell me.
Who gave you this plant?
Is it that wretched eighth mistress?
Give it to me.
Give it!
I said, give it to me!
Give it to me!
Did I say you can grow a plant?
Did I?
Are you going to keep it?
Are you?
Who says you can grow it?
Get up!
Tell me!
You dare to retaliate, huh?
What are you trying to do?
You dare to defy me?
You even dare to hit me!
Leave!
Just you wait!
Where's the key?
Lock the door from the outside.
Do you hear me?
Don't give her water
or food! Let her starve!
How dare she fight me back.
I may not be able to control others.
But I can certainly control her!
Starve her!
How dare she hit me!
Do you hear me?
Yes, Madam.
I said, do you hear me?
She dares to hit me.
- Mr. Shen.
Mr. Shen hasn't eaten anything all day.
He just had a sip of water and left.
How can living like
Mr. Shen be enjoyable?
Don't you agree?
He dresses simply,
with minimal colors.
He doesn't care about food or clothing.
It seems all he cares about is
this big house.
But you all know
that Mr. Shen's
belongings are getting fewer,
and he has few friends or family left.
So
his life isn't
as carefree as ours.
Enough talking. Get back to work.
Come on.
Go.
(Moxi Restaurant)
Hurry up.
Are you saying Shen Zhiheng is alive?
Yes, not only did he survive, but he also made
a public appearance at a charity banquet,
donating a hundred thousand
and stealing the spotlight.
Now the whole
of Haidong is talking about it.
How could he possibly be alive?
Didn't they say
he was beaten to a pulp?
he was run over by a car
repeatedly
and turned into mush?
How could he possibly still be alive?
Where's Li Yingliang?
The Superintendent is asking you
a question.
Mr. Li and Shen Zhiheng are together
at Dongya Restaurant.
So,
Li Yingliang knew
that Shen Zhiheng wasn't dead.
Not only did he fail to report this,
but he's even meeting Shen Zhiheng
in secret.
Great, just great.
How loyal.
Let's join in the fun.
Yes, sir.
This way, please.
He didn't even bring any bodyguards.
He's either incredibly confident
or just naive.
Mr. Shen.
Mr. Li.
I'm truly delighted
that you could grace us
with your presence today.
You're too kind, Mr. Li.
Please drop the formalities.
I'm not inviting you
as the chairman.
I'd rather be friends with you.
As you know,
I've long admired you
and wanted to get to know you.
But I never had the chance.
Your flattery is
too much for me to bear.
Mr. Shen, please head inside.
Mr. Li, you're being overly courteous.
We could have a simple meal together.
There's no need to make such a fuss.
This is way
too lavish.
It's the least
I can do to show my sincerity.
Mr. Shen, here.
I have a stomach issue,
so I can't drink.
Please drink a little.
After a serious illness,
I nearly lost my life.
I finally managed to get better
after a lot of effort.
So I can't help to be cautious.
Surely, you won't think
I've poisoned the wine, do you?
Would you?
Mr. Shen,
let's drop the formalities.
Please enjoy.
Mr. Shen,
I believe we've had
some misunderstandings.
I thought we couldn't sit here and talk
due to our different positions.
I didn't think we could sit together
in the same room
and talk over a meal today.
I'm truly honored.
I believe with your wisdom,
you can understand my difficulties.
My work does involve Chi Shanying
to some extent.
But our relationship is not
as your newspapers suggest.
Besides, I haven't done anything
to harm the country or the people.
The development of Haidong covers
many aspects and details.
I have to handle the connections
for every single one.
Look.
I don't target the poor.
I only address those wealthy individuals
who only care about themselves.
Since you agree with my approach,
may I be bold
to get closer to you
and ask for your understanding?
When reporting news
about the Haidong Army, especially
the Economic Development Committee,
it would be helpful to communicate
with me first.
Of course,
I'm not trying to interfere
with your freedom to report news.
It's just
that everything can be talked out.
Helping others is also helping oneself,
don't you agree?
Besides,
I won't let you help for nothing.
There will be a generous gift
to show my gratitude.
A generous gift?
How generous?
You can name your price.
Whatever you want,
I'll make sure you're satisfied.
I want your life.
What?
I want you
to pay with your life.
Captain, there's noise coming
from inside.
Open your mouth.
It's okay.
If something were wrong,
Mr. Li would have thrown his cup
to signal us.
I usually don't take revenge this way.
It's against my principles.
But you've gone too far.
You didn't even let me die
with a whole body,
which has caused me great torment
and unbearable suffering.
Superintendent Chi,
what brings you here?
I... Mr Li, he's...
Mr. Shen.
What are you doing?
Let go of Mr. Li.
Mr. Shen,
what are you doing?
I want Mr. Li to send me off.
I hope no one minds.
Put down your guns.
Give Mr. Shen some space.
Put down the guns!
Do you take my words for nonsense?
Put it down.
Slowly.
Superintendent Chi,
nice to meet you.
Yes.
Don't just stand there.
After him. Go!
Faster.
Stop!
Mr. Li!
Mr. Li.
Don't scare us.
- Mr. Li.
Mr. Li!
Mr. Li.
What are you waiting for?
Send him to the hospital.
Hurry! Let's go.
Here.
(Xia District. Traffic Inspection.
Violators will be shot.)
Shen,
you have finally returned.
Did you really meet Li Yingliang?
I just let the newspapers criticize
their oppression of the people.
Yet, they want me dead.
If I were an ordinary person,
I'd probably have died that night.
So
did you kill him?
Killing isn't my principle.
Those scoundrels are using
their power to bully others.
The people are constantly criticizing
them for bullying them.
You could have just killed them
and ended it all.
Don't take it seriously.
I was just saying it out of spite.
Weilian.
Enough.
I know you have your principles
and I shouldn't have said that.
Just remember
that you're not immortal.
It would be excruciating
to get hit by those bullets.
Excessive blood loss is really serious.
You should be cautious.
I can't be rescuing you every day.
I'll get going now.
Okay.
(Self-restraint)
If violence could solve problems,
why would I stick
to my principles?
Thank you.
Superintendent Chi,
thank you for saving my life.
Didn't you say Shen Zhiheng is dead?
How is he alive?
Mr. Li, don't...
I did kill him.
But I don't know
how he survived.
Then why
did you meet him in secret?
Because he is extremely suspicious.
I can't find anything about him.
So, I secretly met with him.
I simply wanted to meet him alone
and have a talk.
If the negotiation failed,
I would have killed him myself.
Clever.
Clever, indeed.
I thought he was scared of us.
But I didn't expect...
Is he afraid of us now?
Is he?
I was careless.
With your skills,
how did you get subdued
by him so easily?
At the time, he moved so quickly
that I couldn't see clearly.
And he was incredibly strong.
I clearly dressed thickly.
He managed to stab me in the thigh
with a chopstick.
I...
I'm curious about something.
What were you doing when I came in?
I saw his head
right on your neck.
It was so close to your face.
It was this close.
What were you doing?
What was he doing?
I think he was trying to bite me.
Is he a dog?
Bite you?
Does he have some kind of fetish?
He does have some peculiar fetish.
He watered his plants with blood.
My subordinates saw it
with their own eyes.
Didn't you ever think
that maybe your subordinates lied
to you on purpose
because they were incompetent?
I...
Enough.
I'll get you a new team
to assist you.
Superintendent Chi, I can guarantee
- that I will definitely...
- Save your breath.
Take good care of your injury.
Mr. Li. Help me out here.
Be careful.
Gently.
Shen Zhiheng, this rascal.
I'm going to take him out right now.
Let's go.
Come back!
Mr. Li,
it's my fault this time.
You can punish me.
But there's one thing
I still don't understand.
I clearly killed him and...
But why...
Our investigation was too hasty
and underestimated him.
Call in
more of our men.
Keep an eye on him
around the clock.
Find out
everyone he's met,
his connections, and his family's background
for three generations.
Rest assured.
We'll get to the bottom of this.
Leave some people
to guard.
Yes, sir.
You, at the back. Stay and watch him.
- Yes, sir.
About-face! Forward march!
Shen,
what have you found?
I found it.
"Promise?"
Why are you looking for this character?
A promise is like a thousand gold,
which is as firm as mountains.
A thousand gold?
Are you saying
this is worth a thousand gold bars?
Then I want it.
What are you thinking?
Come with me to the Mi Mansion.
Didn't she say not to go?
Should we not go
even if she didn't allow us?
We're talking
about a life-saving favor here.
Mr. Shen,
what brings you here today?
You're too kind.
It's fine to just visit.
Why did you bring so many gifts?
My husband has been away
to collect payment recently.
So he's not in Haidong.
Well, you see.
I'm here
to visit Mr. Mi
and to thank your daughter.
Mi Lan?
Yes.
Is your daughter here today?
I've prepared
all these gifts for her.
Mr. Shen, you sure have
a sense of humor.
Mi Lan never leaves the house.
How could she possibly help you?
Is your daughter home?
She's not in.
You said, she never goes out.
Where could she be?
She's gone to Jiangnan with her father
to collect payments.
Mr. Shen, I'm sorry.
I'm not feeling well today.
I must ask you to leave.
Someone.
Please see the guests out.
Please come with me.
I'll take my leave then.
♪Of all the marks imprinted in my heart♪
♪People come and go,
the weather is ever-changing♪
♪Endless expectations and reminiscing♪
♪Having no say in one's will♪
♪Oh♪
♪On the same path♪
♪With different burdens♪
♪And different destinations♪
♪Oh♪
♪Different steps♪
♪Pursuing the same goal♪
♪With different sense of belonging♪
♪Oh, I see the exit♪
♪Hey, there's no end to this♪
♪A soul that has found its home,
devoting everything to love♪
♪Oh, reasons that can be articulated♪
♪Hey, can't escape
from the ridiculousness♪
♪Destiny is a maze where those inside
are interconnected♪
♪Oh, have you possessed it before?♪
♪Hey, have you stayed true
to someone before?♪
♪A soul that can't find its home
is still searching♪
♪Oh, it's too late to fabricate♪
♪Hey, it's too late to wave♪
♪Fate disregards all reasons,
putting right and wrong together♪