Noona!
Park Do Ra is here!
Unni!
Unni, love you!
I love you, Unni!
You're so pretty!
I'm so tired, I could die.
Gosh, my tummy is cold.
What are you doing? Let's get going.
Will we stay here all night?
I love you, Unni!
I love you!
How could you make me wear such shabby clothes?
Let's switch the company.
When does our contract end?
There's just one term left, but they offered double for the renewal.
- Do you still want to cancel?
- Double?
Really?
I need to renew, then.
Ask them to get better clothes instead.
It will be sold out today, too.
It's selling out because I wore it.
Gosh, I'm so freaking tired.
So freaking tired.
Jae Dong, we're going home, right?
You have a photoshoot briefly.
You must be crazy.
I can't do a photoshoot looking like this.
Did Mom schedule it again?
Yup.
She's driving me crazy.
I won't even get paid that much.
And Noona...
What is it now?
There's a lead actors' meeting for the series "Straightforward Romance."
I... I said I won't do that series.
Hey. Do you think I should work for that pay?
And I heard the male lead is Cha Bong Soo.
He's not my type.
He's a greasy womanizer. I'm sure he smells greasy.
But they want me to do a romance with him?
The CEO had dinner with the CEO and director of the production company already.
- My mom did?
- Yes, what should we do, then?
Do you have to ask?
First of all, turn the car around to the broadcasting station.
Right now.
Pil Sung. Good morning, Sir.
(T/N: Pil Sung means victory)
You want me to join Hong Jin Goo sunbae's "Straightforward Romance"?
Do Yeong was hospitalized because she might miscarry.
I nagged at her to be careful all the time.
She devoted herself too much to some silly drama.
What do we do?
You're the only one who could join...
"Straightforward Romance."
Yes, I know you worked yourself to death on a daily series
and you're finally going on vacation to backpacking to Europe since it ended yesterday.
Hey...
could you cancel that and do this... somehow?
Station Director, you don't have to beat around the bush to ask me that.
Do Yeong is my colleague, and she was hospitalized. Of course, I should do it.
I'll go backpacking in Europe after finishing "Straightforward Romance" successfully.
Feel free to ask me anything, Sir.
Gosh, man...
How come you always say the right thing?
Gosh, I like you. I like you.
Pil Sung, if you pull this off, I'll let you...
debut a two-part series.
You mean it, right? You're serious.
Yes. But don't tell everyone about it.
So, good luck with this one.
You know what I mean, right?
Yes, got it! Salute!
Hey, you made it. I just got a call from the broadcasting station director.
Director, who's he?
Say hello, Director Go.
You know Ms. Park Do Ra, right?
He's Go Pil Sung, the assistant director who's joining our team starting today.
Hello.
Oh, h-hello.
Why are you so shocked?
Don't you know Ms. Park?
Oh, yes, yes. I know.
Looks like he's too shocked by your beauty, Ms. Park.
What are you doing? Have a seat.
Oh, okay.
W-What happened?
Why is Park Do Ra here?
Was she cast for "Straightforward Romance"?
The official meeting is tomorrow.
What did you want to talk to me about today?
Do you need to adjust the schedule, by chance? Or—
No.
Director Hong, I don't think I could join you for this project.
I wanted to tell you that.
M-Ms. Park, what do you mean? You can't join us?
I made it clear that I can't,
but there must've been a miscommunication while I was shooting abroad.
But I thought I should explain in person instead of talking over the phone.
Wait, Ms. Park, the filming starts this week. You can't do this to us out of the blue.
I'm so sorry.
I'll get going now, then.
Take care.
Take care. I'm sorry. Take care.
Ms. Park. M-Ms. Park!
Ms. Park! Ms. Park Do Ra!
Ms. Park! Ms. Park! Ms. Park Do Ra! Ms. Park!
H-Hold on, please hear me out. Yes, Ms. Park!
The filming starts this week—
Whoa, she's so unbelievable. She doesn't give a crap.
Who does she think she is?
What would happen if she's dropping out?
What do you mean? We can cast someone else.
There are plenty of actors out there.
I can't believe I ran into her here.
But she didn't recognize me.
I suppose, how could she?
My name changed, and we haven't met since she was a kid 15 years ago.
President Kim, didn't Park Do Ra sign the contract?
Didn't you tell me she did?
Come on!
A verbal agreement isn't the same as signing a contract.
She backed out. What will you do now?
Pardon? Where would we find another actor now?
I don't give a crap! You'd better fix this yourself!
Sunbae, I created a list of available female actors.
Sunbae, how about Bi Bi?
Park Do Ra's forever rival.
Look at her recent headshot. She's in great shape.
Her image is a bit different than Park Do Ra's, but she isn't too bad, is she?
I don't care if it's Bi BI or Mi Mi right now!
You can't do this right now. You should go get Park Do Ra back somehow.
Geez, how could this happen right now?
Hold on.
Go Pil Sung, go get a bouquet right now.
Get the most expensive one. A huge one. This big.
A bouquet?
Hurry up, Pil Sung!
Nice.
Yes, slightly to the left.
Great, thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
You did a great job. Seriously.
Look at it.
Looks amazing, right?
Yes.
Gosh, great job, Ms. Park.
Director Hong, what brings you here?
Hey, hey, hey.
Yes?
Ms. Park, here.
Director Hong, I understand why you came all the way here,
but I can't join "Straightforward Romance."
I've worked without taking a day off since I debuted as a child actor at age 12.
I really want to take a break.
Goodness. I know, too.
But just this once, could you—
It must've been very difficult.
You've been working for 15 years without taking a day off.
Sounds like you do need a break.
I know you've been working hard all this time.
But this project was approved because you said you'll join.
But we'll be in serious trouble if you don't, so—
It's not like the pay is high enough.
To be honest, I felt disrespected and upset.
How could I get paid less than Jeon Ga Yeon?
Well, it's because our budget is a bit...
I wish I could pay you more.
And I heard Cha Bong Soo is the male lead.
I don't think we're a good match, either. For many reasons—
You must not like the male lead, either.
You really can't do it, then.
Romance is all about the chemistry between the leads.
Anyway, I'm sorry, Director Hong.
I hope you understand where I'm coming from.
I'll get going now.
Wait, Ms. Park.
Wait, Do Ra, Do Ra. Ms. Park...
Go Pil Sung, you crazy bastard. Are you out of your mind?
You came all this way to ruin things?
Instead of kneeling and begging, you say, "You need a break"?
Sunbae, this is beneath us. Why do this to someone who doesn't want to?
And for your information, you begged me to come with you.
- You didn't want to go alone.
- You bastard. Seriously!
Sunbae! Am I wrong?
Why are you beating me? What am I, a drum?
Geez! You can't hit someone, even with flowers.
Hey, Go Pil Sung, shut your mouth.
Gosh, I'm going crazy.
Ms. Park!
Geez, thank goodness.
I almost got to work with Park Do Ra.
That won't be right.
My goodness.
Gosh, this is so luxurious and pretty.
My gosh!
Aigoo, my goodness.
How lucky are the women who buy stuff like this like it's nothing?
It suits you so well, Ma'am.
Really? Thank you. I'll be back soon.
Okay. I'll call you when we get new products.
That woman looks very familiar.
- See you.
- Okay.
Yes, Do Ra's mom. That gold digger.
Excuse me. Hold on.
Gosh! W-What are you doing?
It's you.
Gosh, look who's here.
They say the enemies reunite on a log bridge.
Ms. Baek, it's me.
Don't you recognize me?
Please let go. You're mistaken.
Come on, I'm not mistaken.
You're the gold digger who ran away from our house 15 years ago.
What are you doing? You'd better look carefully.
- That's not me. Let go! Let go.
- Oh, my gosh.
That gold digger. That gold digger.
Hey, catch that gold digger!
Hey, gold digger!
Gosh, that scamming gold digger.
Where's she hiding exactly?
She definitely went this way.
Maybe she didn't go this way.
Did she go that way?
Gosh, what just happened?
How could I run into that woman here?
That crazy hag. How dare she call me a gold digger?
How come nothing works out these days?
Geez Louise.
What?
Mom, what is it? Is something going on?
No, what is it? What's this about?
What?
What do you mean by that?
Do Ra is refusing to join "Straightforward Romance"?
Mom, you want me to do at least that?
Don't you care about my sense of pride?
Why should I work for less pay than Jeon Ga Yeon?
That's not that bad of a pay.
It's not bad enough to hurt your pride.
And what would you do if you took a break?
You need to work hard while they still want you.
Mom, what do you mean by, "What would you do if you took a break?”
I can't work under such a term.
So don't just get me random stuff.
And I don't feel like working for some reason lately.
I'll rest for six months in New York, where Do Jun is, just so you know.
What? That long?
Are you crazy? That makes no sense.
How doesn't it make sense? I'll rest if I want to.
I've saved up a lot of money.
Hey, D-Do Ra. Ms. Park Do Ra.
I told the production company and director that you'll do it. So...
please try to save my face and do this one—
No, I don't want to, I said.
I made it clear that I didn't want to.
Hey, Do Ra. Do Ra!
You get forgotten if you take a break for a year these days.
What will you do if no one hires you?
There will always be pretty and talented ones. You think you'll always be in your 20s?
You think you'll always be an A-list actor, girl?
You need to row when there's water. Grasshoppers only last a season, too, you brat.
Is Do Ra refusing to do "Straightforward Romance"?
What would happen if she didn't? We'd be in trouble if she didn't.
What would we do if she didn't? What would we do?
Oh, no, seriously. Hey, Do Sik, tell her to go do it. Tell her—
- She won't listen to me.
- Hey, hey, hey...
Gosh, seriously! How could she...
- It's so funny.
- I'm the greatest beauty of this town.
I'm home.
- You're home, Son. Did you have dinner?
- I ate a little.
My gosh, my gosh.
Hey, I-I-I...
I saw that woman. That woman.
What's wrong, Mom?
W-Who did you see? Who's "that woman"?
Do Ra's mom. That cunning thing.
That gold digger.
What did you say? You saw Do Ra's mom? That woman?
Mom, where did you see her?
While I was out today,
I got a spicy naengmyeon pollock at the department store food court.
And I was browsing clothes at the designer shop upstairs to digest.
There was a woman dressed in designer clothes from head to toe
holding shopping bags in both hands coming out of there.
So I was all envious and staring at her, thinking how privileged she was.
It turns out that was Do Ra's mom, that cunning woman.
Really?
Yes, so I said, "Look who's here. You're Do Ra's mom."
But she said she wasn't, and I was mistaken.
And she ran away from me.
- She ran away?
- Yes, that's right.
She ran away because I was right.
Why would she run away otherwise?
Pil Sung, haven't you seen Do Ra at the broadcasting station?
Pardon? W-Why do you ask?
What do you mean, why?
Do Ra's mom took your grandfather's...
She seduced In-law and took 30 million. We need to get that back.
Pil Sung, you can get Park Do Ra's phone number since you work at the broadcasting station, right?
Go find out.
You don't have to, Pil Sung.
Pretend you don't know her even if you run into her.
Pretend he doesn't know? Why?
Mother, please stop bringing up that woman.
Why do you always have to remind me?
Hearing just the word "Do" makes my blood boil.
I know. That's why we need to get that money back.
Hey, 30 million won was a fortune 15 years ago.
If you add the interest, too, it'd be more than 100 million won by now.
I don't ever want to get involved with that woman anymore.
And I don't want to ruin my dad's reputation by bringing up the past because of that money.
My gosh, my gosh. Hey, hey.
Do you think 100 million is a joke or something?
How could you give up on that much money?
We at least need to get the 30 million back. The original principal.
She was all dressed up in designer clothes.
Don't you find it unfair?
Enough is enough, Mom.
What do you mean, enough? We need every penny we could get.
Seon Yeong says she doesn't want to.
I wouldn't want to, either.
Ma Ri, try this.
The tteokgalbi turned out so well today.
I know you like this stuff.
No, Dad. Don't tempt me.
I won't get tricked no matter how much you tempt me.
I know you're on a diet, but you need protein.
- Just one. Here, here.
- I said I can't.
Just leave her alone.
She'll learn her lesson when she passes out.
This won't last long.
I would've become an idol, too, if all it takes is to be on a diet.
My gosh, how dare you? Look at her eyes.
Ma Ri.
The dummy will always be a dummy.
I heard Jin Dan is going on a blind date with Jeil Steel's daughter.
Yes.
The chairman of Jeil Steel is a man of character. I hope it works out.
It's not easy to get a blind date with their daughter.
They said yes because they knew Jin Dan would inherit Angel Investment.
Why isn't Jin Dan coming downstairs?
- Did he come home late?
- Huh?
He left early this morning.
Grandma is always lying through her teeth. She's a total liar.
Gosh, Ma Ri. How could you say something so awful with your pretty mouth?
Ma Ri, I told you not to talk like that.
Uncle didn't come home last night.
Why do you lie he left in the morning?
You just had to say he didn't come home.
I think your mouth is more awful than mine.
W-What?
Cheers.
Why do you like me?
Just give me three reasons. Not too many.
The reasons I like you?
One. You're handsome.
Two. You buy me designer handbags often.
Three. You buy me clothes often.
Hey.
I like you a lot.
I love people who are honest.
Gong Jin Dan! Gong Jin Dan!
Open the door! Open it!
What? W-Who's that?
- It's my mom.
- Open the door!
Open the door, I said!
Mom, you came.
What are you doing here instead of going to work?
Well, the thing is, Mom—
Which girl is it now?
Where is she? Where are you hiding her?
I'm not hiding anyone.
I'm on a staycation because I have some things to think through. Isn't this nice? Look.
What's this?
Hey, Gong Jin Dan. Is this what you call a staycation? Huh?
You drive me crazy.
Who is it this time? Come out right now!
That's not mine. It must belong to the previous guest.
I swear I came here alone. So you should wait in the lobby.
So you should wait in the lobby.
I'll get changed and come down right away. Okay?
Mom. Gosh, Mom.
The makeup turned out great today. So pretty. Aigoo.
My gosh!
Hello, Ma'am.
You have a blind date today. What are you doing in broad daylight with a lowly girl like her?
I said I won't go on blind dates!
I hate stuff like that.
I seek NEs. NEs.
NEs? What's that?
I seek natural encounters.
I seek encounters that were meant to be.
NEs, my foot.
When will you get your act together?
You think your brother doesn't know you're doing this?
That's why he's not giving you Angel Investment. Because you're acting like this.
So what do you want me to do?
I can't help myself, either.
How could you do this to me?
I've been living only for you all my life.
When I was 21, just a young thing, I met your father, who was much older,
and I was called all sorts of names.
I've been enduring humiliation all this time...
Don't you pity me at all?
Okay, okay.
Stop talking about when you were 21.
I'll go on the blind date.
I'll go, okay?
You mean it, right?
I said I'll go.
Jin Dan, it was really difficult to arrange the blind date today.
If you marry the daughter of Jeil Steel, your brother will think of you differently, too.
If you have dependable in-laws, he won't be able to look down on you, either.
You know what I mean, right?
Okay, Mother. That's enough.
Okay, Son. I made a hair appointment for you. Get ready.
You can't be late.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I didn't see you because I was looking at my phone.
It's okay. I was looking at my phone, too.
I think I've seen you somewhere.
Are you the Park Do Ra, by chance?
Yes, I'm that Park Do Ra.
Thank you.
Watch out!
My goodness.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
What are you doing over there?
You almost hurt someone.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
You almost got injured trying to save me.
Are you okay? You must be scared.
No, I'm okay.
I'm glad you didn't get hurt.
Well, then...
Excuse me.
You saved my life.
Could you give me your phone number? I'd like to treat you to a meal or something.
Save your life? Not at all.
It's okay. Well, then...
Wait...
Is this a dream or reality?
Wow.
Hey, Gong Jin Dan. Did you really reject Jeil Steel's daughter?
You crazy bastard. Do you want to see me die?
It was so difficult to arrange that date. How dare you reject her?
Are you sure Park Do Ra isn't seeing anyone?
Yes, I think so.
Should I find out more about Park Do Ra?
No, this is enough. You can leave.
Okay.
Hold on, Secretary Jo.
Why did we decide not to invest in this?
Pardon? Which one?
This one. "Straightforward Romance," the series Park Do Ra was cast in.
Oh, you're the one who rejected it.
You said we shouldn't invest in something so small.
Did I?
Why would I say that?
Don't you know the content industry is one of the most promising industries right now?
I need to invest in this.
- Pardon?
- I think this drama will be a total hit.
I want to invest in it immediately.
Schedule a meeting with the CEO of the production company right now.
Okay, I will.
Yes, I'm that Park Do Ra.
My heart is fluttering.
What's with Park Do Ra?
She makes me feel dizzy...
and makes my heart flutter.
Do I really have a crush on her?
Have you thought about how to bring Park Do Ra back?
Well, Sunbae...
Yes, Pil Sung. Tell me. Do you have a good idea?
I tried contacting Bi Bi.
She said she'd do it with the current pay.
Hey, man, I said come up with an idea to bring Park Do Ra back. Why change the subject?
Sunbae, aside from everything else,
I think obsessing over an actor who doesn't want the role isn't right.
Even if one obsessed over our drama, she might not get it.
The viewers can tell right away if they sincerely want the role,
or they were forced to do it because of money.
Remember what she said yesterday? She eventually talked about money.
I did some research. Apparently, she's money crazy.
Everyone says she only cares about money.
- Really?
- Yes.
And do you know what her nickname is?
Bbakdora. Bbakdora.
(T/N: means enraging)
How much did she enrage people on set that they call her that?
Sunbae, let's just go with Bi Bi.
Park Do Ra is too skinny and unattractive. I really dislike her.
Hey, Go Pil Sung!
- Pil Sung.
- Salut.
- Oh, Station Director.
- Director Hong was here, too.
What brings you here, Station Director?
Where's Park Do Ra? Isn't she here yet?
Pardon? P-Park Do Ra?
Yes, I'm supposed to meet her here.
Do Ra, you were already here.
You came.
By the way, what's wrong with the vibe here?
- Station Director.
- Huh?
I really wanted to take a break for a while,
but since you, who started my career, asked me,
I decided to join "Straightforward Romance" and be loyal to you.
Yes, yes.
By the way, Station Director, I'm sorry.
About what?
I can't work with people who don't trust me?
Trust?
What trust?
What's this about, anyway?
Excuse me.
Curly haired assistant director.
Yes, I'm unattractive because I'm skinny.
And my nickname is indeed Bbakdora because I have a horrible temper.
And I...
I'm really obsessed with money.
So why don't you work with Bi Bi, who's not money-obsessed?
Good luck.
I'll get going now.
Do Ra?
Ms. Park. Seriously...
Ms. Park! Ms. Park Do Ra!
Geez, seriously!
Hey, I might not have kneeled in front of her, but I begged her so much.
I called her countless times to calm her down and persuade her.
I barely persuaded her using the fact we go way back.
Go Pil Sung. How dare you ruin that?
What will you do now? Seriously...
- Station Director, calm down.
- Let go of me!
We just decided to go with Bi Bi. Calm down.
What? Bi Bi?
- D-Did she agree to do it?
- Yes, yes, yes. She wants to join us.
She agreed to get paid less than Park Do Ra, too.
Really? Hold on. Hold on.
The chemistry between the leads is important, too,
but Bi Bi is close to Cha Bong Soo. She's not a bad option.
Geez.
I'm sorry, Sunbae...
It's okay.
What else can we do, right?
It's okay!
I'm not okay!
Why didn't Ae Gyo come today?
Something must be going on.
Like what? Didn't she tell you?
We live in the same house, but we don't see each other often.
I suppose that's for the better.
Soo Yeon, you're basically Buddha.
You tolerate her for all of her behavior.
Right, is your son, Pil Sung, still busy these days?
Yes. He just finished the daily series,
but another team snatched him right up again.
Goodness. Can't the broadcasting station not operate without my son?
I never get to see him since he's so busy with work.
He must be so competent.
He's blessed with work.
I heard even TV producers get paid over 100 million for a contract these days.
Yes, I guess so.
But he's still starting out as a producer. He has a long way to go.
He needs to get more experience.
Your son must be really popular among women.
There must be tons of pretty women at the broadcasting station.
By the way, tell her to be careful of women.
There are so many weird ones out there these days.
I know. I'm worried about that, too.
You know how handsome my Pil Sung is.
Gosh, you're bragging again. You're so unbelievable.
Seon Yeong, your son secured a good job now.
My cousin's daughter is a bank teller.
Should we set them up?
She's a bank teller?
Sounds good.
You don't want me to set up dates for Pil Sung?
A bank teller isn't so bad. Why do you say that?
Isn't it too soon to arrange dates and plan for his marriage?
He can meet plenty of better ladies once he builds his career and becomes a head producer.
I'll set him up with someone from a better family, then.
- Really?
- Of course. He's your son.
And I've seen him since he was a kid.
I want him to marry into a good family.
Gosh, Soo Yeon.
So tell him not to just date anyone.
Okay. You promised me, okay?
Okay, cheers.
Cheers.
Thank you.
Director, thank you so much.
I'll work as hard as I can.
I really love this role, and I'm confident I can do it.
We should be thanking you.
You said yes as soon as we suggested.
What's there to even think about?
I loved the script, and the male lead is Cha Bong Soo.
And you're the one who's directing. How much more can I ask for?
I'll contact the production company, then.
Okay. Tell them I'll sign immediately—
Gosh, President Kim is unbelievable.
Yes, President Kim, I was just talking to Bi Bi—
What did you say?
Just one second.
Sunbae.
Sunbae, what's going on?
Hyung, what's going on?
- Yes, Station Director.
- Hey, Go Pil Sung.
You'd better come up here right now.
Pardon?
Right now?
Sit, sit.
It's okay. Sit.
Pil Sung, what do we do?
"Straightforward Romance" is about to get canceled because of you.
The new main investment company said they'll back out if it's not Park Do Ra.
There's the existing investment company, too. We can figure things out—
Figure things out?
Will you supply the production budget
Since the new main investment company is backing out,
the existing ones are threatening to back out, too.
The drama is about to fail without Park Do Ra.
Hey. We don't even have another drama as a backup.
What do we do?
I'll get Park Do Ra back no matter what it takes!
Yes!
You'd better clean up your own shit!
I'll go to Park Do Ra's management company since I can't reach her manager.
Please find out her home address.
Mr. Go, she's leaving for the U.S. right now.
Pardon?
T-The U.S.? What for?
I called a manager who's close to Park Do Ra's manager.
She's going to New York on a 7 p.m. flight tonight.
So her manager is taking her to Incheon Airport right now. What should we do?
You've got to be kidding.
This is nuts. I'm going to lose it.
Why is there so much traffic?
Excuse me, sir! Sir! Hold on, sir!
Sir, please hurry up a bit.
Thank you so much!
The call is not going through.
- You'll be connected to the voicemail.
- What do I do now?
Do Ra.
Park Do Ra, where are you?
Did she go in, by chance?
Park Do Ra!
Ms. Park Do Ra!
Did you...
Did you just call me "Park Do Ra"? By my name?
I-I'm sorry. It just came out because I was so rushed.
Ms. Park Do Ra, I'm so sorry. I must've been out of my mind.
I sincerely apologize for saying weird things about you.
Did you come all the way here to apologize for that?
I wasn't trying to slander you with a malicious intention.
You said you've been working nonstop for 15 years.
I felt so bad and wanted to let you take a break—
Excuse me, curly-haired assistant director.
Do you think that makes sense right now?
Because you felt bad for me, you called me "Bbakdora"
and money-obsessed behind my back, too?
Pardon?
Ms. Park, I apologize for everything.
You can swear at me and hit me, but...
please work on our drama, "Straightforward Romance."
If you agree to take the role,
I'll do anything you want me to do.
No, thank you.
- Ms. Park.
- My gosh.
- My gosh, how dare you touch me?
- Let go.
If you leave like this,
I'll get fired.
Think of this as you saving my life. I beg you.
What's wrong with him?
Yes, Mom.
What?
You signed the contract for "Straightforward Romance"?
Why do you think you could do that for me?
What's wrong with you, Mom?
What? A blank check?
Really?
They will really pay me whatever I want?
Okay. Okay, I'm coming.
I'm on my way. Hang up.
Let's go back.
- Go back?
- Yes.
Ms. Park,
thank you so much for deciding to join "Straightforward Romance."
Excuse me.
You'd better not let me see you going forward. Got that?
Crazy bastard. Rotten bastard.
He'd never find someone like the daughter of Jeil Steel.
How dare he squander an opportunity like that?
What a bastard. I won't just let this slide.
What? Isn't that Ma Ri?
My gosh, she's 26 years old.
What's she doing with elementary schoolers?
Hey, Gong Ma Ri!
What are you doing with the elementary schoolers right now?
We're on our way to a karaoke. Why?
You're going to a karaoke with these little kids?
Are you taking money from Ma Ri because she's slow?
Grandma, what are you accusing my friends of?
We're going Dutch, okay?
Is she your grandma?
- Apparently.
- Yes, she is.
I'm not her grandma. I'm her aunt.
I told you not to call me that.
What? You yelled at me for not calling you that before.
Ma Ri, is she your grandma or aunt?
To be honest,
she was my grandpa's mistress. A concubine.
Mistress? Concubine?
But she was my mom's high school classmate.
So I keep switching between Grandma and Aunt. I don't know, either.
Hey, you little brat. What did you just say?
- Stop, Grandma!
- Ahjumma!
Auntie! Auntie!
Mom! Dad! Mom!
Ma Ri, what's wrong? What is it?
What happened? Who did this to you?
Ma Ri, what's going on?
Uncle Jin Dan's mom...
Grandma Ae Gyo...
grabbed me by my hair in front of my friends.
- What?
- I lost a clump of hair.
She pinched and hit me, too.
Is that true?
Did you really grab her by the hair, pinch, and hit her?
Yes, I did that.
She told elementary schoolers that I was her grandpa's mistress and concubine. That's why I did that.
Was I supposed to stand back when she said that?
What? Ma Ri, did you really say that?
Yes. She was grandpa's mistress and concubine.
That's the truth.
Listen to her.
Because you two look down on me, even this girl, Ma Ri, is calling me that.
- Hong Ae Gyo.
- What?
How dare you call my name right now?
Yes, I was your father's mistress and concubine. You should call me "Mother," then.
How dare you call me by my name? You backward son of a bitch.
Try treating me like this again. I swear I won't tolerate it.
Mom, what if I get kicked out?
Aigoo, you brat.
That's why you shouldn't have blabbered your mouth like that.
Ma Ri, that brat called me a mistress and a concubine in public.
Was I supposed to do nothing?
Everyone looks down on me for being a mistress and a concubine. Everyone.
Aigoo, you brat. Do you blame them for calling you a mistress?
It's true, though. What will you do about it?
That's how you've lived.
Will that fact ever change? You stupid brat.
Must you say that to me even in death?
Can't you be the only one on my side?
Honey, what's wrong?
What if...
Ma Ri's like this her whole life? Her whole life...
Look at her photos.
She hangs out with elementary schoolers.
She can't hang out with friends her age.
It's not like we can stop her, either.
What do we do with Ma Ri, Honey?
It's okay.
What's wrong with hanging out with younger kids?
People become friends regardless of age in other countries.
Our Ma Ri is so pure-hearted that she's friends with little kids.
There's nothing wrong with that.
So don't worry, okay?
How could I not worry?
This isn't a foreign country.
Honey, whether she befriends elementary schoolers or high schoolers,
I'm happy as long as she has friends.
She just needs to be healthy and happy.
What more can we ask for?
Honey...
I prayed in front of the OR that day.
I asked God to just let her live.
I said I wouldn't ask for anything else.
Honey,
I still feel the same way now.
I'm so grateful she's alive and well in front of us.
Let's...
not ask for more.
They look good.
With her. Like this.
Do Ra, my sweet daughter.
I knew you'd do this. I knew it.
Mom, this is the last time, okay?
Don't sign contracts for me from now on, okay?
Okay, okay.
Gosh, have a seat. Have a seat, Do Ra.
I'm tired. What are you trying to tell me now?
Do Ra, the new investment company, is called Angel.
Do you know the CEO there, by chance?
No, I don't. Why?
Angel Investment is investing in "Straightforward Romance."
But they said it had to be you.
That they'd back out if you didn't do it.
And they told the production company to pay you as much as you want.
Really? Is that true?
Yes. My goodness.
They must be investing in you because they recognize your true value.
I suppose no one's as pretty and good at acting as you.
Not anyone can play the lead.
Mom, once we pay off the loan for the Cheongdam-dong building with the pay,
why don't we buy another building?
Should we buy one near Hongdae this time?
Huh?
Yes, let's do that. I'll look into it.
Go Pil Sung.
You're the best, Go Pil Sung.
Hey, I knew you'd bring Park Do Ra back.
Wow. You even went to the airport to stop her.
You're definitely the man of his word, Pil Sung.
She changed her mind because the new investment company
promised to raise her pay significantly, not because of me.
But it happened because you went all the way there.
Good job. Well done.
- Station Director...
- Yes.
Can I switch to a different team?
Any team but "Straightforward Romance" team.
Hey.
Are you saying that because I yelled at you earlier?
All sorts of things happen in a broadcasting station.
Hey. What you're going through now isn't serious.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Let's have a drink, put it behind us, and work hard on "Straightforward Romance."
I'll be keeping my eyes on you.
Two-part series, okay?
Fighting.
Seriously, this is nuts.
I'll be running into her the entire time we shoot.
What do I do now?
No, no, no.
She doesn't recognize me, anyway.
I need to sit through it just once.
Just once.
Unni, the ends of your hair got so damaged.
- Really?
- I think we need to trim it a bit.
But I'm starting a drama.
I'll treat the hair and scalp, too, then.
Sounds good.
Hey, Jo Bi Bi.
What are you doing right now?
You bitch.
You took the role because you knew I wanted to do "Straightforward Romance," right?
You took "Passionate Girl" last time. You're taking my role again?
I can't believe this.
Hey, Jo Bi Bi.
You think I'm desperate enough to steal your role?
I kept saying no to "Straightforward Romance" because I wanted to rest a bit.
But they kept insisting it had to be me.
The production company, investment company, and broadcasting station begged me. So I had to say yes.
Did you even know that?
W-What did you say?
Why did they suggest the role to me, then? I even had a meeting with the director!
How do I know why he had a meeting with you?
He must've met you as a backup because I kept saying no.
W-What did you say?
And "Passionate Girl..."
The writer wrote that role specifically for me, okay?
You think everyone's like you.
Do you think I'm like you because you steal your juniors' roles?
"Straightforward Romance..."
You stole my role by seducing the main investor. You think I didn't know?
You must've learned from your mother, I suppose.
She got you roles by pouring drinks for people here and there.
Everyone in the industry knows!
What?
- Hey, you!
- What?
Calm down.
How dare you say that? She poured drinks?
What? Was I wrong?
Who doesn't know that in this industry?
Everyone knows about it already!
Are you out of your mind? Let go. Let go!
- Let go, I said!
- You know how Bi Bi's obsessed with Cha Bong Soo.
That's why she wanted to do "Straightforward Romance," but you took the role. That's why.
She thinks you'll steal Bong Soo from her.
What? Seriously...
She's doing this because of that womanizer, Cha Bong Soo?
Wow. I can't believe this.
I won't forgive you for this.
Mom, you swear you didn't meet people from Angel Investment?
No, I didn't.
I don't even know who they are.  Why do you ask?
You're sure, right? Do you promise?
Of course, I'm sure.
I thought you knew them. That's why I asked you if you knew the CEO.
Okay.
Fine, then. Hang up.
She poured drinks?
Wow. What do I do with Jo Bi Bi?
Gosh, how do I kill her?
Hold on.
Bi Bi is obsessed with Cha Bong Soo.
Cheers.
I can already imagine a story by seeing you two sitting together.
Don't you agree, Writer? I think our drama will be a huge hit.
Yes, we won't have to worry. You two make a great couple.
Okay, okay, okay. Let's make "Straightforward Romance" a huge hit.
Cheers to "Straightforward Romance"!
Cheers!
Oppa, I'm in your care.
Sure.
Director Hong, I heard Mr. Cha refused to do kiss scenes.
Is that true?
This is a romantic story. We can't remove kiss scenes.
Gosh, don't worry. I'll try persuading him.
Did his girlfriend tell him not to?
How does that make any sense?
Cheers.
You know how Bi Bi's obsessed with Cha Bong Soo.
That's why she wanted to do "Straightforward Romance,"  but you took the role. That's why.
She thinks you'll steal Bong Soo from her.
I'll take care of it. Convincing people is my specialty.
Ms. Park and Mr. Cha, we're in your care.
The chemistry between the leads is important in romantic dramas.
Get to know each other quickly. You know, right?
Of course, Director Hong.
I'll treat you to the second round for that reason.
- Second round?
- Park Do Ra!
Park Do Ra! Park Do Ra!
Park Do Ra!
Park Do Ra! Cheers!
She worked very hard on this project.
Let's make this work.
Yes, let's make this work.
Take a glass.
I'm in your care. I mean it.
Why don't we sing a little?
We came all the way here. Come on.
- Oppa.
- Yes?
Let's go. Let's sing a song.
- Sing?
-Come on out.
- So Ri, you, too. Get up.
- I can't sing.
You, too, Sook Ja. Come out. Come out.
I heard you're a good singer.
Park Do Ra. Seriously, what's wrong with her?
Wow, we won't have to worry about the drama.
They already have great chemistry.
We should start warming up, too.
Let's join them!
What?
They just met today. What's she doing? How embarrassing.
Go Pil Sung, come on. Come on out.
Come out and dance, Pil Sung! Pil Sung!
- ♫  Her face is beautiful  ♫
- ♫  Beautiful!  ♫
- ♫   Her body is beautiful  ♫
- ♫   Beautiful!  ♫
♫  Everything about her is beautiful  ♫
♫  Her face is slender  ♫
♫  Her body is voluptuous  ♫
♫  She's a total catch  ♫
I want to go home.
I want to go home so desperately.
Why is everyone having so much fun?
When will this end?
Huh? Park Do Ra. You're Park Do Ra, right?
Well, yes.
Wow, you're way prettier in person.
Wow, seriously. I'm your fan starting today.
Why don't we dance together to celebrate it?
Hey, let go of me.
I'm not a bad person. I said I'll be your fan.
I don't need a fan like you. Let go of me.
You're playing hard to get.
Do you even know what I do?
- What?
- You make money with your face. Don't act superior.
What did you say?
What?
Let go!
Apologize to Ms. Park.
Grabbing her arm forcefully and... being rude counts as assault. You know, right?
All of that was captured on CCTV just now.
If you don't apologize now, we'll go to the police station.
Yes, I'm sorry, Ms. Park.
I apologize. Happy now?
Actors don't make money using their faces.
They share their beautiful souls with the world.
What are you saying?
Are you okay?
Well, yes. I'm okay.
Thank you for helping me.
Don't mention it. It's nothing.
Wait...
Where did you hear that cool line from just now?
"Actors share their beautiful souls with the world."
Well, I wasn't quoting it. I just came up with it.
I forgive you for talking behind my back since you just helped me.
And we have to work on the same set from now on.
I hope we get along going forward.
Yes, I can't apologize enough for that. I'm so sorry.
I hope we get along from now on. Thank you.
Let's work well together, okay?
Curly-haired assistant director.
Yes.
By chance, have we met somewhere before?
Pardon?
♫  Make my heart flutter and get me excited over and over  ♫
♫  You keep finding me without fail  ♫
♫  So I can't think about anything else  ♫
♫  I think this is what they call fate  ♫
♫  The sky is clearer than usual, and my feet feel light  ♫
Soo Yeon said he'll set you up with a woman from a prominent family.
I'll find my other half myself. Please don't worry about it.
There's no going back once you choose the wrong woman.
Just wait, Jo Bi Bi. You hurt my feelings. I'll hurt yours now.
She's crazy. She's totally out of her mind.
She's not the Park Do Ra I knew as a kid.
I need to tell you something.
We need time to start getting to know each other.
Park Do Ra! Cha Bong Soo!
What are you two doing right now?
Don't do this on our set. Just talk it out.