♪  My gosh, my gosh, don't do this  ♪
♪  Women's hearts are complicated  ♪
♪  No, why are you doing this?  ♪
Why are you making a kid sing a song at a place like this?
♪  Don't ask me you can't  ♪
She's so young.
What is this?
A kids' talent show or something?
Why are you using a kid for your business?
Where's the owner?
What are you doing? Get the owner.
Get the owner. Get the owner out here!
- What is this, a kids' talent show?
- Excuse me.
♪  I like you  ♪
♪  I love you  ♪
♪  I love you so unbelievably  ♪
♪  Like in a novel  ♪
♪  Like in a movie  ♪
No, no, no.
You were supposed to pay us 500,000 won  (~$372) . Why only pay us 300,000 won  (~$223) ?
Wow, this lady has no sense of guilt.
300,000 won is too much already.
You totally ruined the mood in there. How could you demand 500,000?
I almost had a bottle thrown at me.
She should've twisted and shaken a bit like this.
What are you doing after half-assing it?
What is this, an elementary school talent show?
Excuse me!
She might not look like it but Do Ra is an actor. A child actor.
You can't just slap us with this!
Everyone's an actor these days.
Are you an actor if you were on TV once?
And you should demand money after doing the work properly, Ahjumma.
Right now, I...
I'm giving you that much because I pity the child.
Don't ever come back here.
Don't you ever!
Hey, I got this as a tip earlier. Take it.
Ahjussi! Talk to me for a second.
Seriously.
You should've done it properly. Properly.
We only made 300,000 won because of you.
Mom...
This is why I said I didn't want to do this.
How can you say that right now?
The debt collectors are after me right now, and I'm about to die. Gosh, seriously!
Here.
Take this with you and wait at home.
Until I pick you up, okay?
Where are you going, Mom? Aren't you coming with me?
I can't go home because of the debt collectors right now.
That's why you should've done it properly.
We should've made at least 500,000 won, girl!
I'm sorry, Mom.
Okay. Go now. It's cold. Go now. Go.
Mom, you'll come, right?
I will. Just wait a few days.
Take good care of Do Jun and Do Sik, okay?
It's cold. It's so cold. Get going now. Go.
Hurry up and go! Go, go!
Attention. Say goodbye to the teacher.
Thank you.
Bye, everyone.
- Park Do Ra.
- Yes?
Come here, Do Ra.
This is an exchange coupon.
A philanthropist is giving them to families in need of help.
If you take this to the borough office, you can get rice and food.
And there are gift certificates in here, too. Here.
Miss, my family doesn't need help.
I have both Mom and Dad, and we're rich.
So, I don't need stuff like this.
Tteokbokki. I paid for the tteokbokki yesterday, so...
Hey, Do Ra.
I'm sorry, Miss.
It's true I don't have a father since he passed away.
I'll take the coupons from earlier.
My goodness.
I'm afraid these were ruined.
Where do you live?
I'll carry them for you. Is it far from here?
No.
It's that way over there.
Give me that.
Oh, okay.
You can carry that, right?
Yes.
Hey, Go Dae Choong! Where are you going?
Noona, eat the popsicle and wait.
I'll help her carry these quickly and come back.
Let's go. That way?
Yes.
Is this your place?
Yes, you can go now. I'm on the first floor here.
Do you live in the neighborhood, too?
I don't think we've met.
No, I live in Seoul.
Seoul?
Really?
Yes. I'm just here to get some fresh air today.
Bye, then.
Hold on.
What's your phone number?
I don't have a cell phone.
Why? What do you want my number for?
Because I'm grateful. I'll return the favor later.
Favor?
It's okay. It's nothing.
Bye, kid.
He's such a cool oppa.
I haven't met someone that cool, even at the broadcasting station.
What was his name again?
Go Dae...
I should've asked his name, at least. What a dummy.
So you brought all this, Do Ra?
Yes.
Hey! What are we, beggars?
Why did you accept stuff like this?
What's wrong with it? Don't eat it, then.
Do Jun and I will eat it.
Noona, I'm hungry.
Can I eat this ramen?
Of course. You can have two if you want.
Wow, I'm so excited.
Here.
Noona, Hyung, it's so tasty. Super tasty.
Yes, it's really tasty.
Hyung, Noona, when is Mom coming home?
I like this uncooked ramen,
but I want her beef potato stew, too.
I told you. You have to wait for her for 10 days.
It's already been 10 days, though.
Baek Mi Ja.
Where's Baek Mi Ja hiding?
Come out right now, Baek Mi Ja!
Where's that little rat hiding?
Where did your mom go?
Tell us right now.
M-Mom isn't here.
Are you serious right now?
You bought a boxful of ramen after stealing my money.
Where's your mom? Huh?
Where's that scamming thief?
Hyung! Noona!
We don't know. We don't know. We don't know, either.
Get out of our house right now!
You can't just barge into someone's house with shoes on!
How dare you yell at us!
- Let go! Let go.
- No! Let go...
Let go.
Tell your mom exactly this.
To pay back the money she borrowed.
Bring me the money and get this kid back.
Let's go.
- No!
Let go!
- What are you doing?
- Let go of me!
- Let go!
- No, no!
Let go. Let go.
- Let go. Let go!
Noona!
- No, let go of me!
- Stay put.
- Do Jun!
- No!
- Noona!
You can't take him. Give him back to us.
- Move it.
- Mom said she'll pay you back.
- Get out of the way.
- Give us Do Jun back, please.
Don't do this. You can't.
Tell your mom to come immediately. Immediately.
We have no idea where she is, either.
We can't even reach her. It's true.
So, please give us Do Jun back. Please.
Seriously, come on. Let go of me!
- Hyung. Noona.
- I'll call the police and tell them you kidnapped him!
Tell your mom to pay me back immediately.
Otherwise, I'll sue her.
Let go of him.
- Noona.
- Do Jun.
- Let's go.
- Are you okay?
I'm sorry. Let's go in.
Guys, Do Ra, wake up. Pack your things.
Get dressed. Get dressed.
Do Shik, Do Shik?
Do Shik. Wake up, wake up.
- Wake up, Do Shik. Get dressed.
- Where are we going?
Be quiet and get dressed.
Get up. Get dressed and pack your things.
Mom, where are we going?
We're moving.
Mom, did you pay off the debt, then?
We're moving because we did.
You're serious, right?
Gosh, Ma'am. You can't bring in a family with three children.
Wait, what's going on?
Didn't you say you had one daughter? That's why we signed the contract.
Well, I thought so, too. But this is what I saw today.
You had three kids, but you lied, saying you only had one daughter to sign the contract?
I'm sorry. Please forgive me just once.
They're nice and quiet kids.
We'll live cleanly and quietly.
No other places had a security deposit in the price range.
What's going on here?
In-law, listen to this.
She had three children,
but she lied to the realtor, saying she had one daughter to sign the contract with us.
The place is already tiny. This isn't right.
- Seon Yeong.
- Yes.
So what if she has one kid or three?
The kids can hear you.
- In-law...
- Yes?
the house will feel rejuvenated and bright with many children.
- O-Oh, yes.
- Yes.
Welcome to our house.
Let me know if you feel uncomfortable with anything.
Thank you.
I'll be out for dinner, then.
See you later. Be careful.
Seriously, In-law is way too kind. Too kind.
They already moved in. What can we do?
Go inside, then.
Yes, thank you.
Our kids are really well-behaved.
I'll make sure we're quiet.
Thank you. Thank you.
- I'm home.
- Welcome home, Son.
Why are you all out here?
They just moved in. Say hello.
Hello.
This is my son.
Huh? Are you that little kid?
Oppa from Seoul?
Something that makes no sense at all happened.
I can't believe I ran into him here again.
Is this that oppa's house?
Go, go. Go in. Go inside.
Wow. Mom, the bathroom is so clean. I love it.
Wow. Wow, it's nice.
Wow. It's small, but it has everything.
Wow, how nice.
- Mom.
- Yes?
- I'm so glad we moved in here. I mean it.
- Right?
By the way, Mom, aren't you supposed to eat jjajangmyeon and tangsuyuk the day you move?
Jjajangmyeon. Jjajangmyeon. Mom, I want jjajangmyeon and tangsuyuk.
Yes, let's have tangsuyuk and jjajangmyeon today.
Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
Are you happy?
Wow, it's so nice.
Seriously, I don't like that woman.
How could she lie that she has only one daughter?
She couldn't pay more security deposit. What can we do?
It's hard to find a clean place with a cheap security deposit in the neighborhood.
What does her husband do, exactly?
- Did his business fail?
- I heard he's dead.
My gosh, he's dead?
Yes. I saw the youngest boy in the yard, so I asked him when his dad was coming home.
But he said he's dead, and he's in heaven.
I asked him without much thought.
I felt so guilty. I felt sorry for him, too.
Is she a w-widow, then?
She's a widow with three kids. Why was she dressed like that earlier?
Gosh, I don't think she's just a typical widow.
Why did she have to be a widow? How unsettling.
You're a widow, too. Why are you mean to other widows?
Hey!
Mom, I need 50,000 won to buy a workbook.
- Okay. What kind of workbook?
- Huh?
A math workbook.
Okay, got it.
Let's see.
Here. 60,000 won.
I gave you an extra 10,000 won. Get something to eat if you get hungry while studying.
Thank you, Mother.
Gosh, you little.
How come your wallet opens for Dae Choong so easily?
Why do you buy workbooks all the time?
Are you sure you aren't just taking money?
Auntie, how could you say that?
What do you think of me exactly?
You buy workbooks all the time,
but why aren't your grades improving?
You're poking a sensitive spot again.
Do you want to fight me today, Auntie?
Don't be like that. I'm sure they will improve soon.
Dae Chung, I'll always pay for academy tuition and workbooks.
Just focus on your studies, okay?
Yes, Sir.
- I'll be back.
- Okay.
See you later.
He's your boyfriend, not your son.
By the way, I know she's your best friend,
but isn't it too much to help with your friend's late father-in-law's memorial service?
And even without your help, they're a chaebol family after all.
They must have plenty of chefs to cook for the memorial service.
Soo Yeon's daughter and her husband, Chairman Gong, like my shikhye  (traditional sweet Korean rice beverage) .
So, I just thought I should.
I put some shikhye in the fridge, Mother. Make sure to have some.
I'll be right back. See you.
See you later.
She works so hard to make shikhye for her friend's late father-in-law's memorial service.
But she treats her mother-in-law, who is alive and well, like a neighborhood stray dog.
What did she say? Get it from the fridge?
Gosh, Mom. It's not hard to get it from the fridge. I'll get it for you.
Forget it.
What a bitch. I won't drink her shikhye out of spite.
Gosh, this is great shikhye. Isn't it, Mom?
Yes. Gosh.
Hey, your sister-in-law is good at making shikhye.
She's good at making other stuff, too.
By the way, doesn't she have any self-respect?
Does she really want to go to her friend's father-in-law's memorial service all the time?
Gosh, I'm upset for her.
Her friend treats her like they're sisters.
That's why she's doing this.
Think about how much her friend cares for Dae Chung.
It's not easy to care for your friend's son.
I suppose. By the way,
why is a madam of a chaebol family friends with your unimpressive sister-in-law?
They're obsessed with each other.
Isn't that such a mystery?
You're right.
Maybe Seon Yeong is going for a big-picture goal.
Big-picture goal?
Like what?
Her friend apparently has a very cute and pretty daughter.
Is she trying to make Dae Chung their son-in-law...
Is she laying the ground to become in-laws with her, by chance?
Aigoo, come on. What chaebol family would have an adopted child as a son-in-law—
Geez, what's the big deal? It's just between us.
Mom, you'll get kicked out of the house if Seon Yeong hears that.
You'll get me kicked out, too.
- I'm home.
- You scared me.
Gosh, what's wrong? Why are you so scared?
It's nothing, Oppa.
W-Where's Seon Yeong?
Well, she...
She went to her friend's father-in-law's memorial service. That's where she went.
I see. At Soo Yeon's?
Yes.
Okay.
That was a close one.
Come on.
It's me. I'm on my way now.
Okay.
I won't let it slide today.
I'll destroy them.
Ma Ri, you can take a deep bow for Grandpa, right?
Of course.
Two and a half bow.
You're impressive. Yes.
- You should join her, Honey.
- Okay.
Hold on! Stop!
I'll take a bow, too. I will.
It's my honey's memorial service. Why only leave me out?
Are you crazy? How dare you show up here drunk?
Let go of me!
Am I not allowed to be here?
I'll take a bow just like the granddaughter and daughter-in-law here.
I have the right to take a bow, too.
Chairman, I'm here.
Hong Ae Gyo, whom you used to love and cherish so much, is here.
You're crazy. You're crazy. I'm sorry.
- Get up. Get up right now.
- Mom.
Get out of the way, Mom.
I want to take a bow to my darling chairman. Why are you stopping me, Mom?
Everyone! Don't move!
Don't try to drag me out of here.
If you do, I'll bite my tongue and die here.
Ma Ri, you should go upstairs.
Seon Yeong.
Oh, okay.
Let's go upstairs, Ma Ri.
Jin Dan is my son.
That's an unchangeable fact, and I'm proving it.
So, add Jin Dan as Gong Jin Dan to my family registry.
Give him one of the subsidiary companies.
Hong Ae Gyo is the mother of my son.
She's been hiding her whole life because of me.
So, treat her politely even when I'm dead and gone.
I'll be watching from heaven.
Why don't you answer, Gong Jin Taek? Answer me.
Yes. I will, Father.
Jin Taek Oppa, you said yes to him.
Why won't you let me take a bow at his memorial service, then?
He told you to treat me politely.
Why are you looking down on me, then?
Why are you ignoring his last words?
He's looking at you from heaven right now!
Jin Dan.
My baby.
Gosh, Jin Dan. When did you get here, my son?
Did you get a vacation for Father's memorial service?
Jin Dan, I'm so glad you're here today.
I no longer want to live as his hidden woman anymore.
I can no longer live in hiding anymore.
My Jin Dan is your brother since you share a father, Jin Taek Oppa.
What am I to you, then?
Jin Dan calls me "Mom."
Oppa, you should start calling me "Mother" from now on, too.
And you, Jang Soo Yeon.
You should start calling me "Mother" from now on, too, okay?
And instead of living in the annex outside,
I'll live in the main house here.
I'll use the room Chairman Gong Dae Gil, my honey, used to use.
No one can stop me!
Ae Gyo, no, no.
Grandmother!
Don't stop my mother.
Hyungnim.
I apologize on behalf of Mother.
I'm sorry for causing a disturbance at Father's memorial service.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I want to be alone. Please leave now.
Hyungnim.
I know what you think of my mother and me.
Despite that, you accepted me as your brother.
I've always been grateful for that.
I know it's...
hard for you to forgive my mother, yet,
but she had it tough for a long time, too.
There's Father's will, too.
Could you please accept my mother now?
She's been living in the annex... and I've been living in the main house.
It made me very uncomfortable.
I don't think we can continue doing this.
Once I get married or get my own place later,
I'll take Mother with me.
Please let my mother...
be a part of this family for once, at least for a few years.
So that she'd finally stop being resentful.
I beg you.
Hyungnim.
Gosh, Honey. That's unthinkable.
I can't live in the same house as Ae Gyo.
Do you think I want to?
It's impossible when I consider my late mother.
But what else can we do?
We can't ignore Father's will, either.
She even played the audio recording.
Are you sure about this? Can you handle it?
There are no other options.
It's not like we can kick her out, either.
Jin Dan said he'll get a place for them later. Until then...
Let's just do it until then.
This isn't such a simple matter.
Ae Gyo moving into Mother and Father's old bedroom
means we'll accept her as an elder of our house.
Are you sure you can call her "Mother"?
I can't.
I can't call my high school classmate "Mother."
Just keep that in mind.
You little. You wench!
Get out. Get out. Get out.
No! Over my dead body.
I'll become a ghost in this room.
My goodness. Can you call yourself a human?
Are you human?
You're less than an animal.
My goodness. When we were about to go out on the streets, Madam took us in.
That's how we were able to live like humans.
But instead of being grateful to the Madam, you seduced her husband.
She cried bloody tears before she passed because of you, wench.
How dare you come in here after that? How dare you?
Gosh, Madam. How could I see her face when I die?
- Get out. Get out, you brat.
- I don't want to.
You're unforgivable. Get out.
Grandmother, that's enough.
Grandmother, don't do that to Mom anymore.
Doing that to her is the same thing as insulting me.
What?
And Hyungnim approved...
Mom living here.
W-W-What did you say?
Are you sure? Did he really approve it?
Soo Yeon, why are you giving me so much?
It's not that much. It's nice to share.
I know Dae Chung likes meat. Grill some for him.
- Thanks.
- He should eat a lot at that age.
What's this?
Oh, Seon Yeong, it's because I'm so thankful. I am.
Come on. You don't do this between friends. Then, I can't come over again.
I won't come next year, then.
Come on, girl. Can't you just accept my gratitude, Seon Yeong?
Okay. Think of it as pocket money for Dae Chung, then.
Pocket money from his aunt.
Please? Seon Yeong.
Gosh, seriously.
Okay. Thank you.
No, I should be thanking you.
No one else cares for me like this.
By the way, is Ae Gyo out of her mind?
How could she tell you to call her "Mother"?
I already knew she was thick-skinned, but...
What will you do now?
You'll see her every time you wake up.
I don't know.
I don't even want to imagine what would happen.
That oppa must study really hard.
He still hasn't come home.
♫  I want nobody, nobody but you  ♫
My gosh! You scared me.
♫  Nobody, nobody  ♫
Geez. My heart skipped a beat.
What are you doing here instead of sleeping at this hour, little kid?
The thing is...
I was waiting for you, Oppa.
You were waiting for me?
Why?
You helped me carry heavy stuff last time.
I'm so grateful for that.
This is to express my gratitude.
Make sure to hang it on your backpack.
Gosh, you shouldn't have.
That wasn't a big deal at all.
But that's not how I feel about it, okay?
Okay, then. Thank you.
Wow. Anyway, you're so well-mannered.
Thank you so much.
By the way, wasn't the Noona you were with that time your sister?
I saw your whole family earlier, but I didn't see her.
I want to say hello to her, too.
What?
Oh, right...
Well, she's not my biological sister. She's just a Noona I know.
Oh, I see.
But it's so fascinating that I ran into you here again.
Thinking about it, it's totally crazy.
How could this be? What are the odds that this happened?
Right? Isn't it crazy?
Who put the bridge of connection between us?
Oppa and I. Are we meant to be, by chance?
Hey, you should go inside and get to sleep.
Hey, your eyes look sleepy.
You look out of it.
Pardon?
Oh, okay. You sleep tight, too.
Hey, you almost fell and broke your nose if it wasn't for me just now.
Be sure to stay focused from now on, okay?
Good night.
He and I are meant to be now.
He's my prince.
I'll say goodbye to Heechul of Super Junior now.
That oppa is mine now.
- Thank you.
- So expensive. It's so expensive.
That woman is renting a room from your house,
but she's pretending as if she's from Gangnam.
- Who?
- Who else is there?
Oh, that's Do Ra and her mom, our tenants.
She needs to know her place.
She wants to make her daughter an actor. Look at her now.
She's dragging her around instead of sending her to school.
How money-obsessed do you have to be to do that to your kid?
Aigoo. She doesn't make her skip school every day.
I suppose she has an audition or something today.
She's not just a normal woman. Be careful.
What do you mean, be careful?
Didn't you hear the rumor about her?
Rumor? What rumor?
Seon Yeong.
Hey, Seon Yeong. Seon Yeong, listen.
I think we should evict Do Ra's mom from the guest house.
What are you talking about?
They just moved in. How could we kick them out already?
Say the room Myeong Dong and I use is too tight
and Myeong Dong has to use that room.
Try to get her out somehow.
Why, Mother? Did something happen?
Gosh, the thing is...
Well, there are very bad rumors about Do Ra's mom.
It's weird that she puts on a lot of makeup to go out every night, right?
What else does a woman do with that much makeup on at night?
I suppose...
- I did find that a bit strange.
- She's strange.
Gosh, I wonder if people would think badly of us because of her.
Right on. That's it.
Seon Yeong.
How could you say stuff like that?
Dad.
Do Ra's mom is trying to make ends meet while raising three children by herself.
Instead of helping her living in the same house,
how could you say something so mean?
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'll be out.
Dad, you should wear a scarf, at least.
It will be cold tonight.
You don't want to catch a cold.
Hold on.
He was talking to me just now, wasn't he?
Gosh, I get it. You used to be a school principal.
How dare he lecture and yell at me?
Hello, I'm...
Park Do Ra's mom.
Yes...
Hello, hello. I'm Park Do Ra's mom.
Do Ra worked very hard for this.
I hope you like her.
Yes.
You think we can meet today?
Oppa.
I'll be there as soon as I'm out of school.
Dae Chung must've gotten a girlfriend.
I wonder who.
He can't have a girlfriend.
Dad, my friends have been mean to me.
I've been bullied.
My school uniform skirt was covered with dirt...
Covered with dirt and... so...
It was covered with dirt and torn up,
but no one in the family has noticed it.
But the teacher noticed it and saved me.
Say that.
Gosh, you little. Seriously.
How could you ruin this important audition after what I told you?
How could you get beaten by Bibi, not just anyone? Bibi?
Aigoo, seriously. How could you forget all the lines you memorized?
I said acting is all about focusing.
It's about getting into it.
Do you know how much money I spent today because of you?
For the transportation, pastries, and drinks when I'm already broke.
What will you do now? What will you do? What will you do?
I never said I wanted to become an actor.
Why don't you become one if you want it so badly?
Why are you forcing me? Why?
That little brat!
Go home and care for Do Sik and Do Jun.
- I need to go to work, okay?
- Whatever.
Gosh, that little. Gosh...
Dae Chung goes to a hair salon to straighten his curly hair every day.
He comes home late every day.
And he always giggles while texting.
He doesn't come home late because he studies.
I'm sure there's something going on.
I'll make sure to find out today.
- Yeah. I know. It's so good.
- Where?
- So cold. Let's go. Let's hurry.
- Freezing.
See you later.
See you.
What?
What's with that motorcycle?
Dae Chung!
Noona.
You're right on time.
That unni is...
That's Jeong Mi from Sol Hair Salon.
Where are we going today?
We'll go anywhere you want to go.
Really? Will you travel to the ends of the earth, then?
Of course, I will.
Just tell me where. I'll drive to the ends of the earth if that's what you want.
Dae Chung.
Noona, look.
Yay.
- Hang tight, Noona.
- Go, go!
What did I...
see just now?
No.
I'm sure they're just good friends.
There's no way they're a boyfriend and a girlfriend.
Dae Chung is a high school student.
There's no way he'd date an older unni like her.
There's no way.
Dae Chung, it was so exciting and fun today.
Me, too, Noona.
You should go now.
Good night, Noona.
Good night.
Bye!
Excuse me.
Huh? Do Ra.
Did you call me just now?
Yes.
Huh? What is it?
Are you here to get your hair done at this hour?
Hey, why are you glaring at me?
Unni, what's your relationship with Dae Chung Oppa?
I saw everything. Be honest with me.
Well, why do I have to tell you?
You can't be dating a high school student, right?
There's no way, right?
This is unbelievable.
Do Ra, little kids like you don't have to know.
I'm not a little kid, okay?
- I know you're really old.
- What?
Why were you on the back of Dae Chung Oppa's motorcycle, then?
How does that make sense?
You can't do that with a high school student.
Do Ra, age is not important when it comes to romance.
I suppose a little kid like you won't understand.
Do Ra, go home, eat a lot, and grow up quickly.
You'll understand then, okay?
You're so cute.
You're so cute, Do Ra.
Bye.
Auntie.
I'm not a little kid, I said.
Park Do Ra.
What are you doing here this time?
Oppa, does your mom know what you're doing?
What...
What? What did I do?
I was studying at the library, okay?
Whoa, you're lying now?
You've been riding the motorcycle with old Jeong Mi everywhere.
And you say a library?
Ahjumma! Dae Chung is...
You said you aren't dating Jeong Mi, okay?
That's what I'm telling you.
We're just good friends, okay?
So, you can never tell my mom, okay?
Fine.
You promised you won't see Jeong Mi again, okay?
Okay.
You promised not to let her on the motorcycle, too, okay?
Be a man and keep your promise, okay?
Okay. I will, I said.
By the way, Oppa...
- What?
- You'll be in 12th grade next year.
You can't just have fun without studying like that.
Don't you worry about your future?
How will you make a living?
I'm saying all this for your future.
Study hard and come home early from now on, okay?
Okay, I said. So, just stuff yourself with this tteokbokki.
Okay.
Oppa, I think the secret is too serious for me to keep.
So, tteokbokki won't be quite enough.
- What did you say?
- You're a good dancer.
Do Super Junior's "Sorry, Sorry" dance just once.
I'll make sure to keep your promise, then.
Will you keep this up?
You don't want to? Fine.
Ahjumma is probably still awake.
Hey.
♫  Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry  ♫
♫  I, I, I fell for you, you, you first  ♫
Again, again.
♫  I'm going crazy, crazy, baby  ♫
- Here you go. Enjoy.
- Thank you.
It's good.
Yes.
- This place really is good.
- Yes, it is.
Sir, this is on the house. Enjoy.
- Yes, thank you.
- Sure.
Ahjumma! Get us another soju.
Okay.
Just go ahead. Cheers.
- Here's soju.
- Since you're cool,
- Ahjumma.
- we're being treated, too.
Pour me a glass.
- Pardon?
- Pour me a glass.
Oh, okay.
Ahjumma.
You look young.
What are you doing? Let go!
Don't play hard to get working at a place like this.
I am hard to get.
So, pay me first if you want to touch me.
Do you think I'm a joke because I work at a place like this? Let go!
What? Give me your hand.
- Let go of her.
- Who are you?
What are you doing right now?
Let go of her before I call the police.
Everyone here is watching.
Seriously, how annoying.
It's done. Let's eat now.
Wow, I'm excited.
Hot, hot, hot!
Hot! It's hot!
- Do Jun!
- It hurts here.
Does it hurt a lot? What do we do?
Let me look. Let me.
Gosh, what do we do?
Are you okay?
- It's hot.
- What do we do?
- D-Does it hurt a lot?
- Yeah.
- Gosh, what do we do?
- What's this?
What's this mess?
Mom, I made ramen but spilled it on Do Jun's foot.
It wasn't a lot, but a little...
- What do we do?
- It hurts, Mom!
Gosh, give me a break!
Gosh, seriously!
Gosh, what do we do? You've got to be kidding me.
- Let me look, Do Jun.
- Are you okay?
- Let me look. Let me look.
- Mom.
Let me look. Let me look.
Gosh, you've got to be kidding me! Seriously...
Gosh, seriously...
- Mom...
- Seriously...
- What's going on?
- Don't you know what time it is?
I told you to come home early and care for your brothers, didn't I?
Seriously! Geez!
Let's all go out and die instead of living like this!
What's the point of living like this? What's the point?
I'm sorry, Mom. I'll never do it again.
I won't come home late from now on.
I'll take good care of them, too. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mom. I'll never make ramen again.
It's my fault.
It's my fault. I won't say I'm hungry anymore.
I said I wanted to eat ramen.
Your dad is the worst man in this world.
How could he leave us behind?
How am I supposed to live? How?
I'm sorry, Mom. I'll never do it again.
While you're at work,
I'll cook and do the laundry, too.
Don't cry, Mom. I'll grow up quickly...
Park Do Ra.
Oppa.
I'll give you a ride to the school.
Hop on.
Do Ra, hold my waist tightly.
You won't fall that way, okay?
Okay.
What's this?
He really is my prince.
Being on his bike...
turned my sad and depressing mood into a fluffy and pink one.
Yes, he likes me, too.
That's why he waited for me to give me a bike ride.
I'll forever remember our first date today.
This is how our love is bubbling up.
Sir.
Thank you for helping me yesterday.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Please don't tell anyone that I work there.
I know. Don't worry.
Well, then.
- Dad.
- Hey.
What did you talk about with Ms. Baek?
We just said hello.
- Is it coffee?
- Yes.
I only added a half spoonful of sugar today.
You can't drink it too sweet. It's bad for you.
Why do you keep reducing it?
A full spoon and a half spoon aren't that different.
It's still good, right?
My coffee is the best in the world, right?
It's the best.
My gosh, Dae Chung.
I knew it was your car.
Are you here to see Mom?
Why are you out here instead of going in?
Well, it's something else today.
I was running an errand in the area, and...
I... I got a call. So I was on the phone for a moment.
I see.
Did you do well on your exam? You look happy.
I think I just did okay.
How did you know I had an exam, by the way?
Huh? Well, everyone's been freaking out about the exam lately.
Excuse me.
Dae Chung.
Do you want this?
I think it will fit you.
What's this?
I got it as a sample but thought it would fit you.
Ahjumma, this brand is really popular these days.
I really wanted one, but it was so expensive.
So, I couldn't even ask my mom.
Are you sure I can wear this, Ahjumma?
Yes.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Gosh, it's a large size, and you're big enough already.
You grew a lot, Dae Chung.
Do You think I look okay?
Yes, it suits you well. Very cool.
Ahjumma, I really appreciate it.
I'll become successful and return the favor.
It's nothing. Don't worry about it.
I'll get going now. Get home safely.
- Thank you. Take care.
- Bye.
Son.
Oh, my.
What's that, Go Dae Chung? Where did you get that jacket?
What do you think, Mom?
Don't you think your son looks cool?
This is an expensive brand.
This must cost a pretty penny.
My gosh, this is brand new.
Where... Where did you get this expensive jacket?
You'd better be honest with me, okay?
By chance...
By chance... By chance, what?
What kind of negative thoughts are you having right now?
Do you think I, Go Dae Chung, stole money from you?
Soo Yeon Ahjumma got it for me, okay?
What? Soo Yeon?
Hey, it's me, Seon Yeong.
Soo Yeon, Dae Chung told me you were in front of our house today.
Why didn't you call me, then?
Well, I was running an errand around there
and I got a call while passing by, so I pulled over.
But Dae Chung recognized my car and said hello.
Oh, I see.
Hey, but still.
You can't just leave without stopping by if you were all the way here.
Jin Taek said he was coming home early today.
I'll make sure to call next time.
Okay. By the way, why did you give Dae Chung such an expensive jacket? You'd spoil him.
Gosh, not at all.
He won't get spoiled for something like that.
I got it as a sample, but no one in my family could wear it.
I don't have a son, either.
I let him try it on since I ran into him, and it fit him perfectly.
Did he like it, by the way?
Isn't it obvious?
He got all excited and did a fashion show before he left.
He said he'll study better because of the jacket today.
Really? I'm so happy that he likes it.
Okay, Seon Yeong. Let's talk later.
Bye.
Mom.
Princess, please knock.
Sorry. What are you doing, Mom?
Huh?
What photo were you looking at?
Was it a photo of me?
Yes, it was one of you.
Because I'm so pretty and cute?
Yes. Because you're so pretty, Ma Ri.
My Ma Ri is so pretty. The prettiest in the world.
- See you.
- Bye.
He actually danced because I told him to.
He's so cute.
What a dummy.
What's that? That's...
Sir. Sir, please follow that motorcycle!
Hurry, Sir!
Are you crazy? Did you rent this bus?
- Pardon?
- Go sit down. You'll get hurt.
I'm sorry.
He promised that he'd never see her again.
How could he do this?
How could he lie to me?
Just wait and see.
I'll never forgive you.
Gosh, Do Ra. What are you talking about right now?
Dae Chung was riding a motorcycle with a woman?
Yes, she's much older than him, too.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Do Ra, he doesn't have a motorcycle.
He doesn't even know how to ride one.
This is how clueless moms are about their children.
Well, my mom has no idea I like Dae Chung, either.
Hey, Do Ra. What's wrong?
What's going on?
Ahjumma, what would you do if everything I said were true?
Are you kidding? What are you saying?
Good night, Noona.
Good night, Dae Chung.
Hold on.
To celebrate the first snow this year...
Hey!
What are you... What are you doing to my son right now?
- Well...
- You crazy bitch! Crazy bitch!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
My son is a high school student.
Do you know what your niece did to my son?
- Help!
- Stop, Mom. Stop.
How dare you, you brat.
What have you been doing?
Gosh, I won't let this slide. Hey!
Wow, Ahjumma is freaking scary.
She totally lost it.
♫  You showed up, made my heart flutter, and got me excited over and over again  ♫
♫  You keep finding me without fail  ♫
♫  So I can't think about anything else  ♫
♫  I think this is what they call fate  ♫
♫  The sky is clearer than usual, and my feet feel light  ♫
What are you doing in here, Ms. Baek?
Did you steal from our house just now?
Do you think I want to live like this?
He seems very capable.
He must have savings from being a principal, and he gets a pension regularly, too.
Where could all that money go?
How dare you tear us apart? Why?
How dare an adopted child cause a scene like this?
Who am I if I'm not your son?
Where did I come from?