I wanted to study, but I had no money.
That's why I did that for money.
I did what he told me to do.
"He"?
Who's he?
Who told you to do it?
Jin Sang Gu. It's Jin Sang Gu.
Jin Sang Gu?
W-Who's Jin Sang Gu?
Mom.
Mom, what are you saying right now?
Who's my dad right now?
How could someone like this be my dad?
Are you out of your mind?
Jin Dan, he really is your dad.
The one who gave you life. Your biological father.
So, please stop hitting him.
Why do you keep hitting your dad?
Don't do that, Jin Dan.
Mom...
why would you say something so crazy?
It's not true, right?
It can't be true, right?
What bullshit are you saying right now?
Why do you keep hitting him?
He's your dad.
Yes, Jin Dan.
To be honest, I'm your father.
Arggghhh!
Jin Dan! Jin Dan!
Jin Dan, Jin Dan, are you okay?
Don't even call my name.
Jin Dan.
I don't want to look at your face and I don't even want to call you mom.
Who's my dad?
Someone like him is my birth father?
How could I suddenly have a different father?
Are you joking?
How dare you taint my name like this?
I'm sorry, Jin Dan. I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
Mom, were you always such a scary person?
How could you deceive everyone completely
and pretend Chairman Gong Dae Gil was my dad?
Has everything been an act, then?
No, no, Jin Dan.
I didn't know, either.
I didn't deceive people on purpose.
I just found out recently, too.
I never imagined that you'd be Sang Gu's son.
But he said you might be his son.
So, I did a DNA test. And...
Stop talking such bullshit!
How could a loser like him be my father?
I'm Chairman Gong Dae Gil's son.
I'm Gong Jin Dan.
Gong Jin Dan!
The sauces are tasty, too. Pick the one you like.
Let me know if you need anything else.
Pil Sung, you should go home now.
- Hurry.
- Why, Dad?
Do you not want to pay me that much?
Come on. It's not that.
I feel bad because you're tiring yourself out.
What do you mean? I'm not tired at all.
And Father, I think this might be my calling.
- What?
- You saw it just now, right?
The customers gave me two thumbs up because I grilled tasty meat.
Two more servings, please!
Okay, just one moment!
Do Ra, I'm so sorry.
I've been a fan of Park Do Ra for a long time and you cleared your name, too.
That's why I contacted you to work together.
But the public opinion is still so negative.
And the production company was so opposed to it.
I told the assistant director to explain the situation this morning.
I don't know why he hasn't called you yet.
I'm so sorry about all this.
It's okay.
I'm just thankful you thought positively of me and reached out.
I'll contact you again if I get a chance.
Okay, thank you.
I do feel bad for Park Do Ra.
She was a good actor.
How did the queen of romance, Park Do Ra, become such a reject?
What do you mean, you feel bad?
She has a poor sense of reality.
She needs to stay out of the limelight. How dare she try to act already?
Even though she was framed for prostitution and whatnot, she has the scarlet letter on her.
She's out of her mind wanting to work again.
It's hard to change your image once it's established.
Hey, Assistant Director.
It's okay. Talk to me.
Director Yun?
Really?
Okay, I'll call him later.
Thank you.
She must know the industry if she worked since she was a kid.
The fact that she came here means she's clueless.
Actors are all about their image.
Who'd cast Park Do Ra now?
I think it's probably over for her now.
Do Ra.
What's with you?
Seriously.
You scared me.
So childish. What are you, a child?
I knew you'd laugh.
I just needed one laugh.
Mission accomplished.
Seriously.
Thank you, Oppa.
I was in a terrible mood today.
But I laughed, thanks to you.
It turns out I can actually laugh.
I heard that...
you met with Director Yun today.
I was very upset earlier and...
wondered why people still think of me that way.
But thinking about it,
the situation now makes sense.
I didn't intend to deceive people,
but it's true I fooled them and lied to them.
It's natural that people won't forgive me and think poorly of me.
Do Ra,
let's take a break for a while.
You worked too hard when you were Do Ra or Kim Ji Yeong.
Let's do what we want to do and eat tasty food, too.
Let's take trips to nice places, too.
We'll go on many dates, too.
They say you're supposed to take a break after a fall.
Why don't we think of this as a vacation?
Vacation?
Okay.
I like the sound of that.
I've been working so hard all this time.
I need a vacation, too, right?
Of course.
When a door closes, another one opens, they say.
Not being able to act doesn't mean my life is over.
As you said, I'll think of it as a vacation and rest.
I'll think about what I'd like to do.
Jin Dan must be shocked that someone like me is his dad.
How is he?
Is he taking it pretty hard?
Yes, I think so.
He won't even answer my calls.
Why did you have to tell him?
I deserve to be beaten to death by him.
We've been doing a good job not telling him.
Why did you have to?
Seeing my son cry...
broke my heart in pieces.
What do we do with our Jin Dan, Ae Gyo?
Aigoo. My goodness.
What's he... What's he talking about?
"Our Jin Dan."
"M-My son."
What...
I-If so, President G-Gong...
was Jin Sang Gu's son?
My gosh. My gosh.
My goodness.
What's going on, exactly?
Did some weirdo follow you on the way?
The thing is...
Gosh, how frustrating.
Go on and talk to us right now, mom!
President Gong...
is Jin Sang Gu's son.
Gosh, Mother. What's this now?
Mom, did you eat something funny again?
Why would you say something like that?
Gosh, I really...
I don't know why I saw that.
On my way back from the bathhouse, I saw Jin Sang Gu crying on the phone.
So, I followed him, wondering what was going on.
And he said,
"Ae Gyo, why did you tell Jin Dan I'm his dad?"
And he kept crying.
That's what he said.
No way.
Y-You must've heard it wrong, Mother.
Hey! I'm not deaf yet.
And how could I make up a story like this?
If I did, God would punish me for it.
I suppose. You can't make up stuff like that.
Unless you lost your mind.
You little.
Hey, Sang Gu definitely said this back then.
That he met his first love, and they have a son together.
And then he denied it.
Everything makes sense now.
Seon Yeong, Seon Yeong,
shouldn't we tell Chairman Gong about this?
Gosh, Mother. How could we tell him that without evidence?
It'd flip their house upside down.
How...
How could a bastard like him be my father?
How?
Hey, it's me.
Ae Gyo, something bad happened.
What is it? What's going on?
Jin Dan wants to see me. But he wants to meet by the river.
There are no people around there.
I'm scared, Ae Gyo. I'm afraid... that he'd do something to me out of anger.
Sang Gu, where's the place he wanted to meet?
You came.
You must be very shocked because of me.
I'm not here to share gross words with you.
Pack your things and leave Korea immediately.
And don't ever show up in front of my mom and me.
You were never supposed to show up in front of us.
I didn't show up on purpose. Didn't your mom tell you?
I found out only recently, too.
I was so drawn to you, so I asked her about you.
And we found out through the DNA test.
I...
was so happy that you were my son.
I'll never be an obstacle in your life.
Let's see each other from time to time, Jin Dan.
I'm still your father, you know.
Who says you're my father?
You aren't my father.
What are you trying to pull right now?
J-Jin Dan.
Are you saying you won't leave?
Are you saying you'd still attach yourself to us?
Jin Dan, don't do that! Don't hit him!
Please don't hit him.
All you do is take money from my mom.
How dare you call yourself a father?
Jin Dan, please let go.
Let's talk instead. Let's talk.
O-Okay, I'll leave. I'll leave.
Leave this very moment.
Right now!
Okay, I'll leave.
Don't be angry, Jin Dan.
I'm sorry that I'm your father.
I'll leave.
Hey, aren't you being too cruel?
You grab him by his collar and hit him.
He's still your father who gave you life.
Wake up, Mom!
What do you mean, "father"?
He always takes money from you.
- How is he a father?
- No.
He spent that money for you.
Do you know what kind of things he did for you?
If he didn't know you were his son, he wouldn't have caused Ma Ri's accident!
What do you mean by that?
Ma Ri's accident?
Tell me one more time.
Ma Ri's accident...
That bastard did it?
Is that right?
I told him you've been treated poorly by the Gong family.
He said he won't let you live like that anymore.
If Ma Ri were gone, you'd be the head of the Gong family and no one would treat you poorly.
That's why he did it.
He said he wanted to do something for you.
Grandma, Oppa, what are you doing?
We're making kalguksu.
I keep craving her kalguksu, no matter how much I eat it.
So, I asked her to make it.
It really is a shame that we're the only ones to eat it.
Oppa, should we open a kalguksu shop, then?
Kalguksu shop? I'll do it.
I want to run a restaurant.
Gosh, why would you suddenly say that?
And you need to act.
Oppa,
I don't think I can act like I used to for a while.
You know, too.
The public opinion is still negative and people aren't ready to accept me yet.
Well, yes.
But we can't just keep sitting around.
We need to make a living, too.
And it'd be a shame to waste Grandma's recipe, too.
Let's try it, Oppa.
Yes, I'd love to.
Geum Dong, let's do it.
Okay, let's do it. Let's give it a try, Mother. Yes.
- Yes, yes, yes!
- Yes!
Yes! I love it!
Would you really be okay?
You've been acting since you were 13. Can you live without acting?
That's why I want to try doing something else, too.
I actually sold kalguksu with Grandma for two years.
I lived so happily back then, too.
Oppa, let's sell kalguksu and become successful.
- Okay, let's just go for it.
- Yes.
By the way, how can we afford to do that?
Let's try starting small.
People will come if the food is tasty even if the shop isn't fancy.
I suppose so. People travel across the country to visit good restaurants.
Right.
Hyung, Noona, I have 20 million won.
- What?
- I'll contribute, too.
How could you have any money?
It's the money I've saved working all this time.
Do Jun, you bastard.
Come here, you little.
I'll pay you back the first thing I make money.
- It's fine.
- You turned out so well.
Stop being so gross.
Come here, you bastard.
Yes, let's finish things well and leave immediately.
I finished packing, too.
The money is ready.
Okay. I'll head over there now.
Mr. Jin Sang Gu.
Let go! Let go!
Mr. Jin Sang Gu, you're arrested for instigating murder.
You have the right to an attorney, and you'll have a chance to defend yourself.
You have the right to remain silent, and you can file a wrongful arrest complaint to the court.
- Take him away.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
This man is Jin Sang Gu.
Why did you do that to my daughter?
Tell me why you did that.
I'm sorry.
My business failed in the Philippines, and I heard your daughter was gullible.
I was going to kidnap her and take money. That's all.
Stop lying.
You tried to run over her with a car.
You intended to kill my daughter.
I didn't tell him to kill her.
It's true. Please believe me.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
I did that because someone told me to.
He said he'd pay me if I killed your daughter.
I didn't tell him to kill her.
It's true. Please believe me.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
Who's telling the truth?
But It's certain he tried to kill Ma Ri.
But why?
Seon Yeong! Seon Yeong! Seon Yeong!
How could this happen? Look at this.
Our tenant Jin Sang Gu ran away. He ran away.
H-He ran away?
I just went to his room, and his room was empty.
Jin Sang Gu moved out behind my back.
H-How could he do that without telling us?
We gave him the security deposit because he said he needed money urgently.
We thought he'd pay us back since he's Hyeon Cheol's acquaintance.
But he fled without paying us the rent and security deposit.
He didn't even leave a note.
So, I called him just now, but he won't answer.
So, I called Hyeon Cheol, too.
He left without even sending him a text.
My gosh, how could he do that?
My goodness. He really lives up to his name, doesn't he?
(Jinsang means "nuisance.")
Your friend, Hong Ae Gyo, President Gong's mom.
How could she date someone so low?
Seriously. How do we get the rent money from him?
Because I hate him so much,
I'll follow him to the ends of the earth and get that money.
That's what I can do.
I'm here to see Ms. Hong Ae Gyo.
I'm Go Pil Sung's grandma.
Ms. Hong is out at the moment.
S-She's out?
Well...
Never mind.
Maybe I should've called her first.
I suppose I can come back.
I'll get that money, no matter what.
Pil Sung's Grandmother. Hello.
Hello, Chairman.
What brings you to our house?
Why are you standing here?
President Gong's mom...
I'm here to see Hong Ae Gyo.
But she's not home.
Why don't you wait inside, then?
No, that won't be necessary.
I'll get going now.
Take my car, then.
- Secretary Kim.
- No, it's okay, Chairman.
I can just take a walk.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
By the way, Chairman.
Yes.
W-Well, I...
I can't bring myself to just leave.
I'm not sure if I should tell you this or not.
What is it about?
I'm not sure what it's about, but feel free to talk to me.
Well, the thing is...
my son's...
middle school junior lives in our rental unit.
But he ran away without paying us the rent.
I wanted to receive the rent payment from Hong Ae Gyo.
That's why I came all the way here.
Why would you receive the payment from Hong Ae Gyo?
The thing is...
President Gong's mom, Hong Ae Gyo, and our tenant
are an item, you know.
Pardon me?
I'm saying they have a thing going on.
They denied it and said they were cousins at first,
but I found out they were dating.
They're apparently each other's first love.
But why are you telling me about this?
Well, the thing is...
The reason for the long preamble is because...
I'm not sure if I should say this.
If it's true, I'd be dropping a bomb on your family.
If not, I'd become a crazy person.
It's not so easy to bring it up.
Don't feel pressured, and feel free to tell me.
I'll just disregard it if it's nothing serious.
Hong Ae Gyo's son, President Gong Jin Dan...
is a son of Hong Ae Gyo and Jin Sang Gu.
He's not a member of the Gong family.
What did you say?
Well, there's no evidence.
But Jin Sang Gu said President Gong was his son over the phone.
I definitely heard that with my ears.
And he said he reunited with his first love, but they had a son together.
I heard him say that, too.
Is that...
I-Is that really true?
Get a DNA test done, just in case.
If the test result says it's not the case,
just think a crazy old lady talked nonsense.
By the way,
what did you say the man's name was?
Jin Sang Gu. Jin Sang Gu.
Why do you ask?
By chance, do you know him?
Jin Sang Gu.
♫  The reason I love you is because you're you  ♫
It's time to open.
Should we chant before we start?
♫  I love you  ♫
Okay.
- Say it three times.
- Three times.
Ready, go.
Sunjeong. Sunjeong. Sunjeong. Yay!
Fighting. Fighting.
Can I get kalguksu now?
Yes, absolutely. Come on in.
Welcome. Welcome. Come this way.
Welcome. Two?
She has no conscience. Seriously.
Ma'am.
You came. Get all of this out of here right now.
What's going on?
What do you mean?
Your mom demanded the security deposit two weeks ago, saying she was moving out.
So, I rushed to pay her in full.
But she hasn't removed her stuff, moved out, or she won't answer my call.
What kind of thing is this to do?
Anyway, the new tenant is moving in tomorrow.
Take this with you immediately.
Where's my mom right now, ma'am?
How am I supposed to know?
Why are you asking me about your mom?
What?
- Where are you right now?
-  I'm at home.
I'm at your place right now—
I heard you said you're moving out and took the security deposit.
The landlady wants you to move out your stuff. Where are you now?
It's none of your business.
Keep that stuff at your place for now.
I'll pick it up soon, okay?
Here you go. Here's your coffee.
Okay. Here you go.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Ahjumma, a ramen here, please.
Okay.
Yes.
Chairman, the document was just delivered.
Okay. Leave that there.
Yes, Mr. Gu.
I just received the document.
It's the information you requested.
It's the file from Hong Ae Gyo's dashcam
and the DNA test result for you and President Gong Jin Dan.
Thank you.
No way.
Jin Dan wasn't my father's son.
What did you say? You met Chairman Gong?
Chairman Gong Jin Taek?
Yes. He came to the police station the day I got arrested.
My gosh, what do we do?
What do we do? What are we going to do now?
Ae Gyo, Chairman Gong didn't notice anything.
I'll take care of everything. Don't worry about a thing.
Tell Jin Dan that, too.
Why did you have to come to Korea and do all this?
This wouldn't have happened if you didn't come to Korea.
What will you do about our Jin Dan?
What will you do?
Jin Sang Gu, listen to me carefully.
You'd better not mention Jin Dan even once.
I won't forgive you even after I die.
So, keep your mouth shut until you die.
And I won't see you again.
Forget about me and Jin Dan starting today.
I'll forget about you, too.
That way, our Jin Dan could live.
I won't visit you anymore, either. Just so you know.
Ae Gyo.
Ae Gyo!
Yes, I need to end this now.
That way, I can protect Jin Dan.
Jin Sang Gu. He's a stranger to me now.
Hey, Chairman Gong.
To your office?
Okay, I will.
Why does he want me at his office at this hour?
Why did you want to see me at this hour?
The secretaries already went home, too.
I heard you asked Mom to come, too.
Why did you ask her to come in, too?
What's it about?
Hyung.
What are you doing right now?
Why are you doing this to me now?
What is it now?
Your mom Hong Ae Gyo. Your birth father, Jin Sang Gu.
The three of you plotted together and tried to kill Ma Ri, didn't you?
Did you think you'd be fine after that?
W-What are you talking about?
W-Why would I kill Ma Ri? Why would I hurt her?
Also, Jin Sang Gu isn't my father!
He approached my mom to sell insurance plans.
He's just some bastard who tried to scam her!
W-What's this?
How could this be?
Was Jin Dan really Sang Gu's son?
What do I do now?
What am I supposed to do about this?
Of course, I know what to do. No one knows.
I just need to keep my mouth shut.
This isn't true.
Hyung.
I'm your brother, Hyung.
Our father is Chairman Gong Dae Gil!
You aren't my brother.
You aren't my father's son.
This is the DNA test result for you and me.
How dare you try to deny it?
Hyung, I don't even know who Jin Sang Gu is.
I never even touched the tip of Ma Ri's hair. I swear.
Please, believe me, Hyung.
Please, believe me, Hyung. It's true.
Believe you?
You're begging me to believe you?
You've been embezzling the company's money for years.
You created a slush fund.
Not only that, you lied to everyone about your bloodline.
And you tried to kill Ma Ri, whom you lived with your whole life.
I can't forgive you two.
I'll lock you both up for attempted murder.
I'll put you away for embezzlement first!
Hyung, Hyung, Hyung...
I'm sorry. Forgive me. Hyung, I really didn't do that to Ma Ri.
So, please forgive me for this once. Please, Hyung!
You bastard.
Hyung, I'll really go to jail if that gets revealed.
That'd really be the end of me!
So, please let it go just once.
Please spare me!
You bastard...
H-Hyung.
Hyung?
Hyung.
W-What's wrong with this?
Why can't I transfer the money?
What?
Did he do all this in advance?
Did he block everything?
How? What do I do!
Correct passcode.
The door was unlocked.
Chairman Gong, I'm here.
Did he step out for a second?
What's the deal? He made me come all the way here.
C-Chairman Gong!
Chairman Gong!
My gosh. What happened?
Secretary Kim? Is anyone there?
My gosh.
What do I do?
H-Hello? 911?
S-Someone has passed out.
Please hurry!
My gosh.
Hey, what did Dr. Kim say?
Thankfully, the test results don't indicate danger,
but he's in a coma due to a concussion right now.
What did you say?
Coma?
He's not sleeping from medication,
but he's unconscious right now?
Yes.
He suspects he hit his head hard when he fell.
When will gain consciousness, then?
When will he wake up?
He doesn't know.
He said we need to keep an eye on him.
What if he never wakes up? Chairman Gong...
Aunt.
Hold on. Chairman Gong. Jin Taek...
Ae Gyo, what happened, exactly?
He asked me to come to his office to talk about something.
I thought he wanted to discuss adopting Jin Dan again, but he was passed out.
I called 911 because I was so shocked.
I don't know what's going on, either.
- Oppa.
- Yes, Ma Ri.
Soo Yeon, what happened all of a sudden?
Seon Yeong.
Second Grandma found him passed out in his office.
But they don't know when he'll wake up.
What if he never wakes up?
No, Ma Ri. He'll be okay.
I'm sure he'll wake up, okay?
My goodness. I don't know what's going on.
He was so healthy and energetic.
Why all of a sudden? Gosh.
Well, then...
- Get home safely.
- Well...
Hold on. I...
I need to tell you something, Soo Yeon.
Me?
I think I know why Chairman Gong passed out.
I think it's because of me.
He passed out because of you? What do you mean?
I told him about it. That thing.
Mother.
- Did you really tell him about it?
- What is it?
Seon Yeong, what's going on?
Well, the thing is...
Ma Ri's uncle, President Gong Jin Dan...
He isn't a member of the Gong family.
He's the son of Jin Sang Gu, our tenant.
Pardon?
What did you say?
I told Chairman Gong that.
I think he passed out because of the shock.
My gosh. What am I supposed to do now?
Ma'am!
How could you say such a thing?
What did you say just now?
My son is whose son?
How could you utter such nonsense?
Are you senile, ma'am?
I'm not senile.
I definitely heard it.
Our tenant, Jin Sang Gu, your boyfriend, was on the phone with you
and said "Our son, Jin Dan" and whatnot.
You talked about that with Jin Sang Gu, right?
Gosh, what kind of nonsense is that?
Are you looking down on me because I was a mistress?
You can't be like this.
I can't be here because I'm offended.
- Hey, Ae Gyo.
- Sue me if I'm wrong.
- Why don't you just sue me?
- Mother...
See? See? It's true.
She would've flipped out and said she'd sue me if I—
Mom, you can't just say that without evidence.
Seriously. It's true. I'm telling you.
By the way,
Chairman Gong seemed to know who Jin Sang Gu was.
Chairman Gong knew Jin Sang Gu?
Yes, I'm telling you.
But what should I do if he really did pass out because of me?
What do I do...
The phone is powered off.
You'll be connected to the voicemail after the beep.
After you're connected...
Why is Jin Dan's phone off?
What do I do?
Did Chairman Gong really pass out because of that?
What would happen if he wakes up?
I don't know this number.
Who's this?
Hello?
Mom, it's me.
Jin Dan.
What's this number?
I threw away my phone so I don't get tracked.
T-Tracked? What do you mean by that?
Mom, what happened to Hyung?
He's not dead, right?
Jin Dan, how did you know he was injured?
Did he pass out because of him? Did you do it?
Mom, he found out everything. Everything.
The DNA test result you destroyed. And the video of it.
He went through your dashcam records and found out everything.
And he found out Jin Sang Gu is my birth father, too.
He found out he tried to kill Ma Ri, too.
My gosh. My gosh...
That's not all.
He found out I embezzled the company's money and created a slush fund, too.
So, I was arguing with him and...
Mom, what do I do?
Mom
Jin Dan, pull yourself together.
He isn't dead.
He's still unconscious, but he won't die.
So, don't try to do anything funny, okay?
Mom, he blocked all of my accounts and money sources.
He even put a travel ban on me, so I can't run away.
W-What? What did you say?
So, you'd better move out of that house before he wakes up.
I'm trying to stow away somehow.
I'll contact you if I end up in Hong Kong or wherever.
So, make sure to hang in there until then.
Okay?
No, Jin Dan. No.
How could I live without you?
I can't live without you.
We need to live and die together.
Jin Dan, take me with you. Take me with you!
My gosh, Jin Dan.
J-Jin Dan, what's with this junk car?
Why are you driving this junk car instead of yours?
I'll get caught if I use my car.
- Get in first, Mom.
- Okay.
Jin Dan, will we really be okay if we get to China?
Yes, I kept some slush funds in Hong Kong.
I created a paper company there.
So, we just need to get to Hong Kong through China.
We'll get our money there...
and live in the US, Switzerland, or anywhere.
That's what we'll do, Mom.
By the way, Jin Dan,
if we stow away and disappear, who will send your dad money in jail?
Seriously!
Why don't you stay here and keep sending him money, then?
N-No, I'm sorry.
I got it. Let's go. Let's just go.
Seriously.
Hey.
I'll give you the other half when we get to China.
Okay, okay.
Mom, this is all the money we have.
You can't put it down even for a moment, okay?
Okay, I won't.
I'll bring all of our stuff.
Hold that tightly and wait for me on the ship.
- Okay?
- Okay, I will.
Go.
Come quickly.
Hey, take my hand.
- Take my hand.
- Shit.
Won't you hold it?
Don't be afraid and come.
Yes, come on.
Here.
My gosh! My money!
Turn the engine on!
J-Jin Dan! Jin Dan!
Get these bastards!
Thieves!
Jin Dan!
Hey! Stop right there!
My gosh.
Jin Dan! My gosh.
You bastards! Stop right there!
Stop right there! Come back!
Don't run.
You sons of bitches!
Dad, you just made a noise, didn't you?
Ma Ri, what is it?
I think the Chairman regained consciousness.
Mom, he moved.
He made a noise, too.
What?
Honey. My gosh.
Is that true? Honey.
Mom, Dad is awake, right? He's back, right?
Honey? Honey, open your eyes.
Honey, wake up.
Honey!
Mom, we're here.
Get off.
This is our house.
You can't come here.
Mom, we have no money anymore.
You'd go through hell if you stayed with me.
So, try to stay here a little longer.
I don't want to, Jin Dan.
I'll come with you.
Mom, it's hard enough to be on the run alone.
We'd both get caught if we did this.
So, I'll call you after I get the slush fund in Hong Kong.
Wait just until then, okay?
Jin Dan, I don't want to go home.
I'm sure they'd kick me out.
I'd be so scared without you.
Mom, don't worry.
You're Chairman Gong Dae Gil's wife.
They can't treat you poorly.
So, don't worry and go inside.
Jin Dan.
Go inside, please!
I said I'll call you.
Okay, okay.
Instead, you have to call me when you get to Hong Kong.
Call me often, okay?
I will. I said I will.
- Go inside.
- Okay.
Go inside.
Jin Dan.
- Jin Dan...
- Go.
Jin Dan...
Jin Dan.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I'll be right back.
Who... Who's here, you said?
Aunt.
You bitch!
How dare you come in here?
How dare you set your foot in here?
You're less than an animal.
You deserve to die!
Get out right now. Get out!
Get out immediately! Get out!
Gosh.
I'm sorry, Aunt.
Forgive me.
But I swear I didn't know.
I really thought Jin Dan was the Chairman's son.
I swear, Aunt.
Jin Taek,
I swear to God, I'm telling the truth.
Just once. Believe me just once.
- Mr. Kim, Yeojudaek,
- Yes.
get this woman out of here. And don't ever let her inside again.
- Yes, Chairman.
No, I can't leave!
I can never leave!
I'm still Chairman Gong Dae Gil's wife.
I'm your mother! Mother!
Chairman. Chairman...
Jin Taek is kicking me out.
Aunt is kicking me out!
Get out! Get out right now!
Get out. Get out.
Don't come anywhere near this house!
You deserve to die. You bitch!
- Thank you.
- Thanks for the meal.
- Please come again. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Bye.
- Welcome.
Is this Park Do Ra's kalguksu restaurant?
Yes, it is.
Nice to meet you. I'm your fan.
We were right. We were right.
Thank you.
- Get us three delicious bowls of kalguksu.
- Okay.
Let's see how delicious the kalguksu made by the prostitute Park Do Ra is.
I'll pay you a handsome tip if it's tasty.
You know she's crazy about tips.
If you entertain me, I'll give you all this as a tip.
I took out a lot of cash. Look.
Gentlemen,
the prostitution rumor was proven wrong.
Didn't you see the article? It's not true.
It was obviously staged. No one believes it.
We're not fools.
Please leave, then.
We won't sell kalguksu to people like you.
- Get out.
- I mean... can you treat your customers like this?
How dare you look at us like that?
I see. He's that man.
The director who defended the prostitute.
- You're right.
- It's him.
So, what's it like to date Park Do Ra?
He's so polite, isn't he?
- Get out.
- What the?
- We don't sell kalguksu to customers like you.
- I'm your customer.
- Get out, you bastards.
- How dare you push me?
Do Sik.
How dare you do this to your customers?
You bastard!
What? How dare you? Hey!
Let go!
Why are you doing this to me?
What did I do to you, exactly?
I said it's not true.
I said it's not true!
Why do you do this to me?
Should I have died, then?
Don't you have mothers?
Don't you have daughters or sisters?
Why are you doing this to me?
Why do you treat me like this?
Is it because I'm an actor?
Is it okay to treat actors this way?
I'm trying to live quietly selling kalguksu now.
Am I... Am I not even allowed to do that?
Let's go.
So annoying. That ruined it. That ruined it.
We didn't get to sell lunch.
We can't ruin our dinner business, either.
Let's prepare for dinner, okay?
Okay, you're right.
We need to prepare dinner.
Go inside. I'll clean up the rest.
You scared me.
Did I scare you? I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Just stay like this.
It's so nice to be hugged by you like this.
You must've been very stressed today.
I'm sorry.
Why did you have to come here, anyway?
I told you not to come.
You should leave now, Oppa.
I won't leave.
I'll stay right by your side like a piece of gum.
Slap.
And who'd knead the kalguksu dough if I weren't here?
I think I'm better at kneading than Do Sik.
Come on, Oppa. You're a dummy.
You're a big dummy.
Yes, I'm a dummy. But...
I want to be a dummy for you.
A handsome dummy.
Seriously. You're giving me the chills.
What if someone sees you?
- You're so embarrassing.
- What's the problem?
It's because I like you.
Look at your sweat.
What are you doing?
Baby chick.
Chirp, chirp.
♫  I couldn't do that. Please remember me.  ♫
Baby chick.
Chirp, chirp.
It suits you.
♫  Why did I fall in love?  ♫
♫  I shouldn't have given you my heart at all  ♫
♫  I've already fallen for you  ♫
♫  I'm not able to free myself anymore  ♫
♫  But we're drifting apart  ♫
Chairman, what's the important announcement? What's going on?
Dad, hurry up and tell them.
- Is there good news?
- Congratulations. That's amazing.
What? Stop saying you can't be without me.
You need to be cheerful so I can leave in peace.
- You go in first.
- We're in front of my place.
I need to see you go first, so I feel relieved.
Park Do Ra.