Mr. Qiu.
You finally came to save me.
An Rong.
Even now,
are you going to keep acting?
You...
have gone down the path of crime.
An Rong.
You've really disappointed me.
I just want to live.
I am just upholding the justice I established.
Is that wrong?
Are you still obstinate
now?
The law is the bottom line.
No one is above the law.
An Rong,
turn back.
Go turn yourself in now.
It's not too late.
Ah.
I am upholding justice, Mr. Qiu.
Mr. Qiu,
why don't you join us, Mr. Qiu?
You are hopeless.
Come back with me.
Mr. Qiu,
don't.
Ah!
Mr. Qiu!
Stop fighting! Ah!
Ah!
Mr. Qiu!
No, no!
Stop fighting!
No, Mr. Qiu!
Make your own choice.
Let go!
An Rong,
let go.
You can't leave.
You can't keep making mistakes.
You must turn yourself in.
Since you don't want to join,
just let go.
An Rong, stop running. Turn yourself in.
Ah!
I'm sorry, Mr. Qiu.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I have no way back now.
Dad.
What exactly happened here in the past?
Aunt Rong.
Does this really have something to do with the Scavenger?
Xiaochen.
Don't go any further.
Aunt Rong.
What on earth do you want to do?
Xiaochen.
You are a smart kid.
Don't you know what I'm trying to do?
You want me to be a cleaner.
This is the cleaner's end,
and where I started down this path.
But you probably know by now.
I have ALS.
My days are numbered.
Xiaochen.
Did you come here today
to catch me,
or to help me?
Gu Yuming.
Come in alone.
I've planted bombs inside and outside the factory.
Tell the people outside
not to move.
Nobody move.
There are bombs.
Understand?
Without my order,
nobody moves.
What are you doing here?
Why did you knock me out?
If I told you,
would I still be able to see Aunt Rong?
An Rong?
Do you know what you are doing?
Mr. Qiu said
the law
is the bottom line.
No one is above the law.
Did you forget?
Law?
You are talking to me about the law?
Wang Yuanyuan,
Qi Xiaoling.
When Zhao Wen and her daughter were victims of domestic violence,
where was the law?
When Lin Xiaoai and Yang Xiaomei were sexually assaulted,
Zhou Yu,
where was the law when she was bullied?
When those girls were emotionally manipulated by jerks,
where was the law?
When I
experienced these things,
where was the law?
Law?
You are talking to me about the law?
Hahaha.
Aunt Rong.
I can understand how you feel.
Perhaps
you've had the same experience as them
and have also been in a situation where no one helped you.
So you want to use your own way
to help the weak
and uphold justice.
Am I right?
Xiaochen,
I knew you could understand me.
Your father is too pedantic.
But you are different.
Your investigation methods
and empathy are above his.
You should surpass him.
You should become a true judge,
rather than a so-called lapdog of law and justice.
An Rong.
You're crazy.
Do you want Qiu Chen to join the Scavengers too?
Gu Yuming.
You are as inflexible as your master.
Don't forget,
you clearly had time to save Mr. Qiu then,
but you didn't.
Mr. Qiu died by your hands.
You shouldn't be alive.
You should die too.
An Rong,
come out!
Aunt Rong.
Come out!
I'll join the Cleaners.
Then kill Gu Yuming
to show your determination.
Qiu Chen!
Don't fall for it!
If you go down the wrong path,
there's no turning back.
Xiao Chen.
You've already passed the point of no return.
Ever since you knocked Gu Yuming out
and took his gun,
you've already started down this path.
Think about it.
If Gu Yuming leaves here alive,
will he let you go?
Could you still be a cop?
Don't move!
Do you want your brothers to die with you?
It seems I'm going to die here today,
just like Captain Qiu did back then.
Shut up, Gu Yuming!
Xiao Chen.
I'll give you one more minute.
If you don't kill him,
I will detonate the bomb immediately
and kill everyone outside.
Captain Gu.
If you were me,
what would you choose?
If it were me,
I wouldn't have come here at all.
I don't make deals with suspects.
This is between me and Aunt Rong.
It has nothing to do with you.
Give me the gun.
That's an order.
You still want to order me around?
Can your orders save the brothers outside?
Don't forget you're a cop.
Don't forget how your father died.
Shut up!
You don't deserve to mention him.
Fine.
Shoot me.
Then you'll become trash like this,
hiding in the dark forever,
never seeing the light of day,
just like a cockroach.
Ah!
Qiu Chen,
congratulations.
Congratulations on completing the first step to becoming a Scavenger.
Killing Gu Yuming
was only your first test.
Now
comes your final test.
I've already killed Gu Yuming.
Doesn't that prove my determination to join the Scavengers?
You killed him just now
because the situation forced you to.
Or rather,
I forced you.
But what I want
is for you to make your choice from the bottom of your heart.
The true mission of a Scavenger is not to kill,
but to judge sinners.
Who else do you want me to judge?
Me.
I should have been judged ten years ago.
Because the one who killed your father
was actually me.
I've been waiting
for you to join the Scavengers,
waiting for you to judge me.
Why would it be you?
I never intended to kill Mr. Qiu.
I originally thought
I could get him to join the Scavengers.
He taught me everything I know about law and justice.
I thought we were the same kind of people,
but I was wrong.
He told me to turn myself in.
Right here.
He took out handcuffs to arrest me.
In a moment of desperation,
I had no choice but to push him down.
Why?
Tell me why!
Anyone
who hurts others
should be judged,
including the Scavenger himself.
An eye for an eye,
blood for blood.
So you are the one who should be judged.
Yes.
Chen,
exactly like this.
A Scavenger does not show mercy to the guilty.
You've already killed Gu Yuming.
You have no way back.
Shut up!
Stop talking!
You are angry.
You should be angry.
This is the psychological barrier every Scavenger must overcome,
and it's the hardest one.
Only a pure heart of justice
will show no mercy when judging sinners.
Chen,
come on.
Let the judgment
begin.
Ah!