(Love Me Like I Do)
(The Delicate CEO Should Take Medicine)
(Episode 14)
Xilai.
Those are what I prepared for you:
watermelon juice, pitaya juice,
strawberry juice and hawthorn juice.
From now on,
you need to follow the medical instructions
and face your fear.
What a sin!
Don't be afraid. I'm here.
Let's drink this first.
This is watermelon juice.
I am really happy that you made this for me.
It's sweet.
Take a stronger flavor.
This is strawberry juice.
This is a little sour.
Hawthorn juice helps you with a good appetite.
Good boy.
Tian!
I'm so full.
You have to cooperate with me
so that your blood sickness can be cured soon.
Listen to me.
It's killing me. I can't drink anymore.
Take it off,
or it won't be washed off.
Wait a minute.
You are taking it off here? Right now?
Didn't you ask me to take it off?
She looks so cute when she's shy.
I didn't ask you to take it off in front of me.
Put it on.
Do you want me to take it off
or put it on?
Whatever.
I'm leaving.
Be careful.
Put on your clothes,
or you'll catch a cold.
Let's call it a day.
She's shocked by my perfect body shape, right?
Tian.
Why do you come back so late?
Did you work for your delicate boss,
or did you take care of him in hospital?
Be serious.
But recently,
he is indeed sick, delicate,
and even picky about food.
If he's sick, have him treated.
You're not a doctor.
What's the use of your staying there?
He suffers from a mental illness.
He can't be cured by doctors alone.
I can't explain it to you clearly right now.
Anyway,
I can help him.
Can't you accompany him
after training?
This is a now-or-never chance.
You want to give it up because of him?
But
how would he go through the next three months?
He hasn't suffered from any fatal danger
before he met you.
How could it become hard for him to live without you now?
But he has me now.
Besides, his condition has worsened.
It's reasonable for him to rely on me.
I don't know whether it's reasonable.
I only know
that you've fallen in love.
This girl
hasn't contacted me for two days.
She has never been out of reach this long.
Is she hiding somewhere to grieve over my condition?
Hey, straight to the point, or I'll hang up.
As a vent to your anger,
I knew you would be irritated
once you picked up the phone.
Stop it.
What is it?
Let's go swimming this weekend.
I'm not going.
You must be there.
Otherwise,
I'll tell Xilai
that you
failed to confess your love,
and gave up on yourself.
Liu Xizhao.
As long as I'm here,
I will find a way to mitigate your sadness.
You are...
Delete your impression on me yesterday.
Who would have thought that you just took off your clothes in front of me?
I am not referring to that.
It was what you saw when you opened the door yesterday morning.
What?
So you are thinking about my chest muscles.
You are welcome to do that.
Be serious.
Tian.
Under your treatment,
my condition has improved.
I can go to work today.
Are you sure?
If I don't go to work,
Assistant Tang will get depression.
And I almost suffer from malnutrition.
Mr. Liu, you're finally back.
Mr. Liu, I'll get back to work.
Wait.
Tian.
I'd like to hear you call me Xilai.
Got it, Mr. Liu.
I'll work hard.
It's hard to guess
a lady's mood.
When can my identity be revealed?
Is there any progress
between you and Assistant Tian
that I haven't caught up with?
Assistant Tang.
Have you finished
your work when I was absent?
Tian Tian, the director said
that before you leave,
you may hand your work over to me.
Okay.
(Qiansheng Group)
How can I leave at ease
without his illness being cured?
Assistant Tang,
there's something wrong with the data.
You need to check it with the Finance Department.
Okay, Mr. Liu.
You've been busy the whole morning.
There's nothing urgent for today.
You just recovered from your cold.
Why don't you take a rest?
Only by finishing it earlier
can I get off work early and go on a date with Tian.
Mr. Liu.
I'm here to report my work to you.
Actually,
I'm here to care for you.
Gosh.
Assistant Tang.
Is there anything wrong with my sunglasses today?
Otherwise, why would I feel dizzy when I see red?
Who knows?
Is it getting serious?
Do you want to take a rest?
Tian.
Maybe I need to
rely on you forever.
I want to hold your hands
and grow old with you.
It's just a treatment.
Don't be so cheesy.
You'll get better soon.
I failed again.
Tian.
It's so considerate of you.
You even bring me the horrible juice during working hours.
I made this for you during lunch break.
You need to drink it all today.
It seems that I am looking for trouble.
Tian.
The recent treatment plan
makes me feel stressed.
Good medicine tastes bitter.
Drink this up.
I'll take you to
an interesting and relaxing place this weekend.
Liu Xizhao.
You've grown up, huh?
How dare you threaten me?
Let go. It hurts.
Did you tell Xilai anything?
No, let go of me.
Are you sure?
Liu Xizhao.
I'm going to kill you.
My foundation is not waterproof.
Liu Xizhao.
When will you stop your funny play?
I just want to vent your sadness.
How can you tell that I'm sad?
Don't think you know me well.
In my eyes,
you are just a boy younger than me.
You are only one year older than me.
One year is enough.
Don't think too much.
You heard everything that day, right?
So you avoided me these days
because you knew how I felt.
Okay.
Good.
I see.
You may think that I crossed the line.
How could I leak it?
Tian.
Is this the interesting and relaxing place
you mentioned?
-Tian, I have acrophobia. -Let's go.
Xilai.
Close your eyes
if you are scared.
Don't look down.
Since I'm here,
I want to see
what you can see.
You
have changed.
How?
You
are not as distant as before.
You are opening your mind to others.
Have you heard of it?
If you make a wish at the highest point of the ferris wheel,
your wish will come true.
Now is the time.
I think I have figured out
the significance of this amusement facility.
What's that?
You can stay with the one you like,
and enjoy the whole sky
little by little.
What wish did you make?
Without doubt, I hope
that you can recover soon,
and that you can do whatever you want
in the future.
Did I
go overboard?
Why don't you make a wish?
I don't believe in wish.
My motto is
to earn
what you want.
Do your best
to achieve your goal.
This is also my motto.
But now,
I'm afraid of losing.
I never thought there would be anything
beyond my control.
But now,
I can't predict
every consequence.
In my opinion,
the meaning of making a wish
is to make us convinced
the future we look forward to
will finally come true.
You can always give me confidence.
Okay, I'll try.
Maybe
my wish is selfish.
But I hope
♫Warm my night with blooming flowers♫
Tian can always be with me.
♫The moment I met you♫
♫Love is slowly spreading in our hearts♫
♫A romantic scene appears♫
♫The beginning of our story appeared before my eyes♫
♫Colorful love♫
♫The color engraved in my heart♫
♫Your gentle eyes are staring at our future♫
♫My life becomes colorful because of you♫
♫The starry night shines upon hope♫
♫Telling♫
♫My love♫
♫Your beautiful smile wipes out my haze♫
♫The moment of sweet memories♫
What wish did you make?
♫When the river of time stops for me♫
It's a secret.
I'll tell you
when it is a right timing.
So petty.
I've told you my wish.
By the way,
do you remember
how you recovered from the blood sickness last time?
Maybe
we can try again
with the same method.
Is he trying to trick me?
But why am I looking forward to it?
Kiss your forehead?
Really?
Stop joking.
Of course, it's true.
Last time, after you kissed my forehead,
I recovered.
Why don't we
try again?
I'll start now.
Still dizzy?
Yes.
Yes?
I knew it wouldn't work.
Tian.
Maybe it's because
my condition this time
is quite serious.
Kissing forehead
is not effective enough?
What do you mean?
♫I'll always believe that you only belong to me♫
You
♫We will be forever♫
♫I'm so in love with you♫
♫I'll always believe you'll be here♫
♫My Mr. Right♫
♫Holding my hand♫
♫We'll live in forever♫
♫I remember every step we make it our story♫
♫So you're my love♫
♫You are the one shining all the stars♫
♫In my life♫
♫I will always believe that you only belong to me♫
♫We will be forever♫
♫I'm so in love with you♫
♫I always believe you'll be here♫
♫My Mr. Right♫
♫Holding my hand♫
♫We'll live in forever♫
If I had known
the treatment was so good,
I should have skipped
all the unnecessary parts earlier.
But...
Shouldn't it be the forehead?
You kissed my forehead just now,
but it didn't work.
So kissing here works?
Just now,
I was really into it.
I don't feel anything.
How about
one more time?
It's late.
I should go home.
Leave the treatment tomorrow.
What time is it?
Why don't you stay at your delicate CEO's home?
What are you talking about?
We haven't gone that far.
You are hiding something, aren't you?
How far have you two gone?
Have you gotten closer?
What?
I don't even know what you're talking about.
Rose.
Tonight
is the deadline of submitting the training materials.
So?
So,
if I texted the director
saying that I would give up this opportunity,
would you be shocked?
If it's because of Mr. Liu,
I would not be shocked at all.
Why?
Your love for your delicate boss
cannot be more obvious.
Although dating is not as good as having a career,
when I think about the fact that you will end being single
and fall in love,
I'm happy for you.
Rose, you are so nice.
As long as it's your choice,
be it career or romance,
I'll support you.
Tian, would you like to
come to my home for a meal tomorrow?
Okay.
It's so good to be Tian's de facto boyfriend.
I feel so uneasy
to fool Tian all the time.
I may as well
find a chance today
to tell Tian the truth.
Tian.
You look so beautiful today,
especially this necklace
which suits you well.
Really?
I've been waiting for you.
I'm looking forward to your treatment.
Let's cut some fruit first.
I'll make juice for you.
Tian.
Actually,
you don't have to be busy.
Just focus on my treatment.
You...
Do you like the feeling of giving orders as a patient?
What's wrong?
Had your fingers cut?
Luckily the wound is not deep.
I'll go get the medicine kit.
Wait a sec, Tian.
Tian, I have to answer the phone.
I'll cut the fruit later.
Why doesn't he feel dizzy when he sees red?
Has he recovered?
Great.
My treatment must have worked.
I know.
-Confirm it with him. -I planned to tell her the truth these days.
But I couldn't find a time to see color red or blood.
No.
I saw blood just now.
But I forgot to respond to it.
I think
I've been already exposed.
I...
Tell me the truth?
Exposed?
No dizziness?
You haven't relapse into your blood sickness at all.
Tian,
I was going to tell you the truth these days.
I just…
Tian, let me explain.
Explain what?
I'm worried that you might be in danger.
I'm worried that you won't feel safe under the sunglasses.
I'm afraid I can't make it in time
to help you.
I even gave up
the chance for training that I've dreamed for a long time.
But
I think
all I have done is a joke.
I'm the most foolish one in the world.
Tian.
Calm down and listen to me.
It's because...
No matter what it is,
you knew this training
was important to me.
But you still lied to me and tricked me.
I can't accept it.
Tian.
It's because of Luo Ci.
When I knew he was the lecturer,
and you were going to travel together,
I was very anxious
and even suffered from insomnia.
You admire him so much.
I was scared
that if you spent three months together,
I would lose you.
So you pretended to be sick?
You never asked me about my thoughts.
You wanted
to keep me by your side
in such a self-righteous way.
Do you have any idea
that mutual trust
♫How should I describe this feeling♫
is the most important in a relationship?
You don't even trust me.
♫How should I describe this feeling♫
♫Which song can dispel the loneliness at night♫
You really disappoint me.
♫I've been longing for love♫
♫As long as I'm by your side, I'm willing to offer all I have♫
♫Why am I suddenly emotional♫
♫The promises I made♫
♫When I was with you♫
It's not that I don't want to tell you.
I'm just afraid of the unknown results.
♫When I was with you♫
♫Can they be fulfilled♫
(Bonus Scenes)
Cute Bean, turn it off.
I'm here.
(Bonus Scenes)
Why do you age faster than your peers?
Take care of your spleen, and you will have a beautiful look.
(Bonus Scenes)
Isn't it said that doctors are busy every day?
Why does he forward to me these boring articles
(Bonus Scenes)
every day?
Miss Shan.
(Bonus Scenes)
Have you read the articles I forward to you
every day?
(Bonus Scenes)
You're welcome.
Although we don't have a common topic at work,
we can talk about health care
and the philosophy of life.
His way of "saying hello" is really old school.
Oh my god.