(Love Me Like I Do)
(The Delicate CEO and His Grumpy Assistant)
(Episode 4)
Miss Tian,
since you've already known it,
let's have a talk.
But before that,
there's one thing to do.
What is it?
My sunglasses
can filter the color red,
but they are not rose-colored glasses.
I don't want to be scared again
by Miss Tian's appearance.
Mr. Liu is trying to use the handsome trick?
No wonder he is the boss.
Respect him for doing things by hook or by crook.
If I had physical contact with you,
you wouldn't suffer from
that disease...?
Hemophobia.
I'm just an extreme case.
Every time I see the color red,
it will cause temporary
neurophysiological dysfunction.
That's why I feel dizzy.
When it's serious,
I will even lose my consciousness.
Why me?
I don't know.
But my personal doctor
is helping me with my desensitization.
It's a bit mysterious.
Why didn't you tell me directly?
Why did you beat around the bush?
Tell you the truth
so that you can do whatever you want with my weakness?
I am not as bad as you think.
You have too much prejudice against me.
Humanity is too complicated
and uncontrollable.
I like to solve problems
in a simple and controllable way.
It is your arrogance
that makes me have prejudice against you.
Miss Tian,
I have a suggestion.
Why don't we meet each other halfway?
I hire you to be my personal assistant
and a toy designer.
What do you think?
No.
My bottom line is
a toy designer
and your personal assistant.
Is there any difference?
Of course, it's totally different.
The order decides the proportion.
This woman
is stubborn,
but smarter than I thought.
All right.
No problem.
OK.
Let's talk about other conditions.
From now on,
this is where my dream starts.
Isn't this the strong woman
who knocked Mr. Liu out during her legal rights protection?
Miss Tian.
Welcome to Qiansheng Group.
I'll take you to Mr. Liu.
You need to get familiar with Mr. Liu's work environment
and his habits.
Okay.
Thank you for your invitation.
I will attend this charity event
on time.
Okay, bye.
Mr. Liu.
This is my first day here.
Is there any task
assigned to me?
I hope you can get used to
the role of a special assistant as soon as possible.
Be my guard against the color red.
Okay, Mr. Liu.
As a designer and assistant,
I'll fulfill all my responsibilities.
I'm going back to work.
Wait, Assistant Tian.
I have to remind you
that as a designer, you may not pay attention to details.
But as my assistant,
you have to be exquisite to the utmost.
I saw nothing.
I... I know nothing.
Assistant Tang.
You came at the right time.
Take her to the Toy Design Department.
You must complete the task this time.
Understood?
Yes.
Director Zheng.
Let me introduce.
This is
our chief designer, Zheng Qian.
She is the pillar of the Design Department.
She is the acting design director.
Hello, Director.
This is our designer, Doggie.
Our sketch master.
Hello, Doggie.
I'm flattered.
This is Jiang, the designer.
Our model master.
You are really good at praising each other.
These are our designers,
Wang, Gu and Wen.
Hello, I'm Tian Tian.
Director Zheng,
I'll leave her to you.
It's an honor to learn from you.
I look forward to working with you.
No need to be this polite.
That's your desk.
If you want to get your work started as soon as possible,
you need to figure out the design concept
and product style of the company in the past three years.
Go ahead.
Ms. Qian seems to be distant, but she is warm-hearted.
Don't feel pressured.
Ask me if you need anything.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Mr. Liu.
During the Blue Sky Dream
this afternoon,
there will be an auction
of drawings by children in the orphanage.
So there must be red elements.
Assistant Tian will accompany you to attend it, won't she?
How is she doing in the Design Department?
I've talked to Director Zheng.
She won't be assigned
any detailed task for the time being,
so that she may answer your call at any time.
Go get Assistant Tian.
OK.
Wait.
I can help you if it is necessary.
But don't disturb my work
unless you really need me.
Okay.
Besides,
I want to keep my identity as your personal assistant
as a secret in the company.
I want to keep a low profile
to avoid unnecessary misunderstandings.
I hope you can
understand what I said and respect me.
Isn't it just keeping a low profile and showing respect?
I'll go in person.
Mr. Liu.
Mr. Liu is just passing by.
Just continue with your work.
See you at the parking lot
in five minutes.
Doggie, what's going on?
Don't underestimate her.
Tian Tian...
I thought she was a newbie.
I didn't expect her to be a veteran.
Don't underestimate her.
Is she a little princess gaining some work experience
or a secret lover of the boss?
Mr. Liu.
There's no red color here.
How long will you keep this posture?
And this activity has long been over.
In the name of work,
I take you out for some fresh air.
Isn't that good?
Thank you, Mr. Liu.
But could you please not ask me
to do such trivial matters?
I just joined the company.
I want to do a good job in the Design Department.
This charity event
has limited up the stock price of Qiansheng Group today.
How can it be a trivial matter?
I just want to know
when I can go back.
Now.
I'll ask Assistant Tang to pick me up now.
Sorry, Miss, you can't go in.
I need to talk to your boss.
I really need to talk to your boss.
Let me interview her.
Look at you.
My boss doesn't accept interviews.
-Excuse me, Miss. Please go over there. -Rose.
Why are you here?
I edited a video
of an dedicate boss vs. a brave girl who boycotted plagiarism.
I didn't expect that the views would exceed 100 million.
Our Editor-in-Chief transferred me to the remix team
and increased my salary by 500 yuan.
That's the happiness.
What about sorrow?
Shan.
Why is the click rate still so low
after you are here?
So low.
You should deserve
the increased 500 yuan in your salary.
Your salary.
Did you hear what she said?
She asked me to interview
another weird boss in a week
and make it the next hit.
So,
you're here to interview the owner of the dessert shop?
Yes.
The owner of the dessert shop
printed her ex's profile photo
on the cover of the milk tea.
So her ex was poked by straws every day.
I just want to ask her
how she came up with such an unusual idea.
But I didn't expect...
Rose.
I think
the boss is merciful enough
to kick you out.
What can I do?
Life is so hard.
A weird CEO.
My boss
is the weirdest in the world.
Can you help me ask Liu Xilai for an interview?
Sure, leave it to me.
My position is irreplaceable.
Tian Tian, you're so nice.
Sorry, let me pick it up for you.
It's okay.
Dear all!
Here is the biggest secret.
It's about Mr. Liu.
We have been used to
Mr. Liu's weird behaviors.
We're not interested at all.
Fine.
I thought you would be curious
about the gossip of Mr. Liu and Miss Tian.
What gossip?
Tell me.
Mr. Liu.
I have made an appointment for you
with Dr. Li for a review.
Go inform Assistant Tian.
OK.
By the way,
I heard a rumor
from the Design Department.
It's about you.
Assistant Tang.
Where there is me,
there will be gossip every day.
You need to get used to this.
Don't report to me
such trivialities.
But
the other one involved in this gossip
is Assistant Tian.
Oh?
Tell me then.
I heard
that Assistant Tian is writing you a love letter.
She wants to confess to you.
Confess to me?
Tian, how's it going?
Did Mr. Liu agree?
I can't hold on any longer.
Don't worry.
No matter what,
I will make it.
We are as close as sisters.
Mr. Liu, are you free now?
I want to see you.
She took the love letter.
She's taking actions.
It's thrilling. I want to be on the spot.
Confession is always in vain.
I feel a little nervous for Tian.
Assistant Tian
really fell in love with me.
I have nowhere to hide
my charm.
Maybe there's misunderstanding.
No.
She fell in love with me.
She always
wanted to keep a distance from me.
But this time,
she changed her attitude and tried to approach me.
This is definitely not misunderstanding.
Mr. Liu.
I don't think Assistant Tian...
I am the dream of millions of girls.
You don't understand.
You haven't experienced it.
Well,
Miss Tian is supposed to
accompany you to Dr. Li's
for review.
Forget it.
I'll go by myself.
I should keep a distance
from Miss Tian now.
Okay.
My darn charm.
I'm busy.
No time to meet you.
Why do I feel
he is so indifferent?
What's going on?
Mr. Liu, wait.
Why is it so weird?
Mr. Liu,
why is Assistant Tian so obsessed
with you all of a sudden?
Maybe
she misunderstood
my nice attitude of inviting her.
She fell in love with me.
After all,
an excellent person like me
is destined to bear love debts.
Sounds reasonable.
But Mr. Liu,
I think
it's better to explain it sooner.
How can I bear to do that?
Assistant Tang,
avoid her.
Let her enjoy the sweetness for a few more days.
I have nowhere to hide my charm.
♫The sea of bitterness reveals love and hatred♫
♫No one can escape from destiny♫
♫We are close, but cannot be together♫
♫I spend my whole life believing this is fate♫
Mr. Liu.
That must be the love letter.
It's my fault.
But it is Assistant Tian who has to take the burden.
Assistant Tian,
you are a very nice girl.
You're pretty
and capable.
You're really excellent.
What happened?
Why is he praising me like that?
Is he going to play the act of
a domineering CEO falling in love with me?
No way.
She must have noticed that I'm rejecting her,
so she wants to escape.
Forget it. It's better to cut the knot.
Assistant Tian.
I think
you're perfect to be my personal assistant.
You are unique to me.
I don't want to lose you.
Mr. Liu.
Although I'm very important to you,
you should keep a distance
from me.
She's a little cute when she pretends to be fine.
I wonder
if she can handle my rejection.
Assistent Tian,
don't force a smile.
I admire your taste.
But
it's impossible for us.
Mr. Liu, what are you talking about?
What is impossible?
I know
your thoughts.
You know everything?
Then do you agree?
I'm sorry.
I choose to stay single.
Mr. Liu.
I'll make it clear then.
I know you're holding a love letter.
You want to confess to me.
I didn't meet you,
because I didn't want to refuse you face to face.
Mr. Liu.
Please take a closer look with your eyes.
Is this a love letter?
Mr. Liu, I've admired you for a long time.
You have led Qiansheng Group in the business sector
with great momentum.
You are a famous young entrepreneur.
I wonder if you may accept an exclusive interview with me?
Inviter, Shan Rose.
Invitation for the interview.
Have you seen it clearly?
This is a wonderful misunderstanding.
I confess to you?
There's a whole biochain
between us, OK?
Assistant Tian means
that you two belong to different circles.
Come on. It's different species.
Good.
I am very satisfied
that you don't have such unrealistic thoughts.
Don't worry.
I do not
and will not.
You are not my type.
Very good.
I won't
accept any interview from a nobody.
After all, we belong to different species.
Miss Tian.
Please get off.
Tian Tian. Tian Tian.
Watch your mouth.
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect
he would reject me so firmly.
It's okay.
He is famous for being difficult to cope in our media circle.
Even if he agreed to the interview,
maybe
something else would happen later.
Yes.
The interview must be a failure.
He doesn't look like a CEO.
He's an alien freak.
Someone like Luo Ci
is a real man.
He is talented and handsome.
That's the role model of the industry.
Luo Ci.
You've only seen him once
for such a long time.
You still love him.
Oh.
That's not love,
but admiration.
Luo Ci is my prince charming.
Prince charming.
Your prince charming.
Let me tell you.
He's more handsome in person than in the photo.
This is my idol.
He's indeed a guru.
He doesn't show up that often,
but there are still stories about him.
You get to know him because of his handsome face.
Then you are obsessed with him for his talent.
And finally you admire him for his character.
Luo Ci
is the top one in the design circle.
It's just a magazine cover.
Let me show you
what is called a "nonsuch".
Luo Ci even outshined
Mr. Liu.
Assistant Tang.
Please arrange the interview with Reporter Shan.
Now.
Mr. Liu, you...
I've thought about it.
I can't refuse
Designer Tian's request.
He said no yesterday,
but accepts it passionately today.
What's wrong with him?
Did Tian Tian succeed in confessing her feelings?
She's becoming the CEO's secret lover.
Yes, Mr. Liu.
A little more to this side.
Yes, that's it.
So handsome, Mr. Liu.
Amazing, Mr. Liu.
The most handsome man in the world.
Assistant Tian.
What do you think?
It is well-known
that I am excellent.
Mr. Liu.
Why did you suddenly change your mind
and accept our interview?
Because I want to be on the magazine cover.
Mr. Liu.
Your answer is always unexpected.
Sorry for that.
Genius are always unique.
Mr. Liu has always been the GOAT in the netizens' eyes.
And he's always mysterious.
He's always surrounded by security personnel.
Many netizens asked me where they could meet you.
In their dreams.
Xilai.
Our business runs well, doesn't it?
Don't take this kind of interview anymore.
It's not serious at all.
Uncle.
Young people nowadays like it.
Zhao's Moments
are filled with this.
You are comparing yourself with him?
You're the CEO of Qiansheng Group.
You make a good fortune,
and you have a good look.
Why are you still single?
Uncle,
how about
taking more care of Zhao?
After he returns from abroad,
he can manage the company with me.
I don't know if he has made full use his studying time abroad.
But he said he would come back tomorrow.
If you have time,
let's have dinner together.
I'll arrange it in advance,
and give him a surprise.
Today is the party of the Design Department.
Tian Tian, as a newcomer,
you need to drink more.
No problem.
I need to thank everyone for taking care of me.
You're welcome.
Having a meal together can bring us closer.
You need to adjust to such a warm atmosphere,
and see
how good I am at socializing with others.
Let's go.
My car is parked across the street.
I'll wait for you in the underground garage.
Here's an assignment for you, Assistant Tian.
Sorry.
I have a date
tonight.
I can't attend the party today.
I'll treat you next time.
Go. It's okay. Bye.
Why not?
It's barbecue.
Get in.
Mr. Liu.
Why don't we have a secret code?
Otherwise,
I feel like I'll get caught sooner or later.
Don't you think this is exciting?
Men are indeed immature forever.
Childish.
Are you still going to see Dr. Li today?
Dr. Li is on a business trip.
He'll be back in a few days.
My cousin is coming back from abroad.
I need to buy something
to welcome him.
Your cousin?
Dad, I'm back.
What the hell?
Surprise!
Zhao.
Welcome home.
Don't be so childish.
Zhao.
No way. And you?
You brat.
You're finally back.
Come in.
Zhao.
Your cousin prepared these for you.
What do you think? Isn't it a surprise?
Obviously it is Liu Xilai's taste. Just for his self-amusement.
(Welcome back from abroad)
What a surprise.
I knew you'd like it.
Let me introduce.
My special assistant, Tian Tian.
She came to decorate it with me.
Hello, welcome back.
You're Liu Xilai's assistant.
You don't look like you're a fool.
Brat.
Go change your clothes.
Let's have a meal later.
Okay.
Zhao.
Go to your room.
I prepared another surprise for you.
Another surprise?
Surprise?
Gosh.
This red color.
I thought it was a wedding photo.
(Bonus Scenes)
Assistant Tian.
I keep a low profile.
(Bonus Scenes)
Do you feel my respect?
Can you keep a lower profile?
(Bonus Scenes)
It's hard.
Assistant Tang, it's too hard for you.
(Bonus Scenes)
Assistant Tang.
Are you not satisfied with your salary?
(Bonus Scenes)
Yes.
Very satisfied.
(Bonus Scenes)
Assistant Tian.
As you can see,
I've never wronged my employees.
How much energy does it take
to grow into such a weirdo?
Mr. Liu,
I hope you can keep your promise.
Don't show up around me
as a CEO.
It will bring me a lot of troubles.
OK?
Strong people
will never fear the rumors.