Sometimes, the reality
you're faced with seems unrealistic.
Like, for instance, right now,
as I blissfully walk along this street
all covered in white,
as it snows.
METAPHORS OF DAWN
YU HYEON-U EXHIBITION
I guess it's similar
to when you're in love.
That sensation of being
the most special person in the world.
It kinda feels unrealistic.
Your heart…
it flutters.
Looks pretty erotic, huh?
I know, right?
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL MOMENT OF A LOVER
VIEW FROM BEHIND
NABI
YU HYEON-U
So why is it called "Nabi", then?
No idea.
Let's go.
What do we look at next?
Let's go check this one.
This one?
-Have you heard of him?
-Of course.
Na-bi.
Wait, did he say "Nabi"?
Pretty, right?
All right. I'll see you too.
Na-bi.
Yu Na-bi!
What is love, anyway?
He was a very serious person.
You wanna know what love is?
It's something
that constantly gives meaning…
to something so abstract and unfamiliar.
That's what I think true love is.
Oh.
-I knew it.
-Hm?
The reason I asked
if we could have pizza today
was so I could take a glimpse
into your feelings
by reading into your actions,
like how you share your food.
-My feelings?
-Mm-hm.
Especially your sincerity.
Tonight, the sincerity
of our relationship depends
on whether this final layer
will come between us.
Almost always…
No, actually…
He was always…
Ridiculous!
Are you being serious right now?
What do you mean?
I just wish you wouldn't make
such erratic decisions out of nowhere.
Oh, do my nails really look that weird?
Everyone said they were pretty.
"Everyone"? You should've asked
for my opinion first
before assuming it was fine with me.
But I guess I'm just nothing to you.
Practically a stranger to small-talk with.
Am I the only one serious here?
He's obsessed with putting meaning
into everything,
an endless metaphor addict.
Was my work that embarrassing to you?
Is that why you're crying?
Na-bi. You can't just look
at the exterior of things.
You have to look at the meaning
hidden inside of it.
You could've at least asked me
about it first
before assuming it was fine with me.
Come on!
You're making me really upset,
you know that?
And here I thought you'd be the one
who'd understand me the most.
At one point, I used to believe
it was all so special.
Ew! I'm not sure if I like that.
It's a little weird for me.
But he said he made it
because he loves you, right?
These artists don't just use
any random model they see.
You know what I think?
I think deep down,
he really cares about you.
You're like his artistic muse.
-No.
-Muse?
He's definitely a weirdo for sure.
-It's art, you wouldn't get it.
-You call that thing art?
It had perplexed me.
The boundaries of art.
Excuse me, hello?
I really hope
you don't mind me asking, but…
Yu Hyeon-U is your boyfriend, right?
Mm. Yeah, he is. Why?
I'm sorry, I'm not sure
if I should tell you this, but…
A friend of mine actually attends
that academy.
It's been going on for a while.
Suddenly, I realized the truth…
at such an unexpected moment.
But to be honest,
it kinda felt like I already knew it.
However…
Hey, Na-bi.
I've been swamped at the academy,
plus the exhibition.
Imagine it becomes successful,
maybe I'll quit being a teacher
and just focus on my art career.
Although, I'm not so sure
what theme to focus on.
Mr. Baek wants to express the liveliness
and vigor of people in their 20s…
This jerk doesn't know
how to shut up.
I can't believe I almost blamed myself.
Na-bi.
What are you daydreaming for?
I'm talking about something serious here.
Pay attention.
God, you're an asshole.
What?
Love.
Something that gets trampled on
while helplessly melting away.
As if it were nothing.
Exactly how my relationship ended.
-Na-bi, where are you off to?
-I'm going to the studio.
-See you around.
-See you later.
What are you up to?
-Nothing, just chilling.
-See you in there.
You guys heading to the studio?
You go on ahead.
-What's up?
-Hey.
-Heya.
-Hey, Na-bi.
-Hi.
Hey, Na-bi, where you been?
Just outside.
Na-bi,
how about a little help here?
You can handle it, relax.
Na-bi,
saw your sculpture trying to build itself.
-It's drying up.
-Hey, I need that yellow.
-Get some more.
-That one? Okay.
-Let me see.
-Oh, yeah. All right.
Coming through, guys.
-Yo! Help me with this.
-Good morning!
Amazing, looks like I won
the jackass lottery.
What is it?
This prick!
He's the one who suggested
a hotel instead of a motel.
And now he wants me to chip in.
Who is it?
That guy from the app yesterday?
Yeah! I mean, I wouldn't be this upset
if he actually had any game,
but it wasn't even worth spending
the night with him!
So why'd you sleep with him, then?
Guess he must've had a hell of a face,
she can't resist handsome guys.
Great, I'm annoyed now.
Smoke break, guys?
Hm, can't, I'm quitting for a while.
Ji-wan won't be smoking for three days.
-Wow, three days!
-Hey, psycho, what's in three days?
A blind date. So I'm quitting until then.
And if I don't start shaking,
I might keep it up.
-Another blind date?
-Girl, you're unbelievable.
Are you that addicted to men?
Look who's talking,
Miss Fell-for-the-Hotel.
Point taken.
So loud in here.
-Going to work?
-Mm.
Hm.
-Bye!
-Are you serious?
See ya!
Whoa! Who am I supposed to smoke with now?
What if I get kidnapped
while smoking by myself?
And when my mother gets
-a phone call from them.
-Okay, I'll go with you.
You're the best.
-Come on, girl.
-And just when I got here.
I'm going.
-You don't have to drag me along.
-Just a little bit more.
Don't tell me you climb up
all these stairs
-every time you smoke.
-I really don't mind if it's for a drag.
If he's okay, you swipe right.
If it's a no, then you swipe left.
And if you both end up swiping right
for each other, you got yourself a match.
And then after that?
You two send each other messages
back and forth from the app
and if it's going well,
then maybe you'll decide
to meet up and stuff.
Guess today's not my day.
But nobody actually uses
their real names here, right?
Mm, I don't show my face, either.
But some people go ahead and just reveal
their names and faces for everyone.
Oh, I hate it
when they have tattoos like this.
Tattoos?
Yep, in fact,
the guy I met yesterday
had a huge tattoo on him as well.
You wanna know what it said?
"I will never die."
"Die." How? False advertising.
That thing of his
just kept dying and dying--
-Keep it down, you're crazy.
-It was so ridiculous.
Some tattoos kinda look pretty, though.
Like whose?
Hm?
Are you seeing someone?
Uh… Not what I said.
Like, as if I would.
You wanna join us for drinks later?
It'll be fun.
No, I think I'm fine.
Besides, I'm going to work late.
Again? Wow!
-Your life must be incredibly mundane.
-Whatever.
Look. It's one of our juniors.
Said he wants to buy you a drink.
I'm stuck.
-I haven't slept.
-Sucks, dude.
Unless you have amnesia,
I just got out of a relationship.
Hey, that's not what I meant.
We all know each other except for you,
so I just thought I'd introduce you
to each other.
Um… just not right now.
God, you are so boring.
Oh, my god!
I accidentally swiped left
on a total hottie!
-What the hell did I--
-Show me, show me, show me.
-Let me see.
-Oh! I'll never be able to see him again.
You know, you're acting
a little unlike yourself today.
Well, what do I do? How should I act?
Let's see. Out with the old jerk
and in with the new one. Hmm?
-But this app isn't for you.
-Why not?
You're pretty, I'll give you that,
but you have absolutely no taste.
-You'll only attract the losers.
-Hey!
Hmm?
Well…
I don't know yet.
-Final answer?
-Mm.
You girls have fun.
God, you're so boring.
-Call me later, okay?
-Uh-huh.
EPISODE 1: THERE'S NO SUCH THING AS FATE.
NEVERTHELESS,
THE DAY SHE BROKE UP WITH X
You got here first.
Sorry, who are you?
You're So-ri, aren't you?
Uh, no, my name is Yu Na-bi, actually.
Na-bi.
Na-bi?
Oh.
I guess I mistook you
for someone else, then.
Terribly sorry.
No, it's fine.
It's silly,
but right at the moment our eyes met…
Suddenly, the pain of the breakup
that had been weighing down on me
just a minute ago…
You mind if I sit here?
You're already sitting there, though.
Are you here with someone?
I'm not with anyone.
…melted away like snow.
But then, what about… You sure?
Aren't you here to meet with someone?
What about whoever it was you said
that you mistook me for?
I canceled on her.
Why?
Because…
I felt like
I didn't need to meet her tonight.
Loser grants the winner
a wish, right?
A deal's a deal.
That's not fair,
you conned me into it.
-Aw.
-All right.
Where was it we left off?
So you broke up today?
Oh.
Yeah.
I flat-out dumped the guy.
Guess he wasn't exactly a stud.
Actually…
he was a complete joke.
I was an idiot for going out with him.
To hell with him.
Nothing's holding me back
from going abroad now.
-Sightseeing?
-As an exchange student.
I've always had this dream
of going to Paris.
Pretty cool.
Not anytime soon, though.
Do you like traveling?
I've never traveled properly before.
-At the end of the year, maybe.
-Who with?
Uh…
With anyone?
Or alone? With a friend? Or…
A girlfriend?
Not sure yet.
With anyone.
Here you go.
So it's my turn now, right?
When I do it, why is it so hard?
You haven't had enough practice.
You keep doing it often enough,
you'll get the hang of it,
just like with everything else.
Don't think about the exact spot
you need to hit.
As long as you try and get it anywhere
near that red dot.
It's simple enough.
Oh!
Well, that's different.
What do you mean?
You look a bit different
when you're smiling.
I have no idea what you're saying.
Move your butt over.
Looks like I won.
Of course you did.
You seem pretty happy for a loser.
Well…
maybe it was more fun than I thought.
It sure is.
Anyway, it's just fun being
with you in general.
This guy…
…is seriously bad for my heart.
Right.
-Simple enough.
YU JEONG-RAN
Hi, Mom.
Honey, your aunt made
soy-braised beef.
Want me to send some over?
It's your favorite.
No need.
I still have a lot left over
from last time.
Throw away the leftovers, then.
Then eat the new one she'll be sending in.
You're always telling me
to throw away stuff. Bye.
Why is my baby
in such a grouchy mood?
I just want my daughter to always have
the freshest stuff.
I'm fine, Mom.
When are you planning
on coming home, then?
It's only an hour away by subway,
but for some reason, you never come home.
Because I don't wanna be there while he's…
It's just that the workload at school
is a bit too much.
How's Ttoli doing?
The usual.
Ttoli is always whimpering and whining
because she misses you.
Bring your boyfriend over.
I'll buy you some delicious food.
There is no boyfriend.
What? Did you break up?
Na-bi.
Mom, I need to hang up for now, okay?
What?
Why were you named
after a butterfly?
So that my life would be
as sweet as sugar.
It was my mom and aunt's idea.
I'm just kidding.
Have you ever heard
of Nathaniel Hawthorne?
Well, he's basically
my aunt's favorite author.
He said something that goes like…
Wait, I'm just a little nervous. Wait.
It's cringey, but what he said was,
"Happiness is a butterfly,
which when pursued,
is always beyond our grasp,
but sit quietly, it may alight upon you."
And that's it, my name's back story.
It's nothing special.
You're wrong.
Because I loved it.
That tattoo
on the back of your neck.
Is it a butterfly?
Mm-hm.
I like butterflies.
A lot.
We're all done.
It looks cute.
You sure this is
how you want to use your wish?
Seems like a simple thing to spend it on.
Should I…
ask for another one?
This is stupid.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
The moon looks so pretty today.
Want one?
Take it, it's my lucky stick.
Uh… Actually, I don't really smoke.
Excuse me.
Would you happen to have a cigar--
Oh.
Whoa! Suddenly, I'm all sober now.
How's it going?
Haven't seen you around here.
Can I borrow a ciggy?
I'll return the favor the next time
we bump into each other.
You can call me if you need it back, yeah?
Yeah, there's one left…
Shit, what the hell, dude? Sheesh.
What?
What are you smiling for?
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine now.
Do you want to go see butterflies?
See butterflies? What do you mean? Where?
At my place.
Hold on a minute.
I need to go to the bathroom.
What's up?
Yeah, I miss you too.
Are you going to sleep now?
Mmm.
What?
So after that, you just left?
Did you call him after?
Of course I didn't.
I didn't even get his name
after telling him where my name came from.
Just when you finally mustered up
enough courage.
What's that on your arm?
Oh, this? It's nothing.
Just a little doodle.
That's a sign of love.
Ah, no. It's nothing like that. Shut up!
-So what is it then?
-It's lust?
I don't know. It's just…
-It was really fun.
-That's wonderful.
It's hard to find someone that
you feel an instant connection with.
You ought to consider yourself lucky.
Doesn't matter.
You said he already has a girlfriend.
Cheaters are bad news.
You should never hang out with them.
Oh, that's right.
I need to post that part-time job ad.
Or maybe I should ask
some of the kids instead.
Go ahead.
How about Jae-eon then?
I'm not sure.
Would he actually even do it?
Just leave it to me.
I'll try to convince him.
-Hello, everyone.
-Oh.
Can you check?
-I have a meeting with the professor.
-Right. Yeah. Go together with Na-bi.
-To… Together?
-Together? Both of us?
It's okay with me.
-Sol can go have her meeting first.
-Uh-huh.
Trust me,
it'll be a waste of time.
It's about
the exchange student program, right?
If you both get on one-on-one,
the prof's nagging will just get longer.
Right.
-I'll be going, then.
-Thank you, bye.
That was funny.
-You're really clueless, aren't you?
-What? How so?
You see Na-bi?
She started feeling uncomfortable
because she didn't want
to be compared to Sol in there.
Oh, I didn't notice that.
You only picked the hard places to get in.
Na-bi, it's hard to get accepted
to any of these.
These schools are very strict.
You know that, correct?
Yes.
I'm not saying you're bad.
In fact, you're doing just fine.
But there are only
a limited number of spots.
You'll have to raise your GPA
to stand a chance.
Work harder, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
Remember, going abroad isn't always
the best course of action.
Staying in Korea might be
the better option in the long run.
Our local graduate schools are good.
Besides, you know what they say.
There's no place like Korea for Koreans.
Yeah?
Yeah, I agree. Yeah, that's right.
That's good.
We'll talk about this next time, okay?
And you, Sol? What happened to your list?
I've been waiting
but you haven't submitted it yet.
Yeah, I haven't yet.
You could be starting as soon as
next semester. What are you waiting for?
Something going on
that's holding you back in any way?
There isn't, it's just…
Don't worry,
I'll be making my decision soon, ma'am.
All right. Though I would honestly prefer
you make it sooner.
It's such a waste of time.
You might be thinking it's not gonna be
different from studying here.
But there are a lot of things
you can learn out there, hmm?
This is a great list right here.
So why don't you take a look at this
and make your decision in the near future.
LIST OF PROSPECTIVE UNIVERSITIES
Okay.
What is this gloom and doom
from the both of you?
You two ought to be shining
at this age, right?
You can't stay holed up
in a studio all day.
You should be active in creating
eventful life experiences
because that is the well of inspiration
you must draw from.
Yeah.
Yep.
She must've said the word
"inspiration" over a 100 times.
Keep it, you can have it.
I was gonna give you this file
if you needed it anyway.
Thanks. It'll be helpful.
It was so embarrassing back there.
What was?
I listed up all the great universities
without even thinking about my grades.
I'm jealous of you, Sol.
You can pretty much go anywhere.
I don't think
going abroad is the best idea.
Honestly, it kind of feels like
I'm just trying to run away.
-I was kind of feeling the same--
-Yun Sol!
Oh, so you were hanging out with Na-bi.
What did the professor say?
Did you two get in trouble or something?
-Oh, it was about the exchange--
-Oh.
-Assignment ideas for us.
-Assignment ideas?
That's not fair, why'd she leave me out?
That's some A-grade favoritism
right there. Why?
It was only a bit of advice.
Guess we'll be going now.
Oh, okay. Go, go.
Later, Na-bi.
I'm the one who needs advice right now.
I'm literally all out of ideas.
Oh.
You dressed up all nice for a reason?
I look nice? Really? That's a relief.
Is it because
we're going to a gathering today?
Actually, the truth is,
that blind date was supposed to be
tomorrow, right?
Turns out it can't be tomorrow.
He said something urgent came up
and asked if we could meet later today.
Or else next time won't be for a while.
And you know blind dates,
you shouldn't put 'em off for too long
or it's goodbye.
So I just agreed to meet him
later today instead.
What? Then what's gonna happen
to our gathering today?
You're gonna tell the others for me--
Hey, you're the one who made a thing
about all this. I didn't even wanna go.
I know. I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean for this.
But if you don't show up either,
everyone's gonna curse me to death.
Sol, please do this for me? Hm? Hm?
Come on, Sol. I'll owe you one.
-All right, I'll do it already.
-I love you!
Hey, if things go well with my date,
maybe I could set you up
with someone too, okay?
Yeah, there's no need.
Oh, come on.
Oh, hi.
Anything we can help you with? Hello!
-How are you guys?
-How you doing?
Hello.
-Just carry on, everyone.
-Okay.
There, no problem.
All right.
So, you're packing up soon?
You'll have to raise
your GPA to stand a chance.
Really?
You're just gonna stay here working?
If I don't, I won't finish on time.
My progress is slow enough.
That's what alcohol is best for,
when you're stuck.
I'm gonna end up drinking
with a bunch of kids.
You don't know any
of our juniors, by the way.
Don't you need any assistance
for the exhibit?
You know, at this rate,
you'll set the record
for the first one in our department
to slog through everything alone.
Gosh. Never mind, forget it.
You can forget about meeting a new man.
See ya.
Please call if you change your mind, okay?
Okay.
-Have fun over there.
-Damn right I will!
-That will be 14,000 won.
-Here.
It's him again.
Hang on a sec.
First the library, and now this.
I must be really losing my mind.
So you're really not coming?
Bit-na, what's the place called again?
We meet again.
Why are you also here?
You're here.
Mm-hm. I'm gonna head inside now.
Okay.
That's the junior.
He was asking for a drink
with you like I said.
Oh.
Look, look, look!
You're so screwed now, I'll tell you that.
Damn, this place is flooded
with too many seniors.
What?
-You got a problem with that?
-Already sick of your seniors?
Can't stand to look at us?
No one's sick of anything!
-Well, well, well.
-Calm down.
-Don't embarrass yourself.
-Everyone, there's a newbie among us.
This is a rare appearance from her,
so you better be nice to her.
This is Yu Na-bi.
And this is Park Jae-eon.
Park Jae-eon…
Oh.
That was his name,
Park Jae-eon. Finally.
Yo, what's with the face?
Do you know each other?
We don't.
It's our first time
seeing each other.
It's your first time meeting?
They each took turns taking a leave.
Plus, Na-bi barely attends
any of the school events.
She's pretty much a hermit.
That's right. She never shows up.
Oh, really?
-You should come often too.
-Hello.
-Order another set of garlic.
-Order new drinks first.
Yeah, I can have some.
Oh, uh… hello.
I got butterflies
in my stomach, that was so cute!
-Did you guys hear that?
-"Oh. Hello."
-Seriously!
-I'm Park Jae-eon.
I'll talk casually, if you don't mind.
He's the same age as us.
He used to be a business major
at K University,
but he took the exam again
to major in sculpture.
Oh, is that so?
I think I've already seen you
before, though.
What?
What… You… Where have you seen me before?
Around school.
Ah…
I said I wanted to have
a drink with her right away.
He did.
And now you finally met
each other.
Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you, too.
I'd already stopped believing…
-in old tropes like fate or love.
-Cheers!
And when you analyze moments
like this one…
Totally! Sure.
…it's unrealistic.
That professor's always giving
us assignments, it's endless torture!
You took that class,
why didn't you warn me?
-Your fault for choosing…
-Ji-wan's still not answering?
No.
She hasn't read my messages,
guess she's still with him.
-Ooh.
-Oh. She said she'd make it quick,
but it looks like things
are going really well, then.
Well, as if we couldn't
have guessed that this would happen.
Ji-wan's always been popular with the guys
even way back then.
I'm so jealous.
You know, there was a hoard of guys
asking for her number
-at our high school festival.
-But it seems like this time,
there's a chance
Ji-wan likes this guy as well.
There's no point for the poor dude.
Give her a month
and I bet she'll get sick of him.
I feel bad already.
It's her biggest wish to go on a
couple's trip for a one-year anniversary
for the first time ever.
-That's so cute.
-How cute.
I'll get our order.
It'll be hard to carry it all by yourself.
It's fine, keep talking.
Don't mind me, just carry on.
-Right, so what happened?
-You were saying?
I found out
that he has a girlfriend.
-Oh!
Oh, my god.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Oh!
Are you okay?
No, it's okay.
-What about you, you okay?
-I'm fine.
I was staring at my phone.
Nah, it's all good.
Three! One!
-Two!
-Wrong. Three!
Hat comes off now, buddy.
-Hey, here. He gets the hair tie.
-Take it off, it's the rules.
Let's make a palm tree
out of you.
Go easy on me, please.
I used conditioner today.
Seeing Jae-eon now, he seems fun.
You look so pretty!
I'm sorry, man.
-Off you go.
-That look really suits you.
Come on.
Sorry, I don't mean to bother you, but…
Oh, you wanna have a drink with us?
No, no, but…
If it's okay with you…
Shit.
This won't take long, but could you
please watch me dance for you?
Don't cover your face, it's all good!
-Go, five, six, seven, eight!
-Jae-eon has a way
of making even nasty pranks seem fun
for everyone.
-Twist your body! Twist it!
-What is that?
Good one!
Yeah!
-This is dumb.
-Aw, did that upset you?
It's nice that he smiles a lot.
-Let's play another game.
-Say what?
-Let's just drink up. Come on.
-Oh! Nothing.
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Too late.
-Oh.
-Come on. Shots, shots, shots!
-Shots! Nice!
-Hey, Jin-su.
-Huh?
-Can you pass me that?
Thanks, dude.
Hey, you ate all the entrees.
Not to mention all the meat.
Hey, guys.
Listen up. Listen up.
-I wanna ask you all.
-What is it?
Who did the nasty
in the student council room last sem?
Confess.
Whoa, so it's true that someone found
a condom in the trash can?
Ugh, that's disgusting!
So… so you mean the one on the sofa?
Quiet, shut up.
-Keep it down. All right.
-Seriously? You sure?
All right.
Better confess.
Quit playing detective.
You're barking up the wrong tree.
What was that?
You sound like you know who it is.
-So you really know? Who is it?
-Get the hell off me.
-Please, just tell me.
-We won't tell anyone.
Oh, jeez.
Really? So none of you know?
It was Choi Min-u.
-No way!
-His girlfriend right now is Jeong-a.
Then it was her and Min-u that--
Of course it wasn't. He was sleeping
with someone else back then.
So then he was actually
cheating on her? That freaking asshole!
-How could he even do that to her?
-I feel sorry for her.
There are quite a number
of pretty girls
who balance it out
by having poor judgment.
You'll be surprised.
No wonder you're called
Bit-na News. Bit-na Live! Breaking news!
-Let me pour you a shot.
-Stop overreacting.
Tune in for the scoop now!
-Oh, thank you very much.
-This is boring.
-Is your source even reliable?
-Let's go.
-No way.
-Nah, don't doubt her.
-More drinks over here, please!
-Whose glass is empty?
-Mine's empty! Mine's empty!
-You should take a break.
-But pass them anyway!
-Thank you, my dear.
You're the best!
-So how did you find out?
-Find out what?
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
-I think you dropped this.
-Oh!
Thank you very much.
Look at this guy.
You look a bit different
when you're smiling.
I'm just going to the bathroom
for a bit, okay?
Mm.
Why do I suddenly feel so annoyed?
I should probably get back to work.
I felt like getting some ice cream.
Wanna tag along?
Which one do you want?
That one?
Not that.
Hmm… that one?
No.
This one.
What's so funny?
You. You're cute.
Shut up.
You have a different style, don't you?
-Gimme that.
-Hey, what are you doing?
Let's just skip study hall
and go play some games.
Just watch.
Oh, sorry!
How come you said you didn't know me?
Uh…
Well, I was kinda caught off guard.
Plus, it would've been weird to tell them
that I knew you.
I didn't even know your name or age
and stuff…
So why'd you just suddenly leave that day?
I was drunk. Really drunk.
So if you don't mind, all that stuff
that I told you that day…
Just forget everything.
That day?
You didn't really say much.
Well…
Should be easier for you, then.
Don't worry.
I won't say anything.
Okay.
You didn't erase it.
Oh, this?
Right, I don't know why…
I tried washing it off,
but it wouldn't…
That's pretty strange.
It was a water-based marker.
Oh, really?
Yeah, that is strange.
Didn't you want to see me again after?
Well…
Not much.
But I guess I had a little regret.
'Cause I thought I'd never actually see
you again.
I felt so relieved…
I was able to see you again.
That's right.
To the left, to the right.
Huh? Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Mm-hm?
What's with you coming in together, huh?
-We thought we'd get some ice cream.
-Wow, ice cream!
Just what I wanted. Wanna try this?
No, not at all. I'm good.
Love always begins
with ice cream, you know that?
Come here!
Yeah, yeah.
-Hey! We're going out for a smoke.
-Mm.
-You wanna go with us?
-No, she doesn't smoke.
-Careful! Coming through.
-Really?
Watch out, we're going out!
-All right.
-Come on! Come on!
Damn it.
Here you go. Those are my contact details.
Just text me your bank account number,
and how much it cost you.
I'll wire you the money.
Sure, I'll be keeping in touch.
I'm really sorry about your shirt.
Forget about it.
Your head's kinda turning red,
are you okay?
Uh…
It's okay. My head's pretty tough.
Hard as a rock, you know.
Uh, and you? I ran into you pretty hard.
You don't feel dizzy or anything?
I'm feeling okay, don't worry about me.
That's a relief.
Let's go.
It's too early. Why don't we
just go for another round somewhere, huh?
Everyone here?
No one left behind?
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Hey, let's go.
-See you tomorrow.
-You're going, right?
-Okay, where are we going?
Okay. Stop pushing.
-Come on, we're leaving.
-Let's go.
-Bye, guys.
-All right. Take care.
All right. Bye.
Careful on the way back!
You were putting away
quite a few tonight. Sure you're fine?
Yeah, I feel fine.
I'm not even tipsy at all.
What about you?
Oh, is that your girlfriend?
Hm?
No, I don't have a girlfriend.
I'm taking the bus from here.
Careful going home.
Oh, take care.
We meet again.
I like butterflies.
A lot.
I felt so relieved…
I was able to see you again.
No, I don't have a girlfriend.
Don't tell me this is fate.
Oh, I'm going crazy.
OH BIT-NA
Guys, send me
20,000 won each for the drinks.
PARK JAE-EON
Why are you still awake?
Right now?
Sure it's okay to come over?
-I SENT THE MONEY
-I SENT THE MONEY TOO
Are you sleeping?
Why would he be asleep already?
What the hell am I doing?
Sleeping?
Come on, not you.
SCULPTURE STUDIO 3
HONGSEO UNIVERSITY
Hey, Sol.
Aren't you going for a smoke?
I already did just now.
Okay.
Hey, guys.
Aren't you going out for a smoke?
No, just go. I'm totally busy right now.
Don't bother me.
What about you, wanna go?
No, I'm trying to make
this damn thing stick.
So none of you wanna go?
Jeez!
-Hello.
-Hey, Na-bi.
-What you up to, Na-bi?
-Oh, hey, what's up?
-Na-bi, what's up?
-What?
Oh, nothing. What's up?
I have to work late,
I need an energy drink.
-Na-bi.
-Hey.
-You looking for someone?
-No, I'm not.
I'm just getting some fresh air.
Professor!
-Prof!
-Professor!
Professor!
Professor, can you help me?
Just for a second?
Gyeong-jun! Please help me out!
Over here! Over here! Over here!
No matter how many colors
I try to mix,
I can't get the right color that I want.
Hmm, I'm not helping you
unless you call me Mr. An.
Oh, you're not our senior,
why would I do that?
But I would be really grateful
if you'd just help me out
-with this one tiny coloration.
-Mr. An!
See? He calls me Mr. An.
-Gyeong-jun! No wait, Mr. An!
-I need your help.
But…
After you get the surface
all prepared, just apply the second layer,
and then coat it with primer
in the end. Okay?
PARK JAE-EON
He's in the group chat, though.
What's going on?
PARK JAE-EON
-Mr. An!
-What are you doing?
-Gyeong-jun! I mean, Mr. An!
-Hello, ma'am.
Why were you so startled just now?
To be honest, I'm more startled
at the state of your piece.
Why is there no progress?
Well, I… I'm almost…
I'm almost finished with it.
This shouldn't be only "almost finished."
Understand? Yes?
I'll work late today.
Working late isn't going to do
anything for…
-You and I will talk later.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Hey, Bit-na.
-What's up?
Has everyone paid their share?
What? Yeah, everyone chipped in. Why?
I was just curious, just wondering.
They all sent it.
Hmm…
Jae-eon gave it to me in cash
right before we left..
Oh.
Hmm. Mm-hm.
-Okay, carry on.
-All good?
Focus, all right?
I am focused.
I'm so full.
My stomach's going to explode.
-Not if mine does it first.
-I can barely breathe anymore.
But I can totally still have some dessert.
Cake? Now that I can put away easy.
You read my mind.
I could do cake.
I can have a slice and eat it with coffee.
That's a perfect idea!
Look, we still have some time left.
Shall we?
-We shall, my glutton friend.
-Guess our lunch will never end!
-Right on.
-Oh, yeah.
Guess you're really trying
to build that belly, huh?
Why is he always trying to pick a fight?
-I keep waiting for him to jibe with us.
-Yeah, tell me about it.
Oh, no. Has anyone seen
by Bluetooth earphones?
Earphones, earphones, earphones.
I left them at the outdoor studio.
You might as well kiss them goodbye.
They're gone now.
There are security cameras
everywhere.
Nobody's gonna take 'em,
they're probably still there.
You sure?
It's too far away.
-I'll just ask in our group chat.
-Hold on, I'll go get them for you.
-All the way back?
-Yeah.
It's fine. You really don't need to.
I was about to go back anyway,
it's not like it's out of the way.
I'll look for them and then just put them
inside your locker.
-So just message your passcode.
-I'm so touched right now.
-Thank you.
-It's nothing.
She's so kind.
I couldn't decline.
I'm way too attractive and fine.
Keep dreaming.
She'd never fall for your goofy ass.
Well, I was just trying to rationalize.
Why'd she go off
and do that for me anyway?
She was already about to head back,
it's a coincidence.
-Shh!
-Never mind. Let's go and have some
-of that cake we wanted.
-Hell yeah, cake!
What do you think this is?
Is it a bat?
It's not a bat,
it's a butterfly.
Hmm.
This piece
sure feels different
from all the other ones
that I've seen here.
I agree.
I don't even see him that often
working at the studio.
When did he put this together?
He's probably a genius.
Jae-eon entered and won almost
all the competitions last year.
Plus, he's drop-dead gorgeous.
Life's so unfair, isn't it?
So that was Jae-eon's.
But where did Jae-eon
find the idea to…
Oh, Na-bi, I didn't notice you there.
Hey, hello.
What brings you out here?
Uh, Jin-su said he left, like,
a pair of Bluetooth earphones behind.
Have you seen it?
It's probably in a small case.
No.
Oh, okay, I will…
Oh, it's Jae-eon. Hey!
-Hey, Jae-eon.
-What's up?
Hey, I haven't seen you
in a while.
Hey, you.
Oh, heya.
Looking for something?
No, I'm not.
Jae-eon, that's a butterfly, right?
She said it kinda looks like a bat.
So you actually recognized it?
Everybody thinks it's a bat.
I'm guessing you really like
butterflies, huh?
Your last piece was about the same thing.
You wanna see my butterflies?
Yeah, show it to us.
Yes, please.
Wow, they're pretty.
Is that why you got
that tattoo?
Like when people get tattoos
of their pets?
Do you have names for each of them?
No, I call them all the same thing.
"Butterfly."
I think it's perfect.
I like butterflies.
A lot.
"Butterfly."
I think it's perfect.
Jae-eon keeps making me overthink
about trivial things the same way
my annoying ex used to.
God, I hate reading
into all of this meaningless stuff.
You're such an idiot, Na-bi.
Who's the idiot?
Don't look at it.
So what is it? Is it a bunch of seaweed?
That was rude of you eavesdropping
on my thoughts
and then suddenly surprising me
out of nowhere.
I thought you were insensitive.
You just left without a word.
I was waiting for you to say something.
No, I wasn't planning on saying anything.
I was looking for this thing
my friend left behind at the studio.
You know you can get anyone
you look at to like you, don't you?
It's exactly why you make that face
and talk like that.
Huh?
There's that seaweed you said earlier.
-Come here.
-Sorry.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! Stop it.
-I'm just kidding, I'll wipe it off.
-Wipe it off.
Here, I'll clean it up for you.
I'm sorry, I'll wipe it off!
Hang on. What?
When did they get so close? I had no idea.
Aw, they look pretty good together. Hey!
-Shh!
-Why?
Let's just go.
-Come on. Let's just go.
God, my shoulders are killing me.
I wish they had a high bar at school
so I could stretch.
Loosen up.
I noticed you're hunching your back
whenever you're working.
Wait, let go for a second. Hey.
Wait a minute, hold on, stop. Wait!
I almost fell over because of you.
Bit-na says you practically live
in the studio these days.
It's not how it sounds, really.
I like working at night,
so I often stay late.
I mean, you know what it's like,
don't you?
I might try it more often.
You did make it feel fun.
As our conversation went on,
you could make out the different sides
of Jae-eon.
Hmm. I'm jealous.
There was a time
when it used to be fun for me, too.
You don't think it's fun anymore?
I think the difference is there's
a lot more to think about nowadays.
And I'm not even sure
what I should be doing.
You wanted to be an exchange student,
didn't you?
Seems like a good goal to have.
It's not even that big of a deal.
It feels special till you see
other students do it too.
To be completely honest…
I just wish I could go somewhere far away.
Why?
Well, because of my mom and also…
Let's stop talking about this.
You probably think it's…
I don't think it's boring at all.
Especially when you talk about yourself.
He's so different
from that first impression I had.
I wanted to believe I was the only one
who knew this side of him.
Oh.
There's that lovely moon you like so much.
It's pretty, isn't it?
Very pretty.
May I have your number?
Oh. My number?
Suddenly, it feels like
a new chapter is about to begin.
I'm probably not mistaken.
Yu Na-bi. I saved your number.
It doesn't matter
what it says there.
You know that I'm Na-bi.
Do you want one?
No, thanks, I'm good.
Did you get it customized?
Mm-hm.
Looks pretty, right?
Another butterfly.
Oh, show me the other ones too.
-The what?
-Your pet butterflies.
-Oh, my butterflies?
-Mm-hm.
You wanna go see?
I meant that… the…
I was talking about that video
you showed your friends earlier…
With the…
They're pretty.
What is it that you like so much
about them?
Sometimes they approach me,
then they crawl up around my face
just like this.
And it would make me feel so good.
It's lovely.
That tickles.
On second thought,
I wanna have a smoke, too.
I don't feel like going back inside.
Me neither.
Except that you don't smoke.
You wanna have drinks instead?
Drinks?
Oh, if you're gonna work some more,
then I'll just--
No, no, I'm not. Let's go.
Just the two of us?
Well, we can…
Of course we can call anyone else
who wants to go.
Should I call them?
-Why are you laughing?
-No idea.
You just make me laugh somehow.
So you're happy to have drinks
with just the two of us?
Just us.
I'm pretty sure…
We feel the same way about each other.
I'm using my wish.
I'm sure he does this to everyone.
He's so petty.
Park Jae-eon?
That guy's not the type to date.
So just forget about him.
-I'm falling! I'm falling!
-Are you hurt?
Park Jae-eon,
he really excites me.
Okay, answer this.
Does everyone have to date?
Can't just two people have
a special kind of closeness?
Or simply be near each other?
Do they have to care
if there's something in their hair?
What do I really want
from Jae-eon?
I don't get you.
You're just cold towards me sometimes.
Bit-na and I are planning that
we drink some more at my house.
Wanna join us?
And now, the bottle will decide
who will end up kissing.
Right. Maybe I should see it
for myself and maybe move on.