=The Love Duel=
=Episode 7=
Rascal!
(Oh, no.)
(I'm doomed.)
Your Highness.
It's still early.
I can't sleep.
What?
If you don't like the ground,
we can go back to bed.
No need.
I suddenly remember
I still have some business to handle.
Another time.
Let's do it another time.
Your Highness,
as long as you lie in bed,
I will
give you
a relaxing massage.
Next time.
Do it next time.
I just kicked him off the bed.
He could have come back here.
Why did he run away?
Juanjuan, did His Highness
beat you these days?
When I couldn't see you,
I was so worried.
He didn't.
He's been really nice to me.
But lately,
he's making some strange remarks.
Rather disgusting.
Be very careful, then.
Everyone says His Highness
hasn't vented his anger lately
because he is holding back it.
You don't know
when he'll have a temper outburst.
Well,
he isn't as horrible as you think he is.
But it's really creepy
to stay with him.
Everyone here says,
you love His Highness but can't get him.
Non... Nonsense!
The food is all yours now.
Lian Yue,
keep cool.
What I was saying is
it's not that I love Your Highness
but can't get you.
Precisely, I have a huge love
for Your Highness
but can't get you.
It's true.
I've figured out
where Miss Shen came from.
Tell me about it.
Miss Shen came from Binjiang.
When she was seven, her parents died.
Her fellow villagers
sold her to the magistrate
as a maid.
Later, she was sold to the Red House.
Because she was mute,
she could only be a dishwasher.
Then, Your Highness bought her.
Her parents are dead?
My father
was a famous physician in the village.
A few days ago,
he sent me a new prescription.
So, I'm cured.
A while back,
there was a fire in the Red House
and many people died.
Madam Hong, the superior of Miss Shen,
disappeared after the fire.
I think Miss Shen
is quite weird.
Go on investigating the Red House.
Yes.
How many books have been sold?
I'm asking you.
Why did you kneel?
Stand up and answer it.
None.
In such a big imperial city,
few people know how good my novel is.
Don't be sad, Your Grace.
Sad?
I'm not sad.
Only the ignorant readers should be sad.
Why on earth does no one buy my novel?
Why?
I'll take all those books.
All right.
(Cool Man and Pretty Woman)
Didn't I say
you needn't serve me anymore?
Your Highness,
I didn't please you last night
and I was really ashamed.
Today, I prepared some pastry
and came to apologize.
Guard Lian isn't here?
You care about him?
No, no.
Where are you from, Juanjuan?
Why did you suddenly ask this,
Your Highness?
You don't want to tell me.
Any sad stores in your hometown?
No. It's just a remote place
that isn't worth mentioning.
(He's suspecting me?)
Your Highness, don't beat me.
Let's just talk.
Don't move.
A hairpin for you.
It's pretty.
Don't worry.
I will never hurt you.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Whatever I do?
Whatever you do.
(Prince Heng will never hurt Juanjuan.)
Today, I'm making a pact with Juanjuan.
Whatever Juanjuan does,
I will never hurt her.
This is a written pledge.
Instead of losing his temper,
His Highness
gave me some money.
After all this trouble,
her favorability value is still below zero.
Maybe she's not a babe in the woods?
(When I forgot to play innocent,
he started to suspect me.)
(I have to maintain my persona)
(and keep playing innocent.)
However weird she is,
I have to finish the mission quickly
and go back home.
(Bookstore)
Sir,
are there any storybooks
where the heroine is silly,
weak, and adorable?
Silly, weak, and adorable?
I'll take all those books.
(Cool Man and Pretty Woman)
- Yes, there are.
- All right.
Sir, are there any storybooks
where the heroine
is crazy in love with the hero?
Yes.
Check this one.
It's been selling very well lately.
(Cool Man and Pretty Woman)
Three buyers?
Go get me the three people
who bought my novel.
I'm going to meet these confidants.
(Cool Man and Pretty Woman)
(He can't be noticing)
(that I'm learning to play innocent, huh?)
(She has feelings for me, indeed.)
(To talk with me,)
(she's trying to know my every move.)
What are you guys doing there?
Come over.
After you, Your Highness.
So, you're the author, Your Grace.
Yes. Let me sign your book.
In such a great case, be more active.
By Miss Gorgeous?
Keep it carefully.
When I get famous someday,
you keep it in your room.
It will bless you.
Thank you, Your Grace.
I'll treasure it.
Oh,
I hear you're now serving
as my brother's personal maid.
I thought
you were a snobbish girl.
Unexpectedly, you have a very good taste.
You're pretty and honey-tongued, too.
That's for sure.
My girl
is always the best.
I just didn't know
you also read such love stories.
Yes.
Because I'm lonely.
What about you, Your Highness?
What a coincidence!
Because
I'm lonely, too.
This is terrific.
How about the two of you make a pair
and go shopping with me tomorrow?
♪When a rare meteorite shower
fell from the clear sky♪
♪When crows and swans whispered♪
♪The memory you left
was like remains of the last century♪
♪Gorgeous but unrepeatable♪
♪The more I thought, the deeper I sank,
repeatedly fixing my breath♪
♪Diving deep into no man's sea♪
♪With a cinnabar dot
between the eyebrows♪
♪She picked some flowers,
smiled silently♪
♪And sincerely made a wish to let it go♪
♪When he took off his armor♪
♪Dropping his weapon in the wilderness♪
♪Was what he deserved♪
♪There wasn't a response
at the end of the story♪
♪Until the curtain eventually descended♪
♪I was watching it all the time♪
♪Yet the persona turned out to be me♪
(The right of communication
through information network)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent.)