=The Love Duel=
=Episode 4=
Your Highness.
Are you all right, Miss Shen?
I'm all right.
Thank you, Your Highness.
(He didn't give me a hand,
but now he's caring about me.)
(What a bummer!)
(She's getting shy.)
(She must have feelings for me.)
- Let's go to the garden.
They're for you.
Such beautiful flowers.
Because
I don't want you to have no present
while someone else does.
(Tacky.)
(So old-fashioned.)
What... What do you want?
Wait a minute!
Why haven't you
said happy birthday to me?
Happy birthday.
What about my present?
Fine.
I'll pretend
you forgot to get me a present.
I order you to give it to me tomorrow.
Aye, Your Grace.
Aye, aye.
That's what you always say.
Your Grace,
His Highness needs to be waited on.
I should go.
Stop right there.
(Cool Man and Pretty Woman)
Finish reading this within three days
and write an essay of a thousand words.
Leave this to me, Your Highness.
What are you doing?
(Darn it.)
I'm sexy,
aren't I?
Shaoheng,
what are you doing?
I'm measuring His Highness's height.
With your leg?
Mm.
Shaoheng,
is that true?
It's an adult thing.
A young girl like you
should stay out of it.
Let me measure your height, too.
Don't go.
For your information, Chief,
Hongwu failed her assassination.
What about her?
She hasn't given herself away yet.
Besides,
we've heard from Mr. Yueyin.
(Such a great chance was gone again.)
(Luckily, I got back my dagger.)
(Or there would be more trouble.)
Bullying in such a terrible workplace?
Who did this?
Come out!
Who are you?
It's me.
What happened to your face?
Rou did that.
She said I couldn't clean my face
before I washed these clothes.
Juanjuan, where are you going?
See how I'm going to curse you.
You.
What... What do you want?
To curse you.
You witch... Bla, bla, bla...
(What is going on?)
Bla, bla, bla...
Sorry.
Juanjuan,
let's just do our work.
(What happened just now?)
(Such wonderful curse words...)
(But I failed to say any.)
Miss Shen,
any words against your persona
have to be banned.
Zhang San?
You've shown up at last.
I was in hospital
for a work-related injury.
What?
I'm so sorry.
Are you saying
I can't curse anyone?
Shen Juanjuan is a babe in the woods.
How would she ever use swear words?
Every time you go against this persona,
you'll be silenced.
What kind of fool made this rule?
You did.
You told me.
The wrong persona
would cause big trouble.
My superior thought
it made perfect sense.
So, he made the rule for you.
Oh, darn it.
This is a bonus mission.
As a famous scene in the novel,
it advanced
Shen Juanjuan's assassination.
Take it as an apology.
That's more like it.
To bathe Prince Heng?
You call this a bonus?
It's once in a lifetime opportunity...
Come over here.
(Check Juanjuan's scar)
Bonus mission?
Check Juanjuan's scar.
It's an important scene
where the hero and heroine get closer.
Do it wisely.
(In TV dramas,)
(there's always a sad story behind a scar.)
(When I comfort her accordingly,)
(she'll easily have feelings for me.)
Butler.
Butler!
Your Highness,
here I am.
When I take a bath today,
do have Shen Juanjuan
wait on me personally.
Miss Juanjuan,
when you bathe His Highness,
be very careful.
If you hurt him,
you'll be decapitated.
Why didn't you say so at first? I quit.
No way.
You begged me
to have you bathe His Highness.
Look, you are of one mind.
You want to bathe His Highness
and His Highness wants that, too.
Off you go.
(Now, I'm in a real dilemma.)
Your Highness,
I'm here to bathe you.
(It's the first time
that a woman bathes me.)
(I'm so embarrassed.)
(It's the first time that I bathe a man.)
(Such bad luck.)
- (Isn't it way too awkward?)
- (To get back home,)
- (I'll just do it!)
(Where's the scar?)
(No scar?)
(Is it under her dress?)
(Flirt.)
(If I didn't need to play innocent,)
(I would be unmanning you.)
Ouch.
Mercy, Your Highness.
I was just trying to bathe you very well.
Take off your dress.
What?
Don't you get it?
Flirt!
Give your order to the Death Lord!
♪When a rare meteorite shower
fell from the clear sky♪
♪When crows and swans whispered♪
♪The memory you left
was like remains of the last century♪
♪Gorgeous but unrepeatable♪
♪The more I thought, the deeper I sank,
repeatedly fixing my breath♪
♪Diving deep into no man's sea♪
♪With a cinnabar dot
between the eyebrows♪
♪She picked some flowers,
smiled silently♪
♪And sincerely made a wish to let it go♪
♪When he took off his armor♪
♪Dropping his weapon in the wilderness♪
♪Was what he deserved♪
♪There wasn't a response
at the end of the story♪
♪Until the curtain eventually descended♪
♪I was watching it all the time♪
♪Yet the persona turned out to be me♪
(The right of communication
through information network)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent.)