=The Love Duel=
=Episode 8=
What a coincidence!
Because
I'm lonely, too.
This is terrific.
How about the two of you make a pair
and go shopping with me tomorrow?
Your Highness, do we have to hold hands?
What?
You don't want it?
That's not true.
I don't dare.
There's a cold drink stall over there.
Let me buy you a cold drink.
No, thanks. I'm not thirsty.
Shh.
To me,
you don't need to be courteous.
Well, I'm indeed a little bit thirsty.
I knew it.
Turn around.
The cool man held her hand
and pressed his finger to her lips.
Details.
Don't follow them so closely.
Or they'd feel awkward.
Then I can't get to know
how a man and a woman date.
If you ruin this,
you'll have to date me.
I'm far inferior to you, Your Grace.
Don't be kidding.
Lanterns.
Kites.
Where have they gone?
Why are they gone so soon?
Kites for sale.
Juanjuan,
I heard you had been doing laundry work
since you came to my mansion.
I feel sorry for that.
But it doesn't matter.
From this day on,
you will never suffer again.
(He seems to have
some true feelings for Juanjuan.)
(But what should I say?)
(How come she isn't moved at all?)
Looks like you still don't believe me.
If I'm lying,
let me...
No blood oath.
Or it'd come true.
Come on.
Your Highness,
don't always scare me like that.
I'm so scared.
Juanjuan, your coquetry
looks charming, too.
I love it.
You make me shy.
How could you flirt with me
when we're out here?
I won't talk to you.
"Every time I smile,
I want you to be around."
Juanjuan.
Your Highness,
I guess I ate something bad
and now I'm throwing up.
Because of the cold drink, I guess.
I feel sick, too.
It's not me.
It's really not me.
Assassins!
(Oh, no.)
(If he dies,)
(I can't complete my mission.)
(Then do I have to...)
Danger, Your Highness!
♪The plane trees are lonesome and drear♪
♪The storm roars outside the window♪
♪Cut, it won't break♪
Juanjuan.
Your Highness,
you have to stay alive.
♪Such lovesickness can't be driven away ♪
Juanjuan!
♪But I've fallen in love♪
♪What if I bend my head and get old?♪
Lian Yue.
Kill them all!
Yes.
Xiliu,
where's His Highness?
Juanjuan, you're finally awake.
Tell me. Is His Highness dead?
How come?
If he were dead,
how could I still be here?
His Highness is alive,
with extreme longevity.
If His Highness isn't dead,
why are you so sad?
Just because he isn't dead, I...
Anyway,
His Highness really cares about you.
He not only kept you company
for a long time
but also asked me
to make you some decoction.
(I didn't know)
(this terrible prince
could also be thoughtful.)
Go. Let's go check that out.
I guess she actually loves me.
Lian Yue,
stop the investigation on Juanjuan.
But she is rather suspicious.
She just loves me
and she did all those things to attract me.
If she were a real assassin,
why did she protect me from the stabbing?
(Looks like that accident)
(has let down their guard.)
Your Highness, are you all right?
Lian Yue,
it hurts so much.
Get out now.
But Your Highness,
you only have some minor bruises.
Get out now.
Hurry.
Your Highness,
are you all right?
Your Highness, how are you?
I'm fine.
Juanjuan,
what about you?
How's your injury?
It was my honor to protect you,
Your Highness.
I just didn't know
you could do such great martial arts.
(Zhang San didn't tell me
about his martial arts.)
I'm glad you're fine.
(I also didn't know I could do that.)
My shoulder hurts, but I can bear it.
Let me do it myself.
Let me do it.
- Leave it to me.
- Juanjuan.
- Your Highness.
Thank you for taking care of me today.
You must be kidding.
You even risked your life to save me.
What I did is nothing.
Funny enough,
a few days ago, I suspected you
of colluding with the assassins.
It was rather ridiculous.
How could it be?
There can't be so many assassins.
I'm tired.
Your Highness, get some rest early.
See you.
So hot.
Shen Juanjuan,
why did you betray our organization?
♪When a rare meteorite shower
fell from the clear sky♪
♪When crows and swans whispered♪
♪The memory you left
was like remains of the last century♪
♪Gorgeous but unrepeatable♪
♪The more I thought, the deeper I sank,
repeatedly fixing my breath♪
♪Diving deep into no man's sea♪
♪With a cinnabar dot
between the eyebrows♪
♪She picked some flowers,
smiled silently♪
♪And sincerely made a wish to let it go♪
♪When he took off his armor♪
♪Dropping his weapon in the wilderness♪
♪Was what he deserved♪
♪There wasn't a response
at the end of the story♪
♪Until the curtain eventually descended♪
♪I was watching it all the time♪
♪Yet the persona turned out to be me♪
(The right of communication
through information network)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent.)