=The Love Duel=
=Episode 20=
With these evidential letters,
your dirty deals will finally be exposed.
Xingchen,
this world isn't as simple
as you think it is.
You and I could have
done something great together.
Shut up. We're different.
Xingchen,
you didn't see this coming, huh?
Put the key
into the lock under the potted orchid.
Spin right
and that's it.
Orchid?
You're smarter.
You wouldn't figure out the signal
of the shifted orchid.
This is the day
you're going to die.
Kill her.
It's brilliant of you,
Your Royal Highness.
You predicted that
they would assassinate you.
Princess Consort Heng,
you and Shaoheng both came.
A sweet couple, indeed.
Shen Juan.
Didn't I ask you not to come alone?
You really have double standards.
Let's finish this quickly.
Be very careful.
Indeed the great assassin I picked.
In this case,
I should kill you personally.
Madam Hong,
if you kill me,
you won't be detoxicated, either.
An assassin is destined to die.
If you and I can die together,
it's kind of our fate.
Juanjuan.
Your Royal Highness...
You...
What do you want?
What do you think?
You!
The son of my father's second wife!
How dare you do this!
All this time,
you called me the Crown Prince
but surpassed me in all respects!
I did everything
just to get back
what I was supposed to have!
Don't you know a villain usually
loses his life in his long speech?
You...
You don't dare to kill me.
I'm your lineal brother.
If Father knows this,
you'll be doomed.
And you.
You'll be dead, too.
He knew it a long time ago.
Royal edict from King Changle.
The Crown Prince fought for power
and killed innocent people.
King Changle ordered
the Crown Prince's mansion
be closed down
and the Crown Prince be detained
for later execution.
I don't believe this.
I just don't.
You don't believe it?
Lian Yue gathered evidence
of what you had done.
Today, we came here
just in case you escaped upon hearing it.
Take him away.
Yes.
It's all over.
Then the evidence I gathered
won't be needed anymore, huh?
It's still needed.
It can lure out more bugs.
What is wrong with you?
You didn't tell me about your plan.
What do you think I am?
A strong woman.
But I still wanted to protect you.
So,
I had to keep it from you.
Fine, you're honey-tongued.
Let's go home.
Then whish, whish...
I knocked them down.
Mighty move, Your Highness.
A toast to you.
Well, Your Highness,
you were brave, too.
I used to think
you were a coward.
Unexpectedly, you fought bravely.
To Your Highness.
Why do you not drink?
Why does a man like you
drink so slowly?
Come on. Open your mouth.
♪Fell from the clear sky♪
♪When crows and swans whispered♪
♪The memory you left
was like remains of the last century♪
♪Gorgeous but unrepeatable♪
♪The more I thought, the deeper I sank,
repeatedly fixing my breath♪
♪Diving deep into no man's sea♪
♪With a cinnabar dot
between the eyebrows♪
♪She picked some flowers,
smiled silently♪
♪And sincerely made a wish to let it go♪
♪When he took off his armor♪
♪Dropping his weapon in the wilderness♪
♪Was what he deserved♪
♪There wasn't a response
at the end of the story♪
♪Until the curtain eventually descended♪
♪I was watching it all the time♪
♪Yet the persona turned out to be me♪
♪After you left, the story didn't go on♪
♪I wouldn't know how to love or hate♪
♪In such a weird story,
every dialogue sounds suspicious♪
♪No need to keep asking♪
♪The more I thought, the deeper I sank♪
♪The harder I struggled, the worse I felt♪
♪Got stuck in this absurd drama♪
♪With a cinnabar dot
between the eyebrows♪
♪She picked some flowers,
smiled silently♪
♪And sincerely made a wish to let it go♪
♪When he took off his armor♪
♪Dropping his weapon in the wilderness♪
♪Was what he deserved♪
♪There wasn't a response
at the end of the story♪
♪Until the curtain eventually descended♪
♪I was watching it all the time♪
♪Yet the persona turned out to be me♪
♪With a cinnabar dot between the eyebrows♪
♪She picked some flowers, smiled silently♪
♪And sincerely made a wish to let it go♪
♪When he took off his armor♪
♪Dropping his weapon in the wilderness♪
♪Was what he deserved♪
♪There wasn't a response
at the end of the story♪
Wait a minute.
What?
Last night...
Now,
what is our relationship?
Don't think too much.
Now, we're at most
intimate friends.
Eighty percent?
No wonder she said something like that.
What does she think I am?
(Forget it.)
(If it reaches 100 percent,)
(I'll complete my mission and go back.)
(Leaving her here all alone)
(would be really dangerous.)
(But anyway,)
(in case she loves me
with all her heart,)
(I need to take some precautions.)
♪When a rare meteorite shower
fell from the clear sky♪
♪When crows and swans whispered♪
♪The memory you left
was like remains of the last century♪
♪Gorgeous but unrepeatable♪
♪The more I thought, the deeper I sank,
repeatedly fixing my breath♪
♪Diving deep into no man's sea♪
♪With a cinnabar dot
between the eyebrows♪
♪She picked some flowers,
smiled silently♪
♪And sincerely made a wish to let it go♪
♪When he took off his armor♪
♪Dropping his weapon in the wilderness♪
♪Was what he deserved♪
♪There wasn't a response
at the end of the story♪
♪Until the curtain eventually descended♪
♪I was watching it all the time♪
♪Yet the persona turned out to be me♪
(The right of communication
through information network)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent.)