YoYo English Channel YouTube
Walking, walking, forgetting
The promise is forgotten in the story
The remaining memories are like fireworks burning and scattering
When I turn around and leave
If the world can return to the intersection of farewell
I won't let go of your hand
The promise that can't be kept
When the breath disappears at the edge of space
I have everything
I still love you
Actually, it has never changed
If there is still a promise that will be kept
Please remember that my dream is always there
Episode 2
Do you think everything is spinning here?
I feel dizzy
Why do I feel that this place is spinning?
Can you slow down?
You are quite agile
Are you drunk? Your face is so red
You are drunk
Look at yourself
Hello, I'm here
I'm here
Li Junyu
You have a pair of deep eyes
Very beautiful
Hurry up and go inside
Ok
I'll find a place to open it
Are you not going to open it?
Stop it, you are drunk
Go
I told you to be strong
What kind of alcohol do you drink when you are not drunk?
I'm just a little bit of a return
Don't go
Go
I'm a little bit tired today
Maybe another day
Yang Shuang
Jin Yu
Yang Shuang, drink some water
Why are you so late?
I'm here to see you
Come here
When I was a kid
Ye Meng sent me a message
He was in a hurry
He asked me to come and see a friend
How did you know each other?
It's a long story
A few years ago
Our psychological counseling office
came to Ningcui for a public service lecture
At that time, the people in this town were very secretive
No one came to listen
Only Ye Meng came every time he gave a lecture
And asked a lot of questions about depression
Does she know about your past?
No
She just loves to be idle
Unwilling to do anything
I can't stop her
I remember you came to Ningcui
A few girls like her
You don't fall in love
So I'm encouraging you to try to talk
By the way
I heard your grandma tell me some time ago
Found a girl in Jiangbei
I didn't expect you to be Xiao Meng
No
That's not a relationship
I met him just for my grandma's blind date
I think you are in good shape
It's not your fault
Don't blame yourself
Anyway, as long as you don't mention him
it's easy to say
Jinxue, do you know the white bear's smile?
The more people want to avoid things they don't want to mention
You don't have to be self-conscious
I know it's not easy to forget the past
But don't worry
You don't have to avoid it
OK, if there's nothing else, I'll go back
I'll see you off, uncle
No, no
If you don't want him to know about your past
I'll pretend I don't know you
See you, uncle
I'll go back
Li Junyu
I'm so sleepy
Thank you
Where's Zhao Yanshu?
He left
How is he?
He was my psychologist
I've been seeing him for years
But you
You don't have to see him
What's the matter?
Why are you asking yourself?
My grandma said my mom had depression
I just think
My mom is so cheerful
How can she have depression?
I just listened to a lot of Yang Shu's lectures
Li Junyu
I know you think I'm very realistic
But I'm really afraid of you
Forget it
I just want to tell you
I hope you can open yourself
I'm used to it alone
In my past life
The worst time
I lived alone
I've been through it alone
You have me now
Look at me
I'm stable, rich and fresh
Think about it
What do you like about me?
Just this face is enough
I'm the first person in my life
To be active and threatening
Didn't you tell me
You wanted to ask the shopkeeper?
I didn't say anything
You'd better not annoy me
If I like someone
It won't change
Really?
Me too
You
Are you still testing the evidence?
I shouldn't have let Yang Shu come
I just took you down
See the little water
Who is the principal?
You should thank me
For not taking advantage of others
Come on, you dare
What are you talking about?
It's still early
If I want to do something
There's still time
Do whatever you want
Anyway, it's not my fault
I'm sorry
Good night
It's quite deep
I've been looking for you all night
You're here
What's up?
You're with Ye Meng?
What's the answer?
It's so important to you
You don't like me
But you want to show your affection to me
It's all for the sake of stimulating Ye Meng
You hate her so much
That's called very hate, okay?
From childhood to adult
My classmates like her more
The boys I like
They all like her
Even my parents
Say it all the time
Look at Ye Meng
She's good-looking
I'm also very attractive, okay?
And I'm not bad-looking
Chen Ji dumped her a hundred thousand miles away
How could she become someone else's child?
Maybe in her eyes
You're also someone else's child
Even so
I can't be with her
In a table for the rest of my life
We may hate each other for the rest of our lives
Sorry
I used you as a tool
We're still friends in the future
If you really like Ye Meng
I'll give you another advice
You must keep her in Ningcui
Don't let her go back to Jiangbei
Ji Yu, you're here
He's here
Kite
I have something to tell you
I'm going to Jiangbei
Go to Jiangbei
Where are you going?
To see Li Lingbai
You went to find that woman
No, you don't know how to do it, do you?
I've bought the tickets
What do you think?
She seems to have a serious illness
She's dying
As her son
We have to go over and get a family property
I'll come back and raise you
Take you to eat delicious food and drink spicy food
Don't you always want to learn me to race and jump?
Let's take that world as the flying saucer
Where to stick, where to fly
I don't lack her money
I have money
Stop being a laughing stock
What kind of attitude does she have?
You don't know
OK
Don't go anywhere
I won't stop you
When you land
Tell the doctor
I bought you a price insurance
If anything happens to you
I'll go to Li Pei
Have a good year
Don't even think about it
I'll climb back before the Spring Festival
I'll climb back
Eat fast
Pour some oil first
Then 125 ml of milk
And stir well
After that
We can add our flour
I said you are really good
My legs are just so busy
Don't be tired
Take a good picture of me
The homework of the home and school
Let's take a vlog
It's the power of love, okay?
OK, OK, OK
I'll take a thin face for you
45 degrees
OK, OK
Let me see
Here, take a look
How is it?
Good, good, good
Very good
Last night
You two drank
Went into the room
Nothing
This is a bit too uncooperative
City girls and girls
I'm going to love
You two are too cooperative
They all said
Women chase men, men kill
You two are all
One for one
Is it because you give him
Not enough hints
Or he doesn't want to
If so
He's a bit too aggressive
I actually didn't want to
Do with him last night
Then why did you take others
To the room
You don't understand
You are really in the frame, sister
Don't say
Good, good, good
You're done, Ye Meng
Done
Up
It's snowing
Where?
Really?
Really, really, hurry up
Be careful of your legs
It's snowing in Ningcui
I have to take a picture
I'm afraid
I'll fall down
You just asked me
Is it from Dong Zheng
I don't know
But my first reaction now
Is not to take pictures and post them on the web
What is it then
I'm worried about the snow
Will Li Junyu bring an umbrella
Or will he fall
I don't know
You're like shooting an idol drama
You're really the same
But my first reaction now
Is not to take pictures and post them on the web
What is it then
I'm worried about the snow
Will Li Junyu bring an umbrella
Or will he fall
Where?
Hospital or home
Home
The snow is beautiful
Are you cold?
Can you put the window on?
What do you know
This is romantic
It's the atmosphere
You're awake
Li Junyu is going to celebrate his birthday
What do you think I'll give him
You don't have to give him anything
Just give it to him yourself
Su, you say this every day
I don't have
I can't think about it
I'm not going to give it to you
I'm going to give it to you
I can't think about it
You have a good power
Teach me
Take it away
Don't you have it
I don't want you to do it
I want me to do it
You don't understand the sense of ritual
OK, OK, OK
We don't understand
You are the people who came back from the big city
It's a sense of ritual
It's an atmosphere
I beg you, I beg you
You close the window first
Why are you
fighting with this window
I don't understand
OK, I understand
Choose a color you like
I don't believe you
You draw one first
Let me see what level you are
You draw it like this
Just like this
I was scared
Yes
It's good
Fang Yan
You are really good
You can do it yourself later
OK, OK, OK
I booked a ticket for you
The plane tomorrow morning
will let the driver pick you up
I may go to Jiangbei tomorrow
Come on
Hurry up
If Li Jun finds you
I'll be in trouble
No, sister
I am just
not able to stand up
You are so hard
to push me
Sorry, sorry
I forgot about your leg
Come on, give me that
Give it to me
You see
You are a fireworks
and a cake
Aren't you afraid
your brother will get angry
and get angry
I'm not
Aren't you afraid
your brother will get angry
He has a good memory
and a good mouth
I don't want him to
say that
I made a cake
for his birthday
Give it to me
No, no
It's okay
You are so considerate
Be careful
You two go out first
Okay, Mr. Li
You have changed a lot
You are more and more
like a man
How is grandma
She broke her leg some time ago
She is in Fujian now
She is fine now
Why didn't you
tell me about it
I know
you are still blaming me
Those years
I have let you down
I have let your grandma down
Why are you
sick all of a sudden
Help me
I have lived here
for more than half a year
I often had nightmares
I dreamed
of a storm
You held my hand
and cried and shouted
and said
Mom, don't drive me away
Don't drive me away
Now I think
I should call you
I have checked the information
on my way
I need to do a physical examination first
and then do a bone marrow transplant
Are you willing
to donate your bone marrow to me
You came to me
just for this
The process is more complicated
It takes you a few days
to get here
I will have someone
to move you to the hospital
to do the procedure
Mom, why are you at home
Where is your brother
He is not here
I am feeding him
Where did he go
He went to Jiangbei
so suddenly
He went to the blood bank
Blood blood
No
I heard from grandma
that his mom was seriously ill
We don't know what disease she had
Anyway, it is said that
it is a life-threatening disease
and she had to go to China
I am not sure
I heard that it is a life-threatening disease
and she had to donate her bone marrow to me
That woman is afraid of death
and she knows that she has a son
My brother is stupid
When she heard that her mom was ill
she went to Jiangbei without saying anything
I guess
she still has hope for that woman
My brother is going to celebrate his birthday
He is going to celebrate his birthday
I guess he still thinks
that his mom can celebrate his birthday
I heard that Jun Gu was very sick
He is all alone now
There is no one around him
who can ask him if he is sick
It is so pitiful
Hello
The number you dialed is not available now
Sorry
The subscriber you dialed...
Hello
Jun Yu
Pull over
Mom
I want to ask you a question
Ask away
I am not your biological son.
Fang Fang, you know you are the biggest hero in my heart.
Super big hero.
I know you.
You can do it.
I believe you.
I know you are a very good kid.
I will be with you.
Don't be afraid.
Hello. I want to find a patient named Li Jin Yu.
May I ask which room she is in?
Wait a minute. I will help you find her.
B39.
Thank you.
It hurts.
What?
I am here.
Don't be sad.
That's why I choose silence.
Hold me.
Let time set a blinding outline.
How to live in the memory of the past.
Little by little, memories are mixed up.
Buried in the fire of the past.
I am too persistent.
Too much talk.
How can you understand me?
The silence I gave you.
I still remember the name in my heart.
Don't forget.
Hello.
I am sorry.
I didn't have your phone with me.
I didn't get your call.
You didn't tell me.
You called me to let me go to Jiangbei to pick you up?
How is that possible?
It's because I dreamed of you.
I called you.
I will go to Jiangbei to pick you up.
It's because I dreamed of you.
I called you to ask if you like tofu cake.
When I was in Jiangbei,
there was a tofu cake shop.
We often went there. It was delicious.
If you want to eat it,
I can take it back for you.
No.
Let's go together.
But forget it.
I finally came to Jiangbei.
There are many people who want to see me.
Even if you come,
I don't have time to see you.
You really don't want to see me?
No.
Okay.
Yu Ziyang.
Mom.
I miss mom.
My good son.
Let mom see you.
Are you thin?
You leave so soon?
You spent so much time acting in this art play.
There is no need.
I know.
Li Shuo Fang is sick.
You have a bad eye.
I practiced in front of the mirror for several days.
I will not let you go for nothing.
This is a compensation for you.
This is what I owe my dad.
This drum,
you can use it to whoever you want.
I don't want to know.
Okay.
As you like.
I will go.
Let's go home.
Mom made you spicy chicken.
And braised pork.
And...
Anyway, all your favorite.
Why are you here?
Someone ran to Jiangbei without saying anything.
Why don't you allow me to come and block them?
My fault.
I will eat tofu cake.
How is the thing in Jiangbei going?
Is it going well?
Not bad.
I will go to the hospital.
Okay.
It's all over.
You went there.
You made a mess.
If you keep making trouble,
you will be in trouble.
Did you bring your seat belt?
Okay.
Let's go.
What's up, Lin Hui?
Nothing.
Come to my house.
This...
Mr. Li, please.
Are you ready?
Happy birthday.
I was going to give you a grand opening.
But you went to Jiangbei secretly.
This is the only thing left.
But I made this myself.
And it's my first time making a cake.
You also bought me tofu cake.
So we are both good at it.
You are both good at it.
It's not the way to use it.
I can use it however I want.
Wait.
Come in.
Hurry.
This is the gift I gave you.
Why did you give me a goldfish?
I'm trying to find a partner for your little black fish.
I'm also a role model for you.
Little black fish won't be lonely in the future.
It's lively.
Next.
Come on.
Make a wish.
Li Jing Yu.
You haven't made a wish yet.
Try this cake.
Although it's my first time making it,
I think it tastes good.
Try it.
Xu Xiao Mei is looking for me.
Your sister told me
that you were afraid of being bitten by a mosquito.
So I made a wish.
I'm afraid that you will be bitten by a mosquito.
I'll go and check it for her.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't I tell you?
I called you, didn't I?
You said you didn't want to see me.
So you came back in time.
I went to Jiangbei myself.
Some people don't want to see me.
My heart is broken.
What if I don't come back?
What's wrong?
Do you still want to try it with me?
Yan Meng.
Do you still want to be with me?
Forget it.
I didn't say anything.
I...
I want to ask you.
The question you're asking me now...
Is it because you like me...
or because you're moved by something?
I want to be with someone who likes me.
So I'm not in a hurry to answer.
You can think about it slowly.
Eat the cake.
Try it.
I don't know if it's big or small.
Look at this smile.
It's so like you.
You should smile more.
It's hot.
Oh, she understands.
Fate is hard to avoid.
There's an accident.
It's just that at this moment,
she chose not to say anything.
She didn't think about the results.
It's worth it.
The flower that bloomed in the summer
Flows through the night
How bright the company is
Is it also a kind of answer
The flower that bloomed in the summer
Flows through the night
How bright the company is
Is it also a kind of answer
I met you
I thought of you
I heard any news from you
The love that was raised in my heart
Occupies my mind
Go, where to go
How to avoid
Those memories about you
I'm so addicted to the abyss
Can't cut it off
I'm silent
Put the flowers in the back
Maybe it will make sadness no longer spread
Self-righteousness, pretending to be decisive
But still in the abyss, obsessed
The most perfect lie
Deceive yourself
If love is to let go, let us lose the relationship
Why is this
The moment of tears
Heart still yearns
The most perfect lie
Deceive yourself
If love is to let go, let us lose the relationship