[English subtitles are available]
[Our Interpreter]
[Episode 33]
[My heart, the bird of the wilderness, has found its sky in your eyes]
[They are the cradle of the morning, they are the kingdom of the stars]
[My songs are lost in their depths]
[Rabindranath Tegore]
Mr. Xiao, I was so scared just now.
Luckily, Director Dong
didn't notice the mistake in the minority language.
Xiao, you showed your personal views just now.
The board of directors has rejected the development
of sign language translation several times.
But you purposely mentioned it
in front of Director Dong.
The only reason
why they have rejected it
is the market is too small.
But my purpose is to expand the market.
Mr. Xiao is right.
Let's get to the point.
How do we solve
our problem in the minority language?
Actually, you and I both know
poaching Cheng Yao
is the quickest way currently.
Wait a little longer.
Wait for what?
Is there any other way?
Xiao,
you don't want to poach Cheng Yao.
Is it because of the reason
I have in my heart?
No.
You already know
before I tell you?
Xiao Yicheng, let me remind you.
You are Lin Xi's future husband.
But you have
a more important identity.
You are a founder of Yuyi.
At this time,
you know clearly
what you should do.
Why don't you
go talk to Cheng Yao?
Considering the personal relationship
between Cheng Yao and me,
I don't want him
to make a career move to Yuyi unwillingly because of this.
Listen.
Let me remind you too.
You are Cheng Yao's girlfriend.
But you also have
a very important identity.
You are a founder of Yuyi.
At this time,
you also know clearly
what you should do.
Tong Xin,
let's think from each other's perspective.
The problems we face
are the same.
Mr. Xiao, as you wish,
I'll talk to him.
Mr. Xiao,
I've never seen
Ms. Tong so angry.
Cheng Yao.
I hope you can carefully consider
what I'm going to say next.
[A new virus has broken out in some countries in Africa]
According to Reuters,
today, the Health Department reported
a new virus has broken out
in some countries in Africa.
Many patients
have been confirmed to be infected.
Six people are needed.
You can go.
Stop. I don't want to go.
As you can see,
the translation association asked us
to form a translation team
of 30 members
to go with the medical staff to provide support.
I hope Huasheng's employees
can sign up for it actively.
It's said that
the mortality rate of this virus
exceeds 50%.
I still have
two ongoing projects.
I don't think I'll be asked to go.
Jieyin and Jitianyu's lists
have been finalized.
Huasheng won't
lag behind willingly, right?
I'll go.
Mr. Zhang, I'll go.
Mr. Xu,
thank you for this.
But we have many young employees.
How can we let you go?
Sit.
Count me in.
You've been to East Timor
and Nairobi.
I served in the military before.
I also have experience in rescue operations.
Help me sign up for it.
Count me in.
Me too.
Okay.
Thank you for signing up.
Let's applaud for their courage.
Here's the thing.
We still need at least two people.
I hope
I can see your application forms tomorrow.
This place is not somewhere we can casually visit.
The virus
has a short incubation period and a high fatality rate.
I'm really worried
about these colleagues who will go there.
We definitely can't sign up.
Mommy.
Sweetie,
are you still working at this hour?
No, I'm not working.
Just watching some videos.
Don't spend too much time on your computer after you come home.
It's bad for your eyes.
Here.
Drink the warm milk.
Rest early.
Mommy, you rest early too.
Shasha.
Tian.
Tian, where are you?
Tian. Tian.
What's wrong, Shasha?
Did you sign up for the support project
to avoid me?
What do you mean?
If you signed up for it to avoid me,
I can resign.
Shasha,
I admit
it's indeed a bit awkward
for us to be under the same roof
after we broke up.
But that's not why
I signed up for the support project.
Then...
can you...
not go to Africa?
Why?
You've already
had similar experiences.
That's exactly why I have to go.
But
you still have the Consumer Products Expo's project.
It's not like
that project can't proceed
without me.
But it's dangerous there.
I shall dedicate myself to the interests of the country in life and death
irrespective of personal weal and woe.
Shasha,
although that place
is not the land
beneath our feet today,
in the face
of today's globalization
and a disaster that affects the human kind,
we have the responsibility
and obligation
to help them, right?
I understand what you said.
But I still don't want you
to go there.
Then... what identity are you using today
to ask me not to go?
No matter what identity I'm using,
I hope you can reconsider it.
No matter what identity you are using,
my answer today is
I will go.
I know
you are making the right choice.
But...
when I saw you
write your name
on the application form,
I found that I'm a coward.
I fell in love with you
because of your sense of justice.
You are a hero
in my world.
But later, I found
you are everyone's hero.
But now I'm scared.
I don't want you to be a hero anymore.
I just want you to stay by my side,
even though we're not a couple.
I just want you to be safe and healthy
and be an ordinary person.
Shasha,
let me tell you a story.
Once upon a time,
there was an archaeologist.
When he was engaging in archaeological studies,
he discovered a fragment
of a human thighbone
with traces of repair
and healing.
Do you know what it means?
What I'm talking about with you now
is not to go.
I am telling you
why I should go.
Can I continue now?
The femora
are the thighbones of humans.
They support
the entire weight of the human body.
A person with an injured femur
would be unable to walk upright.
And at that time,
a person with an injured femur
couldn't possibly survive on his own.
Coldness,
hunger,
and beasts nearby
could kill him
at any time.
But the femur
the archaeologist found
had traces of healing.
What does it mean?
It means
someone found this wounded person
and took him
to a warm and safe place
to take good care of him
and give him food.
And it lasted for a long time.
Shasha,
people knew
they should help each other
a long time ago.
Otherwise,
maybe today's human civilization
wouldn't have existed.
It might sound a bit exaggerated.
Just take it...
as a man's superman dream.
Hello, Lin Xi.
Are you free tomorrow?
I want to ask you for a favor.
-No.
-Mommy.
You can't go.
There's no room for negotiation on this matter.
I need to grow up and gain more experience.
I said no, and I mean it.
You can't go.
What happened again?
Dad, take a look.
Yicheng, Xixi,
[Outbound application form
of translators for the foreign medical aid team]
since you're here to visit Grandpa,
help me persuade her, okay?
We can't let her go.
Auntie,
Shasha is an adult.
She has her own judgment.
Right?
Xixi.
Have you made up your mind?
Then promise me
you will come back safe and sound.
If you get hurt, even if it's just a scratch,
I'll kick you out of the priority client management department.
And you'll be punished to clean up the warehouse.
Got it?
Mommy,
Lin Xi also participated
in a support project before.
You heard what she said just now.
I'm sure I'll be fine.
Don't worry.
So,
they are the persuaders you invited, right?
Anyway,
I'm gonna make my stance clear today.
No matter who tries to persuade me,
I will resolutely disagree with this.
Shasha,
you are
our only daughter.
Also, you have an allergic constitution
and you've been spoiled by us.
I would be worried
even if it's a business trip
to some remote areas in China,
not to mention going to Africa for support.
If you
insist on going,
don't call me Mom.
Talk properly.
Don't always say hurtful words.
Dad.
Shasha,
you should understand
how your mom feels.
Xixi,
is it because Wei...
Wei Tian also signed up for it?
I know nothing.
You silly girl.
If you're really worried about him,
you should persuade him.
The right thing to do is to ask him not to go.
Why do you want to go with him?
You...
But, Mommy...
Mommy,
please listen to me.
Okay?
When Tian decided to go,
my initial reaction was to stop him.
Because I was scared too.
Just like you,
I told him everything I could.
I used the hard way and the easy way.
But he told me...
Shasha,
people knew
they should help each other
a long time ago.
Otherwise,
maybe today's human civilization
wouldn't have existed.
So helping someone in distress
is the origin of civilization.
Mommy,
I want to go.
I grew up
in affluent living conditions.
I've enjoyed more than others.
So I should give more
back to the world.
This is how civilization
has been passed down.
Good.
This is what a child of the Gao Family should be like.
Mommy.
Lin Xi,
thank you for today.
No need to thank me.
I didn't help much.
How do you plan to persuade Aunt?
I'll call Dad later
and let him persuade her.
Will your dad agree?
I think he will.
Besides, Grandpa agreed just now.
Have you told Wei
that you'll participate in the support project?
It doesn't matter.
Fine.
Your thoughts are the most important.
We should get going.
Be careful.
Bye.
Xiao Yicheng,
if you were Wei
and I wanted to go...
I agree.
Really?
Although I really
don't want you to go,
I know
this is what you want the most.
Right.
Ling Feng will go there too.
So he wants me
to take care of Third Princess.
I asked him to take it to your house directly.
I didn't tell you in advance.
You won't blame me, will you?
Why would I blame you?
Let's go.
Mr. Zhang.
What is it?
Shasha signed up for it.
We still need one person.
I'll go.
Will Xiao Yicheng let you go?
Mr. Zhang, you underestimated him
and me.
But you already
participated in a support project before.
I have another reason.
Would you like to hear it?
Go ahead.
The Consumer Products Expo.
Director Dong said
he hoped I could be a part of the project.
He was just being euphemistic.
Actually,
what he meant is
he's not satisfied with Director Lu.
If we refuse Director Dong,
Director Dong's dignity
will be hurt.
If so, before our competition with Yuyi
officially starts,
we would already
leave a bad impression.
But if we agree,
we'll hurt Director Lu's feelings.
So if I participate in the support project
at this time,
I can have a reason
to stay out of it.
You really have become a big-picture thinker.
Thank you for your compliment.
But it's too late.
Lu has signed up for it
before you.
Director Lu...
has always wanted to be a part
of the Consumer Products Expo project, right?
But he will leave.
Even if I don't tell you, you know
who will be responsible for the Consumer Products Expo project
after he leaves, right?
It's not specially for you.
Wei and the others also have it.
Just now,
you also went to submit the application form, right?
Don't be surprised.
In most cases, your enemies
are the ones who know you the best.
Not enemies,
but opponents.
Don't think
I have made peace with you
just because I accepted your thing.
You'll always be my opponent.
Of course.
But this time,
you are
an honourable opponent.
Lin Xi,
I signed up for this project
with some personal motives as well.
Director Dong kept asking you
to participate in the bidding
for the Consumer Products Expo project.
This means he wants me out, right?
Instead of being disliked
by the client in the end,
I might as well
find myself a way out.
In addition,
even though I've become the director
of the priority client management department,
there are still people who are not convinced.
I want to gain more experience,
so that I can reinforce my position
after I come back.
Otherwise, I might
be replaced by you somehow.
Then you must
come back from there.
Of course.
Our competition is not over yet.
Wait for me to come back
to continue our competition.
♫When I meet the right person♫
Dear Mommy,
please forgive me for being wilful.
♫I'll stop and wait♫
I grew up
under the care of you and Daddy.
I've never experienced
any setback.
♫I'll be willing to give my all♫
When I fell off a cliff several years ago,
for the first time, I realized
♫To look into your gentle eyes♫
what fear is.
[Mommy]
It was Tian
who saved me from the abyss.
♫There are countless possibilities in the future♫
He gave me a sense of security
and courage.
♫I could either be a part of or leave your life♫
Mommy,
maybe he and I
are not suitable for each other in many aspects.
He's rugged, while I'm meticulous.
♫It's my pleasure to share this process♫
He's straightforward, while I'm romantic.
Many people are not optimistic
♫Our story is still considered complete♫
about our relationship,
including me.
So I chose to give up.
But it's really hard.
♫If the fireworks have seen sunset before they disappear♫
When I see him,
my heart would still beat faster.
When he signed up for the support project,
♫There's no reason for love to just be missed out on♫
I still felt worried.
I think
probably I still can't convince myself
♫Regret shouldn't be a lesson learned♫
to leave him for good.
So, Mommy,
I want to give us
one more chance.
♫Can you not be silent?♫
Please support me this time,
okay?
♫Share with me more♫
♫When my ending has to include you♫
♫It's us on this journey♫
♫The best thing I got♫
Xi,
I'm leaving my Third Princess to you.
Don't worry.
I will treat it
like it's my own daughter.
Go.
Why are you dressing
like you are going to fight today?
Are you going to war?
Professor Gao,
Shasha volunteered to go this time.
I'd like to thank you for supporting her.
Mr. Zhang, don't stand on ceremony.
My two granddaughters
have caused Huasheng
a lot of trouble.
No.
This is work.
It's their duty.
Grandpa,
we have also earned many glories
for the company, right?
Yes, both of them are backbones.
Both of them are backbones.
Let's go.
It's so heavy.
I didn't bring any unimportant thing
this time.
What unimportant thing?
Last time, when I went on a business trip with Shasha,
the security inspector thought
her hair curler was a mace
during the security check.
The things I brought this time
were purchased
according to the list you gave me.
Good girl. You're really good.
Since you didn't bring your hair curler,
how will you do hair styling?
What happened to your hair?
I had a haircut.
After having a haircut last night,
her eyes were as red as a rabbit's eyes
when she came home.
Was it necessary?
Of course.
But...
hair can grow back after being cut.
Everyone is here.
Get ready to go.
Okay.
I'll be waiting for you to come back safely.
Take care of yourself.
You too.
Grandpa.
Take care.
I'm leaving.
Take good care of her.
Grandpa,
take care of yourself.
I'll contact you
when I arrive.
Don't worry.
When I came, your mom told me
she wouldn't come.
Okay.
Go.
Grandpa, take care.
Bye.
Go.
Okay, stop.
Did you bring sunscreen?
Yes.
Give me your bag.
I'm gonna put it in the car.
Mom.
I prepared some sunscreen products
with SPF 50,
SPF 20, and SPF 30
for you.
You have an allergic constitution.
Remember to apply sunscreen.
And you have digestive issues.
I prepared the medicine for gastroenteritis
and the immunity-boosting medicine.
See?
The medicine.
Every day, don't forget...
Mom,
the company has prepared them.
And I've brought them with me.
Is your company as thoughtful as me?
Huh?
Auntie, don't worry.
I'll take good care of Shasha.
Wei Tian, listen.
I'm entrusting Shasha
to you intactly.
If anything happens to her,
you'll be held accountable.
Don't worry.
I'll keep her intact.
Wei Tian.
Take it.
Do your best.
Remember what I told you.
You must be careful
with what you eat.
Hurry. Go.
♫The person who walked passed me♫
Alright.
♫I loved you once♫
Hurry.
Go now.
Take care.
Hurry. Go now.
♫The footsteps of memories never stopped making noises♫
Get in the car.
♫Time can't hide it either♫
Goodbye, Auntie.
♫Our hearts are beating fast♫
♫You're like the other shore pulling me to reach it♫
♫Love remembers♫
♫It finds you and I again♫
♫The breeze brushes past the sunset♫
♫You look at me♫
♫Until the shadows melt into the galaxy♫
Young people have to go through hardships
to grow up.
♫I'll hold your hand again♫
Gao Ling,
♫Gazing into each other's eyes♫
you should be proud of Shasha.
♫Happiness is that I now have♫
♫To the future with you♫
Come in.
I've talked to Cheng Yao.
He said he needed time to think about it.
Cheng Yao is young.
But he's very rational
when it comes to important matters.
If he won't come,
it doesn't mean he doesn't care about you.
I understand.
I respect his choice.
Mr. Xiao. Mr. Xiao.
Bad news.
We're one of the trending topics again.
[Three questions for Yuyi: Why are you bidding for the translation supplier of the Consumer Products Expo when such a serious mistake has been made?]
In the process
of developing Icelandic,
Yuyi made a serious mistake.
As the only AI technology company
attending the Consumer Products Expo,
can it still participate in the bidding on time?
Mr. Xiao, Ms. Tong,
the incident
has drawn much public attention on the Internet.
Our colleagues in the PR Department
have temporarily removed the trending topic.
They have also contacted some official accounts
to release some positive articles.
The stock price has been stabilized for now.
But as you can see,
compared to the opening price,
the stock price has dropped significantly.
What about Director Dong?
Jean.
I've talked to Director Dong.
The situation is not very optimistic.
Make an appointment with Director Dong for me.
I'll talk to him.
No need for that.
You guys go back to work.
Dismiss.
Recently, Mr. Xiao has been busy
with the bidding for the Consumer Products Expo project.
I believe you all know
how significant the Consumer Products Expo project is
to Yuyi
after the IPO.
So?
So...
So the shareholders here
want to ask Mr. Xiao
to be responsible for the drop of the stock price this time.
We think
it's you, Xiao Yicheng,
who have made us suffer losses.
You're no longer suitable
for being Yuyi's board chairman
or Chief Technology Officer.
Ying Tao, don't go too far.
Mr. Ying,
do you have evidence for what you said?
Evidence?
It's obvious.
At the crucial moment
of Yuyi's competition with Huasheng,
Yuyi is embroiled in a scandal
related to its translation device.
Only internal company personnel
know this bug.
But you, Xiao Yicheng,
as an insider,
has been preparing a wedding
with an employee of Huasheng.
The situation is clear now.
If you didn't leak the information,
who else could it be?
Mr. Ying,
I'm in charge of the company.
I would never do anything like this
to harm the interests of the company.
I can accept
the company's internal investigation.
But before the investigation results
are announced,
Mr. Ying,
please be careful with your words.
Mr. Xiao,
you're right.
Before the investigation results
are announced,
all of the company's shareholders
can't possibly let someone who may betray the company
occupy this position.
You... can't represent all the shareholders.
Really?
Mr. Zhang.
[Job transfer of Xiao Yicheng, who leaked the company's secret
Joint letter of the board of directors]
See?
[Signatures of the informants: Ying Tao] [Sun Youwei] [Zhu Lin]
This is a joint letter
from all the shareholders with voting rights,
except Ms. Tong.
Mr. Xiao,
if you
take the initiative to apply for a job transfer,
maybe
you can save some dignity.
If you are not convinced,
you can also
convene a temporary board meeting.
But...
it'll just be a procedural formality.
The result won't be changed.
He came prepared.
Xiao, tell me the truth.
Have you ever mentioned this
to anyone else?
Why don't you just ask me
if I told anyone from Huasheng?
I just want to rule out
all the possibilities
and find the person who leaked the information as soon as possible.
Lin Xi knows.
What?
You told her?
No.
When I called Ma,
my cellphone was connected to my car's bluetooth.
But Tong Xin,
I trust her.
Just like you trust me.
Of course I believe Lin Xi
is righteous and she won't disclose the secret.
But is it possible that she spilt the beans
accidentally?
The speaker is innocent, but the listener may have ulterior motives.
The problem we are facing now
is how to fix the bug.
Let's put aside other problems.
But the problem is
Ying Tao is coming at you.
He wants you to step down.
If we don't find the person
who leaked the information as soon as possible,
you will still be denounced
even if you fix the bug.
I know.
Tell them to have a meeting first.
Xiao.
I'll find a way
to continue to persuade Cheng Yao.
He has refused you.
We can only think of other ways.
This is my business.
We worked so hard
to establish Yuyi.
I can't just
let someone else take it away.
How come you haven't gotten off work yet?
Did Xiao Yicheng tell you?
Tell me what?
He called me and said
he'd be downstairs soon. He is on his way here to pick me up.
Something happened to him.
Look.
[Three questions for Yuyi: Why are you bidding for the translation supplier of the Consumer Products Expo when such a serious mistake has been made?]
Now, Yuyi firmly believes
he leaked the information to you.
He's been transferred to another position.
You came to pick me up so early today.
I bought you
your favorite bread.
I can't eat it.
Otherwise, I won't be able to fit into the wedding dress.
You are hardworking.
You won't gain weight.
You're talking about me.
Aren't you the same?
Be careful.
-Why don't we... go home?
-Let's go eat.
-I'm fine with eating.
-I'm fine with going home.
So... are we going to eat or go home?
It's up to you. I'm fine with anything.
Okay.
Don't you have anything... to tell me?
Then let me say it for you.
You want to ask
if I leaked the information
about Yuyi.
No.
If I say...
yes,
what would you think?
You... are not this kind of person.
Xiao Yicheng,
you think too highly of me.
Whether it's eight years ago
or eight years from now,
the woman I like
would never stab me in the back.
Actually, I really want to do that.
If I really did that,
I would be shameless, right?
But you didn't.
I didn't do that
because Grandma Li said
if I stab you in the back,
Huasheng will win,
but I will lose.
Human translation wants to win,
and it will win
fair and square.
Actually, I...
Don't talk. Listen to me first.
You suspect me.
You want to ask me.
I can understand.
Xiao Yicheng,
this bidding
is a test
for you, me,
Huasheng, Yuyi,
human translation, and machine translation.
But
we must not cross the line.
You know what?
This is the first time that I feel so tired.
I'm even thinking
if it could end like this.
When I started my own business,
no matter how tiring or difficult it was,
I knew what my goal was.
But now,
I feel like
everything I've done is in vain.
I feel so helpless.
Go somewhere with me.
Turn right ahead.
Do you remember this place?
I took walks with you here countless times.
Of course I remember.
♫When I meet the right person♫
♫I'll stop and wait♫
♫I'll be willing to give my all♫
♫To look into your gentle eyes♫
This tree is nice.
Okay, this one.
♫There are countless possibilities in the future♫
♫I could either be a part of or leave your life♫
♫It's my pleasure to share this process♫
♫Our story is still considered complete♫
♫Can you not be silent?♫
♫Share with me more♫
♫When my ending has to include you♫
♫It's us on this journey♫
♫The best thing I got♫
Are you sure it's here?
Yes.
This tree looks unique, right?
Where did it go?
Have you found it?
Calm down.
Is this your dream?
You still haven't found it?
It's been so many years.
Can we still find it?
I even managed to get you back,
let alone a box.
Are you sure
this was not buried by someone else?
This is it.
[Lin likes Xiao]
I made a mark.
When did you make a mark
behind my back?
[Lin likes Xiao]
Also,
why is it "Lin likes Xiao",
not "Xiao likes Lin"?
You fell in love with me first, right?
I remember
you came to talk to me first.
You are asking for a beating.
Stop running.
Come on.