[English subtitles are available]
[Our Interpreter]
[Episode 28]
[Love's not Time's fool, though rosy lips and cheeks]
[Within his bending sickle's compass come:]
[Love alters not with his brief hours and weeks,]
[But bears it out even to the edge of doom.]
[William Shakespeare]
These are for the third quarter.
Check them again, okay?
By the way, one more thing.
Record this quarter's
this, and this
into the computer.
Have you heard?
Xi is returning to the priority client management department.
Really?
Where did you get the news?
I got it from a buddy in the translation department.
It's definitely true.
Ask Tian if you don't believe me.
Tian.
Is Xi coming back?
Stop gossiping and get to work.
Her position and conditions
won't change.
Lin Xi is just cooperating with Director Lu.
Later, we'll also cooperate with
the translation department.
Why is your face so red?
Are you not feeling well?
I'm fine.
Isn't this allergy medicine?
Shasha, do you have an allergy?
No.
I just left it here before.
You need more rest.
If you don't rest well,
your immune system will be weakened,
which renders you more prone to allergies.
Give me the rest of your work.
You can rest today.
Really?
Amazing.
Lin Xi is really something.
Yes.
Xi is here. Xi is here.
She's here.
Xi.
What's wrong?
I'll go first.
The administrative manager
sent me a message just now
to say that Meeting Room No. 9 will be
turned into a mother's room.
You made that happen for me, right?
The HR manager
also called me to say
that he would hire an assistant for me.
As for me,
although I wasn't allowed to buy a cat climbing frame,
it has been announced in the company's group chat
that we can apply for
five days of leave per month
to accompany our pets.
I must have saved the galaxy in my past life
to be able to meet such a good boss like you.
Then, today's lunch will be on me.
You can discuss what you want to eat.
What do you want to eat?
Xi.
I'll make a toast to you with water instead of alcohol.
Thanks to our department's achievement today,
we can really hold our heads high.
I'll make a toast to you with juice instead of alcohol.
Lin Xi.
Now that you're in our department,
our department has been
revitalized.
Here's to Lin Xi.
Don't stand on ceremony.
As long as
you work as you did before,
leave the rest
to me.
As for the benefits other departments enjoy,
I'll make sure we have them too.
Great.
Waiter.
May I have the bill?
For your table,
a lady has already paid the bill.
Where is she?
She just left.
Excuse me for a while.
Okay.
Doing good deeds anonymously?
Come and eat with us.
No need.
You're still the same.
You keep your head down whenever you're troubled.
Xi.
I know
it was you who wrote me a recommendation letter.
Why?
Don't tell me you refused to be a regular employee
because you found out I wrote it?
N-No.
Ling Feng told me
you're having a meal with your employees here.
I wanted to thank you.
Actually, I'm the one who should be
thanking you.
Maybe this makes me
sound a little sanctimonious,
but
it was indeed you
who made me realize
that I should respect
everyone's lifestyle
and values.
I've learned that from you.
Xi.
If you need me for anything
in the future,
remember to look for me.
Good luck.
Xi!
I'm sorry
for what happened before.
Mom.
Why is the soup so salty?
Didn't I tell you about it last time?
Your dad made it today.
Yicheng.
About what happened that day,
don't you think
you should give us an explanation?
What's there to explain?
Are you sure that lady is the one?
You should have control over
your emotional relationships.
But there's one thing.
You must be responsible for everything you do.
Got it, Dad.
You two father and son
sure have a good rapport.
Let me be the bad guy then.
Yicheng.
I've seen countless people.
Do you think Lin Xi's family and our family
are compatible?
Why not?
What's incompatible, Mom?
Marriage is a matter that involves two families.
When you become in-laws,
you should see each other frequently.
Lin Xi's father is a businessman.
Is he able to
get along with our family?
Mom.
What era is it now?
Why are you still talking about this?
Besides, it has nothing to do with the two of...
Fine.
Let's talk about Lin Xi then.
I have some friends in the translation industry.
They seem to have some reservations
about Lin Xi.
Dad, Mom,
I don't want to talk about this with you anymore.
Let's eat.
Yicheng.
Your mom is doing this for your own good.
Back then, Grandma also asked you to take the civil service exam
for your own good.
Why didn't you go?
We're talking about you today.
Why are you talking about your dad?
Yicheng.
You're making things difficult for us.
The relationship between the Lin family and Professor Gao
seems to be estranged.
If you're with her,
our relationship with Professor Gao
will become tricky.
Dad.
I want to marry Lin Xi,
not Professor Gao's family.
If you can get along, that's great.
If you can't get along, then you don't have to hang out all the time.
Anyway,
Dad, Mom,
I'm sure about Lin Xi.
If you accept her,
I'll be happy, of course.
If you don't accept her...
Why?
Are you going to
cut ties with us?
What are you talking about?
What I mean is
if you don't accept her,
you don't have to associate with her
and see her.
I have work to do in the company.
I have to go.
So,
no matter how much we oppose it,
you still have to marry her?
Yes.
See?
I told you so.
What do you mean?
I've never seen him
so serious before.
What do you mean?
We were just
trying to see if you're sincere or not.
After all, Lin Xi
is Professor Gao's granddaughter.
If
you treat her badly,
how could we be accountable to
Professor Gao?
Yeah.
We just wanted to test you.
Dad, Mom.
How old
are you two?
How could you put on a show for me?
All right.
Go back first.
We'll go to the hospital
to see Professor Gao tomorrow.
By then,
introduce Lin Xi
to us properly.
You are not young anymore.
You should settle down soon.
Bye.
Dad, have some water.
Wenli was going to come.
But the school
suddenly scheduled
an online class for her.
She had to stay
to teach the kids.
But she told me
that I must send you
home safely.
Yes, classes are more important.
Is Wenli
still teaching English in an elementary school?
Yes.
The Ministry of Education
wanted to transfer her
to teach English in a high school.
But Wenli said
that English should start with little kids.
It's very important to lay the proper foundation for little kids.
So,
over the past 20 years,
she has been teaching English in elementary schools.
Good. Very good.
Wenli
has always been outstanding since she was little.
If Wenli knows of
your recognition of her,
she will be very happy.
Dad.
The discharge procedures are done.
The taxi I called has also arrived.
It's hard for them to park in front of the hospital.
Let's hurry up and go.
Gao Ling.
Let me drive Dad home.
Cancel the taxi.
Well...
Let Dayong give me a ride.
Okay.
I'll let the driver know.
Dad, have some water.
Professor Gao.
Hello.
Xixi.
You are all here.
Professor Gao.
Are you discharged from the hospital?
The doctor has given me a thorough examination.
I'm fine now.
I just have to go back and rest.
Mr. Lin.
At the dinner that day,
I didn't have the chance
to say hello to you properly.
Same here.
Sorry about that.
I didn't expect
us to be so fated
with Professor Gao's family.
We're even
becoming one family.
Great!
These two young people
are fated.
Xixi.
Let’s send your grandpa back.
How about
Xiao Yicheng and I send Grandpa home?
Yes.
Let us send him home instead.
No.
I must have Xi
and her boyfriend send me home.
Okay.
Let's go.
You're in a good mood.
Mr. Lin.
I wonder if you are free today.
Let's have dinner together.
I booked a vegetarian restaurant.
Yicheng told me
that your wife has vegetarian food every 1st and 15th
of the month.
Today happens to be the 15th.
Ask your wife to join us.
Thank you,
but I don't think it's necessary.
It so happens that Yicheng and Xixi
will join us after
sending Professor Gao home.
Yes.
All right then.
I'll call her and ask her
to go there directly.
Let's go.
What's up?
Lin.
Previously,
we were both abroad.
We didn't know much about
Yicheng's life in China.
I didn't know they were already
acquainted.
I'm really sorry.
Me too.
At Professor Gao's birthday party,
my attitude was
a little too aggressive.
Please don't
take it to heart.
-It's fine.
Let me apologize to you.
I'll drink it up.
Xiao.
Now that you're doing this,
I feel embarrassed.
I have to do it too then.
Come on, let's drink together.
Come on.
Let's drink.
Okay. Leave everything in the wine.
Xixi's mom, let’s eat.
-Okay.
-Let them drink.
Let's eat.
Mom.
Here's some orange juice.
Let's get down to business.
Auntie.
Here's some orange juice.
Thank you.
Xixi's mom.
Xixi's dad.
I wonder if
you have any considerations
about the kids' wedding?
Wedding?
Yes.
Look at how in love
they are.
It's time
to talk about marriage.
For these things,
the groom's side
have to be prepared in advance.
Yes.
I wonder if you have any requests
and rules.
If you don't have any,
we have a few plans.
Right, Xiao?
Last year, when we were in France,
we saw many young couples
taking wedding photos there.
It was quite interesting.
Yes.
They took wedding photos
while traveling.
Yes.
It so happens that Xixi knows French too.
Really?
Wait, wait.
It's not that we don't have rules.
Well...
Here's the thing.
Why are we already
discussing the wedding
and wedding photoshoot?
Isn't it too early?
Lin.
What do you think?
Just share them with us.
Here's what I think.
Well,
Yicheng and Xixi
are in love indeed.
But
they just got together
after all.
I think
we should let them
take some time
to get to know each other.
Wait.
Haven't Yicheng and Xixi
been dating since they were in college?
Yes, Uncle.
Xixi and I
were together when we were in college.
We've known each other for more than ten years.
So, in her college years,
you were the one
who made our Xixi cry?
That even happened?
I don't know.
All right.
Let bygones be bygones.
It's fate that the two kids are together
now.
Uncle.
No matter what,
I will prove my sincerity to her
with my actions.
Lin.
I actually really want to go to France.
Mom, let's find a chance to travel and have fun there.
That's right.
I really want to
go to the museums in France.
They're really great.
I really want to go there.
Fine, fine, fine.
You two
can make the decision for this.
I'll just go along with everything.
That's great.
By then,
I'll be the tour guide for Xixi's Mom.
Thank you so much.
I'll be the photographer of the ladies.
I will
be your assistant then.
Screw you!
Dad.
Stop reading the newspaper. You just got discharged.
Have more of this nutritious soup.
Here.
Shasha.
Why have you lost weight
in just a few days that I didn't see you?
I didn't, Grandpa.
Gao Ling.
Get some more shrimp
for her to eat more.
Grandpa.
I’m full.
You guys continue.
I'm leaving.
What's wrong with Shasha?
What's wrong with you guys?
Dad.
Shasha has a boyfriend.
I don't think they're compatible.
They are completely
on different wavelengths.
A few days ago,
Shasha went to find this guy.
In the end,
her photodermatitis flared up.
She has allergic rashes all over her body.
She's been taking
allergy medicine this whole time.
You know she has a weak physique.
We've been very careful since she was little.
How many years has it been?
How could she have such a severe allergic reaction?
Shasha has grown up.
She should be able to
have the final say in her own business.
Dad, you're right.
But...
I feel sorry for my child.
Well,
she's been defending that boy
and has always been stubborn with me.
Has he ever cared about her?
She's this sunburnt,
yet I haven't seen this boy
come visit her
and care about her.
Let me know if there's any problem.
Okay, Tian.
Tian.
I feel a little unwell.
Maybe I’m really having an allergic reaction.
Wang Qiang.
I need to head out for something urgent.
Text me or send me a WeChat message
if you have any questions, okay?
Okay, Tian.
Wei Tian.
I was just looking for you.
Director Lu.
Yuyi
suddenly added a roadshow document.
It has to be translated by tonight.
We need it tomorrow.
It's urgent and there are few people who can deal with it.
To avoid mistakes,
you'll have to do it personally.
By tonight?
It's a difficult time.
I'm sorry you have to make sacrifices.
Auntie Wang!
Who is it?
The person who delivers the medicine.
Where is he?
He left.
He left?
Yes.
He sent it here.
And he's now making a delivery to his next customer.
The courier
needs to work.
Courier?
Urgent delivery.
Hello, Tian.
Shasha.
Have you received the medicine I bought?
Sorry.
A last-minute work thing came up today.
I can't go there.
It's okay. I'll let you get back to work.
I understand.
Bye.
You eat it too.
The Xiao family has a rule.
Women eat a strawberry's tip.
Men eat a strawberry's bottom.
I've eaten the bottoms.
What other rules do you have?
The Xiao family has another rule.
That is,
when women feel uncomfortable,
men should give them a massage.
Comfortable.
Harder.
Okay.
Wait.
Massage gun.
How do you feel?
Are you taking revenge?
It's just the 2nd lowest speed.
It doesn't hurt.
It doesn't hurt?
No.
Give it to me. You try it.
Here.
How could you say it doesn't hurt?
Does it hurt?
Comfortable.
Comfortable?
Comfortable. It doesn't hurt.
Tell me if it hurts.
Don't keep it to yourself.
It really doesn't hurt.
Really?
The highest speed.
Does it hurt?
No.
No?
It hurts.
You want to find another boyfriend?
No. Of course not.
No.
What's wrong?
Well.
I can't move.
I feel numb there.
Here?
Yes.
It's where I pointed the massage gun at.
Did I hurt you?
I don't know.
Try lifting your head up.
No.
I dare not.
I can't move now.
Let's go to the hospital.
Come on.
No, well...
Three, two, one. Get up.
It hurts.
Why did you use so much strength?
He said he didn't feel anything.
So I went harder.
Young lady,
what you did
created negative pressure
and caused his blood vessels to burst under his skin,
which left a bruise on his skin.
It's very dangerous.
It's irresponsible to do so.
Especially
on both sides of the carotid arteries.
There are the carotid sinuses.
If you create negative pressure
on this area,
it will cause a lack of blood,
a lack of oxygen,
and even cardiac arrest.
Doctor, here's the thing.
This was caused by a massage gun.
Stop talking.
I know.
Doctor, he's hurting.
What's the treatment?
I'll prescribe some patches
for you.
Use them for a few days, and they'll work.
Wait here.
I'll get the patches for you.
Thank you.
Come on. Seriously?
Does it still hurt?
Yes.
What should I do?
How about I ask the doctor
to prescribe some painkillers for you?
No need for painkillers.
But I have a way
to stop the pain.
It really hurts.
Why didn't you listen to me?
Don't blame me for nagging.
Impulse is like a devil.
You must be careful.
Yes, doctor.
How many patches
should he use every day?
How long should he wear it each time?
One in the morning and one at night.
Wear it for 6 hours each time.
Okay.
Don't shower
after you go home today.
Thank you.
Okay.
Remember to come back for a recheck 3 days later.
Let's go together.
My destination is not on your way.
You're not going to the company?
I have an appointment with the legal team
to talk about our listing contract.
Bye.
Maomao, is Mr. Xiao
going on a business trip next week?
No.
He has several meetings next week.
Okay.
What a coincidence!
Let's have dinner together.
Sure.
I still have a meeting
with Maomao.
Next time.
[Chief Operating Officer]
Where's Ms. Tong?
She left after the meeting.
Thank you.
How is the English website project
going?
I archived
all the rarely-used characters.
I promise nothing will go wrong.
Okay.
What about you?
I copied the content
on other listed companies' websites.
It can be used for reference
and help us avoid some mistakes.
Good job.
Mr. Xu,
what about you?
Lin Xi.
Come and take a look.
Look.
What do you think of this paragraph?
Mr. Xu,
you are our rock.
Your translation
achieves faithfulness, expressiveness, and elegance indeed.
Alright.
Take a rest.
I want to buy a drink.
Do you want?
No, thanks.
Ling Feng, go with Meihua.
It's not convenient for her.
Okay.
I'll take a walk too.
I feel uncomfortable after sitting for too long.
Lin Xi,
you should be careful too.
Don't worry.
Hello, Mr. Xiao.
Why are you here?
You must be hungry.
I bought you some food.
Eat it while it's hot.
Here, try it.
Is it tasty?
Not bad.
Try it.
You're so cunning.
Mr. Xiao from Yuyi.
Hello, Mr. Xu.
Mr. Xiao is here to check on our progress.
Yes.
I told him
we will finish it on time.
Wait.
[Pantry]
Mr. Xiao,
are you here to visit us
and bring us some midnight snacks
as our client?
Yes.
I bought you some food.
Come.
Thank you, then.
I've worked for so many years.
I've never met
such a considerate client before.
Mr. Xiao, please come often.
As long as
I don't disturb your work.
By the way, Mr. Xiao,
you are young, successful,
and handsome.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Meihua.
You shouldn't be a translator.
You should be a neighborhood committee worker.
Mr. Xiao,
please don't mind.
Meihua meant no offence.
It's okay.
Actually,
I already have a girlfriend.
You have a girlfriend?
Let me tell you.
Since Huasheng
started cooperating with Yuyi,
my female colleagues
have kept telling me
that you're a single and rich man.
I didn't expect you to have a girlfriend.
Well,
on behalf of
the female staff of Huasheng,
may I ask
what she looks like?
She
is pretty.
She's independent
and capable,
but a little violent.
But most importantly, she's pretty.
How pretty?
Do you have a photo?
Meihua,
try this.
This is their specialty.
These snacks
are Lin Xi's favorites.
Mr. Xiao, good choice.
Mr. Xiao.
Show us the photo.
What photo?
The photo of his girlfriend.
Mr. Xiao said his girlfriend
is pretty.
By the way, Mr. Xiao,
Lin Xi is still single.
Is there
any good man around you?
Introduce one to her.
Sure.
I wonder what Ms. Lin
looks for in a man.
I like men who don't talk much.
I can answer this.
Although I don't know
what Xi wants in a man,
I know
what she doesn't want.
Tell us.
She doesn't like Mr. Han from Han's Technology,
who always wears fancy and colorful clothes.
She doesn't like Bonnie from the interpretation department,
who enjoys making inspirational speeches.
She doesn't like Secretary Zhou from the Translator Association of China,
who's too smooth.
And...
What?
There are so many young men
who fell for Lin Xi?
Mr. Xu,
you're not very observant.
It was quite a spectacle
when they pursued Xi back then.
They did everything but use drones to say "I love you."
Try this.
Even food can't make you shut up.
It seems
Ms. Lin is very popular.
Mr. Xiao,
let me show you
our progress.
Come with me and take a look.
Ms. Lin.
Do you think
it's good to translate this sentence
like this?
It seems you had a great love life
during the years
I was away.
I think your translation
is not accurate enough.
Why aren't you leaving?
I need to take my girlfriend home.
Now your girlfriend orders you
to go back first.
Why can't you tell them I'm your boyfriend?
Is it better to translate it this way?
Mr. Xiao and Lin Xi
have a serious attitude towards work.
We should learn from them.
Especially you, young man.
I see it. I'll keep it in mind.
Have you noticed
they seem a good match?
Cheng.
It's late.
Why haven't you got off work?
He's quite something.
He sent a resignation letter to Lu Keli.
Then, Mr. Zhang asked him
to help us.
Great.
There'll be someone playing PUBG with me
at lunch breaks.
Cheng Yao, are you good at it?
Wait a minute.
Are you two
showing affection in front of them?
Showing affection?
They
stay together every day.
He's even here to accompany her when she's working overtime.
Xiao Yicheng, let me tell you.
As your friend, I have to remind you.
Men shouldn't be too clingy.
What's going on?
Did I say the wrong thing?
I shouldn't have let you come here.
Now we got a problem.
Well, let me put this here.
See you tomorrow.
I'm really sorry
for hiding it from you.
Let me introduce myself formally.
I'm
Lin Xi's boyfriend,
Xiao Yicheng.
Nice to meet you.
Mr. Xiao,
you're really Xi's boyfriend?
It's not April Fool's Day today, right?
Pretty?
You did a nice job
keeping it a secret.
You hid it from us for such a long time.
That's right.
If Cheng Yao hadn't let it slip,
we wouldn't have known it.
Huasheng and Yuyi
are still cooperating,
so...
I'm old.
I have a bad memory.
What were you talking about?
You...
Why can't I remember anything?
My mind is foggy.
I've been listening to music.
Although I heard everything,
I promise
I won't tell anyone.
Well,
let's go home.
Xiao Yicheng, let's talk.
If it's about Tong Xin,
we don't need to talk.
She's been trying to avoid me lately.
Is there really no other way?
Cheng Yao,
are you serious about Tong Xin?
Of course.
You answered too fast.
Love is not a joke.
Think it through first.
Cheng Yao.
Tong Xin is several years older than you.
She had a marriage
and has a child.
Are you sure you aren't acting on impulse?
Xiao Yicheng.
Although Tong Xin
is older than me,
she got divorced
with a child,
and our life experiences
are completely different,
I still fell in love with her.
Because of that, I'm perfectly sure
about my determination.
I see.
As Tong Xin's friend,
I really hope
she can find a good man.
But her heart was broken.
For her, starting a new relationship
is harder than you imagine.
I understand.
But I need
your help.
Since she's the one for you,
as your friends,
we definitely support you.
But remember one thing.
Don't
hurt Tong Xin.
Don't worry.
Tong Xin, let's talk.
-I…
-You're
done with work today.
The video conference
originally scheduled for tonight
has been reschedule for tomorrow morning.
Peter is staying
at his classmate's place tonight.
You don't need to help him with his homework.
So...
Give me one hour,
okay?
♫It floats in the air and drifts away♫
♫We look for the farthest anticipation♫
♫If a storm shakes us♫
♫Remember our original direction♫
♫Just like a match♫
♫Can also light a big fire♫
♫I chase the future and never mend my ways♫
♫Even if I fall onto the horizon♫
♫I'll bloom on this land♫
What do you want to say?
♫If the flame in my heart never goes out♫
I have a friend
who has some relationship issues.
I want to hear your advice.
♫It's not a failure even if I get hurt♫
Go ahead.
♫If a dream is a sin♫
♫I'm willing to spend my life with it♫
He fell in love
with a girl older than him.
But that girl
♫I'll continue being stubborn♫
seems to have lots of uncertainties
and hesitations in mind.
He wants to pursue her bravely.
But she
has been avoiding him.
♫I wait for the day I can fly onto the stage♫
Can you tell me
what he should do
♫And prove my existence with light♫
to get a response?
♫Even the smallest dust♫
♫Can win your favor♫
If you ask my advice,
♫I wait for everything to be settled♫
here's my answer.
♫When love proves my existence♫
Since the girl chose to refuse,
she must have her own concerns.
♫Even the most ordinary dust♫
I advise your friend not to be too persistent.
♫Has a shining halo♫
What if she's the one
for my friend?
Your friend will be disappointed.
Tong Xin.
Cheng Yao.
I know
the man you're talking about is you.
The woman in the story is me.
Then my answer is
I don't like you.
I've been avoiding you, indeed.
Because you have
bothered me.
Do you understand?
I don't understand.
Why don't you like him?
When you like someone, there needs to be a reason.
But when you don't like someone, there doesn't.
Then tell me
what you want in a man.
Let me ask you a different way.
You liked Lin Xi, right?
You tossed and turned thinking about her, right?
But how long did your feelings for her last?
Three weeks?
Three months?
Cheng Yao.
I don't know why you
moved on from Lin Xi to me.
I only see
immaturity
in you.
Your thoughts are hard to follow, and you're changeable.
And this
is what I fear the most.
Do you understand?
Tong Xin,
you can't
deny my feelings for you
just because I liked someone else.
I can tell you clearly
I like you now.
What about the next moment?
Cheng Yao, I have no time
or energy
to have a relationship with you
which won't last.
Please leave me alone.
Tong Xin.
I'll prove it to you.