[English subtitles are available]
[I Belonged To Your World]
Girls, it's the end of the semester.
Why are you all not interested in fighting with the exams?
Have you memorized English?
No.
Have you written your paper?
The High Priestess upright.
I have zero chance of falling in love this month.
Leaving everything untill the last moment.
As expected, boss is indeed the boss.
You're memorizing the script?
What a time it is!
Xie Jiajia.
You really can't do anything.
No.1 in the internal scroll.
Girls,
tonight at seven,
there will be the first performance of me and Lu Xiao
since we joined the drama club.
If you have money, please support us.
If you have no money, please come on time.
Are you rebelling?
Don't you know?
This year's thesis review is particularly strict.
Who said that?
Don't you read WeChat group?
What does the school want to do?
It means if you can't pass.
You'll be juniors next year.
Remember to come tonight.
We're busy.
[ Episode 13 He makes it snow in the south]
Qi Yue, it's a good show.
You only have four actors and four audiences.
Why don't you just lei it go and play the Werewolves of Miller's Hollow?
Four audiences are still audiences.
I have an idea.
Maybe we can change our minds.
How?
Audience is part of the performance.
But there's no rule
the audience must be present.
What do you mean?
It means
the audience can see you
through the screen.
Where did you get the camera?
You can record it with your phone.
Yes, it's like filming a movie.
I see.
If we make a short video,
we must have a lot of views.
If it's a short video,
it cannot be called as a stage play.
You don't understand.
Good things should integrate with each other.
This is called Front Art.
You'll know it when you get old.
Front art.
Front art?
Sounds cool.
Let's stop talking about this.
Let's go along with the recording.
You two stay over there.
You follow me.
Let's go.
You two take close shots.
You take full shots with me, okay?
Juliet and Romeo.
Are you ready?
OK. Three, two, one. Action.
Romeo.
Do you have anything to say to Juliet?
As that vast shore washed with the farthest sea,
I should adventure for such merchandise.
Qi Yue, I...
The line is wrong.
It's Juliet, not Qi Yue.
Professor.
I'm glad you're here.
The nation's top physics competitors
will all come to the winter camp.
The esteemed scholars
you see in magazines
will also be there.
You're the only one from Qingnan University.
Professor, I'm here to submit my thesis.
Professor, someone is looking for you.
Think about it.
Have you revised your thesis?
Yes.
Let me see.
What's wrong?
What did the professor say?
Is there any drama to see?
No.
I finally know
why Qi Yue can't burn you.
She was hurt.
She had a burn?
Yes, the burn was very serious.
She burnt here.
I'm going to the infirmary.
Give me two minutes.
Watch carefully.
You're now the battery.
Qi Yue is on this end.
So you have to
run towards her
swiftly.
Understand?
Yes.
I have to confess my love to her swiftly.
But there's a problem.
If the coil
can't maintain between three millimetres,
the experiment didn't work.
I'll go to the infirmary to find her.
Qi Yue is actually very timid.
You just need to take her to the haunted house
and stand in front of her to protect her.
Then you can confess your love to her.
Don't be afraid. I'm here.
Don't be afraid.
[No Internet]
That's it.
You could at least scream one time.
We ghosts have performance assessment.
Give me the mask.
What are you doing?
Wait for me.
What should I do now?
Why don't you go home?
Let go.
You have to do this.
When the players are chatting,
do the unexpected, attack the unprepared.
It's okay.
Go back and practice more.
Let's go.
Don't worry. We're experienced.
We'll pretend it's a broadcasting failure.
You come in through the right entrance.
And we'll play your video.
Is this the process?
How do you know that?
To be honest,
you are the third person
confessing love here this month.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Where have you been?
It's been too long.
What's wrong?
I can't stand men using this trick
that can be seen at one glance.
I can't believe there're people like it.
I should give up this plan.
[I’m really sorry. Please discontinue the plan we discussed earlier.]
They're so efficient.
Is it broken?
Why is it dark?
What happened?
I'll go and ask.
Don't move.
Sit down. I'll go.
Why are you going?
You look so easy to be perfunctory.
I know this kind of trick.
This is so scary.
What's wrong?
What happened?
What should we do now?
We've bought tickets.
Should we just sit here and wait?
I'm really sorry.
Don't say sorry to me.
Tell me the solution.
Our technicians are checking the malfunction.
I don't want to hear this.
Just tell me how long we have to wait.
It's hard to say.
-Why... -Qi Yue.
Why don't you go back to your seat first?
There might be a surprise later.
I'm afraid not.
What?
The screening device is broken now.
Moisture from rain and snow
can form condensation or water droplets
and cause airflow through the fibre air filter.
Speak like a normal person.
I'll take a look.
Okay, this way please.
[Qingnan University]
How's the date going?
Any surprise?
Lots of surprises.
Tell me.
We went for a movie.
The screen in the cinema broke down.
And then?
Then Lu Xiao went to fix the screen.
What?
I couldn't wait so I came back.
What about now?
Now?
My heart is more cold than the snow in the South Pole.
I have something else to do.
I have to go.
All beings grow. The only way is to reproduce descendants.
What are you talking about?
Look.
Baoguo finally met its girlfriend.
Even animals need love.
No, no, no.
Only hypocritical humans beautify love.
In fact, the essence of all living things
is to reproduce descendants.
Why are you so not romantic?
No, Qi Yue,
I should have enlightened you earlier.
But since you're so obsessed with Lu Xiao,
I couldn't bear
to expose the pink bubbles on your head.
According to your words,
did I pursue Lu Xiao
just to have a baby with him?
It seems like that.
I don't know what you think.
But I bet
that's what boys think.
Impossible. Lu Xiao is not that kind of person.
Wait and see.
[ntelligent Engineering Institute ]
Isn't this Qi Yue's dorm?
Why did you bring me here?
After thinking about a lot of things,
I'd better personally help you
in case anything goes wrong.
Have you watched the movie "Love Actually"?
Qi Yue likes it the most.
Her dream is to hear you confess your love
on a snowy day.
I've already find the spot
for you.
It's the best observation spot.
She can see it directly from the balcony.
But even with this,
it won't really snow.
Time is limited.
It's too late for you to show off.
The artificial snow I bought
is still useful.
This is "on".
This is "add more".
This is "off".
You can only succeed. You can't fail.
Good luck.
I'm leaving.
[Qi Yue, come to the balcony. I have something to tell you.]
See? Lu Xiao is going to confess to me.
What do you want to say to me?
That's what I want to say to you.
Will you?
[Do it]
That's what boys think.
You dog.
[Do it]
[Will you be my girlfriend?]
Look how romantic he is.
Look at you.
Romantic? So childish.
You just don't love me.
What should I do?
Chinese New Year is coming.
Eat something nice then.
Mom,
are you shopping
or running?
Have you never heard of running because of getting mad?
Am I supposed to wander around when I'm angry?
I know you're angry.
Because of your so-called sense of ritual.
I think you should be straightforward
and knock Lu Xiao down.
You have experience.
No.
I've taken the initiative so many times.
Raw but delicious sunflower seeds.
Raw but delicious with the original flavor.
What are you doing?
Turn off the phone.
Since my hint doesn't work,
I'll start a cold war.
You and your affected style...
Listen.
If you bully Lu Xiao like this,
you'll mess up the sure thing.
Trust me.
You...
What are you doing?
Happy winter vacation is about to begin.
What is the necessary connection
between happy winter vacation life
and you becoming a pig?
You don't understand.
This is called a sense of ritual for girls.
Let's go, son.
Coming.
Madam,
on the first day of the winter vacation,
we still have to work hard. Don't slack off.
Get...
Up.
It's okay. It's not important.
Do you remember our agreement?
Get up.
Get up early, learning and pursuing Lu Xiao.
Are you still ignoring me?
There's a limit to my patience.
Don't force me to be rough.
Qi Yue.
Can you just sit there?
You're in my way.
Then I've achieved my goal.
Do you remember the mission today?
What mission?
College English Test Band 4, philosophy theory.
Contact Lu Xiao.
There's no rush for learning College English Test Band 4.
Philosophy is not needed.
Contacting Lu Xiao needs a right time.
It's winter break.
Even the iron man needs rest too.
In that case,
I'll have to be tough.
What's going on?
Electrostatic adsorption device.
Lu Xiao taught me.
You two.
One of you kicked down the ladder,
and the other burnt the bridge.
Are you the ladder or the bridge?
I...
You can't lie down even in winter vacation.
Turn off the TV.
Who cares?
It's time to eat. Stop playing with your phone.
You eat first.
I'm about to make a double kill.
Don't move! There's explosives!
I mean the people in the game.
That one is poisonous. Are you stupid?
Let's surround them from behind.
The people across me are dead.
All their organs are out.
Mom.
Can we eat in peace?
What's wrong, my dear son?
You look pale.
Are you feeling unwell?
Someone is knocking. I'll get it.
Lu Xiao, why are you here?
The topic for the next semester's thesis...
Lu...
Game is good and food is delicious.
Who cares about him?
You're not the mysterious Qi Yue.
You're Qi Yue, the movie queen.
Why hasn't he come to me yet?
You can throw away a big bag of trash,
but you have to divide it into a dozen small bags.
It's everyone's responsibility to classify the garbage.
Aren't you afraid of some neighborhood aunts?
You guys are taking a walk?
Oh my, Ms. Jin.
We're going to throw out the trash.
This is other waste.
This is kitchen waste.
We will perfectly classify them
and put them into the garbage basket.
Ms. Jin, take care.
Okay.
You can throw away the trash alone.
Why do you have to drag me along?
To wait for this moment to humiliate me?
If it wasn't for throwing the trash,
would you stay home all the time during the winter break?
You don't understand.
I'm happy to be fat nerd during this long and fun vacation.
What if we meet Lu Xiao?
Are you not going to clean yourself up?
What's wrong with me now?
Besides,
if he really likes me,
he will like my true self.
Besides,
it's been three days.
He hasn't contacted me.
I set up the mysterious persona first.
Mysterious persona?
You're right.
If I were you,
I would ignore Lu Xiao.
Why isn't it here yet? It's so far.
There's only one garbage station in our residential compound.
Did you implement
the policy of garbage classification properly?
It's the wrong way. Left.
No, right.
Are you sure there is a trash station here?
Of course.
Turn right at this intersection.
Hurry up.
Qi Shuo.
What?
Turn right here.
Qi Shuo.
Forget it.
I'll definitely throw it away tomorrow.
Juliet.
Look thou but sweet.
And I am proof against their enmity.
I wouldn't have them see you for the world.
Romeo.
Juliet!
As that vast shore wash'd with the farthest sea,
I would adventure
for such merchandise.
Juliet.
Whispered!
The yonder window breaks what is light?
It is the east,
and Juliet is the sun!
Romeo.
She speaks.
O, speak again, bright angel!
I can't control the weather,
but I can make snow just for you.
Why are you here?
π bond is you
I'm the б bond.
Many people say it's impossible between them.
But I believe there's hyperconjugation in this world.
We are too small in this universe.
Just like the dusts on the white board.
They're Invisible to the naked eyes.
They're insignificant.
But they can still be together.
I won't let our relationship
become like the Lenz's law.
Lai ju qu liu (An alternative expression for the Lenz's law in Chinese).
Since you came into my heart,
I won't let you leave.
Although
I don't quite understand your words.
[Qi Yue, will you be my girlfriend?]
I understand this one.
Qi Yue,
will you be my girlfriend?
♫The past is like an impassable gully♫
♫I'll never have a chance to feel your tenderness♫
♫I remember the day when you turned around and kept going♫
♫You didn't stop or look back♫
♫So I saw you♫
♫Passing through my world and taking away warm colors♫
♫The wind chases the clouds and surrounds you♫
♫Only the barren wilderness is left♫
♫You left me alone♫
♫But then I tried to travel♫
♫All over the world. But you never passed by♫
♫Maybe we are like ships that pass in the night♫
♫This love has a bad ending♫
♫We missed each other naturally♫
Well.
They two just started dating,
They've been staying together until midnight.
Mother wasn't home.
And she left her son
at home alone.
Oh no.
My waist.
Oh no!
I can't move.
Am I going to lie here all night?
I wish Qi Yue were home.
Qi Yue.
Why are you home?
The law says I can't be home at this hour?
Shouldn't you two
linger with each other now?
No, no lingering.
We were socially dead.
Socially dead?
Help me up.
Hold me.
One, two, go.
You're old.
Don't force yourself if you can't handle it.
Tell me how did you two socially dead?
I want to hear it.
It's a long story.
It's on your mouth.
Do you want more?
I'll buy you more if you want.
Sure.
What?
It is a behavior in love.
A couple should feed each other ice cream.
But
I'm allergic to mango.
It's totally different from what I thought.
Qi Yue,
What are we going to do?
Follow them.
Put your hands up here.
You seem like knowing everything.
What are you two doing?
Are you trying to ruin the place?
It hurts.
You don't sound like
a human.
What should I do?
Dating is so hard.
It's not a big deal.
Ddating is
two people doing boring things together.
He always asked me what we would do next.
I'm not The Book of Answers
He respected you.
You should guide him.
How?
Tell Lu Xiao what you really want to do.
So that he can fully understand you.
What I really want to do...
Yes.
Dating
is to share important things
with each other.
Something important?
Yes.
I understand.
Where are you going?
Get changed.
I'll listen to you.
Do what I really want
and focus on important things.
Thank you, my good son.
She is my blood mom.
I'm her blood son.
[Are things getting better or]
[worse?]
[I Belonged To Your World]
[I always remember that your wish is to see the snow.]
Romeo, how camest thou hither, tell me, and wherefore?
As that vast shore washed with the farthest sea,
I should adventure
for such merchandise.
I've never seen snow
in my life before.
Qi Yue, there's no such line.
Do you know what my dream is?
What is it?
Have you seen the movie "Love Actually"?
Yes.
There's a classic part.
On a snowy day,
a boy used a lot of cards and confessed to a girl.
That's my dream.
I see.
Your dream is to see the snow.
What are you doing?
I'm snowing for you.