[English subtitles are available]
[I Belonged To Your World]
[Your Honey Is My Poison—Episode 7]
[Introduction to Philosophy]
Why are you here?
If the professor sees us,
both of us will suffer a lot.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Me, too.
Bro, I don't have that special hobby.
I'm going to buy some food.
I have some.
I'll take a look in the mirror. Okay?
A spoon can reflect light. Use it as a mirror.
No. Something's wrong.
I'm here to return the clothes.
Thank you for yesterday.
Strawberry-flavored lipstick.
It should be yours.
It is indeed mine.
Thank you.
No.
Am I in the ancient times?
It's just a small distance.
You still treat me as a conveyor.
Tell him face to face.
I'm going to ask the professor a question.
Why are you blushing?
Blushing?
The air conditioner.
It's too hot. You didn't turn it on, right?
Confess and I'll be lenient. If not, I'll punish you severely.
What happened between you two?
Tell me.
Nothing.
If nothing happened, I'll change my surname to yours.
Well, my surname is also Qi.
Aren't you going to tell me?
I'll go to Lu Xiao.
Tell me.
What's wrong with the lipstick?
Strawberry-flavored lipstick.
So,
Lu Xiao saved you yesterday.
But how did he know
your lipstick
was strawberry-flavored?
No girls would use a five-spices-flavored lipstick.
That's not what I meant.
I mean,
when you two were alone,
did you have any
intimate physical contact?
For example,
a kiss?
How is that possible?
Hush.
I think
Just like this basketball, Lu Xiao should be very nervous now,
with his heart beating so fast like it.
And then?
Then...
Then you should
always show up by his side,
and make him notice
your existence more.
Stop spinning it.
It makes me dizzy when I see it.
Yes.
When he feels dizzy,
make him fall in love with you.
Not bad, son.
You know lots of tricks.
What should I do next?
Next?
You should figure it out yourself next.
I can't teach you how to date for every detail.
It's getting late.
I'm going back for nap at noon.
Bye.
Qi Yue.
I sent you WeChat messages.
Why didn't you reply?
Is there any misunderstanding between us?
Zhaoyang.
For words like these,
even in the oldest TV drama,
people wouldn't say them.
Just think about
what you did.
What did I do?
Nothing.
Good luck.
After all, only you
can represent the school to participate in the competition.
Good, Xie Jiajia.
Impressive.
You found a nice place.
This is the night life college students should have.
Don't be angry, boss.
You're the center of the get-together today.
Why me?
We thought about it.
All in all,
you
are the only person in Room 402 who may get a boyfriend.
Wait.
I have a question.
Why must Qi Yue chase Lu Xiao and make him become her boyfriend,
apart from the betting?
Actually,
here's the thing.
Originally,
I also thought Lu Xiao
was the one I'm destined to be with.
But now I find that
though he is good,
I'm not bad.
As you can see,
he can really make me feel safe.
Qi Yue.
Your mobile phone.
Open your WeChat and give it to me.
What do you want to do?
[Post Text]
To lure the fish into the bait.
To test if the fish is asleep.
With all our courage,
it should be enough to deal with this world.
Make our voice heard by the world.
I dare not do it alone.
Where did you copy
such rhetorical words?
The benchmark of dating for science boys.
Wang Xiaobo's quotes.
You don't understand.
Lu Xiao must know.
Then what should I do now?
Wait.
If he really cares about you,
he won't be able to hide it.
He gave you a like.
[Lu Xiao]
He really can't hide it.
Now,
open his chat frame,
and ask him out for breakfast.
Remember.
Don't use an  interrogative sentence.
Use an affirmative sentence.
Affirmative sentence.
Let's have breakfast.
[Let's have breakfast together tomorrow.]
[Lu Xiao: I have an appointment with my classmate tomorrow morning.]
Ask him to have lunch together tomorrow.
[Then let's have lunch together.]
[I have to go to the lab to study the assignment with the professor at noon.]
See?
This guy
doesn't play by the rules.
It looks like
you can't subdue him with ordinary tactics, right?
Qi Yue,
tell me the truth.
Did you do something to him?
He's obviously avoiding you.
I'm just
a weak girl.
What can I do to him?
Don't let your imagination run wild.
You can do this.
Tomorrow morning,
wait for him in front of his dorm building.
Whether he really has an appointment or he doesn't want to see you,
you'll know it after you go and have a look.
Okay.
Boss.
Give me ten more skewers of big kidneys.
Okay.
Aren't you a weak girl?
[School of Mechatronic Engineering]
Hello, Grandma.
I'm fine.
How have you been lately?
Have you received the hand warmer I bought for you
last time?
Let's walk together.
I'm talking with my grandma on the phone.
Someone asked him out before me.
Say hello.
Hello, Grandma. I'm Yufei.
Qi Yue.
Are you here for me?
No, Zhaoyang. I have something to do.
You seem to be avoiding me all the time.
No. It's just that I've been busy recently.
I think
you have a deep misunderstanding about me,
so I have to spend some time
explaining it clearly to you.
There's no need to do this between us.
You haven't eaten yet, have you?
Let's go to the canteen together.
Let's go.
Go.
The truth is just as what I've said.
So you totally misunderstood me.
Do you know that?
I'm sorry.
I was distracted.
What were you talking about?
For the gift you gave me,
I've redeemed it.
What do you mean by redeeming it?
Come here to eat with us.
Come on.
She is the cute girl I've always
mentioned to you.
Qi Yue.
Bro,
I'm sorry for
what happened last time.
What was it?
Well,
I was short of money,
and I sold your stuff.
It's not a big deal. Let me tell you.
From now on, if you have any trouble, just tell me.
I'll help you.
We're brothers. Just ask me for help.
Got it.
I need to go to class.
I have to go.
Okay. Just go.
Without him,
I wouldn't be able to clear my name.
You told people about my name everywhere.
Did you ask for my permission?
Well, they kept asking me
who the cute little girl was.
It was hard for me to refuse,
so I told them.
Lu Xiao.
Look at me.
What?
I've just learned this magic.
You're amazing.
You saw through trick.
You're indeed a genius in study.
It doesn't taste that bad, does it?
It looks bad.
Here you are.
I'm full.
The guy who followed you
won't show up.
I can end my mission to protect you, right?
It seems he's over there.
It's okay.
He won't do anything in broad daylight.
I'm going back to have class.
What are you doing at noon?
Preparing for the Winter Olympics?
You're doing sports so intensely.
If the heroine in the TV drama
broke up with her boyfriend,
she would try to sweat a lot
in the gym, wouldn't she?
You broke up with your boyfriend?
You don't even have a boyfriend, okay?
Did you do everything as I had said?
Don't mention it.
He isn't as nervous as a spinning basketball.
Obviously, he is having fun with Liang Yufei.
Do you mean
this?
At this point,
you still performed such a boring magic trick?
She merely performed a small magic trick,
and you think of it as intimate contact.
You... You saw it.
Why didn't you stop it?
Which side are you on?
She merely performed a magic trick to her classmate.
How could I stop it?
If they were only schoolmates, would she perform a magic trick like this?
This is obviously a hint.
You even helped the enemy.
I think now you should
go to get even with Lu Xiao,
instead of being upset here.
Okay.
I'll go and question him now.
How should I ask him?
By asking him out.
How?
I thought you didn't need me.
Of course you can't catch the chance
like holding the collar.
For such a good opportunity, you must seize it.
How?
Well, tonight,
the SHAN YU HAI Restaurant.
I'll ask him out.
Let's meet there.
By then, don't say that I'm a bad son again, okay?
Now,
I'm very angry.
Don't provoke me.
Good son.
Son, be good.
I'm going to take a shower.
Which of us actually provoked the other?
Bro, even if my foot was bitten by bugs,
it's not necessary to wrap it with such thick bandages, right?
You need to take precautions in advance
to prevent the worst.
What about the city basketball match?
I'm just messing around.
I probably won't be selected.
Such a good opportunity
should belong to you.
Have we taken the wrong path?
It is the downstairs of the girls' dorm, isn't it?
You've hurt your foot, haven't you?
You need to exercise more.
We've taken the right path.
What a coincidence, Qi Yue.
Come on. Here you are.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
He hurt his leg, didn't he?
He can't participate in the city basketball league match,
so I came out with him for a walk.
It looks serious.
I hope you can get recovered soon.
Thank you.
So, I'll go back now.
Okay.
Gravitational waves with the background of feeble fields
is transmitted at the speed of light.
For example, the gravitational field of the solar system is a feeble field.
The gravitational field around a black hole is a strong field.
Why is that?
You've been absent-minded lately.
Sorry, Professor. I was
distracted.
Take a five-minute break and then continue.
Thank you, Professor.
Qi Yue's phone is out of power.
She asked me to ask you out for dinner.
[Qi Shuo]
6 p.m. at SHAN YU HAI Restaurant.
I've checked it.
You don't have any experiment or appointment tonight.
One last thing.
As a man, take the initiative.
Professor,
for the question you mentioned just now,
I wonder whether
there's also a strong or weak gravitational field between people.
Whose message did you receive just now?
It even had the effect to enlighten you.
This way.
Thank you.
Madam,
do you need a Band-Aid?
Sure.
Thank you.
Okay.
Excuse me,
do you have vases here?
Yes.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Your vase.
Band-Aid.
Thank you.
Lu Xiao.
Are you okay?
Did the man following you hurt you?
You really care about me.
Auntie told me
I must protect you at school.
If you get hurt,
she will be worried.
That person
has been driven away by me.
That's good.
You should go back now.
I have an appointment later.
I have to go.
Wait.
Come here.
Look.
A simple candlelight dinner.
You can see the stars when you look up.
[College Spirit]
What do you think?
Isn't it romantic?
Come on.
Wait.
First, fires are forbidden in school.
Second, outdoor picnic is the least environmentally friendly.
Third, I have to leave now.
I'm glad you're fine.
Remember to tell Auntie you're safe.
Lu Xiao.
He'll come.
He won't come.
He will come.
Hello.
Do you have a reservation?
Yes.
Okay. Please come in.
Qi Yue.
Why are you here?
I sensed it when I was passing by.
I'm sorry.
I have an appointment.
What time?
Six o'clock.
It's already seven.
I don't think he'll come.
What do you think?
Wait.
Wait for me here.
I'll be right back.
Ma'am.
I want to buy a pair of shoes.
This pair.
How much?
Twenty yuan.
Pack the shoes for me.
Here you are.
Okay.
Bye.
Thank you.
Just now, I saw your foot was scratched.
Change into this pair and it will make you feel better.
They're too ugly.
I won't wear them.
The old lady at the street stall ahead
has been here all day.
This is the first pair of shoes she has sold.
You won't disappoint her, will you?
Put them on.
Come on.
I'll do it myself.
Come on. Give them to me.
[Xiao: Something came up. I can't make it.]
Will you continue to eat?
Yes.
Of course I'll eat.
I can't treat myself badly.
That's right.
But this restaurant is too expensive.
When I had just come in here,
I saw a pregnant woman queuing up at the door.
That pregnant woman was even with a child.
It's not easy for her.
Why don't we give this table to them?
I'll take you to another restaurant.
Let's go.
[Rice] [Noodles]
Miss Qin.
You're here.
Let's go in first.
Right here.
Let's go.
Miss Qin, two bowls of eel noodles.
Okay.
Eel?
Thank you, Miss Qin.
You're welcome.
Taste them.
Noodles can be made from eels?
Eel noodles?
Do they taste good?
How is it?
Delicious.
Right?
Look. You need to eat like this, and it'll be delicious.
No, no, no.
I can do it myself.
This
is kind of my secret base.
I've never brought anyone else here.
You're the first one.
This restaurant is good indeed.
It's like a treasure.
Right?
In the past,
my parents always quarreled with each other.
Then I would hide here.
I would bend over
that oily table to do my homework.
The next day,
the teacher would ask me to go to the platform and criticize me.
He asked me why I was eating snacks
while doing homework.
Zhaoyang.
I actually understand you.
Because it was the same to me.
But
maybe the way family express love
is different.
Right.
Sometimes I think it's strange.
Why would a closer one be
more indifferent sometimes?
It's like he'd rather give all his love to others
than bring it to his family.
Sometimes I wonder
why I'm not strong enough.
If I'm strong enough,
I can take my mom away from that person.
Zhaoyang.
Don't blame yourself.
It's not your fault.
Just eat.
The noodles are getting soggy.
In the past,
I didn't know you well.
But after hearing what you said,
my opinion about you
did change.
I'm not good at talking.
Anyway,
you will achieve
what you want to do.
No more words.
All the words are represented by the milk.
Just eat.
Did you go on a date or get a drink?
How much did you drink?
A bottle.
A bottle of white wine?
Amazing, Lu.
I admire you.
A bottle of
beer.
No!
A can.
After drinking a can of beer,
you're so drunk like this?
I take back what I said.
What do you take back?
You didn't even reply to my WeChat messages.
You didn't send me WeChat messages.
Have you forgotten?
A woman's heart is like the needle at the bottom of a deep ocean.
Why did you drink so much if you can't drink?
What have I done wrong to suffer this?
I'm the one who is suffering.
Give me back my first kiss.
First kiss?
Please. Please.
With whom?
What else besides your first kiss?
You're not strawberry-flavored.
You're not strawberry-flavored, either.
Stand up.
Please. Please.
What?
Why are your pajamas...
You need to change the hobby of wearing pajamas
inside a bathrobe.
What new fashion is this?
I'm afraid of making my pajamas dirty.
Why are you back at this hour?
Your Lu Xiao
stood me up.
Lu Xiao...
He didn't go?
Then why are you back so late?
I was hungry, too.
None of you loves me.
I have to love myself.
Either You or Lu Xiao
is a bad teammate.
What true love?
He's not my destined one.
Did you
eat alone?
Of course.
I...
I just don't understand.
Is Lu Xiao really the right person?
For others,
the future is unknown.
But for you,
Lu Xiao is already there.
The answer is obvious.
But why does it have to be him?
Because this is fate.
He is and is the only one.
How can you be so sure?
I can be sure that
if you're up to something,
when I can't coax you into telling me,
I can only use tough tactics.
No.
I was just asking.
Alright. It's my birthday tomorrow.
Remember to invite him over for dinner.
Aren't you Taurus?
It's November.
For your marriage,
does it matter in which month I was born?
Son,
with your words,
I will work hard.
[I Belonged To Your World]
[Why doesn't beer taste like strawberries?]
[Did Qi Shuo tell you? 6 p.m. at SHAN YU HAI Restaurant. Have you arrived?] [Something came up. I can't make it.]
Come on. Put them on.
[Something came up. I can't make it.]
[Liang Yufei]