[English subtitles are available]
[I Belonged To Your World]
Not bad.
Now,
you look like a scholar.
Me?
Let me tell you.
When I was young,
I was like you.
When I saw the word "physics",
I also giggled.
But let me tell you.
Doing research
is like sitting on a cold bench.
Whenever it is,
don't let anything distract you.
Understood?
Yes, Dad.
Lu Xiao.
Qi Yue. Qi Yue.
Why are you here at this hour of the night?
Did something happen?
Lu Xiao, I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
When
will we
have a son?
Miss.
What did you say? I can't hear you.
Hello, sir.
I said...
I said you have a great son.
Bye. Good night.
Have an early night.
Qi Yue...
She...
About giving birth to a son,
I have to tell you
the principle of gene mapping
in physics.
It's a long story.
Let's talk inside.
Hello.
Why are you walking so fast?
I'm trying to increase
the ground reaction force.
In fact, dating
is doing something boring
together.
Let me join you.
What are you doing?
Qi Yue.
What did you mean
last night?
Qi Shuo asked me
to tell you what I want to do
and important things
so that you can understand me.
Have you made up your mind?
About what?
We should have a son as soon as possible.
But
we haven't graduated from university.
I don't care.
You have no idea
when a son will suddenly appear
in front of you.
Don't you want to know
what our future son looks like?
I'm thinking about...
I know you want to.
Let's go.
Even if they see their siblings
suddenly disappear,
[Wonder Woman]
they still don't know what life means.
[When will we have a son?]
[Wonder Woman]
Spring is full of life and romance.
It's the season for animals to mate.
The hydras also started their
new day.
Don't underestimate hydras.
The Tfap2 gene in them
can continuously transform stem cells
into reproductive cells.
What's Tfap2 gene,
Dad?
You can construe it as a strong gene.
The healthier you are,
the more natural reaction it has.
Survival of the fittest.
Natural selection.
The same is true for humans.
I see, Dad.
I'll go in and read.
Lu Xiao.
Are you okay?
Dad, I'm reading.
[Qi Yue, I'm ready.]
Are we
playing Squid Game?
Spot the Difference.
Who is this?
The photo of my son combined by
the photos of me and Lu Xiao.
Why doesn't he look like you?
You believe in this?
It's not true.
Besides, I'm already 26 years old.
Girls' appearance has also been changing since childhood.
You're right.
Do you have any photos of you when you were a kid?
Let me see.
No, I don't.
Why would I have that kind of thing?
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I missed your childhood.
But it's okay.
From now on,
we'll make up for it.
How will you
make up for it?
Exercise is effective.
Qi Yue.
This hot spring pool is so comfortable.
This is...
Did you lose your memory?
My cousin, Qi Shuo.
I know.
But
isn't this our date?
We're already here. We just have one more person.
And didn't we agree
to get used to having a son in advance?
When did we agree?
Just now. I said that.
You see him as our son?
Bro, I was forced.
Stop talking. Come in.
It's cold. Come in.
The water will get cold.
Your swimming trunks have a nice color.
How about
we tell
ghost stories before we sleep.
What ghost stories?
Well,
let me tell you the rules of the game.
Now the three of us
continuously pass this candle.
If the candle
suddenly goes out,
it means the ghost is here.
Who starts first?
I'll start first. I won't start.
Cowards step back.
Fine.
I'll set an example first.
Once upon a time,
there was a girl.
She just graduated,
so she didn't have much money.
She could only rent a haunted house.
But strange things
often happened
in that room.
For example,
the sofa suddenly sagged
and became how it was again.
Or the door of the fridge suddenly opened
and suddenly closed.
Sometimes there were footsteps
in the room.
She also heard knocks at the door at night.
Ghosts are coming.
You two can't sleep before me.
Don't be afraid. I'm here.
I might be sleepless tonight.
See?
I know her too well.
I have a question.
What is it?
Are you really Qi Yue's cousin?
Yes, I...
I'm definitely her cousin.
Why did you ask this?
I just don't understand
why cousins can be so close
that you rely on each other for survival.
The word "blood" is magical.
It can make two people who are from
different spacetime and axes
become naturally close
even if they've never met.
I think that's why I'm close to her.
I see.
It's like sodium and chlorine can have a natural combination reaction
without any specific conditions.
Lu Xiao,
you'll marry Qi Yue, right?
Do you know what Hawking's most famous quote
is?
The universe has no boundary.
He said,
"if you are lucky enough to find love,
remember it is rare
and don't throw it away."
Lu Xiao, have a son.
Hello.
Enjoy your meal.
Qi Yue.
You're too thin.
Eat more meat.
Qi Shuo.
You're too thin.
Eat more meat.
Make up for not eating much in your childhood.
Lu Xiao.
You're the host. Eat more.
[Qingnan University]
Wait.
Both of you have to swipe cards.
Can't a couple be counted as one person?
No way.
You can't enter if you don't swipe your card in the new semester.
Swipe your card.
Leave when you're done.
I'm afraid of having diabetes.
Next one.
Isn't she your junior?
Why is she with someone else?
-Hello. -What are you looking at?
You don't need to train at the beginning of the new semester, right?
Hello, I'm Qi Yue from the Department of Philosophy.
Do you need help?
You look weak.
Forget it.
I can ask my boyfriend to help you.
He's Lu Xiao from the Department of Physics.
I don't think it's a good idea.
Right.
I just want to tell you
he is my boyfriend.
Don't go.
Hello.
Me?
Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
Can you help my friend
carry her luggage upstairs?
She seems to need help.
Thank you.
Qi Yue.
If you continue to talk like this,
won't you have enemies?
What's wrong?
I just saved a single girl.
It's a blessing.
Boss.
Xie Jiajia.
You gained weight during the winter vacation.
Boss, come with me.
Where are we going?
Get fertilizer.
I'm going to plant chillies in my dorm room this year.
Again?
You're early.
Not bad.
I heard
you are finally in a relationship.
I envy you.
Why?
Don't you have a girlfriend?
Haven't you heard
that the winter vacation has a negative influence on love?
Tell me the secret of love.
Shower often.
Does it smell?
[Nurse Station]
[Qi Shuo]
Do you want to eat it?
Why did you play tricks on me?
You were distracted.
All right, I'll stop teasing you.
Let me guess.
The person you like
will appear in front of you today.
Really?
Of course not.
I'm talking nonsense.
Who are you?
My allergies are acting up.
I'm here for a dermatologist.
This is the Inpatient Department.
Let me register for you first.
What's your name?
Qi Shuo.
It's amazing.
Don't you recognize me?
Qi Shuo.
Okay.
Dear,
you haven't grown anything last semester.
That's not important.
Perseverance is the most important thing.
Long time no see. Hurry up.
I miss you so much.
Come here.
Open the suitcase.
I brought you gifts.
What?
Have a guess.
Paper?
Are you serious?
This is the pancake I brought back from Shandong.
It's delicious.
Here you are.
It's not fattening. Here you are.
So,
my gift is absolutely simple and direct.
Baoguo. Limin. Zhiqiang. Chaoyang.
I already named them.
We each have one hamster.
What are you doing?
I didn't prepare anything special for you.
I'll give you my couple photos.
I hope you can always land on your feet.
Boss, I've heard it all along the way.
Where there's a will, there's a way.
You haven't become smarter after the vacation.
This is called
"every Jack has his Jill."
Qi Yue,
we also made a contribution.
I hereby announce
all of you
are the shareholders of this league.
League?
Shareholders?
What do you mean?
Will you charge us fees?
Stop thinking about money.
The patient's recovery
is not bad.
But when you go back,
you still have to be careful of the food he can't eat.
Okay.
Don't eat spicy food.
Stop it.
You may
be allergic to a mineral or disinfectant
in spring water.
Disinfectant?
But half a month has passed.
Some people are like this.
It can last for a long period of time.
I've made a note on
how to take your medicine.
Thank you, Shuling.
It's lucky to have you here.
Do you have time for lunch?
Let's have lunch together.
Tomorrow?
Today.
This noon?
No.
Today is the first day of school.
I have to go back to the lab this afternoon.
Although we can't have lunch together,
we can spill the tea.
Tea?
What tea?
I heard you like someone.
Who is he? Did you tell him?
No.
Won't it be too sudden?
Trust me.
What do men like the most?
They like
sudden romance the most.
It's time to remove the needle.
Be gentle.
We don't have many classes this semester.
You
are studying psychology.
You have theoretical foundation.
You
are studying biology. It's related.
As for me,
I'm
a genius of love.
So,
I plan to set up a love class
with you.
I agree.
What?
What can I do?
You'll be in charge of the logistics.
Qi Shuo.
What?
You recognized me?
Your new look of the new semester?
Don't mention it.
We went to the hot spring together last time.
I'm allergic.
My allergies are acting up.
That was a date between two people.
The third wheel has to pay the price.
Why are you
talking like Qi Yue?
[Jin Pi Kang Wang]
Whose notebook is this?
[Qi Shuo]
Why is my name on it?
Maybe she was practicing calligraphy.
Or she likes you.
You're not like you now.
Why did you suddenly become a master of love?
I only found two explanations.
[Qi Shuo]
First, I'm not a master.
It's because you didn't notice
your illness and her feelings before.
Second,
although writing names is childish,
I did it before.
You did it too?
[Deng Shuling]
Are you free tonight?
I have something to tell you.
[Deng Shuling]
Men like sudden romance the most.
No.
She's my mother's best friend.
She's my aunt.
I need to stop her.
I know, Qi Yue.
Your slow reaction is hereditary.
Anyway,
this is
the whole process of how Lu Xiao and I
started to be in a relationship.
Is it appealing
and complicated?
When I have time,
I'll register intellectual property
and create a romantic drama.
The audience will be like you,
sitting here and crying.
What's wrong?
I...
I'm talking about romantic dramas,
not double acts.
You don't have to cooperate with me like this.
Qi Yue.
I... I broke up.
When did that happen?
Why didn't I know?
I was refused
before I told him I like him.
It's hot. Oh no.
You're love-struck.
I wanted to send him a message
and tell him I like him face to face.
The afternoon passed
and he still didn't reply.
Three seconds.
I want all of his information.
What do you want to do?
I'm going to question
and threaten him.
If it doesn't work, I'll curse him.
No.
Then I can't give you the information.
Why?
I don't want to ruin your relationship.
What do you mean? Do I know him?
My goodness.
Are you...
Deng Shuling.
First come, first served.
How could you and Lu Xiao...
I...
He's not Lu Xiao.
Between us, who is love-struck?
That's good.
He's Qi Shuo.
What?
That's impossible.
Why?
Bloody hell!
This is not a romantic drama.
This is a modern version of Thunderstorm.
Let me ask you.
Did you give a hint
to Deng Shuling?
Are you crazy?
She's your best friend
and my future godmother.
How could I give her any hints?
Right.
Is it because I care about her
and take care of her?
I see.
The philosophy teacher said
people's misfortune in their childhood
will be made up for and reflected in their future love.
What do you mean?
Think about it.
These days
you care about her and take after her.
It made up for the love she didn't have when she was a child.
So she naturally
fell in love with you.
What should I do now?
You can't refuse her directly.
You need to stimulate her self-consciousness.
How?
Just do the opposite
of what made she like you.
Get rid of
her affection for you.
It's strange.
How could you say that?
Did we change the scriptwriter this episode?
Don't underestimate me.
Why did she bite her lip?
[Love Class]
Love class?
People tend to lose themselves in love.
As the saying goes, lookers-on see most of the game.
That's why
I want to set up this love class.
Today, I'll mainly about
being neither humble nor arrogant in love.
No one can change your fate.
But love
can help you become a better version of yourself.
Qi Yue, come out!
What's wrong?
Are you here to mess around after losing to me?
You misunderstood.
It was not me.
Qi Yue, thank you.
After having your love class,
I successfully dated the boy I love.
This means the love class
is quite effective.
Yes.
It's indeed effective.
My money was swindled on the first day.
What?
You asked me
to open up.
Tell me, what should I do now?
I asked you to open up.
I didn't ask you to open your wallet.
Tell me.
Who is that bastard?
It doesn't matter.
Just tell me how you will compensate me.
Who is he?
Tell us. Don't be afraid.
We will support you.
Yes.
He's Xu...
Is he Xu Zhaoyang?
What? Xu Zhaoyang?
[I Belonged To Your World]
[Judging by our appearance, we must be a family.]
That's vulgar.
[Love Each Other and Get Rid of Bad People]