[English subtitles are available]
[I Belonged To Your World]
Xincheng.
Are you free tonight?
Yes. What?
I have something to do tonight.
You take my shift in the laboratory.
I'll take yours tomorrow.
What
makes a genius like you
switch your shift with me?
You are obsessed with experiments.
Are you going to date a girl?
No.
I'm just going to celebrate Qi Shuo's birthday.
I see.
I don't think it's your real intention.
Where is Qi Shuo?
Who are you talking about?
Get lost!
I quit.
[I quit. Episode 8]
[12 hours ago]
It's my son's birthday.
I must prepare a big gift.
Tell me.
What do you want?
I didn't expect a gift.
Anything I want?
As long as you name it.
Then...
I want a proper gift.
A proper gift?
What?
Did you receive anything improper?
It's an anti-kidnapping electronic bracelet for kids.
When
you wear it,
if strangers
-or those who didn't input their fingerprints touch it, -No, no, no.
they will get an electric shock immediately.
Let me help you try it on.
Oh no.
I forgot to input my fingerprints.
Son.
I prepared a gift for you.
Look.
So you know
how hard it was for me to survive
considering how unreliable you were.
If it weren't for the little robot I gave you,
you wouldn't have the physical talent.
A daily reminder.
We made three rules.
Qi Yue, Qi Yue, Qi Yue.
What a coincidence, Zhaoyang.
It's not a coincidence.
I've been waiting for you here.
Let's go eat.
I have something to tell you.
Sorry.
My roommate bought me food.
I'm going back to eat.
What happened again?
Qi Yue.
Why are you back?
Xu Zhaoyang is downstairs.
So what?
I promised Qi Shuo
to stay away from him.
If he finds out...
So I came back as soon as possible.
You can't hide like this forever.
We have a public course later.
Help me ask for leave.
Use the same old reason.
I'll go.
I'm calling the roll now.
Looking for Qi Yue?
She has a stomachache. She's in the dorm.
Don't worry.
Someone in the dorm is taking care of her.
Chen Zihan.
Yes.
That's not what I wanted to ask.
Deng Keran.
Yes.
Lu Xiao.
Why are you distracted in the morning?
Come here.
[Marc Chagall's Beautiful World]
You continue to call the roll.
Ma Sisi.
Yes.
Ouyang Lin.
[Qi Yue]
Qi...
Qi Tian.
Yes.
Dismiss.
Lu Xiao.
Are you interested in gossip?
No.
It's gossip for others.
But it's useful
for you.
It's about your little tail.
What do you want to say?
I saw a handsome
sunny boy
waiting for Qi Yue downstairs this morning.
If you really
don't like your little tail,
you'll soon get what you want.
Have you finished your first experiment?
No.
Then why are you still in the mood to gossip?
I'm just chatting.
Why are you suddenly angry?
Take them back to my dorm.
Where are you going?
Boss.
Someone is looking for you downstairs.
If it's Xu Zhaoyang,
I won't go.
I promised Qi Shuo.
It's not Xu Zhaoyang.
It's Lu Xiao.
Who?
Lu Xiao.
Last night, why did you...
For me?
I brought you medicine for enterogastritis
and gastroenteritis.
There are also painkillers.
I asked the school doctor
to write a list of dosages
and put it inside.
But
I suggest you go to the doctor in time.
That's not why I have a stomachache.
Then why do you have a stomachache?
Well...
It's a girl thing.
Even if you have asked for leave for the public course,
your general marks will be reduced.
So try not to be absent in the future.
You were absent last night.
Something came up last night, so I didn't show up.
Never mind.
I'm generous.
How about tonight?
Let's have dinner together tonight.
It's Qi Shuo's birthday.
I'll be there on time today.
Come to my house.
The address is...
I remember.
I've been there.
Thank you for the gift.
Why would anyone take medicine as a gift?
I would.
See you tonight.
A razor?
It's so tacky.
Chocolate?
It's not proper considering the relation between us.
How about a doll?
You really don't know how to prepare gifts.
Didn't you always say
his family members haven't been with him since he was young?
In my opinion,
you can give him a family photo.
A family photo?
This is good.
That's it.
Qi Yue.
Zhaoyang.
Well,
what do you think of me?
I've been waiting for you downstairs for a long time.
I have a lot to tell you.
But I don't know what to say when I see you.
Then don't say anything.
No, Qi Yue.
I like you.
Can you be my girlfriend?
Bro,
can you spare my life?
I'm confessing my love to you.
I'm not blackmailing you.
Anyway,
thank you for your love.
But I have something to do
and I have someone I like.
It's Lu Xiao, right?
Why him?
I guess it's fate.
You won't understand.
You don't have to use fate as an excuse
to refuse me.
Anyway, you are a good guy.
But we'd better be strangers from now on.
[Prescription: Lu Xiao Stomachache]
You're sick?
You should take your medicine.
I'll help you ask the professor for leave.
It's okay
for a man to be fragile.
It's...
It's not me. It's...
I have a friend.
What's wrong with Qi Yue?
She has a stomachache.
She didn't come to the public course.
As the class monitor, I need to...
She should be much better now.
Why hasn't she come out yet?
Where are you?
Why didn't you call me back?
Qi Shuo.
Where's Qi Yue?
She didn't answer my call.
Is she in the dorm or in the classroom?
In the classroom.
In the dorm.
It's just I'm afraid she has a stomachache.
She's always like this.
Yes.
She had her period this morning.
So...
Her period?
When?
Why didn't I know?
This morning.
It's so hard for me.
If Qi Yue wants to skip a class next time,
can she...
Skipping a class?
So every time she said she had a stomachache,
she skipped a class, right?
Not exactly.
Where is she now?
Maybe she
went to the auditorium.
She's doomed.
Someone confessed his love in the auditorium just now.
Did you see it?
Yes.
That boy is from the Department of Physical Education, right?
-That was quite romantic. -Love confession?
Auntie.
You are here for the show?
It's too late.
Everyone has left.
So, was it a love confession?
Did the girl say yes?
She said yes.
You young people know your tricks.
Damn. The ground is so dirty.
Where did they go?
They went that way.
Thank you.
Didn't I warn you
not to get close to Qi Yue?
Are you crazy?
Who are you?
Hey.
Alright.
Calm down.
-That's enough. -Stop!
Who the hell are you?
The hell.
Do you know who the hell I am?
I am your hell.
I want to kick you to death!
Come here.
All right.
Who are you?
It's fine I'm ugly.
As long as my son is handsome.
You're home.
Why didn't you turn on the light?
What's wrong?
Where did you go?
I went to class.
What did you do
before going to class?
Who did you meet?
Is this a gift from Zhaoyang?
Is it for his love confession?
He did confess his love to me today.
What are you doing?
I told you to stay away from him.
Do you know him?
Have you ever got along with him?
Qi Yue, you're so lovesick.
Can you please keep your eyes wide open?
What do you mean?
Can you be reasonable?
I just came back,
and you are blaming me.
What are you doing?
How many times have I told you that
Xu Zhaoyang is not a good man.
You should let him go as far as he can.
Do you know him?
You haven't even got along with him.
I don't need to.
How many times have I told you?
You should stay away from him.
I'm warning you.
Shouldn't you
give me some time?
Can we make it fair?
You told me Xu Zhaoyang is not a good man.
But I've never seen him
do anything bad.
But I still listened to you.
I stayed away from him.
But he has his own rights.
What can I do?
Should I tell him that
my future son asked me to pursue Lu Xiao
and stay away from you?
You don't have to say that.
What should I say?
Should I say Zhaoyang,
I don't know why
I can't get too close to you?
I don't think you're a good person.
And I tell him
to go as far as he can, right?
Let me tell you.
There are 10,000 ways to refuse someone if you want,
right?
Do you understand?
We are in the same university.
We always meet.
Besides,
chasing Lu Xiao
has made me
a joke in the university.
Don't I have any pride?
I didn't ask you
to pursue Lu Xiao with your pride.
That's not why I came here.
Right.
You suddenly showed up.
You told me you're here to change my fate.
You are my son.
Let me ask you.
Am I the only one who should be responsible for
my future misfortune?
Why don't you persuade Lu Xiao to change?
Your fate
can only be changed by yourself.
Do you understand?
The truth is you don't trust me at all.
No.
It's not that you don't trust me.
You don't trust anyone.
You only trust yourself.
Yes.
Everything you say is right.
I don't trust you.
That's why I came all the way here
to bother you.
Listen.
If you know
how to handle everything,
it won't be necessary for me to warn you.
I have the ability to think independently.
From now on, listen carefully.
I won't chase
Lu Xiao anymore.
I knew you wouldn't chase Lu Xiao.
You're such a loser.
If I am a loser,
you're the son of a loser.
If I am such a terrible woman,
why did you choose me to be your mother?
If I had a choice,
I would never choose you to be my mother.
I wouldn't choose you to be my son either.
But now you are still living in my house,
eating my food, drinking my water, and using my things.
Yes, I...
I eat your food,
use your things, live in your house,
and drink your water.
Sorry.
It's my fault.
I should leave.
Goodbye.
You'd better never come back.
Where's Qi Shuo?
Who are you talking about?
Get lost!
I quit.
Why are you giving me a video call?
Nothing.
I'm just passing by
to see if you're off work.
I'm off today.
Okay.
Get some rest.
Is something wrong?
It's nothing actually.
Can I
sleep in your house tonight?
I know it's a bit absurd
[Qi Yue: I'm downstairs.]
and rude.
Qi Yue sent me a message.
Qi Yue said she's downstairs.
What happened to your face?
It doesn't matter.
You said Qi Yue is downstairs, right?
Yes.
Don't tell her
I've been here.
Please.
He ran away from home?
He threw the gift I gave him.
He also talked about Xu Zhaoyang.
What does it have to do with him?
You know what?
Xu Zhaoyang confessed his love to me today.
I refused him without hesitation.
And
today,
I went
to prepare
that ugly family photo.
Well,
there must be some misunderstanding.
Why don't you apologize to him?
Why should I apologize?
What did I do wrong?
He himself has many bad habits
and he wants to change me.
OK. No apologies.
You did nothing wrong.
It's okay.
This...
You know what?
He had a dream one night.
Do you know what he did?
He...
He talked in his sleep？
He sleepwalked.
He recited every number
of Pi.
Stop laughing.
All right.
Why do I feel
you two are quite alike sometimes?
Really?
Like mother, like son.
What are you talking about?
Are you not thinking straight because you are angry?
You're right.
I need to powder my nose.
Wait.
-Thank goodness I didn't spill it. -Oh, no.
Are you trying to murder me?
I...
I suddenly want to take a shower.
Why did your shower head turn on automatically?
I controlled it remotely.
Look, I'm turning it off.
Impressive.
Yes.
I'm going to take a shower.
Go back now.
Go.
What are you doing?
I'm going to take a shower.
Be careful on your way home.
Wait.
If Qi Shuo comes to you,
you must tell me.
-You must tell me. -Okay.
I will.
Bye. Bye.
Are you hiding a man in your house?
Put it on. Don't catch a cold.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I lied today.
Actually, I quarreled with Qi Yue.
That's why I'm here.
Sit here.
I'll clean the wound on your face.
Okay.
By the way, how is your mother?
Much better.
It's okay.
Don't feel pressured.
I need to keep her company in the daytime.
Does it hurt?
Take this if it hurts.
I need to keep her company in the daytime,
and I have to be on a night shift.
If you can take care of Tuantuan for me,
you'll be a great help.
I should have brought some medicine.
Aunt Shuling,
do you think my mom is going to abandon me?
Nonsense!
Your mother
has been busy recently.
Just stay here with me for a while.
I'll play with you, okay?
Are you unhappy?
Look what gift I prepared
for you today.
Take it.
Why aren't you answering your phone?
No need.
That's the alarm set for Qi Yue
to remind her to memorize words.
But
it doesn't matter now.
Because of your supervision,
Qi Yue has become better.
She always said
if it weren't for Qi Shuo,
I wouldn't have done this.
Really?
When? Why didn't I know?
She said it multiple times a day.
Are you guys of the Qi family
all sharp-tongued and tender-hearted?
No way.
I won't be bribed by her sugar-coated words.
I'll be strict
when it's necessary.
What a luck
for me to have two of the Qi family around me.
I'm going to bed.
From now on, the living room is your bedroom.
Qi Shuo, let me sleep for another five minutes.
Just five minutes.
Hurry up and eat.
You need to memorize words for CET-4 later.
You really ran away from home.
[Anger is harmful to human body. If you are always angry...]
[But why are you angry?]
Let me ask you a question.
Is there anything you don't know?
What do girls usually get angry about?
For boys, there are two reasons.
Either they lose in a game,
or their new sneakers are dirty.
Girls are complicated.
It can't be generally summarized.
It varies from person to person.
Who are you talking about?
Qi Yue.
Qi Yue?
It must be because you refused her.
I didn't today.
Then I don't know why.
I don't know her well.
If you want to know,
just ask her.
I did.
She didn't reply.
Qi Yue.
How was yesterday?
Don't mention it.
I had a big fight with Qi Shuo.
He ran away from home.
What about Lu Xiao?
Didn't he go?
I think
I yelled at him and told him to go away.
Seriously,
you are a badass.
Tell me.
If we
give birth to a son
after ten months of pregnancy,
we have to feed him
and raise him.
However,
when he grows up,
he argues with you,
runs away from home,
slams the door,
puts your name on the blacklist,
and even disappears.
Don't you think he is your enemy?
I admire your imagination.
How did you manage to think of your future son
through your brother's running away from home?
I...
I'm angry for his mother.
Damn.
I forgot to submit my paper.
I'm running out of time.
Oh no.
You just forgot to submit it.
I forgot to write it.
-I knew it. -I knew it.
Usually, Qi Shuo would remind me
of things like writing a paper.
I think Qi Shuo's running away from home
is like chopping a leg of yours.
You are just one step from begging.
It's not like
I can't live without him.
From now on,
I will live freely.
Students who just arrived, take a seat quickly.
The class is about to start.
There is a vacant seat beside Lu Xiao.
Why don't you sit there?
It's too crowded.
If you haven't submitted your papers,
I'll give you another chance.
Send them to my email by tomorrow.
This is your last chance.
Qi Yue,
this is my experiment report.
Help me give it to Qi Shuo.
Why don't you give it to him yourself?
We are not always together.
I'm not his deliveryman.
Why should I give it to him?
Good luck.
Your little tail didn't pester you today?
Good.
If it's good,
you should be happy.
To be honest,
do you really hate her that much?
I think she's good.
If you really don't like her,
why don't you introduce her to me?
To be honest,
if I had a girlfriend
like Qi Yue
being so nice to me,
I would
wake up laughing from my dream.
Dream less, and study harder.
What a coincidence, Lu Xiao.
I didn't expect to meet you here.
Lu Xiao.
Come and sit.
Surprise!
[Qi Shuo: 1,000 yuan accepted]
What kind of son is he?
Running away from home after a quarrel.
If you are so capable,
repay your mother like Nezha.
Xie Jiajia.
Yes.
Take a walk with me.
Lu Xiao.
There is a boy from another university who keeps harassing me.
He just won't give up.
Please help me.
Yufei,
I think you should be more independent.
An adult must learn
how to refuse other people.
It also shows your respect for them.
Could anything go wrong?
Don't worry.
Xie Jiajia.
What happened to Qi Yue?
You still don't know?
Qi Shuo is missing.
She's about to call the police.
Qi Yue.
How is it now?
I still can't reach him.
How long has he been missing?
Over 24 hours.
What should we do?
Should we wait here?
Of course not.
Don't worry.
I'll go look for him with you.
Let's go.
Excuse me,
have you seen this guy?
No.
Okay, thank you.
Grandpa.
Have you seen this guy?
Thank you.
Hello.
Have you seen this guy?
Thank you.
Hello.
Have you seen this guy?
No.
Thank you.
We need to think of another way.
This won't do.
Let's go to the police station.
What are you going to do?
Call the police.
No.
Absolutely not.
What are you two doing sneakily?
Qi Yue.
Run when I count to three.
Three.
Stop!
Here.
Why are you putting up advertisements everywhere?
Stop!
Have they
left?
Yes.
Let's...
Let's leave here.
Okay.
I'll go first.
I can't move.
We both move a little to the left.
Left?
To the left.
Okay, left.
I think I'm hungry.
Is there anything you want to eat?
I suddenly remember
Qi Shuo told me
there is an old lady selling ice cream balls
around here.
He said when he was a kid,
his mother was always not with him.
He would go to that old lady.
She would give him
ice cream balls in various colors.
Maybe he went to the old lady.
We may find clues there.
But...
But that's more than ten years from now.
This is it.
It's really here.
Hello.
Is the old lady here?
What old lady?
The owner of this stall.
She went to the bathroom.
How long did she go?
Just now.
What should we do?
[Rainbow Ice Cream]
If you don't mind,
go get it yourself.
Just put the money in the box.
This is for you.
The flavor is strawberry.
How do you know I like strawberry?
Because of your lipstick...
Hello.
I want an ice cream.
What flavor do you want?
Strawberry.
Wait a second.
♫Pass the high mountain and the blue coastline♫
♫Linger on this place. I seemed to come across you yesterday♫
♫Memories sparkle like dreams♫
♫Those images♫
[I Belonged To Your World]
[My son is fierce when he's angry but is cute usually.]
Seriously?
He is sleepwalking again?
Teachers.
Classmates.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Qi Shuo from Class 1, Grade 3.
What I'm going to show you today is
reciting the numbers of Pi.
3.1415926
5358979.
That's all.
Thank you.