Qingge.
Mo Haoran,
everything you've done
is part of your plan against me.
Master,
a letter has arrived from the palace.
His Majesty still hopes that you'll return to the capital to recuperate.
Reply to His Majesty
that I will never return
until I have accomplished the great plan.
Who's there?
Yuan Ying, stop.
What a white medicinal scent.
Ah, no, what a strange medicinal scent.
This man has been poisoned.
Yuan Ying,
take this young lady back to the Front Yard Inn.
H-H-He is in good physical condition.
I should be able to save him.
So that man is the chief of Fengyu Pavilion.
I've heard that the chief of Fengyu Pavilion is resourceful
and is an exceptional martial artist.
If I can get him to come to the capital with me,
my plan will be halfway to success.
Senior Brother, I've left the mountain.
My dad, the Martial Arts Alliance Leader,
actually wants to marry me off as a concubine
to the most treacherous official in the court, the Marquis of Ningyuan.
I plan to go straight to the capital and kill him.
I heard that Dad is going to hold a martial arts assembly in Anle Town.
I'll find some helpers first.
Don't worry; by the time you arrive,
I'll have already led my men to the capital.
Don't worry.
Master, you and Xie Mingyuan have been planning for a long time.
His daughter came at this time.
Could there be
some scheme involved?
I'll rely on Chief Xie's full support
for this plan.
Since it's for the sake of all,
I will certainly do my utmost.
It's alright.
Master, your guest has arrived.
I am extremely grateful
that you have voluntarily offered your private property
to assist in holding the martial arts assembly this time.
However, I've heard
that you
have actually arranged for the daughter of the demon Xie Mingyuan
to stay at the Front Yard Inn.
What is your intention behind this?
Could it be that you have other plans
for the demonic sect?
Alliance Leader Xu, you came to me in secret
just for this matter?
This concerns the Martial Arts Alliance.
How can you make such decisions on your own?
I wouldn't dare.
It's just
that since you need to rely on my Fengyu Pavilion to eradicate the demonic sect,
you have to listen to me
on everything.
You...
If you can truly provide full support,
I will, of course, know my place.
However, these are just empty promises.
Chief Mo,
swear an oath.
Then, I'll give you a token of proof.
Oh?
Could this person also be here to treat his poison?
Get out.
Step aside.
Don't move.
You've been poisoned.
Your complexion is pale,
your meridians appear dark and sluggish,
and your breathing is unstable.
What a fragrant aroma of gardenia.
Your lips are pale.
This is...
I can cure you
of that poison.
What do you mean by that, miss?
This is Jialan...
Yuan Ying, show the guest out.
Go.
Get out.
You're afraid to face your illness.
I've left the antidote for you.
Chief Mo,
did you take
the antidote I left for you?
Thank you for the medicine, Miss.
It helped me sleep well last night.
How did you know about my master's condition?
As the daughter of the Martial Arts Alliance Leader
and a descendant of Medicine Valley,
it's not surprising
that I can identify the poison affecting you.
You have quite a background, miss.
May I ask for your name?
I am blessed with a precious daughter
and have fortunately acquired a treasured sword.
It's a double celebration!
With my beloved daughter, Qingge,
and the treasured sword, Tianba,
what more could I possibly ask for?
I, Xie Mingyuan
from Yanhua Mountain,
hereby joyfully announce the birth of my daughter, Tianba,
and the acquisition of the treasured sword, Qingge.
Thus, I invite all my friends to celebrate together.
My name is Xie Qingge.
Qingge.
Qingge?
Miss Qingge, may I ask
why you're here?
Chief Mo,
now that you've taken my medicine,
you could be regarded as one of my men.
Miss Xie, so you mean...
you're in need of my services, right?
That's right.
From the moment I first saw you,
I knew you
would be my most precious poisoned chief...
Oh no, I mean kindred spirit.
What?
Chief Mo, you control the entire Fengyu Pavilion,
and I
am the daughter of the Martial Arts Alliance Leader.
Why don't we join forces
to storm the capital
and chop off the head of the Marquis of Ningyuan?
Get out of here.
Master,
if she finds out that you are the Marquis of Ningyuan,
will she try to assassinate you directly?
What's there to be afraid of?
She's out in the open, while we're in the shadows.
I'm worried that if she continues to act recklessly like this,
it may ruin our plans.
Yuan Ying,
why do you think
that I must keep Miss Xie by my side?
Is there a purpose?
Xie Tianba,
last time you accidentally fell into his tub.
This time, let's aim for a smooth landing.
You can do it.
Chief Mo,
let's discuss the plan to assassinate the Marquis of Ningyuan.
Why on earth
do you want to kill him?
That scoundrel, Turtle Shen,
a born eunuch,
actually wants to take me as his concubine.
I am the only daughter of the Martial Arts Alliance Leader!
Shen Wugui is the Marquis of Ningyuan
and is favored by both the Empress Dowager and the Imperial Uncle.
He's always under the protection of guards wherever he goes.
This plan is unwise.
Whether it's wise or not,
let's consult the divination blocks.
Both blocks have landed with their flat sides up,
which indicates that this matter will surely go smoothly.
It clearly means
that the situation
you're inquiring about is unclear,
so it should be postponed.
You're familiar with interpreting divination blocks?
Miss Xie, you simply don't want to marry the Marquis of Ningyuan, right?
I have an idea
that can solve this urgent problem of yours.
Do tell, Chief.
Marry me.