[Episode 19 Both Love and Debts Can't Be Easily Repaid]
[Dual Love]
I've looked through almost all the medical books in the world.
But there's still only one sentence I can find,
"Return to the source and learn from analogy."
What on earth does it mean?
When they were writing a book,
why couldn't they make what they were writing a bit clearer?
The method of using one poison to counteract another has been practiced a lot.
But there will be only one shot.
If a mistake is made, he will...
Mo Haoran,
how have you been?
Father, you're still sharp as ever
and full of vigor and energy.
Listen to what you said.
I am always sharp.
Come on,
spar with me for a few moves.
Daodao, you're not focused.
You shouldn't engage in martial arts when your mind is not focused.
Have you forgotten what I taught you?
I haven't.
It's just that...
I wasn't holding Qingge just now.
I wasn't used to this.
I don't think Qingge is what's on your mind.
Father,
tell me,
given how he treated us before,
I still keep thinking about him.
Am I being too weak?
I understand.
I didn't expect Lu to join the Blood Pagoda.
Marquis Shen saved us.
Daodao,
a doctor should have a benevolent heart.
Save him if you want to.
Miss Xie.
Master.
Return to the source
and learn from analogy.
and learn from analogy?
What on earth does it mean?
Return to the source
and learn from analogy.
Miss Xie,
I offended you that day.
Please don't hold a grudge against Master.
After the poison is eliminated,
whether you want to punish or even kill me
is your say.
We people in the martial world
don't have to kneel when a mistake is made.
I came here today to ask you
about how Mo Haoran
was poisoned back then.
Back then, Empress Dowager Xiao wanted to control His Majesty,
so she poisoned him with the Jialan Poison.
Master used the blood deflection method
to deflect the poison onto himself.
You mentioned a secret medicine from His Majesty that day.
Why?
The medicine couldn't work?
It can just slow down the poison's spread to the heart,
in addition to pain relief effects.
Master must have known there was no cure,
so he used the blood deflection method
to save His Majesty.
Blood deflection method?
Blood deflection method.
♫Stories center around sorrow and happiness♫
♫Avoiding worry♫
There is a cure.
♫Let's talk about our thoughts slowly♫
♫If one loves another one so deeply♫
♫He'll finally find himself black and blue♫
♫He'll spend the rest of his life panicking after survival♫
♫Not knowing where to hide♫
♫How sad he looks♫
♫He's all alone, and in the blink of an eye♫
♫He's crazy for love♫
Master, why are you out here?
It's a good day today.
I came out for some fresh air.
Now that I have the strength to leave my bed.
I don't know
if I have many more chances to see the sun.
Master, please don't talk like that.
It doesn't mean anything inauspicious.
Yuan Ying.
Did you send the things I asked you to prepare
to Yanhua Mountain?
I did.
Good.
Maybe one day when she uses them,
she'll think of me.
I'm afraid she'll forget me,
yet I'm also afraid she won't be able to forget me.
What does he mean?
Is he trying to leave me an inheritance?
Who am I to him?
Why would I be entitled to his inheritance?
If he's going to die,
he should die far away from me!
Go back and tell your Master
he should take good care of himself
and I'll come to save him.
Don't think too much.
It's not the time for him to act like a tragic hero described in a novel.
Do you hear me?
Yes.
Go. Go.
Master!
The secret guard has returned from Yanhua Mountain!
Master, there's hope for you!
Miss Xie will surely be able to save you.