[Episode 17: We're End Here]
[Dual Love]
Senior Brother,
how do you feel?
-I'm fine.
-Dad.
This minor injury is nothing.
It's a good thing you moved quickly when I unleashed my power.
Otherwise, your internal injuries could have been severe.
Your power was truly impressive this time.
You instantly knocked out all my internal energy.
Master.
This time, Daodao can dominate the martial world.
Of course.
After all, she's my daughter.
Dad,
we've now been drawn into the power struggle at court.
What should we do next?
Master.
I... want to go to the capital to investigate.
I'll go with you.
Daodao,
this time it will be far more dangerous than the last.
Senior Brother.
Uncle Lu died unjustly.
We must avenge him.
This time coming to the capital,
I must get a clear explanation from Mo Haoran.
Okay.
You've all grown up.
Those in the martial world should experience hardships.
I won't stop you.
Go.
With me here, guarding Yanhua Mountain,
this place will always be our home.
Senior Brother?
Is something bothering you?
Tell me about it.
I thought...
that without the barriers of good and evil separating us,
we might still be able to be together.
But...
it still doesn't work out.
He is a Marquis.
He always has to put the Emperor's orders first.
Today, he can set a trap for the Emperor;
tomorrow he'll have to set another.
These conspiracies and games are too cruel.
Senior Brother.
Tell me...
how can he be so ruthless?
The imperial court and the martial world
are two different worlds after all.
He and I
end here.
Master.
Where's the antidote?
Here, let me.
Come on.
The antidote...
There are only two pills of antidote left.
It's okay.
Let's take a medicinal bath.
Yuan Ying.
Haven't you realized it yet?
The medicinal bath
can't detoxify the Jialan Poison at all.
Marquis of Ningyuan.
I've troubled Your Majesty
by having you come to my villa.
I...
I deserve death for this.
You have done so much for me.
How could I not show some understanding?
Xu Ruolian and the others have all been arrested.
The Blood Pagoda has been completely wiped out.
Fortunately, I...
have not failed in my mission.
Are you here to assassinate the Master?
The Master has been severely poisoned.
He doesn't have much time left.
There's no need for you to do it.
What are you talking about?
At that time, he was already severely poisoned
and had lost too much blood.
He even...
The Master really has feelings for you.
Really?
You underestimate the Master's feelings.
Mo Haoran is ruthless and takes lives lightly.
How can someone without a heart claim to have genuine feelings?
You mean Lu from the Scorpio Gang, right?
He had already joined the Blood Pagoda a long time ago.
He was a spy planted by the Martial Arts Alliance among you.
You're lying.
Listen for yourself.
Xiao Maozhong has used Xu Ruolian,
Yu Xuan, and others as his pawns...
causing countless loyal officials to suffer over the years.
He should be sentenced to death
without delay.
Yes.
Congratulations, Your Majesty, on finally assuming full power.
Wugui,
you've achieved great merit by quelling the rebellion
and capturing the rebel leader this time.
Whatever reward you want, just ask.
Five years ago...
I had just ascended the throne.
Empress Dowager Xiao wanted to take advantage of my youth
and control me completely, so she poisoned me.
Fortunately, you arrived on time
and saved me.
But you were poisoned by the Jialan Poison instead.
Since then,
you've built a reputation
as a ruthless and treacherous person,
secretly clearing obstacles for me to take full control
while dismantling the Xiao family's power step by step.
You've been so loyal,
yet you've been misunderstood by everyone in the country.
Wugui, I am willing to fulfill
any wishes you have.
Your Majesty, serving you
is my duty.
If you truly want to reward me,
please forgive me for the mistakes I made back then.