(In Between)
(Episode 23)
Zhou Bin will be detained
for three days for assault.
Just three days?
(Document
for Administrative Punishment)
(Offender: Zhou Bin)
I'll go
to the police station later...
and request to access
Zhou Bin's statement...
as evidence
of his extramarital affair.
No.
There's no need for that.
Why not?
We already have the evidence.
Why don't we use it?
Sun Han Han wants me...
to get rid of Zhou Bin for her.
We might as well...
let her testify in court.
I think I know what you mean.
You want her to appear in court.
I want to hear her...
confess in court.
Why are you doing this?
Ms. Wang told you, didn't she?
When I was with Zhou Bin,
you were divorced.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Besides, I have no idea
when you two got remarried.
I was deceived.
I know very well now
that Zhou Bin lied to both of us.
However, at this point,
that's not important.
You should know
what's most important.
What do you mean?
Have you thought about it?
Three days from now,
Zhou Bin will be released.
What will he do to you?
The only thing
that can truly unsettle a man...
is his career.
As long as
you're willing to testify,
I can bring
his career crashing down.
By then, let alone controlling you,
he won't even be able
to find his footing in Jiangzhou.
Even if you don't go to court,
my confrontation with Zhou Bin...
will still involve you.
Rumors will spread everywhere.
You'll be as disgraced...
as he is.
Are you really willing to help me?
I'm merely letting you know
the consequences.
Whether you come or not,
it's your choice.
If a person does something wrong,
he has to pay the price.
We can work together.
Mr. Gao.
Ms. Hu has told me...
that the compliant
cooperation agreement is ready...
and has been forwarded
to your secretary.
Here's the hard copy.
You can take a look.
I'm going to the conference room.
- Please check for me.
- Do you remember...
Mr. Gao from Hong Kong?
Gao Peng?
He's here to see Ms. Han again.
Thank you.
Mr. Gao.
Is there anything else?
It might not be a bad thing
that He Zhi Nan saw it.
The invisible barrier between us...
has finally been broken.
Did you call Zhi Nan?
She didn't answer my calls.
Han Su.
I like you.
That's why I'm willing
to use everything I have...
to support your passion.
No matter
what happens in the future,
please believe
that I'll always have your back.
Are you really going to ignore me
because of He Zhi Nan?
The three of us will get hurt.
What's the point?
Mr. Gao.
You're my...
Sorry to interrupt.
Ms. Han.
Ms. Hu is will be waiting for you
in the conference room one.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Are you fooling me?
He likes you.
You sure put on quite the act.
Faking orders is one thing,
but you're still holding
on to that laptop.
I don't think he's suitable for you.
What?
Trying to pin me against the wall?
I really like you.
You might not really like me.
Don't be fooled by yourself.
By the way,
I read the report
you sent over today.
The details are on point.
You're way sharper
than I was during my internship.
When I was your age,
I didn't know anything.
At that time,
did you like anyone?
What I figured out
earlier than you...
is that projects
and work matter most.
Men...
always come and go.
It's Ms. Hu.
Hello, Molina.
What's up?
Yes, I'm here.
After their company went public,
I casually quoted a price...
for legal support
in compliance business with Mr. Gao,
thinking he would negotiate.
To my surprise,
he agreed immediately.
You'll be in charge...
of this project.
I heard Gao Peng confess to you.
Why?
Don't you like him?
Molina, I'll be honest with you.
I don't have any expectations...
for love anymore.
I don't think...
I'll fall in love again.
Men can't provide me
with enough sense of security.
I want to rely on myself
for everything.
You know that a woman's instinct...
is to habitually invest
in love and family.
The reason there are fewer women...
at the top in various fields...
is that once they encounter love,
they no longer want
to conquer the world.
Instead, they start focusing...
on serving men.
That's why...
I don't want to get married.
I want to use my time
to conquer the world.
Can I ask you a question?
Imagine there is a certificate...
that can give you access...
to top-notch networks,
resources, and support.
Would you pursue it?
Of course.
What if...
it's the most prestigious
marriage certificate...
and Gao Peng...
is the certifier?
"The partner, Zhou Bin..."
"withdrew 10 million US dollars
from his personal account..."
"for Australian
investment immigration."
Immigration?
"This money was transferred..."
"through the law firm's
London office..."
"and eventually sent to Australia."
"Is that illegal?"
What does that mean?
Someone reported Zhou Bin
for illegal immigration.
Isn't that jerk at the law firm?
Why is he emigrating?
This should be
Zeng Cheng's second move.
Ruin his career...
and ensure he can't make
a living in Jiangzhou.
This woman...
is like the protagonist.
Come on.
Can you put yourself in my shoes?
I'm the fish on the chopping board.
You still think
this is a revenge film.
How about...
I ask Han Su to talk to her for you?
Han Su?
She...
She's Zeng Cheng's cousin.
Zeng Cheng's cousin?
The lawyer in Hong Kong?
She told me recently.
She said she understands you,
but because her relationship
with Zeng Cheng is close,
she can't get too close to you.
Will she speak up for me?
Let's give it a try.
Sure.
Zeng Cheng.
Is it true that Zhou Bin
wants to immigrate?
I saw the screenshot of the report.
It has been circulating
in several groups.
It's basically true.
That's the effect I wanted.
Aren't you afraid...
he'll find out it was you
who leaked it?
As long as he clarifies
such a report promptly,
it doesn't count for much.
However, he's now in custody...
and has already missed
the best time to clarify.
This move of yours
is really ruthless.
The senior partner
of the law firm...
just called me.
I used the opportunity...
to inform them about the truth...
regarding Mr. Zhou's detention.
Photos of Zhou Bin being arrested...
are all over the Internet.
For those senior partners,
even if they don't care
about Zhou Bin's private life,
they will still worry
about how this situation...
affects the firm's reputation...
and the trust clients place in them.
I think these senior partners...
are currently holding
an urgent meeting...
to decide whether
to issue an official statement...
distancing themselves from Zhou Bin.
You're aiming to cut off
his source of support.
This is just the appetizer.
The main dish isn't here yet.
(Nan Nan)
I have to take this call.
Hello?
I have a favour...
to ask of you.
It's fine.
I'm at my cousin's place.
Don't worry.
I know what to do about this.
Nan Nan, how did it go?
She agreed.
However,
she can't ensure
how it will turn out.
What's the matter?
Actually, I'm a little scared.
When Zhou Bin gets out,
he'll surely come to me.
You can stay at my place.
There's no need.
Even if I come to your house,
it's just a temporary way to escape.
What needs to be faced
must still be faced alone.
If a relationship...
is wrong from the very beginning,
no matter how hard we try,
we will only stray further down
the wrong path.
It won't end well.
Zeng Cheng.
Do you still want
Sun Han Han to go to court?
She's young and pretty.
When she has the upper hand,
she's aggressive and merciless.
When she can't win,
she claims innocence.
That doesn't work for me.
However, we both know...
that when Sun Han Han
and Zhou Bin were together,
you were indeed divorced.
Zhou Bin...
has the ability
to distort right from wrong.
It's a piece of cake for him
to deal with a woman like her.
What do you mean?
Do you want to plead for her?
I just think...
Zeng Cheng, you're so smart.
You should know deep down...
that continuing this struggle
with Zhou Bin...
won't lead to anyone truly winning.
Love can't be reclaimed,
but you can choose to move on.
Speaking of love,
I've lost it all a long time ago.
I admit defeat.
However,
everyone is equal
in the face of pain.
Regardless of whether
you're independent, successful,
rich or poor,
beautiful or ugly,
all women feel the same sadness...
when faced with heartbreak.
Zeng Cheng.
You're the strongest woman
I've ever met.
I believe you'll be able
to let go of this matter.
Su Su.
Being strong doesn't mean
you won't be hurt,
but being strong can guarantee
that you won't be defeated by harm.
How long it takes...
to heal this wound...
is a personal choice.
Some people choose to forgive...
and empathize with their enemies.
That, of course,
is a form of strength.
However, I'm...
not that kind of person.
So you want to strike back?
Only by retaliating...
and seeing them accept punishment...
and pay the price...
can I start...
to heal my wounds swiftly.
Here.
Thank you.
Han Su.
I told you.
Call me Ms. Han at work.
What are you doing?
The desk won't go up.
Here, let me help you.
Here.
This should be here.
Well...
I've been granted the qualification
to conduct my defence.
Congratulations.
Is that all?
What else?
Do you want me to pull strings
and leak the questions for you?
How is that possible?
If you do so,
how can I pursue you in the future?
What I mean is,
I'd like to treat you
to dinner tonight...
to thank you for your help.
Hello?
Han Su.
Can I have dinner at your place?
Sure.
I already ordered hot pot delivery.
They have your favourite dishes.
You can't say no...
and you can't work overtime.
Okay, see you tonight.
I'm sorry.
I have plans tonight.
By the way,
remember to check your email.
You have work to do.
If you have any questions,
feel free to ask me anytime.
Submit it by tomorrow morning.
But...
I'm leaving. Bye.
Please fix the table
before you leave.
But I...
I got...
Wait.
Fix the table.
Seriously?
Han Han.
My cousin has a message for you.
She said...
instead of forgiveness,
what suits you better...
is punishment.
Thank you, Han Su.
Please tell Zeng Cheng...
that I'll see her in court.
It's okay.
Whatever they say,
it's their business.
We all know...
what the truth is.
That's all that matters.
If we're wrong, we admit it.
If you didn't do anything wrong,
no one can hurt you.
Well said.
I was worried
that you would hate me...
and not want to help me.
Actually,
I've never seen
this side of my cousin.
So rather than helping you,
I want to help her more.
Han Han.
We're friends.
You don't have to keep thanking me.
Besides,
there's no hatred between us.
Zhi Nan.
About Gao Peng,
- I...
- You don't have to say anything.
I trust you.
Thank you.
Who said...
friends don't have
to thank each other?
Come on, my friends.
Let's have a toast.
Think of it
the three of us are sworn sisters.
Cheers, my friends.
What are you laughing at?
Actually, since I was little,
I've never had many friends.
I've been convincing myself...
that people
don't have to have friends.
But you know what, Zhi Nan?
Do you still remember...
when we were
at the law firm in Hong Kong?
You told me...
that we are good friends.
It really shocked me.
Zhi Nan.
Thank you.
I finally have a friend.
That's so cheesy.
It's good to have friends.
There sure is a lot of material.
What do you mean?
Based on what you said,
I know you don't follow me.
Lately,
I've been working hard
to update my public account.
However, it didn't turn out well.
I think life is the best material,
but my life alone
isn't exciting enough.
With both of you,
it'll be a hit.
Sure.
For your career and dream,
I can authorize it for you.
I agree too.
However, you have
to make me look pretty.
The ending has to be happy.
It's best if I'm paired
with two handsome guys.
You're so pretty.
Wouldn't it be a pity...
if you don't get
to be the evil mistress?
How dare you, He Zhi Nan.
All right then. Tell me.
How many male secretaries
do you want?
Can I have as many as I want?
Don't you think
your version is too pessimistic?
Look. Let me read it for you.
"After countless times
of wandering,"
"the cutie is back to square one."
"After countless goodbyes,"
"she no longer expects anyone
to love her..."
"nor does she anticipate
loving anyone."
"She doesn't want
any more mistakes about love."
You're the one who told me
to be more sincere.
You can be more proactive
and more hopeful.
When I write that
she's being pursued and loved,
you think that's too much.
When I write that she's dejected,
you think it's too pessimistic.
What exactly do you want?
Hold on.
- Hello?
- Hello.
Are you Mr. Wang, the lock picker?
I'm sorry.
You have the wrong number.
I'll revise it.
We have Member's Day
coming up in a couple of days.
Would you like to join us?
This way, you can engage directly...
with our customers...
and understand better
what they prefer...
and look forward to it.
If you think it might be boring
to come alone,
you can invite your friends to join.
They can help us promote it
by sharing it on social media.
I'll see you then.
By the way, I have another matter
I want to talk to you about.
Go ahead.
It's about your script fee.
Can we pay you
on a commission basis?
What do you mean?
Well,
we really don't have money now.
All our funds are currently
tied up in the factory.
If you want cash,
could you wait
until we receive our salaries?
Is that okay?
You guys are so pitiful.
Don't worry.
I won't lie to you.
Okay?
This meal is on me today.
Think of it as a way
to wish our cutie great popularity,
okay?
Maybe next time we visit,
we'll get to try
a co-branded meal featuring it.
(Freshly prepared upon order)
How is it?
It's not good.
When it comes to
the two luckiest things in life,
one is doing what you love...
and making a ton of money from it...
and the other...
is meeting someone you like...
who likes you back.
The cutie clearly wants everything,
so why force her to choose?
That's the truth of life.
Luck is always scarce.
However,
if she keeps being so conflicted...
and unlucky,
who would want to have her?
You're right.
I'll revise it.
My cutie...
deserves a happy ending.
Being able to see such a sunrise...
is truly a benefit
for us hardworking night owls.
He Zhi Nan.
You're a genius.
(Cutie)
The little girl in the snow.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Look.
My freckles are still on my face.
My dimples are still there.
I'm still that girl
who easily falls for someone.
When I do,
I really get caught up in it.
I know...
many compliment me on being cute...
because I'm not pretty enough.
But that's fine.
Even if I'm not pretty,
even if no one loves me,
I'll still love myself.
I know...
some think I deserve it.
Letting go of
a decent rich boyfriend...
to pursue a handsome guy...
and then getting dumped.
I really do deserve it,
but that's all right.
I don't want
to suppress my feelings...
or calm my disappointment.
I want to be honest with myself.
If there's a next time,
I think I'd still choose
to stumble into the same pit.
That little girl in the past...
always felt...
she wasn't pretty enough...
and was constantly dissatisfied
with her imperfections.
However, so many years have passed.
Look.
I didn't turn
into someone beautiful...
or perfect,
but I've come to embrace
my imperfections.
Now, I have a new name.
My name is...
Cutie.
It's time to pay the rent!
Is anyone there? Open the door!
The door is locked.
Call him.
There's no one here.
How is it? Is the call connected?
Is it connected? Hurry up.
It can't get through.
How do we handle this?
- We fail to collect the rent.
- Call a locksmith.
Hurry up.
It's 306. Hurry up.
Call a locksmith.
It's unit 306. We need a locksmith.
Where did they go?
Hello.
The user you called...
Come on.
It hurts so much.
Seriously. How much do you owe them?
A lot.
Do you know what the worst part is?
It's like misfortunes
never come alone.
My boss fired me.
You lost your job as a modeller?
I don't know
what's wrong with me lately.
Why am I so unlucky?
The endless phone calls
haven't stopped..
and now the investor
has suddenly backed out.
I don't even know...
how much longer
Toys Universe can survive.
You won't give up, right?
You once said you liked it.
Liked it?
Doing something
just because you like it?
Isn't that something
only young people can afford to do?
I'm almost 30...
and all I talk about
is what I like and my dreams.
Don't you think that's immature?
But a lot of people like Cutie.
Everyone is looking forward to it.
Besides,
Member's Day is coming up.
Hang in there.
"Hang in there"?
Chu Yi, Liu Fu, and I...
have repeated these words
over and over again.
It's true.
After saying it so many times,
it just feels like a joke.
It's quite laughable.
I'm done with the story.
She went through many setbacks,
much heartbreak...
and countless breakdowns.
After endless wandering,
she came to understand...
how hard...
love can be.
But despite the difficulties,
she still held onto hope.
At the end of the story,
she didn't become a perfect girl,
but she saw her own charm and worth.
Instead of
feeling sorry for herself,
she set out on a journey...
toward a larger world
without looking back.
As for me,
I'm someone...
who is pretty careless...
and muddles through most things.
Well,
except when it comes to love.
But this time,
writing the cutie's story...
feels very different.
Why are you laughing?
It's really different.
What's different? Tell me.
I think I'm happy.
It seems like...
I've found what I like to do.
It's my dream job.
So I've decided...
to use all my savings
to help the cutie.
I want to be a shareholder
in Toys Universe.
I didn't expect that.
You're quite chivalrous.
Ms. He Zhi Nan, tell me.
How much do you plan to invest?
It's 30,000 yuan.
I haven't saved up any money.
I only have 34,000 yuan
left in my account.
Let me keep 4,000 yuan
as living expenses, okay?
Okay.
All my life,
I've never met...
anyone as straightforward as you.
He Zhi Nan.
Thank you.
Wang Zi Lu.
Happy to collaborate with you.
(Detention Center
of Jianan District, Jiangzhou City)
(Armed police on duty)
This is the court summons.
Our divorce case
is scheduled for trial...
next week.
(Court summons)
You're the one
who's behind all this, right?
I want a divorce.
We can discuss the divorce properly.
You don't have
to go to such extremes.
You used
these underhanded tactics...
to ruin my reputation
and take away my career.
Do you have to be so ruthless?
The reason
I can destroy your career now...
is that it was originally built...
on my support.
I'm just taking back
what I gave you before.
By the way,
Sun Han Han will be in court too.
What did you say?
Zeng Cheng.
Zeng Cheng!
Good morning.
Morning.
Mr. Zhou is back.
Mr. Zhou.
This is Mr. Zhu's office.
You can't come in.
Your belongings
are at the front desk.
Mr. Zhou.
Your primary business
is in the entertainment industry.
Your name is always associated
with celebrities.
In this industry,
reputation is everything.
Once your reputation is tarnished,
everything is over.
According to Article 27...
of the partnership agreement
of the law firm,
your actions constitute...
a significant loss to the firm's
reputation and finances...
due to intentional
or gross negligence,
fulfilling the conditions...
for mandatory withdrawal
from the partnership.