(In Between)
(Episode 2)
He Zhi Nan, wake up.
He Zhi Nan.
Your wage is going to be deducted.
- Morning, Han Han. - Morning.
- Morning. - Morning.
Good morning.
Morning.
Han Su, let me tell you something.
I just heard...
that the Hong Kong branch is asking for someone.
Really?
After the meeting earlier, the district lawyer Mr. Wu...
asked Ms. Xu if she has a suitable candidate.
What did Ms. Xu say?
She told him not to worry.
It seems like she already has someone in mind.
You're so quick to find out.
When filling out the intention survey for HR,
that was what I applied for.
Job opportunities in Hong Kong...
are very attractive to everyone.
But I have to remind you...
that you just became a second-year lawyer.
The work environment in Hong Kong...
is too stressful...
for a junior lawyer.
Why don't you practice in a familiar environment...
for another two years...
before you go there?
Of course,
the income in Hong Kong is much higher.
But the cost of living will also be higher.
Thank you, Ms. Xu.
You're very thoughtful.
But if it's possible,
I'd still like to seize the opportunity...
to work in Hong Kong.
Is there a personal reason?
I'll be honest with you.
The company already has someone in mind.
There's also the language barrier issue.
That's not a problem.
I've been learning Cantonese on my own for a year.
I just hope that the company...
will give me a fair chance to compete.
You came prepared.
Okay.
If you insist.
Go and prepare the application.
But you have to know that the final decision...
is with the major partner in Hong Kong.
Thank you, Ms. Xu.
Han Su.
I'm just curious.
You'll have to spend three years in Hong Kong.
What about your Handsome Qu?
Can you bear to part with him?
He'll definitely support me.
That's good.
Let me see.
Hi.
Xiao Peng.
I sent you an article yesterday. Did you read it?
I did.
It's still early for the meeting.
Why don't we go to my office? I want to hear your thoughts.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Miss.
The client hasn't signed in.
Mr. Qu is my friend from Yinzhong Capital.
Just check the box.
Don't you think...
Ms. J is the type of mistress...
coming from a poor background...
who is desperately climbing up the social ladder in telenovelas?
Have you fallen for the handsome guy?
I do like idol dramas, but I'm not stupid.
These high achievers...
are mostly from small cities.
They want to settle down in a big city.
At a time like this, Ms. J has the money and resources.
She definitely has more advantages...
than innocent, young, and pretty girls.
And Ms. J won't force him to get married.
He can have a romantic relationship with an independent older woman...
and not take responsibility.
Why not?
Hello.
What's your name?
Hello. What's your name?
Let me check. Excuse me.
(Qu Yi Peng: I couldn't say hi to you earlier.)
(Let me thank you for saving me a seat.)
(It's nothing. Don't mention it.)
It's the handsome guy from the food stall.
A lot of girls in our office think he's handsome.
They shared his photos in the group chat.
They said he looks like Xin Yunlai.
How can he be compared to him?
I say, aesthetics have been downgraded.
I think he's quite handsome.
Coupled with the label of a famous company finance man,
he's of top-notch quality.
Creativity means competitiveness.
It also means facing the unknown.
Compared to being fearless,
I enjoy...
facing the fear and doubt of the unknown more.
You're only eating lunch now?
I just finished the final summary...
of the Melon Seed King project.
Golden Harvest is such a big award in advertising.
Even winning it once, I'll be satisfied for life.
Ms. Zeng has won it three times.
She's immune to it.
She's amazing.
When I'm out of ideas, I listen to her lecture.
I always learn something out of it.
Next time,
I should invite her to the company...
to give us a seminar.
Ms. Xin.
Do you know Ms. Zeng well?
She's kind of my mentor.
I see.
This is what they call...
a good teacher produces a good student.
When did you learn how to suck up to others?
But to be honest,
Ms. Zeng is really amazing.
No matter how difficult and boring a project is,
it's always something new in her hands.
Her way of thinking and execution...
is just different from others.
Hi, my babies.
I'm back.
- Monica. - Monica.
You're finally back.
Long time no see. Come.
I came back today...
to give out wedding candies.
It's like I'm back visiting my parents.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations, Monica.
She just did one project with you...
and turned your client into her husband.
I'll go out first.
I brought everything. Hand them out.
Monica.
It has been a while.
Ms. Xin.
I didn't expect you to get married so soon.
- Congratulations. - Thank you, Ms. Xin.
Here, this is for you.
- Thank you. - Come this way.
- So how are you? - Pretty good.
It's my fault.
I've loved Norse mythology since I was little.
To fulfil my dream, Sun took the whole family...
to a Nordic castle to hold the wedding.
Time was tight too. It was really tiring.
Your husband is so good to you.
He's all right.
I just got back last week.,
so I'm still jet-lagged.
But I wanted to see everyone.
- It must be tough. - Monica.
Congratulations on your wedding.
Han Han, this is for you.
Thank you.
I haven't thanked you properly.
What for?
In my heart,
I regard you as my matchmaker.
If you didn't take me on the project,
I wouldn't have met Sun.
Mrs. Sun, congratulations.
Mr. Li, please don't call me that.
Just call me Monica.
Very well. May you have children soon.
Thank you, Mr. Li.
During the economic transformation,
China's macroeconomy...
has generally maintained a rapid growth.
A large group of outstanding entrepreneurs...
stood out from the crowd.
Countless small businesses...
have grown into modern mega conglomerates.
However,
many companies were also affected...
by economic cycle fluctuations at the macro-level...
during their growth process.
Or they couldn't adapt...
to the requirements of economic development...
and the demand for industrial upgrades...
on a micro-level.
Or perhaps...
there were financial crises due to illegal operations...
and so on.
The competition mechanism under market economy conditions...
has caused some corporations in the entire economic system...
to put on a comedy show,
while other corporations...
put on tragedies.
What's more, some corporations...
have become a confluence of comedy and tragedy.
Without a doubt, Delong Group...
has become a typical example of this confluence.
(Qu Yi Peng: Zhi Nan, you have to help me.)
(A girl keeps pestering me.)
(If you don't agree to meet with me tonight, I...)
Delong Group was a small colour photo enlargement shop...
registered in Urumqi...
in 1986 with 400 employees.
After 18 years of development,
in 2004,
the company has developed...
into a multipurpose, multi-industry,
multiregional, and multinational company.
Sorry.
I rushed, but I'm still late.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Ms. J just wouldn't believe that I had an appointment.
I even showed her the message of the restaurant's location.
She still didn't believe me.
She even insisted on driving me to the restaurant.
That's when she gave up.
Ms. J likes handsome guys from prestigious schools.
"Handsome guys from prestigious schools"?
Do you think I'm one too?
He's so good at flirting.
Actually, it's not just about looks.
Education too.
He must be from a prestigious local university.
Since it has to be a prestigious school,
then are Ivy League schools within her consideration?
To be able to go to an Ivy League school,
then his family must be rich.
She doesn't care about having a rich lady image.
Is that so?
Take a look at what you want to eat.
I chose this Western restaurant without knowing what you like.
By the way, where are you from?
I'm from here. I can eat anything.
Being a local kid is lucky.
When it comes to rent, it's a lot less stressful.
Do you live with your parents?
I live alone.
My parents bought me a house.
How nice.
Unlike us from out of town.
We have worked hard for years,
but buying a house isn't considered.
Can I take your order?
Perilla pasta.
Caesar salad. Freshly squeezed watermelon juice.
And tiramisu. Thank you.
I'll have a grilled chicken breast salad.
And a bottle of this red wine.
- Okay. - Thank you.
Is he on a diet?
Or is he trying to humiliate you?
Don't get me wrong.
I'm doing this to complement you.
You eat so much, but you're still so skinny.
You must be the envy of so many girls.
It must be nice to be young.
An old man like me...
has to control his calorie intake.
I have to work out too.
How's your workout going?
I'll show you when I have the chance.
That's too forward.
He Zhi Nan, be careful.
I'm kidding.
After I started working,
I haven't had much time to work out.
But at university, I was in a fitness club.
Every year, we have a bodybuilding competition.
I'm a judge now.
I'll show you the young guys...
who works out next time.
I'll introduce them to you.
Sure.
I love meeting handsome guys.
By the way, the first time I saw you,
you left quite an impression on me.
Why?
It's rare to see a girl...
so naturally relaxed...
and humming a song in the office.
I'm not very good at it,
but the song is quite catchy.
After I heard you hum the other day,
I couldn't help but hum it when I got home.
The key is a bit...
It's a bit like...
a fruit candy, it's sweet.
Excuse me, miss.
Thank you.
Here.
Let's eat.
The cab is almost here.
I'll send you home first.
It's this one. Get in.
I'm here.
I'll take you downstairs.
It's okay.
I don't want you to wait for another cab.
Okay. Let me know when you get home.
I'll get going.
Qu Yi Peng.
What is it?
This is for you.
I'll leave the blueberry flavour for you.
I'm off.
Bye.
Let's go, sir.
Sir, please go around the neighbourhood once.
Then go back to the place we were just at.
- Okay. - Thank you.
He's from Liuzhou.
He has a dad and two younger sisters.
His biggest wish...
is to build a new house for his dad...
and open a milk tea shop...
in his hometown for his younger sisters.
It's obvious he's a white-collar guy from a working-class background.
What are you saying?
You just like to label people.
He doesn't look like one.
But...
But his study days weren't easy.
He went to a boarding school during middle school...
in the county.
On the first day of school,
his dad took a three-hour bus ride...
to get to school.
He had a large woven bag in his hand.
There was a quilt inside...
that his sisters made for him...
and fruits they picked from the trees.
At the time, his dad...
was drenched in sweat.
Standing in front of the school...
was my dad who came all the way here.
He got out of the bus drenched in sweat...
and walked towards me.
There was a girl.
She was my deskmate...
who was the daughter of the county leader.
She was disgusted...
and covered her nose.
She was disgusted by my dad's sweat...
and the smell of dirt.
I'm actually quite an uninteresting and boring person.
I have no hobbies.
I'm like a crop in a field.
Rooted in the ground,
it grows straight.
No distractions.
It only has one goal.
It's to go up...
and up.
Go beyond the mountains...
and live a good life.
Generally speaking,
men like to brag...
about how great they are.
This guy is clearly outstanding.
But he showed me his most vulnerable side.
After this conversation,
I think he's someone very pure...
and sincere.
Like someone I've known for a long time.
We are sorry to inform...
that Flight G1012...
has been delayed due to the weather.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
I'm doomed. The flight is cancelled.
What now?
What else can I do?
Wait for the announcement.
Including 45 securities firms,
28 accounting firms,
and 49 law firms.
Do you know that the competition for this project is fierce?
Yes.
Tell me about your team's strengths.
Okay, let me introduce them.
We're the leading team in corporate finance.
In the past three years,
we've successfully assisted over 20 companies...
to go public in Hong Kong.
The team members we've equipped for this project...
are all IPO experts.
They have a lot of experience in going public...
and a deep understanding of the industry.
Let me add one more thing.
We have offices in mainland China and Hong Kong.
Our biggest advantage is that...
we can provide your company...
a one-stop legal solution through internal cooperation...
between our team of Chinese lawyers and Hong Kong lawyers.
For matters involving legal projects in both places,
you don’t need to deal with two teams at the same time.
We can solve it once through internal collaboration.
Our team provides round-the-clock legal services...
to make sure you get immediate assistance.
(There's a good tiramisu place south of the city.)
(How about going together in the next few days?)
Temperature's going up...
and so is your heart rate.
It's just tiramisu.
And it's going up?
It's not.
Every time you argue with Gao Peng,
you watch movies and reminisce about the past.
Then you are able to forgive him.
Why are you relying...
on tiramisu this time?
You don't want to fix a broken relationship.
You just want to steal a new one.
If a relationship can never get old,
who would want a new love?
When are your parents coming back?
My parents...
are playing mahjong at my second aunt's house...
until after midnight.
When...
I really want to go back.
I really want to go back...
to when we were just together.
You don't want tiramisu anymore, do you?
As long as I still have Gao Peng in my heart,
it doesn't matter if I go or not.
- Then I'll go. - Then don't go.
Han Han, check your email.
Mr. Li said the client gave a suggestion for the proposal.
It'd be best if you could revise it overnight.
You'll have to work hard.
You must send it to me as soon as possible.
- Okay. - Can anyone solve this problem?
That's right.
We've been waiting for so long for the announcement.
Get your boss here.
You're all disregarding the matter. Get your boss here now...
to give us an explanation.
Which one of you is the boss?
I'm sorry.
Ms. Sun, are you okay?
Are you not feeling well?
Don't stay here. Come with me.
Here.
- Thank you. - Don't mention it.
Hello, guests.
These are some tea and snacks for you.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
The waiting time for your flight might get longer.
Sir.
If you need supper,
you can take a look at the menu.
Okay.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
Take a look first.
Please upgrade this lady's seat on the flight.
- Thank you. - Yes, sir.
You don't have to. It's okay.
I'm just redeeming the mileage.
It's free of charge.
Thank you then.
It's nothing. Don't mention it.
You don't look it.
You're so young,
but you're a workaholic.
We're the same.
The upgrade really makes a difference.
With the upgrade,
he can openly sit next to you.
It's a three-hour flight.
The purpose is obvious.
Is that so?
But I didn't wash my hair today.
And my clothes are all over the place.
Plus, I have a stomachache.
I'm in bad shape.
Mr. Zhou, welcome on this flight.
Your seat is over here.
He's here. I have to go. Bye.
Ladies and gentlemen, our flight is about to take off.
Please fasten your seat belts...
and put your phones in flight mode. Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen, our flight is about to take off.
Please make sure...
Su Su.
There's a new Japanese restaurant downstairs.
Let's try it for lunch.
Ms. Shan, thank you for the fragrance.
It's nothing. Lunch is on me.
Ms. Shan.
Just say what's on your mind.
Come with me.
Here, sit down.
Su Su.
I heard you submitted an application to go to Hong Kong.
Yes.
As you know,
my parents both live in Shenzhen.
I've been applying to the company to go to Hong Kong.
It wasn't easy for me to get this chance.
You still have a chance.
Han Su, what I'm trying to say is,
you're still young.
On the account that you were my apprentice...
for a few days when you first joined,
I hope that you can withdraw your application.
As far as I know,
I'm not the only one who submitted the application.
But even if there are more competitors,
as long as you're capable enough,
this opportunity will be yours.
Ms. Shan.
I'm very grateful.
When I first joined the company,
you took care of me for a few days.
But that alone...
isn't enough to make me give up on my goal.
Besides, the selection is decided by the Hong Kong branch.
We're just competing fairly.
The season is changing. My nose is a bit allergic.
I can't use this, but thank you.
Han Su.
Give it to Xiao Qu.
Is he okay with you going to Hong Kong?
That's my business.
What's with that attitude?
I've seen people with no EQ,
but not as low as yours.
So shameless.
In our law firm, there's no shortage of sharp tongues.
However, a disciple talking back to the mentor in person...
is rare.
Zhao Shan took me to my workstation on my first day at the company.
That was all.
Other than that,
she never taught me anything valuable.
So I don't think of her as my mentor.
There are some things that only you need to know.
Why do you have to say it in person?
Because it's more efficient this way.
I don't have to spend time greeting her and smiling at her,
and beating around the bush.
If so, it'll take at least 30 minutes.
I don't have that kind of time...
nor the energy or ability...
to delve into these office small talks.
It's not that you don't have the energy...
or the ability.
You just don't care.
Ms. Xu.
I know you're reminding me this...
for my own good.
I thank you.
But you don't plan to change either.
That's right.
You're an honest person.
Don't change if you don't want to.
I don't have the interest...
or the energy to mediate anyway.
From the perspective of a boss,
I don't mind.
As for the others,
as long as you don't care about them,
it doesn't matter.
Thank you, Ms. Xu.
People who stand up for themselves...
tend to unconsciously build iron walls around themselves...
for support.
As someone who has the experience,
I want to remind you...
that these iron walls...
can sometimes trap you instead.
That feeling of loneliness...
is not pleasant.
You're back.
Have you eaten?
Yes.
Last week, I introduced you to my senior from Huineng Group.
How did the meeting go?
The project...
hasn't been set yet.
I don't think it's going to happen.
Their company's lithium technology is state-of-the-art.
New energy source is the current trend.
You can't just look at the surface.
You have to put in some effort.
Investigate properly...
and research seriously.
"Investigate properly and research seriously"?
Why do you sound so much like my boss?
He only sleeps five hours a day.
He despises anyone who sleeps eight hours a day.
We're doomed.
He suspects us of slacking off in the office all day.
The way you said that is exactly like...
those old-timers in our company.
They can't do their job well.
They're stuck in their comfort zone.
Yet they mock people who work hard for being arrogant.
What do you mean?
I meant it literally.
For the past two years,
I've always heard you complaining about your boss.
But...
shouldn't you look for the reason in yourself?
From what you're saying,
you think I'm too slow to get promoted and get a raise.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Forget it.
The lid of the pickled bamboo shoots jar is not closed properly.
The smell won't get out for half a day.
You don't like the smell?
I just don't like the smell of always being in the house.
This is the smell I've smelled since I was little.
My sister made it herself.
I held it and rode the train for over ten hours...
to bring it back.
I'm just a country bumpkin...
who made it to where I am today.
If I don't smell this for three days,
I'll feel uncomfortable.
If you don't like it, just say so.
Let's be objective.
Not liking it and rejecting it are two different things.
Don't exaggerate.
I'm exaggerating?
The first time I made the noodles for you,
you said it tasted heavenly.
The taste of the noodles never changed.
Could it be that you've changed?
I loved it then and I still love it now.
I just don't like the smell of the sour marinade.
The ventilation in this house is bad.
The smell can't get out. That's the truth.
That's all.
I don't think the bamboo shoots are the problem, it's you.
After all this talk, you finally got to the point.
Yes, the problem is me.
I'm from a poor background.
And I don't work hard.
When I don't finish my writing, I can still sleep.
That's not progressing.
That's a sin.
I stayed up all night for you.
I didn't complain at all.
Thank you, Han Su.
You don't have to complain.
What you said is true.
I can't be as strong and hardworking as you, Superman Han.
I deserve to be despised.
You're trying so hard to hide your hatred,
acting like you care about my pride.
But let me tell you,
it hurts more than just looking down on me.
Qu Yi Peng, be fair.
I just can't stand it...
when you don't finish your work,
but can still sleep peacefully.
It's the truth...
that I can't say out loud or not tell you either.
What should I do?
- What did I do wrong? - You didn't do anything wrong.
I'm the one at fault.
My existence is a mistake.
I think you want to say...
it's my existence that's a mistake.
No. What do you mean?
(Four-year anniversary, tomorrow)