(In Between)
(Episode 3)
I think you want to say...
it's my existence that's a mistake.
No. What do you mean?
Hello, Mom. What's up?
Ms. Han.
I've been calling you all day. Why didn't you pick up?
I was in a meeting. What's the matter?
Xiao Qu...
bought me a smart speaker...
called Tmall Genie.
But I don't know how to use it.
Teach me.
Isn't there a manual?
If you really don't know how, I'll find you a video tutorial.
If I understood the manual,
why would I look for you?
It said something...
About connecting Bluetooth. What's Bluetooth?
- Mom, I have to work overtime. - Ma'am.
Ma'am.
Su Su doesn't know either.
You can ask me. Yes.
Xiao Qu.
- You've lost weight. - Have I?
Well, I must be too tired lately.
By the way, ma'am,
go back to your phone's main page first.
Then find the icon for settings.
Did you find it?
Then look for Bluetooth.
Yes. Then...
Then lots of options will pop up.
Just look for Tmall Genie.
Then press on it. See if you can connect to it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sorry too.
I forgot to tell you.
I'm going to Shanghai for a business trip tomorrow.
For three days.
Okay.
I'm going to Shanghai for a business trip tomorrow.
For three days.
(Four-year anniversary)
(Tiramisu)
This time, we're targeting the youth market...
in first-tier and quasi-first-tier cities.
In this new round of advertisements,
we'll mainly emphasize...
the product's appearance and social attributes.
How do we emphasize that?
First, build the socialization of the brand.
Second, we will use the hot spot to become the centre of attention.
This is a very crucial step.
Third, the customization of the product.
You can take a look at the information you have.
If there's anything you don't understand...
or you want to ask,
you can ask me directly.
The proposal is going well.
The project director is quite satisfied.
Now, it's up to the chairman.
That's great.
Thank you, Han Han.
Ms. Xin, can I go back tomorrow?
I can't take overnight flights anymore.
No problem.
You've been working so hard these few days.
Thank you, Ms. Xin.
Don't you admire Ms. Zeng?
She just gave a talk on insider creative techniques.
Do you want it?
Sure. Send it to me then. I want to study it.
Okay, I'll send it to you now.
(Uncle: This is Zhou Bin.)
(Mr. Zhou, you haven't returned to Jiangzhou yet, right?)
(I'm done with my work here. If you're free, )
(I'd like to treat you to a meal to thank you for your chivalry.)
(Haha, you flatter me. How about dinner?)
(Hangzhou Yuelai International Hotel.)
(Rucheng Advertising)
Last night, my mom nagged me.
She said my second aunt is worried.
She cries with her every day.
What is my mom worried about?
That you and Qu Yi Peng haven't gotten married.
She doesn't dare to rush you.
So she beat around the bush and asked me to persuade you.
Have you talked to Qu Yi Peng about going to Hong Kong?
I'm still fighting for the chance.
I'll talk to him after I get it.
You want to go to Hong Kong so badly.
Is it because of that person?
You know it.
Ever since I found out he's in Hong Kong,
everything I've done is to get close to him.
Is it for revenge?
Remember.
You're doing this for yourself.
To fight for a better future.
Whether this person exists or not, you'd do the same.
Don't think too much.
What about Qu Yi Peng?
What are you going to do?
When I first started dating him,
I looked up to him.
At that time,
just a glimpse of his attention,
his smile,
would make me excited.
I haven't had that feeling...
in a long time.
You were a young girl...
who had just started graduate school.
Su Su, you've grown up too fast.
Relatively speaking, he's still at a standstill.
You went from looking up to him,
to looking at him levelly,
or even scrutinizing him.
You just can't accept this kind of gap.
He...
disappoints me a little.
But you can't bear to part with him...
for real.
He's really nice to me.
Su Su.
Actually, growing up requires learning...
how to live with disappointment.
You can ask yourself.
During the four years you were with him,
you were truly in love.
For the sake of this sincerity,
is hanging in there worth it?
Or putting in more effort?
- We'll get going then. - Bye.
Let's get going too.
- Let's go. - Nan Nan, we're leaving.
- Okay, bye. - Let's go, Shi Shi.
- Ms. Nan, I'll get going. - Bye.
I've been waiting for Tiramisu and heard nothing from him all day.
It's almost time to get off work...
and he sent me a song, "Night Life, Take Us to the Light."
What do you think he means?
Yes. What is he hinting at?
He's just sending a love song to test you.
Don't reply. It's a trap.
I'm not going to reply.
Yes, for appointments that don't have a precise time,
it can only be considered courtesy or a trap.
Should I wait then?
Have a foot in both camps.
Do what you should do.
We should be steady and can't panic at first.
(Do you remember our tiramisu date?)
I'm back.
Aren't you on a business trip?
Why are you back?
I suddenly remembered this morning.
Today is our fourth anniversary.
I tried to use this excuse to tell Ms. Kai Xi...
to arrange for other colleagues to go.
A gift for you.
Every time we pass by this shop,
I can see that you're itching for this computer.
Su Su.
Thank you.
Time really flies.
It has been four years.
That's a whole university degree.
Yesterday,
I wanted to remind you.
I thought...
I'm sorry.
I didn't prepare a gift for you.
Just cook a meal for me.
No, go out with me. Let's go.
I really don't want to go out.
I just want to eat your cooking.
I'll cook for you when I come back.
Let's go out first. Come on.
- Let's go. - But...
Where are we going?
You'll know when we get there. Change your shoes. Hurry.
I'm not telling you. You'll know when you get there.
It's this one, right?
I know you've liked this for a long time.
Try it on.
Okay.
What do you think?
It looks good.
You look so elegant in it, miss.
It suits you.
- We'll take it. - Okay. I'll get you a new pair.
Thank you.
I have to take my sister's call.
- You can make the payment. - Okay.
Hello?
What's wrong? Why are you crying?
No, Dad just recovered.
Didn't I tell you not to let him work?
Don't worry. Stop crying.
I'll transfer the money to you.
Miss, this is brand new.
Would you like to try it on again?
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
If you like it, you can come back anytime.
(Transfer 2,000 yuan)
What happened?
My dad got hurt.
It's nothing serious.
Where are your shoes?
I tried walking in them just now.
The heels are too high. I'm not used to them.
And I thought about it.
I can't find the right occasion to wear them.
I asked the clerk if they had a shorter heel.
But they're out of stock.
We'll buy them another day.
Let's go home. I'm hungry.
Are you really not buying it?
No. It's already on your tab anyway.
You can't run away. Let's go.
Besides, it's almost the end of the season.
These shoes will surely be on sale.
You should be buying me the latest design.
Let's go.
I'm starving.
Starving?
I'll make you your favourite...
- Sweet and sour... - Spareribs.
Okay.
I'm not late, am I?
You're just in time.
I'll take you in.
Hello, sir.
- Mr. Wu. - Mr. Zhou is here.
- Mr. Zhou. - Nice to meet you.
- Mr. Zhou. - Mr. Zhou.
- You're finally here. Come. - Well...
I've arranged your seat.
Come.
You're too kind.
- I've arranged everything. - Miss, come here.
Miss, sit here.
- Here. - Yes, sit here.
- From now on, our firm... - No, sit down first.
Sit down first. Can you let me breathe?
- Okay. - This is my fourth glass.
It's our local speciality.
You can't get it anywhere else.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
It's easier to contact each other.
And last time, we...
- I'll scan your code. - I'll drink to you.
The last case was handled so beautifully.
I have to learn from you.
You're too kind.
- Come on, let's drink together. - Let's drink.
- Come on, let's do it together. - Thank you, Mr. Zhou.
Which dish do you like? I'll get it for you.
Hey, miss. I'm from this firm too.
Stay out of it.
- Come on, let's drink. - Let's drink first.
Drink up and refill.
Let's stretch and massage each other.
This is just the first day.
I'm afraid it'll be even more intense from now on.
Here.
Bear with it.
When are your parents coming back?
My parents...
are at my second aunt's house.
They won't be back until after midnight.
Did you just eat a cherry?
Where's the pit?
I swallowed it.
No. You just...
I suddenly got attacked.
If I spit out the pit,
the mood will be ruined, so I just...
I just...
It was hard to swallow. It got stuck in my throat.
Babe.
Hello.
Just now,
I was eating a cherry...
and accidentally swallowed the pit.
Swallowing the cherry pit must be uncomfortable.
No.
Didn't you swallow it too?
Did I?
Yes.
When we were watching "Love Actually".
"Love Actually"?
Sounds familiar.
Have we watched it?
Of course.
When we watched "Love Actually",
it was the first time...
The first time what?
No, tell me what the movie is about.
Gao Peng.
Do you remember...
the first time you kissed me?
What was it like?
Where was it?
It was at Kangting.
Right?
Let me ask you another question.
When...
you first held my hand,
we were singing in a Tibetan friend's tent.
Was the song "Tibetan Plateau"...
or "Over the Golden Hill of Beijing"?
You even sang?
It has been so long. I can't remember at all.
When those images come to my mind,
there's even background music.
How could you forget?
I didn't forget.
It's just that it has been so long.
No matter how much time has passed,
those were the most important moments...
in our lives.
How could you forget them all?
Gao Peng.
Babe.
Do you still love me?
Yes.
You say you miss me every day.
When do you think of me?
Do you...
think of the beautiful memories we had together?
Think about the songs we listened to together,
the food we ate together,
or the paths we took?
Do you really miss me?
What's wrong with you today?
I do miss you. I really miss you.
Then why?
Why don't you remember...
such beautiful memories between us?
Okay, I was wrong.
I forgot the movie.
I'm heartless.
But it's not that I don't miss you.
You're pretending. You're just pretending to miss me.
No, what do you mean?
What do you mean by pretending to miss you?
I've never heard of that phrase.
I...
He doesn't care about me at all.
I must break up with him this time.
It'll be so lonely if you really break up.
Can you imagine a life without love?
Gao Peng.
We met when we were 17.
We got together when we were 18.
It has been...
seven years now.
During the seven years we were together,
we experienced countless firsts.
But in these seven years,
the total time we actually spent together...
was only...
a little over 200 days.
You've never really known about my life.
I don't know about yours either.
But I've always lived on memories...
and greeting each other.
I thought you were the same as me.
That you've always been trying...
and treating every little detail of our relationship...
as proof of our love.
But you...
forgot all about it.
Are you really going to send it to him?
Should I?
Do you still love him?
Of course I love him.
He's the one who doesn't love me anymore.
If you love him,
why are you breaking up with him?
I'm not breaking up with him.
I just want to write an essay and complain to him about it.
But you just swore that you'd break up.
(Let's break up!)
So are you two considered broken up?
He read my heartfelt essay...
and hasn't replied in 24 hours.
That means he agreed to it.
I now announce...
that I, He Zhi Nan, am completely single.
The good news is...
you can have a relationship with Qu Yi Peng without any burden.
The bad news is, there's no news from Qu Yi Peng.
You're lying.
You did a high-quality facial mask.
Would you be willing to do that if not for a date?
It's human nature. We need something to live for.
This melon doesn't seem ripe.
But it's sweet.
It's all right.
Be honest with me.
If Qu Yi Peng didn't exist,
would you still be so decisive to break up with Gao Peng?
Now I wish...
that Gao Peng would come back...
and have an argument with me.
A fight is fine too.
It's better than being stagnant like this every day.
If it doesn't work out, then focus more on work.
You're a city beauty, an independent woman.
But you don't care about work at all.
What's there to care about?
Folding bills into roses?
I can't be bothered with you.
Can you do me a favour?
A client wants to come to watch the revised advertisement.
I need to borrow a heavy weapon from you.
Got it.
Every bag here...
is proof that he stood me up.
I wish to be stood up like this too.
Who can buy them for me?
Aren't you an independent woman who's pursuing your career?
Why do you need someone to buy you a bag?
Being able to buy it myself...
is different from having a man willing to buy it for me.
Babe. Which one do you like?
Is it Gao Peng?
Did he send it wrongly?
Hello, are you Ms. He?
Please sign here.
(Mr. Gao Peng's purchase forwarding)
(Ms. He)
Gao Peng still loves you.
That's a lot.
Let me tell you.
How much is given is how much love there is.
He loves me?
But he doesn't even want to give me a call...
or talk it out.
Buying gifts is much better than calling.
Anyone can sweet-talk.
What Gao Peng has done is called sincerity.
What? What are you doing?
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
What are you doing?
- I know you're mad. - I've shed so many tears.
- Was it just to get these things? - Don't.
Don't be crazy.
The things are innocent.
Who cares?
You... My goodness.
Don't.
You're mad at Gao Peng.
Why are you mad at them?
My goodness.
They're such nice things.
Why throw them away?
Who cares about these things?
Okay.
Don't cry.
It's such a waste to sell these secondhand.
What's the point of keeping them?
The money from the sale will all be donated.
He wasn't like this before.
Now that he has money,
the things he bought become more expensive.
(I'm annoyed and tired! I'm getting rid of these.)
(What do you guys think?)
He gave me less and less affection.
Also...
(What happened? Did you break up?)
(Sometimes, what's missing is not a bag, but a word. Cheer up.)
(I get you! I've gone through a similar experience.)
(Must a problem that can't be solved with bags. Sell them!)
(He missed out on you and has nothing, )
(but you have yourself and these bags.)
(Be grateful because it's the last bit of wealth he left you.)
Are you selling this too?
I remember you told me...
in order to buy this for you,
Gao Peng starved for half a semester.
Gao Peng's family used to be poor.
When his house hadn't been demolished yet,
his parents tightened their belts...
and cobbled together money...
to send him abroad to attend university.
When I was a sophomore,
there was a girl in my dorm.
Her boyfriend...
Her boyfriend bought her a pendant of the same brand.
I was so envious.
I brought it up...
to Gao Peng casually.
Gao Peng.
Who told you to buy me this bracelet?
What will you eat now?
Working after school is hard enough.
You should save some money to buy yourself good food.
You're driving me crazy.
Babe.
You're so cute when you're mad.
I'm not joking with you.
No. Don't you always say that I'm fat?
I'll take not eating as a diet.
Who told you to go on a diet?
I don't want you to skip meals because of me.
But I don't want you to be envious of others.
I just don't want you to suffer.
You must have what others have.
When I make money,
I'll let you have what others don't have.
We won't be envious of others anymore.
Put the bracelet on and show me.
This is my most...
most favourite thing during those years.
I often couldn't bear to wear it.
Later on, Gao Peng gave me more and more gifts.
But only this bracelet contains his love.
We won't sell it no matter what.
Qu Yi Peng, help me get the pyjamas on the bed.
Okay.
Coming.
You're pricing them randomly.
People will think they're fake items.
What does he mean by this?
(Qu Yi Peng: I'm really sorry.)
(I wanted to invite you to tiramisu last week.)
(Are you free these two days?)
(I didn't mean to stand you up. My dad got injured suddenly last week,
(so I had to rush back to my hometown, )
(to arrange for his hospitalization and surgery.)
Will you go?
What say you?
I don't know.
Then let's not think about it.
Do you really want to sell it?
We've come this far.
Can we turn back?
If you don't want to sell it, then don't.
Why make it so hard?
If I sell the love of He Zhi Nan...
for only 499 yuan,
it'd be too cheap.
(Posted successfully)
I don't understand why women always want a promise.
He never knows what I want.
She never tells me. It's always me guessing.
Guessing and guessing.
Then she gets mad if I guess wrong.
He never makes me feel safe.
I don't know why.
No matter what I do,
she never feels safe.
In the beginning,
he would comfort me.
But now...
I'm tired.
Let her be.
The next one might be better behaved.
It has been three months since we broke up.
Every month,
he would text me to scold me.
So be it and break up.
Back then,
I bought her a new phone by instalments.
My money is still being deducted.
Deduction is successful.
The bank card you used on April 10...
has automatically repaid...
- Look. - the amount of 1,233 yuan.
It's deducted again.
(Bad woman)
(Missed out on a lover)