(In Between)
(Episode 16)
Zeng Cheng.
You must be hungry.
Let's eat.
You're spacing out.
What are you thinking about?
When I was a freshman,
Baidu search was a new trend.
It took me quite a while...
to teach my mom.
One time, I went home during a break.
I found the search history on my computer...
was all about husbands cheating on wives.
My mom was in the kitchen at the time.
The range hood...
was buzzing...
and through the crack in the door,
I saw her crying.
My dearest dad...
was one among countless men...
who made the one mistake he shouldn't have.
I think...
your mom and dad seem quite happy,
as if nothing like that ever happened.
Zhou Bin.
Tell me the truth.
Did the doctor say...
that my condition might be bad?
No matter what happens,
I won't remarry you.
This is my final decision.
This is my final stance.
Whether or not we remarry...
and no matter how bad the test results are,
I won't leave you.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
We've secured Hengliyan's project.
Congratulations. We'll sign the contract tomorrow.
Really?
Come on. Let's celebrate.
Thank you.
Cheers!
- Cheers! - Cheers!
Mr. Gao Peng specifically sent me an email,
praising Han Su,
saying you're diligent, responsible,
and highly capable.
He even copied all the partners.
The higher-ups have decided...
to give you an exceptional promotion...
to lead the entire project.
Han Su, well done.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations, Han Su.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
Thank you, everyone.
It's all thanks to everyone's hard work.
- Good! - Good!
Congratulations, Han Su.
Han Su is awesome.
Han Su, come here.
For this year's award,
I'm going to nominate you.
Thank you, Molina.
Thank you for your help all along.
I didn't do anything.
It was all your own effort.
Cheers.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Here's to the world's most powerful, all-rounded female warrior,
Ms. Han Su.
And to the silliest client's wife...
in the world.
Who's silly?
It's not bad.
It's delicious.
It goes so well with the sweet and sour wine.
A five-star rating.
Really?
I used to get criticized often...
when I cooked...
which made me lose confidence in my cooking skills.
Who criticized you?
Your ex-boyfriend?
What kind of person is he to be able to criticize you?
Tell me more.
It's all in the past.
There's nothing to talk about.
I'm just curious.
Why did you break up?
When I came to Hong Kong,
he had someone else.
He had someone else?
What kind of woman can steal a man from you, Han Su?
What a seductress.
Have you seen her?
She's actually...
very charming.
She has her own charm.
No way, Han Su.
You're taking her side at a time like this?
Are you a saint?
Actually, I broke up with him.
It has nothing to do...
with that woman.
How so?
We're both too...
Too rational, realistic,
and apathetic.
Moreover,
I don't really believe in love.
When it comes to relationships,
I don't want to waste too much time...
or opportunities.
That's why we're destined to break up.
He's probably like that too.
The more idealistic it is in the beginning,
the more chaotic it will be...
in the end.
Love...
may only exist for a brief moment.
only exists for a brief moment.
Han Su.
Do you think...
I shouldn't stay in Hong Kong?
Aren't you and Gao Peng doing quite well together?
The two of us...
have been trying hard to find...
the feelings we had before.
But at the same time, we both know...
that we're no longer the same people we used to be.
It seems difficult...
for both of us to adapt...
to each other's new selves.
Honestly, I have some guilt...
toward Gao Peng.
I fell in love with someone else while I was in Jiangzhou.
Gao Peng and I have been apart for too long.
In my life,
he's more like...
a chatbot...
on WeChat...
or to be blunt,
just an ATM in my life.
When I was at my most lost,
a guy appeared out of nowhere,
giving me affection,
care,
and meeting...
all my fantasies about love.
Stop it.
Why?
Are you silly?
Gao Peng is my client.
You've told me so many secrets.
What if I can't keep them and I tell him everything?
You won't tell him.
We're so close.
That guy actually has a girlfriend.
He broke up with her...
to pursue me.
He also knew about Gao Peng's existence,
but he said he didn't mind.
One day,
he told me he wanted to marry me.
I was so happy at that moment.
Why?
What do you mean why?
You love him so much.
Why didn't you stay with him?
He disappeared.
Disappeared?
Why did he disappear?
One afternoon,
I couldn't find him.
I couldn't find him anywhere.
He didn't reply to my messages.
I was dumped just like that.
He worked so hard to pursue you.
How did it end up like this?
Why do you think he worked so hard?
Well, after listening to what you said,
I think...
he's a bit strange.
Now that you mention it,
I think he's a bit strange too.
Han Su.
You're from a famous university.
Then your ex-boyfriend must be from the same university too, right?
He's from a famous university too.
The three of you might even know each other.
Zhi Nan.
I have something to tell you.
Actually...
It's my best friend.
Excuse me.
Han Han, what's up?
I arranged to meet Zhou Bin directly at the forum site of Zeng Cheng.
Are you sure you want to do this?
I'm not sure.
Nan Nan, I'm so anxious.
What would you do if you were in my shoes?
I'd run away if I were you.
The three of you are going to confront each other.
The thought of it sends chills down my spine.
(Zeng Cheng, Artificial intelligence...)
Zeng Cheng.
You're back to full health.
My health is all good now.
What a narrow escape.
That's good. Thank goodness.
I took a good rest for a while...
and Zhou Bin was always there with me.
For this love, I can give up everything.
I just want him...
to clarify everything...
in front of me and her.
What if...
I mean, what if...
he feels pressured or something,
wouldn't you be left with no way out?
Do you really want to remarry him?
Not long ago,
I lay on the hospital bed,
feeling utterly defeated and wishing I were dead.
Looking back, it still scares me.
In comparison,
having a bit of sand in my eye is nothing.
He's here. I have to go.
He promised me...
that we would start over.
He said...
that neither of us...
will bring up the past again.
He'll break up with her.
But do you still believe him?
What's more important than that...
is my willingness to believe him.
Actually,
I can only choose to believe.
He asked me to give him a chance,
but deep down,
I know I'm giving myself a chance.
Okay.
All right. I respect you.
Get back to work.
Bye.
What's wrong?
Why are you spacing out?
What did you want to tell me just now?
I...
I suddenly forgot.
I can't remember.
Come on.
You've lost weight.
I've been pulling all-nighters lately.
I know you've been taking care of her.
I've been pulling all-nighters too.
I have a lot on my mind every night.
I'm sorry, Han Han.
I'm jealous,
but I'm not completely jealous.
I think you're a loyal person.
Now I know...
how complicated it is to love someone.
My reservation is over there.
Let's sit down and talk, okay?
Okay.
(Technological empowerment and integrated innovation)
(Integrated Media Advertising Summit Forum)
You knew she was here, right?
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
I want you to hold my hand and walk all the way there...
to her.
I want us to confirm our love for each other under the sun.
Can you not force me?
I can let bygones be bygones.
However, for the future, you have to make a choice.
The three of us should meet face-to-face...
and talk everything out.
It's best for everyone.
Zhou Bin, I really can't believe your one-sided story anymore.
Sun Han Han.
Have you thought about the consequences?
Are you that confident?
Dear.
What a coincidence.
You didn't know I had a meeting here today, did you?
There are a lot of acquaintances inside.
Let's go in and say hello.
I have something urgent to do.
I can't do this. I have to go.
Dear.
Haven't you told her yet?
Zhou Bin.
What do you want to tell me?
You should go.
Let's meet next time.
What do you mean?
Just go.
I'm begging you.
- I'll get going then. - Stop right there.
I'm going to make you tell the truth...
in front of me and her.
Zhou Bin.
Tell us.
Zeng Cheng and I...
got back together.
Let's go.
There's someone I want to introduce you.
Are you sad?
No.
Don't misunderstand, Zeng Cheng.
I called her here to make things clear.
She overestimates herself...
and ends up shooting herself in the foot.
Who can do anything about it?
Ms. Zeng and Mr. Zhou, you are here.
It has been a while.
Han Su.
To you,
what's the perfect love?
The perfect love...
probably only exists in my imagination.
It's like two people...
appreciating and attracting each other...
under a certain vacuum condition.
It seems perfect.
However, once they come into contact with the air,
everything changes.
Fresh braised duck...
(Zhou Zhou)
(Chat messages)
(Settings)
(Block contact)
(Zhou Zhou)
(Confirm)
Fresh braised duck...
They may find themselves scheming and fighting...
due to the instability of the relationship...
and conversely,
become bored...
when the relationship feels overly secure.
Either way, it'll go against what they originally wanted.
That's right.
So the purest and most beautiful love...
is love that hasn't started yet.
How so?
When I was in high school,
my school was quite a distance from home,
so I often arrived early.
Often, the school gate wasn't even open yet.
At that time,
I'd always run into a boy.
(Jiangzhou Yi'an High School)
He didn't have a good reputation in our school...
because he was a bit of a troublemaker...
and his grades were just average.
We would often stand at the school gate,
one on each side.
We were too shy to look at each other.
We were like two stone lions.
Later on,
he started bringing me breakfast.
It was really cold in winter.
He took a bun from his pocket...
and tossed it to me.
It was steaming hot.
Sometimes,
he'd pass by our classroom...
and secretly glance at me.
He'd leave a few candies on my locker.
I also heard...
that he went to warn those who liked to chat with me,
telling them not to disturb my studies.
Do you like him?
He and I...
never spoke to each other...
the whole time.
Why?
I don't know.
It was like some kind of unspoken understanding.
Until we graduated,
we never really got to know each other.
However,
the steam of the bun...
and the texture of the chocolate...
still feels fresh when I think about it.
Love is like life.
As long as it never starts,
it will never end.
Why are you so pessimistic?
Love is still beautiful.
Are those your parents?
Your mom is so pretty.
You look like your mom.
Your dad is handsome too.
You can tell?
In my memory,
that man...
is nothing more than a blurry image.
In my family,
my dad doesn't exist...
and my mom never talked about him.
I found that photo by accident...
and my mom doesn't know I've seen it.
Thank you.
There's a gray hair.
Really?
Where?
Here.
You have good eyesight.
That day, you fell asleep at the hospital.
I woke up in the middle of the night...
and just watched you.
I didn't want to wake you, so I didn't pull it out.
When you first get...
a few strands of gray hair,
it can make you feel anxious.
But when you start getting more,
it doesn't matter as much.
When a flaw...
becomes something you can no longer avoid,
it eventually turns into a habit you simply accept.
(Fidelity agreement)
Is it necessary?
Yes.
I'll feel more at ease if you sign it.
I got it drafted by a lawyer you don't know.
You can still make any necessary changes...
if you have concerns.
(Zhou Bin)
I must emphasize once again the urgency of time at this stage.
Before we enter the printing phase,
starting tomorrow,
all of us...
including the company, all intermediaries,
underwriters, underwriters' lawyers,
and the company's lawyers...
will come together...
to thoroughly review, discuss, and revise...
the prospectus for the company's IPO,
as well as the documents we'll be submitting...
to the stock exchange.
The final materials will then be handled by the printing company.
(North Point)
One moment.
Okay.
Take it first.
Okay, thank you.
(What they mean by saying goodbye to the wrong person...)
Hey.
Is this how you announce being single on social media?
Your intentions for finding a partner...
are way too obvious, Sun Han Han.
Indeed,
young men are flocking to me like fish,
sending private messages, likes, and comfort.
My schedule is fully booked until at least the weekend.
You're not really planning...
to go on dates with so many people, are you?
It's not really a date.
It's just to unwind.
I can't be alone right now.
What about Zhou Bin's things?
Did you give them back to him?
That jerk can just die.
Why should I return his gifts?
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
The taste is identical...
to that of the small stall across the overpass...
from my home.
It'd be even better with some peanuts and edamame.
No problem.
Nan Nan, why did you call me back so urgently?
You're finally back. Here.
What's this?
Skewers.
You've been so busy lately,
so I made your favourite to reward you.
I recently got to know a girl who enjoys researching food...
and we hit it off.
I asked her to teach me.
Try it.
Is it good?
Is the meat too tough?
It's okay. Wait for a while.
It's good.
Leave it here.
Did you ask me to come back so urgently...
just to eat this?
I'm so busy with the company's IPO.
You didn't have to call me back just for a bite.
I've been busy all day.
You don't have to be so mean.
If you feel wronged, then don't do it anymore.
I'm going back to the office for a meeting.
Gao Peng.
You've changed.
You're ridiculous.
I'm now in charge of a company with thousands of employees.
I can't be at your beck and call.
Also, I'm not that interested in playing house with you.
I'm leaving.
How long do you think...
the printing process will take?
Usually, we work over 18 hours a day...
for about a week straight.
Eighteen hours?
Actually,
it feels like crossing into the gates of the underworld...
for us.
Only the most physically and mentally fit lawyers...
can withstand it.
It sounds like...
a complete transformation.
I'm looking forward to it.
Really?
Do you think...
I'm the kind of person...
who only knows how to have fun?
I didn't mean that.
Well,
it was fun at first.
However, after having too much fun,
I realized...
that happiness became light...
and bland.
Then it became boring.
Happiness is actually quite fair.
No matter who it is,
it's not that easy to get it.
Actually, to many people,
I'm just a rich, silly guy.
However, I still want...
to learn more things as soon as possible...
and manage the company well.
At the very least, I don't want to let my parents down.
I hope you can help me.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
I should thank you.
Ms. Hu took a screenshot of the email you sent...
and shared it in our firm's WeChat group,
earnestly complimenting me.
She said...
that receiving such recognition from a client...
is a great honour for our profession.
Your work has been impressive and you deserve all of this.
I still owe you a favour for this.
Thank you so much.
- Look up there. - I see it.
(Am I Pretty?)
Did you see the clouds?
Do you like me because I'm pretty?
It's because you're cute.
Honey.
Am I pretty?
You?
You look normal.
What do you mean by normal?
What do you mean by that?
- What? - Why do I look normal?
Who looks normal?
I'm asking if I'm pretty.
- You're pretty. - You said I'm normal-looking.
Do you like pretty girls that much?
It's not that I want to see them.
They pop up on my feed.
Can't you look at me then?
Am I ugly?
Let's eat.
You talk about this every day.
It's annoying.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
So...
ugly people...
don't deserve to be happy?
Don't you know what you look like?
Of course I do.
I know I'm ugly.
There are many things in this world that are more important than looks.
You're pretty.
After I'm gone,
you can go out and look around.
They'll all like you.
Gao Peng has changed.
He used to be very patient.
If you love him enough,
you'll be able to accept all his changes.
What does it mean...
to love enough?