(EXchange - Another Beginning)
(I'm being a little swayed right now.)
Finally, this is the last episode...
- of EXchange - Another Beginning. - Yes.
In the past, EXchange consisted...
of 20 episodes, wasn't it?
- Right. - Right?
Since this one is only eight episodes, it's very short.
I knew that it'd be short, but...
It's too short.
While watching the first episode,
I expected it to be...
fun and casual.
From friendship to flings,
- their emotions keep changing. - Right.
It became escalated especially after the 1st-come, 1st-served chat.
Yes, it's so much fun.
In the preview, they were making their final decisions.
I can't wait to find out...
how this show will end.
For Kwan Woo and Hye Seon,
we thought that they were a couple...
- from the start. - Right.
- However, - During their last conversation?
It seemed like they were falling out.
I wonder how it will turn out.
Finally, we will find out everything today.
After their 1-on-1 trip,
there will definitely be a change of heart.
- Right. - Definitely.
Let's watch how things change.
- I can't wait to find out. - There will be changes for sure.
(The day of their last trip on Jeju Island)
Hi.
- Hello. - Hey.
I was happy.
I thought that Hwi Hyun also wanted to get to know me better.
Whom did you expect?
I thought that it'd be you.
Were you waiting for long?
No, I just got here too.
"Oh, I'm relieved that it's Kwan Woo."
Let's draw each other's faces...
and our dog.
Let's wear the shirt tonight.
I should draw very well.
It was my first time looking at her up close.
I was nervous in the beginning.
There are wedding dresses here.
Are we getting married?
It made me feel strange.
It really felt weird.
The photo shoot made it feel like a real date.
It feels like we're on a honeymoon in Bali.
You're really good at posing.
(Everyone went on a 1-on-1 trip that made their hearts flutter.)
- You've got some on your nose. - It's delicious.
I've spent most of my time...
with Min Jae.
It made me rely on him.
Of all the four days,
was there a moment that made you the happiest?
It's right now.
- Right now? - Yes.
I felt comfortable around you.
He was an even better person than I thought.
I'm so cold.
Hurry. I'm cold.
- It looks pretty. - Isn't it cute?
You look like a model.
The T-shirt looks like a luxury brand on you.
It wasn't my intention to flirt with her.
She looked so pretty that I couldn't help but say it.
(Episode 8: Another Beginning)
(On their way back to Jeju Island House)
Let's get going.
I wonder what we will do back in the house.
Are we eating something delicious?
Their T-shirts match.
They look cute.
I used up all my energy.
I didn't expect to work so hard.
I didn't expect making T-shirts would be this fun either.
It was fun.
Didn't it make you feel ambitious?
Yes, I wanted to do a good job, and we did.
We made them nice and cute.
I feel proud of the result.
Honestly, I'll be able to wear it when I go out.
Me too.
- When you go out? - Yes.
- It's very cute. - Let's meet up in this T-shirt.
It's exactly what I like.
Setting up a date?
They promised to meet so naturally.
When you make something together...
or wear something given by someone,
you keep thinking about that person.
- Right. - Definitely.
It will definitely happen.
- There's a bump. Be careful. - Gosh.
The bump is high.
- Do I park anywhere? - Yes.
(Hwi Hyun and Na Eon return to Jeju Island House.)
Nice.
- Thank you for driving. - Thank you.
- The ride was very smooth. - Yes.
(Hwi Hyun runs up to Na Eon with a jacket in case she's cold.)
(He puts his jacket on her.)
Thank you. Let's hurry inside.
It's so cold.
Where would Own be?
Is the house empty?
Yes.
Should we keep our T-shirts on?
- Let's keep it on. - Okay.
It's quite chilly now that it's the evening.
It's very cold.
(Min Jae and Lee Ji Yeon come inside right after them.)
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hello. - When did you get back?
- Five minutes ago. - I see.
What did you guys do?
- What? - What did you guys do?
This.
- What's that? - What is it?
- Did you make T-shirts? - We drew them.
- Did you draw it? - We drew it ourselves.
- Is it attached? - We also had food.
Today, you look like...
a real couple.
Black looks good on both of you.
That's nice.
Hi.
- Hello. - Did you have a safe trip?
Yes, we just got back.
What did you do?
- What? - What did you do?
We went to an amazing place.
- We shot a drama. - We shot a drama.
You shot a drama?
What kind of drama?
Did you go to a filming location?
A filming location for a drama.
- No, it wasn't a filming location. - Really?
Our presence turned it into a filming location.
I can't wait to find out...
- where they went. - Me neither.
It was beautiful.
I liked it.
Can you take a photo of me?
With a good shot of this T-shirt.
- We made T-shirts. - What's that?
He keeps bragging about the T-shirt.
As Hwi Hyun is wearing the T-shirt,
it looks even better.
- He has a nice figure. - Right.
What's that? It's so cute.
- We made T-shirt. - My gosh.
I'll take a photo of you.
They did something more fun than us.
Are you jealous?
What?
- Are you jealous? - You shouldn't have said that.
(Min Jae finds the situation funny.)
I wasn't exactly thinking.
Hwi Hyun's T-shirt looked so cute,
so it just came out.
That's scary.
Disappointed.
Our Uyuni Salt Flat was nice too.
We...
You must have gotten some beautiful photos.
(Kwan Woo is busy coming up with excuses and posing.)
(They take a break while drinking some coffee.)
What do you think of my outfit?
Should I just wear this?
Do you have a different color for the T-shirt?
Why do you look so sad?
(Na Eon wants to keep the T-shirt she made with Hwi Hyun on.)
I have so many clothes but nothing to wear.
This is the only thing I have...
that I can wear over this T-shirt.
That looks better...
- without the vest. - Is this better?
- Shall I wear this? - Yes.
- It looks cute. - Doesn't it look weird?
No, it reminds me of Christmas.
Holy, holy Christmas
- Can you send it to me? - I put your jacket up there.
- Really? - Why aren't you wearing it?
Is that it?
I thought that it would look similar to his.
- It looks nice. - It looks like you.
I drew her dog, Dal on the back.
- You drew well. - It looks pretty.
She gave me a nickname "Silken Tofu Boy."
I also wanted to give her a nickname related to food.
The shape of her face reminded me of an acorn.
It looks like her.
Are you going upstairs?
- Are you going to the living room? - Wait.
- What are you doing? - Hurry over here.
I thought of an incredible game just now.
- What? - What?
A friend flirting with your girlfriend versus...
your girlfriend flirting with your best friend.
(Which one is worse?)
Wait, what did you say?
- What did you say? - This is insulting.
- It must be his girlfriend. - My girlfriend...
Wait a minute.
- Wait. - It's your best friend ever.
- With my best friend... - Someone you grew up with.
What if your best friend is flirting with your girlfriend?
That? I see.
My friend flirting with my girlfriend is worse.
That would be horrible.
(Min Jae's answer is true.)
- Why doesn't it detect you? - Even I...
I'd never do that.
- Goodness. - Let's do this one.
- Okay. - Okay.
How far can you go with physical contact in public?
- In public? - Yes.
Let's say that your girlfriend is here.
- How far can you go? - Everyone is looking at you.
As far as hugging.
- Say your answer. - As far as hugging.
- You can't even give her a peck? - Are you telling him to hug?
How can I give her a peck in public?
- Everyone does it. - Why not?
- While everyone is watching you? - Who cares?
I was going to ask if you could give her a French kiss.
(Hwi Hyun lied.)
You were lying.
What a sneaky boy.
"Sneaky boy?"
He's showing different sides of him.
- What a sneaky boy. - He said that he'd only hug.
After saying that pecking wasn't possible...
This is funny.
This is a lie.
The lie detector is lying.
You're lying.
This is so funny.
- The detector is lying. - But why...
Let's do this one.
Who do you think is the best-looking?
- The best-looking? - Yes.
That question sounds...
- direct. - What?
Ji Yeon's answer was Gyu Min.
- The best-looking? - Yes.
It's very difficult for her to answer.
I'll say Kwang Tae.
- I don't believe you. - The way she said it...
(Kwang Tae is the best-looking. True.)
- Did you change your opinion? - What?
They spent a long time together.
Is it love?
Hye Seon, how was your day?
Today?
It was the best date I ever had.
- Your best date ever? - Yes.
That's fascinating.
I don't mean the best date of my life.
- I mean, ever since we came here. - Okay.
- During our time here? - Yes, during our time here.
- Would you like some? - Yes.
It has a baby smell.
A baby smell with some musk.
It gets absorbed very quickly.
It isn't sticky.
I need some rest.
- Let's take a rest for a minute. - I'm so tired.
- Lights out? - Lights out? Okay.
(They decide to take a short rest.)
Ji Yeon.
- What? - Was it just comfortable...
hanging out with Min Jae?
How shall I put it?
I don't know if it's lovey-dovey with him.
It's hard to tell.
We talked about relationships.
I don't know...
if everyone else talks about that.
- It's hard to compare. - I see.
Kwan Woo and I talked for a while.
Over such...
a short period of time,
my heart has never fluttered.
I never had that experience.
On the other hand, Kwan Woo seems...
capable of it.
And so, how shall I say this?
He's so different from me...
that I'm not on the same level with him.
Now I feel...
quite comfortable with him.
I still don't know...
what kind of person he is.
Kwan Woo is very careful...
when he talks about himself.
I felt the same way about him.
He thinks before he speaks.
It sounds funny to put it that way.
Everyone thinks before they speak.
Sometimes, I speak without thinking.
- No way. - You know what I mean?
I often speak without thinking.
It seems like Kwan Woo would think before saying something.
He says that he filters his words 3 or 4 times.
I don't mind his filtering,
but it's hard to get to know him.
He hasn't talked about himself much.
He doesn't bring up personal things about him.
He answers to my questions very well.
However,
- he doesn't say more than that. - He doesn't give much information.
When we make a point of contact,
our conversation can get deeper.
That's when I feel touched,
but we haven't gotten that far yet.
In our conversation.
- Such a conversation is important. - Of course.
I wanted that kind of conversation because we don't have much time.
I asked him if he had questions for me.
As he asks me questions,
I could ask him as well.
If he has no questions for me,
it might not be polite to keep asking him questions.
- Some people... - It makes you more careful.
Some people hate talking about themselves.
- That's why. - Right.
He's very cautious.
The reason why Hye Seon feels that way...
could be Kwan Woo's personality.
Or she can't open up to him...
because he doesn't show enough interest in her.
- The reason could be the latter. - Right.
She wants to take her time to get to know him.
- The spark between them isn't big. - No.
I think it's his personality.
They have to see each other in private.
Min Jae talks about his family a lot.
So I felt comfortable enough to talk about my parents too.
I really liked that.
He wasn't so discreet, so I could feel the same.
I can talk to him about anything.
He's also down-to-earth.
That's why we get along so well.
- He might not agree with me. - Right.
(But I get along with him.)
Are you more interested in him now?
Yes, I feel comfortable around him.
It's so unfortunate that tomorrow is our last day.
Seriously.
It's true.
- If we had more time... - If we had a few more days...
(The trip seems very short.)
Things could be different.
- Right. - They get along so well.
They really do.
They're comfortable around each other.
Their age gap is ten years.
- But I don't see any gap. - Eleven? Exactly.
They should be given at least two weeks.
Everyone is so bummed out.
(The sun sets, and the night approaches.)
- Hye Im. - Yes.
What are you doing?
I'm looking at this.
- What is it? - Do you know...
this application?
- What is it? - I don't have time...
to go to department stores.
- I use this a lot for shopping. - Really?
It has many brands.
Their products are of good quality.
- Is it Handsome? - Yes.
- You know it, right? - Yes, I like Handsome.
- This looks good. - Top 100 looks good.
Isn't it easy to shop?
I bought this top on this app.
Really? I like your sweatshirt.
- Isn't it cute? Right? - The quality looks nice.
I like it. The jeans are cute too.
Let me see how they fit you.
They have a pretty straight fit.
They also have this detail.
- I also like the length. - Right?
They go well with your sweatshirt.
They look cute.
- This is my outfit for dinner. - You should.
I'm wearing a T-shirt that Hwi Hyun drew for me.
Is it an acorn or a person?
An acorn person.
- He says that it's Acorn Na Eon. - Seriously.
It's our last day. We should drink.
Are we getting drunk tonight?
(Everyone has gathered in the communal space.)
Hwi Hyun, you should give a toast.
- Me? - Go ahead.
Really?
- My drink is getting heavy. - Today...
- "My drink is getting heavy?" - It's been nice to get to know you.
Thanks to you, I feel like I'm dreaming.
Cheers. Wait.
Shall we say, "Let's go, EXchange?"
- Okay. - That sounds good.
- Let's go, EXchange! - Let's go, EXchange!
Let's go.
That's funny. His speech...
- It's annoying how he's good at it. - I agree.
- He's so good. - That was a nice toast.
Seriously.
- If we didn't ask him... - I prepared it.
He's the type to be the class president.
- Exactly. - Right?
If we didn't ask him, he would've been sad.
Seriously.
It's strong.
It has too much alcohol.
- A drink should be this strong. - Who made it?
- I made it. - Hwi Hyun.
You don't like it? Why?
Can I try yours?
- It's delicious. - Isn't it the same as yours?
I made them the same.
- Do you want some? - Are you saying that it's strong?
(Exclaiming)
- It tastes okay. - It's strong.
- "It's strong." - I added more tonic water to mine.
- I'll let it go since you're cute. - Do you want to try it?
- Even the color is different. - The color is different.
- Even the color is different. - They're very different.
Look at these.
Mine is sweet.
- He acted surprised. - It's very strong.
Hey.
(What will their relationship be like after their last night?)
(Hwi Hyun checks on his looks in the room.)
- Isn't that cologne? - Is he putting on some cologne?
Checking himself out.
Is he checking on his smell?
- Checking on his smell. - Checking on his smell?
He's planning to make some small talk.
(Hwi Hyun hurries off to somewhere.)
Are you on a date with Own?
- Isn't he adorable? - Yes.
I got closer to Own.
Where are you going, Own?
Should I play this? It's good.
- Is it playing? - Na Eon.
- What is it? - Open it.
What is it?
Did you buy the cap?
- It looked so good on you. - When did you buy it?
When you went to the restroom.
- Really? That's amazing. - Yes.
I don't have a yellow cap.
It looks good on you. You look like a farmer.
- Does it look good on me? - Yes, put it on properly.
- You try it on. - Will it mess up your hair?
I don't look good in hats.
Doesn't she look much better than me?
- It looks better on her. - Really?
Yes, it looks cute on you.
I'll take a look in the mirror.
Your face looks very small.
- It looks cute. - I told you.
(Hwi Hyun bought it secretly after seeing Na Eon.)
While looking around,
we found a cap that I liked.
While I went to the restroom, Hwi Hyun bought it for me...
as a gift.
The cap was so pretty.
I liked it.
She seemed happy, and it made her smile.
Giving it to her made me feel proud.
I wanted to thank you for driving.
Thank you for the pumpkin cap.
It looks so good on you. It definitely belongs to you.
It's a little big on me.
- Does it... - How small is your face?
- Do I look good? - Yes, it looked good on you.
- It fits me well. - It looks amazing on you.
- The color is nice on you too. - Yes.
It fits me very well.
I'll do it this time.
Wait.
(Hwi Hyun's Surprise Gift)
- Hwi Hyun can do things like that? - I know.
Do we even know him?
Hasn't it only been a year?
He became a different person after graduating.
- He even uses cologne. - I feel proud of him.
Why do I feel proud of him?
- That's a new side of him. - He bought a present for her.
It feels like watching him grow.
When did they go out?
Aren't they cold?
- I know. - It must be freezing outside.
They aren't even dressed...
warmly.
It's so passionate between them.
Can we listen to music...
for one minute?
- I want to make a request. - A request?
I listen to it the most these days.
There's a song called "To Lady" by Byun Jin Sub.
It came up right away.
- I'll listen to it. - I love it.
- You might recognize it. - Let's listen to it.
When I get obsessed with one song,
- I listen to it on repeat. - Only one song?
(They concentrate on the song.)
This song is very...
The lyrics speak to me a lot.
- Really? - Yes.
I'll listen to it.
It's like...
(I want to get to know you in detail)
(But you don't talk to me for some reason)
(I want to visit you in your dreams at night)
(And listen to you quietly)
I'm very bad at expressing myself.
Even when I'm interested in someone.
In a way...
During the bridge.
He spoke up at the right time during the bridge.
Right?
Is he a DJ or something?
- He's confessing his love to her. - Exactly.
The language of flowers is followed by the lyrics.
I know.
I'm very bad at expressing myself.
Even when I'm interested in someone.
In a way,
I could seem pathetic and timid.
When the other person is asleep,
I'll visit her in her dreams and ask.
That's what the lyrics are about.
I find that really beautiful.
That's why I like this song.
- In her dreams? - Yes.
- Since you can't talk in reality? - I don't have the courage...
to approach you and talk to you.
So when you're asleep,
I'll visit you in your dreams.
The lyrics are lovely.
They're turning...
their bodies toward each other.
After listening to a song called "To Lady,"
they'll listen to a song called "To My Bride."
That would be perfect...
- once the relationship gets deeper. - After that,
- "Old Couple in Their 60s?" - An old couple in their 60s.
(The 3 MCs are drawing a big picture.)
They make a great couple.
I went on a date with someone I feel very comfortable with.
I see.
We had a talk yesterday.
- With Park Ji Yeon? - Yes.
Surprisingly, we chose each other.
- Really? - Yes.
- We picked each other. - That's good.
Didn't it work out for you too?
Me? I went out with Hye Im.
Right.
I wanted to get to know Hye Im.
She has a great personality.
- Right? - Yes.
- Doesn't she smile a lot? - Yes.
They're amazing people.
I agree.
You know what would be fun?
Spending two more days in Jeju with someone you like.
That would be great.
- Don't you think? - Yes.
It was so short.
I expected it to be long,
but our time was very short.
- Really? - Cheers.
- There's a lot left. - Really?
(They were worried that it'd be long and boring, but it passed by fast.)
(It feels sad to say goodbye.)
It's the last day.
From the start...
It's delicious.
I was cold, but now that we played a game...
- I feel heated. - That's funny.
The highball is really good since it's chilled.
What's this?
- This is really delicious. - Yes.
(The last night of their trip is coming to an end.)
Now that the trip is coming to an end,
people are getting thoughtful.
They're becoming more emotional.
Surprisingly, I'm worried about Hye Seon and Kwan Woo.
Hye Seon seems concerned.
- Yes. - I agree.
Is it because it feels awkward when they're together?
- Kwan Woo wasn't so enthusiastic. - Right.
He wasn't very talkative.
- So... - Right.
Hye Seon didn't make it obvious, but she seemed a bit disappointed.
Right.
The fact that she feels disappointed means...
- that she's interested in him. - Right.
They seem very similar to each other.
They also make a good couple. If it's just a misunderstanding,
- Right. - I hope that they'll sort it out.
(It's the morning of their last day.)
(Seogwipo Submarine)
Gosh, it's so cold today.
(He's preparing a simple breakfast.)
(He notices something.)
What?
What's this?
(There are 9 notes on the table.)
When did she write all these?
Na Eon wrote them.
(Na Eon wrote letters to everyone last night.)
- I see. - Na Eon did?
- Really? - To everyone?
Writing to nine people couldn't have been easy.
After listening...
- to that song... - Enchanted by the song?
She must have written them while listening to the song.
Na Eon is very attentive.
Yes.
- Hey, Kwang Tae. - Yes?
- You got a letter. - What?
I didn't know what it was about.
Go ahead and read it.
Isn't it that we're supposed to write to each other?
I was touched.
What? When did she write this?
I know. Isn't it touching?
Yes.
I'll eat upstairs.
It's so cold.
It's very cold.
(They go upstairs to have breakfast in the warm room.)
It was so short.
I can't believe we're leaving already.
I know.
- It's so cold. - It's cold.
- "It's freezing." - "It's freezing."
- "You didn't hug me." - "You didn't hug me."
- "Shouldn't you apologize to me?" - "Shouldn't you apologize to me?"
- "Apologize to me." - "Apologize to me."
That's hilarious.
It's hilarious.
- What is it? - I wrote them.
What is it?
I think some people took theirs. Am I wrong?
What is it? I'll read it.
- Hey. - Seriously?
- When did you write it? - When?
I wrote them because I couldn't fall asleep.
Goodness. Thank you.
This is really touching.
Not everyone is here.
My goodness.
Gosh, the princess is here.
Hye Seon, over here.
It's your mission card.
You made her nervous.
- Did you sleep well? - Hello.
- Na Eon. - Good morning.
- Na Eon. - Yes?
It was so touching.
When did you take it?
- I woke up early this morning. - Really?
I read it while having breakfast.
You almost made me cry.
Come on.
(Hye Seon also read the letter.)
Goodness. When did you write this, Na Eon?
Seriously.
How nice of her.
What is it?
- What will you wear on top? - A coat.
- Really? I'll wear my padded... - Is everyone wearing a coat?
I wanted to put something else on, but everyone else is wearing a coat.
- Hello. - Good morning.
- Hwi Hyun. - Hwi Hyun.
You got a letter from someone.
Am I supposed to write to everyone?
Who wrote it?
- I wrote one to everyone. - Na Eon.
Thank you.
I wonder what she wrote to Hwi Hyun.
She probably had the most to say to Hwi Hyun.
- Right. - He's the last one to receive it.
(Hye Seon is writing something in her notebook.)
(What is Hye Seon writing?)
Do you want me to send you photos from yesterday?
- Me? - Yes.
- Yes. - I'll send them to you.
- Gosh. - What's wrong?
- My bangs... - Send me all the photos.
I sent them all.
My bangs look good on me.
- Did you put it in? - Yes.
We got a text. Goodness.
What is it?
What?
(Your trip is over. Please write the name of a person...)
(you want to start a new relationship with...)
(and send a message to him or her.)
A person you want to start a new relationship with?
Yes, they're choosing someone to start with.
- A new relationship? A fling? - Yes.
That's a possibility.
Or someone you want to get to know more.
They didn't spend enough time...
- to call it love. - Right.
They aren't just acquaintances.
Their relationship is special.
It's too early to say...
- that they're in a relationship. - Right.
I think that it's more than friendship.
They will probably send the message to someone...
they want to continue their relationship with.
- It doesn't work. - It doesn't?
Why are you looking at me like that?
What?
What is it?
It seems like she's reading the look on my face.
(Hye Seon read the text in the room.)
(They need to send a text now.)
(Everyone's texts have been sent.)
(Final selection)
(Na Eon received a text.)
Why is it so long?
I think he referenced some things I wrote in my letter.
I was surprised at how long it was.
(Hwi Hyun went upstairs alone with the letter.)
(He slowly read the letter.)
I didn't have to think about it.
I sent it to Na Eon right away.
(I enjoyed every moment in Jeju with you.)
(I hope we can still see each other and talk about whatever...)
(even after the show. Hwi Hyun.)
(If you want to start a new relationship, )
(please go to the address below.)
(If not, please go to the airport.)
It says to go to the address below if she wants a new relationship...
and to go to the airport if she doesn't.
Wait.
So even if she sent a text,
- she could not go to meet him. - Right.
- Right. - You're right.
They need to meet for the selection to be complete.
In a way, it's not just up to Na Eon.
- It's up to Hwi Hyun too. - Right?
Hwi Hyun could go to the airport after sending the text,
or he could go to that location. It's up to both of them.
They could not come after seeing the text?
That's possible.
So what the text says must be really important.
If it's done like this,
I think we'll only get one or two couples.
When we were making predictions, we said the selection process...
seemed very comfortable and not overwhelming.
- Right. - But it could actually be harder.
Before, they would at least meet at the location...
- and say goodbye. - Right.
But this time, they're just left alone.
This is more cruel.
We'll have to see. They gave it a twist.
(If you want to start a new relationship, )
(please go to the address below.)
(If not, please go to the airport.)
(Where is Na Eon's heart headed?)
Could you open the trunk?
(Final selection: Cho Hwi Hyun chose Park Na Eon.)
I don't see a reason not to continue this relationship.
I want to continue our relationship even after the show.
I want to get close to her.
I was shaking partially because I was cold.
But I was also shaking because I was nervous.
He's cute and feels like a friend,
but we had so little time.
I thought I needed more time...
to get to know him.
Because we had so little time,
we couldn't get so close. I'm a bit sad about that.
I waited for quite a while, but she didn't come.
So I thought, "Did she go to the airport?"
"Did I come on too strong?"
(Where is Na Eon's heart headed?)
(Hwi Hyun is still waiting for Na Eon.)
(Right then, a car arrives.)
- Oh, she's here. - She's here.
It's not someone else, right?
- She's here. - No way.
It can't be, "Let's go to the airport."
- That's so cruel. - Please get out of the car, Lady.
(Is Na Eon in this car?)
(Final selection: Park Na Eon chose Cho Hwi Hyun.)
Hi.
- Where do I go? - That way.
(Hwi Hyun is finally smiling.)
- Hi. - Isn't it cold?
- What? - Isn't it cold?
- Why is it so hot? - It's hot?
- Yes, it's not cold. - Really?
I was totally shaking while waiting.
- Should I sit here? - Yes.
Do you want to use this as a blanket? It's warm.
You should. Your legs must be cold.
Okay.
Yes. They suit each other well.
She came. Spring is here.
This doesn't mean they're officially a couple,
but our reaction is almost...
- We're acting as if they're dating. - They're like a couple.
Nice.
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Two nice people like them should continue...
- their relationship. - Exactly.
- They need to meet in Seoul. - Congratulations.
We decided on our own that they're already dating.
Right. I hope they continue this relationship.
You didn't go to the airport.
Did you get my text?
Yes, mine was so short, so I...
But you wrote me a long letter.
- Right. You saw my letter. - Yes.
I was so touched.
I wrote a long letter to some...
- and a short one to others. - I see.
So I folded all of them in the same way.
- Oh, really? - You were the last to take yours.
And yours...
- Yours was long. - It was one of the longer ones.
- It was a long one. - You totally filled...
- the whole page. - Right.
I appreciated it.
She seems nervous.
I was looking back on it, and on the first day,
I wrote the introductory letter about you.
- Oh, right. - That was random.
I had three options.
- That's really interesting. - Yes.
That was really random.
- Right. - Yes.
Those weren't all Hwi Hyun, right?
So that day, I picked Hwi Hyun for the first time.
That made me wonder, "What kind of person is he?"
That made me more interested in Hwi Hyun.
Looking back, that was pretty...
(Looking back, that day started everything.)
"Hwi Hyun is a kind, silken tofu-like person."
"I don't know him very well, and we're not very close yet,"
"I believe he'll be even cooler when I get to know him better."
Then she drew a cat.
(Things started between them by chance.)
(They had time to themselves thanks to Na Eon's courage.)
You were the person I wanted to get to know more.
You have a really cute face.
(Na Eon was honest about her feelings toward him.)
Your face looks very cute.
(Our shy silken-tofu boy started to change.)
I'm very bad at expressing myself.
Even when I'm interested in someone.
When the other person is asleep,
I'll visit her in her dreams and ask.
That's what the lyrics are about.
The lyrics are lovely.
(Thank you for treating me softly and tenderly...)
(like white silken tofu. I'm still listening to the song...)
(we listened to together. I kept listening to it, )
(and I got this peculiar feeling. It fits this season really well, )
(and I think this song will become important to me. Na Eon.)
(I'm glad we became so close on this trip.)
(Let's keep being good friends. Na Eon.)
I thought I wanted to spend a bit more time with you.
I was happy that I got to do so.
Right. My feelings for you grew...
- during that time too. - I see.
You're so kind, considerate,
and fun to be around.
Yes, it was fun.
We both came here...
- very light-heartedly. - Right.
If I had to pick one person who I want to get closer to...
after the show, it would obviously be you for me.
So I picked you for this final selection.
But I want you to take it not too seriously...
- and not too lightly. - Right.
That's why you picked me too, right?
I picked you because I wanted to hang out with you the most.
I appreciated that you thought positively of me.
And you have the cutest face.
(And you have the cutest face.)
You have the cutest face.
After Own?
- No, you're cuter than Own. - Really?
- Own is the cool type. - I see. It's the first time...
Own is kind of a Pomeranian-Jindo mix.
- A Pomeranian-Jindo mix? - Yes, a Pomeranian-Jindo mix.
I have a cute face?
Yes, you have a cute face.
That's nice.
It's true that at every moment of our trip,
she seemed pretty to me and gave me butterflies.
I want...
to meet her a few more times and stay close to her.
I think I'll stay true to how I feel.
- Oh, my! - Oh, my.
- He's good at expressing himself. - Right.
Go tomorrow. Have some flatfish and soju.
You don't have to hurry.
I think that was the prettiest facial expression...
I've seen Na Eon make.
The prettiest smile.
Smile.
(They grew close during their trip.)
Wave at the camera.
Hi.
Let's become even closer.
(All EXchange seasons assemble. You're the cutest.)
- Shall we turn around? - No.
I don't think that's it.
Why? Let's shoot a travel vlog.
No. I don't think that's it.
We don't get along.
I don't think we do.
Come to walk Dal.
Sounds good. What kind of snacks does Dal like?
Dal likes everything.
I feel bad, but I'll have to take...
some of Kong and Song's snacks.
I'll come to see Dal soon.
- Please come. - Of course, I should go.
- Seasons 2 and 3 came together. - You're right.
- They look so good together. - Exactly.
It makes me happy to look at them together.
We felt like that the whole time we watched them.
- They promised to walk their dogs. - Exactly.
Oh, goodness.
(A text from Kwan Woo arrived.)
I saw the long text...
and felt a bit weird.
(If you want to start a new relationship, )
(please go to the address below. If not, please go to the airport.)
Oh, Hye Seon.
- She was thinking a lot. - She must be, seriously.
I think she'll still say she wants to get to know him more.
Will she go?
- I think Hye Seon will go. - Right.
I think that text must've been very important.
When she was...
- thinking so hard until the end... - Right.
Hello.
Our first date was the most memorable.
I felt on that date...
that he took care of me a lot.
(They rode ATVs together after Kwan Woo chose her.)
(Kwan Woo took good care of Hye Seon.)
I kept seeing afterimages of you.
You as a person.
- Oh, really? - Really.
Please grab each other's hands.
(And their partner yoga experience with Dong Jin and Da Hye)
It feels like we're on a honeymoon in Bali.
Korean version of Bali.
Natural, like a couple.
(My love, you are pretty and flawless.)
(Final selection: Lee Kwan Woo chose Lee Hye Seon)
Is there something to think about?
I'll be so happy if she feels the same way as me.
She expressed her feelings to me a lot.
I hope she's thinking about me just as much.
I believe she is.
(Kwan Woo is putting trust in Hye Seon.)
Okay. He came.
Right. I think it'd be sad for him if he didn't go.
(Meanwhile, Hye Seon seems to be deep in thought.)
Why does she look so sad?
I knew he was a good person.
But I realized I didn't know what kind of person he was.
He doesn't bring up personal things about him.
When we make a point of contact, our conversation can get deeper.
That's when I feel touched,
but we haven't gotten that far yet.
What do you usually do outside of work?
I spend most of my time working.
Do you like a calm atmosphere or a lively, noisy atmosphere?
I think it depends on the situation.
- You say this a lot. - But seriously.
It does make sense.
So difficult.
You can ask me questions if you have any.
It's just as I said before.
Is there...
anything more to talk about?
Since I don't know,
I just accept things as they are.
(And a text from Hye Seon arrived.)
(I want to tell you thanks one last time. Hye Seon.)
She wants to tell him thanks one last time.
Hye Seon said.
- Doesn't that mean... - This is...
- Isn't she saying yes? - They both chose each other, right?
(What did Hye Seon mean by "one last time?")
(Hye Seon reads the text that Kwan Woo sent again.)
I had partially...
made a decision on my own.
But when I saw the text,
my feelings did waver.
(A new star shines extra brightly in my universe today.)
(It's a small and very white star, )
(and it has started to become my sun. Kwan Woo.)
I think he was describing me in his poem.
I felt a lot from that.
(This morning, Hye Seon gave Kwan Woo a book of poems.)
- I honestly... - Thank you so much.
I really love it.
I especially like poetry books.
Thank you so much.
Oh, she was writing in that book.
Oh, she gave it to Kwan Woo.
Hye Seon said she was attracted...
- by poets and painters. - Exactly.
I compared Hye Seon to a star in my text.
"I like you."
"I enjoyed our time together today."
Instead of saying that directly,
I wanted to express it in a warm way.
It's similar to that poem.
"He came to me and became a flower."
- It's similar to that. - Right.
I'm not sure why her feelings wavered...
after getting this message.
- She wasn't going to go. - She wasn't going to go,
- and then her feelings wavered. - Right.
- At first... - But in her message earlier,
she said she wanted to tell him one more time.
- Later? - She just meant that she wanted...
to tell him thanks one more time.
- I think she means, "I want..." - One more time. Yes.
"to tell him thanks one more time while we're here."
- I think that's what she meant. - Oh, here?
- Not later? - Yes.
So this message could answer...
some of Hye Seon's questions...
- and curiosities about Kwan Woo. - Right.
This could really sway her. His words were so lovely.
- I think it was really sincere. - It was sincere.
- I think he thought about it a lot. - Yes.
Will she come?
The longer I waited,
the less sure I became.
(After thinking for a long time, )
(Hye Seon made up her mind.)
Sir.
Please go to the airport.
- Why? - Why?
Seriously?
It's so...
- Why? - But...
I think she could feel...
that even the last message was too indirect.
Could that be it?
Please go to the airport.
(Final selection: Lee Hye Seon didn't choose anyone.)
(Lee Hye Seon wants to maintain the current relationship.)
(Please head to the airport.)
I was disappointed.
In a way, I understand her.
The Hye Seon I saw during our time here...
was...
a very careful person.
I don't think she wanted to make a rash decision.
This could be a decision...
I don't regret...
or a decision I do regret,
but the reason I made this decision...
was because I felt that 5 days and 4 nights...
was too short of a time...
to become certain about someone.
No matter who that person may be.
I'm sad.
(I'm sad.)
I'll think about her a lot.
I'm really grateful.
And you're such a good person.
I really want you to be successful and happy.
This trip...
will leave me...
with grateful...
and happy memories in many ways.
- Both of them were sincere. - Exactly.
It's a bit...
- Things are... - Right?
Too out of place.
They were sincere about each other.
In the end, he wasn't selected.
No.
Hye Seon's decision is odd, right?
They were getting along well at first, so I had my hopes up.
- Me, too. - I think...
she understood it as the first step of a serious relationship.
Hye Seon was much more sincere about it.
- She didn't think lightly of it. - No.
Either way, it's a bummer.
It sure is a bummer. It's not like she has to start...
dating him right away...
after choosing him. What a shame.
How the two interpreted it was different.
Exactly. Their views were different.
- It's a shame. - Yes, a shame.
It's a real shame.
(Another participant is heading to their final selection.)
(One participant is waiting for him.)
(Final selection: Park Ji Yeon chose Kim Kwang Tae.)
What? Yes. Ji Yeon is waiting for him already.
- Really? - Ji Yeon made her decision.
The two seem to be interested in each other.
- Yes. They look good together. - Right?
Isn't getting to know people exciting?
I prefer...
being with someone whom I feel comfortable around.
Do you want pasta, Ji Yeon?
I want to eat pasta.
Leave some for Ji Yeon.
It made me happy.
Can you show me your profile for a minute?
I probably look bad.
You don't trust me?
It's so funny to see you wearing it.
- This? - Yes.
(The two got friendship rings.)
They're so smooth.
If only we could've gotten closer a lot sooner.
He was an even better person than I thought.
(Ji Yeon waits for Kwang Tae with a fluttering heart.)
(He has arrived at the final selection site.)
What? Isn't he getting out?
Why isn't he getting out?
(What is Kwang Tae thinking?)
- He got out. - That scared me.
Yes. The two suit each other.
- They look great together. - Right.
These two are closer to...
- A romantic relationship. - Yes, they're closer to that side.
There's an air of romance around them.
It's exciting. Now the two can run away together.
- Go. - Run away to Seoul.
(Final selection: Kim Kwang Tae chose Park Ji Yeon.)
When did you get here?
Me? Twenty minutes ago.
Twenty minutes ago?
- You got here late. - Me?
Well...
Isn't it warmer than yesterday?
- Yes. It's warm. - Right?
Did you think I'd come here?
Remember coming here in secret yesterday?
(In the last 1-on-1 trip)
Should we run away?
- What? - Should we run away?
Run!
Let's run away to the west.
How about we set up the stone?
Should we? Should we go down?
(With that, the two went on a beach walk.)
That will become a place of memory for the two.
I wonder if the stone tower from yesterday is still there.
- I bet it's still there. - Let's go check it out later.
Since you wanted to see the beach,
I did, too.
I loved it when we came here.
I agree. It was really nice.
- Yesterday... - I came wearing the ring.
Nice. Same here.
It's awkward.
- Did you think I'd choose you? - What?
Well...
- No. I didn't. - Did you think I wouldn't?
No.
But you could choose no one.
So...
Why is he being awkward? How funny.
- They look youthful. - Right?
They suit each other.
Because I wasn't getting any texts,
I thought I should stay behind and go have lunch or something.
That was what I thought, too.
- Really? - Yes.
The last sentence of our texts was the same.
Did you read it?
I did. But didn't you...
reply to my text?
- What? No. - For real?
- Isn't it cool? - Yes.
(I can't believe it's the last day. Time really flies.)
(The more I get to know you, the more interesting you get.)
(Let's go have dakgalbi in Seoul. Kwang Tae.)
(Kwang Tae Vicky, thanks for making good memories with me.)
(You made me laugh a ton.)
(Let's go have dakgalbi in Seoul. Park Ji Yeon.)
Ji Yeon told me that was her favorite restaurant.
That's right in front of my workplace.
Isn't it really cool?
When we return to Seoul, we'll likely go to that restaurant first.
- They sent the exact same thing. - I know, right?
- Really? - The two must've talked about it.
They must've for real.
And both remembered it.
Yes. You can tell right away that they suit each other.
I'm always at Apgujeong...
during lunch.
- I'll drop by often. - Let's have lunch together.
It's close, right?
- Yes, it's close. - Good.
Let's meet there next time.
- After we leave. - Okay.
Should we go to Seoul?
- Let's go. - Shall we head to the airport?
You must be cold. You'll catch a cold.
- You were here all along. - Let's go.
- What? - Let's buy some carrot cake to go.
I'm in.
Great. Let's go.
I feel light-hearted now.
A new beginning...
doesn't necessarily mean...
having to date right away.
I found the need to get to know people slowly...
and for a long time.
I met someone...
whom I could really get along with like Ji Yeon.
I don't jump...
the gun.
Timing is important in everything.
(Timing is important in everything.)
That's right.
Kwang Tae was all about someone with a cat face.
- Meow. - Exactly.
- He found himself a real cat face. - Ji Yeon is... Yes.
Yes, a real cat face. She's a human cat.
And their personalities fit.
- Exactly. - Yes. Kwang Tae has changed a lot.
- Right. - He gave off the feeling...
of a runner in a rush...
- Yes. - during EXchange.
That gave us a good laugh.
But he's become the calmest person.
- Yes. He's also become cautious. - Right.
His actions spoke louder than words.
Exactly. And Kwang Tae felt that, too.
The only flirting move...
- he made was... - "Should we run away?"
solely to Park Ji Yeon. It was only for her.
That itself was very cool.
There's a big possibility that they started a relationship.
I agree. The two make everyone excited.
Let's go in.
- Are your shoes all right? - Yes.
- Is it gone? - Is it this one?
- No. - Yes, it's this one.
You're right.
- Should we stack more up? - Yes.
We placed something on top here.
A small one.
(Placing today's memories on yesterday's memories)
Like that one?
Stack it up.
(What will their relationship build into?)
Isn't there a small one?
All done. It's cute.
Nice.
I've always wanted to get this close.
Go into the water.
- You want me to go into the water? - Yes.
Go in.
- Be careful. - Okay.
(Kwang Tae and Park Ji Yeon's another beginning)
Now then. Lee Ji Yeon, Min Jae, Hye Im, and Gyu Min...
must make their last selection.
I really want to know how Min Jae...
- Right. - and Hye Im feel.
I havent the vaguest idea.
Min Jae...
I don't think he'll choose anyone.
Min Jae will send the text to Hye Im...
but won't choose anyone. He'll head to the airport.
I think so, too.
In the end, Hye Im's feelings for Min Jae...
were too intense.
Hye Im's initial interest in Min Jae...
was quite deep.
But did Gyu Min...
take away that interest during the four days?
I'm quite curious.
I don't think he did.
- It was too short. - Too short?
Maybe.
Why am I nervous?
I'm nervous.
Ji Yeon looks happy after getting the text.
Bye, Own.
Be happy.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Their first encounter was awkward yet heart-fluttering.)
- Which Chinese zodiac sign are you? - Sheep.
"You're really tall with a pretty smile."
Is it you?
It made me really happy.
(Like a reliable older brother...)
(and a friend at times)
(I had the best time today.)
- This is... - What's with that?
(Min Jae made her laugh and her heart pound.)
I sent it to Min Jae.
I spent...
the most memorable times with him on Jeju Island.
When I think about the person who made me laugh the most,
it's Min Jae. Hence, I sent the text to him.
(Final selection: Lee Ji Yeon chose Kwak Min Jae)
(Hi, MJ.)
(This trip with you was fun and full of happiness. Thanks.)
(It helped me find a new side of me.)
(I hope your life is filled with more happiness.)
(Lee Ji Yeon.)
I have no clue.
I can't guess...
who Min Jae chose.
(Min Jae has an unreadable expression.)
(Hye Im was curious about Min Jae and Ji Yeon's date.)
- What was it? What did you do? - We just...
It was a date, wasn't it?
It was more of a trip than a date.
You look nervous.
I became nervous because you looked at me.
Fine. I won't look at you.
- That's it? - Yes.
Take a look.
Take one for me with Min Jae.
(Hye Im knew him well, like an old friend.)
Don't you know Gen Z?
- I'm not Gen Z. - I'll take it.
- Okay. - It's something like this.
The more I date them, the more my feelings grow for them.
- That's how I am. - Right. Me, too.
My ideal type was always a manly guy.
That was in the past.
Now, I prefer someone sweet.
We had a good conversation.
(Can Min Jae and Lee Ji Yeon's coincidences lead...)
(to a new relationship?)
(Having you around was reassuring and relaxing.)
(Thanks for taking good care of me.)
(It was a short trip, but we were able to talk...)
(and settle the little awkwardness...)
(we had with each other.)
(Min Jae.)
(Final selection: Kwak Min Jae chose Jeong Hye Im.)
He eventually chose Hye Im.
I don't find it a surprise.
But I'm worried Hye Im might not choose Min Jae.
Same here. There's Gyu Min.
Won't Hye Im choose Min Jae?
But Min Jae's text message...
I'm sure the one eating Hye Im up inside was Min Jae.
True. But she didn't go on the 1-on-1 trip with him.
- Right? - And yet, will she choose Min Jae?
We'll have to see if Hye Im will come or not.
(Kwak Min Jae wants to maintain the current relationship.)
(Please head to the airport.)
It was quite a shame.
But in the given situation,
I think I've expressed my feelings a lot.
There's not much regret.
If I had to spend time with someone tomorrow,
I'd still want to spend it with Min Jae.
During this trip, I was able to meet...
a dear colleague.
I'm very grateful.
He's a precious friend now.
I want to continue to get along with him.
(My love, you are beautiful and cheerful.)
(Gyu Min has arrived at the final selection site.)
I sent the text to Hye Im.
(Final selection: Jeong Gyu Min chose Jeong Hye Im.)
How about writing it to the one you want to gift it to?
Who are you giving it to?
I already have someone.
(Hye Im)
(She was my first choice.)
I thought it was out of awkwardness.
"It's 100 percent friendship."
It was sort of insisted.
I'd be lying if I said...
my heart didn't flutter at all...
while spending the day with her.
She definitely gave me butterflies.
(Gyu Min chose Hye Im throughout the whole trip.)
(Do you think Hye Im feels the same?)
I'm not sure.
Hye Im could've thought...
I was just a really nice friend.
(Hye Im! Seeing you take care of others during this trip...)
(made me realize you were a really nice person.)
(Thank you for the 5 days and 4 nights.)
(Let's get along more from now on. Gyu Min.)
(Hye Im received 2 text messages.)
Hye Im will appear in 1 of the 2 places.
- Yes. - Or she might not choose anyone.
True. She might not choose at all.
(If you want to start a new relationship, )
(please go to the address below.)
(If not, please go to the airport.)
(Kwak Min Jae: Pyoseondangpo-ro, Jeong Gyu Min: Taesinhaean-ro)
Hello.
- Please go to... - Okay.
"Please go to..."
- Please go to the airport. - The airport.
What she said was quite short.
Min Jae.
I think it's Min Jae, too.
What about you?
Min Jae for me, too.
If she chose someone, it would be Min Jae.
The possibility is 80 to 20.
During the date with Gyu Min,
Hye Im didn't give off much of that atmosphere.
- Please go to... - Okay.
What? It's Kwak Min Jae.
Hold on. There's a bug on you.
It's a small fly.
Thank you.
I had you come to give you this.
It's a camellia flower.
In the language of flowers,
camellia means something like I still love you.
When we came here, I realized...
you were a really great person.
(You're a great person.)
While spending time together here,
I thought you were a really nice person.
- That's not true. - No.
But while I watched Season 1 before appearing in Season 2,
you were my first choice.
(Gyu Min confessed his true feelings to Hye Im.)
Like this. Isn't this better?
- Yes. - We'll go with this.
It felt like a date,
which made me feel odd.
Do you not regret coming here?
- This was the best. - Was it?
(Hye Im received two texts.)
(Where is she heading to?)
(Final selection: Jeong Hye Im chose Jeong Gyu Min.)
For real?
Seriously? Why did she give him the camellia?
We got it all wrong.
- We got nothing right. - But why?
I didn't see this coming.
Min Jae must've simply been...
a good person.
He was like that to her.
Hye Im must've had...
- a sudden change of heart. - Maybe.
Gyu Min told her she was his first choice...
and showed interest in her.
Hye Im says she likes a man who likes her.
- Can't that be the biggest reason? - Right.
Gosh.
- I was worried you might not come. - Take a seat.
- Really? - Yes.
Why were you worried?
Thank you for coming.
(Jeong Hye Im wants to maintain the current relationship.)
(Please head to the airport.)
Right.
That laugh is a real response.
It can't be helped in Min Jae's shoes.
How funny.
- I mean... - He's a cool guy.
It was a lot more fun than I expected.
Before getting here, I was filled with worries.
I contemplated for almost a month.
But I'm glad I chose to be on this show.
Selecting and being selected...
is just a part of it.
Meeting great people...
made it more meaningful.
(If you were to say some last words to Hye Im?)
I really enjoyed our trip together.
Thank you for inviting me.
Thank you for coming.
- It's very awkward. - It is.
What took you so long?
Was I late?
I wanted to come early.
- The text message you sent... - Yes?
Lacked sincerity.
That was what worried me.
(I'll see you outside! Hye Im.)
"I'll see you outside."
- I thought... - Yes?
We'd have time to talk after I sent...
that text message.
I wanted to say things in person,
so I wrote them down on paper.
- That's why... - I see.
If you read what you wrote, I'll forgive you.
- Really? - Yes.
Then I'll take my time saying them.
- I have it with me. - Okay.
First off...
I did a lot of thinking after coming here.
"There are other participants,"
"but why will I care about Gyu Min?"
When I thought about it,
any relationship, be it friends,
has to start with an interest in that person.
Yes.
Thinking that we'd be able...
to get along more after we leave Jeju Island,
I chose you as my final selection.
Thanks.
This was what "I'll see you outside" meant.
I get it.
While waiting for you here,
I did some thinking.
I didn't think you'd be the type to go to the airport...
after...
you received my text about selecting you.
Of course.
It made me happy. And...
it made me reflect on myself for sending four words.
I thought...
you might go to the airport...
after reading that.
Shall we shake hands again?
What's with this?
When Hye Im came in, greeted me, and sat down,
I got nervous...
and could feel my heart flutter.
"I must have a bit of romantic feelings for her."
It made me realize that.
(The end of this trip is the first step...)
(to another beginning.)
With that, everyone has made their final selection.
Three teams made the final selection.
It's cute how everyone became shy. Right?
Out of the three teams,
I think Kwang Tae...
- is most likely to become... - I agree.
- a real couple. - Same here.
Yes. I think so, too.
Compared to when they appeared on their seasons of EXchange,
they've matured.
- A lot at that. - I agree.
- Especially Hwi Hyun and Na Eon. - Exactly.
They left a great impression.
Seeing them relaxed...
- was really pleasant. - Right.
What makes Ji Yeon and Min Jae...
cool is that,
although they didn't choose each other,
both were honest and confident until the end.
That was nice to see.
(They came on this trip not knowing...)
(what to expect with whom.)
(Among the people they have never met before, )
(the first day was awkward yet exciting.)
Seeing the people...
who were on TV in person itself was amazing.
Now, I've got to know them personally.
I knew them...
but never had the chance to spend time with them.
(They made fun memories on a casual trip.)
(Those moments were more amusing as they had each other.)
I had fun...
and had all the conversations I wanted to have.
I've checked everything off my list on this trip.
Let's shake hands.
(They settled buried emotions...)
(and became more comfortable with each other.)
(All were happy when excited...)
(and comforted each other when they became emotional.)
You two look adorable.
(Priceless memories they made together)
Yes!
Getting to know nine friends...
was the best part.
What's this?
Each and every person has become an invaluable friend.
We'll continue to get along well.
(The end of this trip is the beginning of new relationships.)
I hope everyone treasures...
the feelings and memories...
they made during this trip.
Another beginning.
It has various meanings.
We could've found a new love...
or...
looked at a new version of myself.
(Another beginning of my life)
It was a moment where I could learn many lessons.
For 3 nights and 4 days...
Thanks to you, I feel like I'm dreaming.
- Okay. - That sounds good.
- Let's go, EXchange! - Let's go, EXchange!
Let's go.
(Thank you for watching EXchange - Another Beginning.)
Don't we have good news?
Yes. EXchange Season Four...
will return this fall. That's right.
I'm saved.
On Season Four...
Simon Dominic. We're waiting for you.
Now then, we'll return in the fall with EXchange Season Four.
Let's meet again on TVING.
Bye!
Simon Dominic will be with us.
We'll all be here.
Season Four.
(EXchange - Another Beginning)