Sorry, I forgot my bag—
There it is.
Wait a second. Fill me in.
When did you two start...?
It's a misunderstanding, Dr. Kisugi! There is nothing going on between us.
Nothing happened.
I heard she suddenly collapsed outside, so I came to check on her.
Why are you here?
I was worried about her.
Ryuko told me that she fainted.
Coming!
Dr. Kisugi?
You look better than I was expecting.
Here, I brought some food for you.
I feel sorry, you didn't have to do that.
How's your fever?
It's alright now.
I'm glad. Well, I brought some vitamin C to help lower your fever.
Some fiber to help with digestion.
Please have it.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
That was really delicious.
It was just a little cold, I suppose.
Well, judging by how she looks,
she's probably okay now.
Yes, my appetite is back thanks to you.
You can leave now. I'll keep her company.
- What?
- She still has a fever, so I can't leave her alone.
What are you talking about? Why does it have to be you?
Then you stay with her.
Sakura is a member of Team Tendo, after all.
Nurse her back to health.
No way! Are the two of us going to be alone all night?
He's so close...
Go to sleep already.
I can't sleep!
How's your fever?
D-Doctor?
Do you want some water?
Drink.
What? What do I do?
What's going to happen next?
I know this is not a reality.
This is just a dream, isn't it?
Who cares? Please don't wake me up from this dream!
Work your magic, REM sleep!
Where's Dr. Tendo?
[Take the medicine and rest well]
It was a dream after all.
[Hiura General Hospital]
Good morning.
Good morning, Miss Hero! Are you feeling better?
Yes! I'm all better, thanks.
Thank you so much for covering my shift!
We help each other out when one of us gets sick.
So Miss Hero, could you take Anri Shirahama from pediatrics to Dr. Tendo for me?
Sure!
Excuse us!
[Treatment Room A]
He's not here yet.
Shall we wait for him inside?
Look at this, Sakura. You see?
My legs got fat! What a bummer.
This is just a little swelling.
Isn't Dr. Tendo coming yet?
Why are you here?
Excuse me?
Tendo's in the next room.
[Treatment Room B, In use]
Excuse us!
I'm sorry for being late!
- Good morning, Anri!
- It's good to see you again!
You, as well.
- Let's give it our all today, okay?
- Yeah.
[Idiot!!]
I'm very sorry.
You got scolded again?
Yes... I've lost "100 hit points" this morning.
But I think you're on the right track, Sakura.
Based on his behavior last night,
Well, judging by how she looks, she's probably okay now.
I think he's actually concerned about you.
Do you think so? How do you know that?
My intuition. Have confidence in yourself.
You think so? Alright!
Yay, yay, yay!
Oh, careful!
- I feel so much better now!
- Really?
Actually... I'll let you in on a secret.
That night, I had whined to Dr. Tendo that I wanted to quit,
and he said: "You're on Team Tendo, aren't you?"
And he hugged me so gently!
It wasn't a dream! Dr. Tendo really did hug me.
He hugged you gently?
Numazu!
You're such a pain!
Did the Devil hug you?
It's not what you think. Because I wasn't feeling well, so I—
Gently? He hugged you gently? What?
Please don't tell anyone about this.
That's right. Don't make it a big deal.
If Dr. Tendo hears, he'll get mad and call me an idiot again!
I got it. I'll keep quiet. You can trust me, Miss Hero.
Okay!
Hey, big news! That Devil hugged Miss Hero gently!
What?! He hugged her gently?
Numazu!
You didn't last even a second.
No way, I just couldn't resist!
It's not what you think. There's nothing going on between us.
He rejected me a long time ago...
Well, the game has just begun.
Enlighten us on all the details at the welcome party for the newbies!
I can't wait!
In any case, become a better nurse as fast as you can.
I bet Dr. Tendo will see you as a woman once he sees you in a new light.
Will he really?
- Ugh, it's Sugamo again!
- Again?
[Nurse call: Manabu Sugamo]
Who's going?
Alright! I will!
Sugamo, what's the matter?
Implanting a ventricular assist device?
Yes, Anri...
She's advanced from stage C to stage D treatment-resistant heart failure.
It's nice weather today, isn't it?
Look, I found a weirdly shaped cloud!
- Did you know? It's called a butterfly cloud.
- Really?
Until she can get a heart transplant,
we have to keep her current condition stable.
This is just like that other case.
What's wrong, Sugamo?
What do you call this? This food combination is disgusting.
Food combination?
Are you...
trying out a new health routine again?
He's trying out "Color Energy Treatment" this time.
It's some sort of healing remedy about converting his daily vegetables into energy.
Give it.
Right! This arrived for you.
Sugamo, your meals are prepared according to the doctor's instructions.
You don't have to worry, you're recovering very well.
But they pushed back my discharge, didn't they? Go ask the doctor when I can leave.
I'll ask the Doctor.
When can he leave?
Could you talk to him?
He works as a highway express bus driver, and he's mentioned how they're short-staffed.
That might be why he's in a hurry to leave.
His renal artery stenting was successful.
We're administering medicine to prevent thrombosis,
so why aren't his INR levels improving?
(T/N: International Normalized Ratio)
That is strange...
Leave it to me, Doctor!
I'll do a follow-up and solve this mystery of Sugamo's!
Tazawa?
Tazawa was admitted today. He has angina.
- You mixed up their names.
- What?
Look!
[Shin Tazawa]
You put Tazawa's notes under Sagawa, and Sagawa's notes under Tazawa!
Your face says... I have five seconds until you call me an idiot.
Five, four, three, two, one...
Idiot!
I'm sorry!
[An Incurable Case of Love | Love Will Last Forever]
[Episode 3]
When does it look like I'll get out?
We'll decide after your next blood test.
I just really want to get out of here.
I'm sorry I'm late!
I brought you an earphone.
- I already bought it.
- What?
You were taking forever.
- I'm sorry, Doctor. He's always like this.
- No.
I'll do everything I can to speed up his recovery.
Run the blood test.
Okay!
Shin Tazawa. I'm Tendo, your attending physician.
It's nice to meet you.
How are you feeling?
I have no subjective symptoms.
I'll come back in a bit for your consultation.
I'll be drawing some blood now, Sugamo.
Sure.
Gently close your hand around your thumb.
How long are you going to be here?
What's with your attitude? I came all the way here to visit!
You might feel a pinch.
Ouch!
I'm sorry! I'll redo it right away.
That's rare for you, Sakura.
She's usually quite good at that.
I'm sorry, I'll do it again.
Ouch!
I'm sorry, I'll do it again. I'll do it on your right arm this time.
That's enough! You do it, instead.
You kept messing up?
And then after, I couldn't do it for Tazawa, either.
So what happened?
I did it for her.
Thanks.
What's wrong with you?
When you mess up once, you get nervous and keep messing up.
A negative feedback loop. It's very common.
- You're forbidden from handling needles until you improve.
- What?
You'll just get in the way.
He is as harsh as ever.
Banning her from needles... We're short-staffed as it is.
I'll improve myself soon! I'll practice.
I'm sorry for all this trouble.
I'm sorry!
No, I'm sorry!
Come on. Watch where you're going!
Did something happen?
I'm frustrated with him.
I don't know what his problem is, but he's always losing his patience.
I have a job, too. I'm just so swamped right now.
You're so busy, yet you still come to visit.
I think it's amazing.
That makes me feel better. Thank you.
You're welcome.
- MMI?
- Yes.
It's the latest model of a ventricular assist device.
The clinical application of the device has started.
I think this would be the best approach for Anri.
Thank you. I'll study up on them until our joint conference.
Thanks.
Dr. Sayoko, here are Anri's test results.
- Sorry for the trouble! Thank you.
- Not at all.
It looks like the Devil...
I mean, Tendo Sensei is just as busy as ever.
He really is. I worry if he gets any time to sleep.
He must have no personal life, working like that...
He doesn't have a girlfriend, does he?
A girlfriend...
[Diagnosis: dilated cardiomyopathy]
Wait. Does he have one?
Well, I suppose you should know about it, Miss Hero.
What? Dr. Tendo had a girlfriend?
That's right. She was a fellow resident.
But in the end, she became a patient.
A patient?
Eight years ago, she died from dilated cardiomyopathy.
The same illness as Anri's!
Dr. Kisugi?
Here you go.
Practice on me.
No, I wouldn't dare.
I can't practice on your arm. I feel bad.
If you don't practice, you can't do your job.
What's wrong?
Operation Shu Cream...
I might swoop in and take her.
You can leave now. I'll keep her company.
You did all that stuff and cheered me on...
because you're worried about Dr. Tendo, didn't you?
I heard...
about Dr. Tendo's girlfriend.
What was she like?
Minori...
Usually people don't want to hear about an ex.
I want to know.
Alright, then...
She was like a bulldozer.
Excuse me?
When we were residents, there was the biggest snowstorm of the decade.
Trains and busses had suspected operations. No one could come to work.
But she pushed her way through the snow and made it to work.
I made it!
You came? In this snow?
Of course.
I thought you guys would be swamped, so I pushed through the snow!
Don't you live far away?
It's fine. I love winter, after all!
I'm going to go change.
Now we have to wipe the floors.
She was strong and honest... always looking forward.
Don't cry, Kairi.
Before he became a doctor...
We don't have time to dwell on the situation.
We'll get through these, one at a time,
we'll save the next one.
But she fell ill during her residency.
[Echocardiography Report. Name: Minori Wakabayashi]
[Diagnosis: Dilated cardiomyopathy]
When I get better, I want to go eat buckwheat noodles.
The noodles in duck soup that we eat before.
Okay. Let's go there again.
Yeah.
She was waiting for a heart transplant, but...
I've only seen once...
Tendo was crying in the room Minori stayed at.
I've never seen him cry like that since then.
Or laughing out loud.
That's why I've been hoping
that someone would show up and break the chains that bind him.
Dr. Tendo... is so lucky.
To have a friend like you.
Sawatari, you'll be getting a new medication.
Thanks.
You'll be taking this one before bed.
Sugamo, I'll be drawing some blood...
- Sugamo?
- Sakai, can you do it?
Don't worry, Sugamo. I can do it.
Come on, hurry.
Do it for her instead, Sakai.
Alright.
I'm sorry.
- I'll wrap this around your arm.
- Okay.
[The Fundamentals of Nursing]
To be honest, it's hard...
to work with someone like Sakura.
I can't even count on her to draw blood when Dr. Tendo's around.
I end up with more work,
and my work performance is suffering.
That's a lot to ask of you.
I'm sorry I didn't notice earlier.
No, I'm sorry.
I really don't like to say things like this.
Sho, are you well enough to walk now?
Your fever went down, didn't it?
Your fever went down? That's great!
Let's go back to your room!
Why are you here?
I remembered your business card.
I was in the area, so I thought I'd swing by.
I thought I'd never see you again.
So? Did you grow up?
Pardon?
Nishi!
Could this be your girlfriend?
No, not yet at least.
Get away from her.
Stay away from that woman!
What do you mean by that?
Sayoko? Long time, no see!
Why brings you here?
You're as stunning as ever!
It's a lie! She's lying through her teeth! She's always been like this!
What?
From up-close, you look old.
See? See that?
- What are you talking about?
- It doesn't matter! I forbid you from interacting with her.
We have a history.
History?
Me or Sayako... The choice is yours.
Do as you please. Here.
Sayako, see you later. Bye-bye!
[Prothrombin Time, Inernational Normalized Ratio]
[Nurse Report: Nanase Sakura. He left some of his dinner. He's purchased health products, too. Will need to confirm their safety.]
[Nurse Report: Nanase Sakura. Sugamo said how important vitamins, minerals, and fiber were for healing the body. He's been learning about green energy treatment...]
[Health products]
[Vitamins, minerals... green energy]
I've had it enough!
What are you doing?
I said I'm leaving!
Stop that!
What's going on?
Stop him, Sakura!
They started fighting!
Sugamo, please wait!
Shut up. I'm going home. I can't stay in a place like this.
You can't! You don't have the doctor's permission for discharge.
That's enough, Dear.
Get off of me!
- Sugamo!
- I'm leaving!
Doctor!
Sugamo, you can't go home yet.
I said I'm leaving.
May I ask you a question?
- What now?
- What have you been drinking every day?
Excuse me.
You've been drinking this, right?
Yeah.
Green juice?
Yes. He was drinking it on his own for health benefits.
It makes sense. That's why the warfarin wasn't working.
It's less effective for a patient who consumes too much vitamin K.
I'm sorry. I should have explained his medications more thoroughly.
I didn't even notice. I'm so sorry.
But how did you find out?
It was written in the nurse reports.
The nurse reports?
[Cardiology Staff Station]
[Nurse Report: Nanase Sakura. He left some of his dinner. He's purchased health products, too. Will need to confirm their safety.]
[Nurse Report: Nanase Sakura. Sugamo said how important vitamins, minerals, and fiber were for healing the body. He's been learning about green energy treatment...]
[Nurse: Nanase Sakura]
I had no idea the green juice was bad for my health.
I didn't notice, either. I'm so sorry for causing all this trouble.
Not at all. I'm glad we found out the cause.
But why did you want to go home all of a sudden?
I'm sorry.
Because his attitude was horrible,
I told him I wanted a divorce. That's when he went berserk.
Are you worried about work?
Well...
It wasn't about work.
I was worried about my wife.
What?
Your wife?
When I wasn't able to work, she took on more shifts.
I thought that if I didn't get home, she would end up collapsing.
That's why?
And you bought things online to lessen the burden on her?
Oh, Sugamo! You may not look like it, but you're a truly devoted husband!
What?
Don't I look like one?
Of course! I'm sorry, I misspoke.
Here.
Brace yourself.
If you mess up...
I can't do it.
I can't do it to you, Doctor.
Then quit being a nurse right now.
[The Fundamentals of Nursing]
Please let me try it.
- Don't be silent. Say something.
- What?
The patient will get nervous if you just stare at the needle.
If you're nervous, talk while you're doing it. Relax.
But I can't think of anything to say out of the blue...
I'll answer all your questions right now.
Have you...
Minori?
ever...
wanted to quit being a doctor?
Never.
I'm determined to heal patients.
I'll save them.
That was my vow.
Since you can draw blood from me, there's nothing to worry about.
Go back to your regular duties tomorrow.
Doctor!
Thank you very much.
You must be proud for supervising her.
Excuse me?
Your bandage of honor.
You let her practice on you.
If the work will be delayed any longer, it would cause an inconvenience for our patients.
There's no honor about it.
Then I'm the proud supervising physician.
My best pupil is finally interested in mentoring others.
You were right. Perfect on the first try!
I'm all better now!
Sorry again for all the trouble.
You've really improved, Sakura.
Thank goodness!
For all of our sake!
Well, I'll be heading out.
Congratulations on your discharge!
- Yeah! Congrats!
- Congrats!
Thanks for everything!
Take care of yourself.
Become an outstanding nurse, okay?
I will.
Everyone, raise your glasses for the newbie welcoming party!
- Cheers!
Way to go!
Refreshing!
As usual, the night shift team couldn't make it,
- but this year the bill's going to—
- Hey!
Sorry!
I know. I'm paying, right?
Thank goodness!
- Thanks, Director!
- Thank you!
What's that for? Your girlfriend?
Yeah, she's bugging me about where I am.
What? Girlfriend?
Yeah, she's a childcare worker from Osaka. When she moved here, I came too.
A girlfriend?
What? Did you think I'm not good enough to have a girlfriend?
- No!
- Nothing like that!
I envy your happiness!
How's your hunt for a marriage partner going?
It's hopeless!
I feel like I'm forever wading around in a pond with no fish!
Marriage isn't all that great!
After work, you come home exhausted, wash the mountain of dishes...
then wake up at 5:00 A.M. to do two loads of laundry. Does that sound fun?
Because you don't like listening to those complain, isn't that what got you to divorce, right?
Divorce? Who did?
Me?
Oh, I did, didn't I?
He's gotten divorced?
Dr. Tendo!
Glad you made it, Tendo! Have a seat.
You're the one who told me to come.
It's a rare occasion for you to join drinking parties!
Take a seat right next to Miss Hero! Sit, sit!
We'll get to the bottom of this today, for sure!
Bottom of what?
Those two.
Those two? Who and who?
Lower your voice.
Here you are!
Do you at least care for Miss Hero like the rest of us do, right?
Say what?
Of course, he does! He hugged her gently, after all!
"You're on Team Tendo, aren't you?"
What were you blabbing about?
I'm sorry!
Does that mean it's true?
What? She didn't just imagine it?
- What? Imagine what?
- I told you, those two—
Look!
I'm sorry for causing so much trouble over this!
But you're wrong. He was just taking care of me when I was sick.
It was nothing romantic!
- Wait, really?
- Obviously.
I keep messing up every day.
I always think that I'm not cut out for this job, so I should just quit.
It's true that...
I like Dr. Tendo.
I really like him.
But... that's why...
I want to become an outstanding nurse.
That's why... from now on,
I'm going to devote myself to my work! I'm going to press on!
I appreciate everyone's guidance and encouragement!
Fantastic!
Good for you, Miss Hero!
Thank you for listening!
Bottom's up!
Ah, wait! Dr. Koshikawa! You haven't drunk at all!
- Oh! Thanks for pouring my glass.
- Please allow me.
I can't lose, either.
What are you smiling about?
I was thinking about joining the game, too.
Excuse me!
One more beer, please!
Watch the stairs.
Man, she's completely drunk!
T-Take care of her, Tendo.
What?
Don't you live in the same building?
Let's go to round two!
- Let's go.
- Shall we?
- Let's go, Sakai!
- Take care of yourself, okay?
What a troublesome rock.
♪ Raw egg over rice, fermented beans, and rice! ♪
♪ Mix it up for a pick-me-up! ♪
Be quiet! You're causing a disturbance.
♪ Grated mountain yam over rice and okra rice! ♪
♪ Mix it up for a sticky— ♪
Shut up!
Water!
Here.
Drink it so we can get going.
The lid.
You'll remember this...
Of course, I'll remember.
You'll just get angry again, right?
"You idiot! You stupid rock!"
"You useless burden!"
No one's said that.
You can say it.
I'm just a... useless failure of a nurse.
If you were serious
about what you said before...
If you are serious about becoming an outstanding nurse...
I do want to. Seriously.
If so, I'll nurture you.
I wouldn't say that if you didn't have potential.
I'll make you indispensable.
So...
have confidence.
Even if you hit a wall,
just overcome it.
You too.
I wouldn't say overcome it, but...
After losing someone important,
and working so hard that everyone calls you the Devil,
it must be painful maintaining that stern expression all the time.
So I'll make you smile, Doctor.
Whether it's a forced smile, a half-smile, or laughing for joy...
Any will do!
As long as you're happy,
I'll be...
happy-happy-happy!
♫ I love... I stop saying in mid-sentence ♫
♫ I love, I love, so many times ♫
♫ In the midst of growing love and changing emotions ♫
♫ You shine brightly ♫
Don't fall asleep.
♫ Like paints diving into a water tank and melting ♫
♫ Irregular. I wouldn't have noticed... ♫
[An Incurable Case of Love | Love Will Last Forever]
[Next Episode: Is the Devil Jealous!?]
- Dating.
- With Dr. Kisugi?
Sakura, when did you swap over to Team Kisugi?
If I could see her one last time...
[Miss Hero hears a dying wish...]
I want her to want to live again!
- Stay back.
- Get out of my way!
[They stumble into dire straits!!]
- Doctor!
- I wish I could have spent more time with you.
Sakura!
[This drama is fiction.]