Mom
What happened?
Yiran
My heart...
The doctor said I only have a few days left.
I just hope that before I go,
I can see you have a happy family.
Mom
This is my boyfriend.
I've been busy with work.
So I haven't had a chance to tell you.
Enough already.
We both use the internet.
We already knew.
You know,
even if you don't want to marry Xiao Li,
you can't just bring home some random guy.
And cause a scandal.
Aren't you just degrading yourself?
What do you mean, "random guy"?
Uncle, I...
You, be quiet.
This isn't your place to speak.
Yiran, hurry up and get us some money.
Honey
Don't be so harsh with the child.
Yiran knows what she's doing.
What does she know?
Look at how sick you are now.
Can she really come up with the money?
Auntie is so seriously ill,
why isn't she in the ICU?
Mom
Are you doing this to pressure me into marriage again?
Are you putting on an act for me?
What?
Acting
Why is your mind always on acting?
You go
Go, go act in your play
Look at you, why is your life so hard?
We worked so hard to raise our daughter
But what's the use?
Dad, let's talk back in the hospital room
No, we'll talk right here
Let's make things clear now
Give me a straight answer
Your mom is this sick
Are you going to pay or not?
And you're supposed to be a big star
So unfilial
Yeah
Her mom is so seriously ill
And she's so indifferent
Truly heartless
Do you not have any money?
If you don't have money
Then you should
Hurry up and marry someone rich
Get money to treat your mom
I think that young Mr. Li is pretty good
Auntie is so seriously ill
Why are you two still arguing here?
None of your business
We've been discovered.
He's just a designated driver.
Can he even support you?
I can support him.
You want to support him?
Where would you get the money?
If you had money,
you should cure your mom's illness first.
Kid, let me tell you something.
As a man,
I can understand why you'd want to live off a woman.
But as your father, I advise you
to give up on that idea as soon as possible.
Dad, what are you saying?
Yiran,
it would be great if you married Li Tianhao.
You'd be a wealthy lady without any worries.
You don't have any acting jobs now anyway.
I'm your real mother, would I ever harm you?
Your conscience might not harm her,
but your ignorance might.
Auntie,
what gives you the right to talk to me like that?
I just saw your medical scans.
I didn't realize your illness was this serious.
Look here,
the heart,
liver, and stomach
all show shadows.
What does that mean?
What does this mean?
You—stop trying to curry favor here.
It's useless. Just be quiet, be quiet.
What does this mean?
It means you often get angry, causing your energy channels to become blocked.
Auntie, let me guess.
When you wake up in the middle of the night,
do you have a dry mouth and chest tightness?
And irregular heartbeat?
How did you know that?
I saw it from your scans.
You have deficiencies in both energy and blood.
Your heart pulse is weak.
For this kind of illness, anger is the worst thing.
Just imagine,
if, without realizing it,
you get angry,
and as a result, you still lose your mother because of it,
wouldn't that be harming her?
Is it really that serious?
My mom is really sick.
Your mom snores when she sleeps.
Are you lying to me?
Auntie, at a time like this,
would I lie to you?
Look,
after you got anxious just now,
didn't you get a bit of a headache?
My head...
Are you feeling dizzy?
Everything you said is true—my hands, my hands...
Let go, Auntie, don't worry.
Don't listen to his nonsense, dear.
You be quiet.
Xiaoye, how do I treat this?
Auntie, don't worry.
I'll prescribe you some herbal medicine.
Just take a few courses and you'll be fine.
But you must absolutely remember,
do not get angry.
Especially, do not pressure anyone to get married.
Thank you for today.
Cheers.
Taking the pulse
Prescribing medicine
How do you even know how to do these things?
Maybe because
I used to be
an old traditional Chinese doctor who helped people
An old Chinese doctor?
You saw it yourself today
This is my life
Isn't it pretty bad?
My parents
have never really cared about me
They just see me
as a money tree
and always want to control my life
I remember
once when I was filming
it was pouring rain
and I came down with a high fever
The crew told me to take a couple of days off
But my mom
was afraid I'd delay the shoot and break the contract
so she forced me to go to the set
I ended up fainting at the doorstep
My dad even thought I was faking it
just to slack off
Why am I even telling you all this?
It's all in the past now
Even though the lead female role was taken by someone else
I can start over
and work hard to get a new role
I can't talk about this anymore
If I keep talking, I'll cry
Let's have a drink
Don't go
Mom
Don't go, Mom
Don't leave me alone
I promise I'll make money for you
Why does something strange happen every time I get close to her
and strange images always appear?
Wake up.
Today is the eye-opening launch event.
We have to go.
I've already been replaced.
Why should I still go?
I just want to give it a try.
Because today, there's someone
very important coming.
Alright, I'll go change.
And get ready.
Why is she still coming here?
Exactly.
Does she even have the right to be here?
Thank you.
So shameless.
Look over here, look here!
She thinks she deserves to be here?
Yeah.
Long time no see, long time no see.
It's been a while.
New boyfriend? Is it official?
Really?
Song Yiran.
Why are you here?
You've already been replaced.
Still not giving up?
I know.
You really, really want to be in this movie.
I understand how you feel.
But without me,
you can't make it happen.
Don't worry, Yiran.
With your popularity and talent,
the investors will make their own decisions.
Let me tell you now,
the entertainment industry is all about fame and fortune.
There are plenty of talented people out there.
Not everyone can be the leading lady.
Yeah, the entertainment industry is huge.
Does your Li family think they can control everything?
Well, sorry to say,
our Li family really does have that power.
You don't know President Su, do you?
The main investor.
So, do you think
she'll listen to me
or to you?
If you
agree to marry me,
I'll definitely put in a good word with Mr. Su.
The lead female role will still be yours.
Thank you.
No need.
Mr. Su, this way please.
Mr. Su.
The latest casting proposal—
Have you seen it?
Yue Linglong is the most suitable for the lead female role.
You don't need to ask me about these things.
You and your son can handle the details.
I'm only responsible for the investment.
Thank you, Mr. Su, for your support.
This way, please.
Hello, Mr. Su.
I think, as a film investor,
what should be considered more is
the quality and market of the film,
not just the profit.
Wait, hold on.
Who do you think you are?
Are you lecturing Mr. Su?
Go on.
First,
a lot of promotion has already been done for the film.
Changing the lead at the last minute is inappropriate.
Your previous films have all had great reputations.
Casting suitability is the most important thing.
In terms of appearance,
Song Yiran is also more suitable.
So you mean
What I mean is
to keep Song Yiran as the female lead.
Maintain the original casting.
What do you think?
Who do you think you are?
Why should Mr. Su listen to you?
Listen to him.
Switch the female lead back to Song Yiran.
Done.
I... I don't think Song Yiran is suitable.
What's your reason?
Look,
I'm only thinking about the project.
She's surrounded by negative news right now.
Plus, the contract termination issue.
I don't care about any of the risks.
I'll take responsibility for any consequences.
We'll use Song Yiran as the female lead.
Look at him again.
He's just a lousy driver.
Living off her.
How can we use someone like that?
Why should we listen to him?
Because I believe in him.
And one more thing.
What you just said,
I hope it's the last time I hear it.
Just you wait.
Thank you, President Su.
How will you thank me?
I'm always grateful and repay kindness.
However you want me to thank you, I will.
Come to my house at 3 p.m.
Come alone.