Mr. Li
The task is complete.
Ye Wuming is dead.
I pushed him downstairs.
I made it look like he died from a fall.
Good.
Once things quiet down,
and I’ve confirmed the body,
I’ll transfer the money to you.
Mr. Li
You’re truly impressive.
You actually managed to use public opinion
to make Ye Wuming look like a murder suspect.
Park Nanzhi had a car accident on the way to the hospital.
His death can’t be for nothing.
No one will care whether he lives or dies.
Everyone only knows that Ye Wuming hit him.
What about the smear video of Song Yiran?
How did you manage that, Mr. Li?
After all, I’ve been in film and television for decades.
I used montage techniques
to splice the video together.
Thirty percent truth, seventy percent fake.
No one can tell the difference.
Brilliant.
It really is brilliant.
Mr. Li
How is it?
Surprised to see me, aren't you?
You...
You're not dead.
How could I, Wuming, possibly die?
It must have been tough for you.
You really wanted to wipe the two of us out.
Nice acting.
So you were all putting on a show for me, huh?
Since we're all in the entertainment industry now,
of course we have to learn some acting skills.
Stop.
Are you okay?
Wuming.
It's a real shame you're not an actor.
Brother Wuming.
You acted so well.
I almost want to be your agent.
With my limited skills,
I can only fool Mr. Li by filming with my phone.
Let's hope he falls for it.
But how did you know
that Mr. Li would definitely come looking for us?
He's naturally suspicious.
He definitely wouldn't believe it so easily.
Just because you two changed.
So we turned his own trick against him.
Call him.
Okay.
Hello, Mr. Li.
Let's meet up.
There's a surprise.
Let's go.
Let's go see him.
What you just said
I've already recorded it all
With this testimony
we can prove Yiran's innocence
I recorded it too
There are two copies
Song Yiran
You're ungrateful
President Li
How many times have you said that line?
Don't you have anything new to say?
You know how fast my blade is
You know that
Brother Wuming won't let anyone leave
No one is leaving today
Isn't he your target?
Why are you following him?
The two of us sisters
Our greatest skill is shapeshifting
But in front of Brother Wuming
it's useless
He's someone we truly admire
and the most worthy to follow
Fine
I admit defeat
I give up
As long as you let me go,
I'll clarify that you didn't kill that person.
And I'll admit that the incriminating video
was made by me.
It's too late.
If you knew this would happen, why did you do it in the first place?
Everything you just said,
I can do right now.
So what do you want?
I just want you to confess and accept your punishment.
Boss Ye,
aren't you pushing your luck?
The rest
save it for the police.
Keep an eye on him.
Brother,
Mr. Li is already in a vegetative state.
The doctor said
there's no chance of him waking up.
Kai,
have you found out who hit him?
Yes, we found out.
It's just an ordinary office worker.
He has no connection to the Four Major Corporations.
From the scene,
it looks like a regular traffic accident.
How is that possible?
There's no way it was just a coincidence.
There must be a conspiracy.
All coincidences are carefully planned.
Mr. Li getting hit is definitely not simple.
I went to his house and company.
This guy took all the blame
onto himself.
He completely cleared his bastard son, Li Tianhao,
of any involvement.
Li Tianhao is such a coward.
He didn't even care about his own father and just ran away.
But don't worry, brother.
Our people are still searching.
We'll dig him out sooner or later.
By the way,
I found a USB drive
in his safe.
I've copied everything onto it.
Hello, Mr. Ye Wuming.
By the time you see this video,
I should already be dead.
This drive contains all
the evidence of me slandering you and Song Yiran.
Of course,
there is also a video of me apologizing to you.
Having come to this point,
I am no longer in a position to negotiate with you.
However,
I still sincerely beg you to spare Tianhao.
Because he is no longer a threat to you.
This is a father's
final request.
Thank you.
Although this man has done many bad things,
he can barely be considered a qualified father.
Forget it.
No need to look for Li Tianhao.
Upload this video online.
Go ahead.
Recently,
a video was released online
of an apology from Li, an executive at a film company,
along with evidence of slander.
Ye Wuming, chairman of Wuwei Pictures,
was cleared of murder suspicion.
The public controversy surrounding actress Song Yiran
was also resolved.
The suspect, Li,
became comatose in a car accident
during the investigation.
The case is still under investigation.
The public security authorities
will pursue criminal responsibility according to the law.
No Name
Thank you.
Do we really need to say this between us?
The online controversy has passed now.
I want to make an official announcement this time.
To make our relationship public.
Still,
Although Mr. Li has been dealt with,
he was just a pawn.
The mastermind behind the scenes is still there.
So we should act even more discreetly.
Alright, I'll listen to you.
Senior Brother
I'm here to apologize.
Come in and let's talk.
Senior Brother
Sister Yiran
I came this time
just to apologize to you both.
I shouldn't have lost my mind.
I listened to what President Li said
and did those things.
I caused trouble for both of you.
I'm truly sorry.
It's okay, Linglong.
Actually, we should thank you too.
After going through all this,
it made me even more certain
about my feelings for Wuming.
Let the past stay in the past.
We should all look forward.
Don't you think?
Sister Yiran
You're so generous.
It makes me feel even worse about what I did before.
Junior Sister
Your contract with President Li
should be automatically terminated now.
If you don't mind, you can sign with me.
It's okay, Senior Brother.
I've already agreed to go with Senior Sister.
That's fine.
We'll definitely have a chance to work together again in the future.
That's good too.
We're all family.
Senior Sister will definitely help you too.
Then I'll get going.
I wish you both happiness.
Do you feel it's a pity?
Such a good Junior Sister,
and she truly cares about you.
What do you think?
Dad
I will definitely avenge you.
Yiran
This is the last scene.
You're the one driving.
And then,
the lions and tigers
are chasing you from behind.
And then,
as you keep driving,
the lights suddenly go out.
They go out.
Then you get out of the car.
You check what's going on.
Connect the power.
The power is connected.
Then, as soon as you touch the switch,
then you
get electrocuted.
But don't worry,
nothing is actually connected over there.
The fuse box isn't connected, it's very safe.
It's all fake, fake.
Okay, okay, I understand.
I understand.
Will this really electrocute her?
Only if Song Yiran dies
will it count as avenging my dad.
Okay.
Alright, take a moment to get ready, okay?
All departments, get ready.
We're about to start filming.
No problem.
Episode 24, Scene 12.
One take.
Three, two, one, action.
Okay, stop, pass.
One take, passed.
Awesome, Yiran!
Yiran.
Dad.
I avenged you.