Come on, everyone, keep up.
Everyone, keep up.
Everyone, take a good look.
This is Ye Wuming, the one who killed the master of Nanzheng.
Everyone,
I'm reporting this at great risk.
I might be in danger.
If I don't show up in the next few days,
please call the police for me.
Everyone, listen to me.
Let me give you a grand introduction.
This person here
is the famous Ye Wuming, President Ye.
He used filming a movie as an excuse
to beat a friend of Nanzheng to death.
And now he can still
sit here like nothing happened.
Who will speak up for the deceased?
Impossible.
I used soft force, it couldn't have hurt anyone.
This is soft force?
One punch sent him flying over ten meters.
Everyone, record this well.
Look, his internal organs were knocked out.
Guys,
You can't judge a book by its cover.
Look at how handsome he is,
who would have thought
he's actually a vicious villain.
If I really wanted to kill him,
it wouldn't have to be so complicated.
Did you see that?
The murderer is threatening us.
Everyone, take a good look.
Stop!
Who allowed you to come in?
Mr. Su.
You came here today—
You're not here to cover up for the murderer, are you?
Li Tianhao, stop trying to confuse right and wrong.
Park Nanzhi died on the way to the hospital
in a car accident.
The coroner has already issued a report.
It has nothing to do with Senior Ye Wuming.
You expect anyone to believe that?
How come I heard
that the fake car accident was staged by you
to cover up the truth?
That's right.
Don't use these questionable things
to fool us.
We want the truth.
Yes, we want the truth.
Show us the truth.
Fine.
I'll give you the truth.
These are photos from the accident scene,
and the hospital's vital sign records upon admission,
as well as the coroner's autopsy report.
These pieces of evidence are enough to show
that Park Nanzhi's death
has no direct connection to Ye Wuming.
Aren't you all here for the truth?
Go ahead, record it.
Get closer with your camera.
What are you filming for?
Besides,
it's so easy for you to fake evidence.
If Ye Wuming hadn't injured Park Namjik,
how would Park Namjik have ended up in the hospital?
I'm sure
Ye Wuming is directly connected to Park Namjik's death.
Am I right, everyone?
Yes, that's right.
I think you people are just here to cause trouble.
You want the truth, right?
I already called the police before I came.
Just you wait.
Notify the lawyer.
Every single one of you spreading rumors and slander,
will be sued.
Sorry, junior.
It was my oversight.
I let them bother you.
That person just now,
do I have a grudge against him?
You mean that tall guy?
Of course you do.
It's all because of Song Yiran.
Junior brother,
about this matter,
they are deliberately trying to frame and slander you.
No matter what you say,
they won't believe you.
Don't let it weigh on your mind.
The innocent will always be clear; you don't need to worry about them.
I understand, senior sister.
I know my limits.
I know.
That's good.
I'll publish this evidence online.
As for you, just focus on your recovery.
I've already bought this sanatorium.
The security has also been replaced with our people.
From now on,
this kind of thing won't happen again.
Every single person spreading rumors and slander,
will be sued.
There were too many people at the scene back then.
Ye Wuming was cleared of suspicion.
We couldn't frame him successfully.
Now we can only mix truth with lies.
There are two opinions online right now.
Some say he brought honor to the country.
Others are calling for a life for a life.
Let them argue about it.
Only when there's debate does it get attention.
This time, Mr. Li,
you did a good job.
It's all thanks to your strategic planning, Mr. Feng.
Next,
how do you want to stir things up, Mr. Feng?
Su Mingzhu will definitely make the evidence public.
But people only like to hear gossip.
As long as we blow things up before she exposes it,
make the situation big,
no one will care about the truth.
Spending a fortune just to make a beauty smile.
Fighting fiercely to steal someone's love.
Pretending to have amnesia to cover up the truth about the murder.
Pretending to have amnesia.
It's refreshing to talk to smart people.
You're still the clever one, Mr. Feng.
Using public opinion to destroy someone mentally.
I'll find someone right now
to write this press release.
Come in.
Senior Brother.
Junior Sister.
It's time to take your medicine.
Why are you dressed like this?
Master will be angry if he sees you.
Why are you making it sound so scary?
I picked this out especially.
So, do you like it?
I'm really nervous too, Senior Brother.
My heart is beating really fast right now.
Do you want to feel it?
Stop messing around. Go back to sleep.
Just feel it and see.
Junior Sister, stop fooling around with me.
Master taught you martial arts
not so you could avoid romance.
We already have a marriage arrangement.
We'll end up together sooner or later.
Master was just joking about that.
Don't bring this up again.
How could that be a joke?
A teacher for a day is like a father for life.
Master wants us to be together
because he thinks we're a good match.
Senior Brother, you wouldn't go against Master's wishes, would you?
Senior Brother.
Come on.
But in my heart,
you've always been like a younger sister.
Then let your little sister give you a hug.
Song... Song Yiran.
What did you say?
Junior Brother
Senior Sister
Right now, the internet is flooded with news
all saying you're suspected of murder.
They all claim it was an on-set accident.
An international friend was sent to the ICU.
They even released some
maliciously edited videos.
They don't mention the car accident at all.
Senior Sister
Those self-defense materials are useless.
They've had little effect.
The legal team has also responded to their rumors
by sending lawyer's letters.
But it hasn't helped much.
They're taking things out of context.
Even if they're caught,
they'll just say the reports are incomplete
and didn't follow up on the aftermath.
It doesn't affect the spread at all.
Looks like they're targeting me.
It's okay.
I think we should stay put for now.
They'll show their true colors sooner or later.
So just stay here and rest easy.
Don't go out these days.
Wait until they come out into the open.
Okay.
I'll head out now.
Get some rest early.
Get up.
Senior Brother.
Why are you so insensitive?
Senior Brother, come a little closer.
Junior Sister, Junior Sister.
Yes, yes.
Don't move.
Junior Sister.
Junior Sister, I said no.
Why not?
Alright.
Senior Brother.
Junior Sister.
Wait a moment, Junior Sister.
Have you made enough of a fuss?
Stop messing around.
Go back to sleep.
Get some rest early.
I thought you had already let it go.
Senior lost his memory before.
I gave my blessings to him and Yiran.
Now his memory has returned.
Why shouldn't I give it a try?
I've already lost once.
I can't lose again.
Only those who lack confidence are afraid to lose.
Senior sister.
I know you like him too.
Why do you say that?
Then why won't you let him see Song Yiran?
You clearly know that seeing her now
is when it's easiest for him to regain his memory.
Besides,
I've never seen you care about someone this much.
Do you like him?
Yes.
Senior sister.
It's me who is engaged to senior.
That was just a joke Master made before.
You're the only one who took it seriously.
Master doesn't joke about things like that.
Our engagement is real.
Hello
Yiran
They said Wuming can't see you
They're lying to you
These days are when he
is most likely to regain his memory
Ma San, how do you know that?
I just overheard it at the sanatorium
Sis, you need to think of something quickly
Otherwise, Wuming will really forget you
Then I'll go over now
Sis
There are a lot of people guarding the entrance
You can't get in
Maybe you should think of another way
Okay, I got it
Taste can trigger people's earliest memories
Brother
Try this tomato and scrambled eggs
So, does it remind you of anything?
It tastes terrible
Thanks for your hard work, Kai
Actually
You don't have to make it so tense every time
It's fine
Mr. Ye gave instructions
When he's not around
we're supposed to protect you
So he was behind the scenes
quietly doing so much for me
This is an alarm
Press this if anything happens
We'll be nearby
Thank you, Kai
I'll head back now
But this taste is very familiar.
I must have eaten it somewhere before.
All of this was made by Sister Yiran herself.
It wasn't easy for me to bring it in.
Yiran.
Song Yiran.
Yes, yes, that's right.
That name sounds familiar too.
But I really can't remember.
It's okay, bro.
It doesn't matter if you can't remember.
We can always get to know each other again.
You two can as well.
Sister Yiran.
I'm not someone who likes to beat around the bush.
Tell me where that bank card is.
I can spare your life.
That bank card...
I really have destroyed it.
Then there's nothing I can do.
You could have used it to buy your life.
When the enemy is strong and I'm weak,
the first thing is to block the opponent's line of sight.
After the power is cut,
the attacker will guard the main door right away.
To prevent you from escaping.
Find a place to hide.
Make sure not to make any noise.
Try to find a way to call for help.
You want to call the police, right?
You really underestimate me.
I've already blocked the signal here.
Remember,
no matter how the other side tries to lure you out,
never come out.
Three years ago, you killed Ye Wuming's master.
He'll find out sooner or later.
I didn't kill his master.
So you were here all along.
Then go explain it to him.
See if he believes you.
I believe you.
It's okay now, Yiran.
Yiran.
I'm here.
Wuming.
Sister Yiran.
You don't know how good I am at imitating, do you?
Yiran, come here.
Let big brother take good care of you.
I suggest you hand over your bank card quickly.
Or else, on your pretty little face,
I'll carve a flower.
I advise you not to do that.
Wuming.
Weren't you at the hospital?
Surprised I got away, aren't you?
Let's go.
You...
How did you get out?