Come to my place at 3 p.m.
How did you know you needed to win her over?
Is there something going on between you two?
Let me make it clear first.
I really don't know her, this is my first time meeting her.
There's really nothing between us.
It's truly our first meeting.
What exactly does President Su want from me?
Could it be...
...the so-called unspoken rules?
President Su.
That smile...
Is something going to happen?
Judging by her expression...
Is she really going to make a move on me?
Why is it taking so long for them to come out?
What are they talking about?
Hello?
I'm not buying a house, thank you.
Junior apprentice.
We finally meet again.
President Su.
You must have mistaken me for someone else.
I don't know you.
This is the protective armguard from Master for you.
It can enhance your strength.
Do you sometimes feel...
...like you can't control yourself?
Yes.
President Su, what else do you know?
Three years ago, you left the mountain for training.
Since then, there’s been no news from you.
I didn't expect it was because of amnesia.
Drop your shoulders.
Lower your elbows.
Tuck in your chest.
I remember Master now.
The day you left,
Master also passed away.
But Master was perfectly fine.
How could he have died?
There are so many suspicious points about this.
It's very strange.
I must find out the cause of Master's death.
Junior Brother,
stop being a bodyguard.
Come be the vice president at my Mingzhu Group.
Let's investigate together.
I promised Song Yiran to be her bodyguard.
One must keep their word.
Is she
very important to you?
I don't know.
Alright.
Then I respect your choice.
But the vice president position
will always be open for you.
You can come anytime.
Thank you for your kindness, President Su.
But
if you are really my Senior Sister,
why didn't you come to find me before?
There must be a conspiracy behind Master's death.
To ensure your and Junior Sister's safety,
I think we shouldn't reveal our relationship for now.
Do you know what President Su said?
She said she didn't miss you.
Do you want to know?
What just happened upstairs?
I'm not that curious.
Alright.
Then I won't say.
Let's go.
If you really want to say it,
then go ahead.
Ms. Su said
she's my senior.
Senior?
Ms. Su is your senior?
Yue Linglong is your junior?
Is your whole group having a team-building event?
No idea.
Let's go home.
Let's find a media outlet.
Say that Song Yiran is hiding a lover.
And not just one man.
Sis, we can buy a trending topic.
Sure.
Buy a trending topic.
You're the smart one.
Song Yiran.
Last time I didn't take your lead role.
This time,
don't blame me for being ruthless.
Senior brother,
I will definitely win you back.
Don't talk, just come with me.
I can't walk fast in these shoes.
Sorry.
They were just two reporters.
We can't take any chances, understand?
Let's go.
They're coming out! They're coming out!
Hurry, hurry!
Take pictures, quick!
Song Yiran.
Song Yiran! Song Yiran!
Rumor has it you're keeping lovers in secret.
That you have several men.
Is it true?
Your public boyfriend, Ye Wuming—
—is he just a cover?
Please answer, please answer, Song Yiran!
Song Yiran! Song Yiran!
Please answer my question.
Why are you hitting people now?
Seriously...
It's not just trending online.
Even my home address has been exposed.
If it's not President Li,
then it's your junior who did it.
They just want to make my life miserable.
Looks like your place isn't safe.
Let's get a hotel room.
A hotel won't work.
Let's go to your place.
My place?
My place won't do.
I share it with San'er.
And it's old and shabby.
You definitely wouldn't be comfortable there.
Can you stop thinking I'm so delicate?
I'm used to wearing high heels.
I can even walk barefoot.
And isn't it better if we don't stand out?
Does your house have a back door?
The entrance is soft and smooth.
One sip and you can tell it's pure grain liquor.
Brilliant.
San'er.
Brother Wuming.
You, you...
Why are you back, bro?
Couldn't get used to living in the celebrity's mansion?
Is that it? You first...
Put your clothes on first.
What's wrong, bro?
I see you've been living in this big mansion for a while.
Hello.
Are you Ma San?
An idol!
Why, why are you here?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sit, sit, sit.
Sit here, sit, sit, sit, sit here.
San'er, tidy up a bit.
Bro, what's going on?
Why didn't you say you were bringing the goddess over to hang out?
Not to hang out, she's living here.
Living here?
So we'll be roommates from now on.
Roommates with a celebrity?
Not us, just the two of us.
That's fine then.
We can squeeze in together, just the two of us.
Sorry for disturbing you.
I heard from Wuming
that you've always wanted to travel, right?
I don't want to...
No.
You do.
I happen to have
an invitation from a foreign tour group.
You can go for as long as you want.
No, no, no.
No, it's not like that, this—
I'll make up your salary, double.
It's not about the money.
Mainly, I just really want to travel.
Isn't that right, bro?
Bro.
Right?
Isn't it?
I knew you liked to travel.
Let me tell you,
Southeast Asia is really great.
The fruit is delicious.
It rains a lot—you like rain, don't you?
It's been a while since you washed, huh?
San'er, Song Yiran coming to my place is supposed to be a secret.
You absolutely can't tell anyone.
Don't worry, bro.
Me, I'm the kind of person
who keeps my mouth shut.
Alright.
Then I wish you a pleasant trip.
Call me when you arrive.
Okay.
Let's go, San'er.
We're leaving, bro.
Hello, Linglong.
Guess who's back.
My bro Wuming is back.
And he brought Song Yiran with him.
So about this...
It's complicated, sis.
He even knows Su Mingzhu.
This guy is really hiding his true abilities.
Looks like it's time to play a trump card.
Boss, who are we waiting for?
Mr. Li
I’ve been posing as Song Yiran’s manager.
For so many years.
Are you sure you want to play this trump card of mine now?
Do you really want to use it now?
Lu Bingqing
Originally, I shouldn’t have revealed you so soon.
I shouldn’t have played this ace so early.
But now Song Yiran wants to terminate her contract.
There’s no point in you staying hidden any longer.
This Ye Wuming is not simple.
I still haven’t figured out his background.
Don’t worry.
Leave it to me.
I’ve been a manager for so long.
Surrounded by nightlife every day.
My skills haven’t gotten rusty, have they?
Boss
You—this...
Mr. Li
If I had just been holding a knife,
you’d be dead by now.
Sleight of hand.
Alright.
Defeat Ye Wuming.
Get back the bank card from Song Yiran.
Bring it back to me.
The money will be transferred to your offshore account.
And one more thing.
Remember, don’t break the law.
I don’t want to get the police involved.
Boss, I’m leaving.
Beautiful.
Come in.
How is it?
Looks good.
You adapted really quickly.
You tidied up so well.
Of course.
Don't treat me like
a helpless actress.
Four years ago,
I was just someone working hard
to make a living as a small-time actress.
So all these things
I had to do myself.
It's so dirty.
That's why I said,
I'm easy to get along with.
If you think
I'm not easygoing enough,
maybe you should look at your own issues.
What do you think?
Me? What issues do I have?
Figure it out yourself.
I'm going to take a shower.
Dirty?
Just a little bee.
How did you get in?
Take a guess.
You sly dog, Ma San.
What do you want?
Senior brother.
I came to help you get your memory back.
It's too late today. Let's talk tomorrow.
It's not late, senior brother.
Senior brother.
Are you going to choke me again?
Who's going to choke you?
I just want to flirt with you.
If Yiran sees this,
how will I explain it?
I need to get her to leave quickly.
I don't want to talk about the past with you right now.
Then let's not think about the past.
Let's focus on the present.
Do you like me?
Guess.
I do.
Guess again.
I'm a bit thirsty.
Why don't you pour me a glass of water?
Once this passion candle is lit,
as long as you inhale the scent,
it will arouse desire.
Drink this glass of water, then leave.
Senior brother.
When will we trim the candlewick together by the western window?
And talk about the rainy nights in Bashan?
Come on.