Healthy living, beautiful morning.
Celebrities really are disciplined.
This is yours.
I'll eat this.
No.
Isn't that a bit fake?
Persona.
It's all just personas.
No, no.
Did you forget?
You said tomorrow you have a scene
where the lead actress is hungry for three days.
You need to experience hunger.
Oh, right.
That scene is really important to me.
The role comes first, I'll stay hungry for now.
Good evening.
Are you okay?
I haven't eaten all day.
I have to do well in this scene.
You can do it, boss.
Once we get through tonight,
we can have a big meal.
Sit down first, let's have a feast.
I'll get you a glass of water.
Sis,
why do you look so pale?
Your face looks so sunken.
You're not looking much better yourself.
Don't talk about me.
I haven't eaten all day either.
But sis,
I have some incense here.
Smell it, quick.
It'll help you feel refreshed.
Don't collapse during the shoot later.
How is it?
You two teachers,
get ready for the next scene.
Okay.
Get ready to run through the scene.
Boss.
Yiran.
What happened?
Where's the medical staff? Hurry, get the medical staff!
It's due to prolonged starvation.
This has caused bodily dysfunction.
There's also hypoglycemia.
Administer glucose intravenously.
She should wake up soon.
She inhaled the calming incense I specially prepared.
I guarantee you'll sleep until tomorrow and still not wake up.
What's going on?
We're behind schedule again.
We can only use this set today.
It's been booked by others after today.
This is the most important scene.
The two sisters are struggling to survive together.
We can't do it without either of them.
Director, I have an idea.
How about we change the script a bit?
Let's make it so the older sister is unconscious.
The younger sister tries desperately to save her.
That classic line from Yiran,
let me say it instead.
There's no other way.
We can only try this.
She worked so hard for this scene.
If we change it now,
she'll definitely be heartbroken.
Director.
Give me ten minutes, I can wake her up.
I've tried for so long and she still hasn't woken up.
Ten minutes? How is that possible?
Send her to the hospital right away.
If you mess around,
I'm not responsible if anything goes wrong.
I'll give you five minutes.
All departments, get ready.
We'll shoot with the new plan.
Yiran has overexerted herself too much.
Even giving her medicine doesn't help.
Senior, acupuncture isn't working.
Quiet.
Don't waste any more time.
Hurry and get them to the hospital.
Give all the lines to Linglong.
Awake, awake, awake!
Really awake.
This is amazing.
That's impossible.
They smelled my incense.
And woke up so quickly.
Still, really awake.
Awake.
This is incredible.
Director.
Sorry.
I just need to touch up my makeup and I can shoot.
No need, no need, no need.
You look perfect right now.
It fits the survival scene perfectly.
Let's shoot it like this.
Let's shoot it like this, director.
That shot...
Get ready, get ready, get ready.
Ready for the actual shoot.
Move aside.
Here we go.
You can do it!
Okay.
Come on.
One take.
Three, two, one.
Action.
Sister.
Younger sister.
What doesn't kill us
makes us stronger.
So no matter what,
we must never give up hope.
Sister.
Stop.
Done.
Alright, alright.
Thank you, director. Thank you. Alright.
Thank you for your hard work.
Good job, good job. Let's take a break.
Let's rest first.
Okay, let's go eat something first.
Okay.
That was great.
Let's go, let's eat.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Thank you, teacher.
Thank you.
Take a break.
Director, how was my performance?
What are all these?
Health food.
You often post about them on Weibo.
They're all yours.
All those personas on Weibo are just for show.
Do you even know what a persona is?
It's all fake. You actually believe that?
I don't get it.
I'm doing this for your own good.
You've just recovered from a serious illness. Eat some of this.
Just make do with it.
I'm not settling for that.
Look at all this green food.
Do you think you're feeding a rabbit?
I want Kung Pao Chicken.
Braised pork.
Crayfish.
I suggest you think this through.
Someone on your right is taking your picture.
How do you know?
I love eating these green foods the most.
Tasty means healthy.
Let's quietly switch seats now.
Why switch seats?
My left side looks better on camera.
Aren't your left and right sides the same?
What do you know?
Different angles, lighting,
and even my hair.
The way my face looks in photos
is totally different.
Come stand next to me.
You need a bodyguard even when you eat?
Get closer.
A little closer.
Tilt your head like this.
Okay.
Let's give them a shot of us hugging and kissing.
Make our relationship look more real.
You celebrities are so fake.
Sorry, sorry.
Sit back down.
Did you do that on purpose?
I didn't do it on purpose. Someone just...
You don't believe me.
Then let's do it again.
Go back.
Sit down.
Open your mouth.
Let me see.
That's it?
And you still speak up for her every day.
Is this really my artist?
Who does things like this?
Mr. Li, please don't be angry.
There must be some misunderstanding here.
I'll go talk to her again.
Don't worry.
Look.
They're even trying to trick me with camera angles.
These two have been playing me all along.
Still trying to pull this on me.
Bingqing.
I know you're doing this for my own good.
But dating is my personal business.
Besides, it hasn't affected my work.
Alright, alright.
Let's not talk about this for now.
We're here.
Finally, I can eat.
I think people should be genuine inside and out.
You can't act one way online and another in real life.
Those are all just official statements.
Besides, I'm an actor.
Just think of it as me creating a character.
Then why not create
a sincere character?
Life wouldn't be so exhausting.
Then I'll eat later.
Tell me first,
how did you notice today
that person was secretly taking photos?
I heard the sound of his camera shutter.
You could hear it from that far away?
Then when I usually
am alone in my bedroom...
Last night when you were sleeping...
Ye Wuming, you—
I'm done talking to you.
I'm going to sleep.
Ye Wuming.
Boss
We still have the prop bear from your last movie.
Go
Lao Qi
Big Brother, I'm here, I'm here.
Go, go, go
Let me tell you
I'll give you one more chance
I think this Song Yiran is
not giving up until the bitter end
Take some people to the set and scare her
Got it, Big Brother
I'll take care of it right away
Let's go
Today
Let's really scare Song Yiran
Mr. Li will make sure everyone is rewarded
Don't worry, bro
We'll definitely make her regret it
Ms. Song
Director
Today's scene
is about the female lead returning from surviving on a deserted island
coming to attend this party
While you're dancing
some thugs
will try to approach you and harm you
Grab your props
Find something handy
But don't worry
These thugs are all our stuntmen
You'll be very safe
Okay? Okay
Come on, Ms. Song, please come inside
Alright
Okay, three, two, one
Action
Extras, come in
Let's go
Why are you here?
Your posture is wrong—hold the waist.
Someone wants to hurt you.
They dare to be so blatant?
Don't worry, I'm here.
I've already called the police.
Continue.
Keep going.
Why can't I see the wire?
Okay, stop.
Assistant director.
Where are the actors? Why are they all out of frame?
The lead is in the frame, director.
I'm talking about the stunt team.
Um...
They flew out.
Bro, how are you doing these days?
San'er.
It's a long story.
No way, bro.
You all slept together?
You, you, you...
What are you doing?
Can you respect my privacy, please?
You're my bodyguard.
Only I get privacy.
You don't.
Why are you still up so late? What are you doing?
Let me tell you...
Every time I close my eyes,
I feel like someone wants to hurt me.
I need you to stay by my side and protect me.
You're still not out of character?
I'm going to take a shower.
Go stand guard at the door for me.
Don't come in.
Just stand here and protect me.
Don't stand too close.
But don't stand too far away either.
Don't go past that.
Otherwise, it might bite you.
It fell over.
Should I pick it up if it falls?
I didn't see anything, I didn't see.
Didn't see.
Why do you still have cigarettes?
I'm taking a shower.
The body wash that female celebrities use smells pretty nice.
What brand is it?
I can only hear the sound.
It's so frustrating not being able to see anything.
It fell over again.
I’ll prop it up again.
Those guys all got arrested by the police.
How many times have I told you not to break the law?
Don’t do things like this on your own again.
Mr. Li,
When Ye Wuming gets into a fight,
he’s like a wild beast.
He’s not even the same kind as us.
We really can’t hurt him.
You’re so resourceful.
You’ll definitely come up with a better solution.
You...
I’ve already set up a big plan.
First,
at tomorrow’s “Eye-Opener” event,
during the press conference,
we’ll announce that the female lead
will be changed from Song Yiran to Yue Linglong.
This year,
the company is mainly promoting her.
Sorry, sis.
This time,
I’m taking your lead role.
Then we’ll buy a trending topic.
Let her get caught up in the casting controversy.
Her reputation will collapse.
The last move is the trump card.
Persuade her leeching parents.
Uncle.
Las Vegas.
You owe quite a lot in gambling debts, don't you?
I heard the interest alone is skyrocketing.
It's almost ten million, right?
It's ten million.
She was just replaced.
It's all over the internet.
Her career is over.
She has no income.
How are you going to pay off your gambling debts now?
You'd better think this through.
No one can betray me.
I want Song Yiran's career and family
to be ruined at the same time.