Mr. Li
I'm here to make a bet with you.
Looking for me?
What are we betting on?
If tomorrow, "Needle in the Embroidery"
can have preview screenings in 200 theaters across the city,
then all the shares of the film will belong to me.
And I'll have nothing more to do with you.
Brother
You only have five theaters under your control right now.
You think you can secure 200 theaters in one night?
Mr. Li, you—
I'm talking to you.
Alright.
I accept your bet.
If you win,
I'll give you all my shares of "Needle in the Embroidery."
All of them.
But if you lose,
her new film "Eye-Opener"
all the shares you have in Wuwei Pictures
you have to give them all to me.
Deal.
Brother Kai, Brother Kai, Brother Kai
Brother Kai
You guys go over there.
We'll go this way.
Okay.
Boss Ye
Have some tea.
Manager Li, how did it go?
No problem, no problem.
Boss Ye is really loaded now.
He thinks money can buy everything.
But reality is often very cruel.
Money isn't all-powerful.
It can't buy off every theater manager
out there.
I don't lack money at all.
Take your money and get lost.
Don't try to threaten or bribe me.
I won't agree to it.
How many are left on this side?
There are two left.
Let's hurry up.
Bro,
this probably isn't your wife, right?
What should we do, Dad?
They've already closed deals with 164 theaters.
Go make some arrangements.
Find twenty
theater managers who are close to us.
Make sure they don't give in, no matter what.
Got it.
Boss Ye, have some tea.
It's nine o'clock.
No rush.
The theater doesn't open until ten.
It's so early in the morning.
Let's not bother others.
There are 204 theaters in the whole city.
Our family alone controls twenty of them.
You're bound to lose.
Young man,
do you know why you're losing?
I'd like to hear the details.
You're too arrogant and showy.
You only see the surface.
We're betting on 200 theaters.
As long as I control a small portion of them,
you won't achieve your goal.
You should know,
ruining something
is easier than accomplishing something.
It's much easier.
No wonder you're Mr. Li.
Even something so despicable
you can make sound so dignified.
A loss is a loss.
Why so much nonsense?
Lao Qi,
bring the contract.
You're so sure of yourselves.
Aren't you afraid I'll make a comeback?
You think this is a novel?
A comeback, really?
How are you so sure
there are only 204 theaters in our city?
Who are you people?
Manager Zhang, right?
Yes.
We're here to invest and save your business.
You really came to our aid in our time of need.
Our thirty public welfare cinemas
were about to close down.
With this funding
we can reopen right away.
The movie that's about to be screened
I'll arrange it immediately.
I'll sign right now.
Please take a look.
Not very good.
Today,
214 cinemas in our city
officially held preview screenings.
The film starring the famous actress Song Yiran
"Needle Hidden in Embroidery"
The audience was very enthusiastic.
Tickets sold out instantly.
It caused a huge sensation.
This move brought things back to life.
It's quite clever.
President Li has such a good reputation in the industry.
I believe
he will definitely keep his promise.
Good tea.
Who does he think he is?
You should be asking me what to do.
What should I do?
How would I know what to do?
Kai, you really have hidden talents.
It's all thanks to Mr. Ye's arrangements.
I just help out by running errands with the guys.
Mr. Ye.
Thanks for your hard work, Kai.
I've already transferred the money.
Bring the guys tonight.
Second floor of Wenjun Hotel.
I'll take care of it.
No need.
I don't want to owe you.
You don't have to say that to me.
I just think
Kai, you're so capable.
It's a waste for you to be a driver.
I like being a driver.
It's a free job.
Our Wu Wei Films
is missing a marketing director.
Annual salary of one million plus commission.
Think about it, Kai.
You just can't stop pretending.
One million.
Brother Kai.
This one million.
How many driving gigs would we have to do for that?
This money isn't just enough for you to live on.
It could support all of us brothers.
Why are you talking so much nonsense?
Brother Kai, don't be mad.
Back then,
I taught you all these life lessons.
Do you all remember?
Back then, you taught us.
How could we bow and scrape to the powerful?
It would only make us unhappy.
The marketing director position
has been vacant for a while.
A lot of work can't move forward.
Do you think we should hire someone?
No rush.
The person should be here soon.
Here.
Come with me.
I'll take you guys to be white-collar workers.
Let's go.
Brother Kai
Call him President Ye
President Ye
I was wrong before
From now on, I'll follow you
The past is the past
Now we're all good brothers
Let's make money together
Come on
Brother Kai
We used to be in the same business
From now on, we're colleagues
President Ye is impressive
I admire you
Who do you think you are, Ma San?
Brother Kai, you can't say that
This is President Ma's company
President Ma's last name is Ma
My last name is Ma too
Doesn't that make you think of anything?
To tell you the truth, brother
I'm President Ma's dri
ver
What are you thinking, Brother Kai?
I'm the driver, of course
Mr. Feng, you’re here.
Ye Wuming’s film company
is thriving right now.
It’s getting better and better.
His movie is really eye-opening.
It’s about to start filming soon.
After this,
he’ll be even harder to deal with.
Don’t worry.
Someone will take action on their own.
They’ll solve this problem openly.
He’s at the peak of his success now.
Who would be willing to act at a time like this?
His enemies.
A deep-seated grudge.
Enemies who cannot coexist.
One general’s success comes at the cost of countless lives.
Ye Wuming’s master
was Zhang Tiansi, the last head of the Eight Immortals Fist.
Back when Zhang Tiansi traveled around,
he defeated many top fighters both at home and abroad.
Some of those experts couldn’t bear the humiliation and committed suicide.
Tell me,
isn’t that an irreconcilable enmity?
It is.
All those disciples and followers are waiting for revenge.
Who would have thought?
Zhang Tiansi died three years ago.
Ye Wuming is Zhang Tiansi’s true successor.
This irreconcilable hatred
naturally falls on him now.
Brilliant.
Once they find out,
they’ll definitely seek revenge on Ye Wuming.
There are many things
you don’t need to do yourself.
You have to learn
to use others to do your dirty work.
Use others to do your dirty work.
They’re here.
These are the three masters Mr. Feng mentioned.
Why are they dressed so strangely?
The Eight Immortals Fist belongs to our Nanzheng Kingdom.
I want to take it back myself.
I must use the blood of the Eight Immortals Fist successor
to wash away the shame Zhang Tiansi brought us.
I have only one purpose for coming here.
To kill Ye Wuming.
Or be killed by Ye Wuming.
Yiran, Yiran.
Yiran.
Stop acting.
It's too fake.
Get up.
I prepared for this for a long time.
Why didn't you give me mouth-to-mouth?
The props are wrong.
We should have used a rope.
Doing mouth-to-mouth with a knife stuck in makes you die faster.
Really.
That's what it says in the script.
How could they lie like that?
Yiran.
Don't play this kind of joke on me again.
Wuming.
Don't be mad.
I just wanted you to give me mouth-to-mouth.
I'll listen to you.
Today's scene,
is an important one.
It's about the male lead
being attacked by three top fighters.
After a fierce battle,
he manages to escape.
Understand?
Okay.
Mr. Li, sorry to keep you waiting.
Um,
Didn't you say three top fighters would be here today?
These three
are the top martial artists in the world.
As a co-producer,
it wasn't easy for me to get them here.
This is great.
Alright.
Let's clear the set and get ready to shoot.
Okay, let's go.
All departments, get ready.
Three, two, one.
Bro, are you okay?
Director! Director!
He's not okay, Director.
Take him to the hospital! Take him to the hospital!
Get another stunt double.
Okay, got it.
This is obviously wasting time.
Is there anyone else who can fight?
Don't we even have a suitable stunt double?
Can we keep filming?
If not, let's wrap it up.
There's no one left.
Say something!
Can you get someone out here?
I'll do it.
Be careful, junior.
Bastard, you hit so hard.
No, isn't this just obviously wasting time?
He's like a paper doll.
Time is money, Boss Ye.
Don't you agree?
I thought the Eight Immortals Fist
was supposed to be amazing.
Turns out it's all just useless fancy moves.
Has the Eight Immortals Sect died out?
Where is he?
I'll do it.