Do you really believe that man?
Geum...
can't you tell?
He's not from here.
What do you mean?
You already know.
We're not from this village, and he's not from here either.
Even if he fails to deliver my letter,
he says he has a place to return to, so we must let him go.
Tinted With You
Negotiations for Peace
If I die,
live your life.
Marry a pretty girl also.
You must have children and live happily.
Why won't you answer me?
I can't live without you, Your Highness.
Geum. All your life, you lived for me.
Of course, I would love to live a long time with you, but—
Your Highness, please don't say such things.
I will protect you forever.
I know
that you will definitely protect me even in death.
I'm saying this just in case.
Well, I-I'm about to leave.
So... please finish what you were doing.
You'll die on your way dressed like that.
What am I supposed to do then?
I have spare clothes in my room.
Wear that when you leave.
Your Highness.
Hurry up and change into it.
I'm going! Stop pushing me!
Geum. Hold on a moment.
You have to put it on properly.
♫  The memories which are tinted in the moonlight♫
♫  A night which makes my heart cold ♫
It's harder than I expected.
♫  In the silent, dark, lonely time♫
♫  In the silent, dark, lonely time ♫
What is this?
♫ When ♫
I don't see any difference from how I tied it.
♫ the feeling of yearning intensifies ♫
♫ The sight of you approaching ♫
Your Highness. Then I will do it.
Hey, but... no, but I... that's not what... It's okay.
♫ crosses time and comes to me. ♫
It's really okay.
Oh, gently, gently, gently.
♫  Like then♫
♫  holding you in my embrace  ♫
♫  can't our eyes meet?  ♫
It's not that but...
♫ Don't leave ♫
I'm really going, okay?
♫  as though you are running away
♫
♫  Please stay here for me.
I really am leaving.
♫ Forgive me ♫
♫ for foolishly not being able to hold you back ♫
I'm really leaving!
I'm leaving, I said!
♫  Return to me ♫
I'm really going.
Can't I not go—
Be safe!
I left, but...
Is this really inside a painting or what?
♫ The one who smiles brightly at me ♫
♫ I see you there ♫
♫ A dream which wandered in the pouring rain ♫
♫ If I wake up, will I miss you? ♫
♫ Even If I hasten my footsteps ♫
♫ and almost reach you, you disappear ♫
[History of Joseon Art]
♫  Can't our eyes meet holding you in my embrace like then? ♫
♫  Don't leave as though you are running away♫
♫  Please stay here for me. ♫
♫  Forgive me for foolishly ♫
♫  not being able to hold you back  ♫
Could this perhaps be...
♫ Someday we will meet ♫
♫  Even if I stay up crying all night♫
♫ I am full of unforgettable memories ♫
♫ You'll be in my arms and whisper like a star like then ♫
♫ I love you. I miss you. ♫
♫  Let's return ♫
You'll have to finish your mission to return.
What that lady said was
true.
♫  Return to me. ♫
What's this? Why are you here?
Heon.
This is my friend who came from the same place I did.
Heon?
But why have you returned?
I met him by chance while on my way.
I heard then that there's a way to go back if I meet Heon.
Right, Seo Jin?
Huh?
Where is your jurisdiction?
You're doing it again. Again.
He's not from some jurisdiction but he's my friend. I told you, just now.
Why do you keep doing that? It's rude.
Then how are you going to deliver that letter?
Since he's here with me, I'll look for a way to return home first.
I'll make sure to deliver this.
Fine. Let's eat first.
Thank you!
It seems like a real meal after such a long while.
I always ate alone, but it's far tastier since I have people to eat with.
Geum. Let's eat together.
I'm all right. Please eat comfortably.
He says he's all right.
When did you get here?
I got here... yesterday.
Yesterday?
So what did that lady say to you? Tell me in detail.
I'm too tired.
Let's sleep for now and talk tomorrow.
Hey, you're acting strange.
We have to hurry back right now.
I'm just so tired, that's why.
Sleep well and let's talk again tomorrow.
Huh?
Hey, no way. Did you...
miss early admissions?
Seo Jin, you should have told me.
It's okay. It's fine.
You can prepare well for the college admission exam
and pass regular admissions.
It's okay.
Are you sleeping?
Fine. I won't talk.
Tinted With You
Why was he exiled?
That he was
beloved by everyone.
Why are you coming out of that room?
Are you a painter?
Do you know that you're subtly cute?
Eun Ho, you're the first.
♫ Fallin' for you  ♫
♫ I know the more time passes ♫
♫ my feelings grow stronger ♫
Tinted With You