[English subtitles are available]
[Out Of The Dream]
[Episode 18]
Our meeting went much faster than I thought it would.
How about
I change your air ticket?
I miss you. I said it just now.
You used speaker.
It's not my fault.
I never thought
I'd see you in love
in my lifetime.
Is that strange?
Okay.
Let's not talk about this
and get down to business.
It's good to go back early.
Let's get this over with
so we can get back
to handle matters in Jiubai.
By the way,
I have an appointment with Boss Zhang of Xianhao Culture later.
Go pack up
and we'll set off
in about half an hour.
Is that ok for you?
Yes. Go.
Okay.
I'll go get a cab.
Guanjiu, good night.
Do you eat well?
If you're uncomfortable walking in heels,
there're band-aids in your bag's compartment.
There really are.
Guanjiu, did you sleep well?
There're eye patches and melatonin in your suitcase.
Guanjiu, do you eat regularly?
There's a energy bar in the pocket of your jacket.
And there really is.
Pumpkin.
Why does this kid care so much about me?
Mengru,
I'm thinking of a way
[Shandengting]
for the last fight scene.
That's it.
[Shandengting]
Sister.
[Succession]
Why are you alone today?
It's not busy in Shandengting lately.
Master is not here either.
Everyone is out to find something to do.
And you gave up doing live stream?
It's because I'm handsome
and became widely known.
Then uncle found out my live stream.
He cut off my Internet for a month.
Now the Internet
has a very short memory.
By the time I got back on air,
your little brother
has become a legend.
Is everyone else okay?
Yeah.
Just getting by.
How many shows are there
in a week now?
Maybe two or three shows a week.
Let's not talk about that.
What are you doing back today, sister?
There's a stage play
I need your help with.
They need an actor with martial arts background.
I thought of you.
Yeah.
Good.
How can I refuse you, sis?
Thank you then.
I'll have them contact you then.
It's nothing.
I don't have anything to do anyway,
do I?
Originating from southern branch of opera in the Song and Yuan Dynasties,
the poetic dramas of Ming and Qing Dynasties
matured in the late Qing Dynasty,
and reached its peak in the early Anti-Japanese War.
Chinese opera has been passed down
for more than 800 years
and is an important part of
traditional Chinese art.
From the Zaju of the Jin and Yuan Dynasties to the poetic dramas of the Ming and Qing Dynasties,
from the prosperity of Music And Opera Of Kunshan and Yiyang to Hui Combo's entering Peking,
Peking Opera eventually became the quintessence of Chinese culture
and entered its golden age.
And all we have to do today
is to take the torch passed down by our predecessors,
so that the poetic dramas on the red woolen carpet
will continue to be sung from generation to generation.
But is it a compliment
or a tragedy
for an art to become the quintessence
of national culture?
[Shandengting]
[Bai Feili]
Why is her phone ringing?
She didn't even mute it?
How can she forget that?
Living in a museum,
in a database,
living as a quintessence of national culture,
as an art form,
it is not really living.
An art form needs to become a part of people's daily life,
be listened to, discussed,
and even be cursed,
to be
truly alive.
Few people can appreciate highbrow art and literature.
But many can understand popular art.
If an art form
shuts its door
and refuses to be understood and appreciated,
but is afraid of criticism and misunderstanding,
only clings to some of its past glory,
and indulges in self-admiration.
I'm afraid it can only
remain where it was.
So,
today I think
spreading is more important than inheriting.
But without innovation, how can we spread and inherit it?
There's no way...
Stop talking!
So what kind of spreading and inheriting are you thinking of?
It was not about opera at all.
If you are born a fish,
you grow wings
because other people like birds.
And you even extract your bones
because other people hate fish bones.
The only thing left will be a monster.
Innovation in opera
doesn't mean denying itself,
nor putting it in another form
just because you like it.
It doesn't mean abandoning the origin to pander.
Do you think pandering is the only way
to make people appreciate operas?
Do it over.
[The inheritance and development of Chinese opera]
Do... Do it over?
I've been making the craft for so long.
Do it over.
Coffee's ready. Let's go.
What happened?
We gotta go.
We have a meeting with the media company later.
Let's go.
Tell me,
what would be the reason
if you met someone you loved
but didn't
tell your boyfriend about this?
You're not gonna go back
and find out now, are you?
A typhoon is passing through today,
there may be a storm,
I can't guarantee
the flight.
You can decided on your own.
Thanks, sis.
I've already been contacted.
It's nothing. We should thank you.
But
Stage play actor is a different profession.
Please let me know
if it keeps you from practicing operas.
Not at all.
But, sis,
I think
maybe it's time for me
to give up operas.
Why?
Is it because
I said you didn't work hard at an early age
and didn't practice well?
Don't take it seriously.
That's not the reason.
You know,
just like this cloudy day.
It is only natural
that it rains.
But
I also need to earn my living.
But you made it through the hard times.
You've finished your apprenticeship now.
It's such a pity if you give it up.
We used to
play a bit role on TV shows,
But now we don't.
After that, we were asked to make commercial performance tours.
After they were kicked out several times by uncle,
no one asks us to perform any more.
Yeah. What's more,
fewer and fewer people like to watch operas now.
I'm afraid,
you know,
what can I do
if no one
likes to watch operas?
I can't do anything for a living
except sing a few plays, sis.
Don't say that.
I really love opera.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have been practicing it
since I was seven.
But does it help?
Can I earn a living just by loving it?
Sis, maybe my life
will be ruined by opera.
That's not going to happen.
Let's not talking about that. Cheers.
Why is it raining again?
Do you have an umbrella?
The rain is quite heavy.
Un...Uncle.
Shandengting trained you for 12 years.
But you associated yourself
with irresponsible people
and do marginal things.
[Associate with the rich and make more friends.]
Kneel.
Sis...what are you doing?
Uncle,
I'm not going to act in the play.
Please don't blame her.
I instigated him to do this.
The responsibility lies with me.
You're not one of us anymore.
No matter how you despise yourself,
I am not qualified to teach you.
I'll take the consequences.
Can you?
I accept all the punishment.
♫The tears in my eyes.♫
♫Who do I act all this for?♫
♫They misunderstand each other.♫
♫But I'm at your mercy.♫
♫Where is...♫
You sung this, I suppose.
Yes.
Yu Fei.
You grew up in Shandengting.
I taught you operas
for ten years.
Is that what
you're supposed to sing?
To speak bluntly,
it is not easy
to cultivate a profitable character.
But you're different.
You could have been a famous actress.
I didn't want you to be restrained
by a small place like Shandengting.
I didn't want you follow me
for your lifetime
only to sing something like
"a romantic crabapple flower".
I want you to go out,
to a bigger place.
I hope you can sing The Romance of the Three Kingdoms
and Wu Zixu.
Do you know that?
But you disappointed me.
What were you singing?
It's my fault.
I did it wrong that
I instigated him to change a job to make money
when I saw his life was hard.
I did it wrong that
I spoke out my true opinions
on Peking Opera and Zaju,
disobeying the teacher.
I did it wrong that after I left Shandengting,
I still couldn't forget uncle's kindness.
Stop saying that.
I did it wrong that I fell in love with uncle,
just because I was friendless and helpless at an early age,
and uncle was indifferent to me,
looked down upon me, thinking I was unable to become a character.
Say that again?
Stop.
Uncle.
Uncle, are you alright?
What are you doing, Bai Feili?
I should never have come back to you.
♫In the dim light, I stroke your profile against the candle light.♫
♫In tipsy state, let my missing send me to sleep.♫
♫Under the silent night sky, loneliness scatters around,♫
♫resting on the sleepless lights.♫
[Yu Fei]
♫Light and shade staggered, the moon shines over you and me.♫
[Power off]
♫Embrace each other's weaknesses, and don't miss anymore.♫
♫ Time passes quickly, don't let go of my hand.♫
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed is power off.
♫Can we hold each other all the time?♫
[Bai Who Will Definitely Come Back]
♫Write the eternal that we all want.♫
Humans have a strange instinct.
When faced with the unknown,
♫ Love will know, when memories fade ♫
the first reaction is to close their eyes.
Therefore,
♫you'll still be in my heart.♫
not being able to answer the question in the first place
is because of evasion.
It's mine.
What are you doing?
I saw it first.
I picked it up first.
No, it's mine.
It's mine. It's mine. It's mine.
Stop.
It's mine.
I'll give you something in exchange.
Look, this is a merry-go-round.
Look.
This is the bunting. There's another guy over here.
There are so many pine trees here.
Look. Look.
There's a ferris wheel.
A ferris wheel.
And that one.
There. Isn't that a little ferris wheel?
Every time I would say "welcome"
at the door to those kids
in white gauze skirts
riding on their dads' shoulders.
Why is this still spinning?
Little snail,
tell me,
am I to blame for this?
But he hit him.
It's his fault.
Besides,
he didn't give me a chance to explain.
Don't be angry.
Please don't be angry.
[Zhan Garden]
What a coincidence.
I still need to explain to you
what happened today.
You know that right now
we are rehearsing South Song 2.
We need a martial arts actor.
Then I went to Lanting for help.
So I invited him to dinner.
After that...I...
I have to go back.
[Zhan Garden]
No. No.
That's not the right place to put it. Here.
Okay.
Yu Fei is such a good kid.
Even though they had a fight,
she made dinner
for our boy.
What's more,
she just said that
she was afraid he would be late and had to eat cold dishes.
She asked us to put them in the microwave
and heat them up before eating.
They're in the microwave now, right?.
It's raining.
Yu Fei didn't bring an umbrella.
Didn't bring an umbrella?
She is sure to catch a cold if she is caught in the rain.
She is.
Business travel has its advantages.
I can save up several episodes of the anime
and watch them in one sitting.
It's been a long time
since I had my own anime party.
Guanjiu,
Last time I saw you were
refreshing the page for this ticket.
Why am I hearing
that kid's voice?
Impossible. Impossible.
It looks like I was spying on her.
It's better to be direct.
Guanjiu.
Would you like to watch
Little Lies with me?
No. No.
Imitating the way Dao talks makes me look greasy.
Guanjiu.
Why. Why would I run?
This kid's really annoying.
Why are you running so fast, Guanjiu?
I'm going home.
Going home? You live upstairs.
You don't want the suitcase?
I'm here to get something.
Well. It's getting late.
You, a little boy, should go home.
I...
I have a date later.
I gotta go, bye.
Since you have something to do,
I'll just get this straight.
Guanjiu,
I want to see this with you.
Well.
See you tomorrow at the theatre gate.
I gotta go.
Don't you see what I mean?
I mean
I have a date today.
I know.
But this ticket is for tomorrow.
I'm going to have wine
with some other guy later.
A date. The kind of...
adults' thing.
So if you're gonna drink later,
you gotta eat something too.
If that guy is paying,
you can order something expensive.
I won't go to the theater. I won't.
I'll wait for you.
See you tomorrow.
I gotta go, bye.
[Little Lies]
Miss,
the flower...
Sorry, here you are.
♫Toss and turn ♫
[Message]
[【Seamless】A red envelope of 6 yuan is on your account]
What kind of advertising it is?
♫Thoughts in a mess♫
♫You're my whole world♫
♫It's okay♫
♫My stranded heart♫
♫Love has been cooled down by the time♫
♫After a few more worlds♫
♫I'm still here♫
♫Hope the men you meet♫
♫All love you like I do♫
♫I once had you♫
♫That's the reason why I miss you♫
♫Every effort is therefore worthwhile♫
[Jiubai]
Cucumber, cucumber, cucumber.
And cucumber.
Eel, eel.
Eel.
Eat, eel.
What are you guys doing here?
We worked overtime.
Boss, why are you here?
Get breakfast out.
Such a hearty breakfast.
I could write ten more.
Wait. Here.
This is for Yu Fei, right?
Recently, the convenience store had a sale.
I saw you were working overtime,
so I specially bought some more.
Since you bought so much,
let me eat it for you.
Wait.
Hao Shi is not even here yet,
and you're eating?
He asked for leave.
I'll eat his breakfast for him.
Thank you, boss.
Thank you, boss. Thank you, boss.
What's wrong with that kid?
I said I won't go there.
Maybe I should call him back.
Everyone works so hard for rehearsal.
Why are you late?
How could he ask for leave
at such a time?
Who approved it?
I'm gonna call him back here right now.
I approved it.
He seems to have an exam today,
and an important date
after the exam.
Well.
Why didn't Yu Fei come today?
She asked me for leave.
Yes. She asked for leave.
I forgot it.
[The mountains are so picturesque that they bend like screens.
Yan Guang had never really enjoyed the beauty of landscape.]
Her voice was husky
and had a stuffy nose, and you know it.
Tell her for me.
[I've just met you, but it's like welcoming an old friend home.
The moon is new on the horizon.]
Tell her what?
[Jiubai]
Tell her
don't get sick during rehearsal.
[I've just met you, but it's like welcoming an old friend home.
The moon is new on the horizon.]
Odd.
To go or not to go?
Why is it still 38.5°C?
Coming. Coming.
Who is it?
You've got a fever
and you're running around with so few clothes on.
I don't have an A.I. robot
in my house.
If I don't run around,
who opens the door for you?
Legs.
Now that rehearsal is so intense,
it's not appropriate for you to have a fever.
Don't worry, boss.
As long as I can last,
I will attend rehearsals on time.
I will live up to the part-time salary you paid.
How long do you expect to be sick with pay
if you keep drinking cold water?
Drink it up.
Which page?
Mr. Bai, I can still turn the pages.
You're working so hard with a fever.
How badly do you want to take the classes of the professor?
He can't see how hard you're working.
I was laughed at every day,
and I had to endure the humiliation
and worked hard to get into college.
Of course I have to
attend lectures every day.
Give it to me.
I have an exam on Monday.
Where are you going?
Do you want to follow me
when I go to the bathroom?
Make way.
Why did he come here all of a sudden?
♫The smiling stars hop into the night,♫
I'm so unkempt.
♫meeting sweetly in the dream.♫
I didn't wash my hair or my face.
Healthy quickly-made dishes.
♫The moonlight carries my miss.♫
♫The lingering breeze and petals flush on the cheeks. ♫
♫In peaceful sleep,♫
♫I've fallen for you before I knew it.♫
Two abalones.
♫Do you have the same feeling?♫
♫Our distance is shrinking. ♫
♫Our hearts are getting closer each day.♫
The one in the bathroom,
♫As long as you're around.♫
is there something wrong with your gas stove?
♫Until ♫
You need to press it
and then rotate it to open it.
♫time is frozen at this second.♫
♫Breathing and heartbeat are forgotten.♫
♫The frequency matches one's signal. ♫
♫The atmosphere is just right.♫
Too greasy.
♫Until♫
♫when I can safely rest in your eyes.♫
Five, four, three, two, one.
♫Regardless of the storms and noises outside.♫
♫Regardless of what may happen tomorrow.♫
♫My world turns around in your arms.♫
♫I've fallen for you before I knew it.♫
♫Do you have the same feeling?♫
♫Our distance is shrinking.♫
♫Our hearts are getting closer each day. ♫
The one out there,
♫As long as you're around.♫
can you not
keep the tap running like that?
♫Until♫
The one in the bathroom,
I'll pay for your utility bills this month.
♫time is frozen at this second.♫
I'm not talking about utility bills.
I mean,
♫Breathing and heartbeat are forgotten.♫
you're wasting water resource.
♫The frequency matches one's signal.♫
Do you know that
a lot of kids in Africa
♫The atmosphere is just right. ♫
don't even have access to water.
♫Until♫
♫when I can rest in your eyes forever.♫
♫My world turns around in your arms.♫
♫I believe you are the one for me.♫
♫In my dreams, the twittering♫
♫makes you up word by word.♫
♫Finally I have found you.♫
I look terrible. Put on some blush.
That's too much.
Isn't that too obvious?
Less.
♫Until♫
I finally figured out why they sell eggs
by the box in supermarkets.
♫time is frozen at this second.♫
The failure rate is so high.
♫Breathing and heartbeat are forgotten.♫
♫The frequency matches one's signal.♫
♫The atmosphere is just right.♫
Much better.
♫Until♫
The one in the bathroom,
be quick.
Otherwise, it won't taste good when it gets cold.
♫when I can safely rest in your eyes.♫
♫Regardless of the storms and noises outside.♫
♫Regardless of what may happen tomorrow.♫
♫My world turns around in your arms.♫
What a powerful gene.
He's got Mr. Shan's DNA.
You won't want to eat the eggs.
But you can have some nutritious porridge.
Is it bad?
Not bad.
You look like I wasted food.
I didn't expect that
this combination
would produce
this magical effect.
It's good.
Look, there's abalone,
dried scallop,
and matsutake.
Such nutritious nutrition porridge, drink more,
or it will be wasted.
Enough, stop.
I know it tastes bad.
Actually,
I'm so touched
that you're here.
Actually, I was touched that you washed your hair
while you're sick.
Well. Well. You make me dizzy with anger.
Cover yourself so your cold won't get worse.
I was...
You what?