=Stealing Heart=
=Episode 20=
(Lifelong Vow)
(Wait.)
(With his skills,
he shouldn't have missed.)
(He did it on purpose to show Mr. Gao.)
I brought you a cat.
Cats are clingy.
It can keep you company.
Sleep well and take your medicine.
Your wound will heal faster.
Can I pet?
Yes.
Just a pet.
You said it yourself.
Lin Chuning.
What did you just call me?
Lu Chuning.
Xiaorou used to call you that.
What's wrong?
Does it hurt again?
♪Beyond the mountain,
the view fills my eyes♪
What are you doing?
Didn't we always do this before?
You never did this before.
Well.
If we didn't before,
it's not too late now.
♪The wind passes between us♪
♪The sky wakes at first light♪
♪After the light goes out,
the warmth still lingers within♪
♪Holding tightly on to our bond,
I no longer feel the cold♪
Stop testing my patience.
You were being all dominant just now.
What's wrong?
♪Unwilling to let each other go♪
Are you a cat?
Don't you like it?
No.
Yeah.
You're not Lu Siyan.
♪I recall the days behind♪
Sister.
♪When your presence
lit the path I longed to find♪
♪Let it go for now♪
♪Wait for the dark to make peace
with the light somehow♪
♪And as I reflect with care♪
♪Those meant to meet again♪
Let's eat.
Did you prepare all this?
Yes.
I prepared them for you.
That's impressive.
I know
you locked me up here
to keep me safe.
But you said
that we'd fight side by side.
No matter what comes at us,
come hell or high water,
I want to be with you.
I know.
By the way,
what's inside
Mr. Gao's
boxes?
Girls.
Girls?
Siyan,
look around.
Men and women find pleasure here.
I gave them joy.
Once the new Wenrou Lounge
is finished,
it'll be even more thrilling
than the previous one.
Gao Yunfeng.
Lu Chuning,
why are you still alive?
Are you surprised?
You villain are not dead yet,
why would I be?
It can't be.
I trusted you so much.
I can't believe
you still see yourself as a Lu.
Father,
I'm only doing what needs to be done.
Nothing more.
Gao Yunfeng,
you're sanctimonious
and ruthless.
You pretended to be helping baby girls
for the Foundling Home.
In fact, you sold them to Wenrou Lounge
when they grew up.
Even now,
you won't stop
your evil act.
You're still trying to traffic girls.
Have you no shame?
That's slander!
Yes, I made mistakes.
But they're the same mistakes
all the men make.
I just
went to Wenrou Lounge
for pleasure.
But that doesn't make me the boss
of this place.
You're still denying it?
Very well.
I'll expose your true colors
through and through.
Siyan.
Siyan, don't...
You!
(Where are they?)
(Why did they all turn into porcelain?)
Found anything, eh?
Lin Chuning,
as everyone knows,
I like
collecting things.
Chuning,
just tell me directly if you like these.
I can give you one.
Gao Yunfeng,
you're so sinful.
Don't think you can get away with this.
You keep saying I'm sinful.
Where's your proof?
Fine.
You ask for proof?
I'm the proof.
I, Lu Chuning,
accuse Gao Yunfeng of attempting rape
and of trying to abduct me
to Wenrou Lounge.
But who would
believe you?
All your accusations
are nothing but an excuse
to take over the Lu Group.
First you drove me out,
and now you're pinning
these charges on me.
You want me dead.
Chuning, I'm telling you.
Even if...
Even if I were the owner
of Wenrou Lounge,
who could prove it?
I can prove it.
I can prove he's the owner.
I can.
- We can prove it.
- I can prove it, too.
Father,
I can prove
you're the owner.
You're not getting away this time.
You...
You ingrates!
Get away?
Why should I get away?
There are no outsiders here.
Fine, I admit it.
I own Wenrou Lounge.
So what can you do about it?
Men and women seeking pleasure here
is a natural thing to do.
What I built
isn't Wenrou Lounge.
It's paradise.
They're to blame instead.
They don't know how to enjoy it.
They're being so dramatic.
I created a paradise for them,
but they want to send me to hell.
Who do you think
is the real sinner here?
Fellow reporters,
did you all hear that?
You...
How did you all get in here?
Get out.
It's you.
You're welcome.
You ungrateful son!
Gao Yunfeng,
I know you've got people
inside the police force.
If you give me names,
I'll consider
asking for mitigation.
Mr. Gao.
Chief Shen.
Repent yourself at the court.
Hold Lin Chuning hostage.
Lu Siyan won't dare to take risks.
Maybe
you still have a chance.
Go.
Go to hell!
Don't move.
Drop the gun.
Lin Chuning,
you ruined me.
I'm going to kill you.
And you, unfilial son!
After I kill her,
I'll kill you.
Die!
Drop it.
Reporters.
Mr. Gao committed a lot of crimes,
and he's beyond redemption.
As the Chief of Police,
I have a duty to protect every citizen.
Given the severity of his crimes,
he should be held accountable.
Hence, I shot him.
Thank you, everyone.
So, the one backing Wenrou Lounge
is Shen Mochen,
that's why he was desperate
to silence him.
Gao Yunfeng deserved to die.
But still,
he's your father.
He gave me life, but never raised me.
To me,
he was an evil man.
Your wound.
Does it still hurt?
It does.
From now on,
you'll always be in my heart.
Tell me now.
When did your memory come back?
Honestly, I still don't remember a lot.
But one thing I know for sure is
I love you.
Mercifully, you're still alive.
From now on, just stay by my side.
Don't go anywhere.
I won't ask you to be rich
or successful.
I just want you to be safe
and healthy.
Father,
Mother,
I have to report back
to the flight academy tomorrow.
The accident last time
was because our aircraft
and technology weren't advanced enough.
If we want to defeat the enemy,
we need to have the spirit
of not fearing sacrifice or death.
Father, Mother,
I hope you both can support me.
No, Siyan.
It's dangerous.
Master,
say something.
Back then,
I used to think going to flight school
was a waste of time.
But now I understand
they're doing
something great.
They protect the country.
It's an honor.
I support you.
Thank you, Father.
Be honest with me.
Are you afraid I'll get into
another accident again?
Don't ever say that again.
Instead of
breaking your wings,
I'd rather
give you a hand
and see you soar in the sky.
I envy you, really,
you have a dream.
I used to
have no idea
what I really wanted.
But now I do.
I hope
I can do everything in my power
to help women stand on their own feet.
I hope, one day, there'll
no longer be places like Foundling Home.
It will happen.
Because
you're the unstoppable
Lin Chuning.
Let's go.
I prepared dinner all by myself.
I doubt they're edible.
Might not suit your palate.
Father.
Mother.
I don't have much appetite.
Please enjoy dinner.
I don't feel like eating either.
Please enjoy the food.
Though Siyan survived the plane crash,
I somehow feel that
the two of them
are not getting along well.
What's on your mind?
I'm thinking about
when I should tell Father everything.
If this keeps dragging on,
when will it ever end?
Aren't you afraid
he'll kick you out of the house
once you tell him?
Then what?
If I end up homeless,
please take me in.
Wouldn't that be expensive?
I have to think about it.
No at all. I'm easy to feed.
Really?
Yeah.
Mother.
I know it's my fault
that you can't date openly.
But please
give me a little more time.
I'll confess to Master.
I understand, Mother.
Siyan,
will you
still accept me as your mother?
You'll always be my mother.
Chuning.
Mrs. Lu.
I'm sorry.
(Punish Evil, Uphold Justice)
Congratulations, Chief Shen.
You've become
a hero of justice to the people.
Out with it.
What did you come here for?
I want you to kill Lu Siyan.
Mr. Gao is dead,
and Lu Siyan abandoned you.
Do you think
you're useful
to me now?
You used me and hung me out to dry?
I'm discarding
a worthless pawn.
You bribed the mechanic
in the flight academy
to tamper with the aircraft
Lu Siyan was in, didn't you?
Also, you made me take the blame
for that sachet.
Go on.
Keep talking.
The boxes Mr. Gao had
didn't contain porcelain.
You swapped the girls out beforehand
to scheme against Lin Chuning
and Lu Siyan.
Poor Mr. Gao,
he died without even knowing
he was your scapegoat.
(Account Book)
What is this?
I'm pledging my loyalty to you.
This is Mr. Gao's account book.
If you wish to build
your own Wenrou Lounge,
you'll need this.
I'm just a poor, helpless woman
who's trying to look for someone
to cling to.
Well.
Please take pity on me, Chief Shen.
This dress...
Do you like it?
I had it made for you.
I like anything you pick.
I'll take you somewhere.
Where?
You'll see.
All right.
Here. Feet up.
Careful.
Take it slow.
All right.
Here we are.
Okay.
Hold this.
Chuning,
there's something I want to say.
I fell for you at first sight.
But I didn't know
what love was.
So after going through ups and downs,
and when I realized
I had truly loved you,
I found out you were my sister.
I don't think anything could be worse
than that.
That's when I knew
my feelings for you
run so deep.
Otherwise, even after losing
all my memories,
I wouldn't have remembered
that I love you.
After everything we went through,
I'm going to be brave once again.
Chuning.
Will you
marry me?
No, I won't.
♪Barging into the sea
that bears your name♪
♪Swimming to the end with loneliness♪
♪Going against the current
and over the reef traps♪
♪Clearing the fog
just to get close to you♪
♪Pushing away
the gravel hidden beneath the seaweed♪
♪Wandering near your heart♪
♪I imagined
our encounter countless times♪
♪So close, yet out of reach♪
♪Keeping
all this lonely courage to myself♪
♪I was never part of your world♪
♪If your silhouette
was etched upon the sea♪
♪The sky as your wedding dress♪
♪Turn me into a cloud♪
♪Keep a sliver of the past♪
♪If love is like an illusory bubble♪
♪Together forever in my dreams♪
♪I'd rest forever in your arms♪
♪Barging into the sea
that bears your name♪
♪Swimming to the end with loneliness♪
♪Going against the current
and over the reef traps♪
♪Clearing the fog
just to get close to you♪
♪Returning to the land
left bare by the receding sea♪
♪Withering like a fallen leaf♪
♪The message in a bottle
buried on the shore♪
♪No one asked♪
♪All this lonely courage for myself♪
♪I'm no longer part of your world♪
♪If your silhouette
was etched upon the sea♪
♪The sky as your wedding dress♪
♪Turn me into a cloud♪
♪Keep a sliver of the past♪
♪If love is like an illusory bubble♪
♪Together forever in my dreams♪
♪I'd rest forever in your arms♪
♪If the sea didn't wait
for the evening breeze♪
♪And swim with me to you♪
♪I'd become♪
♪A whale
who forever keeps the sea company♪
♪If love is like a night storm♪
♪Unable to stop for a moment♪
♪Let the wind scatter my traces♪