=Stealing Heart=
(Adapted from Dianzhong Tech's
Flash-Married and Pampered)
=Episode 8=
(You Owe Me An Explanation)
Chuning.
You lied to me.
You approached Lu Siyan back then
for the Lu family's wealth.
But now you've fallen for him.
He's your biological brother.
Getting intimate with your own brother?
Don't you find that disgusting?
I was just putting on an act with him.
Lu Siyan
is still a useful pawn.
Chuning.
For you,
I'd go up against the whole world.
Chuning.
Don't ever betray me.
I bought this for you.
Thanks.
I've handed
all the dividends to Mr. Gao.
He's quite pleased.
He probably won't
mistreat Xiaorou for a while.
Your father already said
he'll host a banquet
at the end of the month
to announce my identity.
I plan to go to Wenrou Lounge
that day
to rescue Xiaorou.
But
before that,
I need to drive Mr. Gao
out of the Lu Residence first.
Okay.
Let's go.
Father-in-law,
I brought this book back
for you from abroad.
Have a read.
Sure.
Father. Mother.
Siyan. Chuning.
Your brother-in-law and I
were discussing the engagement.
We'll all be family soon,
visit each other more often.
Father-in-law,
I'll get straight to the point.
I want to marry Chuning.
You already have Jing.
Is that not enough?
What now?
You want
both daughters
of the Lu family to serve one man?
Father-in-law,
what you promised me was
the eldest daughter of the Lu family.
The current eldest daughter
is Lu Chuning.
Father-in-law,
you're a well-known businessman,
and I now hold
the position of Chief of Police.
If we fall out,
it will get ugly.
Don't try to pull rank on me here.
Don't forget how you
even became the Chief.
Welcome, Chief Shen!
- Welcome, Chief Shen!
If I could get you that title,
I can take it away.
Father-in-law,
your son leans
on his identity as the Lu heir,
yet he's worthless.
But me?
I'm different.
I take my duties seriously.
With my current standing,
going against me
might not
be the wisest choice.
You...
Let's go.
You can't marry her.
You're already engaged to Jing.
Everyone in town knows about it.
For a woman,
reputation is everything.
Both daughters
of the Lu family are cherished gems.
You want them
to become fodder for street gossip?
Uncle, it's rare for you
to sound reasonable.
It's actually quite unsettling.
Chuning!
Show some respect to your uncle!
What kind of uncle am I?
I share no blood with the Lu family.
To be honest,
Chuning and I
have already been
physically intimate.
That's nonsense!
I should've shot you back then.
Wait.
Say that again. What did you just say?
What did you say?
Brother...
If you're angry, then take it out on me.
Back then,
when Chuning confessed
her feelings to me,
I couldn't help myself.
But at the time,
I honestly didn't know
she was your daughter.
So it just happened before I knew it.
But don't worry.
For the rest of Chuning's life,
I'll take care of her.
I'll support her.
Chuning...
What's going on here?
Father...
Do you believe him?
Master.
Back home, we have a method
to test whether a woman's still pure.
But I'm afraid
it may wrong Ms. Lin.
Asking an innocent girl
to prove her innocence?
You have no right to demand that.
After what she's done,
what is there to be ashamed of?
Siyan,
this concerns your sister's reputation.
If you care about her,
you shouldn't stop us.
Alright.
Father,
I'll go with them.
Ms. Lin,
I'll need a drop of your blood.
Siyan,
come with me.
This way, Ms. Lin.
Brother.
Let me explain.
Please don't blame me.
You know me.
This is just how I am.
I really didn't know
she was your daughter.
So I just...
Shut up!
This is Ms. Lin's blood.
We drop it on a budding yellow flower.
If the flower stays fresh,
she's still pure.
If it wilts,
then she's lost her chastity.
Father...
Don't call me that!
I have no daughter as shameless as you.
Father-in-law,
I'm willing to marry Chuning.
Are you serious?
You don't mind her past?
I, Shen Mochen, swear here and now,
that I will marry her with full honor,
with full bridal attire,
with drums and gongs,
and bring Chuning home.
Still not saying anything?
If you stay silent now,
your future might be decided.
Uncle...
You said
you've been intimate with me.
Then tell me,
is the birthmark on my waist
on the left
or the right?
Birthmark?
It's
on the left.
Wrong.
It's on the right.
Madam Wang saw it just now
when she drew blood.
Didn't you?
Tell them.
That's right.
It's on the right.
Wrong again.
I don't have a birthmark
on my waist at all.
Why did you lie?
Just now...
I...
I didn't notice while drawing the blood.
Chuning.
Even if your uncle
didn't take your chastity,
you're still not pure.
That is clear.
A woman must respect herself.
From now on,
live a good life with Mochen.
Don't ever degrade yourself again.
Well said, Mother.
A girl must respect and love herself.
But that blood just now was mine.
I may be a flirt,
but I'm still untouched.
Father,
you must stand up for me.
I feared someone
would tamper with things,
so I switched the syringe.
But look at the flower.
It still wilted.
This proves
someone is deliberately
trying to frame me for losing my purity
to ruin my reputation!
That's unforgivable, Father.
Madam Wang,
what really happened?
Speak.
Master...
It was me.
I lost my judgment.
Yes.
I took
a bribe from Mr. Gao.
You...
That's nonsense!
When did I ever bribe you?
Brother, hear me out.
Shut up!
Don't call me brother.
From this day forward,
you are no longer part of the Lu family.
Get out!
And you too!
Both of you, leave the Lu residence!
Out!
Don't you think
the air in the Lu Residence
feels clearer
ever since Mr. Gao was thrown out?
To me,
the air here
has been different for a while.
(From the moment
you stepped into this house,)
(my life has felt alive again.)
Thank you.
No need.
That's what I'm here for
anyway.
You heard that?
Heard what?
Then, explain it.
Forget it.
There's nothing to explain.
Either way,
I'm still going to marry Shen Mochen.
What if I say I object?
And what position
are you in to disapprove?
I just don't want to.
You...
Shh.
Do you really mean to be
so cold and heartless?
Do you really enjoy
being two-faced
in front of everyone?
That's how
you fooled Shen Mochen, right?
Fine, I admit it.
I did fall for you.
But so what?
I need to save Xiaorou.
I need to run the Foundling Home.
I still have to stay alert
around your parents.
Love is a luxury to me.
I don't have the time
or the heart for it.
♪My response is ambiguous♪
♪Against my heart♪
I must head for the Wenrou Lounge.
Mr. Siyan,
so long.
♪With yours♪
Leaving after using me?
♪You're the dark snow slowly arriving♪
♪Too high above the clouds♪
♪Unashamedly, I climb to reach♪
♪Offering up my life with both hands♪
♪Praying for the ones I love and hate♪
♪Can hold on for a few more years♪
♪But who can truly leave unscathed?♪
♪You are the peerless one
with a quiet gaze♪
(Lin Chuning,)
(I won't let you marry another man.)
Lin Chuning,
what's the meaning of this money?
You're apologizing?
You had the nerve
to kick me out of the family.
Don't come trying
to make peace with cash now!
Do you think
I'd even talk to you
if it weren't to save Xiaorou?
You should be thanking me on your knees
for the fact that I didn't end you.
Back to business.
Kicking you out of the Lu family
was just a cover
for secretly moving assets.
During this time,
you'd better take good care of Xiaorou.
Otherwise,
I won't let you off easy.
As long as you cooperate,
this cage you're in
will be replaced
with a golden one soon enough.
Which looks better?
Both.
Wrap up everything
my fiancée picked out.
Ms. Lin.
The young master gave orders.
If you or Chief Shen come to shop for
wedding gifts or dowries, we won't sell.
It's alright.
Let's look elsewhere.
This one's nice.
Take it out so I can have a look.
No need.
Wrap that up for me.
The young master said
as long as it's you,
we're not selling.
It's fine.
Let's look elsewhere.
Not for sale?
I'll pay myself.
The young master instructed.
If you're shopping with Chief Shen,
we're not selling, period.
Chuning.
It's okay.
The Lu Department Stores
aren't the only ones in town.
We'll go somewhere else.
There are plenty of department stores.
But there's only one Lin Chuning.
He's not good enough for you.
Everything in Lu Department Stores
belongs to her.
From now on, whatever she wants,
send it straight to her room.
Brother,
I'm about to marry your sister.
She really dotes on you.
So for today,
I'll let it slide.
What happens between me and my sister
is none of your business.
You haven't married her yet.
Stay out of our relationship.
Well, well, Mr. Siyan.
Where have you been lately?
You haven't come looking for me.
I missed you so much.
Can't you see I'm talking?
Take it back.
I don't need this.
Chuning.
Mochen,
let's go.
Excuse us.
Thank you.
Mr. Siyan...
Get lost.
Leave!
Chuning.
What happened that day
was not on purpose.
But I never expected
you'd still agree to get engaged to me.
Mochen,
you and Mr. Gao
were in on it together,
weren't you?
Jing is my father's precious daughter.
If you broke off the engagement,
if it were me,
my father would never agree.
But if I lost my purity,
and it was with Mr. Gao,
then to save face,
my father would have to give me up.
So in the end,
you three abandoned me
all over again.
Chuning,
I would never abandon you.
I'm the only one who won't leave you.
The Lu family,
and even Lu Siyan,
can't be trusted.
But I am different.
No matter what you have done,
or what you want to do,
I will always
stand by you.
It's getting dark.
Prepare for the engagement banquet.
Alright.
I'm really looking forward to that day.
You like eavesdropping that much?
Seems to me
you don't trust him all that much.
I don't trust him.
I don't trust you either.
I don't think you really doubt me.
At first,
you planned to use the banquet
as cover to rescue Xiaorou.
But after the drama
with Shen Mochen and your uncle,
the banquet got canceled.
So you just went along with the change
and asked Shen Mochen
for an engagement party.
Am I right?
Correct.
But that doesn't mean
I will marry you.
Before this,
you wanted to use my lowly status
to rebel against your parents.
You always knew
there was never any future
for the two of us.
Whether there's a future or not
has nothing to do with status.
It all comes down to feelings.
I didn't love you before.
But now I do.
So it doesn't matter
who you are.
Even if Mr. Gao didn't succeed,
I still...
You are in no mood
to talk about love right now.
I just want to secure my place first.
Once you're done with everything,
I'll be waiting.
For the life ahead of you,
I'll be there for you.
♪Even for a moment?♪
I want you to know this.
Just like a torchlight,
I hope
to be the light in your heart.
♪You're the moon above the trees♪
♪The finest of all in charm and ease♪
♪Born with eyes
that hold the world's desire♪
♪By my pillow lies your name♪
♪In dreams,
my heart still burns the same♪
♪You took my hand
to ride beneath the stars♪
(As long as Lin Chuning lives,)
(Siyan will remain in danger.)
(Lin Chuning,)
(you should have
stayed away from your brother.)
(You never should have come.)
(I'm here)
(Chuning,)
(Fear not)
(don't be scared.)
(I'll always be with you.)
(Lu Siyan,)
(thank you.)
(Fear not)
(Lu Residence)
Jing threw a fit when she heard
you're getting engaged
to Chuning.
They are both my daughters.
As their mother,
this puts me in a tough spot.
All of this is my fault.
I caused both of you trouble.
Nothing wrong with loving someone.
Chuning grew up away from home.
She's suffered so much.
From now on,
I'm counting on you
to take good care of her for us.
Don't worry.
I feel exactly the same way as you do.
Chuning will be
treated well.
Alright.
She is waiting at the workshop.
Go now.
Mother,
I'll be going now.
Tell Ms. Lin to go to the workshop.
Say the young master needs to see her.
Yes.
♪Barging into the sea
that bears your name♪
♪Swimming to the end with loneliness♪
♪Going against the current
and over the reef traps♪
♪Clearing the fog
just to get close to you♪
♪Pushing away the gravel
hidden beneath the seaweed♪
♪Wandering near your heart♪
♪I imagined
our encounter countless times♪
♪So close, yet out of reach♪
♪Keeping
all this lonely courage to myself♪
♪I was never part of your world♪
♪If your silhouette
was etched upon the sea♪
♪The sky as your wedding dress♪
♪Turn me into a cloud♪
♪Keep a sliver of the past♪
♪If love is like an illusory bubble♪
♪Together forever in my dreams♪
♪I'd rest forever in your arms♪
♪Barging into the sea
that bears your name♪
♪Swimming to the end with loneliness♪
♪Going against the current
and over the reef traps♪
♪Clearing the fog
just to get close to you♪
♪Returning to the land
Left bare by the receding sea♪
♪Withering like a fallen leaf♪
♪The message in a bottle
buried on the shore♪
♪No one asked♪
♪All this lonely courage for myself♪
♪I'm no longer part of your world♪
♪If your silhouette
was etched upon the sea♪
♪The sky as your wedding dress♪
♪Turn me into a cloud♪
♪Keep a sliver of the past♪
♪If love is like an illusory bubble♪
♪Together forever in my dreams♪
♪I'd rest forever in your arms♪
♪If the sea didn't wait
for the evening breeze♪
♪And swim with me to you♪
♪I'd become♪
♪A whale
who forever keeps the sea company♪
♪If love is like a night storm♪
♪Unable to stop for a moment♪
♪Let the wind scatter my traces♪