=Stealing Hearts=
=Episode 10=
(Ruined and Broken)
Alright.
We're safe now.
Let's go.
Mr. Siyan!
The fire's raging inside.
Going in is suicide.
Even if it costs my life,
I want to die with her.
Mr. Siyan!
(If I can't have him,)
(no one else can.)
You two can die as lovers, then.
Xiaorou.
Chuning.
Chuning!
It's okay.
I'm here to get you home.
Come on.
Let's go.
I'll put you down first.
This door can't be opened.
Are we going to die here?
Don't worry.
We'll definitely be fine.
Gao Yunfeng wouldn't leave himself
without a way out.
Follow the airflow
and we'll get to the exit.
Just hang in there. We'll make it out.
This should be it.
♪Barging into the sea
that bears your name♪
♪Swimming to the end with loneliness♪
♪Going against the current
and over the reef traps♪
♪Clearing the fog
just to get close to you♪
I can walk.
Are you afraid
of being seen by Shen Mochen?
♪I imagined
our encounter countless times♪
♪So close, yet out of reach♪
Chuning!
Let me down.
Do you care a lot about Shen Mochen?
I wouldn't want them to gossip about us.
♪Was never part of your world♪
♪If your silhouette
was etched upon the sea♪
- Quick, go inside and save them.
- Yes, sir!
Chuning.
Are you okay?
I'll get you home.
I'm taking her home.
♪Together forever in my dreams♪
♪I'd rest forever in your arms♪
Die!
I was wrong!
You wench.
You think
you get to ride Lin Chuning's coattails
just because she became
the Lu family's heiress?
No, I don't.
Listen up.
All of this is just wishful thinking.
It's wishful thinking!
I...
Well,
what if I told Chuning
that to please me,
you lured those girls
from the Foundling Home
into the Wenrou Lounge?
Would she still think of you
as her best friend?
I never wanted to leave you.
I only stole the ledger for your sake.
The ledger wasn't burned?
Lin Chuning has it?
Exactly.
Chuning burned your Wenrou Lounge down.
Don't you want revenge?
If I stay close to her,
I can avenge you.
I'd even kill her for you.
You better not be lying to me.
Otherwise,
I'll plaster these photos of yours
all over the streets.
Gao Yunfeng!
You'll die a horrible death!
Perfect.
With this ledger,
I can send Mr. Gao straight to prison.
He's got a long life ahead,
but it sure won't be a happy one.
Ms. Lin,
someone asked me to pass this to you.
(Bring the ledger to Garden Café
to exchange for Xiaorou.)
What's the matter?
Nothing.
(Bring the ledger to Garden Café
to exchange for Xiaorou.)
Kill Lin Chuning for me
and I'll give you what she offered you.
I want her dead even more than you do.
Chuning.
Xiaorou.
Give me the ledger.
You can't run
from the long arm of the law.
Even if you escape this time,
next time will be worse.
Cut the crap and hand over the ledger.
Or I'll kill her!
Chuning, don't give it to him!
Shut up!
(Ledger)
Get up.
Chuning...
Let her go!
Chuning!
Lin Chuning!
You ruined my Wenrou Lounge.
You ruined everything!
Today,
I'll send you to hell.
Mr. Siyan!
You came.
Sister.
It's okay now.
"Sister"?
Actually,
you're the real heiress
of the Lu family.
That makes you
Siyan's biological sister.
After all that suffering
and everything I've been through,
now you're telling me
I'm the Lu family heiress?
That I'm Mr. Siyan's biological sister?
Well, what was all that pain for?
Xiaorou.
It's all in the past now.
From here on out,
you'll have a good life.
Easy for you to say.
You took my place.
You're in love with my brother.
How could you ever understand me?
Sister.
Don't say that.
Everything Chuning did
was for your sake.
Whether it was her initial plan
to avenge you
or her attempt to save you,
she did all this for you.
So you can't criticize her.
For my sake?
My life is all ruined and broken.
What's the use of her saving me?
I'm barely living.
Siyan.
Could you excuse yourself?
I need to have a word with Chuning.
Why can't I hear it too?
Siyan.
You should head back first.
Sure.
Take your time, then.
Xiaorou.
Don't worry.
As long as I'm here,
you won't be bullied after this.
Chuning.
Can you promise me one thing?
I'll try my best to help you
within my capability.
Can you
leave Lu Siyan forever?
And you call yourself my best friend?
I didn't even blame you
for taking over my identity.
Yet you can't even do me
this small favor.
Lin Chuning.
You're aware what I've been through.
And now Siyan's my brother.
My life's already miserable enough.
Chuning.
Could you make my life easier?
Please, Chuning.
Xiaorou.
Let's go home first.
We'll talk about this later.
(Soon,)
(all of this will be mine.)
(Lin Chuning.
It's time to pay what you owe me)
(with your life.)
Xiaorou.
Careful.
Chuning.
I accidentally broke your photo frame.
I have myself to blame.
I hurt my hand saving you.
Now I can't even hold a frame steady.
It doesn't matter.
By the way,
I told Mr. and Mrs. Lu
that your house caught fire,
so you're staying here for now.
Someone tried to kill me before.
I suspect
it was due to my identity
as the Lu family heiress.
Once I'm sure the danger's passed,
I'll return your identity to you.
Chuning.
Aren't you curious what I went through?
Xiaorou.
That's a painful memory for you.
If you're reluctant
to tell me about it, then...
I want to do so.
I want you to know
just how miserable I was.
Back then,
I wanted to buy you a birthday gift,
but I got tricked by Mr. Gao
into the Wenrou Lounge.
That's where I met Lu Siyan.
I thought we just had one night together.
I then got pregnant.
So I ran for my life.
I went to Foundling Home to find you.
But I didn't expect Mr. Gao
to follow me there.
Chuning!
Chuning, where are you?
Xiaorou.
I knew you'd come here.
- Trying to run again?
- Let me go!
Let me go!
You think
you can marry into the Lu family
just because
you're carrying Lu Siyan's child?
He was just toying with you.
That's all.
This is for abortion.
Lu Siyan made it for you himself.
Don't take that one-night stand
too seriously.
What a shame.
Xiaorou.
I'm actually trying to help you.
Lu Siyan told me to do all this.
Just blame him for it.
Xiaorou.
Xiaorou!
What's happened, Xiaorou?
You're scaring me!
Lu Siyan didn't want our child.
I was such a fool.
Avenge me.
Xiaorou.
Xiaorou!
- Xiaorou!
- Chuning.
Chuning.
Xiaorou.
What's the matter with her?
I have no idea.
It was all my fault.
I failed to protect her.
No, wait a second.
It was Lu Siyan.
Lu Siyan did this to her.
He did all this to Xiaorou!
It was all his fault.
Poor girl.
Chuning.
I watched both you and Xiaorou grow up.
So I'm basically your guardian.
Let me handle
Xiaorou's funeral arrangements.
Take care of the other girls.
Don't let them find out.
They're still so young.
They couldn't take such a heavy blow.
Don't tell them anything.
Xiaorou...
Lu Siyan.
I will kill you.
I'll avenge Xiaorou.
You thought
you were dead?
Too bad.
You're still alive.
You devil.
Only disobedient ones
find this place hellish.
From now on, you'll only stay here.
Well,
you really should thank our child.
He died in your place.
Our child? What do you mean?
Since it's come to this point,
there's no need to keep lying to you.
That night,
the one you were with
wasn't Lu Siyan at all.
Lu Siyan never even touched you.
Well...
I was with you on that night.
And I was way better
than Lu Siyan.
Since our child died
to protect your pathetic life,
you'll stay with me from now on.
Considering how lucky you've been,
you'd bring me fortune.
I'm going to find Chuning.
Where is she?
Idiot.
Think about why you're even here.
It was your precious best friend
who handed you over to me.
It's been all my fault.
From now on, I'll listen to you.
Whatever you want you to do,
I will do it.
That's more like it.
Actually, I survived it.
Mr. Gao tricked you into burying me,
but he secretly brought me
back to Wenrou Lounge.
I had to suck up to him
and grovel like a slave.
I ended up becoming his toy.
Chuning.
You and Lu Siyan ruined my life
completely.
So, how could you still be together?
(Xiaorou's been through so much.)
(She can't take any more shocks.)
(For now,)
(I'll leave the Lu family.)
Chuning?
Chuning!
Siyan.
Lin Chuning is gone.
What do you mean?
She told me everything last night.
She only came to the Lu family
to get close to you so she could save me.
Now that I'm back,
she can finally run off with Mochen.
She would never say that.
She and Shen Mochen
had an arranged marriage from childhood.
Didn't you know?
Stop looking for her.
Even if you do, you won't find her.
I'll find her no matter what.
Siyan!
♪Barging into the sea
that bears your name♪
♪Swimming to the end with loneliness♪
♪Going against the current
and over the reef traps♪
♪Clearing the fog
just to get close to you♪
♪Pushing away the gravel
hidden beneath the seaweed♪
♪Wandering near your heart♪
♪I imagined
our encounter countless times♪
♪So close, yet out of reach♪
♪Keeping
all this lonely courage to myself♪
♪I was never part of your world♪
♪If your silhouette
was etched upon the sea♪
♪The sky as your wedding dress♪
♪Turn me into a cloud♪
♪Keep a sliver of the past♪
♪If love is like an illusory bubble♪
♪Together forever in my dreams♪
♪I'd rest forever in your arms♪
♪Barging into the sea
that bears your name♪
♪Swimming to the end with loneliness♪
♪Going against the current
and over the reef traps♪
♪Clearing the fog
just to get close to you♪
♪Returning to the land
Left bare by the receding sea♪
♪Withering like a fallen leaf♪
♪The message in a bottle
buried on the shore♪
♪No one asked♪
♪All this lonely courage for myself♪
♪I'm no longer part of your world♪
♪If your silhouette
was etched upon the sea♪
♪The sky as your wedding dress♪
♪Turn me into a cloud♪
♪Keep a sliver of the past♪
♪If love is like an illusory bubble♪
♪Together forever in my dreams♪
♪I'd rest forever in your arms♪
♪If the sea didn't wait
for the evening breeze♪
♪And swim with me to you♪
♪I'd become♪
♪A whale
who forever keeps the sea company♪
♪If love is like a night storm♪
♪Unable to stop for a moment♪
♪Let the wind scatter my traces♪