=The Fallen Lady Returns=
=Episode 12=
Marquis Ding'an left this
from the child swap.
Don't move.
There's something on the beam.
A swaddling cloth.
A star.
This is the Empress's mark.
Go.
Bring the Zhous here.
Your Majesty.
There was a fire in the dungeon.
All the Zhous
died in the fire.
What?
Your Majesty.
I'm not afraid to confront them.
But the Zhous are gone.
I wonder if Prince Ji
has other evidence.
Even if there were,
the Empress must've erased it.
You can't make baseless accusations.
You can't convict Mother
because of a cloth.
As you claimed she swapped her child,
you'd best have proof.
Your Majesty,
I do have proof.
When the Princess was born,
the Zhous entrusted the child
to this woman.
Your Majesty, please trust me.
This belonged to the Princess at birth.
I have kept it safe all these years.
Present it to me.
It's the golden lock
I had someone make
for your unborn child.
Didn't you say it was lost?
The Empress ignored the law
and deceived His Majesty.
She swapped a daughter for a son.
Such a deed cannot be forgiven.
Your Majesty, please calm your anger.
Xuanming...
Xuanming truly is your child.
However,
Li Yuewan is also your daughter.
Your Majesty,
the Empress gave birth to a pigeon pair.
If anyone were to find out,
the Princess would be in great danger.
Ignoring Her Majesty's objections,
I asked the Zhous to take care of her.
If that was the case,
why kill all the involved back then?
Shut up.
I did nothing of the sort.
Do not slander me.
Your Majesty,
if you did not do this,
why did you keep pushing me
to the brink?
Someone set fire to Huaguang Temple,
trying to burn Zhang Xiyin
and my sister alive.
These arrowheads here
were taken from the flaming arrows then.
During the imperial banquet,
Zhang Xiyin was attacked again.
This blade was pulled from the assassin.
Tonight,
the Zhous died.
These arrowheads
came from the assassin too.
Coincidentally,
they all bear the same pattern.
What can these arrowheads
prove?
They can be forged anywhere.
The pattern of the star
is the emblem of the Empress of Dayu.
Who would dare to forge them?
Father, this...
Enough.
Now, all the evidence is here.
What more can you say?
Yes.
I did want to kill Zhang Xiyin.
Li Yuewan is my daughter.
It's my duty to protect her.
What's wrong with that?
Zhang Xiyin keeps provoking me.
Does she not deserve to die?
You...
Li Xinwan.
You have truly let me down.
From this day on,
you are stripped of your title
and confined to Qiankun Palace.
Without my command,
you may not leave the palace.
As for you,
since you know nothing of this,
then treat your Mother
as if she has passed away.
Humph.
Father, Father!
Please take back your order.
Withdraw your command.
Father!
Please withdraw it!
Step aside.
Leave.
Xuanming.
Mother.
It was I who killed them.
You need not cover for me.
I'll go
and explain it to Father now.
Xuanming.
Li Yuewan's task has failed.
I've arranged for someone
to take her somewhere safe.
You have more pressing matters.
You must get the complete
Trade Route Map
from the Zhangs.
The Trade Route Map?
Only
the imperial merchants
can hold this map.
I must have it.
From here on,
everything depends on you.
Mother,
once I ascend the throne,
the whole realm will be yours.
Why do you want that map?
It's for our future
and the greater cause.
Xiyin.
Why are you suddenly here?
Father, you still won't tell me
the truth even now?
Why is the Empress targeting us?
Xiyin...
I've thought about the reason
why she keeps targeting us.
Maybe it's for the Trade Route Map.
In that case,
we are in greater danger.
Fine.
As things have come to this point,
I won't hide it from you anymore.
What's this?
This is the key to the Map.
But why is it incomplete?
The key is split into three parts.
The most crucial piece
is the one you hold now.
The other two are with me and Shou'an.
Shou'an knew you'd come,
so
he gave me
his piece.
The Map was granted by His Majesty.
Only imperial merchants possess it.
It's a hidden route
for transporting goods
that stretches across Dayu and Xiliang.
Can it also serve military uses?
Yes.
Aside from His Majesty and us,
no one knows its exact location.
So,
we must guard our post
as the imperial merchant
for generations.
Then why does the Empress
want it so badly?
Could it be...
Useless fools.
You can't even secure a few shops.
Yes, yes.
Xuanming,
why are you so upset?
Go away.
I'm just furious at Zhang Xiyin.
She opposes the Ministry of Revenue
at every turn
as the imperial merchant.
She's just a lowborn woman.
Dealing with her is no trouble at all.
Xuanming, no need to be upset.
I manage the Ministry of Revenue,
yet it's hard for me
to allocate money to palaces.
Xuanming,
no need to worry.
As an imperial merchant,
she handles every aspect
of the Palace's needs.
One slightest mistake
can easily crush her.
In that case,
I'll leave it to you.
My Lady, this wine smells delightful.
It was worth your time
choosing it yourself.
Only the finest wine is fit
for His Majesty's longevity banquet.
Your taste never fails.
Stop.
Who are you?
How dare you not curtsy
to Princess Yongjia?
Greetings, Your Highness.
I'm Zhang Xiyin.
Oh.
Your family is the one
clinging to the imperial merchant title.
We earned that title through capability.
We're not clinging to it.
How insolent!
How dare you defy me?
What are these things?
This is the wine
for His Majesty's longevity banquet.
Open them.
(Wine)
How bold of you.
How dare you offer
such poor wine to Father?
The chosen imperial merchant
lacks taste indeed.
You can't even pick the proper wine.
I almost mistook it for swill.
Guards.
Zhang delivered poor wine to the Palace
and harbored ill intentions.
Smash all this swill for me.
Your Highness,
this wine is of the finest quality
from its ingredients to its craft.
Why not try it yourself?
How dare you offer such wine
to the Princess?
Do the Zhangs wish to lose their heads?
If the wine is truly so fine,
why don't you
taste it for me first?
I am a Rank II Countess
by His Majesty's edict.
If I err,
His Majesty will punish me.
Your Highness,
are you overstepping your bounds?
Since when do I need
a commoner to instruct me?
I'll do it myself.
Enough.
Even you can't drink this wine.
How dare you present it to Father?
Open your eyes and see
what you should fight for
and what you cannot afford to offend.
Let's go.
My Lady.
♪Wandering in the world♪
♪Braving the storms♪
♪Destiny twists and turns♪
♪I'm trapped in a web of intrigue♪
♪My eyes reflect the cold world♪
♪Feuds and grievances tie my heart♪
♪On a night fraught with peril♪
♪The abyss yawns before my gaze♪
♪Beneath a defiant facade♪
♪Grief is tightly wrapped inside♪
♪Suddenly, a ray of light appears♪
♪Piercing right through my doubts♪
♪And becoming my sun♪
♪You are my light♪
♪Driving away endless darkness♪
♪Guiding me toward what's to come♪
♪Rushing toward dawn♪
♪You are my light♪
♪You shine upon my path♪
♪Walk this journey with me♪
♪Echoes of time resound♪
♪Each year settles in my heart♪
♪Wherever you are♪
♪You kindle a fire in my chest♪
♪Give me the strength to soar♪
♪Through the boundless crowds♪
♪Step by step, I'm walking♪
♪Closer to your side♪