Help!
The puppet is killing, help!
It is all Miss Meigui's fault.
Just watch how I deal with you.
Sun Laoban is not the killer.
Why?
This motive for murder does not hold up.
We originally thought once Wu Laoban died,
Sun Laoban would become the biggest beneficiary.
But this song and dance hall is losing money.
They were just waiting for the puppet show to open
so they could make a big profit.
At that moment,
if Sun Laoban killed Wu Laoban,
would that not be a losing bargain?
What do you think?
The timing of the murder does not fit.
The killer committed a locked room murder.
He controlled the puppet
and hid in the crowd after the killing.
But that day Sun Laoban
was the last one to arrive.
He has an alibi.
Then who is the killer?
If we analyze by motive for murder,
Miss Meigui
is actually very suspicious.
Think about it.
Once Wu Laoban dies,
no one will be promoting Wen Qing.
Then the Star Dancer spot
will naturally go to Miss Meigui.
Then I will go investigate Miss Meigui.
No need.
Darn it, I will go.
You go look for other evidence.
No, I...
Why will you not let me go?
Look, we
can follow Miss Su's plan first.
Let us all listen to her for now.
Move out immediately.
I am begging you.
I will never talk back again.
Wen Qing's arm is so badly hurt.
Do you know how much I am losing?
Can you even afford to pay for it?
I was wrong.
I really know I was wrong.
I have all sorts of ways to deal with you.
From now on, I will sing whenever you tell me to.
I will sing whatever you tell me to sing.
I was waiting for you to say that.
Work hard for me from now on.
I will not treat you badly.
You came to laugh at me, did you not?
I never laugh at anyone
who has to bow to life.
Wipe it off.
Get up first.
You are a cop, right?
No.
I am a forensic doctor.
I told Sun Laoban that there was something off about you.
I made him drive you away.
How did you figure it out?
The song and dance hall is a real mixed crowd.
All sorts of people from all walks of life.
You smell too proper,
and that actually gave you away.
Ask whatever you want.
I have nothing to hide anyway.
There was a murder in the song and dance hall.
Why did you not leave?
To earn money for my father’s medical bills.
The dance hall pays quickly,
so I became a dance girl.
Sadly, my father still was not cured.
He passed away.
I have also been in this dance hall for over ten years.
I am used to it.
If I leave here,
I do not even know where I could go.
Are you the killer?
No.
I heard
Sun Laoban is really good at taking photos.
If there is a chance,
take a few pictures for me.
My skills are nothing but petty tricks.
If you like,
I will take some for you then.
We are here.
Please come in.
Come on, come on.
Please, please, please.
Just treat Boss Zhou like you would Wu Laoban
After your arm has healed
Miss Wen
As long as you behave
You can get anything you want
Baby
Wu Laoban, Wu Laoban is here
Is that you
I have no grudge against you
Please, do not come after me
Wu Laoban, I am begging you
I beg you, I beg you
I do not want your wages
Wu Laoban, I do not want your wages
I will give up my wages, Wu Laoban
I really do not want the wages
No
No more, no more, no more
I really do not want it
How is it you
Do you realize
You scared me half to death
You are here pretending to be a ghost
I was not pretending to be a ghost
That scary sound
came from the phonograph
Besides, the one faking ghosts is not me
It is under that stage
The person who set up this phonograph
Do not be scared
Important clue, let me say it first
Look
Someone actually put one under the stage
They placed a phonograph there
to play the sound of screams
That must be Sun Laoban
To make the puppet show go smoothly
he bribed the master to put on an act
This clue you mentioned is very helpful
But
the police station is calling us back now
They say the case is closed
The killer is not even found, how can it be closed
The killer turned himself in
It is Wen Qing's old flame
Liu Dazhu
I am the one who killed Wu Laoban
Liu Dazhu, I am telling you
This is called intentional homicide
You will be sentenced to death for it
I know
Then why did you kill him
Wen Qing and I
were childhood sweethearts
We were in love with each other
Wen Qing loved to sing and dance
I came with her to try our luck in the big city
We found work at Wucheng Song and Dance Hall
Wen Qing
soon became the hall's Star Dancer
Wu Laoban took a fancy to Wen Qing
He picked a fight and had me kicked out
I went back to see Wen Qing several times
but I was stopped every time
No matter what job I tried to get
Wu Laoban would secretly ruin it
I ended up begging on the streets
Hurry up and get out of here
Wen Qing gave me money several times
She wanted me to leave Wucheng
And go back to the countryside
But I flat-out refused
Wu Laoban stole Wen Qing from me
He drove me into a desperate corner
I hate him
So I waited for the right chance
And killed him in one go
How did you kill him
And how did you get out of the sealed
Changing room and escape
First I killed him
Then I set up the puppet properly
To make it look like the puppet killed him
And scared them all away
After that I used the cover of night
Threw away the black clothes
And slipped out disguised as a waiter
Without the gods knowing
Or the ghosts noticing
Since this whole matter
Has already been cleared up
I say we can close this case
Congratulations, you have kept your job
He is not the killer
His leg is injured
So he could not pose as a waiter
And slip away in the chaos
Even less act while disguised as a puppet
This case is closed when I say it is
Stop investigating it
Stop creating trouble for the station
Take him away
You picked a good room
Very well hidden
Boss Zhou
We agreed on this
From now on
We will be relying on you
Of course
I will agree to anything
As long as you
Do as you are told
It hurts
When your injury is healed
Wu Laoban
Didn not he say no puppets were allowed
In the changing room
Why is there still one here
Such bad luck
Why
The song and dance hall case was closed
So why are puppet murders still happening
Chief
It is possible
Maybe this is a new case
The killer
Wants to frame the hall puppets
Closing the case before it is clear
Will make the public think
We are a bunch of useless gluttons
Yang Zong
I am assigning you to keep investigating
You must wrap it up quickly
All right
No
What is your objection
You stop or resume the case as you like
You really do not take us seriously
If you want us to investigate
You must meet my three conditions
Let us hear them
First
Zhao Wei
Is not allowed to meddle in this case
Second
Yang Zong was demoted before
Now he must be reinstated
Third
Once this case is solved
The bonus
Must be tripled
Those three conditions
I accept them all
Restoring the stations reputation
Is our top priority
Solve it quickly, do not fail
Thank you, Chief
Yang Zong
You must protect Su Qingyun for me
Yes sir
We have not solved the case yet
This money really burns in my hands
All right, Old Li
You are actually paying me back
No need
I just negotiated it, we are back on the case
If we solve it, the bonus
will be tripled
Really
Well, since you put it that way
If you are saying it like that
I do have a new idea
Officer Yang, look
How did you find it
The dancers found it while they were changing