[Previously]
Remember this feeling.
"Péngyǒu."
Do you remember it?
Maybe because you think of me this way, we no longer are close friends.
Did you notice that about me?
I thought you only had eyes for Mackie.
I always keep my eyes on you.
Help me. Don't take my bag.
- Give it to me.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Palm!
- Help me.
Put your heads down!
You need to protect him.
Can I trust you to do that?
Yes, Khun Thanya. I'll do my best to take care of him.
I'm sorry, Dad. I forgot my belt.
Palm, if you are going to ride to school with him, you should arrive before him.
How could you let your boss wait for you? Do you understand?
- I'm sorry.
- Get in the front seat.
Let him sit in the back with me.
Is it a good idea?
I don't want to sit alone.
One more thing: if someone sees him getting out of the car, he won't be teased about it.
It's okay. He can handle it.
Me, too. I will be teased, too.
All right, Khun Nueng.
Palm. Today, go sit with Khun Nueng in the back.
- Yes, Dad.
- Hurry up.
[Authentic Branded Sport Shoes - 2,500฿]
You only think about basketball.
Did you memorize the vocabulary the teacher taught us?
I think I'm doing all right. I remember most of the words you taught me.
Knowledge is also important.
Mental skills are as important as physical skills.
Learning a second language will be useful to you someday.
Your body will deteriorate, but no one can take away the knowledge in your brain.
What if we were hit on the head?
If we have a concussion from being hit, there's a chance that we will forget it.
Rubbish.
No, I just believe that physical skills are as important as mental skills.
Then you use your muscles. I'll be the brain.
Then we will be a good match.
[Pond Naravit Lertratkosum]
[Phuwin Tangsakyuen]
[Rasee Diskul Na Ayudhya]
[Nat Sakdatorn]
[Perth Tanapon Sukumpantanasan]
[Chimon Wachirawit Ruangwiwat]
[Pitisak Yaowananon]
[Panadda Ruangwut]
[Pawin Kulkaranyawich]
[June Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee]
[Never Let Me Go]
[Enemies]
The words written on the board were randomly chosen by me.
[Phoomphiphat Wittayalai High School]
Please read them out loud and use them to compose a sentence.
Is there anyone who wants to do it?
No?
Okay, I'll pick from the student numbers.
No. 21.
- It's me.
- Go ahead.
- "Dírén."
- It means enemy.
- Good.
"Dírén" means enemy.
Pannakorn, please compose a sentence using the word.
Speak up, well-connected boy.
I want to hear your wise words.
He can't do it.
No ivory will come out of a dog's mouth.
Very good.
Nuengdiao, what is the word you used to compose a sentence?
"Gǒu."
It means "dog."
Well done.
Nuengdiao got one point from Pannakorn's question.
Let's move on.
Next word.
[Vocabulary]
[Enemy / Dog]
[Cheater]
Take a look. Who did this?
He deserves it.
Look at it.
He's a cheater.
Let's take a picture and post it to embarrass him.
Move!
He's here.
What the hell is this?
The cheater is here.
You deserve this, Cheater.
What the hell are you doing?
Mind your own business. Leave!
What have I ever done to them?
It happened again?
Since your dad died, the bullying is getting worse.
I'll help you handle them.
How is your family doing?
It must be chaotic after your dad's death.
We always have problems.
My mom needs to step up and manage the business.
My uncle is upset that my mom became the CEO.
I also need to adjust to this new life.
Life is not as easy as when my dad was still alive.
I know how you feel.
What about your dad? How is he doing?
I just saw him on the news.
He's okay.
That is business between adults. I'll let them handle it.
Don't worry about me.
Nueng, I saw what happened at the lockers.
Do you want me to help you find out who did it?
Why does everyone think that I can't take care of myself?
I know that you can take care of yourself,
but you should learn to open up to people.
The world is not as cruel as you think.
You don't need to carry the whole world on your shoulders.
Can I ask you something?
What?
You and Palm...
What is your relationship?
We're classmates.
Why? Do you have a problem with him?
No, I don't.
I was just curious.
I saw him get into your car after school.
Are you living together?
If I tell you, you can't tell anyone else.
You can trust me.
He's my driver's son.
My mom put him in the same school as me.
After my dad died,
my mom is worried that I might get attacked.
So she sent him to protect me.
So Palm... is your bodyguard?
No, he's not.
He's a friend.
Oh, I see.
Actually, you don't need him.
If you want a friend, or someone who can take care of you,
I think I can do that.
Do you not believe me?
You can call me your bodyguard.
I do need a bit more training.
I also need a cool pair of sunglasses and to wear a suit.
I'll walk behind you like a bodyguard.
Like John Wick.
Do you know how to shoot and box?
Are those the requirements?
No, of course not.
I just want someone who believes in me,
who doesn't treat me like I'm weak.
That's enough for me.
Then I can do that for you.
I don't need extra training to do that.
Hey, Palm.
Ben...
Are you interested in dancing, or are you just tagging along with Nuengdiao?
I like the atmosphere here.
I like vintage things.
So I tag along.
Isn't it because Nuengdiao's mom sent you to protect him?
Nueng told me everything about you.
I understand that his mom is worried about him,
but you don't need to go this far.
You should give him some space to live his own life.
He doesn't need a bodyguard.
I don't think anyone is planning to kill him;
it's just bullying at school.
I'm the class president,
and I can handle it.
So you will have time to do whatever you want.
Don't you like basketball? Why don't you apply for the Basketball Club? Do you want me to do that for you?
It's okay. I can manage my own schedule.
Okay. That's up to you.
I do have something to tell you.
Lately, you will see me around often.
So...
I hope you have a little more trust in me.
I won't hurt Nuengdiao.
- Ben.
- Maggie.
Are you here to play music?
No, I'm here to support Nuengdiao.
Why do so many people come here to cheer on Nuengdiao?
Both you and Palm.
I was the one who told him about the position.
I need to see him with my own eyes.
The elderly like him.
Seeing young people here helps them feel younger.
The club will hold a party.
You must come because it's a really cute party.
People will wear costumes.
It will be the day that I look the prettiest.
Palm, you can come, too.
Don't forget to dress up. You can come dance with me.
You don't need to invite him. He doesn't like dancing
as he prefers physical activities.
If you dance with him, he might step on your foot.
If you come often and practice dancing with me, you will get good at it before the party.
Believe me.
Nuengdiao, good job. You're amazing!
Thank you, Maggie.
- Are you done?
- Yes.
They will turn on music for them to dance .
Anyway, what are you doing here?
I came to see the person who said he doesn't know how to play the piano,
can't play the piano, or is bad at the piano.
You're being too modest.
You play like a professional.
- You're overstating.
- I mean it.
I love this song.
My dad used to play it when I was little to teach me to dance.
The song makes me feel good and want to dance along to it.
Do you want to dance with me? I'll teach you.
It's okay.
I'm not good at counting dance steps.
It's okay. You will get better after practicing,
especially with a good trainer like me.
Come on, let's go, Palm.
Give it a try.
Put your hand on my back.
Hold my other hand.
Do you want to dance with me?
No. It's not my thing.
It's just dancing along to the music.
I'll lead you in a dance.
You don't need to be serious if you get it wrong.
No one is watching you.
[Ballroom Dance Club]
[ben_is_here]
I know that you can take care of yourself.
But you should learn to open up to people.
The world is not as cruel as you think.
[MaggieGirl: I need to make him fall in love. I mean with dancing. ;)]
What are you thinking?
It's late. You need to get up early tomorrow.
Go to sleep.
- You can't go in.
- Let us in!
We deserve justice!
Khun Thanya, how will you handle the tenants who are currently filing complaints against you?
Is there anything unusual in the lease contracts?
The land lease agreement has reached the end of its 30-year term.
Our company is looking for a new form of investment that is more suitable to today's world.
Many tenants said they didn't know about it.
That's impossible.
We have informed them one year in advance.
We also told them that we are willing to give compensation to those who are affected.
Like everyone here, I'm also affected by it.
My agreement with the company,
it was signed when Phiphop was managing the business.
We had this agreement a long time ago.
After Phiphop's wife took over his position, she made changes to the agreement.
This is not right. She can't do that.
Everything that I've been building is…
What's wrong? Why do you look so stressed?
I saw the news about the land eviction.
So I'm worried about you.
You don't need to worry about me.
It's not a big deal. I can handle it.
This land is ours.
We need to take it back.
We have let them do business on our land for too long.
They also use our land for a business that is our competitor.
We didn't do anything wrong, Nueng.
Can I ask you something?
Do you really want to take over Dad's position in the company?
I don't want people to hate you. I don't want to see you being attacked.
But this is what I have to do.
I don't trust others enough to let them take over.
I'm working hard.
I'm doing all this for you.
You know this, don't you?
Soon you will take over after me.
You need to take better care of yourself. You need to be careful.
After Dad passed, the world seems more dangerous.
I can take care of myself.
I want to see you be able to take care of yourself.
Okay?
Yes. I enrolled Palm in your shooting class.
So you will have a friend.
I want you to open up to him.
He may be different from you.
But I believe...
he will be someone that you can trust.
Don't worry about me.
- Okay?
- Yes.
I can take care of myself.
There are the four rules of firearm safety.
The first rule is to treat all guns as though they are loaded.
The second rule is to only point your gun in the direction of your target.
The third rule is keeping your index finger off the trigger.
The fourth rule is being sure of your target,
and making sure that your bullet won't harm anyone else besides your target.
Why are you so good at shooting?
How long have you been shooting?
For several years.
When I went to work on a fishing boat, I always carried a gun.
In case there were any thieves.
When you pull the trigger, what are you thinking?
Are you thinking about the person you hate? The one that you want to kill.
No. I don't use hatred to drive me.
When I pull the trigger,
I'm thinking that I am protecting someone.
Someone important in my life.
Someone that I love.
Someone that I really care about.
Someone who I can't live without.
When I think of that person,
I feel more determined.
Love is much more powerful than hate.
Khun Nueng, why don't you give it a try?
Think about the person you love the most. The person that you will die for.
Do you have that person?
My mom.
My mom is the one I care about the most.
Then think about her when you pull the trigger.
Try to aim at the target.
Imagine that you are protecting your mom.
What about you?
When you pull the trigger, who are you thinking of?
Do you have a person that you love the most?
♫ Don't be afraid even if we are apart ♫
♫ Just stay where you are, and I'll find you ♫
♫ No matter what tomorrow brings, please remember this ♫
♫ I will live only for you ♫
Hey. What are you doing here?
My dad came to talk to your mom.
I guess it's something important.
On the way here, he took his frustration out on me.
What about you? How is your plan going?
Did you become rich from stock trading?
Did you become a young billionaire?
I think the one who should be called a young billionaire is you.
My goal is still far away.
But you will definitely become the owner of a hotel business soon.
Do I need to call you "CEO Nueng"?
Nonsense.
Can I ask you something?
You're close to Ben, the class president, aren't you?
We used to be close when we were in 10th grade.
Why?
Nothing. He asked me to join the music club.
So I want to know what kind of person he is.
He's nice.
He's very talented.
So everyone loves him. That's why he was elected class president.
Why aren't you still close with him?
How should I explain it?
As we grew up, we had different interests.
That was why we drifted apart.
Don't get too close to him.
He can't stay close to someone for long.
What do you mean?
Nothing. I'm just talking gibberish.
You will know him after spending time together.
Let me ask you for real.
Are you sure you can take care of all the businesses?
Our company owns many hotels. The management cost is escalating.
Why do you need to keep them all to yourself?
Your husband is dead. You have only one son.
Nuengdiao shows no interest in the business.
Look at my son, Chopper.
He has better potential. He earns hundreds of thousands of baht from stock trading every day.
That's good. You and your son can open your own business.
You don't need to worry about Nuengdiao.
I'll teach him.
He has a lot of time to learn from me.
He's talented enough to excel in anything he does.
I hope he does well.
His dad is dead.
His mom makes enemies everywhere.
You are lucky that the conflicts aren't serious.
But if you continue on this path, it's not that I'm cursing you...
It will be dangerous.
Do you need to get hurt more than you already did before you give in?
Are you worried about me or threatening me?
I'm worried.
I'm worried about both you and Nuengdiao.
If something happens to you, what will Nueng do?
Do you want him to become an orphan?
Thank you for worrying about my family,
but you don't need to worry about Nuengdiao.
If something happens to me,
the only one who has the right to take over the business of the Kiattrakulmethee is Nuengdiao.
Are you sure he can handle it?
There are dozens of enemies out there.
Give him some time.
I will be strong enough.
One more thing.
External enemies are not as scary as internal enemies.
Internal enemies can cause deeper wounds.
It's hard to get rid of them.
They never feel full no matter how much you feed them.
I hope that Nuengdiao won't end up like his dad.
Ai Palm.
Are you living here?
Yes. My dad works here.
Why are you so polite to me?
Just talk to me like when we are at school.
It's okay.
Aunt Thanya is generous.
She sends you to the same school as Nuengdiao.
Do you need to act as his servant when you are at school?
I'm sorry if my words offended you.
I didn't mean it.
I promise. I won't tell anyone at school.
I don't want them to tease you.
But from your body, I think you can knock them out.
How are you? Did you join the Basketball Club tryouts?
Yes, some of them.
If you have any problems at school, you can tell me.
Chopper. Let's go home.
Who is this?
A new servant?
I'm Chanon's son.
Chanon has a son?
Ai Palm is in the same class as me.
You are Palm?
How can Chanon afford an expensive school for you?
Khun Thanya helps us with that.
Khun Thanya.
Khun Thanya is generous.
She does charity work for education.
She gives a less fortunate kid a good opportunity in life. That's good.
Doing a lot of charity work may help extend her life.
Let's go.
I have to go now.
[Phoomphiphat Wittayalai High School]
Nueng.
Aren't you going to swim class?
I will after I put my stuff in the locker.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
I'm exhausted.
I only finished one lap.
I'd rather have swordplay as a gym class.
I'm too tired to talk right now.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Or should I pee in the pool?
No one will know it anyway.
Gross.
Why are you telling me that? If you didn't say it, I wouldn't know.
- All right.
- Go away.
If you can, you will choose to stay in the pool all day, right?
You look so happy.
Everyone wants to do things that make them feel happy.
For you, it's the piano.
Now you dare to talk back to me.
That's good. You know how to talk back.
Now you won't be the only one who gets scolded.
You didn't scold me.
You are just a nagger.
When you see a chance to talk back to me,
you don't let it go.
Khun Nueng.
I have something to ask you.
What?
Did you tell Ben that I'm your servant?
Did he tell you that?
I didn't mean to tell him.
He saw you got in the car.
I didn't want to lie to him.
I'll talk to him about it.
It's okay. I'm not mad.
To be honest, it's your right to tell anyone you want.
But I've never called you my servant.
It's okay. You can call me whatever you want.
I don't mind.
[Gym: 8 minutes]
Phum.
Hey, Nueng.
I knew it was you.
Now you're getting smarter.
I've been suspecting you for a while.
So I took off my necklace in front of you.
I put it in a box with a GPS tracker.
I knew that my bully would target the item that I love.
So what?
What are you going to do to me?
Are you going to wake up your dad,
who was killed after cheating the villagers, and asked him to have me killed?
My dad didn't cheat.
Why? I thought we were friends.
Do you want to know why?
Do you really want to know?
It's because of your trashy parents.
You are mad about my mom's land eviction?
That's right.
The contract that my family signed with your father is also not fair.
After he died, your mom canceled the contract.
Do you know how much money my family lost as a result of it?
My family is breaking apart.
My dad tried to kill himself.
It's all because of your capitalist parents.
Is that why you bully me?
You are behind all those pranks, cutting my bag and the flyers.
Yes.
I want everyone to know that your father was a jackass.
As his son, you don't deserve anything good that he left behind.
Your dad was a jackass.
So you should be treated like a jackass.
Okay.
I understand why you are angry.
I won't ask for anything from you, except for the necklace that my dad gave me.
He gave it to me before he died.
That's all I want.
And let's call it off here.
This necklace,
is it a gift from him?
It reminds you of your trashy cheating father.
Your mom is now carrying on his trashy legacy.
Your family are all cheaters.
Your whole family are cheaters.
Your dad deserves to rot in hell.
Stop talking bad about my dad.
Why?
I won't stop.
Your dad deserved to be dead.
Your dad is dead.
Your trashy dad won't wake up and come back to you.
Asshole, stop talking about my dad!
Do you want to try me?
What the hell are you doing?
Khun Nueng, are you all right?
Khun Nueng.
Khun Nueng, why do you need to butt in?
This is between me and Nuengdiao.
Get lost!
Why can't I butt in?
Why are you protecting him?
Are you his underling?
Or his boyfriend?
Now, Khun Nuengdiao, the mafia's son, has a handsome boyfriend protecting him.
All right.
If you want to butt in, then bring it on.
He's too scared.
Khun Nueng, are you all right?
Are you okay?
Palm!
Palm, watch out!
Palm.
Palm, behind you!
Phum.
Khun Nueng!
Palm, that's enough!
What are you thinking?
Are you thinking about the person that you hate? The one that you want dead.
Palm, that's enough!
What are you doing? Stop it!
Break it up! Stop it!
No.
I'm thinking that I am protecting someone.
Someone who I can't live without.
How are you?
Phum was sent to a hospital.
His condition is quite serious.
Palm was a bit too violent.
What about Palm?
How is he?
His condition is pretty bad.
He was sent home.
He will probably get disciplinary probation.
I don't know how severe his punishment will be.
The teacher will announce it later.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry that I didn't help you.
It's okay.
Thank you for all you have done for me.
Do you need my help?
It's okay, Khun Nueng. I can do it myself.
Don't be stubborn.
Give it to me.
Don't move.
Stay still.
Do you know that you will get into trouble for helping me?
Photos of Phum are spreading.
He was beaten up badly.
I think the whole school is probably afraid of you.
Are you afraid of me?
No. I'm a bit surprised.
What made you that furious?
I think it was instinct.
Instinct?
Then you have a crazy instinct.
You did it without worrying about yourself.
The person that I need to worry about is you.
Whatever reasons you have,
next time, you need to think about your future before you do anything.
You can let me get hurt sometimes.
So I can learn my lesson from it.
We can learn from our wounds.
Next time, you don't need to be that protective of me.
When did you get it back?
When I was fighting with him.
When I saw a chance, I pulled it off him.
Thanks.
I'm really very thankful.
I'd better go back to my room.
Can you stay with me? I want to talk to someone.
[Next Week]
My room is big.
I get lonely sometimes.
Even if you come sleep with me, there's still plenty of space in my room.
If you really like him,
you should tell him.
I…
I like you.
You can dance with her, but why don't you want to dance with me?
What the hell is wrong with you?
♫ Don't be afraid even if we are apart ♫
♫ Just stay where you are, and I'll find you ♫
♫ No matter what tomorrow brings, just remember this ♫
♫ I will only live ♫
♫ For you ♫
♫ Don't be afraid even if we are apart ♫
♫ Just stay where you are, and I'll find you ♫
♫ No matter what tomorrow brings, just remember this ♫
♫ I will only live ♫
♫ For you ♫