YOUN HYUN-JAE
SONG SEUNG-IL
PARK HEE-SUN
SHIN HYEON-WOO
KIM GO-EUN
KIM JAE-JIN
HAM YE-JIN
WOO SUNG-MIN
KIM MIN-GEE
LIM SU-BEEN
LEE SUNG-HUN
LEE JOO-YOUNG
CHOI MINA SUE
LEE HA-EUN
JO I-GEON
SINGLE'S INFERNO
Go-eun!
Oh. Yeah?
When are you gonna hang out with me?
I'll be down later, okay?
The three of us could hang.
Let's hang out later.
We'll be down later after our chat.
All right.
He can't seem to say to her,
"Can the two of us go somewhere to talk?"
I-geon can't?
It's because he knows
Sung-min won't let her go.
- You think?
- Yeah, it's kind of awkward for him.
Think he's blunt?
What's going on with you, Mina?
What's the situation?
Well, as of today, I think
I've finally settled on just one person.
- My first choice.
- After going back and forth?
- After a lot of back and forth, I--
- You were indecisive?
Yeah, I was before.
You must be relieved.
But he's gone to Paradise.
- Of course.
- I know.
- Ah, today--
- I'm off to find my love.
Wait. Why?
- Go-eun again? Okay.
- Yeah, I'm off to see Go-eun.
I suddenly thought to myself,
"What am I doing here?"
- You have to fight for love. Go.
- Yes, I'll go and fight for it.
- All right.
- He's going off to fight for it.
I don't feel that bad about it.
Sometimes you have to say those things.
They're just so competitive.
- Are they really?
- Seriously.
They've been talking for a long time.
It's gotten dark outside.
- Sung-min's such a chatterbox.
- But I think that's part of his appeal.
You know how some couples talk
on the phone for three hours each time?
He must be accommodating
when it comes to that kind of thing.
Mmm.
I…
What are you two talking about
that's taking so long?
- Us?
- Are you ever gonna stop?
Shall we go in since it's cold?
- Okay.
- Yeah, it's cold.
Where's "in"?
Let's go to the dining area then.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Those two just won't leave her alone.
Sung-min won't leave.
There's no "I'll let you two talk"
or anything.
You'd think he'd give them privacy.
- He's talked to her for a long time.
- For two hours.
He knows he can't leave them alone.
- Should I sit in the middle?
- Yeah.
Here, sit in the middle.
- Sit in the middle.
- Okay.
- I'll sit here.
- This is funny.
What were you guys talking about
for so long out there?
- You know, just this and that.
- You were talking forever.
If we'd been left alone,
we would've talked till dawn.
Oh.
- Gosh.
- There you go.
Oh, hang on.
Did you two go to Paradise together?
- Once.
- Oh.
Hmm. Right. So, who chose who?
We chose each other.
- You matched?
- We matched.
- We paired up in a game.
- Yeah, we matched with each other.
Mmm-hmm.
We played a game together
and talked after then got matched up.
That's what happened.
Ah.
I can't wait to see what happens tomorrow.
Yeah, seriously.
Yeah. Me too.
They're all hanging out together?
Look, they make such a funny picture.
A literal love triangle.
I wonder what we'll be doing.
Sung-min's guarding his spot there
despite doing nothing
but making small talk.
- He's keeping watch.
- For sure.
I wonder what we'll be doing.
I might go get an ice cream.
WATER FOUNTAIN
- There's ice cream?
- At the water station?
ONLY OPEN AFTER SUNSET
1 PER PERSON, NO DELIVERIES
One per person.
The amenities have improved a lot.
Ice cream reminds me of college retreats.
I might go get an ice cream.
With who?
- "With who?"
- The three of them together?
This time I'll go with I-geon
and have a chat with him.
I'll go with I-geon
Go and get ice cream.
- See you later.
- Okay.
What could you possibly
talk about for four hours?
- Four hours?
- Yes.
What are you talking about?
It wasn't four hours.
I was trying to be patient
the whole time and not…
- I was, uh… you know?
- You know?
In the end,
I was forced to, like, be the third wheel.
Did you say four hours?
- Maybe not four hours.
- No.
- Have you been there?
- Where?
- There.
- Uh, yes, I have.
Oh.
There's basically nowhere
you haven't already been.
Seriously.
- Well…
- This is so annoying.
There are loads of places
I haven't been to, oppa.
Which way is it?
- We keep going a little further.
- Okay.
- All right, here's the spot.
- Yeah, I've been here once.
- For water?
- Yeah.
- There isn't anywhere you haven't been.
- Well, I have to get water.
- So we can only come here after sunset?
- Yeah, it has to be totally dark.
Oh, yum! I want Okdongja.
Oh. It's melted a bit.
You should have it quickly.
- Oh.
- Oh no.
Oh, that looks really good.
- It's tasty.
- Mmm.
- What's wrong with me?
- Here. Get up.
Just get up and launch it off. Yeah.
Honestly, what's wrong with me?
This always happens.
- You always drop food?
- Mmm.
I got it all over the table.
Should I rinse it off with water?
Uh… I'll do it.
Get up for a sec.
What was that?
Ah…
I can't help but laugh with them.
It's because we're following
the emotional arc of these two.
- Such a small thing but so funny.
- I know.
Oh no. I totally missed, didn't I?
Seriously, oppa, you com…
This is nerve-racking.
- You completely missed.
- Just wait.
This is so funny.
It's so funny.
Oh shit.
- Watch me.
- Okay.
I got it?
Oh, nice, nice.
I am curious
what you're like as a boyfriend.
- Me?
- Yeah.
How about you? As a girlfriend?
I really hate it when they repeatedly
do something I dislike.
Such as?
- I hate being addressed as "hey" or "you."
- Oh, "hey" or "you."
That's why you asked me
that question in Paradise.
Mmm. Mmm, that's right.
DAY 4 PARADISE
Since I don't know the guys yet,
I'm not sure what to ask.
Yeah. Joo-young?
Is there anyone
you're most attracted to right now?
There is.
- There is?
- Mmm.
Watch and see if you can guess.
Like, "Hey, it's him, right?"
Do you say "hey"
when calling your girlfriend?
Huh? My girlfriend?
- No, of course not.
- Mmm.
- No, really, I don't say "hey."
Who addresses their girlfriend
with "hey" or "you"?
Exactly. Even if we're fighting,
if someone calls me that--
- When they're angry? Yeah, I see.
- I'm…
I have a feeling you'd say that
when you're fighting.
- If I'm being honest…
- Yeah.
Let me think for a second.
When I was fighting…
My memory might be a bit distorted,
but I don't remember
addressing a girlfriend with "hey."
- I think I've called them "you," though.
- "You" is kind of…
"You did this, you said this,"
I may have said that.
That's not bad, I guess.
That's not so bad.
And you, when you're fighting?
When fighting?
- Well, you--
- I kinda want to see you get angry.
I don't think
I bring things up right away.
- I keep it to myself.
- Why?
Because I could be mistaken
or could've misunderstood something.
- I know exactly what you mean.
- Yeah.
Let's say I have
a particular thought at night.
If I wake up the next day and have
that same thought, then I take action.
Usually, I don't still have
that same thought.
Exactly. You're not the same person
at night as you are during the day.
That's right.
Talking to you is really fun.
Then you should've come down sooner.
Don't you think?
- I--
- Yeah, it's true.
- This is the kind of energy.
- The energy is different.
Yeah, it's totally different.
- Seriously, you were so funny.
- How so?
It was so funny when you threw the water.
Seriously, that was a total miss.
That was…
It was just--
I was going to do it myself,
but you insisted.
So funny. You're a funny guy.
And you're just super easy
to talk to as well.
- I think so too.
- Oh, I see.
When I hear them talk, it feels like
they're having conversations
that further their connection,
conversations with substance
that couples have.
But I've never seen those
between her and Sung-min.
There really must be something
about the first Paradise trip.
- Like your first love?
- It feels like that.
Both Mina Sue and Go-eun
have said the same thing.
Because she went
on her first Paradise trip with him.
Like, "Oh, maybe
Sung-min is special to me."
Is that what she's thinking?
Still, from where we're sitting,
I-geon seems to be her top choice.
- That's how it looks to us, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
But we really can't tell
if she feels that way herself.
We don't.
- Can we come in?
- Of course. Come in.
Which is Sung-hun's spot?
Sam?
- That one.
- This one?
All right. I saw him reading a book here.
Ooh, I'm cold.
What the heck?
Seriously, what are you doing?
Ugh, seriously? What's wrong with you?
Ah, that hurts.
What's wrong with you?
No.
This is what he reads?
He must be out of his mind.
Option Volatility and Pricing?
What the…
- What are you doing?
- I'm so curious about him.
I want to know everything right now,
but Hee-sun's going to find out first.
It's all right. You'll get your chance.
Ugh, why today?
I had to lose today of all days.
Why couldn't I have come in third?
Oh, actually, not third.
I would've had to come in second
to get a chance.
Well, if you get a chance
to go another time…
But there was significance
to being the first.
- You wanted to be the first.
- Yeah, I just…
I so badly wanted
his first Paradise trip to be with me.
- Mmm-hmm.
- But Hee-sun will get to know him
during their time together.
So when she gets back,
she'll know things I don't.
She'll know them before me.
That gets to me.
But didn't you feel Sung-hun's feelings
for you were pretty firm?
That's what he said.
But what if he's not telling the truth?
Well, Samuel has a unique kind of…
- Standard?
- …determination.
Everyone's telling you
that you have nothing to worry about.
Just have some faith in him.
Why does our girl Mina Sue always do this?
She has no interest in them
when they're by her side
and then pines for them when they're gone.
- It's such a shame.
- Such a shame.
What good does it do
to be moping on his bed?
He's in a different bed right now.
In Paradise.
- That sounds very provocative.
- Word.
I think she's one of those people
that only realize
what they're missing once it's gone.
PARADISE
PARK HEE-SUN & LEE SUNG-HUN
- Let's go in.
- Let's get in.
- Oh my god, that's so good.
- Isn't it warm?
It's so warm!
This is so nice.
Mmm.
- Good?
- Delicious.
What's your love language?
What makes you…
What do you like to receive?
- I think I like being taken care of.
- Oh.
Wow, okay, great.
- Why "great"?
- I like taking care of people.
- Oh, really?
- Acts of service.
Oh.
Why didn't you take care of me?
In Inferno?
How could I
when you were with someone else?
- Mmm.
- No, I don't like to bother anything.
Okay, so then,
which love language do you give?
Do I give?
- Well, I like giving gifts and--
- Gift giving?
Ooh.
That's kind of similar to me.
And I also like taking trips together.
- Oh, me too.
- Mmm.
We're kind of compatible
in practical ways.
Yeah.
- I like vacations too, traveling together.
- Mmm.
When you're dating,
do you see your boyfriend often?
Mmm.
I didn't get to very often 'cause I had
lots of long-distance relationships.
I like seeing my girlfriend every day.
Well, I guess New York's close.
- Everything's close in New York.
- Yeah, that's true.
Getting to know you better,
I'm still amazed.
Like, what the hell?
Seriously.
I feel like we could be a good match
when we leave here.
- Mmm.
- That's a big consideration for me.
After we leave this place
- and then go back to reality…
- Mmm.
…who could I, realistically,
have a relationship with?
I think, on paper, we're a good match.
Just date then.
- They are a good match.
- They suit each other.
You know, now that we're on day seven,
this feels like my life.
- Everyone's all in now.
- Exactly.
Our life is get up in the morning
and immediately, "Let's talk."
"Let's talk."
We haven't had breakfast yet,
but let's talk.
You never asked me to talk.
No, I haven't really talked
that much to many people.
Have you talked a lot
with Mina Sue, though?
I think so.
But she's honestly
kind of hard to figure out.
Her feelings, I mean.
- I'm sure she'll figure them out.
- Self-service.
- Love is self-service.
- Mmm. Uh-huh.
Love is self-service.
- It's everyone for themselves.
- Exactly.
From now on, though,
I told you, I will ask you more.
- I'll talk to you tomorrow.
- Okay.
And the next day too.
- Things are changing.
- Yeah.
This would work
because they're both in the States.
- I think there's a real possibility.
- Yeah.
- The vibe here was hot and heavy too.
- Mmm, right.
- I mean, it could work logistically.
- That's right.
They would be able to see each other
in the States.
Sung-hun definitely has to go back there,
so that's a factor you can't ignore.
Someone who ticks all the boxes
has suddenly appeared.
Exactly.
I also think it's not just
from Sung-hun's side.
I think Hee-sun's
really flirting with him.
Like, "Why did you never approach me?"
I think Hee-sun's
really tempted right now.
Yeah.
They're good together.
They suit each other.
But why does it have to be Sung-hun,
who's already connected to Mina Sue?
If the odds are that Sung-hun
and Hee-sun will end up together,
then there's a really high chance
that Mina Sue will end up
with nothing at the end,
apart from having gone through
this extreme arc of personal growth.
Yeah, there's definitely something here.
Bad news for Mina Sue.
PARADISE
LEE JOO-YOUNG & KIM JAE-JIN
Here we are.
I feel good after a shower.
- Do you want to eat?
- Yeah. I'll probably eat.
- Could you pour me a glass?
- Oh, sure.
Today you'll have whatever you want.
Anything you want.
- Ah, that's the picture I wanted.
- This is it.
- Yeah.
- This is the spot I wanted.
Since you're the queen today,
I'll wait on you like royalty
and bring you a fry.
Okay.
- And cheesecake, please.
- Of course.
- A little cheesecake.
- Coming right up.
Mmm.
And what now?
Cheesecake, please.
- Remember, we can't leave any of it.
- True.
I do think I'll miss the cheesecake
when I leave this place.
- It's so good.
- Mmm.
- Is this for me?
- Are you tired?
- Mmm.
Your eyes look sleepy.
Yeah, I am.
Go brush your teeth.
- With you as well?
- Mmm.
Go ahead then.
Can't you just brush them for me?
Okay.
Oh.
What's with that look?
Go brush your teeth.
Should we change into our pajamas?
Do you have pajamas?
Isn't this so cute?
Seriously.
Once we're all ready for bed,
let's do face masks.
Okay. But…
If you're tired, go to bed.
I can't sleep 'cause I've slept too much.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- We'll be together tomorrow too anyway.
- Good night.
I hate that I keep on smiling
like an idiot watching these couples.
I was grinning too.
- Yeah, you can't help it.
- I can feel it in the corners of my mouth.
- I think it happens to all of us.
- But it just keeps happening.
- Well, Jae-jin…
- I gotta close my mouth.
PARADISE
KIM MIN-GEE & LIM SU-BEEN
- Are those your pajamas?
- Yeah.
These are my pajamas.
- They suit you.
- Thank you. They were a gift.
- Mmm…
- Shall we sleep together?
- No.
- Oh, don't make me laugh.
I know I said it, but don't make me laugh.
- No, I promise you I was getting up.
- Mmm.
Well, we can just talk
until we fall asleep.
I like drifting off to sleep
while talking to someone.
You must enjoy spending time with me.
Yeah, I really do.
- Mmm. I'm glad to hear that.
- Yeah.
This is fun.
If we get the chance, I would really like
to come here again with you.
- Really?
- Well, this is the first time ever
that I've clicked with a guy so well
right from the start,
- and I don't want the conversation to end.
- Right.
And I'm thinking,
"Oh no, we're running out of time. Ugh."
Low-key panicking
but trying to play it cool.
- Right.
- And I'm going, "Give us more time."
"I wish we'd come here together earlier."
Yeah, I do feel like
it's so late in the game.
Yeah, we came really late.
Now that we're here,
I find your face cute too.
So strange.
Seriously, how did we end up
coming here together?
You don't just come here with someone
'cause you feel like it.
Yeah, true.
But we did end up here
because I felt like it.
Are you laughing?
- No, it's just…
- Yeah.
Well, to be honest,
compared to, uh, the first impression
that I had of you…
Yeah?
I don't know if I should say this,
but you're kind of cute.
Mmm.
But I'm even cuter.
I'm even cuter than I am now.
I haven't actually shown you
my cute side yet.
- Hmm.
- Yeah.
- There's tension between them too.
- There is.
You know, I've never seen
Min-gee like this before.
Yeah, we got the impression
that she was unwavering,
like a stick of bamboo
or a tree with deep roots.
But at the end of the day,
Min-gee can be fickle like the rest of us.
I think she really has been possessed
since she had that conversation
with Mina Sue.
The demon's gotten to her. For real.
The demon's moving
from one person to another.
- The demon's moved on to her.
- Like the two have been switched.
This is nuts.
Hey, yeah,
it's a totally logical theory, actually.
The two of them are both suddenly
on completely different paths
- from the ones they were on.
- I'm not used to seeing her like this.
She's acting so cutesy all of a sudden.
- Wake up.
- Did you get up early?
Man, what a hangover.
I definitely feel horrible
the day after I drink.
My body feels so hot.
She must've drunk a lot.
- Enough for her to get a hangover.
- Yeah.
Hmm. Hey, did we sleep together?
- Your memory. Did you drink a lot?
- Yeah, I must have.
How does he not know?
Did… Did I sleep here?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
So… why did we sleep together?
- Huh?
- Why did we sleep together?
LAST NIGHT
He slept there.
They must've slept in the same bed.
Oh, he woke up. Oh.
He must've just gone in.
Oh, I was just gonna sleep here, but…
Oh, I'm so cold.
- Min-gee, can I get in the bed?
- Hmm?
Yeah.
- He was really sleepy.
- And cold.
He genuinely just needs the comforter.
Yeah, he's pulling the blanket out.
There's no ulterior motive here
on his part. He's just cold.
Well, that was harmless.
Sleeping together in this particular case
was purely due to being drunk and cold.
- He needed the comforter.
- They just slept.
Yeah, it was literally just to sleep.
Yeah.
Are you laughing?
Oh, aren't you being
a bit too casual with me?
- No.
- Wow.
INFERNO
- Is this the place you work out?
- Yeah, this is it.
They're talking again.
- That's so hardcore.
- Seriously?
- Wow, seriously?
- He won't leave her alone.
I mean, we know he's a chatterbox,
but this is just…
Bright and early.
- The crack of dawn.
- Jesus Christ.
What's your workout going to be,
Mr. Paper Doll?
- I do it all. I can lift that easy.
- Oh.
Oh, really?
- I can't imagine it.
- Seriously?
I can totally bench-press that.
I go hard when I work out.
- You actually work out?
- Yeah.
Is your face puffy?
No. Why? Don't look at it.
- Is it not?
- I think it is a little.
Oh, it's definitely puffy.
- What?
- It is a bit puffy.
- Is it?
- Yeah. Your cheeks look kind of chubby.
Oh no.
I'm sure it'll go down if we keep walking.
I saw Go-eun and Sung-min
out walking together.
They even walked past me
while I was working out.
I got so annoyed by it
that I ended up completely overdoing it
with my workout today.
I guess I'd probably be kind of annoyed
too if I were in his shoes.
Of course it's annoying.
I mean, couldn't they have
at least said hi?
- I bet that was a workout booster.
- Yeah.
- An all-natural workout boost.
The sun's not coming out yet.
- So what do you think?
- About?
About early morning in Inferno.
It's nice.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Mmm.
You know, your first
Paradise trip with Min-gee?
How was it? Was it good?
- You want to know?
- Yeah.
According to Min-gee, she didn't feel
anything on that first Paradise trip.
- Really?
- Yeah.
But it was the same for me.
I didn't feel any chemistry
between us either.
But I definitely did feel it
when I went to Paradise with you.
Be honest with me.
What do you think you felt
when we went together,
from your point of view?
I always thought I was more of a listener.
- Well, that's how it's always been for me.
- Oh.
Yeah, but I found myself talking,
and I really liked that.
I found I was talking about myself a lot.
And I really enjoyed the experience.
It was so nice to be listened to for once.
Mmm.
Yeah, I really liked
being a chatty person.
Yeah.
My first impression of you was good too.
But when I got to know you better,
I liked you even more.
- Oh, I see.
- Yeah.
So that's when I fully made up my mind.
You've been my solid
number one choice since then.
Mmm.
You know, there must be
something between them
that we are just not seeing.
- When I watch them, yeah.
- Yeah, for sure. You're right.
Maybe it's because
Sung-min speaks courteously?
For example,
instead of addressing her as "you,"
he'll address her as "Go-eun."
That could be the kind of thing
she finds appealing in him.
Well, let's guess.
in terms of her feelings
for I-geon versus Sung-min,
what would the split be?
I think it's 80% I-geon and 20% Sung-min.
- That's pretty uneven.
- Yeah.
I'd say 60-40,
60 for Sung-min, 40 for I-geon.
Only because if it were me,
I'd find it really hard
to sit through those boring conversations
for such long periods.
Because if you didn't like him,
being around him all the time
and having those kinds of conversations
non-stop would be excruciating.
The fact that she says she likes him
means she has feelings for him.
They look like they talk five hours a day.
For real.
So, honestly, there's no way
she doesn't have genuine feelings for him.
Rather than
a dopamine-fueled relationship,
it could be that Go-eun prefers
a comfortable, uneventful relationship
where, practically,
all they do is chitchat all the time.
You might be right.
That could be the case.
I don't know.
Did you manage to do
everything you wanted to yesterday?
- Yeah. Well, pretty much.
- That's good.
- I want to go to Paradise again.
- Oh, yeah?
Got it, got it. I'll do my best.
- Yeah. Try your best.
- Okay.
- They're here.
- No, you're lying.
- That's a lie. Really?
- But there are only two couples.
Oh, what's going on?
- Joo-young and Jae-jin.
- They're behind them.
Oh.
Why sunglasses when there's no sun?
Ah…
Oh, Mina Sue.
- Hello.
- You're back.
- Welcome back.
- Hi.
- We're back.
- Hello.
Welcome back, welcome back.
Did you have a good time?
- Hello
- Hi. Hello.
- Hello.
- Hi.
So, did you have a lot of good food?
- Yeah, we did.
- Did you eat a lot?
- What's this?
- You look pretty today.
- Your shoes are so cute.
- They're cute.
Oh wow.
She's feeling awkward
'cause she enjoyed herself.
- I know.
- You think that's how she's feeling?
She can't approach--
Things are a bit awkward between them.
- Yeah, that's why.
- Right.
Did you have fun?
I'm curious about Sung-hun.
I wanna hear
how his first Paradise trip went.
- I want to know his job and age.
- What do they do?
Totally. Tell us, Hee-sun.
Talking to him, I found…
we have more in common than I thought.
So now I feel more comfortable
with him than I did before.
I think he's someone who understands me.
- Like, he just gets where I'm coming from.
- Mmm.
- That kind of…
I feel he's more comfortable and proactive
when it's one-on-one.
In a group setting like this,
he holds back.
- It's a challenge for him.
- He finds it difficult.
- For Sung-hun.
- It can be difficult.
- I think so too.
- Me too.
I bet he's a really caring guy.
- Like, sweet?
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, he's so thoughtful.
- I bet he's funny.
- He's so funny.
He's hilarious.
He's always like, "Oh, damn, damn."
It's always, "Damn."
- "Damn."
- "Holy, holy."
"Holy." His English is so good.
That's what makes it funny.
- Oh, Mina Sue.
- This is hilarious.
Not long ago,
Mina Sue would be the one talking,
and Hee-sun would get anxious and stuff.
- But now…
- The tables have turned.
- …the tables have turned.
- Yeah.
- How was it?
- I had fun too.
- You need to be more specific.
- More specific?
Honestly, it was so much more fun
than I thought it'd be.
- Think you're compatible?
- Yeah, we are.
As in, romantically?
Well, first of all, our values
and dating styles are identical.
Like, the way we think
is literally identical.
- Really?
- It was like talking to a mirror.
We were both like,
"Wait, you feel that way too?"
And that was basically
how the conversation went.
Like, "Wow, that's so weird."
- So we had a lot of fun.
- You can't know until Paradise.
Yeah, I think so. Mmm.
But to be honest, I don't think
it would have been this great
if I had gone with one of the other guys.
- Oh, really?
- Really. Yeah.
Yeah, I think it was mainly so fun
because of how similar we are.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
Right.
Didn't Mina Sue's face
look like that a minute ago?
This is funny.
- She's frozen.
- This is fun.
In terms of what's changed
since this Paradise trip,
a fire has been lit in Mina Sue's heart.
- She's much more desperate for Sung-hun.
- Mmm. Yeah.
I think that's what's changed.
It's Mina Sue's turn
to experience heartache.
Oh, that scared me.
- I hate this.
- I wish this would stop.
Today, there is a guys' game
taking place to win a date to Paradise.
- Oh.
- It's a guys' game.
Here we go.
- I'd like to see them fight this time.
- You keep saying that.
I mean, it's true.
I want to see a bit of a brawl,
if I'm being honest with you.
Please gather at the challenge zone.
Here we go.
Let's not get hurt, guys.
- I-geon's a bit scary today.
- He is.
Wow. I think he'll be
up for revenge today.
Come on, let's go.
What are those lines?
- Maybe it's tug of war.
- I wonder who'll win.
- I-geon's got bangs going on.
- He looks good with bangs.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- Something's in the center.
- Could it be long jump?
Today, the guys
will be competing against each other
to win a date to Paradise.
At the end of the game,
the top three guys, in order of placement,
will each get to pick a girl
to take with them to Paradise.
Same as usual.
I will now reveal today's game.
Please open the box by the trench.
What is it?
What's this?
- Ropes?
- They're not balls.
Oh, no way.
- It's tug of war.
- Oh.
Today's game is Trench Tug of War.
Do they pull each other into the water?
The guys will wear harnesses
connected by a rope
and take their places
on opposite ends of the trench,
where they will begin the battle.
Once the signal sounds,
the person who successfully
drags his opponent into the trench
will win the game.
If there is no winner
at the end of the one-minute time limit,
the person who is furthest from the water
will be the one who wins.
The game is structured like a tournament.
Okay, so basically what it means is,
if they move forward,
the person behind them falls in.
That's crazy.
We've had something similar,
but they didn't fall in the water.
- That's true.
- Now, if they lose it, they fall right in.
They'll fall backwards
into the water like this.
- Like splat!
- Wow.
That's the worst thing that could happen
in front of a girl you like.
- You're totally right, that's awful.
- Too cruel.
Given that this is the last
Paradise trip of the season,
- they really need to go all out.
- Need to fight tooth and nail.
Sung-min's got to bring it this time.
He needs to show off his strength.
You know how Go-eun's
calling Sung-min a paper doll?
It'd be nice for him
to finally prove himself
and show everyone
he's stronger than they think.
Go-eun called Sung-min a paper doll?
- Yeah, she calls him a paper doll.
- She did call him that.
That's why it struck a nerve earlier,
and he said, "I can do that too."
"When I work out, I go all out."
That kind of thing.
So this is his chance to prove that.
Oh, you know what?
I want to see a Sung-min versus I-geon
head-to-head here.
Oh, that'd be fun.
Sung-min versus I-geon.
- Come on, Sung-min, I-geon.
- I know, seriously.
The matchups
will be decided by drawing balls.
- Jo I-geon, yellow.
- It's yellow.
These damn balls. Seriously.
- I don't even want to draw one.
- Why?
Lee Sung-hun, blue.
Woo Sung-min, white.
Ah.
It's okay.
They can still battle in the next round.
It's a tournament.
- No one has the same color.
- I know.
- Hmm.
- Youn Hyun-jae, blue.
Sung-hun and Hyun-jae.
BLUE BALL
LEE SUNG-HUN VS YOUN HYUN-JAE
They're friends.
- Lim Su-been, yellow.
- I-geon.
YELLOW BALL
JO I-GEON VS YOUN HYUN-JAE
Kim Jae-jin, white.
WHITE BALL
WOO SUNG-MIN VS KIM JAE-JIN
There's a chance Sung-min will advance.
That's not a bad draw.
- The battle of the paper.
- We all have good matchups.
- "The battle of the paper."
- Let's go, Team Paper.
- Good luck.
- So it's Hyeon-woo versus Seung-il.
Oh wow, so that's going to be
the big match.
Yeah.
Our match should've been the final one.
Song Seung-il, Shin Hyeon-woo, red.
- This is basically the final.
- Yeah, these two are strong.
- They all go at the same time?
- Yeah.
Wow. Really?
Wow. This tension is no joke.
- Seung-il, let's go.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna win.
Just don't get hurt, guys.
No injuries.
If you win this round,
you're pretty much guaranteed to go.
- Yeah, just one more win.
- Yeah.
Who are you rooting for?
Tell me.
Just go for whoever's
trying their hardest.
You got this!
Start when you hear the signal.
Ready.
Three, two, one.
- Oh my god.
- Wow, right from the get-go.
Hold on.
Oh my god!
- Fast and furious I-geon.
- Yeah, that's him.
Wow, I-geon. Oh my gosh.
Oh my gosh.
Look, Su-been's being dragged right now.
Wow.
Hold on.
Look how hard they're straining.
Oh, this is hard. So damn hard.
He can't move forward.
It was really impressive
how hard he was trying.
He was clearly giving it his all,
but it was also tough to watch him
in that much pain, struggling like that.
I couldn't help worrying about him.
And I kept glancing back at him,
hoping he'd be okay.
Thirty seconds remaining.
No!
- He got thrown.
- That's right. He was out to dunk him.
- Song Seung-il is out.
- You okay?
Oh gosh.
Twenty seconds remaining.
- Come on, guys! Whoo!
- Let's go!
What's going on
with Hyun-jae and Sung-hun?
- They're both holding their own.
- Yeah.
I think you need to move forward
a little more.
Just staying still
takes a lot of strength.
- I-geon, no.
- I-geon, don't strain too hard.
- That's it. Keep holding.
- He'll get dragged back.
Wow, Sung-min's incredible too.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six…
- Just a bit more.
- …five, four, three, two, one.
- Oh.
- Who won?
Awesome job. That was great.
I will announce the results.
The winners of this round
are Woo Sung-min, Jo I-geon,
Youn Hyun-jae, and Shin Hyeon-woo.
The four contestants
competing in the semi-finals,
please put on your shoulder harnesses
and stand at the starting line.
Wow, look, apart from Hyun-jae,
they're all going for Go-eun.
- All of them.
- You're… Wow.
I've got goosebumps now. You're so right.
- All three of them.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- Go-eun.
- Really?
- She's right.
I think this is
a Sung-min, I-geon head-to-head.
Please.
There were two other guys
going for the same girl as me,
so I knew I really needed
to come in first place.
It was game on.
I was nervous 'cause
I needed to beat Sung-min and I-geon.
I knew if one of them
ended up winning and taking Go-eun,
all bets were off.
Just the thought of it stressed me out.
I really wanted
to go to Paradise with Go-eun.
Like, this was my one shot.
And just the sight of those two guys
pissed me off,
so I really wanted to beat them.
- His anger makes sense.
- "Pissed me off."
Wow. They really
need to bring it in this round.
Who do you want to go with?
I really can't figure out
my feelings right now.
That's understandable.
And now, for the semi-final matchups.
Oh, this is the important bit.
Shin Hyeon-woo and Youn Hyun-jae.
- Go, guys.
- Hyun-jae, hold your ground.
Go easy, Hyeon-woo.
Jo I-geon and Woo Sung-min
will go head-to-head.
- Just what I wanted. I-geon.
- Wow.
- Yeah, I-geon.
- They need to have it out.
- I-geon's smiling.
- This is the moment he's been waiting for.
His face is saying,
"I'll wipe the floor with you."
Do you think
that one is a match for Go-eun?
Sung-min's stronger than you think he is.
I know. He always makes it to the end.
Oh no, Paper Doll.
I'm sure even one round is exhausting.
Let's go!
- There's pride on the line now.
- They need to dunk each other.
Start when you hear the signal.
Ready.
You look even more on edge than them.
I have faith in you, Hyun-jae.
Three, two, one.
Oh my god, I-geon. I-geon's unbelievable.
- Oh my god!
- Whoa! Is this I-geon?
Oh my god, I-geon. I-geon's unbelievable.
I-geon's unbelievable.
- He really fell in like a paper doll.
- Oh, there was no way around this. I-geon.
- Woo Sung-min is out.
- Ah.
Woo Sung-min is out.
Wow, I-geon's unbelievable.
- Seriously, he's an animal.
- Yeah, I-geon's strong.
Oh my god.
- Hyeon-woo.
- Hyun-jae.
- Look at Hyun-jae.
- What's going on?
- Oh my god.
Oh my god.
Woo Sung-min is out.
- Look at Hyun-jae.
- What's going on?
- Has Hyun-jae won?
- Hyun-jae? Hyun-jae!
- This makes no sense.
- He beat Hyeon-woo?
- Look at Hyun-jae.
- What's going on?
- Oh my gosh!
- Finally.
Hang in there. Just a little longer.
Just a little more.
- Oh no!
- He's lost his footing.
- No!
- Wow.
No, now's the time! Push forward!
Oh, has he made it? Hyeon-woo, no, no!
- He fell.
- Oh my god!
- Hyun-jae, walk. You need to walk too.
- This is his chance to push forward.
- He's flipped.
- What's he doing?
That's it!
- Did he just win?
- Oh no!
Hyeon-woo, no, no!
That's it!
Yeah!
No, please!
Hyeon-woo, no, no!
Hyun-jae, it's the final stretch.
He can do this. He can do it!
- Come on, flip around.
- What's happening?
- Ten, nine, eight, seven…
- Oh no, he might not win this.
…six, five, four, three…
- Oh no.
- Come on. You got this.
Just a little more, just a little more.
- …there, two, one.
- Hang in there. You got this.
Youn Hyun-jae is out.
The winner is Shin Hyeon-woo.
- Wow.
- All the matches were amazing.
- Well played.
- They're really strong.
Wow, they're really good.
It was crazy watching how much effort
they were all putting in
because they knew they needed to win
first place to take me to Paradise.
I was kind of curious how much
I actually meant to each of the guys,
so, yeah, it was interesting to watch them
all battle it out for me in that game.
Players,
we will now proceed to the playoffs.
Woo Sung-min and Youn Hyun-jae
will compete for third and fourth,
while Shin Hyeon-woo and Jo I-geon
will compete
for the first and second place.
Since Go-eun was the only choice
for both me and I-geon,
I knew I couldn't hold back.
This wasn't the time
to play it safe or second-guess myself.
I had to give it everything I had,
no matter what.
I knew that if I lost,
Hyeon-woo would take Go-eun to Paradise,
and just the thought of that made me sick.
That was enough to light a fire in me.
I couldn't let that happen,
no matter what.
"Made me sick."
So the only thought going through
my head was that I had to win.
I've come around
to liking how I-geon speaks.
The way he talks is so cute.
- I've fallen for his charms.
- That's just how he speaks.
Seeing the girl you like walking off
with another guy would make you sick.
Start when you hear the signal.
Ready.
- This is the real one-on-one.
- You're right.
I can't wait to see who wins here.
Wow, I-geon's going to fight to the death.
Oh, this is scary.
Good luck, guys.
Three, two, one.
You know, I-geon--
I didn't think
his legs would be so strong.
- His lower body's solid.
- Yeah.
Oh, that rope is so tight.
- They're holding on.
- Hold it, hold it, hold it.
If I-geon just keeps that up, he'll win.
Yeah, just keep holding.
Thirty seconds remaining.
- I-geon's face is about to explode.
- Is he moving?
- He's the type to put it all on the line.
- Yeah, he really is.
This is bad.
- I-geon's so strong. I think he's got it.
- Yeah.
I-geon really is strong.
Twenty seconds remaining.
His face is about to explode.
Some people just have this grit.
Proving he's the game changer.
Yeah, exactly,
by beating the strongest guy here.
I was thinking,
"Is I-geon really trying this hard
because he feels like he has to win
so he can take me to Paradise
and not lose me to Hyeon-woo?"
It caught me off guard.
Have I actually become
that important to him?
The thought made my heart race.
He's banging his head on the ground.
- If he's doing that for you, date him.
- Seriously.
- Isn't that so hot?
- Six months for this amount of effort.
Six months? Unni.
- He's so desperate.
- Yeah, right?
- No, no. Don't get angry.
- Did he get a second wind?
This guy gets a power boost
when he goes into a rage.
Oh, Hyeon-woo.
Hang in there.
You're winning. Hang in there.
Wow, I-geon's holding out really well.
His stamina is unreal.
Ten, nine, eight…
Hyun-jae's insane.
- Oh wow.
- Hyun-jae's insane.
Let's go, Hyun. Let's go, let's go!
Come on,
hang in there just a little longer.
Lock in with your legs.
Hang in there just a little longer.
- Lock in with your legs.
- …four, three, two…
- …three, two…
- So scary.
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four, three, two, one.
…three, two, one.
Jo I-geon is the winner of the final.
1ST JO I-GEON, 2ND SHIN HYEON-WOO
3RD YOUN HYUN-JAE
- He's full of surprises.
- Wow.
This is cool.
As they say,
"No one stays on top forever."
- Oh, I-geon. I-geon's day.
- Wow.
Wow, I-geon did it.
What if I-geon falls asleep
as soon as he gets to Paradise?
- What?
- He's drained his energy.
He has.
He arrives, eats, has a quick lie-down,
next minute, it's morning.
I know, right? He overexerted himself.
- She'll be like, "Good morning."
- I'm worried about him.
You're so mean. Seriously.
- I'm really worried.
- Wow, he's so mean.
This is the last Paradise trip.
What?
I just get the sense that
Sung-min won't let go of Go-eun
until she's leaving for Paradise.
- Oh, I agree.
- Seriously.
I think he'll stay by her side
from this very moment.
He'll be like,
"Don't change your mind there."
- Ah.
- So funny.
Even just watching them was hard.
- Don't you think?
- I had a really tough time.
I wonder who I-geon has feelings for.
I think it's kind of obvious, isn't it?
It's Go-eun.
He's always trying to talk to her,
and you can tell he wants her attention.
He wouldn't have gone that far otherwise.
His mind was set.
- Especially given that his opponent was…
- Him.
- Hyeon-woo?
- I had no idea he would beat Hyeon-woo.
What are you thinking, Go-eun?
Right now, I like them all equally.
Today's trip is going to be important.
- Hyeon-woo's in a bit of a tough spot now.
- I know. Who will he go with?
I know.
It will fully depend on what I-geon does.
Singles, you are now free
to go and mingle with one another.
What the hell?
- See you guys later.
- This is hard.
Look at Sung-min. He's off to the races.
- Wow.
- You were right.
- I totally called that.
- Yeah.
He won't leave her side until she goes.
What is this?
We can mingle freely.
Ha-eun, where's Go-eun?
- I'm in here.
- Where?
- Come on over.
- Come on, everyone.
- The guys you're looking for are all here.
- Come in.
Hey, could I please speak to Sung-hun?
- Oh, Mina Sue's…
- Everyone's being so proactive.
- I'm so stressed out.
- Are you really?
For the first time since coming here,
I'm really stressed.
- I'm irritated.
- Are you?
- Sung-min will take her far away.
- Yeah.
There. All the way over there.
As far away as he possibly can.
What are you thinking about right now?
I am feeling so uneasy.
- So uneasy.
- Why?
Because anything could happen
while you're there.
Mmm.
I'm honestly dying to know
what's going through your mind right now.
- Me?
- Yeah.
I'm not sure either right now.
- Right now?
- It's difficult right now.
You're so unpredictable.
I can't help it.
You're all such good people,
and you're all so good to me.
I'm just trying to find
the person who's best for me,
- that I click with the most.
- Hmm. You're right.
So you're being dragged away again.
- I'm not leaving yet.
- That's what my gut is telling me.
- You're really uneasy.
- Mmm.
Well, I'm totally sure how I'm feeling.
But I'm worried you might change your mind
or just aren't fully sure
of how you're feeling,
so of course I'm uneasy.
Are you worried?
A bit. Actually, a lot.
You weren't worried to this extent
when I was going with Hyeon-woo.
- You weren't like this.
- No.
Well, I didn't feel this way for you
when you were going with Hyeon-woo.
But I feel anxious this time.
Like, very. Yeah.
I think going with someone twice
is different from going once.
That's true.
Maybe I've been too relaxed.
- You?
- Mmm.
When you're in Paradise,
don't talk too much.
Don't say anything.
Just sit there and listen to him.
- Just listen.
- Mmm.
- I'm kind of curious about Hyeon-woo.
- Yeah.
If he'd come in first, I'm sure
he'd be thinking the same thing I am.
I wonder who he's going
to pick now, though.
It's kind of hard not to be curious.
So Hyeon-woo's really
only interested in Go-eun.
Do you think he's wondering which choice
will inconvenience the others the least?
Or do you think that he's planning
to go with his second choice,
even if it potentially is someone
that he really doesn't have
any interest in at all?
- I don't get the sense that he does.
- You don't think so?
No.
He's devoted to one girl.
INFERNO
Contestants, we will now begin
the Paradise-bound couple matching.
- They're choosing.
- Interested to see what Hyeon-woo does.
Mmm.
Today is going to be interesting.
Let's start with Jo I-geon,
who finished in first.
Please select the person you'd like
to go on a date with in Paradise.
From the very beginning,
my only thought was that
I had to come in first place,
no matter what.
The person I'd like
to go to Paradise with…
is Kim Go-eun.
The girl that Jo I-geon
has selected is Kim Go-eun.
…Kim Go-eun.
- Oh wow.
- Jo I-geon and Kim Go-eun,
- please hold hands and leave for Paradise.
- See you later!
- Bye!
- What are you gonna do?
Go and enjoy yourself.
- Have fun. Bye.
- Have a good trip.
- You're so popular.
- See you tomorrow.
I'm not surprised. I saw them
get ice cream, I-geon and Go-eun.
Mmm.
Oh, I think something big's
gonna happen between them.
Don't you think?
This Paradise trip will seal the deal.
Maybe it was because
my feelings had changed,
but for some reason,
leaving for the second Paradise trip
felt totally different.
The moment I stepped out of the lodge,
I was weirdly nervous.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Right in front of him.
Don't look, don't look.
- Wow, they look like newlyweds.
- Yeah.
- They're both wearing white too.
- Oh yeah.
- My palms are sweaty.
- Why?
- Are you nervous?
- I must be.
Ugh, I'm not really
the type to get nervous.
Really?
Next up is Shin Hyeon-woo in second place.
Who do you think Hyeon-woo will choose?
- I don't know.
- No one knows?
I actually think someone totally new.
Ye-jin, Ha-eun.
Oh, I'm so curious.
Me too. Who will he pick?
The only one here
who isn't connected to anyone is Ye-jin.
Yeah.
Could it be Mina Sue?
I'm so curious.
Shin Hyeon-woo, please select the person
you would like to go
on a date with in Paradise.
The person I want to go
to Paradise with is Kim Go-eun.
But since I-geon won first place
in the tournament,
I had to think really hard about
what other girl I would potentially
want to take to Paradise
if he ended up choosing her.
Shin Hyeon-woo has selected…
I am forfeiting my trip to Paradise.
Huh? Is that allowed?
- Are they--
- Can he do that?
- This is a first.
- Yeah, it's the first time.
Shin Hyeon-woo has selected…
no one.
What?
Shin Hyeon-woo
has forfeited his right to choose.
- …no one.
- Wow.
What the f***?
I didn't realize
we were allowed to not choose.
I had no idea that was an option.
I ended up making the decision
to forfeit my trip to Paradise today.
It wasn't a hard decision.
Aside from Go-eun, there were
no other girls that interested me.
I had no second or third choice
and didn't want to go as friends.
So I decided not to go.
Aw. There's no Go-eun
even if he stays, though.
- Exactly.
- Seriously.
- When Go-eun finds out…
- He must have his heart set on her.
My arm hairs are standing on end,
every one of them.
Wow. This is just so crazy.
- I have so much respect for Hyeon-woo.
- Yeah, a lot of respect.
- I have to hand it to him for this.
- For real. What a plot twist.
He's totally head over heels for Go-eun.
Damn.
Lastly, Youn Hyun-jae in third place.
Please select the person
that you would like to go
on a date with in Paradise today.
The person I'd like
to go to Paradise with…
is Lee Joo-young.
- Of course.
- Yeah.
Last-ditch effort.
- He's giving it his best shot.
- Yeah.
Lee Joo-young.
Youn Hyun-jae and Lee Joo-young,
please hold hands and leave for Paradise.
- See you later.
- Have fun.
Lee Joo-young.
Hello.
I'm sorry about the rain.
It's too bad.
- Ugh. Why did it have to rain?
- How-- I know.
It's raining.
Why did it have to rain when I won?
Today's Paradise-bound
couple matching is now officially over.
I can't believe he forfeited.
We've never had that.
Hyeon-woo forfeited his choice.
- Hyeon-woo.
- Apparently he decided not to take anyone.
He's not coming.
- Ah.
- Is that allowed?
It's 'cause of you.
I was really surprised to hear
that Hyeon-woo forfeited his choice
even though that was totally
something he would do.
It completely caught me off guard.
I didn't see it coming at all,
but it really got me.
I'm so touched by it.
Oh, Hyeon-woo, that was so admirable.
Not at all.
It wasn't admirable. I'm bitter right now.
I'm just so bitter.
Look at her. Her mind is elsewhere.
With his experience,
I-geon will navigate this successfully.
He'll navigate it well
until he reaches success.
PARADISE
JO I-GEON & KIM GO-EUN
Do you mind if we rest for a bit?
Sure.
Oh, wait. That's what I need to do.
There's something I need your help with.
- What?
- I need to get something out of my nail.
Oh. Is it sand?
Yeah, but I…
I can't really tell
if it's sand or dried blood.
- See it?
- Mmm.
- Does it hurt?
Is this… Is it sand, do you think?
- Yeah.
- Just try to take it all out in one go.
- Wait. Hold on a second.
- You were about to push it in.
How do I…
Why do I have to do this?
Hold on. I have tweezers. Wait here.
Tell me if it hurts.
- So, is it sand?
- Mmm.
What's this black thing, though?
Hold on. Let me poke it first
to see if I feel anything.
It hurts too much to take out.
I guess I'll just leave it.
- All right, good.
- Good?
What's good about it?
- So if you hadn't won…
- Yeah?
…and I came to Paradise with someone else,
who would you have come with?
I really don't know
because there's literally no one.
Maybe just Ha-eun?
But Ha-eun likes Jae-jin, so…
Oh, this is what I was going to say.
Because we were in a position
where we could find out about each other,
even though I was denying it to myself,
I think I was still kind of wondering
how much you actually knew about me.
Like, what you'd picked up on
and what kind of person you thought I was.
- Seriously.
- Yeah.
I thought it was a shame that
we hadn't gotten time together.
- I agree.
- I think that's actually what was…
That's partly what was
holding me back at first.
- Me too.
- Mmm.
That's what got me confused
about my feelings for you at first,
because, like,
I just couldn't work you out
- and didn't know what you thought of me.
- Mmm, exactly.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah, I do.
After our first conversation,
you know, when we thought
we might have a mutual acquaintance,
after that conversation,
I thought to myself,
"Maybe I should have told him
that we should disregard all that
and just start from scratch."
You were really impressive
in the game today.
- I'm now the strongest guy.
- Yeah, you are.
- I'm the new strongman here.
- Exactly. The strongman, Jo I-geon.
Did you root for me?
- No, I didn't. Not at all.
- Why not?
Because at the time, you wouldn't have
chosen me to go to Paradise with.
I knew it, so…
- What?
- I was praying for you to lose.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
See this, the scratch?
Did you get it during the game?
Yeah, I got scratched
by that cat, Hee-sun. Mmm.
Hee-sun was really impressive.
Oh, and I wasn't?
Uh, maybe a little.
Am I not impressive?
Hee-sun was just too dominant
in that game.
Her facial expression and everything
was so cool.
- Mmm. Hmm.
- Seriously.
Then why didn't you talk to Hee-sun?
- I wanted to.
- What's wrong with you?
Seriously, what's wrong with you?
Ugh, minus 50 points.
For real.
I'm leaving.
Hey, look who's talking.
- I can't believe this.
- I'm out of here.
You're one to talk.
- I'm leaving. You can have dinner alone.
- Seriously.
Even today, you were out walking.
You're unbelievable.
I'm busy. I'm a busy girl.
You need to ask me on dates
well in advance.
I couldn't believe it when I saw you
out walking today. Seriously.
Get some sleep.
- I would like to sleep. That sounds nice.
- Why aren't you sleeping? Jeez.
Tomorrow, I'll go out walking with you.
No, I'm gonna sleep.
Let's do a lap here.
- A lap around the pool.
- Seriously?
- First thing in the morning.
- Okay.
"Okay?" Really?
Are you messing with me?
- Jesus Christ.
- What's with the "okay"?
We can't do that. It's too early.
Are you the jealous type?
- Yeah. Totally.
- Mmm.
Totally?
When I like someone a lot,
I find it hard to control myself.
- Mmm.
- It kind of scares me, actually.
'Cause if I can't control my emotions,
it's hard to control
my actions or my life.
- Sounds like you fall really hard.
- Yeah.
I'm kind of a hopeless romantic.
And you, do you get jealous?
Yeah, a lot.
- A lot?
- Mmm.
- You don't look like the jealous type.
- I know, right?
- I get that a lot.
- I can see that.
Is it starting to rain a lot out there?
Yeah, it's really
starting to come down now.
Can you open that curtain a bit more?
What? It's already open all the way.
- Oh, I--
- How am I supposed to open it even more?
Oh, he's right, he's right.
- Oh, I--
- How am I supposed to open it even more?
I just wanted to see
more of the rain falling into the pool.
I didn't think you'd actually do it.
- Like this?
- Yeah.
Oh. That's perfect.
- It was already open.
- I know.
I like the way he responded, though.
He still went and did whatever he could.
- You're right.
- Even though he was complaining. Yeah.
This is too funny.
- Can you see the rain from where you are?
- Yeah.
Mmm.
- I feel so content right now.
- Yeah.
I don't think
I'll ever forget this moment.
- I-geon's definitely charming.
- For sure.
He doesn't entirely go
in the direction that you want him to,
but at the same time,
he's got so much going for him.
He's serious, he's playful.
- That kind of personality is so appealing.
- This is a matter of chemistry.
Go-eun and Sung-min are like friends
while she and I-geon feel like a couple.
I've noticed we always
lean towards I-geon, though.
I feel like Go-eun likes Sung-min,
but we panelists keep trying
to push her toward I-geon.
Seriously, you really think so?
- Are we the ones who like I-geon?
- Look, honestly speaking,
Go-eun acts completely different
towards I-geon and Sung-min.
I personally think
it's really obvious, you know.
Her energy is noticeably different
depending on who she's spending time with.
Even when, like, I-geon jokes around
with her, Go-eun takes it really well.
So, yeah, they're so fun to watch,
and they totally seem like
a couple already to me.
Who did you come here with last time?
- Let's just stick to pleasant topics.
- No, I'm just curious.
- It was with Sung-min.
- Oh, that asshole?
- It's fine, he's older.
- My gosh, that's so hot.
At first, I was a bit iffy about this,
but this is just the way he speaks.
- It's grown on me by now.
- Yeah, it's so refreshing.
It is refreshing.
- Is it cold?
- No, it's fine.
It is a bit cold, actually.
The water looks pretty clear, though.
Can you swim?
- I learned to swim in elementary school.
- Oh.
When I went in the water,
my body just knew what to do.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I'm not a good swimmer.
- Do you know how?
- This is about as much as I can do.
I'm not very good.
- Shall I teach you?
- Okay.
You'll get it in no time.
Give me your hands.
Lift your legs.
- My legs--
- Tense your arms.
Wait. Stand up.
- Really? I'm supposed to tense my arms?
- That's what you have to do at first.
No.
Is this right?
- I--
- Can't you put some more muscle into it?
Your body has to be
a straight line, like this.
You're not so great either.
My muscles aren't strong enough.
And my legs won't float.
This is funny.
Do you usually care about height in girls?
- Height?
- Yeah.
- Mmm-mmm. More so proportions.
- Oh.
But doesn't that usually mean
you care about height?
No, I don't really care
about height at all.
Petite girls are kind of like fairies.
- Mmm.
- And tall girls are like goddesses.
Oh. Mmm.
When it comes to guys, though,
short guys are jerks,
and tall guys are bigger jerks.
All jerks, except me.
- Especially Hyeon-woo and Sung-min.
- Why?
Are you jealous?
- Hmm?
- Are you jealous of them?
- Do they bother you?
- Mmm.
Mmm.
In the game today,
I won because I knew I wouldn't
be able to stand the sight of you
leaving for Paradise with someone else.
I think that was the biggest factor.
- Lucky I came with you then.
- Yeah.
You're good-looking.
You're pretty.
Did I embarrass you?
I was just struck by it again.
My left side's prettier.
Only look at that side.
- So every time I move back and forth--
- Yeah, I'll keep turning for you.
Both sides look the same.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Wow.
That right there,
that's the kind of guy Go-eun likes.
The way he looks at her is so sweet.
- He looks ready to pounce.
- What?
- He's ready to pounce, yeah.
- "To pounce…"
Mmm.
You know, your face is cute too.
Is it?
- Sometimes you're cute.
- When am I cute?
Come on, tell me. I want specifics.
Uh…
So frustrating.
It seems like you don't actually
get jealous that often, oppa.
It's only once in a while,
when I talk to Sung-min.
Right. Mmm.
I usually…
try my best not to show that I'm jealous.
But for some reason,
you and Sung-min walking this morning
bugged me so damn much.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- It did.
- I didn't know you'd be working out.
You didn't even say hi to me.
Didn't I?
This thing is… It's really hot.
- What is?
- Your scratch here.
You must have cats around too.
Sung-min?
What are you thinking?
Should I go to you or not?
What?
What are you thinking?
Will you come to me or not?
You come to me.
I'll go around.
Do you think
the age gap between us is big?
What?
Do you feel like
the age gap between us is really big?
I don't know.
But if…
we can't feel it, then does it matter?
No.
This is nice.
Hmm?
What?
Why are you smiling?
- I-- I like you.
- Mmm.
I think I like you.
There's no heavy physical contact,
but they're so sexy together.
Mmm, mmm.
Personally, I think this was the best
pool scene of the entire season.
- These two just now.
- Yeah.
The-- The whole
"Should I go" thingamajig--
What? "Should I go thingamajig?"
How could you be so--
- "Should I go to you or not?"
- I couldn't imitate.
And the pose, the pose.
He was like that.
Leaning back like this, going,
"Will you come to me or not?"
- Wow.
- From opposite sides.
He looked like a male deity.
It was like some kind of standoff
between a god and a goddess.
- I've always taken…
- Mmm.
…the long way.
Go-eun's feelings
have shifted toward him a lot.
Yeah, it's kind of like she feels that
I-geon is a little too rough
around the edges for her,
but she can't help being drawn to him.
With the others,
she feels relaxed and at ease.
They make her laugh and say sweet things.
But with I-geon,
there's this underlying tension
whenever they're together.
It's complicated.
And I think that's why
she's intrigued by him.
- Yeah, there's tension. Right.
- That's why I enjoy watching.
Enjoying yourself, huh?
No, I mean,
watching them together makes you go,
- "Aw."
- "I like you."
- Want to take a picture?
- Okay.
Hold on a sec.
You're wiggling your eyebrows.
I did exactly what you did.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Oh, jeez.
I'm taking that one with me.
I think this one's actually
gonna be really funny.
I can't wait to see it.
Wait.
Is this
what my facial expression is usually like?
No.
- Is this what I look like?
- Not at all.
I look like a fool.
This is nice.
So, what age do you want to get married?
28, 29?
Huh? That's not far off.
No.
- Isn't that two or three years from now?
- Mmm.
I'm not confident
I can get rich within that time.
Wow.
He's moving fast.
I'm not confident
I can get rich within that time.
- I could earn--
- I need about five years.
Well, I can earn money.
- You don't have to be rich.
- That's good.
- So, do you like what-ifs?
- Hmm?
- Sure. Try me.
- Well, if you and I got together,
what do you think
we'd argue about the most?
Oh, I think we'll have arguments
now and then over the way you talk.
- Yeah, we'll argue about that too.
- Yeah.
- But…
- But I think I'd fix it right away.
- Mmm.
- Once you told me.
- This convo is so delicious.
- Yeah.
These two have already moved on
to talking about next-level stuff.
- Yeah.
- This is like one last test
before they allow themselves
to get together.
- Right?
- I think so.
I kind of…
get angry easily,
but then I also forget easily.
Yeah.
What?
Do I sound dumb?
No, no.
This time, I was thinking you were cute.
You're not dumb.
If you ever did something
to make me angry,
mmm… I'd just keep it to myself
until the following day.
Then I'd probably forget about it.
- Are you talking about when we're dating?
- Yeah.
- If we were to start dating?
- Yeah, as long as…
As long as it wasn't something serious.
If we were in a relationship
and you did something to make me angry…
hug me, and I'd be over it.
- Really?
- Mmm.
- I'm easy.
Keep this to yourself.
I think they slept in the same bed.
- Hmm?
- Yeah.
NEXT EPISODE
Oh, Seung-il.
You're the jewel of CMU, I'm telling you.
What did you talk about with Hee-sun
while you were in Paradise?
I really want to be
totally honest with you.
- She's keeping her options open.
- I've got goosebumps.
Why didn't you choose anyone yesterday?
I'm not interested in anyone but you.
I won't change.
My feelings are going to stay
exactly as they are now.
No matter what.
Watching you talk with another guy
made me realize
I shouldn't give them any kind of opening.
I think I need
a greater show of affection.
Contestants,
we will now begin the final decision.
The person I'd like to leave Inferno with…
What?
I can't believe
none of us saw this coming.
I know. This is the first time
we all got it wrong.