YOUN HYUN-JAE
SONG SEUNG-IL
PARK HEE-SUN
SHIN HYEON-WOO
KIM GO-EUN
KIM JAE-JIN
HAM YE-JIN
WOO SUNG-MIN
KIM MIN-GEE
LIM SU-BEEN
LEE SUNG-HUN
LEE JOO-YOUNG
CHOI MINA SUE
SINGLE'S INFERNO
The person I'd like to go
to Paradise with is…
Choi Mina Sue has matched with…
Lim Su-been.
Lim Su-been,
please step outside your lodging.
You were right.
- The game had a huge impact.
- It did.
He enticed her with his muscles.
Lim Su-been.
Lim Su-been,
please step outside your lodging.
Lim Su-been.
Lim Su-been,
please step outside your lodging.
Have a great time.
- Have a good one.
- See you.
Hee-sun lost her smile.
Hello.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
- Let me help you with one.
- Then can you help me with this one?
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Thank you.
This is surreal.
- I'm getting excited.
- Right?
This isn't easy. This place isn't easy.
I'm losing my mind.
I'm interested in Min-gee right now.
We were told to converse freely,
but our conversation got cut off
while we were still talking.
So it felt like I only watched the preview
of a film I'd been waiting for.
She had an easygoing personality,
and that caught my attention from day one.
And today, we somehow ended up
chatting for a long time.
During our conversation,
I realized we might have
compatible personalities.
That's when I became
even more interested in Min-gee.
The person I'd like to go
to Paradise with is…
It's probably Seung-il, right?
She hasn't had a chance
to chat with Hyeon-woo.
Kim Min-gee has matched with…
Song Seung-il.
- I'll get going.
- Song Seung-il.
Please step outside your lodging.
I knew it.
It must be disappointing for Hyeon-woo.
Here we go.
You have so much stuff.
Do you need help with that?
- Need a hand?
- Maybe just this one?
- What's heavier?
- This one? I don't know.
- Give me this.
- This?
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- My heart almost dropped.
- Were you worried I wouldn't call you?
- Yes.
- I guess I had my hopes up.
- I see.
Aren't you leaving too often, Min-gee?
This is only my second time.
What do you mean?
And why are you speaking casually?
- Ms. Min-gee?
- Good.
- They're hitting it off.
- Yes.
Their conversations are playful.
They have a similar vibe.
Today's Paradise-bound
couple matching is over.
- I'm the only one who never left.
- Stop it. You'll be going nonstop soon.
I seriously want to go home.
Not me.
- I'm going to see this through.
- Really?
- What about you?
- Me too.
Until the day I go to Paradise
with Joo-young.
You two are such manly guys.
- I'll follow through.
- I can't stand losing.
His competitive spirit is kicking in.
- In any case, four couples have left.
- Yes.
The couple we're looking forward to
the most is probably Mina Sue and Su-been.
- I'm curious.
- It's Mina Sue and Su-been.
- Mina Sue-been.
I feel like they'll make my heart flutter.
- Right? I bet.
- Yes, totally.
- We'll get our dose of dopamine.
- I'm excited.
I'm excited for Seung-il and Min-gee, too.
- Those two.
- Right?
They seem fun.
It seems like they'll have a good banter
back and forth.
- Their personalities seem to click.
- Yes.
- I look forward to it.
PARADISE
KIM MIN-GEE & SONG SEUNG-IL
Let's go.
I got it. I really got it.
- It heavy, isn't it?
- My gosh.
- This place is nice.
- It really is.
- Where's the room?
- Right here. It's this way.
Let's see the room.
I'm at a loss for words.
This is the room.
This place is huge.
I can't get used to it.
Here, Min-gee. These are your stuff.
I want to look over there.
Sure.
- I guess that's the only bedroom. Oops.
- It is.
You could've asked.
You said you weren't in this room.
- They're the same with a few differences.
- I see.
- Really?
- Yes, they all look similar.
The bathroom is as big as my room.
I mean it.
He looks fascinated.
Of course, he is.
He's just like me.
Can I change into comfy clothes?
Seung-il?
- He's checking the water pressure.
- And looking around.
Man, this place is insane.
It's so nice.
Where do you keep going?
- I'm just looking around.
- Okay.
It's so nice.
- Come here.
- Is it that nice?
- Did you see the pool outside?
- Yes.
- I've seen it.
- Right.
- How cute.
- He's so endearing.
That place looks really nice.
I completely understand how he feels.
- What if you catch a cold?
- The water's warm.
- Both?
- I mean, they both seem warm.
Look at the steam.
- You're right. It's warm.
- Yes.
- But this is so nice.
- Isn't it?
Seeing this is making me feel emotional.
I'm serious.
- Really?
- Yes.
They'll have lots of fun joking around.
- But I think Min-gee…
- Yes?
- I think she's getting too laid-back.
- Right.
It's a shame
that her charm is slowly fading.
I know even today,
she'll come across
as almost too laid-back in that room.
- I'm a bit worried about that.
- But some people are into that.
Aren't you also into people like that?
- Yes, I like to joke around.
- Like friends.
I still think romance can blossom.
- Have a seat.
- What?
Let's talk.
We began to talk casually,
almost too naturally.
I assumed that you'd be
much more comfortable that way.
- True.
- Yeah.
- That's what you mean.
- Like that.
- Like this.
- Hold on.
Look at her pose.
"Let's talk."
Why is she like that?
But, Jin-kyung,
I'm sure some people are into that.
Don't you prefer this to being fake?
- Isn't this too much?
- Sitting like that is beyond easygoing.
- "Let's talk" is a bit…
- It's a bit…
- It could've gone better.
- "I said, let's talk."
I assumed that you'd be
much more comfortable that way.
- True.
- Yeah.
You're different from what I thought.
- How?
- When you first walked in,
- you seemed aloof and not very talkative.
- I know, right?
- Yes.
- Everyone says so.
- You looked a bit cold.
- Yes.
But the moment you sat next to me,
I could tell what you were like.
- I didn't even say much.
- No.
But you're very different
from how you look, too.
You have a great personality.
- You're--
- How do I come across?
- Like a bad boy.
- I look like a bad boy?
But you're the total opposite.
You're quite gentle, unlike how you look.
- I am?
- Yes.
Really?
But I'm aiming for an image with a calm
- and serious vibe.
- Sure.
- Someone who's--
- Not even close.
I think that unexpected difference
makes you more attractive.
- Really?
- Yes.
I guess today is the first time we talked.
Yes, so this is all new.
I'm intrigued by you.
How did I seem on the first day?
- Did I seem gentle back then?
- No.
Like you said, you gave off a strong aura.
- Did I look serious?
- Not exactly, but…
That's why only my forearms are tanned.
- It was intended.
- Was it to give off that aura?
Because I sat like this.
You try to talk like a tough guy,
but your words are really sweet.
I think this is it.
- You are the main character.
- I am?
- You came in last.
- Is that so?
- Is there a type you particularly dislike?
- People who wear masks.
Is that why you chose me?
Yes, I really like people
who are easygoing and not pretentious.
People who aren't two-faced.
- Yes.
- Yes, they're the kind of people I like.
- What's your ideal type?
- Someone that I'm drawn to.
I need that jolt of attraction.
- That feeling?
- Yes, someone I keep glancing at.
Or it could be someone who intrigues me.
- Well, someone like you.
- Why are you flirting with me?
Should I keep quiet?
Someone like you.
So I need to get that feeling first.
Only then will I want
to get to know who you are.
I like your sense of humor.
- Humor?
- Yes.
You say random things out of the blue.
- Like earlier.
- "Get out."
- You told me to jump.
- "Jump off."
Do you want to jump off?
- Hey, what was that?
- What was that?
That's so childish yet funny.
That's how they grow on each other.
That's what we used to do as kids.
Those are the things I find funny.
- That's how I hang out.
- I like that.
- Yes, me too.
- That's how I have fun.
Just like friends.
- They both find it fun.
- Yes.
- That's great news.
- It is.
- They're a good match.
- Yes.
- Let's eat.
- Sure.
- Time to eat!
- I'm so happy.
- Welcome.
- It's Korean food.
This is Paradise.
I'm so happy right now.
- Let's eat first.
- Yes.
You must be starving.
My gosh. I'm dying
to know how old you are.
- My age?
- Yes.
- I have a feeling you're younger than me.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- Really?
You're probably younger.
Do you prefer someone older, younger,
or around your age?
I think age is just a number,
but I prefer someone older.
A person's maturity
is very appealing to me.
I like older guys, too.
- What now?
- I like older guys.
Actually, I like people
who are on the cuter side.
- Not someone who acts cute.
- Cute guys?
There are times
when people suddenly seem cute.
- You mean the person?
- Yes.
Just like how you just said, "The person?"
When you see that cuteness
in someone older, it's really cute.
Younger guys are cute by default.
- When they have an unexpected charm?
- Yes.
I think people are really cute
when they have an unexpected charm.
- I see, like a twist.
- Yes.
It's hard for me to tell how old you are.
I want to take a guess.
Want to guess my age?
You seem like you were
born in 1998.
- In 1998?
- Yes.
I thought the same for you.
I'm 30 years old.
- You're 30?
- Yes.
I was born in 1996.
- In 1996?
- Yes.
- Did you say 1998 for me?
- Is he?
- He's maybe 26?
I'd say he was born in 1997 or 1998.
- Did you say 1998 for me?
- Yes.
- Why are you so happy?
- I'm happy to hear that.
I was born in 2001.
- Oh, my gosh!
- No way!
Hearing it now, I can see it.
- I knew he'd be young.
- He looks so young.
- He's a baby!
- Is he 26, then?
Look, he looks like a high school kid.
Exactly.
He's way too young.
Is he five years younger?
I was born in 2001.
- Really? You're that young?
- Yes.
Born in 2001?
- I was born in 2001.
- Are you serious?
My gosh.
- No way. Were you really born in 2001?
- Yes.
You're really mature for your age.
That's wild.
- Should I talk politely again?
- Yes, how dare you?
You're five years younger.
No, speak casually.
That way, I'll seem younger.
I knew you wouldn't get it right.
It is a bit of a shock. It's wild.
- You said you like older guys.
- Yes, but I also like cute guys.
I like someone who's mature.
Younger guys aren't too bad.
You're good.
Yes, this is what I'm talking about.
What do you do?
- For a living?
- Yes.
I work at a fashion marketing company.
- I'm a marketer.
- It suits you.
I currently work as a marketer
at a fashion marketing company.
I'm in charge of advertising expenses,
meeting with advertisers,
providing brand consultations,
and handling everything the client needs
to grow their business with us.
SONG SEUNG-IL,
BORN IN 2001, FASHION MARKETER
- How cool.
- Are you curious?
Born in 2001?
- What?
- I still can't get over your age.
I'm still trying to process your age.
- But I've been working since I was 20.
- I see.
I began work right away.
- You're next, Ms. Min-gee.
- Yes?
So, what do you do?
I'm a track-and-field athlete.
It's like…
- What's your specialty?
- It's 400 m for me.
- You run 400 m?
- Yes.
We can't go running together.
No, I run longer distances
at a slower pace. I find it hard, too.
- Where do you live now?
- I live in Hwaseong now.
- Gyeonggi Province?
- I'm on a team with Hwaseong City Hall.
I know my way around Hwaseong.
This is what I find cute.
Yes, that was cute.
- That was just so cute.
- How cute!
So very cute.
- "I know my way around."
- "I know my way."
I see. That's what they mean.
- I still don't get it.
- I didn't know, either.
- How cute.
- It's things like this.
That was so cute,
like a child pretending to be an adult.
- He's just a kid, though.
- I see.
This is what I find cute.
Yes, that was cute.
No, I'm so serious right now.
No, you were so cute just now,
like someone born in 2001.
- Why aren't you eating?
- Me?
Did you know you lose your appetite
when you're sleep deprived?
Do you want me to feed you?
- You said you couldn't eat.
- No, I can eat.
But if you feed me, I won't say no.
This is nice.
You're so annoying.
- I do feel happy here.
- Right?
Today feels like
my very first time in Paradise.
- That's how I feel.
- Why?
I thought
I'd naturally have these feelings,
and I expected that yesterday,
but I didn't feel anything.
I was so worried on my way here.
- About what?
- If that continued…
I was afraid I might go back home
without feeling anything.
But I'm definitely
feeling something today.
I'll make you feel it today.
"I'll make you feel it today"!
- He just gave me chills.
- He's the real deal.
He's full of vigor.
- That was sheer vigor.
- It was.
He's on a roll now. He's on the rise.
- He's on fire.
- I got chills.
I'll make you feel it today.
- I thought you liked older guys.
- Can you talk louder?
- I feel too shy to talk louder.
- Right?
You keep mumbling,
but I have excellent hearing.
I noticed.
I didn't think you'd hear me, but you did.
My hearing is still good.
You're only 30.
- Only 30?
- Yes, you're young.
Well, it's funny coming from me.
Seriously.
I love how they're interacting.
- I love this.
- That was the best line so far.
- "I'll make you feel it."
- "I'll make you feel it today."
The best pick-up line.
Is this what younger guys are like?
PARADISE
KIM GO-EUN & WOO SUNG-MIN
It looks good.
They look amazing.
- You should try some first.
- Should I?
Oh no.
Shouldn't you eat first?
Try the soup first.
You shouldn't drink on an empty stomach.
Isn't it good?
It surprised me when I first tried it.
I can eat it from here.
- Doesn't it taste better today?
- It does.
It's good.
- How is it? Is it good?
- Try it. Yes.
So how old are you?
- Do I just say it now?
- Yes.
Take a guess.
How cliché.
I really didn't want to say it,
but I couldn't help it.
I'd guess you were born in 1997 or 1998.
Are you stunned?
- I was born in 2000.
- Really?
I was born in 1996.
Really?
We're not that far apart.
What do you do?
You said you'd guess.
Something that has…
to do with computers?
- Not at all?
- No.
- A lyricist?
- Nope.
- I'm an optician.
- What? Really?
- I make and sell glasses.
- Wow.
That's amazing.
What do you do, Go-eun?
- I'm a model.
- You are?
I work as a model.
I currently model
for beauty and fashion brands.
KIM GO-EUN
BORN IN 2000, MODEL
- You can speak casually.
- Sure.
- Let's both do that.
- Okay.
What was your first impression of me?
I'm curious.
I told you I called you
a taller version of the Little Prince.
So everyone remembers you
as the Little Prince.
So…
Yes, it's my fault.
But I think your shorts
made you look even younger.
Even younger.
- Only I was in shorts.
- Yes.
But it was nice.
- It was? It was embarrassing.
- It suited you.
You know, being tall
when you look like this is…
- Is it odd?
- It's odd.
- Do I not look tall?
- You don't look tall.
So…
Yeah…
How tall are you?
- I'm 168 cm.
- You are? You're tall.
- Everyone's tall.
- Everyone is.
- How tall are you?
- I'm 186 cm.
I thought I'd be the tallest,
but some are taller.
- Who? Hyun-jae?
- Yeah.
- Hyun-jae and--
- We talked yesterday.
How did it go?
It was just…
Never mind.
What's it like talking to me?
It's fun.
- It is?
- Yes.
I'm a really boring guy.
You're fun.
- I'm not a lot of fun, either.
- We both seem to think that way.
We both seem
to think of ourselves as boring.
Only people similar to me
tend to find me fun.
What matters is
being on the same wavelength.
- Yes.
- I'm glad.
Before the game began,
all I had on my mind was,
"What am I going to do?"
Was it after the game when you decided
you wanted to talk to me?
Actually, I wanted to talk to you
even on the first day.
That was why I wanted to change my pick
on first impressions.
- Was that why?
- Yes.
Are you not curious about the two guys
you picked yesterday?
I don't think
I need to get to know them any further.
I kept thinking,
"I wrote down the wrong name."
- "I want to change my decision."
- Why?
I kept thinking,
"I made the wrong choice."
One thing's for sure.
It feels different from yesterday.
- Really?
- Yes, it feels quite different.
- I don't know what it was like yesterday.
- No, but I do. I know.
It feels different.
Do you drink often?
Not this often.
I actually decided to get drunk
only four times a year.
Today might be the day.
That sounds great.
I love that.
You won't be sleeping tonight either.
I don't think I can
with this dopamine rush.
Where do you live?
- I--
- I live near Konkuk University.
Really? I'm nearby.
- I live in Seongdong-gu.
- Really?
- Do you live alone?
- No, I live with my family.
How many siblings do you have?
- I have an older sister.
- You do?
I have an older sister
and a younger sister.
Our family is kind of unique.
My younger sister and I
are 18 years apart.
- A late-born child?
- Totally.
She must be adorable.
I think your daughter
will be really pretty.
I really want a daughter.
I've never seen you so passionate.
I really want to have a daughter.
My family has
a strong streak of daughters.
We're all girls.
The thing is, I love children.
That's why I honestly thought
I'd get married very early in life.
You know, while I was in my 20s.
Find a girl in her 20s.
- You're in your 20s.
- Yes, I am.
I'll leave it at that.
Don't they seem
like they're getting along well?
- They do.
- Right?
More than anything,
I think Sung-min is smitten.
He looks completely different today
from how he was in Paradise yesterday.
He's so intrigued and smitten by her.
I can tell how badly
he wants to get to know her.
They both seem to be
attracted to each other.
Yes, definitely. That's for sure.
- Do you like it?
- It smells like a pool.
- This place is just for us.
- Really? No way!
Look at that.
- Man.
- This is amazing.
Seung-il would've cried if he came here.
- Totally.
- Without a doubt.
Do you want to swim?
I just want to float like this.
Go ahead. I can hold you.
Shouldn't you put your face inside?
- No, I'm just going to float.
- No?
I'm just floating.
- You're--
- This is too hard.
Next time, I'll get wine…
We should've ordered wine then.
- We don't know who it'll be with.
- Yes, right. That's true.
Feelings can change.
When we held hands in the pool,
it felt nice.
This is really embarrassing.
Come here.
How do I turn on the flash?
It just goes off automatically,
so we have to take it like this.
No, I want to take a photo of us
in the mirror.
I like taking mirror selfies.
- Can you see?
- Yes.
- There will be dots.
- Why?
- Because of the flash?
- Yes.
Have you done this before?
Yesterday.
I did it yesterday.
Then, I wouldn't have taken one.
- Well, you wanted to try it.
- I've always wanted to try it.
I did something like this.
Yesterday? I don't really want to know.
- You should be curious.
- I'm not. I don't want to know.
- Only answer the questions I ask.
- Okay.
- How do you feel after the swim?
- It's nice.
- How do you feel?
The thing about today was that
I kept wondering
if what I was doing was right.
I thought I might be able
to make up my mind if I came here.
So it was really nice
to get a chance to talk to you.
- I think so, too.
- Right.
That's why I also understand
your ever-changing feelings.
Try everything out while you're here.
- You too.
- I will, if I get the chance.
But I have a feeling…
I'll stay the same.
I'll probably stay like this.
How can you be so sure?
Because I know me.
I just do.
There won't be any change.
Am I drunk?
About this much.
This much?
Just a little.
No, not this much.
- This much.
- Just a bit.
It's that much?
This much.
- Today is the day she gets drunk.
- It is.
Go-eun must feel relaxed
after having a drink.
I think that was her being herself.
Being sweet and cute.
I wish Sung-min would
show his feelings more openly
if he's really into Go-eun.
But he hasn't expressed much.
- It feels like he's shy and is nervous.
- Yes.
Maybe because he likes her so much.
I don't think he's the type
to take the lead in a relationship.
- No.
- I want to see his move.
It's a shame we didn't see that.
This is nice.
PARADISE
LEE JOO-YOUNG & KIM JAE-JIN
- Do you want to sit?
- Sure.
When we wrote down the names earlier,
- was it hard to decide?
- No.
- It wasn't?
- But it was hard for you, right?
- No, it wasn't for me either.
- No?
- No.
- But--
- I told you, didn't I?
I said that I decided right away.
Even though today was the first time
we actually interacted,
playing a game together
helped me bond with you.
So I wanted to talk to you,
but I wasn't able to.
We'll have another chance
to have some coffee.
Come in.
- Excuse me.
- Hello.
- Can we talk?
- Sure.
- See you.
- Okay, see you.
That was
quite a bummer.
I'm glad we both chose each other
for our first trip to Paradise.
We really clicked.
What's your ideal type?
Tell me your ideal type.
My ideal type?
I'm not sure what that means.
- What do you mean?
- This is what I tell people.
I say I like someone who is sexy,
but I don't mean someone with crazy curves
or anything like that.
No, but more like their aura?
Simply put, I like people
who seem sexy to me.
I see.
I don't want to limit
my ideal type with words.
That's why it's a bit difficult for me
to talk about my ideal type.
We usually talk about the kind of vibe
we're looking for in a person.
I guess I'm the one at fault.
- Shall we try again?
- Here's my ideal type.
I like someone smaller
and slimmer rather than chubby.
- I like someone who is slim.
- Someone slim.
Someone with big eyes
instead of very small ones,
and with double eyelids rather than none.
I swear I'm not describing you.
- Someone who can be sexy, then cute.
- "Sexy, then cute"?
That's just how I put it.
When it comes to looks,
I prefer someone with a good vibe
rather than someone
who's stunningly good-looking.
- A good vibe?
- Someone with a nice aura.
That's when I start wanting
to get to know them.
It's a bit hard to explain.
- I think they're into each other.
- Right.
- They seem to be lovey-dovey.
- You're right.
That looks good.
Do you want some?
- What is it?
- Tofu.
Tofu is…
made with soybeans, right?
Yes.
Soybeans.
- They have lecithin.
- What? How do you know that?
I don't know. I just do.
- I enjoy reading nutritional information.
- You do?
- That's new.
- I thought everyone was like me.
- No, not everyone.
- Right? I realized it much later.
You cracked me up earlier
talking about sweet potatoes.
The corn talk.
- That was funny? All right!
- Yes, it was so silly that it was funny.
I have a hundred of those.
I can do it with everything here.
But I'm happy
as long as you find it funny.
- Someone who can find this funny.
- I see.
Especially the random things.
Things like, "It raises blood sugar."
How do you feel about women
with an appetite?
- Add that to my ideal type list.
- Someone who eats well?
But I did say I like someone slim.
Someone who's slim but eats well?
There are too many prerequisites.
I can't believe I met someone…
Did I just meet my ideal type?
Jae-jin flirts quite a lot, too.
- He must find her cute.
- He's falling for her.
This is odd to discuss over steak,
but how old are you?
26.
- I was born in 2000.
- Wait, I should've guessed.
Why didn't you ask?
I thought you'd go, "Try to guess."
That's so boring. Everyone does that.
- That was fun.
- Yes.
- I wanted to be different.
- Yes, I love it.
- How old are you?
- I was born in 1998.
- Not a huge gap.
- Surprising, right?
You look very young.
Nicely done.
You have a good eye for people,
so you saw through my immaturity.
I noticed you were a bit of an oddball
starting from the game.
Do you enjoy what you do for a living?
- I do it because I like it.
- You do?
It's something I've always done.
It's either arts or sports.
You're right.
I studied furniture design,
and now I'm a craft designer.
That's what I do.
I'm a craft designer.
While studying furniture design,
I started making home decor.
My main focus is on resin-made vases,
and my designs are patented.
I really love flowers,
and because I felt sad seeing them wilt,
I began using resin
to preserve them longer.
That idea has led me to where I am today.
I hold exhibitions
and continue to pursue my artistic career.
LEE JOO-YOUNG
BORN IN 2000, CRAFT DESIGNER
I mostly make home decor.
- Do you know what that is?
- Of course, I do.
- I'm a modern dancer.
- You do modern dancing?
Arts and sports? All right!
It's nice to meet someone in this field.
But really?
- You're a dancer?
- Yes.
- Do you perform on stage?
- I do.
It suits you.
What are you like when you date?
I have to fall in love
to start dating someone,
and once I'm smitten,
I tend to accommodate her needs.
When it comes to love,
I think I'm a strong believer in fate.
- Those who are meant to be will meet.
- I agree.
I believe in fate.
Would we have had this time to chat
if we hadn't played that game together?
The past is the past.
Let's not think about that.
Let's focus on the positive.
Unbelievable.
Well,
you might laugh more with the others,
but I'm probably the most fun.
- You are fun.
- I know.
You're really unique.
- You can't take it that way.
- What?
I've devised everything
to make this funny.
You planned everything? Don't do that.
- It's a habit. I want to be funny.
- Really?
- I'm obsessed with saying odd stuff.
- Stop that.
It's because I want
to see you laugh once more.
- You must be racking your brain.
- It's that smile.
- I do it without thinking, just for this.
- Really?
- You know what I mean?
- Sure.
Seriously…
One thing's for sure.
- What is it?
- I don't know what'll happen to us later,
but if our feelings are real,
we would've met
even if we hadn't played that game.
- We would've met anyhow?
- That game didn't matter.
- Those who are meant to be will meet.
- Yes, you're right.
I love those eyes.
- Yes, it's nice.
- Yes.
We got to see how Jae-jin changes
when he's with someone he likes.
When people are with someone they love
and feel drawn to,
they show their most natural
and loveliest sides.
I think their innate charm
naturally emerges
when they're trying to woo someone.
- I saw a bit of love in Jae-jin's eyes.
- Yes.
PARADISE
CHOI MINA SUE & LIM SU-BEEN
- Is this place all for us?
- I think so.
So, how were…
the last two days like for you?
- At first, you didn't seem to talk a lot.
- Yes.
There are a lot of people there.
So instead of getting to know everyone,
I wanted to focus on the one
I'm the most interested in.
Something like that.
What did you think
when you first came yesterday?
You know…
- About first impressions?
- First impression.
Well…
You left the best impression on me.
- Really?
- Yes.
I have a question.
This was on the first day.
- You wrote your letter, right?
- Yes.
Who did you send it to?
- I can't tell.
- I'll keep this one to myself.
But I really want to know.
Let's go back to the first impressions.
- You seemed like--
- You're changing the subject.
- I want to know.
- What?
I'll keep it a secret, so can you tell me?
It wasn't me, right?
- Why do you think so?
- I don't know. I don't think it was me.
How many did you receive?
I got three.
- I doubt you sent it to me.
- You don't think so?
- I said I'd focus on one person.
- You did.
- Yes.
- Really?
- For real?
- Yes.
- Are you serious?
One of the three was from me.
- I see.
- Yes.
I knew it. I was correct.
Because towards the end,
we had a chance
to have a quick conversation, right?
- We talked about MBTI types.
- Yes.
- Are you shy around strangers?
- Just a little, when I first meet them.
I want to know your MBTI type,
but I'm not sure if I can ask, so I won't.
I think I can guess yours.
- My MBTI type?
- Yes.
Try taking a guess then.
Good luck guessing my MBTI type.
- Is this a bet?
- Yes, okay.
- I think I can guess yours.
- Okay.
- Let's talk about it later.
I had a feeling that moment
might've been memorable.
- It wasn't because of that moment.
- Really? I thought it was.
For me, it was all about
your first impression.
- My canary dress.
- Yes.
Hello.
You walked over with confidence,
but when you sat down,
you seemed rather shy.
So, that was an unexpected charm.
I see.
I had no idea.
I can't tell what you're thinking
from your face.
Me?
Yes, I get that a lot.
- You do?
- Yes.
My ideal MBTI type is INTJ.
- Really?
- I keep thinking you might be an INTJ.
That's my guess.
Okay.
After you had chicken breast with me,
did you talk to anybody else?
No, I haven't.
Mina Sue seems really pleased.
- Yes.
- Very much.
She loves that he only talked to her.
I'm starving.
- I could eat a cow.
- I could eat a horse.
Yes, I bet you're hungry.
- Oh my. This is--
- Wine first?
A toast with wine?
Should we toast with the same drink?
I'm not very good at this,
so please bear with me.
It's all right.
Goodness.
Hey, wine expert. What do you think?
He didn't use the lever.
- He just used his power.
- Just his power?
- Yes.
- We usually use the lever.
He just pulled it out.
- I want to try the soup first.
- Yes, sure.
How is it?
It's good. I feel much better.
- It's really good.
- You look so happy.
- Can you look that way, please?
- What?
You can stop now.
This really is Paradise.
It really is.
Is it good?
I'm so curious.
I don't know where to begin.
My thoughts are all over the place.
What's at the top of the list?
Honestly speaking,
I want to know how old you are.
- But you want to say that last.
- Yes, I'll tell you that last.
Okay, then.
What do you do?
- What do I do?
- A model?
What you said before
was kind of right, too.
- An athlete?
- Yes.
Really? See? I knew it.
Athlete? Are you an athlete?
I think you might be an athlete.
I used to be an athlete,
but I'm now a model.
- May I ask what sport you played?
- Take a guess.
Volleyball?
Is it basketball?
Throwing… Baseball?
- That's right.
- You did baseball?
Yes.
- I see. For how long?
- For about ten years.
- Ten years?
- Yes.
I was a baseball player for ten years.
I was a pitcher, but I had to quit
because I injured my shoulder.
Man, a baseball player
who looks like that?
- That's so unfair.
- Gosh.
And he was a pitcher, too.
I'm currently working as a model
for lookbooks and advertisements
of many clothing brands.
LIM SU-BEEN
MODEL
That was why you were so good at throwing.
It was so fast, scary even.
I didn't notice yesterday
because you were wearing
oversized clothes.
But today, you were different.
Yes.
I thought you had a nice shape.
From my first impression of you,
I also had a feeling you were a model.
- Really?
- Yes.
Do you want to know?
Yes, I don't have the faintest idea.
- I'm still a student.
- I see.
I'm studying Communications
at a university in America.
And currently interning at a beauty brand.
- I see.
- Yes.
I'm currently a student.
I study Communications
at the University of Illinois.
I'm currently on leave,
so I've returned to Korea
to work as an intern at a beauty startup.
I'm primarily responsible
for English communications
with international buyers at my workplace.
CHOI MINA SUE, UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS
COMMUNICATION MAJOR
- That's why you were good at English.
- Yes.
I spent quite a while overseas.
- Ever since you were a child?
- I was born overseas.
- I see. In America?
- Australia.
- Australia?
- I was born in Sydney.
We have completely opposite personalities.
You mentioned MBTI types, right?
I think we have the exact opposite.
- Right?
- Come to think of it, yes.
I am an INTJ, as you said.
- See? I told you so.
- Yes.
- Did I surprise you?
- You did.
- People rarely guess INTJ.
- I always hit it off well with INTJs.
What are the exact characteristics?
I don't know them well.
First, they aren't talkative.
Right.
They aren't too outgoing.
And they get fully invested
in what captivates them.
When they're into someone,
they go all in with only that person.
Are you drawn to INTJ
because it's the opposite of yours?
I think so.
As you may have noticed,
I'm the chattering type.
- INTJ types don't talk a lot.
- No.
So, they seem to be intrigued
and fascinated by that side of me.
If not, never mind.
That was interesting.
Can you tell me your age now?
My age?
May I take a guess first?
- My age?
- Yes.
- Which year do you think I was born in?
- The year?
Either 1999 or 1998.
Are you around those years
or are you younger?
- I'm not older.
- So you're younger?
I was born in 2002.
- What? In 2002?
- Yes.
- In 2002?
- He's so young!
- Really?
He looks young.
- Mina Sue must be older.
- I think so.
Why?
- You were born in 2002?
- Yes, am I too young for you?
No, the difference isn't too big.
It's my first time
meeting someone born in 2002.
- Pardon?
- Yes.
It's your first time
seeing a World Cup baby?
- Yes, he's a World Cup baby.
- A World Cup baby.
He really is.
- That's right.
- A World Cup baby is on Single's Inferno?
It's your first time
seeing a World Cup baby?
It's my first time.
I've never sat down and had a meal
with someone born in 2002.
In my life. Really.
- When were you born?
- Well, I'm not that much older.
- I was born in 1999, like you said.
- I was right.
That's nothing.
But in 2002? I had a feeling
that you might be older than me.
- I see.
- So, I thought you might be older.
Have you never dated anyone younger?
- Not even on a blind date?
- No.
- I knew you'd be older.
- You did?
- Because I'm on the younger side.
- I see.
But I thought we'd get along
- regardless of our ages.
Thank you.
I'm a bit taken aback right now,
so I might start glitching.
- All right. I'll give you time.
- Okay.
You can speak casually with me.
- Me?
- Yes.
Speak…
- Can I take my time and do that later?
- Yes, of course.
If I do that now,
I might act like I'm older.
But I won't call you "noona."
- No?
- No.
I kind of want to see you do it.
But don't do it.
I might start acting weird.
I can't do it back there anyway.
Right, it's a perk we can only enjoy
while we're here.
Yes.
- Can you swim?
- Of course.
Okay, let's go swimming.
- Why are you suddenly talking casually?
- I tried to do it naturally just now.
Okay.
- Why did you point it out?
- Because my heart skipped a beat.
- Okay, let's move on.
- Okay.
- Let's go swimming.
- Shall we?
This is nice. They revealed their ages,
but the dynamic hasn't changed.
I love how it's the same.
- And the difference isn't much.
- Just three years?
- And Su-been is calm.
- Yes.
- He's mature.
- He is.
Do you want to jump in?
- Really?
- Yes.
- You really did it.
- Of course.
- She went all the way in.
- Even her face!
- Isn't that a first?
- She's so bold.
- Yes, totally.
Gosh, that was so satisfying.
I'm jealous. I want to do it, too.
I'm the happiest I've been
since we got here.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You must like getaways.
- I really do.
This is fun. It's waking me up.
This was a great idea.
- They look so free.
- Yes.
- She's like a Disney princess.
- She's so pretty.
- They're both good-looking.
- I love seeing these two together.
I had the most fun when we went swimming.
It felt really freeing.
I liked how we spent time
enjoying that moment together.
Who do you think will play tomorrow?
Men or the women?
Probably the women.
I wonder if I can win.
I want to win and come back here.
- With me?
- What?
Yes.
As more time passed
and the night deepened,
we got to have more honest conversations.
After I took off my makeup
and put on comfortable clothes,
that's when we became closer.
Do something sexy for me.
- Sexy?
- Yes.
Sexy?
Yes, stick out your waist.
Excellent.
Here we go. One, two, three.
- Let's take one together.
- Sure.
One, two, three.
- Why did you look?
- I didn't look!
What is this? You don't look ugly.
You have to look even uglier.
I had a lot of fun today.
Me too.
I had much more fun than I imagined.
- You had that much fun?
- Yes, it was that fun.
I hope it was the same for you.
It was.
- Good night.
- Night.
They're the type of couple
that makes you smile.
This season is a lot of fun.
And Su-been is different
because when guys are younger,
they try to act more mature,
and that becomes almost too predictable.
But he doesn't pretend.
He just naturally seems mature.
Mina Sue said
she has never dated a younger guy,
but I don't think she's against it.
She's interested in Su-been.
I think she's into him.
- I look forward to seeing them.
- Yes.
He's young, but he doesn't act like it.
- No.
- Right.
What I like about Su-been is when he said,
"I won't call you 'noona.'"
- That's the perfect attitude.
- Yes.
He's saying
he'll keep his appeal as a man,
and it probably made her heart flutter.
But there could come a time
when he suddenly calls her "noona."
- That's another twist.
- She'll fall for that, too.
Why are you excited?
- I mean, I was watching them.
- What's with you?
He's on her list.
Please try to understand
when we put ourselves in their shoes.
- Especially, as we watch the footage.
- Yes, of course.
- All right.
- That's the fun of the show.
Did you imagine him saying that?
No, I…
- She did.
- I want to see it happen.
We might see it in the future.
Su-been is a cool guy.
- I like him.
- Yes.
They're cute together.
- Yes, they're cute.
- Such a cute couple.
We're back in Inferno.
They must be at the Cafeteria.
What if there's someone new again?
- They're back.
- What? Where?
The Hyun-Hyeon brothers.
- Hello.
- It's nice to see you.
We're back.
Welcome back.
- Wait, you haven't eaten?
- I couldn't eat a lot.
Sweet potato.
That was quick.
How was everyone?
Not bad.
Did you have fun?
- Not bad.
- Not bad?
- Not bad for everyone?
- Yes.
Did you do anything fun?
- I went swimming.
- Really?
Breaststroke, with my head out.
- Can you say…
- I put on a show all by myself.
We dove into the water.
We jumped in.
- We counted to three and jumped in.
- That sounds fun.
- We went to an amusement park.
- It was all to ourselves.
- I wanted to do backstroke.
- We would've…
- Right?
- Swam the night away.
We made a bet,
so we became competitive and jumped in.
This is bad.
Those who were left behind
start to feel spiteful,
while those who had left are still happy.
- You're right.
- Yes.
Who are you most curious to ask?
Me? Seung-il and Sung-min.
- Us two?
- Yes.
I was surprised that Go-eun and I
seemed to be on the same wavelength.
I thought otherwise.
For me,
Min-gee was just as I thought
she would be.
She's friendly,
and our personalities seemed to click.
What about you, Su-been?
For me, I never had a dull moment.
- Really?
- No.
She's really energetic.
I had a lot of fun.
You're smiling way too much.
- Yes, his smile…
- He's smiling ear to ear.
No way.
- You're beaming.
- Literally ear to ear.
It's great to have everyone back.
Yes, do you know how lonely I felt
sleeping here alone?
- Everyone here had left.
- You two had each other at least.
- Who did you miss the most?
- Me?
Who do you want
to talk to the most, Hyeon-woo?
Me? My first choice.
- First choice? Who?
- Yes.
Yeah.
- Wasn't it Go-eun?
- Go-eun?
Min-gee?
- Was it Min-gee?
- It was Min-gee.
- Who did you miss?
- I missed Joo-young.
I missed her the most.
Start talking.
You start talking. Now.
What was it like, everyone?
Jae-jin?
- Joo-young?
- Jae-jin?
- Jae-jin.
- I had fun.
- You guys had a nice vibe.
- Yes.
- You seemed closer.
- Yes, we are now.
We got to talk a lot.
We really got to talk.
He was similar to the idea I had of him.
- Really?
- Yes.
I think he's a very composed guy.
- He was.
And calm. Yes.
Now, Go-eun's turn.
Me?
Did you two hit it off?
- I had fun talking to him.
- Are you more interested in him?
I am.
If you could go there with him again,
would you?
Yes, I think I would like to.
I understood why people
want to go to Paradise.
Not only is it about the environment,
but you can also talk more freely
about everything.
You seemed really happy.
- Me? What do you mean?
- Yes.
Your eyes were full of love.
Love was written all over your face.
You're lying.
I could see his eyes sparkling
through his sunglasses.
He put them on intentionally.
It was more fun than I anticipated.
But did having fun together
spark more interest?
Well…
I became more interested than I expected.
We became really close.
But we seemed closer last night.
Things were awkward when we woke up.
We also heard
that Su-been is taciturn and quiet
even when he's with the guys.
- I'm not so sure about that.
- Really?
- He must've been talkative.
- He must've felt awkward with the guys.
Min-gee's turn.
I had fun.
- What?
- I had so much fun.
Isn't that enough?
I was quite happy. All right.
Don't look at me with those eyes.
- Seriously.
- Like a deer in the headlights.
Did your heart flutter?
My heart definitely skipped a beat.
I think my heart fluttered.
I think so. Probably.
- It's different.
- Maybe?
- Your response is different from day one.
- But I was really nervous.
- Really?
- I got nervous, me!
I mean, me!
Anyway, the conversations were fun,
and he was just my type.
I said I wanted to talk to others
because I was curious about them, right?
But I'm not curious at all now.
- Really?
- Wait, really?
They all had a great time in Paradise.
The older girls all fell
for the younger boys.
- They are all smitten.
- Completely.
But I'm not curious at all now.
- I don't need to explore now.
- I got goosebumps.
My gosh! She got goosebumps. What is this?
- She really got goosebumps!
It's all over.
- Is he your type in terms of looks, too?
- I'm not into the bad boy look.
But now that I like him, he seems cute.
I even like the way he looks now.
He wore his hair down today,
and even that looked really cute.
Oh no.
It's over once they start to look cute.
If she's that open about it,
others might find it hard to approach him.
He looks so cute.
Even his smile looks cute.
- That's love.
- It's not that serious yet.
But he's cute.
- It's over if they look cute.
- It is.
When women find men cute,
the game is already over.
But I'm not sure about how he feels.
Did anything happen to you two?
You must've had one-on-one conversations.
- Did you get to know anyone?
- No, not really.
- At this point, I'm back at ground zero.
- Zero?
Really?
Geez!
Singles, please gather
in front of the Photo Studio.
Over there?
- We're taking pictures…
- We are?
Do we get to see them?
What will we be doing?
What is this?
Today's mission is a photoshoot.
A photoshoot?
What?
A photoshoot.
- That's new.
- What's a photoshoot mission?
- Isn't this the first time?
- Yes.
The theme of the photoshoot
is being the hottest couple in the world.
The hottest?
- That's hard.
- What? That's hard.
- That's really hard.
- It's so hard.
The couple that gets voted as first place
will receive a special benefit.
We will begin matching couples.
Women will draw numbered balls
and choose the men in that order.
I'm doomed.
However, one woman has a chance
to select two men.
That's the winner.
In the couple photoshoot mission,
one woman gets to choose two men.
- Just one woman.
- An advantage.
- Just one.
- Lucky her.
If the woman in the front
does not pick two men,
the next person in line gets the chance.
Next in line?
What happens if nobody picks two men
and the process keeps going?
Then, automatically,
the woman who's in last place
- will get to do it with two men.
- I see.
For example, if the woman
who got first place doesn't want two men,
she can just shoot
with one person if she wants.
- Then the next person gets the choice?
- You're right.
This can be risky.
Let's say we have a good relationship,
but if I choose someone else
to do the photoshoot with…
- This dynamic might become awkward.
- You're right.
They'll have to be careful.
- Will you be greedy?
- Right.
Or will you go for one person?
But you have to pick two men
to enter two different photos.
- It's a better chance.
- That gives you a higher chance to win.
Mina Sue said that was the winner
because the probability goes up
when someone picks two men.
Now, please take turns drawing the ball
starting with Kim Min-gee.
Kim Min-gee.
Let me announce the order in which
you will select your photoshoot partner.
First, Lee Joo-young.
Second, Park Hee-sun.
Third, Kim Min-gee.
Fourth, Ham Ye-jin.
Fifth, Choi Mina Sue.
Sixth, Kim Go-eun.
Lee Joo-young.
Please choose the person
you'd like to do a photoshoot with.
Oh, right now.
Will it be one or two?
- One person.
- One?
- It might be two.
- She wouldn't do that.
The person I'd like to do
a photoshoot with is…
There's a chance it might be Hyun-jae.
Youn Hyun-jae?
The person I'd like to do
a photoshoot with is…
Shin Hyeon-woo.
- Shin Hyeon-woo?
- Hyeon-woo?
What's going on?
Shin Hyeon-woo.
I was the first to make a choice.
I gave my vote to Hyeon-woo.
She did write the letter to Hyeon-woo
because she was interested in him.
- Really?
- You're right.
We haven't had a chance to talk,
so I decided to choose him.
I see.
- This is a new dynamic.
- Yes.
We forgot about the first impression vote.
I was a bit heartbroken
when Joo-young chose Hyeon-woo.
But I just figured it was for the mission.
I tried not to read into it.
I hope she gets to know Hyeon-woo…
and return to me.
Park Hee-sun.
Please choose the person
you'd like to do a photoshoot with.
The person I'd like
to do a photoshoot with is…
Lim Su-been.
- There we go.
- Yes.
They'll make a nice picture.
Lim Su-been.
Kim Min-gee.
Please choose the person
you'd like to do a photoshoot with.
The person I'd like
to do a photoshoot with is…
Song Seung-il.
Ham Ye-jin.
Please choose the person
you'd like to do a photoshoot with.
Youn Hyun-jae.
Choi Mina Sue.
Please choose the person
you'd like to do a photoshoot with.
I'm so nervous
that I'm blanking out on their names.
Name…
I'm sorry.
I'm…
What's going on?
- What?
- No way.
I'm so sorry.
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn