YOUN HYUN-JAE
SONG SEUNG-IL
PARK HEE-SUN
SHIN HYEON-WOO
KIM GO-EUN
KIM JAE-JIN
HAM YE-JIN
WOO SUNG-MIN
KIM MIN-GEE
LIM SU-BEEN
LEE SUNG-HUN
LEE JOO-YOUNG
CHOI MINA SUE
SINGLE'S INFERNO
Choi Mina Sue.
Please choose the person
you'd like to do a photoshoot with.
I'm so nervous
that I'm blanking out on their names.
Name…
I'm sorry.
I'm…
What's going on?
- What?
- No way.
She must be really nervous.
- She's flustered.
- Yes, she's nervous.
I'm so sorry.
I was honestly really flustered.
When Hee-sun said Su-been's name…
The person I'd like
to do a photoshoot with is…
Lim Su-been.
I actually wanted
to do the mission with Su-been.
So I became flustered,
and my mind just went blank.
Her mind completely…
Her mind must've gone blank.
Seung-il and Su-been were both chosen,
so she panicked.
Sung-hun must be heartbroken.
Lee Sung-hun, Kim Jae-jin, Woo Sung-min.
The person I'd like
to do a photoshoot with is…
Lee Sung-hun and…
Who else…
Seung-il.
- Seung-il?
- He's already chosen.
- Gosh.
- Oh no.
You should've just picked one person.
Seung-il.
- He's chosen.
- I picked him.
He's chosen? I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- I'm sorry.
Sorry, I keep forgetting their names.
Take your time.
I'll start over. I'm sorry.
The ones I'd like to do a photoshoot with
are Lee Sung-hun and Woo Sung-min.
Since all the couples have been decided,
Kim Go-eun will do a photoshoot
with Kim Jae-jin.
Woo Sung-min
must not feel too good either.
Seriously.
- Right?
- She struggled a bit there.
What in the world is this?
COUPLE PHOTOSHOOT
LEE JOO-YOUNG & SHIN HYEON-WOO
KIM GO-EUN & KIM JAE-JIN
I think this is our spot.
Do you want to go first or later?
I haven't thought of any ideas yet.
- So, you want to go second?
- Yes.
- Actually, we can go first.
- Why?
An idea just popped into my head.
- An idea?
- Yes.
All right.
COUPLE PHOTOSHOOT
LEE JOO-YOUNG & SHIN HYEON-WOO
Shall we start by sitting down?
- What should we do?
This is tough.
Shooting by the ocean looks good, too.
- He has to watch them.
- Right, that must be torture.
I'll pose like this, and you can…
Should I put my arm up
or hold you like this?
Instead of that,
you can pull me in your direction.
Like this?
- Pull this arm.
- Grab this side?
I'll look this way.
Like this?
- I'll look this way.
- Like this?
- Okay.
- But…
Don't lean over like this.
I'll lean closer to you
so we can be closer.
Okay.
- Ready?
- Yes.
What's wrong?
You can be bolder.
- I don't mind.
- Okay, I will.
Okay, let's begin.
Pull me toward you.
Why'd you pucker your lips?
Why'd she pucker her lips?
- It's very natural.
- Why'd she pucker her lips?
- Her lips naturally…
- She did this.
- No, she…
- Without thinking.
It's because she was trying to smile
but stopped halfway.
Why'd you pucker your lips?
Let's continue.
- One more time. Focus.
- I'm still shooting.
- Okay.
I'll look at your lips.
- Hyeon-woo is very into it.
- Yes.
How is he like that?
He's actually taking the lead.
How do you feel?
She was your partner yesterday.
Right.
She has quite a small frame.
- Yes, she's so slender.
- And he has a larger frame.
- She looks like a fairy tale princess.
- Like Tinker Bell.
They had great chemistry.
I tried my best…
not to care about it.
- Do a lot.
- Okay.
- Did you just tell me to do a lot?
- Yes.
- I should do a lot, right?
I don't get jealous over things like this.
Getting jealous over
who they partnered up with for a game
is such an immature way of thinking.
It doesn't look that hot.
Is your MBTI the thinking type?
The mission was to be a hot couple.
He seems jealous.
- Jae-jin seems very bothered.
- Yes, he does.
- How about this? Come here.
- Touching foreheads?
- Come here.
- Okay, we'll touch foreheads.
Shall we look at the camera?
- At the camera?
- This one?
- To the side.
- Like this?
- That's a nice shot.
- It is.
Zoomed in like that.
I think seeing them pose
in front of him like this
might trigger Jae-jin to pose more boldly,
like he's about to kiss his partner.
- Don't you think?
- Yes, it'll trigger him.
It'll provoke jealousy.
This is quite entertaining.
Why is this so entertaining?
COUPLE PHOTOSHOOT
KIM GO-EUN & KIM JAE-JIN
- They look really good.
- Very nice.
- Go-eun is…
- She's a model all right.
- Look at her go.
- She sure is a model.
- What if my face looks huge in the photos?
- I'll lean forward.
I had a strategy in mind.
My appearance…
doesn't really give off hot vibes.
So I tried my best
to play the supporting role,
emphasizing Go-eun's charm
as much as possible.
I'm not wearing any jewelry.
Want to wear my bracelet?
- Your arm looks bare.
- Should I?
- Right?
- Thank you.
I wanted to do a wet hair look, too.
Is there any water?
- Just make the ends look spiky.
- I think that's enough.
Try doing the thing.
- I'll try my best so you can stand out.
- I'm not sure if it'll look good.
- Can I really step on you? I'm not sure…
- Let's give it a try.
- I don't know how it'll look.
- Just look your best.
That pose is saying, "Trample on me."
- That's…
- She's stomping on him.
It's definitely hotter than before.
- Totally.
- Right?
I can see the difference.
- Here we go.
- Okay.
This is hard.
- It's kind of--
- Want to lean on my chest?
By my neck?
- How?
- Lean your head back on my chest.
- By my neck.
- Like this?
- Look at them.
- That's nice.
- This is hard to beat.
- It's very hot.
She's used to this as a model.
She's on a different level.
Jae-jin said he wouldn't go shirtless,
but he did right away.
Seeing Jae-jin,
who I went to Paradise with,
do the mission with someone else
felt quite strange.
It felt kind of weird.
I almost forgot.
Shall we hold hands?
Now that's a hot couple.
- Are you looking ahead?
- Yes.
They're lying down.
Our goal is to get the best shot.
- Their expressions are…
- They look serious.
- His face is…
- Right? They're getting closer.
- Their expressions are a bit spicy, too.
- You're right.
- Slightly hot--
- Oh my gosh.
- My gosh.
- They got the shot.
That could be the poster
for Single's Inferno.
- A dancer's body is truly built different.
- I agree.
Look at his muscles.
Look, that's what I wanted to do.
They're doing exactly that.
Still…
Do you regret it?
No, I feel a vicarious satisfaction
watching them do what I'd pictured.
I think Go-eun did a great job.
I think if Go-eun and I
had combined our boldness,
we would've created the hottest photos.
What does Hyeon-woo do?
- I'm really curious.
- Me too.
I didn't know he was like this.
He's very competitive.
He's also very confident.
But Go-eun and Jae-jin
looked great together
during their photoshoot.
Watching them made my heart flutter
more than I thought it would.
COUPLE PHOTOSHOOT
CHOI MINA SUE, WOO SUNG-MIN, LEE SUNG-HUN
PARK HEE-SUN & LIM SU-BEEN
Ready, go.
Hello.
- You look gorgeous.
- Yes, you're both dressed up.
- I don't think we'll need to pose a lot.
- I agree.
I think I look quite simple.
Yes, simple is best.
- I'm curious to see Mina Sue.
- Mina Sue.
- Me too.
- Sung-min, Sung-hun.
Go further.
- How about here?
- Okay.
I was thinking of posing like this.
- And we look back.
If you look this way,
it'll show your side profile.
- This way?
- Wait, I'll come up.
Okay.
Is everyone experienced in this?
- They're not shy.
- They look like professionals.
- Mina Sue--
- She's like a professional.
- Her facial expressions--
- Her gestures too.
- Look at her eyes.
- If this is her first time,
she has to be a model.
She's a natural.
- She's talented.
- She is.
- Let's do this.
- Making eye contact?
- Like this.
- Like this?
I think we can get closer.
- We should do some bold poses.
- Yes.
I think it'll look better if we're closer.
- My gosh, Mina Sue.
- Mina Sue looks like a model.
- She knows how to pose.
- It's like a movie poster.
I hope we do well and don't look awkward.
- Let's try to look natural.
- Okay.
Are you okay? Is it uncomfortable?
- Is it uncomfortable?
- No, I'm okay. I can bend further back.
She can bend further back?
Mina Sue is determined.
- I'll show my leg when we take the photo.
- Do you want to lift your leg up?
Wrap it around me.
- Like this?
- Yes.
Up here? Then can you hold my leg?
- Good job. That was fun, right?
- Good job.
- We got this.
Good job.
- We've got to kill it.
- Right.
How did we do, Sung-hun?
- You guys did great.
- Was it good? Really?
- It's cold.
- So cold!
- Or--
- How about this?
I'll hold you.
COUPLE PHOTOSHOOT
PARK HEE-SUN & LIM SU-BEEN
My hair.
- Should I turn?
- Yes, you can lean on me.
- Why are you laughing?
- We're too close.
What should we do?
- It must be awkward.
- Because she likes him.
- Should I hold your waist like this?
- Yes, sounds good.
Like this?
- I think it'll look good.
- I agree.
It looks nice.
- They're so cute.
- Good models get good results.
Aren't they both so cute?
- I don't know.
- You don't?
No, I don't.
- They're both cute.
- She doesn't see it.
- She's jealous.
- She's transparent.
There.
That's a new pose.
It'd look nice
if you hugged him from behind.
- True.
- Hug him from behind.
Tell us the poses we forgot to do.
Try hugging him from behind.
- Or I could--
- How do I hug him?
- Should I hug him from behind like this?
- Then put your face here.
- Let's do the Titanic pose.
- Okay.
Oh my.
What was that?
- That's so…
- It was a body check.
She frisked him
like they do at the airport.
- What was that?
- It passed by in a flash, right?
I wonder what she was thinking.
He's just a friend to her.
- She has no feelings for him.
- There's no spark whatsoever.
That shocked me for a second.
- I think it was just a joke.
- A joke?
Lying down on the beach.
How should we do this?
Let's pose like this.
We'd like a close-up shot.
- Should I fully lie down?
- Sounds good.
I'll lie down with you.
- Should we hold hands?
- Was it covering you?
- The corners of her lips are moving again.
- They are.
- She really can't hide her feelings.
- She's so easy to read.
Let's look at each other.
- Is that possible?
- Yes.
I don't know what to do.
Let's change positions.
Your eyes have a tint of green.
Don't say things like that.
During the couple photoshoot,
there were shots
where we made eye contact.
We were really close to each other,
so my heart fluttered.
She looks smitten.
- She's nervous.
- Of course.
- But Hee-sun is lying so far down.
- Who?
She's lying down so comfortably.
- She's not a professional model.
- She should've lain down at an angle.
- She's not a model.
- Right.
I know, but she looks way too comfortable.
- It might be better to not have feelings.
- I agree.
Right?
Yes, it bothered me. I was very annoyed.
I don't know exactly why,
but it bothered me.
But I didn't want to make it obvious.
I really wanted to hide how I felt.
- But it showed.
- It was obvious.
- It's written all over her face.
- Exactly.
- She's not as chill as I thought.
- It's because she likes him.
I think we're done.
All done.
- Good job.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
Very cool.
- You got this.
- I got this.
- How about here?
- It's nice.
COUPLE PHOTOSHOOT
CHOI MINA SUE & SAMUEL LEE
Here?
Right here? How about over here?
- I'll try sitting down.
- Okay.
- I can do this.
- Nice.
- Okay, I'll do my best.
This is my best.
- That rock is a great spot.
- It is.
I think it'll turn out well.
- We have to be super close.
- Yes.
You can like…
It's okay if we touch a lot.
- Okay, you got this?
- Yeah.
- I think you can get closer.
- How do I get closer?
Is it hard to position yourself?
- He kind of looks like a walrus.
- Hold her, Sung-hun.
- Hug her.
- He does resemble one.
- That was a timid attack.
- He's being quite harsh.
Want to try grabbing my neck?
- No, not like that.
- You told me to choke you.
- Not choking.
- What do I do then?
Did you see him grab her neck?
- He grabbed her neck?
- Yes, he did.
No freaking way.
- What do I do?
- Wrap your arm around me.
Hang on.
- Oh my gosh.
- How could you choke her?
I misheard her. I swear.
My hair…
Focus on your core.
So that's their vibe.
- Her gaze is so intense.
- It's beautiful.
They look so good together.
Pose like you're conquering me.
Shooting with Mina Sue on the beach
while shirtless
was pretty intense.
- He's very blunt.
- "While shirtless."
Sung-hun is adorable.
I think we may have grown a little closer.
I think Mina Sue still thinks of me
like more of a friend right now,
but I'd like to get to know her
more one-on-one.
I think this pose will look good, too.
Look at me.
- That's nice. That might win first place.
- Looking good.
- Nice.
- Great pose.
The angles are great.
You have beautiful eyes.
Hang on.
- Don't make me laugh.
- It's okay if you laugh.
I really want to win first place.
But they're doing so well.
- Yes.
- But we…
I didn't really care for
Sung-min and Mina Sue's photoshoot.
But when Sung-hun
and Mina Sue were shooting,
I got a little upset.
For some reason,
I just didn't like watching them.
How much time do we have?
He put on his sunglasses.
If I were Su-been,
I would've splashed them.
I wouldn't be able to watch that.
COUPLE PHOTOSHOOT
KIM MIN-GEE & SONG SEUNG-IL
This is the dodgeball field.
- Sit down first.
- Let's discuss a plan.
- Sit down.
- Should I squat?
Sit in a comfortable position.
- Like this?
- Yes.
Sit comfortably on the ground.
- Sit down, please.
- Okay.
I'll slightly put my leg on your thigh,
so it's like I'm getting on top of you.
Like you're getting on top of me?
Yes, like right before
I get on top of you.
- I'll adjust to however you pose.
- Okay, let's give it a shot.
- Like we've been caught.
- Nice.
- "Like we've been caught."
- Caught doing what?
Why are those two so funny?
- Like we've been caught.
- Nice.
Why are his eyes like that?
What's he doing?
He's trying his best.
- I get what they're going for, but…
- They want to win, okay?
It's cute.
- Seung-il…
- Why did he freeze there?
Nice. I'll try climbing up a little more.
- Should I hold your leg like this?
- Sure.
- You can lean against me, Min-gee.
- Okay.
- Should I lean?
- For my hair, you can squeeze it.
"Squeeze it"?
- How can you squeeze hair?
- Why would she squeeze your hair?
- He must want to try something intense.
- He's adorable.
- This is so funny.
- How would she squeeze it?
- Should I lean?
- For my hair, you can squeeze it.
- Sorry.
- We can't laugh.
I shouldn't, but I keep laughing.
I was very nervous.
It was so nerve-racking.
My heart was pounding
and I was a nervous wreck,
but I really tried my best.
- The photo looks cool.
- Yes.
It came out great.
- Are we touching cheeks?
- Yes, so I'll come closer.
Come closer.
Min-gee's body was pressed against mine.
I felt very nervous for some reason.
The Min-gee I'm familiar with
is quite playful and easygoing.
But during the photoshoot,
Min-gee took the lead in coaching me.
Let's put our faces together.
- But your hair…
- This much is okay.
I'll put my nose against you.
I saw a different side of her.
- His heart must've fluttered.
- Yes, that's another charm.
- What a hot photo.
- The results are great.
- Nice.
- They're great.
- It came out well.
- You gave really good suggestions.
Really? What a relief.
- They have no desire to win.
- They look like newlyweds.
Newlyweds.
- It's pretty.
- They're cute.
COUPLE PHOTOSHOOT
HAM YE-JIN & YOUN HYUN-JAE
- We can pretend to blow it.
- Sure.
Make the shape with your lips.
Nice.
We really look like a married couple.
Our theme is to show
the passionate future of newlyweds.
- They went to make memories.
- How lovely.
They really have no desire to win.
Next up is the voting
for the photoshoot mission.
Enter the studio one at a time
and vote for who best suits
the title as the World's Hottest Couple.
YOU CANNOT VOTE FOR YOURSELF
LEE JOO-YOUNG & SHIN HYEON-WOO
It's nice, but…
PARK HEE-SUN & LIM SU-BEEN
- Goodness.
- It's beautiful.
KIM MIN-GEE & SONG SEUNG-IL
HAM YE-JIN & YOUN HYUN-JAE
Cute.
It's a cute couple photo.
CHOI MINA SUE & LEE SUNG-HUN
- Look at that.
- Oh my.
Look at her eyes.
CHOI MINA SUE & WOO SUNG-MIN
- Mina Sue.
- She did great.
She's incredible.
KIM GO-EUN & KIM JAE-JIN
- Look at them.
- They look good, too.
- They're front-runners.
- Yes.
- It'll be a match between two couples.
- I agree.
I will now announce
the results of the photoshoot mission.
What do you think?
- I want to win first place.
- Me too.
- It's a fierce battle.
- It is.
I was shocked
because the photos were intense.
It made my heart race.
Yes, my heart fluttered
while looking at the photos.
It felt so weird.
The couple that won first place…
is Kim Go-eun and Kim Jae-jin.
They did it.
- They were hot.
- They did well.
It was good.
…is Kim Go-eun and Kim Jae-jin.
All right.
Nice.
As expected, everyone has good taste.
Good for them.
- Their photo was nice.
- Yes, they were very…
- We won thanks to you.
- Thanks to you, too.
Here are the special benefits
for the couple's photoshoot mission.
I'm curious.
Kim Go-eun and Kim Jae-jin,
you may choose one person
and view their top three contestants
of most interest to them.
That's a great idea.
- Their top three.
- Yes, top three is a lot.
- You can see how they feel.
- Yes, that's a huge benefit.
- That's crazy.
- I've got goosebumps.
My hair is standing on end.
Goosebumps…
Who will they choose?
More than the result,
something else interests me.
You know how you get really close
during the shoot?
Didn't you get butterflies while doing it?
You did, right?
Yes, from time to time.
Any changes of heart?
In our rankings?
My ranking changed.
- Really?
- To whom?
- Sung-hun?
- Sung-hun.
- Is Sung-hun on her radar?
- Did Su-been move down?
My ranking changed.
How?
Completely?
Not completely, but it's kind of…
I'm interested in…
But is it normal
that my rankings keep changing?
- Sure, why not?
- That can happen.
Right now, my first place
is Sung-hun.
Finally!
Sung-hun hit the jackpot.
He's in the game.
He got really lucky.
- The games really matter a lot.
- Seriously.
My second pick is Su-been,
and my third pick…
is Woo Sung-min.
The reason Sung-hun is my first pick
is because when I came back from Paradise,
he kind of lingered on my mind.
And when I saw the photoshoot results,
Sung-hun looked very attractive.
He also accommodated me well
throughout the shoot,
and we had good chemistry.
So I'm more interested in him now.
How are your rankings?
Did this affect them at all?
I can't say it didn't affect me.
I can't say it had no effect.
This made me want to get
to know Hee-sun better.
I hadn't talked to her much before,
but we got to talk a lot this time.
I thought I might develop feelings
if we talked more.
So I want to talk with her more.
The physical contact from the photoshoot
definitely seems to sway emotions.
This is what I think.
It was the same last season.
Many contestants didn't really pursue
their top three picks in the end.
They changed their minds?
Yes, they'd say someone was their top pick
but wouldn't treat them accordingly.
That's why I'm not fully convinced.
This reminds me
of what Mina Sue said in the beginning.
She said it'd be hard for her
to date someone who didn't speak English.
Sung-hun is the only one
who can speak English.
- Mina Sue's Korean is pretty good, though.
- She has a great vocabulary.
That's true.
"A great vocabulary."
Look. What is that?
What is this?
- What's all of this?
- There's beer.
- Awesome.
- There's soju, too.
Soju?
- It's a campfire.
- This is bad.
The campfire…
- This will be a disaster.
- In the show's history…
- Something always happens at campfires.
- That's right.
I'm scared of that campfire.
- I want draft beer.
- I want them all.
- That's the issue.
- Where should I sit?
I want to sit here.
- Why is everyone standing?
- Come on, let's all sit down.
Just sit anywhere.
- You're here.
- Here I am.
- Sit down.
- I want to sit here.
- Hey.
- Hello.
I'd originally wanted
to sit next to Mina Sue.
But Hee-sun was next to me,
so we naturally sat together.
- Hello.
I really think something big will happen.
- There might be some changes.
- I'm sure there will be.
No, I…
- Excuse me, Ye-jin.
- No, stop.
Would you mind switching seats with him?
- Can we switch seats?
- Sure.
- Are you okay, Hyun-jae?
- Yes, this is lovely.
- Shall we all raise our glasses?
- Sounds good.
This is our first group dinner in Inferno,
so let's have fun.
- Cheers.
- Good job today.
- You too.
Man, it's like water.
- Sorry?
- It tastes sweet.
- Try this.
- Okay.
- I can't tell what this is. Is it potato?
- Is it fried?
Oh my gosh.
- It's so refreshing.
- This is so nice.
I'm so happy.
- Wasn't it hot during the photoshoot?
- During the photoshoot?
I think I was okay.
I guess you don't burn easily.
- I brought salve in case you got burnt.
- Really?
I do have one burn.
- You do?
- From my curling iron.
It touched my shoulder.
But really? You brought this yourself?
- That's great.
- It's for you.
- That's so sweet.
- Of course.
You were sweet
to bring the watermelon, too.
- This is your second sweet moment.
- That's just who I am.
Being sweet?
I said I'd make one move every day.
- So, is this today's move?
- Yes.
He's really showing off his charms.
- "One move every day."
- How cute.
This is an uncomfortable spot.
- There's no table.
- No table?
- Should I move over?
- I can move over.
Or you can move to this side.
Let's move back.
Is that okay?
- Have some of this.
- Thank you.
Have some.
- I noticed you're left-handed.
- Yes, that's right.
- How did you know?
- I noticed when you were writing.
I think we were writing
our first impressions.
- You sat next to me, right?
- Yes.
DAY 1 POPULARITY VOTE
- I like left-handed people.
- Really?
I have a weird taste.
She has a unique ideal type.
- She likes left-handed people.
- It's true.
I remember that.
That situation was quite memorable for me.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Is it too far?
- How's the drink?
They spoke at the same time.
They talked over each other.
- Is it too far?
- How's the drink?
- Hold on.
- How's the drink going down?
It's going down smoothly.
What did you say?
- Take your time.
- I will.
Yes, I should calm down.
- What a strange vibe.
- It's uncomfortable.
It's a love triangle.
What is this?
- It looks like a tortilla.
- I see.
What's it like to eat something new?
It's a first, right?
It really is.
I'm happy.
- Is the meat in Paradise good?
- It's incredible.
I'd better go soon.
I feel bad now.
- Must be nice.
- That sounded sincere.
It's making me feel sorry.
I'm sad…
It irked me to see him with Hee-sun.
Logically, I understand
this is an environment
where we get to know various people.
However,
I felt like
he could've given me some attention
while he was with Hee-sun.
- Her number one pick is Su-been.
- You're right.
Despite what she said,
he's still on her mind.
- What if Mina Sue turns evil?
- Because of today.
- How was it?
- Going to Paradise for the first time?
Did you develop feelings
or do you feel the same?
Honestly?
- What do you mean, no?
- She's turning more to the dark side.
Is there anyone you want to get to know?
There is.
Being here makes me feel…
I'm not usually like this,
but I keep changing my mind.
- It's the environment.
- Because of the environment.
- Don't tell me…
- Why?
Here are the results
of the confession vote.
- They're being revealed?
- Really?
- It's not a secret?
- No way.
- It was a secret ballot!
- Oh no.
1 HOUR AGO
Now, the confession vote will begin.
We're voting again?
This is getting fun.
Please go to the mailboxes one by one…
and deliver a red chocolate
to the person you're interested in
and a gold chocolate
to the person you're curious about.
Red is for interest.
For someone you're curious about…
- Only two?
- We can pick two people?
We can only vote for two,
so it'll be tough.
Their top pick is based on interest,
and the second pick is out of curiosity.
I wonder who'll get the most chocolates.
Among the women, I'd say it's Mina Sue.
- She interacted with many people.
- She did.
- She'll get the most votes.
- I agree.
For the men, maybe Su-been or Jae-jin.
Su-been will definitely get one
from both Hee-sun and Mina Sue.
Su-been will surely get
at least two votes.
- Jae-jin might get a lot for curiosity.
- I think Jae-jin will receive a lot.
He makes people curious.
Please take the box with your name on it.
CONFESSION VOTE RESULTS
I'm about to have my pride hurt.
- Gosh.
- Can we shake them?
Lim Su-been, please open your box.
- Really?
- We have to show it?
- Here?
- Like this?
- Oh no.
- I need more soju.
This is so cruel.
I have one.
It's red.
There was one red heart in my box.
I think it was from…
Hee-sun, who showed me the most interest.
I think Mina Sue voted for someone else,
so I was upset about that.
- Of course.
- Yes, I knew this would happen.
Mina Sue didn't vote for him out of spite.
You're right.
Park Hee-sun, please open your box.
PARK HEE-SUN: 1 GOLD
Curiosity.
I was relieved
to receive at least one this time.
I hope it was Su-been who gave it to me.
Kim Jae-jin, please open your box.
Kim Jae-jin has one red chocolate
and two gold chocolates.
He's Mr. Popular.
He's quiet yet powerful.
I was surprised and happy
I got more chocolates than I expected.
I hope the red chocolate
was from Joo-young.
It was hard to guess
who gave me the gold chocolates.
That's wild.
Shin Hyeon-woo, please open your box.
Shin Hyeon-woo has three gold chocolates.
Kim Go-eun, please open your box.
What if she has five?
Unfortunately, I only have four.
- That's unfortunate?
- "Unfortunately"?
- What?
That's impressive.
I got two red chocolates
and two gold chocolates.
I think I got a red from Sung-min
and a gold from Hyeon-woo.
I'm so curious
about who the other two people are.
Woo Sung-min, please open your box.
WOO SUNG-MIN: 1 RED & 1 GOLD
I had one red and one gold.
I think Go-eun gave me the red heart.
For the gold heart,
I have no clue who it was from.
I have no idea. Who's it from?
Choi Mina Sue, please open your box.
- She'll have two reds.
- Two reds?
- I don't think so.
- From Su-been and Sung-hun.
I'm so curious.
Choi Mina Sue has
one red chocolate and one gold chocolate.
What?
I don't get it.
Honestly,
I thought I'd get more.
I think I'm a bit overly confident,
but I thought I'd get a few more.
I wondered if the red one
was from Sung-hun.
I thought Sung-hun had continually
expressed interest toward me.
I think the red one is from Sung-hun
and the gold one is from Sung-min.
Did Su-been change his mind?
Su-been didn't connect
with anyone else though.
- But Sung-hun--
- Hee-sun didn't get a red one.
Sung-hun could've given
his red one to someone else.
He could have.
- Sung-hun?
- Give it to whom?
During the photoshoot,
Mina Sue might've enjoyed it,
but maybe Sung-hun
didn't enjoy it as much.
Then to whom?
He didn't connect with anybody either.
- I don't know.
- It's getting more confusing.
Lee Sung-hun, please open your box.
Lee Sung-hun has one red chocolate.
Ham Ye-jin, please open your box.
Ham Ye-jin has one gold chocolate.
Song Seung-il, please open your box.
I had one red chocolate.
Since Min-gee and I
had previously gone to Paradise,
I thought it was very likely
that the red chocolate was from her.
Since I received only one chocolate,
it seemed like
Mina Sue wasn't interested in me.
In regards to that,
I was pretty disappointed.
Kim Min-gee, please open your box.
Impressive.
Kim Min-gee has two red chocolates
and one gold chocolate.
I was really surprised I got so many.
I'm certain one of the red hearts
was from Seung-il.
But it got complicated.
Because at the time, I was thinking
of going all in with Song Seung-il.
So it felt strange.
Youn Hyun-jae has one red chocolate.
Honestly, I thought my box would be empty.
I was a bit surprised I got a red one.
To be honest, my feelings
for Joo-young are so strong.
If it wasn't from her, I wouldn't be
that curious about who it's from.
I got two red hearts
and one gold heart.
I think the red hearts
are from Jae-jin and Hyun-jae.
Those were the confession vote results.
This is really rough.
I'm even more lost.
We will now play the Truth Game.
- I knew this would happen.
- So much dopamine.
No way…
What's this Truth Game?
Each of you will pick a question
from the box and answer it.
Can we skip our turn?
Me first?
You cannot refuse to answer.
Why not?
They can't refuse?
- There's no alternative?
- I guess not.
They took shots before to skip questions.
But now, they have to give an answer.
They have to answer.
- It's time for total honesty.
- How brutal.
- There's no escape.
- They can't lie.
That's so cruel.
Why is this season so brutal?
Now, Lim Su-been will go first.
- Do I open this here?
- Oh dear.
"Who is your top pick right now?"
How brutal.
How's that the first question?
- That's intense.
- So intense.
He has to say it in front of everyone.
- What's he going to do?
- That's crazy.
- It's his current pick.
- Yes, current.
- It could've changed.
- Hee-sun.
- Wouldn't he still say Mina Sue?
- I think it's Hee-sun.
He could still feel spiteful
and have chosen Hee-sun.
Man, this is so hard.
What's going on?
What's he doing?
- What?
- What is this?
- Where is he going?
- Is he going to throw it?
What's going on?
- Is he sitting next to her?
- He's sitting?
Really?
He has to sit next to his pick?
Did it say he had to move?
It's you.
"It's you"?
Poor Hee-sun!
It's too much.
Like A Midsummer Night's Dream…
Really?
- Gosh, Mina Sue is excited.
- Mina Sue's spite melted like snow.
- It's all gone now.
- Yes.
Really?
When I picked that question…
WHISPER IN THEIR EAR
…I was shocked and confused.
I knew I should pick Mina Sue,
but I felt shy admitting it.
When I said, "It's you,"
I didn't want anyone else to hear,
but it came out louder than I expected.
I was shocked.
During the confession vote,
I gave my red chocolate
to Sung-hun.
I really had no idea
that Su-been gave me his red chocolate.
I thought he gave it to Hee-sun.
Was there something else?
"Who is similar
to your ex-boyfriend and why?"
You can't refuse to answer.
What kind of question is that?
- What an awful question.
- Did she have to get the worst question?
- That's the worst.
- She has to talk about her ex.
Why'd she have to pick that one?
My answer is Su-been.
They look a bit similar.
Isn't that a bad thing?
- No, it could be a good thing.
- It's a good thing.
I wanted to take the chance to express
my interest in Su-been.
Honestly, they don't look that similar.
But I wanted to hint to Su-been
that I gave him my red chocolate.
There's nothing else.
Maybe there was more on his paper.
Depending on the question…
No, he just went over
because he wanted to.
I'm sure that's it. That's all.
We'll see if it's written.
- Wait, look at his expression.
- This is starting to scare me.
- What is it?
- Here comes a tough one.
- Why?
What is it?
Oh no.
"Who do you want to go
to Paradise with next?"
This is fun.
Do you have to sit beside her?
Next to your pick?
- Really? I guess it says so on the paper.
- This is wild.
- Go for it.
- How did I end up like this?
Do we have to get up?
Let's do a love shot.
What is this?
- What is this?
- This is wild.
- Oh my.
- Gosh.
- What is this?
- This is wild.
- Oh my.
- Gosh.
- There must be a mission.
- Really?
- Really.
- Hyun-jae.
I am appalled.
I should sober up.
- Hyun-jae…
- He must be annoyed.
Actions speak louder than words.
- It's impactful.
- Yes.
He left after doing that?
Going to Paradise with Joo-young
kind of solidified my feelings for her,
so I gave her my red heart.
And using my benefit as the winner,
I checked Joo-young's top picks
for who she was most interested in.
Upon seeing her picks,
I was happy to see that the results
turned out just as I'd anticipated.
1. KIM JAE-JIN,
2. SHIN HYEON-WOO, 3. YOUN HYUN-JAE
"Who is your top pick right now?"
WHISPER IN THEIR EAR
Gosh.
I realized that Hyeon-woo
was also interested in Go-eun.
"This will be interesting."
That's what I thought.
This is the worst.
"Which two people
received your chocolates?"
DON'T MENTION THE COLORS
These two.
On her left and right.
After winning the photoshoot mission,
I chose to see Hyeon-woo's rankings.
I was curious about how Hyeon-woo felt,
but I didn't have many chances
to talk with him,
so I was curious how he felt.
1. KIM MIN-GEE,
2. KIM GO-EUN, 3. CHOI MINA SUE
She checked Hyeon-woo's.
- She did.
- She was second?
Choi Mina Sue is included there, too.
How fascinating. She is always included.
- In third place.
- She's everywhere.
Seeing that I was his second pick
made me more curious about Hyeon-woo.
Knowing that she felt the same way I did
was very exciting.
I realized I had a chance with her, too.
"Who received your red chocolate?"
HOLD HANDS AND LOCK EYES FOR 10 SECONDS
What is this?
It says to lock eyes.
Gosh, what is this?
- This is intense.
- Really.
This is how it's going to be?
At the time,
I think they were both on my mind.
I felt the same about both of them.
They both lingered on my mind.
"Who do you want to go
to Paradise with next?"
SAY SOMETHING FLIRTY TO THEM
- My gosh.
- Mina Sue got a major question.
- It won't be Sung-hun, right?
- It'd be wild if it was him.
She did say Sung-hun was her top pick.
- But we can't trust the interviews.
- No, we can't.
Wait, she's moving.
Why don't we go together next time?
Wasn't he her third pick?
- That's a bold move.
- What was that?
Why don't we go together next time?
How interesting.
I'm kind of confused by this situation.
- It was a random choice.
- Everyone's confused.
This is honestly so confusing.
Didn't she say
Sung-min was her third pick?
- I'd understand if she chose Sung-hun.
- Same.
- She chose Sung-min, the one next to her.
- Su-been even expressed his feelings.
- Is she trying to make Su-been jealous?
- I don't think so.
Maybe it's because
she hasn't been to Paradise with him.
I thought she'd pick me.
But even if she chose someone else,
I didn't think it would be Sung-min.
Aside from doing the photoshoot together,
I don't think they interacted much,
so I was surprised and confused.
To explain my decision,
I had a really great time
doing the mission with both of them.
I chose him because I wanted
to get to know him better.
Do you want a snack?
No, thank you.
- Obviously.
- I wouldn't want one either.
Why add fuel to the fire?
"Which two people
received your chocolates?"
Gosh.
- Gosh.
- Two people?
The two ladies he picked.
It's Kim Min-gee and…
Choi Mina Sue.
- Really?
- Yes, I gave them to you two.
As soon as I read that, I thought,
"I'm screwed. Now everyone knows."
I've had my eye on only two women.
- You and--
- Is it Go-eun?
Not her.
Mary Sue.
- What? She's Mina Sue.
- Right, Mina Sue.
I thought Seung-il was the type
to go around showing interest in everyone.
But when he said that, I had an epiphany.
I realized I wasn't misreading it.
Seung-il actually had some interest in me.
That's when I began
to develop an interest in him.
- Now she's interested in him?
- Hang on.
Something is really wrong here.
Part of me thinks
she's going a bit too far.
But I wonder if this is okay.
I'm conflicted.
I understand she's trying
to explore her options,
but she's doing it
with whoever shows interest.
Yes, that's how it's going.
Now, Mina Sue is involved
with four people.
"Who do you want to go
to Paradise with next?"
Man, this is really…
- Link arms.
- Okay.
- She's saying, "He's mine."
- Yes, she's cool.
- She's a go-getter girl.
- Go-getter.
- Go-getter girl.
- She's so charming.
- Link arms.
- Okay.
She's a total girl crush.
Aside from Seung-il,
there wasn't really anyone else
I wanted to go with.
I wanted to express
more of my interest toward Seung-il.
I think I showed the others
that he's mine.
"Who is your top pick right now?"
Please choose quickly.
This is a nail-biter.
- Gosh.
- There's more.
- She's up to something.
- Excuse me.
What is she doing?
Why is she moving all of a sudden?
Hey there.
- Nice to see you.
- You too.
I had worked so hard to sit next to her,
so it was tough to see her go.
Joo-young wasn't paying me much attention.
I kept thinking about that.
What use is there
in making an effort for hours at a time?
It's over with one Truth Game.
"Who do you want to go to Paradise with?"
SAY SOMETHING FLIRTY TO THEM
Joo-young…
you have a beautiful smile.
Thank you.
I could see things were going well
between her and Jae-jin,
so I was worried it might put
too much pressure on Joo-young.
But I think I did well
in showing how I felt.
"Who received your gold chocolate?"
HOLD HANDS UNTIL YOUR NEXT TURN
There goes Hee-sun.
This is wild.
- Gold was for curiosity.
- Gold is for curiosity.
That's bad luck again.
Why did it have to be gold?
- It would've been great if it said red.
- Right?
- She's not so lucky.
- It's not working out for her.
- How unlucky.
- They're so random.
I'll pick one.
"Who do you want to go
to Paradise with next?"
TAKE A LOVE SHOT WITH THEM
Switching seats again?
Please move aside.
What is going on?
"Please move aside."
- Oh, come on.
- Seriously.
"Please move aside."
Let's do a love shot.
Gosh.
What are they doing?
What's with Jae-jin?
I can't believe this is really happening.
It's just a game.
This is kind of…
You can stay like this. It's fine.
- They have to keep holding hands?
- Yes, until her next turn.
- This is uncomfortable.
- It's okay.
"Who is your top pick right now?"
Will he say another name
while holding her hand?
Hey there.
- Oh my goodness!
- How cruel.
- What was that?
- That's mean.
This is unbelievable.
Who came up with this game?
- Who?
- He was holding her hand.
- But he chose someone else.
- Why are you guys so cruel?
- What is this?
- What…
- That was mean.
- This is so brutal.
- Poor Hee-sun.
- Right?
- This is so cruel to Hee-sun.
- I'm tearing up.
Hey there.
- Nice to see you.
- What is this?
This is like that meme of the couple
holding hands behind someone's back.
This is making me dizzy.
- My head hurts.
- It's chaos. My head aches.
"If you were to go to Paradise,
would you pick someone new
or someone you previously went with?"
- That's a tough one.
- It really is.
This is so fun.
She's choosing
between Hyeon-woo and Sung-min.
This will decide things.
I'm scared.
I'd pick someone new.
"Who do you want to go
to Paradise with next?"
Could he have changed his mind?
- What if he suddenly picks Mina Sue?
- Yes, what if he picks Mary Sue?
This is really tough.
Let's go again.
Oh gosh.
Is this a battle?
I'm not sure.
"Who is your top pick right now?"
Well…
Can I suddenly change my mind
in the middle of the game?
- Sung-hun?
- What is she saying?
What does she mean by that?
It's what you feel right now.
Is it Sung-hun?
She's saying this now
because things have changed.
This is crazy.
Can I suddenly change my mind
in the middle of the game?
- Of course.
- Go with your current feelings.
- Current pick.
- Current.
Her last pick isn't her current pick.
- Is she going to Sung-hun?
- Is it Sung-hun?
- What?
- Who is she going to?
- Who is it? It's not him?
- Really…
- Really?
- Earlier, Seung-il…
- Because she's his second pick?
- What?
This is absolutely wild.
Hello.
Isn't this interesting?
I want to go on a date with you.
That's when I started feeling a bit upset.
I was sure she'd pick me.
Didn't she say she was interested in me?
I became confused.
I think that moment was the most shocking.
Since she'd shown interest in Sung-min
and Su-been also went over
to whisper in her ear,
I didn't think she'd come here.
But she sat with him after all that.
- She's definitely honest.
- Too honest.
- She's just honest.
- Being honest is one thing.
How can her heart flip-flop like that?
- She was initially interested in Seung-il.
- Right.
She backed off
thinking he wasn't interested,
so when he expressed interest,
she came to a realization.
- Right.
- So she's expressing her feelings now.
"If you were to go to Paradise,
would you pick someone new
or someone you previously went with?"
- This is important.
- Yes. It's an important question.
What will he do?
I'd pick someone new.
Gosh, that's crazy.
Min-gee must feel so lost.
It's like a butterfly effect.
What are you doing?
I'd pick someone new.
"Who is your top pick right now?"
- Will Min-gee change her mind?
- She wouldn't.
- Don't switch. Go all the way.
- She might change her mind out of anger.
It's you. You.
There we go.
- This is it.
- Yes!
That's a true go-getter girl!
- Go-getter girl!
- Kim Min-gee!
You go girl!
- She's so charming.
- She's exploding with charm.
It's you. You.
Wow, so tough.
That's impressive.
That's amazing.
This is fun.
- She's cool.
- What a cool lady.
- That was iconic.
- So cool.
- Min-gee is so cool.
- She is.
I've become a fan of Kim Min-gee.
- You can't script that.
- No, you can't.
- What are the odds?
- Right?
This is really…
- I can't believe what I'm seeing.
- Let's review Mina Sue's feelings.
- Okay.
- Let's give it a try.
- Let's start.
- First, Su-been is most interested in her.
- So she kept him by her side.
- Yes.
But she gave the red heart to Sung-hun
in the confession vote.
Right.
Then she said she wants
to go to Paradise with Sung-min.
And now, she's suddenly
interested in someone new.
- Her current top pick.
- Her current interest.
- Seung-il.
- It's Seung-il.
- This season doesn't need a game changer.
- It doesn't.
Mina Sue is the game changer.
She's GC Mina Sue.
- "GC Mina Sue."
"GC" stands for game changer.
That's Mina Sue for you.
Of course, she's allowed
to make that choice.
- Of course.
- Everyone can.
- We can't criticize her.
- It's not bad.
- The rules allow it.
- Right.
But it's a shame that she doesn't care
about Su-been's feelings.
It surprised me
that she doesn't think twice
about how her actions could upset him.
Yes, exactly.
Regardless, Mina Sue is staying true
to the Single's Inferno spirit
and only focusing on love
and how to win it.
- Sure.
- What are you saying?
- If that's not the case--
- Be quiet if you have nothing to say.
Yes, stop.
- Don't say weird things.
- We should try to defend her.
- This is a mess. What will they do now?
- She doesn't need to be defended.
It's good to be honest,
but she could end up looking too selfish.
It's making everyone uncomfortable.
- Yes.
- This is wild.
Is Hee-sun still holding hands?
The Truth Game is now over.
Free time.
Can we talk?
- Want to talk to Hee-sun first?
- What?
- Hee-sun… Can we talk?
- You want to talk right now?
- Is that okay?
- Yes.
Mina, are you busy right now?
- I--
- Are you busy?
- Go ahead.
- Wait, I'm free.
- I can talk with him later.
- Really?
Do you want soju or beer?
A light beer?
- A light beer sounds good.
- Or we can get deep with some soju.
- Beer?
- Beer.
NEXT EPISODE
I've been curious
about the same two people from the start.
If you're curious…
This is like a horror movie.
You said you disliked indecisive people.
I'm annoyed.
I don't like seeing the person
I went to Paradise with around Hee-sun.
Honestly, I can't empathize
with Mina Sue anymore.
She's an unprecedented character.
I think I need to interrupt you guys.
Do you two need more time?
I'll go to the restroom. Be done by then.
Set a timer, will you?
- They're practically fighting with words.
- It was a verbal fistfight.
Now, we will begin the one-on-one dates.
- A game changer.
- A new woman.
She looks very innocent.
Is that a man?
There's a man, too?
What does he look like?
- I got goosebumps.
- It's a game changer.
Two game changers at once?
I'm intrigued by someone.
- What?
- Again?
- I wonder who it is.
- Who is it now?
Who am I? I'm Choi Mina Sue.
Mina Sue, do everything you want.
Is it possible
to leave Single's Inferno with two men?
Subtitle translation by: Eunice Kim