- Oh, my.
- What's going on?
We're getting new contestants now?
- What is this?
- What's going on?
What kind of format is this?
I guess we have another male contestant.
What?
Or maybe not.
I thought, "This is mind-blowing."
The show's full of twists and turns.
I appreciate it, though.
This means I have more options to explore.
I thought, "That can't be."
But I was right.
I was so startled
to see more people join us
and relieved to learn
I wasn't out of the game.
I'm relieved that we have new people.
Hello, my name is Lim Su-been.
I've never experienced
love at first sight.
I hoped to find someone
who would steal my heart instantly,
so I applied to be on the show.
Many have told me I'm mature.
I've often been told
that I have golden retriever energy.
I get told that I look sexy
when I work out.
- He's got a toned body.
- Hot damn.
- Insane!
- How are they so fit?
I'm good with all kinds
of athletic activities.
I go to the gym every day,
and I also enjoy swimming
and playing baseball.
My ideal type is a tall woman.
I'd like to meet someone
with the same allure as Ms. Lee Da-hee.
- Da-hee!
- Da-hee.
What's this?
Perhaps over a team dinner…
See? We need one.
- Let's do it.
- Let's fix a date.
- He picked you out right away.
- Da-hee.
He's playing a whole different game.
I want to meet someone in Inferno
and make our relationship public.
- He's good-looking.
- Doesn't he resemble Song Joong-ki?
- Yes, I can see that.
- Right?
- He's like a movie star.
- He's so fine.
- Hello.
Hello.
Su-been
is pretty close to my ideal type,
when it comes to looks.
I'm not sure how to explain it.
I guess you could say I like what I see.
- Wait.
- There's another guy?
- We have seven men, then.
- Really?
This is wild.
- This is even better.
- They're all confused.
- I see another guy.
- It's a man again.
Yes, it's a guy again.
It's a man again.
What's going on?
Seven men…
Hello, I'm Lee Sung-hun.
I currently live in New York.
People tell me I sound cute
when I speak Korean.
I guess I come across as sharper
when I speak English
because I can express myself more clearly.
I think my warmth, competence,
and hidden charm are what attract people.
I'm the best in my field of expertise.
He feels so different.
He's so cool.
He's so unique.
- Hello.
Hello.
So, we only have two women.
- Did he just…
- He did say he was straightforward.
That's the worst way to break the ice.
- He could be serious.
- He's hilarious.
- It's a terrible line.
- Definitely.
"We only have two women."
He didn't mean anything bad.
- He's disappointed.
- But it's an awful line.
- Disappointed, all right.
So, we only have two women.
Well, yes. For now.
Why are there only two?
- It's a woman.
- It is.
Here comes another woman.
I'm relieved.
If it were another man…
My gosh.
Come on, Sung-hun.
- He's hilarious.
- He's just awkward.
- Hello.
Hello.
Hello, my name is Lee Joo-young.
I've been popular
since the day I was born.
This isn't our first rodeo.
I swear our writers
didn't feed her that line.
- I guess she was a popular infant.
- "A popular infant."
When I was a teenager,
I was nicknamed the school's goddess.
I had guys fighting over me
in the men's room.
I'm often told I'm like a ray of sunshine.
I may look calm and elegant,
but I have a bubbly personality.
People often call me a smart cookie.
True to my nickname, I'll be smart
and find my love on Single's Inferno.
I love her dimples.
- She's striking.
- Yes.
Among the newcomers,
Joo-young had the most memorable
first impression.
She has such a bright smile,
and that stood out to me.
We won't get more contestants, right?
I see someone coming.
- There's more?
- More people?
She looks really tall.
Hello, my name is Choi Mina Sue.
I can be rather self-centered
in a relationship.
What can I say? I like myself the most.
I can't help but prioritize myself
even when I'm in a relationship.
I don't think that's a bad thing, though.
I'm not that big on all-out, fancy dates.
A date over chicken feet
sounds perfect to me.
In terms of physique,
I like guys with full lips
and broad shoulders.
I, too, have broad shoulders,
so I want a guy who can cuddle me.
I'm a ball of fire,
so I enjoy high-energy sports.
I especially love scuba diving.
It gives me peace of mind.
What is my resolve going in?
Are you all ready to fall for me?
She's so graceful.
- Totally.
- Yes.
- She's a charmer.
- She really is.
She'll put the other ladies on edge.
Hello.
I'll take a seat here.
The smile on Hee-sun's face
has been wiped away.
- Gosh, Hee-sun.
- Finally.
- Oh, no.
- What do we do?
- She must feel threatened.
- She really is a strong contender.
Yellow looks great on you.
Really? I was rather worried
it might not look good on me.
What's your name?
I'm Choi Mina Sue.
- Four syllables.
- Choi Mina Sue? Okay.
I'm Lee Sung-hun.
YOUN HYUN-JAE
SONG SEUNG-IL
PARK HEE-SUN
SHIN HYEON-WOO
KIM GO-EUN
KIM JAE-JIN
HAM YE-JIN
WOO SUNG-MIN
KIM MIN-GEE
LIM SU-BEEN
LEE SUNG-HUN
LEE JOO-YOUNG
CHOI MINA SUE
SINGLE'S INFERNO
Greetings, newly joined singles.
Today's Paradise-bound
couple matching is over.
What does that mean?
- We did it earlier.
- Really?
I don't get it.
Does Mina Sue know?
- Mina…
"Does Mina Sue know?"
Goodness. He's too much.
Sung-hun is hilarious.
The four of you are the newcomers.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Have the others already left?
Oh, man. That must mean
we can't go to Paradise today.
Not today, no.
But I'm starving right now.
You can go tomorrow.
I didn't even get to see the others.
That was rather disappointing.
I look forward to seeing the others go,
"Hey, there's a new face."
I can't wait to see their reaction.
Did I sound overly confident?
Gosh, she's so gorgeous.
She has that natural grace.
- Yes.
- It's like…
- It's not forced.
- It's genuine.
She's hard to beat.
Today's Paradise-bound
couple matching is over.
- But we have four newcomers.
- Right.
The newcomers
have a whole new set of charms.
- They are no joke.
- I totally agree.
Out of the new contestants,
who do you think will be most popular?
Choi Mina Sue by a landslide.
- Same here.
- Right?
She's the type the guys will fall for.
She seems so sincere.
- Guileless, even.
- I agree.
She gives off a natural and fresh vibe.
I agree.
She has elegance.
- She does.
- Exactly.
She's got a face you'd never get bored of.
She's beautiful and elegant,
but I think younger men
may find it hard to approach her first.
- She has that aura.
- She does.
She has a certain vibe.
- As for Su-been, he's the serious type.
- Yes.
A guy like him is typically popular.
- He's Mr. Popular.
- Spot on.
Don't you find a guy like that
somewhat unapproachable?
I think the women
might feel that way about Su-been.
- What do you think about Su-been?
- Well…
I think it depends on
how he carries conversations.
Are you picturing yourself talking to him?
She's not joking.
I was being dead serious.
- It's dinner time.
- Okay, let's get it.
- I can't wait.
- I hope we'll get some rice.
- What if we get carrots again?
- Carrots?
I love carrots.
- We've had enough, haven't we?
- We did.
- You've already had some.
- Yes.
- What is it?
- I wonder what it is.
Hey, I'm getting chills.
Shall we open them?
- It's a map.
- A map.
What's this? A treasure hunt?
The canned food is in the pool.
This is seriously…
My gosh, in the pool?
- That's water.
- Water.
- I see chickens, too.
- Oh, for eggs?
- There are vegetables.
- We'll have to harvest them.
They have to work for their food.
- They have to go get it.
- They have to earn their food.
Do we have to go harvest food?
- Yes.
- I see.
Are you good at digging?
Then, can you two go harvest them?
You mean us?
Okay, we'll go get them, then.
- Let's do this.
- Okay.
How about we go collect the eggs?
I'll go get water, then.
Shouldn't we send two guys to get water?
I'll join you.
- Okay. Let's go together.
- Yes.
- Off we go.
- Let's go.
See you later.
Good luck.
Let's do this.
Which way do we go?
- So, you speak English?
- Yes, English is more comfortable for me.
- I can tell.
- What? No way. My Korean is excellent.
- Your Rs give you away.
- Really?
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Hold on. Where are we going?
Is it that, over there?
KITCHEN GARDEN
What even is a kimchi garden?
"Kimchi garden."
- "Kimchi garden"?
- Is he actually from abroad?
Kimchi garden…
- It must be because of the cursive.
- Oh, sure.
- Shouldn't it be easier for him?
- Why would that give him any trouble?
Having someone here who speaks English
- makes me feel at ease.
- Same here.
Are you familiar with the Korean phrase
"subjective intimacy?"
- I'm not great with colloquialisms.
- Really? Well…
- Really?
- Of course.
- He has fallen in love.
- His gaze has gone lovey-dovey.
I think Sung-hun is quick to fall in love.
- What's your ideal type, by the way?
- My type?
- I have a question for you, actually.
- Ask away.
Are you okay with non-English speakers?
Actually, I find it a bit hard.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I'd be your only option, then.
- Honestly, it's difficult.
Oh, well…
I guess?
Or maybe not.
Look over there.
- I can see the chickens.
- Goodness.
CHICKEN COOP
- You can manage, right? I'll stand watch.
- What do you mean?
The eggs are inside.
What do we do?
- Can you do it?
- No way.
- Really?
- Can we actually go in?
- Don't you want eggs?
- Of course I do.
Why is everything so difficult?
- Gosh, their wings…
- They've come to greet us.
How many should we get?
- Two.
- Two?
Hey, guys.
Excuse me. Coming through.
What's the name of the guy
who walked into the coop?
- That's Seung-il.
- He's Seung-il.
- He's Seung-il?
- Your favorite.
- Oh, was he?
- Yes.
- "Was he?"
- I forgot.
He's an old fling.
- He's my ex.
- "My ex."
Hey, guys.
Excuse me. Coming through.
- They're not flying.
- Come on in. They don't fly.
Sorry, guys. Let me get these eggs.
Take one, Go-eun.
Are these all?
One, two, three, four, five. Let's go.
- I'll get going, guys.
- Thanks. We'll enjoy them. Sorry.
- Watch your steps.
- Got it.
They might follow us out. Oh, no.
No, wait.
Gosh, what do I do?
He's mischievous.
No, wait.
Gosh, what do I do?
What do we do?
What do we do? Get back in.
- Hey.
- Hold on.
Hey.
Come on. This way.
There we go. Get in there.
- Come here.
- Follow her lead.
Great job.
- Oh, dear.
- You should've let me out, not the hen.
- Gosh.
- Easy-peasy.
What on earth?
- Are they pranking us?
- Seriously. What do we do?
Do we have to get that?
Wait, the food…
Are they actually in there?
I thought we'd find a small pond here.
- Me too.
- What's all this?
- Can you do it?
- I'll see what I can do.
CHALLENGE AREA
I'll stay here you can throw it.
- He might fall.
- What if he falls?
- It'd be humiliating.
- Exactly.
- It'd be a nightmare.
- Oh, no.
- I see Hee-sun's pair over there.
- Yes.
My gosh, he's actually doing it?
- Isn't that very challenging?
- You bet it is.
- How is he doing it?
- Showcase your charm.
- It looks like he'll fall.
- No, he'd never fall.
That's cool.
My gosh.
Gosh, it fell.
- Oh, dear.
- What now?
Poor guy.
He could've just shaken the rope
to drop the sack and collect it.
Yes, if it was going to fall anyway.
Gosh, it fell.
Hold on.
What do we do?
- We chose well.
- I would've dived in.
We've made a wise choice.
Hey, it's coming my way.
Come here.
Are you okay?
Is it…
I mean,
he should've just gone in earlier.
Both the sack and Hyun-jae
ended up falling into the pond.
- It's a shame because he was so close.
- Yes, so close.
- It didn't even look cool.
- I know.
- Shall we start the fire, then?
- Sounds good.
- Be careful.
- That should get the fire going.
It looks like something's
going on between them.
- Right?
- You bet.
Is there anything going on between us?
- Nothing, don't you think?
- Really?
- There's nothing?
- But good vibes.
What can we make with potatoes?
- Can we just…
- I wonder what the food team will bring.
How's this?
We could stir-fry the potatoes.
What do you think?
- Good idea.
- Right?
In that case…
- I think that's ssamjang.
- We've got ssamjang?
- Do we have a strainer?
- You can find one over there.
In here.
- This one?
- I'll take that, Go-eun.
Pass me the washed potatoes.
- Got it.
- I'll peel them.
How can I help, Mina?
Let me think.
What else is left?
- Why don't I--
- Can you set the table?
- Set the table?
- No?
- She's sending him away.
- It means "Go over there."
"Go over there"?
I can do that later.
I'll do it then.
- Oh, no. I'll do it then.
- We can do it together.
Hey, that's a good idea.
I'm sorry, but what's your name?
- I'm Go-eun.
- Oh, you're Kim Go-eun?
- That's right.
- Okay.
- How was harvesting the potatoes?
- It wasn't bad, actually.
Really?
- Are you done with them?
- Yes, just a second.
We've made it back. Good work.
- You too.
- Are you okay?
- Yes
- Yes.
Are you sure?
I saw you doing something cool.
- This sack was up there--
- What's inside the sack?
- Canned tuna.
- The whole lot?
Then, let's mix the tuna with gochujang.
- For spicy tuna?
Sounds good.
What's it called…
- Do we have spatulas?
- Spatulas?
- Do we need some?
- They're inside, I think.
Where are they?
Do we have spatulas?
- A tool to mix stuff?
- To mix stuff?
- I'll wash one for you.
- Oh, here it is.
- Something like this?
- I think so.
Hee-sun is right next to Su-been.
- Remember what she said?
- That he's her type.
- She likes him.
- That's why.
I get it now.
How are you feeling?
- I'm a bit hungry.
- Right?
But I'll be fine once we eat.
- You must be hungry, too.
- Yes, I'm starving.
Thank you.
- Shall I pour it in?
- Yes.
- This is scary.
- Go ahead.
What are we having?
Scrambled eggs.
It wasn't hot enough,
but there's no going back.
- Hey, we're done for.
- No, we're not.
- We can wait a bit…
- Wait for it.
It's not over till it's over.
- Understood. Yes.
- Okay?
I'll cook it nicely.
Am I doing it right?
We'll probably get
a softer texture this way.
- I agree.
- It's cooking slowly.
Like an omelet, you know.
I think it'll taste amazing.
Was the yellow dress your first choice?
No, I actually had two options.
I wanted to wear white, actually.
If you think about it, only a few people
can pull off a yellow outfit.
Did I look okay?
All I could see was you.
- Really?
- Yes.
Seung-il and Jae-jin are so charming,
but in different ways.
- But both are--
- Jae-jin?
Yes.
Jae-jin wasn't even in the footage.
- You keep--
- They are her favorites.
She's comparing her favorites.
- That startled me.
- The way I see it,
Go-eun is interested in Seung-il.
Go-eun is into Seung-il?
Yes, remember how Seung-il and Mina Sue
tried their best to send
Go-eun and Sung-hun to set the table?
- But she kept returning to the sink.
- I see.
- To go back to Seung-il?
- Right.
- She did that?
- You've gotten so sharp.
- I'm amazed you caught that detail.
- I hope you're wrong, though.
How come?
I seriously hope it turns out
you misinterpreted things big time.
Because of her great track record?
- You're so confident.
- I'd like to see you get it wrong.
I'm hesitant
because I got everything wrong.
- Enjoy.
- Let's enjoy the meal.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
You're quick.
Okay. Then…
Dig in. You two can go ahead.
Take some.
Go ahead.
What happened to your hand?
- My gosh.
- What's wrong?
- When did you get hurt?
- I don't know.
Maybe when we got the water?
- I see.
- Oh, no.
- You're bleeding.
- It's nothing.
- It is a big deal.
- Not at all. Enjoy your meal.
Shouldn't we apply some salve now?
It's all right.
Would you like some potatoes?
Yes please.
Isn't it good?
- Can I have some potatoes too?
- Me too.
- Do we have some more left?
- Sure.
Potatoes saved the day.
- Here.
- Potatoes.
Thank you.
How's your hand?
- It's fine. Don't worry about it.
- Are you hurt?
I didn't realize, but yes.
Really?
- I'd say Go-eun is pretty into Hyeon-woo.
- Right, I think so too.
- I think she's just playing the game.
- Pardon?
- She's leading him on.
- Really?
- Are you set on going against me?
- What? No.
I just think she's baiting him.
At first,
Go-eun seemed the type
to enchant all the guys.
- I thought so, too.
- I don't think it'll work.
It won't go according to her plans?
- I wish we had time to talk with them.
- Totally.
We've only had group activities so far.
Yes.
What do you look for in a man?
I like manly guys,
but I want them to have
a cute side and composure.
What about you, Go-eun?
I'm into left-handed guys.
- Why?
- Really?
I don't know why,
but they always get me interested.
That's interesting.
We actually have a lefty.
She must've noticed.
- Could it be Hyeon-woo?
- How did she…
- Did you see one earlier?
- Yes.
Who is the lefty?
Hyeon-woo is left-handed.
- See? That explains things.
- Yes.
- That's why she felt drawn to him.
- I'm surprised she saw that.
You'll now choose the person
you are interested in.
What?
What do we do?
- My gosh.
- I've got goose bumps.
Please find a postcard in your lodging
and write a candid note
to the person you're interested in.
Then, slide the card into the mailbox
with their name on it.
It's the moment of truth.
Let's make predictions
about who'd write to whom.
I think Mina Sue
will receive multiple cards.
- Me too.
- Same here.
I think Seung-il
is definitely interested in Mina Sue.
- The same goes for Sung-hun.
- Exactly.
But I don't think Mina Sue
is that into Sung-hun.
- Agreed.
- Really?
- She's not interested.
- Right.
If she liked him,
she wouldn't have sent him away.
In Hee-sun's case,
she's practically smitten with Su-been.
- I saw her tend to him over the meal.
- Yes.
- Hee-sun and Su-been.
- But Su-been hasn't shown any interest.
- Right.
- I'm not sure about him.
MEN'S MAILBOXES
That guy's hilarious.
What's his name again?
Sam…
He's really funny.
Even when I don't want to laugh,
he makes me burst into laughter.
Something happened.
- He made her laugh.
- I think so.
- Sung-hun has his charms.
- With his sense of humor.
LEE SUNG-HUN: 0 VOTES
- She got our hopes up for nothing.
- Seriously.
Poor guy.
Things are rough.
- Are you putting on an act?
- Sorry?
- You're acting, aren't you?
- No, I'm not.
- Did you receive five cards?
- No way.
- You're acting out of pity for us.
- Never.
It's tough here in Inferno.
I didn't get any postcards.
It's Su-been.
- He'll get one vote at least.
- That's guaranteed.
- He's got one.
- He does.
"You're my ideal type."
How cute is that?
I'LL START A CONVERSATION!
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT
- You can tell who wrote it from the tone.
- Yes.
LIM SU-BEEN: 1 VOTE
It said that I was her ideal type.
I think Hee-sun wrote it.
I could be wrong, but it felt like
she was glancing my way.
- I'm a bit hungry.
- Right?
- It'd be hard to not notice.
- I know.
- He's shameless for playing dumb.
- She's merely inches away.
Gosh, you startled me.
- She was like this.
- Yes, this is--
She had no reason to be standing there.
You could get splashed there.
- To stand there at that angle…
- She's like this.
Exactly.
YOUN HYUN-JAE: 0 VOTES
He's got nothing.
- It's not going well.
- He's having a rough time.
Oh, it's Hyeon-woo.
- We can expect two votes.
- At most.
One from Go-eun?
This is difficult.
- There's just one.
- Just one?
"Let's get to know each other better."
"Great work today."
SHIN HYEON-WOO: 1 VOTE
- One vote.
- That's from Go-eun.
It's from Go-eun.
- Seung-il got two votes.
- Yes.
SONG SEUNG-IL: 2 VOTES
I'd say those votes
came from Go-eun and Mina Sue.
- Come on, not Go-eun.
- But Go-eun…
Don't you think Go-eun chose Hyeon-woo?
No, she's only keeping him on the hook.
Then, who do you think chose Hyeon-woo?
- How would I know?
- He's got a vote--
I'm not an actual fortune teller, am I?
Hey, hold on. That must be from Mina Sue.
- Of course. They scrambled eggs together.
- Yes. Didn't I say she'd vote for him?
The other one might not be from Go-eun.
- Let's see what the other one says.
- Yes.
Right, let's see.
"The meal was great.
Next time, let's eat alone."
- What?
- That's just…
That's not enough for us to guess on.
There's not much to go on.
This is hard.
I received two postcards.
I honestly didn't think I'd get any,
so I felt grateful to find two postcards.
I also think that the ladies
might welcome it if I took the initiative.
WOMEN'S MAILBOXES
- I'll be back soon.
- See you.
- Off you go.
- Bye.
I hope I'll get at least one vote.
- I have a terrible poker face.
- Same here.
- Let's see how it is for Joo-young.
- Joo-young.
- I think she'll get one.
- I agree.
Or maybe not.
LEE JOO-YOUNG
- She's got one.
- She does.
"I'll talk to you tomorrow."
LEE JOO-YOUNG: 1 VOTE
It was something of a declaration.
I kept wondering,
"Who had I not talked to today?"
I kept going over that question.
Why am I so nervous?
I'm so nervous.
We've decided not to say anything.
- You have to come in with a long face.
- Yes.
So they're not going to let it show?
But Joo-young's face
is radiating with happiness.
How can she not feel happy?
Is that Hee-sun?
- Yes.
- Hee-sun.
- I'm worried about Hee-sun.
- She must be nervous.
I hope she gets one.
I think she got one.
- I hope she got one.
- Did she?
- She's got one.
- Has she?
- How could they?
- She didn't get any?
I'm heartbroken.
That means Su-been
didn't give her his vote.
- Yes.
- Right?
But she's gone this far
to make her interest obvious.
- How could he not?
- He likes someone else.
- He voted for someone else.
- Really?
PARK HEE-SUN: 0 VOTES
You have to look upset.
You look so tired, Hee-sun.
You're spot on. I'm worn out.
I didn't get any postcards.
It saddened me not to receive any.
- My gosh.
- How many are there?
- Oh, man.
- She received three votes?
- I knew it.
- She's very likable.
- Totally.
- She's genuine.
- She's relaxed.
- Right.
- I guess we all get the same vibes.
- She must be over the moon.
- Oh, my. What is she going to do?
"The yellow dress looked great on you.
It suits your personality."
"I want to get to know you better."
- That's from Seung-il for sure.
- Of course.
He's sending a clear message.
- Totally.
- He's practically saying it's him.
"It's a shame we didn't get to chat much.
You looked amazing in that yellow dress."
The yellow dress got mentioned again.
But he said he didn't get to talk to her,
so it must be Su-been.
- Su-been?
- Oh, him.
- It must be.
- I think it's him.
"Thanks for cooking today.
Let's get to know each other better."
- That's from Sung-hun.
- It's from Sung-hun.
- The handwriting gave him away.
- It has to be from him.
CHOI MINA SUE: 3 VOTES
I was scared out of my mind
because of the bugs out there.
It felt amazing.
But when I returned to our shared room,
I tried my best not to show it.
I don't think anyone caught on.
- I'm guessing Hyeon-woo wrote to her.
- Me too.
"Let's get better acquainted.
It was nice meeting you today."
KIM GO-EUN: 1 VOTE
I want to see it again.
The anonymous note said,
"I hope we get to know each other better."
Seung-il was the one
I got to talk to the most.
What?
- What was that?
- Who did she say just now?
We went to the chicken coop together,
so I'm guessing Seung-il wrote that note.
I gave my postcard to Seung-il.
See? All my predictions
are turning out to be correct.
Why did Go-eun show concern for Hyeon-woo?
I wrote a letter to Mina Sue.
I wanted her to know that I wrote it,
so I mentioned that I thought
the yellow dress suited her.
She was someone
I felt most drawn to
when we first met as a group.
I wanted to talk to her more over dinner,
but I didn't get to do that
because we sat too far apart.
It was a shame.
The person I addressed
my card to on the first day was Seung-il.
Well…
We prepared the scrambled eggs together,
and that gave us a chance to chat a bit.
I found him charming then,
so I wrote "egg" on my postcard
and slid it into Seung-il's mailbox.
I wrote to Mina.
Mina and I worked
in the Kitchen Garden,
and I had a lovely time with her.
In my card to Mina Sue,
I complimented her on her dress
and added that I'd like
to get to know her better.
Even if Hee-sun voted for me,
I still want to focus my energy
on Mina Sue.
So it won't change my mind.
I wrote my postcard to Su-been.
I straight out stated that he was my type.
The person I addressed
my anonymous postcard to last night
was Go-eun.
I thought that we had
something of a strong bond…
How's your hand?
- Oh, it's fine. Don't worry about it.
- Are you hurt?
I didn't realize, but yes.
I'm hoping Go-eun is the one
who sent me the postcard.
I addressed my postcard to Hyeon-woo.
I only met everyone yesterday,
and he caught my eye
when I first walked in.
So, I wrote to him.
I addressed my postcard to Joo-young.
I have a thing for ladies
with a beautiful smile,
and she had such a lovely smile.
So, I wrote my postcard to Joo-young.
I thought I should start
expressing my interest
in Joo-young more from tomorrow.
This is pretty complicated,
so let me check one thing.
Are any of them into each other?
- Yes. Mina Sue and Seung-il.
- Mina Sue and Seung-il.
Other than those two,
- it's all gone haywire, right?
- Yes.
Joo-young wrote to Hyeon-woo,
but Hyeon-woo wrote to Go-eun.
Go-eun wrote to Seung-il. This is just…
But the couples in Paradise
aren't particularly into their partner.
It's rather awkward there, too.
Things are bound to get spiced up
when they return the next day.
Jae-jin will be back tomorrow.
- Oh, yes.
- Jae-jin…
- You remembered him.
- It should be fun.
It's almost like the calm
before the storm.
I feel a whirlwind of emotions coming.
- Of course.
- I'm sure of it.
- Let's eat breakfast.
- Sounds good.
There's hot water. Are we having ramyeon?
We have apples.
Apples.
What's this?
- I'm guessing it's oatmeal.
- Oatmeal.
How do you eat oatmeal?
- You pour hot water--
- And soak the oatmeal.
Shall we prep the oatmeal, then?
- Yes. Let's do that.
- Let's go.
I guess we're in charge of the apples.
Where did everyone go?
How was last night for you?
- Last night?
- Yes.
Do you mean after checking the letters?
Yes.
All the men said things were rough here.
- How come?
- I'm not sure.
Did you get any?
I'd say things were slightly rough for me.
Really?
I wonder why.
I'm not saying I didn't get any.
- Hee-sun wrote to him, didn't she?
- Yes.
Let's go check out the oatmeal.
I've been wanting to talk to you.
- Really?
- Yes.
Come on.
She's practically trailing after him.
She's like a puppy.
Didn't you realize?
Oh, I mean…
Are we allowed to be open about it?
I don't think I've said anything.
All we need to do is slightly…
He still went over to where everyone was.
- I know.
- When she wanted to chat.
He said he's interested in Mina Sue.
- He said he wanted to get to know her.
- Right.
- Shall we dig in, then?
- Yes.
- I'm starving.
- It looks delicious.
Can I take a seat here?
Of course.
- Did you prepare this?
- Yes, it's oatmeal.
It looks incredible.
- Is this too much?
- I'll try my best.
When will the ones in Paradise return?
Pretty soon, probably.
I hear one of the ladies
won the popularity votes.
- Yes.
- That's right.
Can you tell me why?
I guess I just felt drawn to her.
She has that easygoing vibe.
- Come again?
- She seems very down-to-earth.
Did you just vote without getting to talk?
Yes, we were just sitting here.
- Right here?
- Yes.
We were eating canned food
when we were told to cast our votes.
- My gosh.
- It was over carrots.
So basically,
she seemed easygoing
while eating carrots and chicken breast,
so you voted for her?
She was sitting to my right.
A casual conversation can tell you
if the other person is easygoing or not.
We didn't have enough time
to talk properly.
Why did that upset her?
- Because she's interested in him.
- Yes, but…
But is it such a big deal
for her to be that upset?
So that's how guys think.
Also, I think Seung-il
just spoke on behalf of the guys.
Totally.
But Mina Sue seems
to have misinterpreted it
as his own point of view.
That's probably why she's more upset.
Judging by Mina Sue's expression,
she likes him a lot.
- Totally.
- I know.
I didn't think she liked him that much.
- I suppose they're all waiting for us.
- Right?
Hey, they're coming back.
They're here.
- I can see them.
- What?
They're here.
No way. Really? Where are they?
- I see some new people.
- Latecomers.
- Are they latecomers?
- I see more people.
I'm curious.
They must be startled, too.
I guess,
because four more people are here.
- Did they come yesterday?
- What's this?
My gosh.
- How many came?
- What's going on?
You said she's easygoing,
so I can't wait to meet her.
Hello.
- Hello.
Welcome back.
We're back.
- Hey, they're having a nice meal.
- At least they have a decent meal today.
- Did you have breakfast?
- Yes, sort of.
- Didn't you have fancy meals?
- Not at all.
Seung-il gave me
a brief introduction of Min-gee.
He described her as an easygoing person,
and I could tell who it was right away.
I am rather interested in Seung-il,
so I can't help but be bothered by her.
Hey, so we're all rooming together.
We're home.
- Hello.
Sweet dreams, guys.
I didn't get any sleep.
- I guess you couldn't have.
- I want a nap.
I'd like to know
if you chose your partner
or if you were chosen.
- She won the most votes…
- Wow.
And so, she chose Sung-min.
What are the guys like?
Sung-min is the calm type.
- Really?
- He's quiet.
But he seems…
- Right? He seems lively.
- Yes.
- He seems lively.
- But he's calm.
- Seriously?
- He's unflappable.
That's how he is.
- That's him being the most expressive.
- I guess he's very calm.
He's being as communicative as he can.
He was more quiet
and calmer than I thought.
Want a bite?
But seriously you look so cute.
That cuteness is your weapon.
You're holding onto dynamite.
- No comment, please.
- Sure.
He's really avoiding eye contact.
I wonder what the others are doing.
- Me too.
- Yes.
I wonder if they feel at ease like us.
- You're feeling at ease?
- Yes.
- There's no excitement?
- We're chill.
I mean, there's an easygoing vibe
under the excitement.
Isn't it the other way around?
- Aren't they basically the same?
- I get it.
- So you're not excited.
- My heart does flutter.
- Oh, sure.
- Yes, it really does.
I hear you.
- You must be excited.
- Yes.
- He doesn't look excited at all.
- No.
- It's over for them.
- Yes, it is.
What's Jae-jin like?
Can't you just picture it?
Is he a tough guy?
- Does he seem that way to you?
- Isn't he?
He does look like a tough guy.
He's very calm.
- He's calm too?
- Really?
- They're both calm?
As we kept on chatting,
I couldn't help but notice
where we didn't click.
That's the only thing for us to look at.
What do you think it is?
- Balloons.
- Balloons?
Bean sprouts.
Bean sprouts?
The end.
Do you want to know what Type N sees?
Yes. I'm intrigued.
Answers don't mean much to Type Ns.
We keep on imagining things.
"Why do we have a tree-shaped figure
adorned with balloon-shaped ovals?"
I don't think I want to know.
They are shaped like branches, right?
- That's true. With--
- One trunk and many others branching out.
Try imagining just a bit more.
- Over that sculpture?
- Yes, now I'm curious.
Well…
They probably put it there
to prevent it from looking empty.
Right? Imagine it not being there.
His sense of humor
and mine weren't exactly compatible.
Look what we have here.
Don't you think putting it on your mouth
would make it hard to breathe?
- This is new.
- I know.
That left me on edge,
thinking and second-guessing
what I should do and how I should react.
I must've run 50 simulations at a time.
That wore me out.
While this is upsetting to admit,
I doubt I'd ever feel drawn to him.
Ye-jin must not have felt
a spark between them either.
The Paradise dates matter.
Is it too early to discuss
who we're interested in?
Is there anyone
you are interested in, or not?
- I can't say yet.
- Not yet?
Mina seems to have someone in mind.
I keep going back and forth,
so I'm not so sure.
Yeah…
I think Mina Sue
would be the most popular.
First of all,
she radiates this wholesome energy.
I think her charms
are pretty similar to mine.
She's always confident.
I think she's very charming.
That scared me!
In a few moments, you will play a game
to win a special treat.
Please get changed
and gather at the beach.
For goodness' sake…
This is wild.
Here we go.
- It's about time they played one.
- Single's Inferno.
- Are we playing dodgeball?
- Looks like we'll be drawing balls.
Today's game is Couple Dodgeball.
- I knew it.
- It's as we expected.
- I was right, wasn't I?
- Yes, you were.
Are we defending the women?
Once the game begins,
the women must stand
behind the men they're partnered with.
Only men can make offensive moves,
and the couple must maintain
physical contact at all times.
A couple is eliminated
if they lose contact
or if the woman is hit by the ball
thrown by an opposing team's player.
So women can't throw the ball.
- We need to dodge well.
- Right.
What a bummer.
The last surviving couple's team
will be declared the winners.
It's a team competition.
The final winners will receive
an Iced Americano and watermelon slices
as a special treat.
Americano!
- I'd kill for that coffee.
- Me too.
- I'm going to win no matter what.
- I want them.
We will now begin the draw.
However, the male contestant
who picks the pink ball
will not be able to participate
in the game.
That's so cruel.
- Please…
- I want that cold drink.
- Kim Min-gee, please draw a ball.
- Yes. Okay.
It's a gray ball.
KIM GO-EUN, BLUE BALL
I got a red ball.
LEE JOO-YOUNG, BLACK BALL
I got the yellow one.
CHOI MINA SUE, WHITE BALL
Why do I feel I'll pick pink?
I got a flash of the future.
Same here.
I think I'll end up with the pink ball.
Youn Hyun-jae, please draw a ball.
Gray. Kim Min-gee and Youn Hyun-jae.
Let's take first place. Great.
I swear I'll make you the winner.
- I promise.
- Great.
I'll dodge the ball like crazy.
Wow.
LEE SUNG-HUN, PINK BALL
- He can't seem to catch a break.
- Tell me about it.
Wow.
Oh, no.
It was the worst.
I was so disappointed
to be barred from the game.
I wanted to get to know Mina,
so I wanted to be paired up with her.
- He must've wanted to play.
- I feel bad for him.
He drew the pink ball.
LEE SUNG-HUN CANNOT PARTICIPATE
Blue. Kim Go-eun and Woo Sung-min.
I marveled at my good luck.
I initially chose Go-eun
during the first impression pick.
YESTERDAY
The person I'd like to go to Paradise with
is Go-eun.
Because I was attracted
to her vibes.
I made my decision
based on her first impression
and the energy I got from her
when we first met.
Red. Ham Ye-jin and Song Seung-il.
- Yellow. Park Hee-sun and Shin Hyeon-woo.
- Yellow.
- Black.
- Black. Lee Joo-young and Kim Jae-jin.
Hey, the white ball was picked last.
White. Choi Mina Sue and Lim Su-been.
I was paired up with Mina Sue
just as I had hoped.
I thought this was my shot.
Even before the game was announced,
Mina Sue mentioned she wanted coffee,
so I thought I had to win at all costs.
You will be divided into two teams
based on whether your ball
is in an achromatic or chromatic color.
Please enter the court with your team.
Please start when the whistle blows.
Get ready!
- You have to stick together.
- Okay.
- Hold onto me.
- Sure.
- Good luck.
- We've got this.
Bring it on!
- Take three quick steps to the right.
- Okay.
Su-been.
Why do you--
Why do you keep targeting me?
Put more force into it.
Hey, that packed a punch.
- You're doing great, Su-been.
- Keep it going.
- Are you sure Go-eun wasn't hit?
- She wasn't.
Okay. Throw it right away.
Oh, no.
I'll keep holding onto you.
Su-been was incredible during the game.
He had broad shoulders,
and how he played impressed me.
I don't think he's that talkative.
But he showed a completely different side,
and I found that charismatic.
That was hot.
My heart did skip a beat.
Sung-hun is just standing there.
- Is he the referee or what?
- I know. Poor guy.
He's just standing there.
- I think we should go out.
- You think so?
That way,
the team can keep hold of the ball.
All right, Ms. Leader. I trust you.
Just a second.
Stay hidden.
Get it. Quick.
Kim Min-gee's pair is eliminated.
Get that ball.
- Get that ball.
- Good job.
Well done.
What is this?
- Ham Ye-jin's pair is eliminated.
- See you later.
- Sorry, Ye-jin.
- It's fine.
- We got carried away.
Hey, wait.
- We're out.
- Choi Mina Sue's pair is eliminated.
My hand slipped.
Kim Go-eun's pair is eliminated.
What do we do?
We can't lose.
Make sure to stay together.
I'll guard your hands.
I had my hands on Jae-jin's waist,
and he covered my hands with his.
That was pretty memorable.
That's when I realized
he was doing his best to take care of me.
- This way.
- Pass the ball right away.
- Okay.
- To those guys.
Okay. I'll pass right away.
Right away!
Oh, no.
- Okay.
- Pass the ball around.
- Move forward.
- I've got this.
- Pass the ball to the back.
Joo-young and Jae-jin
got pretty touchy-feely during the game,
and it bothered me.
Still, we were on the same team,
so my goal was to win no matter what
and get Joo-young the special treat.
Great job.
Lee Joo-young's pair is eliminated.
Good job.
- Seung-il.
- Well done.
- Team Chromatic Color wins.
- That was so freaking cool.
Great job, everyone.
He's sweating so much.
Joo-young seemed pretty disappointed.
I wish I could've gotten her that coffee.
I really do. I feel bad.
Moreover,
the couples who played the game together
will have a one-on-one lunch date today.
Where does that leave Sung-hun?
Really?
- Poor guy.
- Blame it on his bad luck.
Hello.
- Hello.
- I'm glad you can join me.
- The feeling's mutual.
- We finally got a chance to chat.
- I know, right?
Thank you.
- Shall we?
- Cheers.
How's the coffee?
It's great.
- Do you like coffee?
- I do.
I enjoy coffee.
I only heard after we returned here.
Did the four contestants
join right after we left?
What was it like?
I cheered silently.
Why did you cheer?
I mean, you guys left us behind,
and we had some new company.
I thought,
"I should get to know them better."
- Of course.
- Yes.
Tell me this, then.
Do you have someone you'd like to talk to?
I mean, do you have someone in mind?
I've been wanting to talk to you.
At the moment…
- I'd like to talk to Seung-il, too.
- Seung-il?
- Why?
- Just because.
- I was curious.
- I see.
What factors did you consider
when deciding who you wanted to talk to?
I chose guys
I talked to the most
or made the most eye contact with.
I see.
Who did you vote for yesterday?
Someone entirely different.
I ended up changing my mind afterwards.
- I voted for you.
- Really?
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- Really.
- Oh, my.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Go-eun softens up when she talks.
- She does.
She may not be as feisty
as I initially thought her to be.
- She's shy.
- Yes.
- Really?
I voted for you.
You voted for me,
but I didn't get to go to Paradise.
It's such a shame.
What's your ideal type?
I like someone
who is kind yet manly.
- You'll have to keep talking to the guys.
- That's true.
That's the only way
you'll know if they are.
Exactly.
From our short chat,
I can sense
your gentleness.
You seem sweet.
- Me?
- Yes.
Thank you.
- It's nice talking to you.
- Likewise.
- I've been wanting to do this.
- Same.
Why do I feel so nervous?
Hello.
My gosh.
Those are my favorites.
I saw the winners enjoying coffee
- and watermelon. I'm so jealous.
- Me too.
I remember you saying
how you wanted coffee earlier.
- Yes, it's a shame we didn't win.
- I think my enthusiasm got in the way.
But you rocked. I mean it.
You were so cool.
I even told everyone how cool you were.
Can I ask about your type?
What kind of girl do you like?
Well…
For me…
In terms of physique, I prefer tall women.
How tall are you?
- I'm not sure…
- I'm 172cm tall.
You're 172cm tall?
- She's tall.
- She said, "That's me."
And personality-wise,
I like frank and open people.
You seem frank, too.
- What's this?
- I look forward to seeing them together.
What about you?
I think I prioritize
personality over physique.
- I see.
- I'm pretty chatty.
I'm pretty talkative, you see.
So I like people
who find my chattering funny
rather than being annoyed.
A sense of humor must be important to you.
That's true. But my partner
doesn't have to be funny.
I'm not a fan of flirty people.
I mean,
if the guy who's attentive to me
acts the same way to other women…
That's rather off-putting.
- I mean, it's hard to miss.
- I get what you mean.
- Did anyone catch your eye?
- Well…
How about you?
One woman did catch my eye.
Is she tall?
I suppose so. She's on the tall side.
What's this?
- What's wrong?
- Even I'm getting butterflies.
- Yes, they're hitting it off.
- Indeed.
Are you shy around strangers?
- How do I seem?
- I'd say a bit?
- I think I am.
- I thought so, too.
I think I know
your Myers-Briggs Type Indicator.
You seem like an INTJ.
- You think I'm an INTJ?
- Yes.
I'll tell you on our Paradise date.
I'd love to join you.
- Sorry?
- Take me there.
- My gosh.
- He's keeping her intrigued.
She asked him to take her out.
I'll have to win the next game.
- I can't wait for the next game.
- Do you think you can win?
I'm sure I won't lose.
I guess you'll win then.
Their conversation was lovely, wasn't it?
- My heart fluttered.
- I loved it.
- For sure.
- It's what we've been waiting for, right?
- A budding romance.
- Exactly.
No cryptic comments.
- No one's being evasive.
- Exactly.
- They weren't being overly direct either.
- Right.
- It was almost poetic.
- Totally.
They took a poetic approach.
Everything was meaningful.
Rather than saying, "I like you,"
they spoke their minds in an indirect way.
He was so smooth
saying he'd tell her in Paradise.
- He's saying, "Let's go to Paradise."
- Exactly.
Singles.
Today, there will be another
Paradise-bound couple matching.
That's wild.
The matching will take place in an hour.
Good luck.
Please converse
with your fellow contestants freely.
- This is all too much.
- "Freely"?
What's with the watermelon?
- Let's go steal a bite.
- Okay.
Go grab them. Let's go get them.
Bring us the watermelon.
Can I have a bite?
- Here, Hyun-jae.
- Just one.
- Take the whole slice.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Have it all.
- Can I steal you for a bit, Seung-il?
- I suppose.
- You can have it all.
- Really? Did you have enough?
Not really. I couldn't enjoy it.
It was too hot.
- Hey, you had quite a bit.
- I did.
- What's your ideal type?
- Well…
Someone I can click with.
- So…
- A good sense of humor?
Yes, someone I can banter with.
I want my partner
to also be my best friend.
- So those are what I value.
- We have a lot in common.
For me, as long as we hit it off,
everything else is fine.
I mean it.
If you think about it,
you spent two days in Paradise…
Wait, I meant Inferno.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Keep going.
- You've been here in Inferno.
- Right.
Has someone grown on you,
or has anyone intrigued you?
You, Min-gee.
- You're so honest.
- Yes, you're one of them.
I've had my eye on only two women.
- You and--
- Is it Go-eun?
Not her.
Mary Sue.
- What? She's Mina Sue.
- Right, Mina Sue.
- "Mary Sue."
- "Mary Sue"?
"Mary Sue."
I knew someone would slip up like that.
- I knew it.
- "Mary Sue."
- "Mary Sue"? It suddenly feels sacred.
I've had my eye on only two women.
- You and…
- Is it Go-eun?
Not her.
Mary Sue.
- What? She's Mina Sue.
- Right, Mina Sue.
- So, you like women like us.
- Yes, you two.
- Yes, I have a clear preference.
- I see.
Still, it was really funny
how you got the pink one.
You were already so funny
and when I saw that pink ball…
- I cracked up big time.
- No, don't.
- It was so funny.
- Don't say that.
When I drew that pink ball…
This is random, but…
can I speak casually?
- Yes, let's do that.
- Okay.
I feel so at ease when I'm with you.
- Really?
- Yes.
It's almost like I'm with a family member.
- The yellow dress?
- Yeah, and that you're glamorous.
- Really?
- Yes. It was a great first impression.
Hello.
- What's your type physically?
- Physically?
I guess someone with full lips?
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
- Goodness.
- He does have full lips.
I love his character.
I think we'd have fun
if we went to Paradise.
- Can we have a chat, Min-gee?
- Yes? Let's go.
- You're very chill.
- Oh, yes.
- I like it here.
- This is my spot.
So did you get to talk with everyone?
Yes, I think I did.
I just followed my heart.
- The end.
- Already?
Now, we're going to match the couples
who will go on a date in Paradise.
- Let's talk some more later.
- Okay.
Really? He was just about to talk to her.
Hyeon-woo.
He can't catch a break.
Just when we think Hyeon-woo
finally gets his chance to shine,
the ill-fated timing takes his shot away.
Sadly.
Now, we're going to match the couples
who will go on a date in Paradise.
The men have already chosen
the woman they'd like to go
to Paradise with.
This is wild.
Kim Go-eun.
- Oh, no.
- Please step outside your lodging.
- Have fun.
- See you.
Oh, come on.
- Enjoy your date. See you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow.
When you get to Paradise
after being stuck here,
I bet you'll be flooded with emotions.
I have a feeling she'll go to Paradise.
The person I'd like to go
to Paradise with is…
Kim Go-eun has matched with…
I think she'll leave with Sung-min.
- I don't think so.
- Really?
- Sung-min is her safe choice.
- If she plays safe, she'll pick him.
Go-eun has matched with…
Woo Sung-min.
- Me?
- Sung-min.
Woo Sung-min, please step outside.
He's a Paradise regular.
- Didn't they play the game together?
- That's how you catch feelings.
How interesting.
I think their chemistry will take off
when they arrive in Paradise.
You never know what'll happen there.
After a few glasses of wine.
- Are your bags heavy? Shall I carry them?
- Just this one.
You should've offered sooner.
I was almost crushed by the weight.
- What did you bring?
- A woman needs a lot of things.
I'll dig into every little detail
once we get to Paradise.
- Me?
- Of course.
Who else would I look into?
So I'm your target? It won't be so easy.
- We'll see.
- Okay.
The person I'd like
to go to Paradise with is…
I chose Joo-young
without a moment of hesitation.
I didn't feel drawn to Joo-young
all throughout the dodgeball game.
But as we talked after that,
I felt relaxed around her.
When you use cornstarch for deep-frying,
it doesn't turn brown.
You get snowy crisps.
Really?
It's like I'm listening to the radio.
You're very generous
to laugh at my boring tales.
I tend to laugh a lot.
So, I wanted to talk to her some more.
I can't tell at all.
I chose Joo-young.
I didn't consider any other women.
I've wanted to talk
to you the most, Joo-young.
Oh, really?
When we were eating,
I saw you smile and thought,
"I'll have to write her name
if we vote today."
- We have this in common.
- The dimples.
- So you noticed.
- Yes, the dimples.
You noticed.
- Maybe they drew me in.
- You saw them.
I think this is the first time
we're seeing Hyun-jae
look at someone else directly.
The close-up shot, I mean.
- He's so attractive.
- Agreed.
He has such an intense gaze.
I think you'd be very popular here.
You think so?
- Really?
- I'm sure of it.
But I'm not worried.
I'll find a fair and square way
to win your heart.
I'll do my best.
Joo-young has matched with…
I can't wait to find out who she chose.
- Jae-jin's chance seems pretty good.
- Jae-jin?
- Won't it be Hyun-jae?
- I think so.
He's a sure bet.
Joo-young has matched with…
Kim Jae-jin.
Kim Jae-jin, please step outside.
…Kim Jae-jin.
Seriously, these two
are becoming regulars.
- Congrats.
- I'll get on my way.
Have fun!
See you.
Those two are trouble.
Do they have something special we don't?
Where else could we see
someone like Hyun-jae looking so dejected?
- Good point.
- Right?
It's a rare sight indeed.
He's like a character
out of romance comics.
- Hello.
Shall we go?
Yes.
- Was it a tough decision for you?
- For me?
Not at all.
Same here.
Let's have fun.
- Yes, ma'am!
- It took you too long. Try again.
Let's spend quality time together.
Let's share what's on our hearts.
Sounds good.
When I pondered on
who to go to Paradise with…
Since Sung-hun
is such a pleasant person to talk to
and has a comforting presence,
I thought a Paradise date
with him would be really enjoyable.
I got to know Su-been better
during the game and saw his charms.
He was really incredible.
When he threw the ball,
all his muscles here rippled.
Seeing him in action blew my mind.
Then, there's Seung-il.
I don't think I got to have
a one-on-one conversation.
We didn't get to go on a date,
so I'd like to talk to him a bit more.
The person I'd like
to go to Paradise with is…
Who did she hit it off with?
- Probably Su-been.
- Yes, Su-been.
Wait, could it be Seung-il?
The person I'd like
to go to Paradise with is…
I'm so curious who her choice will be.
Seung-il?
- Su-been.
- Su-been?
Su-been.
Subtitle translation by: Jeongwoo Kim