YOUN HYUN-JAE
SONG SEUNG-IL
PARK HEE-SUN
SHIN HYEON-WOO
KIM GO-EUN
KIM JAE-JIN
HAM YE-JIN
WOO SUNG-MIN
KIM MIN-GEE
LIM SU-BEEN
LEE SUNG-HUN
LEE JOO-YOUNG
CHOI MINA SUE
LEE HA-EUN
JO I-GEON
SINGLE'S INFERNO
- I have a question for Go-eun.
- Oh.
Was there a moment that made you decide
on your top pick right now?
If so, what was that moment?
Well…
- It's the chat I had today.
- Today?
That decided your top pick?
I mean that
I pretty much confirmed my decision
through our conversation today.
That means all three have a chance.
- Yes.
- Exactly.
I was hoping to see Go-eun show
her feelings more explicitly by now.
I've noticed this from the beginning,
but her ambiguity
has continued to confuse the men.
- It's a shame.
- Yes, right. It's tiring.
I'd like to ask Go-eun this.
Who's the third among your picks?
If you can't answer it,
you can always drink.
- Yes.
- Third place.
- Tough day for whoever's third.
- Right.
This is hilarious.
Drink up if you can't answer.
- Seung-il.
- Yes, ma'am.
- She has to drink.
- Drink up.
My gosh.
- She has to finish that?
- No, just one sip.
Only as much as you can.
Yes, only drink as much as you can.
Sung-min, what do you think…
makes Go-eun so charming?
Everything.
My gosh.
- Come on.
Everything about her. Why?
- I guess it's possible.
- I guess.
- Sure.
- Everything.
- It can happen.
- Really?
- Everything about her.
Don't ask me.
A question for Hyeon-woo.
Is there something
you're dying to say to Go-eun?
- Wow.
- Hey.
I want to hear everything.
From the moment I chose you,
all my moments were for you.
Gosh.
Geez.
He learned romance through books.
- Exactly.
- Yes, that can happen.
But he wanted to move her.
- Yes, exactly.
- Yes.
- That can happen.
- Sure.
From the moment I chose you…
I don't want to see that again.
Why did you rewind? Fast forward.
From the moment I chose you,
all my moments were for you.
- Look at them.
- They feel the same way.
See? Right?
- We weren't the weird ones.
- I'm so glad.
- We were--
- I had to cover my mouth.
- I'm glad.
- I thought we were mean.
- We weren't.
- Exactly.
Hyeon-woo is wrapped up
in his own emotions right now.
- In that moment.
- Yes.
Jae-jin.
- What now, Jae-jin?
- Save us.
I'm about to die. Save me.
Gosh.
But Go-eun must be happy with that.
Go-eun.
- It's a busy day for Go-eun.
- It really is.
- She'll drink again.
- You're so popular.
Who did you go to Paradise with
more than once?
- You.
- Precisely.
That was your question?
- That was your question?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
- That was cute.
- It was cute.
- It was.
- Really.
- It was new.
- He's a player.
- Yes, it was new.
- You.
- Precisely.
That was your question?
- That was your question?
- Yes.
- All right.
- Even I could've answered that.
I could've answered that too.
Is he rubbing that in everyone's face?
- Exactly.
- Yes.
- He showed them.
- But why?
I want to ask I-geon.
What did you like about me?
What will he say now?
I want to know what he'll say.
- I'm curious.
- Me too.
- It's the last test.
- He can stand out.
- Yes.
- It's that point.
- The last test.
Can you hold this?
Sure.
It would be faster
if I listed the things I didn't like.
- He likes too many things about her.
- There are too many?
- That was it?
- He's done?
- That was all?
- Yes.
At times, people think too much
and end up playing an awful move.
- Well, it's…
- He's being indirect.
- I get why he did that.
- In that situation,
- it could've been simple.
- One said, "Every moment was you."
- Yes.
- Yes, "All my moments."
The other two already answered
with "everything" and "every moment."
- Really?
- "Moments."
I have a feeling
he was beating around the bush.
At that moment,
I thought of all my dates with Go-eun.
I wanted to share
everything I liked about her,
but I couldn't share everything I felt
in that moment.
That's why I shared my honest feelings.
Go-eun's reaction at that time…
I don't really know.
I'm not sure if my feelings got across.
Go-eun.
Is there anything
you'd like to tell I-geon?
Well…
I had a lot of fun
on our date at the swimming pool.
It was memorable.
What about you, I-geon?
You'll need to give her a response.
You need to give an answer.
I knew it.
I guess she had fun at the swimming pool.
That can happen.
That was all.
I didn't want to know what they did there
and what happened there.
I just thought she had a great time.
Go-eun.
Among your time
in both Inferno and Paradise,
when was the most heart-fluttering moment?
The most heart-fluttering moment?
- Oh, my.
- Goodness.
She must be thirsty.
- What?
- She drinks so much.
She won't answer?
- She's leaving room again.
- Gosh.
She's hiding too much.
- Oh, my.
- She'll sleep well tonight.
- Totally.
She always sleeps well.
Even better now.
- Go-eun.
- My gosh. Why are you doing this?
Why couldn't you answer the question?
- Exactly.
- Yes.
- I'm curious.
- That was a good question.
- It's time to talk.
- Yes.
Why couldn't you answer the question?
Well…
I had a moment with everyone.
They all made your heart flutter?
My heart must flutter quite often.
I've been expressing my feelings
to everyone through our conversations,
so I thought
I had shown my feelings enough.
I didn't feel the need
to tell everyone how I felt
while we were there as a group.
- Well, that may be the case.
- Right.
That's up to her.
She said she has almost decided.
- Yes.
- Who do you think it is?
- I think it's I-geon.
- In the end, I also think it'll be I-geon.
- What's sad is this.
- Yes?
She just said she shared her feelings
with Hyeon-woo,
Sung-min, and I-geon, right?
- Yes.
- But she didn't.
I have a feeling
that she doesn't really realize that.
I think that's how she usually is.
She can't give a direct opinion
in case she hurts someone.
Yes, she's ambiguous.
- I think she's like that.
- She's a bit indecisive.
- Yes, something like that.
- Right.
If you think about it,
I-geon also didn't pursue her
that earnestly either.
We even said we were looking forward
to see changes in him
because he wasn't expressive.
- He isn't doing much either.
- He expressed himself.
I-geon said he liked countless things
about her and that it would be faster
to list what he dislikes.
- He didn't say "countless."
- That was what he meant.
No.
- Wait.
- It was implied.
- No, it wasn't.
- Wait.
It would've been great
if he had said the word "countless."
I think he tried to look too cool.
But in my opinion,
it felt like I-geon did his best.
He felt the pressure
that he could be falling behind.
- So he kept lurking around from the start.
- Yes.
He even pouted cutely too.
- He's doing it.
- He did it when others weren't there.
I think he expressed his feelings
- in his way.
- He made sure Go-eun knew.
Also, he asked,
"Who did you go to Paradise with twice?"
- Yes.
- He wanted to hear his name.
- He expressed it in his own way.
- He did.
But as you just mentioned,
it may not have been enough for her.
I guess I-geon hasn't done enough
in Go-eun's standards.
- Yes.
- The way he expressed himself.
- He should've been clearer.
- Exactly.
- I think I-geon is doing a lot.
- This is why it's hard.
She likes expressive guys.
- Yes.
- But I-geon is doing the least.
- But she likes him best.
That's how ironic the situation is.
I guess love can change
with these little details.
We're witnessing
something like that unfold right now.
Yes, but even we don't see
eye to eye on this.
I'm sure our viewers feel the same.
And we should respect
everyone's take on this.
- That's right.
- Let's continue.
I didn't expect a debate from this.
Right.
- Let's all make a toast.
- Okay.
Good job, everyone.
- Sung-hun.
- Cheers.
Are we drinking this?
Cheers.
- It really feels like the end.
- No, don't say it's the end.
- That's making me sad.
- Gosh.
But really,
it's quite sad to think
that this has come to an end.
I was very happy to have met all of you.
It would be great if we could meet up
even after we leave this place.
Can you cry?
- Are you crying?
- No.
I had to think.
Staying here was one of the most
challenging times of my life.
But it was also
the most memorable and beautiful time.
Thank you.
Well…
First of all,
I wanted to be honest until the end
even if I seemed fickle at times.
But I'm pleased that I could show
my truest self while I was here.
Thank you so much.
- All right!
- She's good.
I showed my most honest self
without any pretense.
I just followed my emotions.
I may end up getting hated by someone
for acting like that.
But despite that,
I tried to act the way I wanted,
and I did just that.
There were tough moments,
fun moments,
moments that made my heart flutter,
and definitely some moments
that felt offensive.
But I personally think
a colorful life with many ups and downs
is a truly meaningful one.
I am so grateful that I got to experience
something like this.
I mean it.
Very much.
Yes, thank you so much. I mean it.
In a way, Mina Sue
might have been the most courageous one.
- I realized that now.
- She was.
She showed everything
she was feeling inside.
She did.
The most transparent one yet.
HAM YE-JIN
This is the hottest inferno in the world.
Single's Inferno.
LEE HA-EUN
SONG SEUNG-IL
And now…
KIM MIN-GEE
…you will make your final decisions.
KIM JAE-JIN
YOUN HYUN-JAE
CHOI MINA SUE
LEE SUNG-HUN
JO I-GEON
KIM GO-EUN
If there is no one you wish to choose…
WOO SUNG-MIN
SHIN HYEON-WOO
…you may give up
on making your final decision.
PARK HEE-SUN
For the first time in Single's Inferno,
the contestants get to back out
if there is no one they want to choose.
But will anyone here back out?
- Yes, there is.
- What?
Who do you reckon it is?
I have a feeling Hee-sun
might not make her final pick.
- Right.
- Yes.
- Maybe.
- And give up?
- Yes, I think she may give up.
Because after that moment,
Su-been didn't make any moves on her.
I would understand why.
- Yes.
- Even if she gave up, that is.
And one more person.
If another one gives up,
I think it'll be Go-eun.
- What?
Because she didn't get
the reassurance she wanted
from I-geon the night before,
she's unsure about him,
even though he seems to be her top choice.
I think she may end up deciding
that she won't make her final pick.
- Gosh.
- Let's say she does that.
Then Jin-young, you've got
the sharpest instincts.
I mean it.
And if you're wrong,
you're buying dinner today.
Great.
Jin-kyung.
- Will I be the sharpest?
- I mean it.
- Let's go.
- Or the dullest?
- The dullest.
- Will he be paying for our team dinner?
Gosh.
Kim Min-gee.
Please proceed to the Gates of Inferno.
I hate starting things off.
I hate being the first.
Gentlemen, if Kim Min-gee
is your final choice,
please go stand in front of her.
Stop smiling.
I felt the most like myself
when I was with her.
It was nice to feel butterflies,
but I felt much more at ease
when I could relax around her.
I could be my authentic self
with her more than with anyone else.
She's smiling from ear to ear.
She's so happy.
They even kind of look alike.
She's fidgeting.
Good work.
Let's go eat something good.
What is it?
Well…
I'm actually the type
who doesn't believe in destiny.
But I feel like…
I found mine here.
I'm a competitive person.
I like to win,
which is "seungri" in Korean,
and winning first place,
or "ildeung" in Korean.
That must be why I like you, Seung-il.
She likes "seungri"
and winning, "ildeung."
- It was an acrostic poem.
- Yes, with his name.
- An acrostic poem with Seung-il's name.
- That's something she'd say. It's nice.
This is embarrassing.
I have feelings for you. I like you.
What was that?
I love this.
I have feelings for you. I like you.
Good for him.
Kim Min-gee,
please reveal your final decision.
The person I'd like
to leave Inferno with is…
Song Seung-il.
Come on. Let's go.
- Do you feel shy?
- What?
Bye.
They're locking their fingers.
My gosh.
- What was that again? "Seung-il"?
- Yes, "Seung" and "Il."
I like to win, "seungri,"
and winning first place, "ildeung."
Really? You know,
that line was pretty witty.
- Yes, right?
- Yes.
Yours was tacky.
- Me?
- Yes.
- I meant what I said.
- Okay.
- I said what I--
- What you wanted to say? Me too.
Okay.
Why am I the only one
saying these cringey things?
Why is it easier for me?
Why am I the only one?
I'll do it next time.
- Next time?
- Yes.
- There is no next time, kid.
- I'm really bad at expressing myself.
- Do it for me.
- My emotions…
Do it for me!
- Okay.
- Do it for me!
Gosh, my feet hurt.
- Should I carry you?
- Yes.
Carry me. All right.
You're really carrying me.
She's doing that in a dress?
Most people don't do that.
It had slits too.
- But not her.
- She doesn't care.
- She just goes.
- Yes, that's her.
She's such a go-getter girl.
- A go-getter girl.
- Look at her from the back.
- It's a rare sight.
- Indeed.
Jumping on his back in a dress.
- That's crazy.
- That's so Min-gee.
- Yes.
- That's her exit.
- It really is.
- My gosh.
Park Hee-sun.
Please proceed to the Gates of Inferno.
I'm not sure about Hee-sun.
She might not choose.
It's so vague. What now?
Gentlemen, if Park Hee-sun
is your final choice,
please go stand in front of her.
She was more determined
and persevering than she seemed,
so that twist made me fall for her.
There's no reason in liking someone.
If she doesn't choose me,
I'll jump into the sea.
These two are a bit unstable.
First of all,
I was grateful for everything you did
while we were here.
Because you were here,
Inferno felt like Paradise.
Well…
You can relax.
I'm the type who holds some grudges.
I'm guessing it wasn't that serious.
That's my take.
- She doesn't look so happy.
- Right.
I think she'll back out.
She doesn't look happy.
Park Hee-sun,
please reveal your final decision.
Will she be the first to give up
in the history of the show?
I doubt it.
The person I'd like
to leave Inferno with is…
Will she go?
- Will she?
Just go.
"Su-been"?
"No one."
- "No one."
- I guess not.
- No.
- Really? No way. It's Su-been.
No.
The person I'd like
to leave Inferno with is…
Lim Su-been.
- Yes, see?
- All right.
They should go on dates out there
and have a talk.
- Yes, talk.
- I hope they become honest.
- Good for them.
- Su-been.
- Just a bit.
- Be more honest.
I think you were the first person
I ever actively pursued
and showed my feelings to.
Thank you for bringing out
that honest side of me,
and thanks to you,
Inferno also felt like Paradise.
Let's go and eat something delicious.
Let's go.
I'm the type who holds some grudges,
so I wasn't 100% satisfied with him.
But he came to me first and asked to talk.
Hee-sun.
- Are you asleep?
- What? Why?
Do you feel unwell?
- No, I'm fine.
- Okay.
He went to see her.
- I see.
- He was there.
- They had talked.
- I'm glad.
I wanted to say this
and clarify everything.
We didn't sleep on the same bed
because we had agreed to.
I mean it. It wasn't like that.
I'm sorry for not telling you that.
It hadn't crossed my mind.
I'm sorry.
- They actually talked about it.
- Yes.
- The crew didn't show us.
- It's a shame.
- Yes, that's why.
- This is it.
- We took it the wrong way.
- We've been too accurate.
- They hid it?
- Yes, on purpose.
So we'd get the wrong idea.
- To keep us on edge.
- It was to confuse us.
- It was thrilling.
- It was.
I also feel really bad
because I should've come up
and told you that first,
but Seung-il brought it up first.
- Yes.
- Exactly.
I realized that it must've made you feel
even worse.
So that was…
It was my fault.
I think my problem is that
I am bad at sharing my emotions.
- It seems so.
- Yes.
I guess I failed to do that.
Yes, you don't share how you feel.
So I couldn't tell
how you were feeling, Su-been.
- You felt that way?
- Yes.
- I want to change that about myself.
- Change what?
- The way that I don't share stuff.
- I see.
You can be like that.
I'll try to understand.
- Did I almost lose your favor?
- Yes.
In a way,
the way I felt awful in that situation
actually proved how much I liked Su-been.
So I guess it was another chance
for me to realize my feelings for him.
My gosh. It's so pretty.
This is it. My gosh.
- Come closer.
- Or together?
- Yes?
- Let's take one together.
One, two, three.
- Does it look okay?
- Yes.
One, two, three.
It looks great.
- It looks good.
- It's cute.
- Wow.
- I like it.
We kind of look alike.
- Right?
- Don't we look alike?
They say those with similar jaw structures
end up together.
We kind of look alike.
I'm so glad that I participated
because I ended up
meeting someone wonderful.
My heart flutters at the thought
of spending time with that great person
even after the show.
Take one.
Blue suits you.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
What do I do with this?
- Good.
- What's this for?
- This is just like your outfit.
- Right.
Tell the others.
- That I got flowers?
- Yes.
Show off the proposal.
You're so silly.
- Did he say "I love you"?
- No.
I heard it wrong.
Who cares if it was that?
- They're an item now.
- Yes.
EARLIER THIS MORNING
Well, in my case,
the more I talked to you,
the more I liked you.
As I got to know you,
I started to see different sides
of you day by day.
And your unexpected sides
kept drawing me in.
I want to keep seeing you after this.
Okay.
You should call me "oppa" then.
- Stop calling me Mr. Su-been.
- What about Been?
Call me "Been oppa."
How cute.
All right. Let's go.
- Oppa.
- My gosh.
Yeah?
What will you treat me to?
Anything.
What are you craving?
Everything sounds good.
Gosh.
- You know what?
- Yes?
I was going to say what you said.
- Really?
- I was shocked it was the same.
- I was thinking, "What now?"
- I was going to say exactly that.
- Right.
- I guess we're meant to be.
- Yes, we're wired the same way.
- It's our first time holding hands.
- Right. You have tiny hands.
- I do?
- Yes.
Your hands are frail.
How did you grab that tail
with these hands?
Tightly.
That must've been memorable.
- Yes.
- Right.
- Congrats.
- The second couple.
- Yes.
The second couple.
In the end, Hee-sun
had been sulky against Su-been.
- She was disappointed.
- Yes.
But they talked it out.
- He did.
- Yes.
I thought they weren't expressive,
but I'm not worried now.
- No.
- Right.
- They're good as a couple.
- They're all holding hands.
They're hand in hand.
They'll be cute together.
They seemed to do better
as soon as they left the island.
They just need to talk a lot.
They'll be fine.
This is great.
Choi Mina Sue.
Please proceed to the Gates of Inferno.
Gentlemen, if Choi Mina Sue
is your final choice,
please go stand in front of her.
I was very drawn to her.
She was more special to me than others.
And I want to get to know her more
outside of this place.
Be it Korea
or America,
I'll come and see you anywhere.
My gosh.
My goodness.
Well…
Thank you very much.
- He was moved.
- Yes.
- He's seriously in shock.
- He's about to cry.
- Gosh, Sung-hun.
- And she knew.
- That it'd be better in English.
- Yes.
That's why she did it in English.
Choi Mina Sue,
please reveal your final decision.
The person I'd like
to leave Inferno with is
Sam Lee.
Gosh, that was amazing.
- Wonderful.
- How heartwarming.
This couple also had
so many ups and downs.
Not like that.
I didn't know we would end up like this.
Right?
- It was because you kept wandering.
- Wait, me?
No way. You too.
You wanted to be friends.
Yes, that--
I wasn't joking.
Our pink boy, Sung-hun, is wearing pink.
Yes, the cursed pink.
I overcame it.
Lee Joo-young.
Please proceed to the Gates of Inferno.
Gentlemen, if Lee Joo-young
is your final choice,
please go stand in front of her.
I only had feelings for Joo-young
from the beginning,
so I want to make her my final decision.
She was the most compatible with me
and understood me well.
I also thought she was the most stunning.
That's all.
Thank you for spending time with me
while we were in Inferno.
Let's go and have a chat out there.
Joo-young.
You have such a pretty smile.
Jae-jin.
I had such a relaxing and romantic time
with you in Inferno.
Do you want to go get ice cream?
Hyun-jae.
You were always so cool,
and I was grateful for you.
I loved how you were always the same.
Thanks to you, I felt like a child again.
You and I should
go get some kalguksu together.
Lee Joo-young,
please reveal your final decision.
The person I'd like to leave Inferno with
is Kim Jae-jin.
Shall we?
Come, kitty.
You, come with me!
- Gosh.
- Yes, that one.
- He was thinking about that.
- My gosh.
They're such a cute couple.
You, come with me!
I'm adopting you!
Come here. Let's go.
Beep.
Input complete.
You can't say,
"You, come with me," like that.
I don't think I gave you the right input.
I think you coded it differently.
This is nice.
- You're drying the sweat.
- Yeah.
What do you think?
Me?
I was serious. I meant it.
Every moment with you.
You fell for me as soon as you saw me.
- I know that.
- I didn't.
- You did too.
- It was after we talked.
You fell for me.
- Not at first sight.
- Yes, you did.
That's why I like you more.
My ideal type is not about the looks.
- Okay.
- It's someone I can talk to.
And?
- That's--
- Of course, you're beautiful.
- That's a big aspect.
- Sure.
- I like you even more now.
- Good.
I don't know why I'm smiling
like the silliest guy on earth.
Look at how happy they are.
Jin-kyung, I'm adopting you!
Check yourself.
"Check yourself"?
Gosh.
Geez.
I'm sorry.
- I learned a lot from Jae-jin.
- Yes, really.
He's admirable.
- He's a cool guy.
- He had many right answers.
Kim Go-eun.
Please proceed to the Gates of Inferno.
Gentlemen, if Kim Go-eun
is your final choice,
please go stand in front of her.
Gosh.
- The men didn't give up.
- Here we go.
- The three came out.
- They all walked out.
Kim Go-eun is my final decision.
I'll keep being curious
about her out there,
and I want to keep getting to know her.
I want to follow
the emotions I'm feeling right now.
I could feel
that she and I were on the same page.
I liked her a lot,
and my heart kept racing.
That was why I felt more awkward
about expressing myself.
What if she gives up?
No, let's take a look. I'm dying to know.
- No, right?
- She'll make a choice.
- Yes, she will.
- I'm seriously so curious right now.
She'll decide.
It must have been straining
both physically and emotionally.
You've done so well.
Why don't you walk with me now?
Well, good work.
I had fun.
And stop getting confused already.
It's a hot day. Let's leave quickly.
I've missed you
and I've waited.
I like you a lot, Go-eun.
When I was with you, Hyeon-woo,
you reminded me a lot
of how I dated as a teenager.
Thank you so much for reminding me
of that young and pure romance once again.
And I was so grateful that you showed
your feelings without changing.
And…
Well…
Will she decide?
I think she will. She will.
- She should.
- I don't think so.
- But she thought this hard.
- Yes, she'll do it.
No, she won't.
For my final decision,
I'm torn between Sung-min and I-geon.
I already know that they bring out
different sides in me.
You're very handsome.
You're beautiful.
So I've been thinking and wondering
which side of me I like best
between those two sides.
I-geon, I had so much fun
whenever I talked to you.
And you were the person
I could share
my thoughts with most easily.
I felt the most relaxed with you,
and you brought out
my favorite side of me.
We should go back to Paradise.
You have the worst hunches.
Who will it be?
- It's I-geon.
- It has to be I-geon.
What about you? Who will it be?
- I-geon.
- Right? It's I-geon.
- It has to be.
- There are no twists.
- No.
- Yes, it's I-geon.
Kim Go-eun,
please reveal your final decision.
- Why am I scared?
- Right?
- No way.
- In case she gives up?
The person I'd like
to leave Inferno with is…
- I-geon.
- It's I-geon.
- It must be.
I'm so nervous.
The person I'd like
to leave Inferno with is…
Woo Sung-min.
What?
- Really? I got chills.
- Really?
Wow.
Why?
Woo Sung-min.
- Holding hands.
Let's walk to Paradise.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- It must've been tough.
- Yes.
Good job.
Gosh, it's over.
This is nice.
- It's nice.
- Yes, it's nice.
Let's go.
My gosh. See? He can't accept it.
- It won't be easy to.
- He can't accept it.
I guess Go-eun had her own standards
when it comes to men.
- Yes.
- I guess it was the confusion.
- Well, Sung-min didn't make her doubt.
- No.
- He shared his feelings.
- Yes.
- Because he did that?
- She wanted someone like that.
- I think that was why she chose Sung-min.
- That could be the case.
I want to hear their chats.
We need all four hours
of their conversation.
I had a lot of fun talking to I-geon,
and the dates drew me to him,
but I expected more
from our conversations afterward.
He seems like the type who doesn't share.
So that was the downside.
I wish he had shared all his feelings,
so I could truly understand
what he was feeling.
Then my attraction to him
could've grown even more.
Sung-min has a way of making me relaxed.
And I think he made small gestures
to check on me
and look after me
even when I wasn't looking.
I think that's why I decided on Sung-min.
Being expressive must be important to her.
Yes, she must've wanted much more.
We thought I-geon had shown enough,
- but she wanted more.
- More.
- That's who she is.
- Just like Sung-min.
- Someone who keeps coming.
- Yes.
She wanted a guy who shares about himself
and continues to check on her.
Wasn't I-geon expressive?
- I thought he was.
- I thought he was expressive too.
- He did his best.
- Especially for a guy like him.
- He really tried.
- He really did.
I don't think she'll choose me.
I'm doing my best
not to care about the results.
I don't think that is something
I can change.
It's her decision,
so I'll just accept the result.
- He saw it coming?
- All right. Let's accept it too.
- We should.
- It's just us.
- Only we won't accept it.
- Right.
Yes, everyone did but us.
- But her choice was unexpected.
- Really.
They were the first couple
that everyone failed to predict.
We knew her feelings were with I-geon.
- Or so we thought.
- Yes.
- But the result was different.
- You know what?
I think the chemistry varies by person.
Some people are drawn to someone
who doesn't show their feelings
and leaves them wanting more.
But there are others
who need someone to be there
and express their love for them.
We're all different.
As an avidly invested person
who's watching this
as a viewer and not a host,
I guess I personally hoped
she'd pick I-geon.
- That's how I felt.
- We all did.
- We were immersed.
- We were captivated by him.
- We fell for him.
- We did.
- Me too.
- I guess so.
After all,
it's her choice and relationship.
- Give her a hand.
- Yes, Go-eun.
- Congrats.
- I hope they work it out.
- And be a real couple.
- They're cute together.
- This is a good beginning.
- Yes.
My final choice
is Kim Jae-jin.
Let's get out there and grab a bite.
I hope we can feel comfortable
with each other and stay good friends.
There isn't anyone I wish to choose.
I will not make my final decision.
- Gosh.
- Geez.
All right. If I were to describe
this season of Single's Inferno
in a phrase, I would say this.
- Brutally honest.
- Seriously.
In this season,
the contestants were really blunt.
They often left us shocked and applauding.
- There were many memorable scenes, right?
- Yes.
And it wasn't just a few
standout couples we enjoyed.
We enjoyed every single one.
I couldn't believe
how interesting each chemistry was.
It was such a memorable season.
Well, did you guys share about this?
I've been telling people
about this season so much.
Me too.
- It was the most interesting.
- Me too.
It was the most exciting one yet.
Yes, I think so too.
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn