Episode 18
Where is Ju Hye In? Where did you hide her?
Someplace where you'll never be able to find her.
Someplace where you won't be able to kill her again.
Tell me. Where did you take that wench?
You dare treat me like an idiot!
You're not even human.
Trash. Murderer!
None of that is important.
Since we've gotten to know about each other much more,
we can be a more harmonious couple now.
Crazy bastard.
All this time you've acted too gracefully,
elegantly, and high end.
A woman like you needs to be punished.
A punishment for deceiving her husband and thinking about other things.
After you receive your punishment,
everything will go back to how it was.
Where are you going?
We're not done talking.
Madam please leave this house immediately.
I can't leave without my children.
Madam.
Do you want to die by the Chairman's hands? Please go!
I need to take my kids!
Sim Su Ryeon!
Where did you go, Sim Su Ryeon?
Housekeeper Yang, I will come back for my children.
So please take care of them while I'm gone.
I'll kill you.
Secretary Jo. Catch Sim So Ryeon immediately!  Immediately!
Ju Seok Hun? This little—
Let go of my arm!
Leave mom alone.
If you go after her, I'll tell everyone.
That Min Seol Ah died at Hera Palace.
This bastard.
If you want to hit me, hit me. Here.
Hit me all you want. Hit me!
I'm no longer scared
of someone like you.
Hye In left safely.
Once she arrives in America, I'll get a call.
Thank you.
I'm just paying back what I couldn't do for Seol Ah.
Secretary Hong is going to take care of her until she gets to the hospital
so don't worry too much.
Are you okay? You didn't get to say goodbye to her.
If I had seen her,
I would've felt like I wouldn't be able to let her go.
Both Seol Ah and Hye In,
both Seok Hoon and Seok Gyeong,
if they had met a better mother,
there wouldn't have been an incident like this.
All because I
wasn't a good mother,
all because of me, my children are suffering.
It's driving me crazy.
Once everything is finished here, I'll take you to Hye In.
Let's go to America together.
Get away from Ju Dan Tae and start a new life. I'll help you.
Do you think
I have the right to start a new life?
I'm not a victim.
I am also
the mother of the children who bullied Seol Ah to her death.
My dead child
was killed by my other children.
I can't forgive myself for that.
No.
I will make you happy.
I am going to keep my last promise to Seol Ah.
I'm going to do that.
Husband
The person you are calling is not able to be connected—
Ju Dan Tae Village
Sim Su Ryeon, I'm going to kill you! How dare you touch my safe!
Chairman! Chairman!
Did you find her?
Ju Hye In just left for America.
What? Are you telling me that to brag or something?
What about Sim Su Ryeon? Where did she go?
Not yet ... I'm doing everything I can to find her.
You worthless bastard!
If you have time to tell me that, then go find her yourself!
Calling... Oh Yun Hui
I'm sorry for calling you this late at night. It's me, Ju Dan Tae.
Let's meet right now.
Unni Su Ryeon
There's no need to feel guilty.
It's the same as Unni Su Ryeon using me to avenge her daughter.
All I need to do now is protect my daughter.
Wow.
Something ... you look different.
Is that so?
Why did you call me?
We share a special secret so can't we have a drink together?
Even so isn't our relationship such that we shouldn't meet late at night?
Did you forget that I'm close with Su Ryeon?
If that had bothered you, you wouldn't even have come out.
Isn't that so?
Unni Su Ryeon
Answer it. If you don't want to create any secrets from my wife.
Hello?
Yun Hui, why haven't you been answering? I've called multiple times.
Sorry, Unni. Something came up.
I left the penthouse.
What does that mean?
Ju Dan Tae is involved with my daughter's death.
Come with me to the police station tomorrow and make a statement about Seol Ah's death.
The only person I can trust right now is you.
I'm going to catch that murderer.
Please help me, Yun Hui.
Yun Hui, are you listening to me?
Yun Hui.
Do you know
where my wife is right now?
If I tell you,
what can you do for me?
Everything Oh Yun Hui wants.
Unni Su Ryeon
What did I do?
I'll be at the lounge.
Let's have breakfast together.
I'll have a coffee first.
If you are curious about something, ask.
There's probably a reason you waited for me,
That's right.
Being straightforward is more like you.
I thought about it,
and I'm wondering why your attitude toward me changed.
I feel like it's an extraordinary reason.
If you think about it,
I'm your best friend's husband,
and having an affair with the woman you hate the most.
Didn't your relationship with Su Ryeon end a long time ago?
And your relationship with Cheon Seo Jin seems over as well.
Why do you think that?
I felt it at the villa.
The way you treated Cheon Seo Jin.
It looked like you wanted her to leave your side.
It was the face of a man who was sick of her.
- That's how I felt.
- So?
That means the spot next to you is vacant.
And you wavered towards me.
Do we need more reasons?
A woman who becomes more interesting the more I see you,
especially the fact that you betrayed my wife, I like that very much.
I didn't betray her.
She betrayed me first.
Pretending to help me, pretending to care for me,
she was acting.
All of that was a lie, and I know that now.
Ju Dan Tae, she was using me to bring you down.
So? What are you going to do now?
Are you going to get your revenge on Sim Su Ryeon?
Whatever it is.
Whatever it takes to protect myself.
I like it. You.
You're honest and bold.
And you're beautiful.
Use me.
The thing that you want,
I may be able to tell you.
I want to know where Sim Su Ryeon is.
And who's working with her.
And what she's planning.
It's me, Chairwoman.
What happened? Did you find the person who sent the video?
I couldn't find the sender.
You told me you took care of everything that day.
Why would something like this happen?
There must've been someone who was there that day.
Someone saw me!
All the security footage from that day was deleted,
so we can't confirm who was at the school that day.
Stop telling me you can't do anything,
and find out at all costs. Do whatever it takes.
Find out who shot the video,
and who dares to threaten me like this.
I will find out.
Just wait till I catch you, I'll kill you.
Where have you been this early in the morning?
Wearing that?
By chance, did you stay out all night?
And you, you look like you didn't get any sleep.
What? Do you have something to worry about?
By any chance, were you not able to get in contact with your lover?
That's not your concern.
This is my last warning.
Don't stick next to Chairman Ju like gum, and leave him.
Do you not have any pride?
Not having any pride and sticking next to him like gum,
isn't that you, not me?
Seeing him up close, it looks like he's having a hard time.
- So I'm just advising you.
- What?
Don't trust men too much.
The most useless and easy thing in the world is a man's heart.
Watch your mouth.
As long as I'm Cheong Ah's chairwoman,
your daughter won't even be able to graduate or go to college.
You think so? I guess we'll find out in the end.
Although I'm not sure if you'll be able to keep that position.
No way.  Did Oh Yun Hui send that video?
Why aren't you answering your phone?
You called?
Where are you coming from?
I just got back from a business trip.
I have to wash up and go to work.
I'll call you later.
She's become a pain.
Ju Dan Tae.
You're becoming ruder and ruder.
- Where are the kids?
- They went to school.
You still haven't found Sim Su Ryeon?
Her phone is off and she hasn't gone to work.
You idiot.
So you've been helping Sim Su Ryeon behind my back all of this time?
You betray me after helping you for more than ten years?
I feel sad, Housekeeper Yang.
I have nothing to say, Chairman.
My kids have really liked you, Housekeeper Yang.
How long has it been?
Since you betrayed me and took Sim Su Ryeon's side.
I never betrayed you. I wouldn't dare betray you—
Don't make excuses. You wore her clothes and pretended to be her.
Did she tell you to do that? To throw me off her trail?
I did wrong, Chairman. Please forgive me once.
I will pay you back for letting me live.
I will work for you until the day I die.
- Drag her out.
- Chairman.
Chairman, no! No!
Please forgive me!
I can't leave this house! I'd rather die in your hands. Chairman!
To be honest, Gu Ho Dong found my weakness.
So I had no choice.
Stop.
Gu Ho Dong?
Weakness?
You guys worked hard taking your midterms,
Don't go running around because your exams are over.
Starting today,
Prepare for you final exams starting today.
My dad and your mom are having an affair. That disgusting affair you keep talking about.
So let's live quietly.
Before you and I embarrass ourselves more.
No! No, no!
Eun Byeol what's wrong?
Did the stress from the exams get to you? Did you fail today's test too?
Why are you pressuring her?
Eun Byeol, are you ok? Is something wrong?
I'm going to go to the nurse's office because my head hurts.
What are you doing here?
Why are you looking through my phone?
Mom. Is it—
Is it—
Nevermind, it's nothing.
What's wrong with you? What happened?
Get your filthy hands off of me!
What? Filthy?
How dare you speak to your mother like that!
I'm so disappointed in you, Mom.
Eun Byeol. Ha Eun Byeol!
What does she know that she's acting like that?
- You're here?
- Y-Yeah.
I'm sorry for  repeatedly avoiding your calls.
After hearing what you said,
I had so many thoughts.
I just needed some time to figure things out.
Whether our friendship was genuine or not.
- I'll believe you.
- Thank you for understanding.
You once said,
that a mother can do anything for her child.
That sometimes they even become a villain.
I want to know who's helping her
and what she's planning.
You didn't hear anything from my husband?
He's probably  going crazy trying to look for me right  now.
Not yet.
Don't worry. I won't tell him I met you.
Of course I believe you.
But I'm just worried you would be
in an awkward position because of me.
Is it time for you to be worried about me right now?
Why did you suddenly leave your house? What about your kids?
I'm really going to end it with him.
It's time now.
To reveal Min Seol Ah's
murderer?
I need to punish the people who killed my Seol Ah.
Ju Dan Tae, Cheon Seo Jin,
and everyone at Hera Club.
I'm going to return to them exactly what Seol Ah went through.
And what if you get hurt in the process?
You know the power that the people at Hera Palace hold
especially Ju Dan Tae and Cheon Seo Jin. They're not easy opponents.
Do you think they'll just stand by and watch?
They killed my daughter.
You want me to leave them alone, knowing that?
What about you? If Ro Na went through all that,
would you be able to stand still?
Min Seol Ah's death was very heartbreaking but
I'm just worried you'll get hurt.
And on top of that, you said there was no solid evidence.
Just by saying you saw Cheon Seo Jin's ruby red ring,
do you think the police will believe you?
Please say you'll stop here.
Please don't do anything. Then I'll stop too.
Please, Unni.
You shouldn't live like nothing happened after committing a crime.
I put my life on the line.
I believe the truth always comes out eventually.
If you just tell the police exactly what you happened that day,
everything will come out slowly.
I already told you.
I already told you.  There's nothing for me to say.
That day I was really drunk,
and I fell asleep as soon as I got home.
Did you really
really not see anything?
You have nothing to say to me?
I should've seen something at least for your sake but
I really didn't see anything.
So I won't be of much help even if I go to the police.
Is that so?
So where are you staying right now?
What are you going to do alone with no one by your side?
Don't worry. I'm somewhere safe.
Where is that?
I'll tell you once I settle down.
Excuse me for a minute.
Hi, Ro Na, I'm kind of busy right now.
The exam? You did that well?
Yes I'm telling you.
The two I took today were 100%, and I only missed one in social history.
I think Ha Eun Byeol flunked again.
See? No one can beat my daughter when it comes to your ability.
Ro Na, what do you want to eat? I'll make you something really delicious—
Okay, I'll see you at home.
I love you my daughter.
I see you made up with Ro Na.
That's good.
Thanks to you.
You look really happy.
I'm sorry. With your situation and everything.
It's okay.
Seeing you smile gives me strength.
You know how much I like you.
Yun Hui, you're such a great person.
Su Ryeon, let's be friends forever.
Let's never fight or betray each other.
No matter how badly you mess up,
I'll never hate you.
What will you do once you find out the truth?
She'll probably throw me in jail right?
Or she might even kill Ro Na.
No. Come to your sense, Oh Yun Hui.
Su Ryeon believes that Cheon Seo Jin is the culprit.
You can't get caught. Think about Ro Na.
J King Holdings
You met her? Where is she?
I don't think she chose a place to stay yet.
Why didn't you tell me you would met her? You should've told me before you left.
We agreed to meet again.
Did you ask about who's helping her? Anything stands out?
She seemed the same as always.
She's as elegant as always and
nothing seemed off.
She didn't even pack anything from home.
I'm certain that someone is helping her.
There's no way she's working alone.
There is someone I'm suspicious of.
But once I'm more certain of it, I'll let you know.
Now it finally feels like I've met a partner that I match with.
Good work. If there's any favor you need to ask of me, let me know anytime.
Can I ask that favor now?
Of course. Whatever it is.
Even if it involves Ro Na?
Why did you crawl back here when no one welcomes you?
Do you think this is the delinquent center?
How can you say something like that, not even knowing if I'm recording or not?
VERITAS LUX MEA
(T/N: "Truth is my light." Motto of Seoul National University)
Now you're even threatening?
I ask of you.
Seeing you bothers me so much.
Can't you just leave? For the sake of the peace in our school.
Did Teacher Cheon tell you to do that?
To bother me and kick me out of school?
Or do you act on your own in favor of those in power?
You're so aggressive. Really aggressive.
This is why I hate you. You don't know your place and you're fearless.
And you don't seem like the type to receive love from your students.
Do you know what love is?
You'll never be able to graduate from this school!
I'll put my name on the line to ensure that. You got it?
You got it?
So disgraceful.
Chairman Ju Dan Tae
Hello? I will be loyal to you until the day I die. This is Ma Du Gi.
Yes, Chairman?
What's the occasion, coming all the way to my house?
I'm sorry for coming here without contacting you when you're resting.
I was very rude to you all this time.
Which rudeness... do you mean by that?
Do you mean when you backstabbed us and ran off during Ro Na's Cheong Ah Admissions?
Or when you shamelessly appeared as a teacher at Cheong Ah Art School?
Or when you were ostracizing and punishing only my daughter by giving her penalty points?
I don't know which one you're talking about so I'm a bit confused.
Come to think of it, I was really a bad person.
I give my sincerest apology.
I don't know why you're suddenly doing this but it's uncomfortable receiving your apology.
All this time, I didn't pay enough attention to you.
Especially if I had known you were Chairman Ju's best employee,
I would never have made such a mistake.
I already knew you were a person easily swayed by authority,
but this is too expected.
I'm just a naive person. Please look at me favorably.
Since it's come to this, I'll be honest with you. Ro Na will become the subject of special care from now.
No, she is already in, as per Chairman Ju's special orders.
A subject of special care?
She'll be cared for at the same level as Seok Hun and Seok Gyeong.
I see your eyes sparkling. From now on,
please do not hesitate to contact me about anything regarding Ro Na's academics.
Just like how you are peacefully lying here and relaxing to the core,
I will take care of everything.
As proof of Ro Na's special care system,
I'll introduce you to the internal detail oriented academies.
There is an academy like that?
An academy that holds the most of Cheong Ah Arts School's exam information.
It's even a secret among the parents.
All the kids at Hera Palace have already been attending.
I will escort you there myself.
A fog keeps obstructing my sight.
There is too much negative energy.
It's filled with someone's sorrow.
Sorrow? Whose sorrow are you talking about?
I wouldn't know that. You two should know.
No way, Min Seol Ah—
Why is her name coming out of your mouth? Flip the last card.
Death
There will be a bloodbath.
Someone might even die soon.
Death
That just brought down my mood. I just wanted to ask if Je Ni was going to be accepted into Seoul University.
What was she talking about? Saying nonsense like sorrow and death.
I came all the way down here and paid good money because I heard she could tell the future well.
A subject of special care. A subject of special care.
My Ro Na is special now too.
If I could do more things for my Ro Na..
I also have a favor to ask. Could you stop by my house?
The penthouse?
Tell my wife you'll pack some of her things and bring it to her.
She'll need lots of things because she left in a rush.
There should be no one home at 7pm.
Hera Palace
It's so beautiful.
I'm sorry. I'll get changed immediately.
I told you. I can let you have whatever you want.
Even if that means the penthouse.
Then get rid of your wife Sim Su Ryeon first.
To some place where no one will find her so she can't return.
Can you do that?
That's what I want.
I heard from Hye In that she arrived at the hospital in America.
Luckily, the tests showed that there was nothing wrong. Don't worry about Hye In.
She's at the best hospital receiving the best care.
Thank you.
How is the contract with Ju Dan Tae going?
Tomorrow, everything regarding the contract will be finalized.
Now is the start. The date is set to three days from now.
Three days from now...
Do you think they'll admit the crimes they've committed?
We have to make them. They'll take the bait.
2020 Soprano Grace Jo's Special Private Concert  Recital for the Children 2020.04.25 7pm
They'll know once they go through the same thing.
What crime they committed.
♪ You visited in my dreams and talked to me ♪
What's the matter?
He said he would tell us once you got here so I don't know either.
I'm sure you're very shocked since I called you this late at night.
But this is a very big issue.
Take a look.
Adulteress alimony lawsuit?
10 billion won for alimony?
Is this woman Sim Su Ryeon insane?
Divorce lawsuit?
Being in this position is really difficult for me. Why did Su Ryeon ask this of me?
This was why you two should've—
I know. Love is like that.
If the conditions are right, you can  file for divorce through agreement.  The conditions are—
Give up the penthouse, the child custody, parental rights.
Prohibited from seeing the children,
giving up 90% of my property,  what kind of crap is this?
This is just telling you to eat loads of crap.
Is this fun for you? You look like you're having a blast.
What have you been doing that you couldn't control your wife and had to make her come after me?
Shouldn't you have been able to stop something like this?
I have so many things to worry about. Why are you involving me in such dirty things?
Don't say another word.
I'm not in the mood to deal with your hot headed temper.
Caller ID restricted
Voice Message
Did you like my video present, Chairwoman Cheon Seo Jin?
Who on earth is this bastard?
Don't hide like a coward and show yourself!
Requiem in D Minor K. 626 by Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart
The caller is not available. Please leave a message—
Why isn't she answering?
Unni Su Ryeon
Unni Su Ryeon, I packed some clothes and makeup from the penthouse.
If you tell me where you are, I'll bring them.
Yes, Logan.
You're going forward with the contract?
Today?
Co-investment contract
Logan Lee
I didn't know you would decide so quickly.
No, there was plenty of time to think about it.
Besides, I was mainly convinced by the fact that you, Mr Ju,
you yourself showed interest in establishing an investment company.
Even with your Myeong-dong land as collateral. That was all the commitment I needed to see.
The only problem is, who will be the chairman.
Of course, if we considered the investment amount, it should be you.
But to convince investors on our side, it would be easier if it were me.
Ah yes, yes. Ms. Oh did mention something about that to me.
Not a problem.
A thing like that shouldn't get in the way of our contract now, should it?
I have faith in you, Mr. Ju.
Then I'll set a meeting with investors during the investment explanation next week.
All right. I'm already looking forward to it.
Oh, and in celebration of our successful contract,
I prepared a special little gift for you.
J King Holdings.
Here you go.
What's this?
Let's just say I have some acquaintance with Soprano Grace Jo.
Soprano Grace Jo?
She's having a concert here in our country.
- That's right. Your daughter, she's studying opera, right?
- Yeah.
So when Grace found out about it, she wanted to hold a concert for her.
So then I thought it'd be a good idea to invite your daughter and all of her friends as well.
The kids will really like this.
So it's all going to be happening this weekend.
Oh, and another thing. The adults will be invited to a separate dinner party.
We'll send you a limousine.
A dinner party?
I don't know how to thank you for such an amazing gift.
Mr. Ju. Now that we're officially partners,
there's no need for such formalities.
Your daughter, she's also studying opera, right?
Yes.
This one's for her.
Thank you, Logan.
Sure thing.
Kids, kids! Let's take a picture together.
Oh, my Je Ni, you're shining.
Grace might want to take her to Italy after she sees her.
One, two, three, cheese!
Do they like it that much? Aigoo.
They're going to faint of happiness.
Grace is not an easy person to meet.
And she only invited our kids. A private concert.
That invitation is worth millions.
Logan is a generous person. He's holding a party for us too.
That's why I like American silver spoons.
Honey, honey! You brought the gift, right?
Don't worry. I brought it right here.
What? You guys prepared a gift by yourselves?
You're trying to get all the attention yourselves. We should've bought it together.
What is it? What is it?
Tell me what it is!
But where's Seo Jin and Chairman Ju?
Are they coming out together?
Don't talk if you don't know anything.
That's not how things are going on right now.
It's a bit strange.
Both Teacher Cheon and Chairman Ju.
What are you talking about?
I saw and heard something.
Why did you ignore my calls all day?
You still haven't explained why you were at the villa with Oh Yun Hui.
I was just resting there.
Oh Yun Hui happened to be there with me after the company dinner.
Oh Yun Hui was wearing my clothes that you had gifted me—
Cut. Cut!
Why is Oh Yun Hui appearing right now?
That's what I'm saying. Why is Oh Yun Hui appearing?
Don't cut me off and listen till the end.
He said she changed because she ruined her clothes.
Do I have to explain every little thing?
I heard you signed the contract with Logan Lee. So kick Oh Yun Hui out immediately.
Logan Lee wants her, as much as I do.
What?
Be careful. There are lots of eyes watching.
Don't change the subject.
I don't know what you're thinking but remember this.
The promise we made when we started over, that I would decide our relationship.
Meeting together and breaking up,
"is all"
"decided by me."
- Right?
- Wow!
They're over, right? They broke up, right?
Oh Yun Hui. I thought she was a calm cat.
But if she connects everyone here and there...
And me—
Seo Jin must've had a hard time.
No way. Oh Yun Hui and Su Ryeon are best friends.
How could she meet Su Ryeon's husband?
Yea, Oh Yun Hui hates Chairman Ju.
Right, Doctor Ha? You know they have a bad relationship.
If they have a bad relationship, how could they work together?
I could tell they fell for each other.
She must've been so lonely living alone.
Stop that!
Stop it already.
You scared me.
Why are you like that?
For me,
ex-husbands can hear this much information.
Like foreign vibes, the cool ones.
Why don't you ask her personally.
Chairwoman, you're here.
Seo Jin. No.
Our Chairwoman, your beauty today is like that of an actresses.
And your color selection is amazing.
That's right. I haven't seen that before, is it new?
You look so beautiful, Chairwoman.
Take me shopping with you.
So I can learn how to have a good taste like you.
I'm Logan Lee's secretary.
The car is here.
Are we leaving right now?
I'll escort you to the party.
The kids can enjoy the concert in the community room.
- Eun Byeol, I'll see you later.
- Have fun.
Hey don't do anything bad.
But isn't Logan Lee close with  Oh Yun Hui? Why didn't he invite her?
What are you doing here?
We wanted to thank you. This is my daughter.
- I'm Bae Ro Na.
- Hi.
I really like Grace Jo.
Thank you for inviting my daughter to the special concert.
No, it's my pleasure.
Besides, you played a big part in establishing the contract.
Think of it as a compliment.
But the concert is held in the crystal room in this hotel, right?
The Hera Palace kids thought it would be at the community earlier.
I think there must have been some kind of a mix up. I'll be sure to let them know.
Now if you'd excuse me, I was in the middle of doing something.
You guys have a great day now.
Thank you.
Bye.
Let's go.
Where have I seen that bag?
Mom, I'm so excited and I can't wait. My heart feels like it's going to explode.
Am I really going to meet Grace Jo?
How many times are you going to ask? Are you really that happy?
Mom, you're so cool.
You work with such an amazing person. You're so cool.
Let's go.
You're were surprised, weren't you?
I'm ok. I'm going to go first.
I'll see you later.
Su Ryeon.
Be careful.
You too.
Here, all together.
Cheers!
How long has it been since we gathered like this?
It's the first time since Eun Byeol's family divorced, right?
Doctor Ha, you have an American mind.
You stay friends even after divorcing.
It's so nice to see.
There was need for you to come too.
You're the unwelcomed guest.
I got properly invited as an investor.
Investor?
The Myeong-dong land I invested in became a part of a co-investment company with Logan Lee.
You didn't know that?
Chairman Ju must have a lot of secrets from you.
The honeymoon phase is usually not like that.
The kids were so happy, I'm so thankful to Logan.
But how come Su Ryeon didn't come? I haven't seen her in awhile.
She went on vacation. For her hard work while the kids took midterms.
What's with this mood on such a nice day?
This won't do. Everyone, come on.
One shot!
Cheers!
- This is beautiful.
- Right.
Grace Jo Solo Concert
I'm going to get Grace's autograph on this dress.
If I have a daughter some day, I will pass it on as a family heirloom.
Do you mean we're meeting the prima donna of the New York Opera?
She is going to perform and even do an audition for us.
Can't I write down this kind of meeting on the personal statement?
'I received a personal audition from Grace Jo.'
By the way, why did Grace Jo invite us?
Father's business partner is an American theater owner so he must be close with musicians there.
Anyway, he must be very rich in America.
This is an important event so everyone be careful not to mess up.
Why am I
so tired?
Why isn't she here yet?
I know right, it's been a while.
It's my mom.
Mom, did you arrive yet? How's the party? It's awesome, right?
Hello? Mom, why aren't you saying anything?
Je Ni, save me!
What's wrong? What happened?
What?  What's going on?
I don't know. She just called me crying asking me to save her.
What's wrong with my phone? I don't have signal anymore.
I'll call Father.
It doesn't work for me either.
It's dead.
At Hera Palace? There's no way.
This won't do. I want to go out and try calling.
Me too.
What is this? What's wrong with this?
The door doesn't open!
What are you talking about? Move.
What the heck?
What are you doing? Why would the door be locked?
Open up!
Everyone, go back down and take your seats
What the—  Who is that?
- Who is it?
-Whose voice is that?
Who's playing this kind of joke!
Everyone, calm down.
The show is about to begin.
Cut it out and just open the door!
Chairman Ju!
Doctor Ha!
Attorney Lee, Attorney Lee!
- Ugh my head.
- Teacher Cheon!
Get up!
Ow, my head.
Sang Ah, wake up.
Wake up!
Where are we?
Oh, hey.
Ah damnit.
What is this?
- What is that over there?
- What?  What is it?
It's on fire.
What?
What the—
What is that?
Mom?
Mom!
What is that? Mom!
Why is my mom there?
Mom!
Hera Palace
Let us out!
I have your parents. They need to be punished.
What bullshit are you spewing!
Are you saying you kidnapped our parents? Do you even know who my dad is that you're doing this?
Come out right now.
Is anyone out there!
We're in here!
Pick up!
She's not answering. Mom.
Mom!
No!
It's no use.
No one is going to come and help you.
This voice.
That's... the place.
What do you mean?
Min Seol Ah?
There's no way.
Why would Mom and Dad be there?
Mom!
- Mom!
- Dad!
Mom! I was wrong!
No!
What is this?
- It's gasoline!
- Shit!
What! What's wrong?
It's a bomb!
We have to survive no matter what!
- No, no! Don't touch it!
- Don't move!
Look at here! The door is locked!
What?  The door?
Save me! Save me!
Save us!
There's no signal!
Mine too.   There's no signal.
Over there! There's a person over there!
- Where?
- Over there!
Over here!
Don't just stand there but open the door!
- Please take us out of here!
- Come over here and help us out of here!
Our dresses are all ruined!
What's going on?
Mom!
What is this?
Your parents are going through exactly what you guys did in the past.
Is there something wrong?
Your parents will die instead of you.
No. No. No, Mom.
No!
No! Mom!
I was wrong!
No!
What an idiot.  I think the fire spread on.
Fire?
I damaged the door earlier.
Save me! Open the door!
Open the door!
- Let's go.
- Then what about her?
- I don't know.
-Don't go!
- She'll figure it out herself.
- Let's hurry go.  What if the car blows up?
Don't leave!
Mom!
Why did I call out for mom back then?
If I had a mom, wouldn't I have gone through something like that?
What on earth do you think you're doing?
There are people in here! Won't you stop this instant?
Hey, are you insane? Why did you start a fire?
Why? Are you scared of dying?
What the—
Was it okay when your kids did it?
Your kids started a car fire and ran away.
- What are you talking about?
- Tell me in a way we can understand!
- Min Seol Ah!
- What?
What are you saying? What do you mean Min Seol Ah?
That day, there was a fire in the van.
What do you mean a fire?
The kids lit the candles on the cake
and said Min Seol Ah almost burned to death.
The Penthouse Preview
Kidnapping, trapping, blackmailing!
Min Seol Ah is my daughter!
Take a lot of crap so screw yourselves.
- Do you like me?
- It was hard, wasn't it?
Don't be mistaken and think it's going to end like this.
The sin that I mistook the real culprit who pushed Seol Ah for my friend.
You can just kill her!
In the most painful way at last.