Venus delegates Program D
Episode 12
The future is a lie
The past is a lie
The Future is a Lie
Youth Dream
Brothers TV
忙 hangs out at night
Guess what about the熱-blooded
Chao Xiaoying
Chaoying
Could я became put into y Effectiv state?
Here it is!
A bunch of invention?
How dare I lock myself up here?
and killed your wives walk the Mia's land.
You think you can kill us all?
Who are you?
ẩ乐月
The mysteriousồi
was slipped away.
Is this why my parents
came with it?
Do you know me?
Come back to your seat.
Do you...
Who is it?
No one.
No one can tell a story with me.
I miss you so much.
げ there is another men.
You are the Man in Black.
Either you and your sí組 그렇죠解於某冥淵,
or your soulmate,
Everyone
You've given me so many silver silk books.
Since you never talk,
I'll call you Xiao Hei.
If you don't talk,
you'll be a stranger.
Right?
Xiao Hei.
Do you know the story of silver silk books?
I'll call you Xiao Hei.
I made a mistake
when I was young.
I was punished and banned.
Father locked me up.
I left the place to look for my mother.
But I couldn't find her.
I found a silver silk book.
I took so long for it.
That's the best dessert I've ever had.
Later, you told me that it's the silver silk of the Zhou season.
From then on, I'll buy it as long as I want to.
Xiao Hai, why don't you help me to send my letter to my mother?
My mother is the most elegant and most noble woman in the world.
She loves me the most. She'll give you the best thing and try to save me.
Really? Can't I just leave?
Write it down. Actually, I've been thinking for a long time.
You've been keeping an eye on me, but you're not too bad.
At least, you didn't win the project.
I'm still your enemy, right?
You dare not kill me and let me go.
But, I'm too helpless to stay alone.
How about...
You guys kill me.
Please kill me!
Xiao Hai, Xiao Hai! Xiao Hai!
I'm still being rejected.
It's okay.
It's okay to live.
Just live like this.
Your mom said that the people here are too cold to fight her.
And, she's Installian from elementary school.
Mom,Derials, shall we go?
Nothing else.
Zhu Ze
I'm here.
Great.
I can finally go back to the bottom.
Do you want to know who he is?
Xiao Hei.
Mother.
Get him out of here.
Love,
and your life expression.
You're my brother here.
Mi name...
Ni name...
Su potion.
I could drop you out.
Is the man ready?
I can't remember.
Didn't the neurological operation
make a difference?
Yes, doush wizard!
Spiderjetlar!
Do you know
Why did I come back to Xia Guang?
I understand.
So,
I'm just a blind man.
I'm just a joke.
I'm sorry.
Qing Ling,
I have something important to tell you.
I need to do something for the rest of my life.
I understand.
I've been in the prison.
I've seen Qing Chuan.
You're awake, Xiaohui.
You fainted just now.
Are you okay?
Xiaohui,
I'm thinking,
do you come to visit me often?
Do you feel the same way as me?
It's okay.
Just like the seed you gave me,
there's always something to blossom.
The body was found under the sea of ​​chongkong in the city.
Who killed him?
Yes.
Mo Qing Chuan.
He was so arrogant.
He was afraid that he wouldn't be able to hide.
Will you hate him for me?
Master.
In your heart,
I'm more important than Mo Qing Chuan.
Qigong.
It turns out that
I'm different from Master and Mo Qing Chuan.
Master.
Where have you been?
I've seen an old friend.
Old friend?
A friend I treasured.
Why didn't Qigong hear about it?
Master, you still have such a friend in the capital?
Maybe you'll meet him in the future.
You two look alike.
You might be very fated.
Very similar?
Is it normal to be with Qigong?
A little bit more mature than you.
Then, should Qigong be changed to a new one?
Yes.
Then, why don't you bring Qing Lei wine to him?
Okay.
I'll bring it to him next time.
Master, in Qigong's eyes,
Master and Qigong are not alike.
Qigong.
Junior brother, I'll be in the morning tomorrow.
Let's eat together.
Yes.
Master.
Junior brother, what's wrong?
Mo Qing Chuan.
You really came back?
Since he chose Qian'en Manor,
he can't let him open the door before the world.
Yes.
My wine is only for Master.
But Master can change anyone.
Clearly!
Master is upset.
His anger hasn't Inside what he wrote.
Master couldn't read.
Your anger isn't Chun entschieden Thirteenth Master.
Oh yeah.
Tomorrow is the birthday of Senior Sister.
What good will you buy?
Master's sweet and sour pork ribs are so delicious.
No, Master's everything is delicious.
Okay, get ready to eat.
Okay.
By the way, Master, I forgot to buy watermelon.
I just tried the watermelon.
I want to eat it.
Okay, I'll go buy it with you.
Oh no, I forgot to buy the watermelon.
Master, do you have money?
No, Master's money is all here.
I'll go get it.
Master, wait for me. I'll be right back.
Jiang Kun!
Master...
I...
Since you're here,
just die here.
Come.
Master, don't!
Master!
20...
30...
Such a powerful knife. Why didn't I hear about it before?
Why didn't I see you use the Mo family's knife before?
Why did you lie to me?
So, this is the real destruction.
Master!
How are you?
Master has a wound.
We can't stay here for long.
Who attacked you?
I don't know.
Who are your enemies?
Chen Siqi, Zhou Zheng, Mo Junyu...
And...
Can you hold on?
Yes.
We can't stay here anymore.
We have to go.
Where?
In the Prince's Mansion.
Senior Sister, take a seat.
Here, take the medicine.
Master!
If you see him one day,
he will tell you in person.
He will tell you in person.
He has been looking for you.
I have met General Mo Junshan for a long time.
Now I am suspicious.
I am the traitor Mo Qingchuan.
Actually, I used to be the old man of the Mo family.
I have been hiding for a long time.
I am the one who saved you and me.
Come with me.
Master, you are Mo Qingchuan.
Yinchuan City, Xuxia City.
Yinchuan City, Yinchuan City.
Please, two things.
First, find a famous doctor.
And get the new doctor.
Second, protect this place.
Wait for me to come back.
Yes.
Mo Qingchuan has not only recovered,
but also recovered.
He has recovered.
He has become so much better.
Yes.
But he is still in a good mood.
He seems to be injured.
He was saved by Xia Qi Guang in the Prince of Jiang's Mansion.
He must not be recovered.
Find an excuse to investigate the case.
I will take down the Mo Wang.
If he dares to resist,
I will make him pay for his crime.
Master Shi.
The general is resting.
The capital is just back.
He is treating Mr. Mo.
The capital?
Mr. Mo's uncle.
The capital is almost broken.
I can only take care of it.
I am very good at the medical skills of my uncle.
If I have the chance to meet him,
I will take you to meet him.
I understand.
Come in.
Both hands and hands are almost broken.
The front window is white.
The air is warm.
The back window is white.
The front window is warm.
So he suffered so much in Chu.
You are his disciple.
The crown prince who broke the crystal.
Xia Qi Guang.
He sent a letter to me earlier.
He asked me to come back to you.
Master, how is he?
He is fine.
He is looking for you.
It looks like the fetal is left as far as possible.
You cannot see the muscle chorus frompineilis.
How is it?
The details were confirmed.
Explorer thought the same.
She thought we had a war still.
tan side- provide nobody.
Even in the bad times year is not to know.
allowed toarina
hair weapon
release
cut the teacher
jie
mon your
love
Double
Bolton
discharges
who
he
lot
on fine
He was forced into a deep place.
That's why he practiced such a bad technique.
Don't let him be in the cave.
Otherwise, he'll die.
Send me back one day.
I water now.
How to do it?
Do I have to stand here?
After thehanГethe's amounts of ants.
There are about twenty of them,
collaborate with them and give them money.
It's written on theした.
girl.