♫  Dive with you, towards the wide sea  ♫
♫  Jump in love, I fly with wings called you  ♫
♫  There is nothing to be afraid of  ♫
♫  In the world called you, it sparkles and lingers here  ♫
♫  What I found while wandering was you who
was always by my side  ♫
♫  I'm already ready for you  ♫
We're Cheol and Mi Ae.
(T/N: Music group)
♪  Don't misunderstand  ♪
♪  Tell me who that guy is  ♪
♪  It's not true  ♪
♪  Then tell me the truth  ♪
♪  I only love you  ♪
♪  I'd rather you tell me you're leaving  ♪
♪  Why are you...  ♪
♪  I gave myself up and only loved you  ♪
♪  Was that enough for you?  ♪
♪  How could you be like this to me, who's like an idiot?  ♪
♪  I want to love again  ♪
♪  I want to  ♪
♪  I want to meet someone  ♪
♪  Hey, come on!  ♪
♪  I want to love again  ♪
♪  I really, really want to  ♪
♪  I want to love  ♪
Every once in a while, we need to karaoke and tune our vocal cords.
- Man, my stress is flying away.
- Right?
- Man!
- What?
I forgot to sing "Never Ending Story."
It's a must karaoke song.
How could I forget to sing that?
♪  If I long for her  ♪
♪  I'll meet her eventually  ♪
Stop, please stop.
♪  I hope some movie-like events  ♪
♪  occur to me  ♪
♪  On a tough day...  ♪
You look like you're having a tough time.
Right?
♪  I couldn't protect you  ♪
♪  You remained in my beautiful memories  ♪
Whoa... and then all together.
♪  Whoa...  ♪
When you... sing...
you lack soul.
What are you saying? I'm full of the soul from head to toe.
Hey, honestly, sincerely...
have you ever longed for someone?
- Of course.
- Who?
Min from pre-med, Hyo Eun from med school.
Ha Jeong from residency.
Li Yeon, Ji Hye, Ji Seon, Jae Eun, Eun.
I wonder how they're all doing.
Not like that.
You feel a pang in your heart when you think of that person.
You feel like you absolutely need that person.
While walking down the street or while eating,
someone who keeps visiting your thoughts...
Someone you want to meet even by coincidence...
You have someone like that?
Well, do you?
Just... Well...
I do have someone...
who feels like an unfinished story.
It's all over once you break up.
Stop being so hung up by yourself.
You shouldn't sing "Never Ending Story."
Why not?
Affectionate and lonesome...
A never-ending love, never-ending longing!
If you've never felt these things,
you have no right to sing this song.
You're right.
Man, sorry. I won't sing it.
I won't.
♫  When I open my eyes again  ♫
♫  I feel like I'm so far away  ♫
♫  I watch helplessly like this  ♫
♫  As we're left behind like a beautiful scene  ♫
♫  The reason why it hurts so badly like this  ♫
♫  The reason why I keep having expectations, thinking perhaps  ♫
♫  We're so beautiful, no need to envy anyone  ♫
♫  Needing nothing more  ♫
Shit, where is it?
You're up?
Yeah.
Do you want coffee?
Yeah, sure.
It looks good on you.
Have you seen my clothes?
What clothes?
What do you think? My clothes!
- The clothes I wore yesterday.
- They're gone?
You hid them, didn't you?
Me?
Are we the fairy and the woodcutter? Why would I do that?
(T/N: Korean fairytale)
They disappeared. Knock it off and give them back.
- Are you sure you searched thoroughly?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
- Gosh! Go look for them. Hurry up.
- You want to bet?
- Go ahead.
Hold on.
I'm going to look for them.
- It's a bet, for sure.
- Look.
- A bet.
- They're not there.
Let's see.
You probably hid them.
They should be around here...
Look!  They're here.
See? They're here.
See?
I was certain they weren't there.
In any case, you have a tendency to suspect others.
Get out. I'll change and be right there.
Let's eat breakfast and then get changed.
Let's have breakfast.
Try it and see how it tastes.
I'll enjoy it.
Park Jae Hoon, you're quite the cook.
It's delicious.
You want some jam on that?
Thank you.
It's good.
I love you.
My heart hurts when I think of you.
And it absolutely has to be you.
I keep thinking about you.
Don't I have...
the right to sing "Never Ending Story" now?
Yeo Reum,
let's stop playing tag now.
I don't want to argue about trivial things...
or play hard-to-get. I just...
I just want to be genuine with you.
There's not much time left until Kingdom ends.
Filming ends this week,
so first...
the things I need to do in Kingdom,
and take care of what needs to be taken care of.
And then,
let's properly talk about this again.
What do you think?
Sure.
Let's do that.
- Writer Han.
- Yes.
Where's John Jang?
I think he's still at the gym.
Can we talk for a moment?
Go ahead.
You know how you promised to expose your butt before the program started?
I did.
I think the time has come.
Kingdom is going to end earlier than expected, though.
And?
I don't want to flash my butt on a sinking ship.
Nothing can get in my way right now.
The recording of the interview where you
volunteered to show your butt if I let you join the program...
It's in my hands.
I also have the video of you blabbering about how you flirt with hundreds of girls.
How about it?
Should we expose that instead of your butt?
Where and how do you want me to expose it?
My hip...
John Jang.
- Yes.
- Actually...
how do you feel about a kiss instead of exposure?
A kiss?
It's going well with Jang Tae Mi.
I'm not sure if it's going well enough for a kiss.
Like you said, we're ending the program early.
A butt reveal is a bit...
iffy timing.
Let's make it romantic
and go for a kiss on the last date.
- Hee Chang.
- Yes?
Are the cast all ready?
Yes, they're on standby.
- They all have their mics on?
- Yes.
Okay, make sure to follow them.
- Okay.
- All right.
Should we also add more flowers?
In my opinion, adding more flowers would be nice.
- Over here.
- Yes.
- When they come in later,
- the cast members...
- All right.
Their faces need to show.
So Yeon, we'll start filming.
Okay.
Excuse me, PD Goo Yeo Reum.
Yes?
I want to go home.
So Yeon...
you feel that way because filming is tough, don't you?
I just want to quit everything.
Do you know how lousy and embarrassing...
it feels when no one...
likes you?
Every time I have to choose someone in the Kingdom...
every time I have to be chosen...
I want to disappear.
So Yeon...
you know... my wedding was called off. Right?
At the time, I felt... really humiliated.
I just wanted to disappear from the earth.
But if I just run away,
that's really cowardly.
In the end, I need to take responsibility for my life,
so I forced myself to endure.
My humiliation... was directed at my acquaintances
and my parents' acquaintances,
but it must be tougher for you.
I know how hard it is to put your name
and your face on the line
to come out on TV.
So hang on...
Hang in there for a bit longer, So Yeon.
I can't endure it any longer.
Senior,
we start filming in five minutes.
Han So Yeon,
you need to be on standby...
Hee Chang, go on ahead.
Oh, okay. I understand.
So Yeon, let's begin filming for now,
and let's talk afterward.
I'll do my best to think about what you can do from your perspective.
I'm going to mark the slate. One, two, three.
We'll begin filming.
Today, before the final selection, you'll go on final dates.
We're going to hand out time coupons to each of the members.
- The time coupons.
- Okay.
How cute.
You can use your time coupons on whomever
you want to go on a date with.
However, the date
is only possible when the same amount of time is exchanged with each other.
The members can now ask anyone they'd like on a date.
Will you go on a date with me?
You should go on a date with me.
This guy...
I'll use two hours with Hwang Jang Goon,
and one hour with Lee Hoon Hui.
She's using two hours on Hwang Jang Goon.
I know...
How unexpected.
This time,
I'll go.
Ji Wan, your first date was with me.
Let's go on this final date together, too.
Okay.
Do you want to do it together?
I'd like to.
Excuse me...
Hold on.
I'm sorry.
Please, go on a date with me.
Just for 30 minutes.
Sure.
Something must've happened between them.
Close up on Tae Mi's expression.
What just happened?
Writer... What's wrong with Park Ji Wan?
I don't know.
Why is she asking John Jang on a date?
Did something happen while the camera was off?
I wouldn't know.
That's so random. It's annoying.
The members who still haven't decided on their date,
please make a decision now.
Will you go on the final date with me?
Jae Hoon,
your words seem somewhat more meaningful than it sounds.
Hwang Jang Goon, Geum Soo Mi, two hours.
Geum Soo Mi, Lee Hoon Hui, one hour.
Jang Tae Mi, John Jang, two hours and 30 minutes.
John Jang, Park Ji Wan, 30 minutes.
Park Ji Wan, Kim Jun Ho, two hours and 30 minutes.
Park Jae Hoon, Han Ji Yeon, three hours.
- PD Kim.
- Yes.
What are you thinking so deeply about?
There's a picture I didn't predict.
You mean John Jang and Park Ji Wan?
I think it'll be entertaining.
As a topper.
We'll see once we're done filming.
Ji Wan.
- Joon Ho...
- Just now...
What was that?
Why did you ask Chef John Jang on a date?
- Well...
- Are you playing with me right now?
It's nothing like that.
Everything has come to an end now.
For the last time, I wanted to go on a brief date with him...
with Chef John.
You have a skill for screwing someone over.
I wasn't aware.
I don't think I did anything wrong.
In "Kingdom of Love," you can freely share conversations with anyone you want to.
All this time, there's a story we've been weaving.
What will people think while watching the show?
The picture...
The picture doesn't look right.
The story isn't pretty.
God, this is frustrating.
Jae Hoon.
Yeo Reum.
What are you doing here?
Just briefly in thought.
Sorry.
For what?
For complicating things.
Acting smart,
acting like a professional producer,
I put on all sorts of acts, and tried to look cool.
I thought I could at least
govern my own heart without a problem.
The possibility...
of you becoming someone else's Jae Hoon...
instead of my Jae Hoon pains my heart
and makes me so jealous.
So I'm sorry for complicating things
for you at this time.
I'm sorry I'm so selfish.
Yeo Reum,
it's okay for you to be selfish.
To me, anything is okay.
From start to finish,
it's okay for you to do whatever you want.
Why is that okay?
Why is everything okay with you?
As long as you're my Goo Yeo Reum.
As long as I'm your Jae Hoon.
Whenever I had a tough time, you were by my side.
You were by my side until the end.
I think that's why I was so confident.
You were always watching over me.
So even in humiliating situations, I didn't feel humiliated.
I'll continue to be like that.
♫  Even if I love you in my excitement  ♫
When everything goes back to the way it was,
at that time...
I'll be good to you, so you can be selfish to me
until the end.
I'll do that for you from start to finish as well.
♫  Or probably just telling myself as I endure  ♫
Thank you.
♫  A love so precious under the scorching sun
burned me black and left  ♫
♫  I hoped you'd be my final love  ♫
- Hee Chang, you'll accompany John Jang, Park Ji Wan, and Jang Tae Mi's date.
- Okay.
And Writer Han can accompany Hwang Jang Geum and Geum Soo Mi's date.
Okay.
♫  What's wrong with you? You saw wrong  ♫
♫  I've lived by my guts all this time  ♫
♫  But after loving once, I got hurt big time  ♫
♫  Summer, I can't live without you, never  ♫
♫  I miss you, please come back to me  ♫
Oh, yes!
♫  I'm going to leave you by my side again  ♫
It's an honor to escort you.
Watch your head.
♫  This summer, where are you, my love?  ♫
♫  I think I know what love is now  ♫
♫  You don't know how much I need you  ♫
♫  I can't live because I miss you so much  ♫
♫  I loved you with tears, and you made me leave  ♫
You said... you absolutely wanted to show me someplace...
It was here? Hang Jang Goon's gym?
Yes, shall we go in?
Wait! Do we need an entire hour and a half in there?
You're right. We should get a move on then.
Let's hurry and go in.
Okay, be careful.
Your date time is up.
Soo Mi will ride the staff car to Seoul now.
Oh, okay.
It's already time?
Gosh, what a bummer.
Jang Goon, you should get ready to go, too.
Okay.
Soo Mi, I'll go after I take a quick shower.
- See you at the resort later.
- Sure.
Okay.
By the way, Hwang Jang Goon.
Yes?
- To be honest, I'm upset.
- Why?
In order to advertise your gym, you insisted on dragging me here.
If I had known this would happen, I wouldn't have gone on a date with you.
What do you mean by advertisement? That wasn't the intention I had in mind.
Who do you think you're kidding?
Out of the two-hour date, we spent an hour and a half on the ride down to Cheonan,
filmed you working out, and filmed you boxing.
You call this a date?
It's an advertisement.
I think... there's been a misunderstanding—
What misunderstanding?
I was...
even envious of the term dirt spoon.
(T/N: People born into poverty)
I lived without any hope.
Without a spoon and just my bare hands and body, I worked like a dog to get to where I am now.
As soon as I graduated high school, I spent fruitless time as an uncommissioned officer in the military
and barely gathered enough money to open a Muay Thai gym.
And with that, I gathered more money to expand the business until I got to this point.
With just my body alone, I became the CEO of a 300-pyeong fitness center.
(1 pyeong = 35.5832 sq. ft.)
I understand that you're exhausted, earnest, and desperate,
but it's a fact that you manipulated me.
It wasn't that I manipulated you.
I just wanted to show you.
The merit I possess is my resilience.
Just that alone.
I've accomplished this much and will live more diligently going forward.
And I wanted to show you that I could fight with anyone and knock them out.
That's why I brought you here.
So Yeon, I'm PD Goo Yeo Reum.
Are you inside?
So Yeon.
The person you are calling is not answering the phone...
So Yeon?
By the way, where are we going?
You'll know once we get there.
What the heck? You're making me curious.
You'll probably like it.
It's so incredible here.
Right?
How did you find a place like this?
I learned about it coincidentally, and I planned to bring the woman I like here.
Am I the woman you like?
Jae Hoon.
Yes.
Today, you give off a different vibe.
I do?
It's different than usual.
Well,
it is the end.
It sounds... somewhat foreboding.
I have a feeling it'll be...
a heartbreaking ending,
not a joyful one...
while observing your expression.
Ji Yeon...
I'm sorry, but can we share a conversation without any cameras?
Would you like that?
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Hold on.
Ji Yeon,
since I met you on the blind date, until I met you in "Kingdom of Love" again,
I've made great memories thanks to you.
Did you ask to talk privately, so you could tell me that?
I don't...
think I can reciprocate...
your feelings.
I'm sorry.
Is that... the conclusion you've come to?
Yes.
It's because of PD Goo Yeo Reum, isn't it?
What can we do with our feelings?
I can't control my feelings, either.
It's probably the same for you.
I don't know what you'll think of me,
but please hear me out without getting offended.
I'm going to...
make a final selection.
I'm going to select you.
In "Kingdom of Love," my final selection...
reflects my sincerity toward you.
Please regard it as my responsibility and courtesy...
toward a person who deserves respect.
What about a green onion?
- A green onion?
- Yeah.
They'll carry a green onion like a bouquet of flowers,
and ask, "Will you stay with me until our hair turns white like the roots of a green onion?"
(T/N: Common question asked in wedding ceremonies)
And then?
If rejected, they get smacked in the face with a green onion.
What do you think about the green onion slap? Doesn't it sound good?
It is funny...
This is funny?
I think it's totally lame.
I like it.
Keep it for now.
Kang Chae Ri, let's proceed with some sincerity.
The original plan was to make the final selection romantically happen on Jeju Island.
Can't you tell? There's no romance.
Since the moment early termination was decided, season two is bound to end ridiculously.
There is romance.
Confessing with a sincere heart, exchanging bouquets,
and also lay down some candles in the garden.
It's boring.
Let us focus on the nature of this.
The viewers are interested in who ends up with who anyway.
It's that result.
Must you mess with the process in the middle?
Yes, I must.
Cliché is lame.
What's up, PD Kang? Have you got a good idea?
Goo Yeo Reum...
I guess we need to go the romantic route, as you said.
What's this? This is giving me bad vibes.
- Writer...
- Yes.
Please prepare a cake... and make it...
a very sweet one.
Try some. It's the signature dessert of my restaurant.
Thank you.
It's... really delicious.
You were... surprised because I asked you out on... a date, weren't you?
I wasn't surprised.
I had in mind that you were a good person, so...
I also wanted to have a conversation with you.
But why is it 30 minutes?
Is there a reason why you asked only for 30 minutes, ripping the card in half?
I thought you might refuse if I took...
too much time from you.
Since it's the last date... every second is precious.
So I thought I shouldn't take... too much of your time.
You could've asked for one hour.
It's lunchtime.
You came to a restaurant, but I'm sorry I couldn't even...
treat you to a meal, you know.
It's okay.
The cake is... really delicious.
Excuse me, 30 minutes are up.
Park Ji Wan, please move to your next date location.
John Jang, we'll have Jang Tae Mi come in now.
Thank you so much for coming...
out to the date.
I was bored to death waiting outside.
Oppa!
Oppa, are you ready for today?
For what?
You didn't hear it from PD Kang Chae Ri?
Are you okay with that, Jang Tae Mi?
Even if the scene of you kissing me gets broadcast?
We did already come out here. So it'd be nice to gain some attention.
It's better than being the background.
I'll look forward to it.
It looks delicious.
Please enjoy.
What's this?
I'm sorry.
I left... my phone here.
Ji Wan!
Park Ji Wan!
Here.
It's your phone.
I'll get going.
John Jang didn't kiss her?
Yes, the mood was disrupted in the middle.
What the heck, seriously!
The dating scene came out nice and romantic, though.
Chef John did the whole fire show, too.
Should I just have him flash his butt tonight?
- Kang Chae Ri?
- Why?
Let's just move on.
You think I can't do it?
You will, and you can.
I'm sure you can do it.
However, the final selection is tomorrow.
If we just flash the butt with no context, even the cast will be awkward.
Also... we're busy tonight.
Right, Hee Chang?
We have to finish the sponsor advertisements.
There are more important things than Chef John's butt.
Hee Chang... go out and bring me the PPL film times.
Okay, I got it.
- Please get the full view.
- Okay.
You have the pictures you took during the dates today, right?
Male casts, please go out to the garden and upload them with your phones.
Female casts, please
confirm the pictures through the TV here.
Please move to your positions now.
All right, let's go.
Looking good. You two look good together.
We'll check the dating pictures right now.
- Isn't that Soo Mi?
- Yes.
You two went to the gym?
Yes, we went to Jang Goon's gym.
My Soo Mi is here? Was it fun?
Yes, it was. Look at the pictures.
No, I don't want to.
Whoa, Ji Yeon is so pretty.
You went to such a beautiful place.
By the way... she's really gorgeous.
Where's that?
We just had a date... at his restaurant.
What's up with that dad joke?
What? What did he say?
Would you...
sleep with me once?
- There.
- Yes, yes.
We'll begin preparing to shoot.
Male casts on the left side and
female casts on the right side, please.
PD Goo, what do we do?
I can't find So Yeon anywhere.
- What do you mean?
- She's not in her room.
I looked everywhere she might be, but she was not there.
Whoa, we have to start shooting now, though.
When did you last see her?
Well... this morning.
She was definitely here until the morning.
- Ahn So Yeon disappeared?
- Yes.
I had the entire staff look for her for 30 minutes,
but she's nowhere to be seen.
Talk about pulling all the stops...
She ran away out of embarrassment.
What shall we do?
Postpone the shooting until we find her?
Let's just go with it.
She's a side character, anyway.
Even so, it doesn't...
look so great since it's the last episode.
We can't postpone the shoot just because of her.
We have more to lose than to gain.
Okay then.
- Are we ready?
- Yes, we are.
We're now going to go into final selections.
Please get ready.
It's the finale.
Everyone, please make your final selections in order.
I'll... also make the final selection!
Senior...
Ahn So Yeon?
- What's she doing?
- So Yeon?
What? What's wrong with her?
Hee Chang... call 911 first, just in case.
Yes, I got it.
Ahn So Yeon!
PD Goo.
So Yeon... what are you doing here?
What am I doing? I'm making the final selection.
So Yeon! First...
it's too dangerous over there. Just wait...
Hold my hand and come over to this side.
I don't want to. Don't come closer!
So Yeon...
I know...
you had a hard time at the Kingdom all this time.
Even so...
doing this here is too dangerous.
I'll hold you, So Yeon. Okay?
PD Goo...
people said...
I look cheap...
and my eyes look weird.
People who don't even know me well...
Why are they talking shit about me?
Why are they running their mouths as they want?
Who do they think they are?
Who do they think they are...
So Yeon...
That's all... my fault entirely.
You're a really good person, So Yeon.
I should've caught the good sides you have
on camera and showed them to people...
but I failed to do that.
I'm really sorry.
It's all the staff's fault.
It's all my fault completely.
So, So Yeon, hold my hand...
and come over here. Okay?
Gosh...
So Yeon... one second.
Try holding my arm.
I feel so dizzy.
So Yeon...
Give me the bottle.
Get yourself together a bit.
So dizzy...
- Hee Chang...
- Yes.
- You go up there.
- Okay, I got it.
What do we do?
- Hold my hand and...
- O-Okay.
Pull your legs up.
Come down here now.
Yeo Reum... Goo Yeo Reum!
Yeo Reum, wake up.
Goo Yeo Reum!
Can you hear me?
Yeo Reum.
Yeo Reum, get up.
No...
♫  We laughed together, those obvious moments  ♫
♫  So that they don't get erased  ♫
♫  Your name that's always been by my side  ♫
♫  Now, closer, closer, closer  ♫
♫  I miss you even if I write it down  ♫
♫  It's engraved with happy memories  ♫
♫  After hovering around me for a long time, then little by little  ♫
"Kingdom of Love, Season 2" filming ends here.
Everyone may go back home now.
A knifing incident and falling at the filming scene...
Submit a letter of apology and stand by.
I'm sorry.
What happened at the location?
Are you worrying about others even in this situation?
I just get that way without knowing.
I only had one thought that day.
What thought?
That I didn't get to answer you.
I wanted to tell you all along.
I love you.