PREVIOUS EPISODE
How do you feel about Toey?
Toey, who loves you.
PREVIOUS EPISODE
I’ve got a good feeling about him.
It seems there’s something within him that makes me feel good
PREVIOUS EPISODE
when he’s around.
It’s like I’m watching a masterpiece of art.
PREVIOUS EPISODE
If you even compare him to a piece of art,
I think this is not normal.
PREVIOUS EPISODE
You should clear things up with him.
Your class is done, right?
PREVIOUS EPISODE
Let’s eat.
Where are you taking me?
PREVIOUS EPISODE
You’re no longer mad at me, right?
I’m fine.
PREVIOUS EPISODE
You’re fine?
Well, then…
PREVIOUS EPISODE
Let’s make up.
I’m fine.
If you’re fine,
hold pinkies.
Q.
What’s up with this?
You suddenly took me to a meal.
Weird.
Eat quickly. I’ve got a class after this.
I also do.
What?
What is freaking wrong with Toey?
Damn it.
Shit.
Asshole.
Not now.
Get out of here.
DIRECTED BY SIWAJ SAWATMANEEKUL
So, how was it, Toey?
You had a meal with him.
I don’t know.
Hi, friends.
Babe, sit here.
Why are you bringing so many people to my place?
Come on, Peem, my friend.
They’re your acquaintances.
This is Khaofang, my dearest babe.
That’s Beer and Mick.
They know Toey.
With more people,
we can help brainstorm various ideas, you know.
Phum already told me about it.
Don’t make that sad puppy face.
Do you want me to punch him for you?
Babe.
My babe, relax.
Q is my friend, too.
So, how has the situation been going?
Well, it’s okay, I guess.
Really?
Actually, Q told me he has good feelings for Toey.
He did?
Well, yes.
If Q likes Toey, and Toey likes Q,
why not just date already?
Come on, Mick.
It’s not that simple.
Right.
That sounded like a piece of cake or something.
Honestly,
I think it’s good Q found out about this
because we should strike while the iron is hot.
I’ll make a move on Q!
Huh?
My friend, you must be out of your mind already.
You were still crying the other day.
Before this, I didn’t know how Q felt about me,
but you said he also has feelings for me, right?
He said he felt comfortable around you.
So, what are you going to do next?
I’ll keep fighting
because no matter Milk Frappe Boy and Toey,
Q has feelings for him.
So, I’m not afraid of anything anymore.
That’s the spirit, my dear bro.
So, let’s stick to the original plan, then.
Huh?
Q already knows I pretended to hit on Toey.
How could we stick to the original plan?
So Q will finally realize his feelings.
I think he has already realized it.
But what we should worry about or figure out is
whether Q will admit how he feels. That’s the point.
Honestly, I think we don’t need a plan anymore.
You just have to talk it over with him directly.
But give him some time first.
Don’t talk to him now.
No way.
I’ve been in pain for several years already, Peem.
I won’t waste another second.
What has gotten into you, Toey?
That’s my bro.
If Q doesn’t like talking nicely,
I’ll show him the real deal.
You’re the real deal, buddy.
Make him realize he’s messing with the wrong person.
Add some villain energy into yourself.
You must win.
He will be yours.
Add that energy.
You said you would make a move on Q.
What do you mean?
I’ll remain his mentee
and show him how I feel.
Are you sure?
Peem, you don’t believe I can do it?
I’ll wait and see, then.
Wait and see.
Peem, I’ll show you.
Q.
Well, what are you doing?
Working, obviously.
What do you want?
Nothing.
You said you weren't scared of him anymore, didn’t you?
You said it yourself that you'd show him the real deal.
Peem, Q is mean.
You said he has feelings for me too, didn’t you?
Did you lie to me?
I didn’t.
I told you already to give him some time.
What should I do then?
First of all, let go of my arm.
I told you already you’d need our help.
[Our target isn’t yielding at all.]
[What should we do?]
[You’re asking the right person.]
[I’ll drop by this evening with a surprise.]
Can we really believe Pun?
Trust me.
Let’s wait and see.
How savage this guy is.
Why did he ask us to come here?
No clue.
He said he’s bringing a surprise.
He kept us waiting too long.
If he doesn’t show up soon, I’m leaving.
Hey, hold on.
He’s arriving soon.
Just wait a bit.
My friends, I’m here.
It took you ages.
What’s up?
I have good news to announce.
Well, what is it?
Why do I strangely have a bad feeling about this?
You’re all going to Kanchanaburi.
We’re going to a volunteer camp!
Huh?
Are you happy?
Not even a little.
So this is your surprise?
Yeah.
Come on.
I thought it’s something about Q and Toey.
Peem!
Huh? What?
Me? Why?
Q and Toey are mentor and mentee.
Right?
Yep.
Right. That’s what he was getting at.
I’m not going.
I’m sorry but,
I’ve already signed us all up.
The professor also approved it already.
I’m the camp president this time.
So, what do we have to do?
Activities at school.
Read to kids and fix some stuff.
But now we still need more volunteers.
We need to recruit more people.
Stick these posters up around your faculties
to get more people to join us.
So, what do you say?
Do I have any choice?
I’m going to the Dentistry Faculty.
Come with me, Pun.
Sure, buddy.
I’ll handle Engineering.
Peem.
Huh?
Come with me.
You take them to your faculty with Toey.
Matt.
Yes, bro.
Where do you want me to stick it?
For the drink…
- Stick it on the drink?
- Pay for us.
Huh?
We don’t have any cash now.
Cover it for us.
Let’s go.
See you later.
I’ll pay you back later.
Peem, hurry up.
Alright. Wait a second.
Pay for mine, too.
Q, won’t you wait for Toey?
Do I have to pay for yours too?
Eh?
Money?
What’s wrong with you?
You were mad,
then avoided me
and then took me to a meal.
I can’t keep up with your moods.
You’ve been so up and down.
I’m not mad.
You’re not?
Can you act normally then?
Do you feel that uncomfortable when I’m around?
What do you mean by normal?
Just not like this.
You mean…like this?
You want it this way, right?
Stop.
We aren’t in the same league, Toey.
Q.
Why did you make me come with you?
So Q and Toey can get to talk.
Is it a good idea to leave them alone together?
This morning, Q still ignored Toey.
Come on.
I’m sure Toey can handle it.
But let’s get to work.
Take it.
Hurry up and stick it.
Why are we sticking so many?
Come on.
Just do it. Stop complaining.
What are you guys doing?
Hey.
We’re putting up posters to recruit more people to join our camp.
What camp?
Volunteer camp?
Yep.
Join us.
Invite Fang too.
Invite him yourself.
But someone like Fang won’t go.
Really?
But if he joins,
it will be our first time
on a trip to another province together.
Peem.
Huh?
Let’s head to the Architecture Faculty.
We’ve stuck enough posters here.
Also, we’ve got three more members already.
If you aren’t going, I’m leaving first.
I’ll go with you.
You aren’t eating with us?
You two go ahead.
What are you looking at? Let’s go.
Let’s eat.
Yeah.
Hey, since you have Phum here helping you,
take care of this for me.
I’ll be on a love mission now, buddy.
Bye-bye.
Tan!
You left me just like this?
You want to help me that much, right?
- Take them.
- All of them?
Go. Put them up.
Fang.
Peek-a-boo.
Why did you suddenly show up? What’s up?
Let’s go to the volunteer camp.
Nope.
I’m lazy.
Come on.
But I’m going upcountry
and spending nights there.
Can you stand not having me around?
Is it you or I who can’t stand it?
It’s me, of course.
Come with me.
- Please. Please.
- No.
Come on.
Come with me. Please.
I’m not going.
You’re going. You’re going.
Say, I’m going.
You’re going.
I’m not going. I’m lazy.
I can’t stand being without you.
Come with me, okay? Please.
Fine. I’ll go.
Let go already. I’m working.
Whose boyfriend is this?
He’s super cute.
Damn it, Tan.
You left me alone again.
Why are you going to the camp?
It’s Pun’s idea.
He wants Q and Toey to spend time together.
He didn’t ask if we wanted to go or not, though.
Let’s talk about you, then.
Someone like you joining a camp?
It won’t be comfortable, you know.
Why?
Do you think I can’t stand it?
I don’t know.
Are you heading home?
I want to take some pictures around.
Come with me.
Where?
Nearby your place.
Alright.
[Volunteer Camp Project]
[Book Donation]
Hey, I want to ride a bicycle.
You know how to?
You’re underestimating my skill again.
Follow me.
Hello.
I want to rent a bicycle, please.
Sure.
Ride well. Don’t let me fall off.
Hey.
What’s with you?
If you don’t want to fall, hold me tightly.
Are you ready?
There’s one spot where I want to take some pictures.
Really?
We’re almost there.
I’ll take some pictures around.
Just a minute.
You like taking pictures?
Uh-huh.
I feel taking pictures can capture good moments.
What did you just do?
Took a picture of you.
Why did you secretly do that?
I want to keep this moment.
Give it to me.
- What are you doing, huh?
- Give it to me.
Hand it to me.
Why?
You don’t like your picture taken?
It’s not like that.
But you secretly took it.
I don’t know if I look awkward in the picture or not.
Nope.
You look adorable.
Well, do you want to give it a try?
I’ll take a picture of you then.
Why?
To get back at me?
Nope.
You enjoy taking pictures, don’t you?
Those who enjoy taking pictures usually don’t have photos of themselves.
Give it a try.
How is it?
Handsome?
So-so.
So-so?
Let’s take a look again.
It’s still so-so.
So-so?
How about having a proper look?
Well, I’m leaving.
Where?
I’m heading home.
My camera?
If you want it, come get it yourself.
Do you remember me?
I hit your head the other day.
I see.
I remember you.
That was quite a knock, though.
I still couldn’t forget it.
What are you doing here?
Asking me to pay back for the drink?
Nope.
I’m applying for this camp.
Seriously?
I’m Kluen, third year.
I’m Peem, third year also.
Why are you joining this camp?
I think it looks fun.
How about you?
Do you see that guy?
He’s the camp president,
who forced all of us to join.
You’re here alone?
Yep.
I also invited my friends,
but they didn’t come.
I’m kind of lonely here.
Lucky enough, I still know you.
Don’t worry.
Tons of my friends are here.
Guys.
This is my friend, Kluen.
He’s coming solo.
He’ll be joining us.
Phum.
Beer.
Mick.
Q.
Fang.
Tan.
Chain.
Those two boys are second years, Toey and Matthew.
Honestly, I can’t remember their names.
What?
But I’ll try to remember them one by one.
Fair enough.
We can talk then.
Which faculty are you in?
Architecture.
Babe, he’s from your faculty.
Do you know him?
Are you sure?
Probably your boyfriend skipped class?
Don’t be surprised.
Hey. Don’t insult my boyfriend. He did attend.
It’s just that he slept in class.
I’m kidding.
Hello, Kluen.
Hello, everyone.
This is our volunteer camp’s first meet.
I’m Pun, third year from Political Science.
I’m the camp president.
This feels so weird.
I’m not used to seeing this version of him, really.
He can handle something formal, too, huh?
Did someone swallow him?
I’m curious too.
I think someone swallowed him whole.
Huh?
What?
We’ll divide our responsibilities later.
But this evening, we’ll open for book donation.
If you’re free, join me.
I’m not going.
I’ve got work to wrap up.
I’ll accompany you, Fang.
You two are glued together, aren’t you?
Exactly.
Can’t even be separated?
Sure thing.
Q, are you going?
Beer and I already committed.
We’re playing music there.
How about you?
Are you going?
I don’t think so.
I have to handle stuff at the faculty.
Architecture students are swamped with more assignments than us, huh?
Since we’re playing music,
should I prepare to dance?
If you think you can dance, just go ahead.
Mick, you said you’d dance, didn’t you?
♪ Come on, come row ♪
♪ Water runs deep, let’s keep the flow ♪
Hello, everyone.
We’re from the volunteer camp.
We’re going to Kanchanaburi.
You can drop off your books here for donation.
But if you don’t have any to donate,
feel free to listen to lovely music here.
Let’s go.
Why didn’t you go with your friends?
Why are you here watching me?
I want to be with you more.
Being with me is super boring.
How?
Sitting here and watching you work is relaxing.
It’s up to you, then.
Cute.
I’m talking about you.
Help me then.
Nope.
Today, I’m just here to watch.
So you aren’t helping?
Okay.
I didn’t expect we’d get this many books.
That’s right.
Let’s do it again next time, shall we?
I had so much fun today.
You had fun for sure.
I saw you dance the whole time.
That’s because you guys played music well.
How could I not dance?
Honestly, I’m a genius for choosing you guys to handle the music.
That’s more likely because you don’t know anyone else.
Come on.
Matt, is it heavy?
- You’re walking comfortably, carrying nothing.
- Did you enjoy it?
Yeah. It was fun.
It’s super heavy.
Hey, thanks a lot for today, guys.
Safe trip home.
See you later.
See you.
- Bye.
- See you.
Why did you come home?
I have something to talk to you about.
What is it?
Let me ask you a question.
Why do you like Tan?
Strange.
I’m just curious.
It seems like you usually don't pay much attention to him.
Are you expecting a serious answer?
Yep.
Well,
liking someone doesn’t need a lot of reasons.
He’s cute.
He’s funny.
When I’m with him, I feel at ease.
Especially when I’m stressed because of work,
he can help lighten my mood.
Good boy.
I’m not your dog.
Hey.
Are you listening?
You’re head over heels in love with him, bro.
Keep this between us.
Don’t tell him.
By the way,
can you tell me already why you asked?
Nothing much.
I’ll take a shower. I’m exhausted today.
I bet you’ve already found that person too, right?
I heard what you said.
Pun is dropping by, right?
He said he would make a camp banner,
asking me to prepare some colors.
We also need to help him.
A camp banner?
Yeah.
We’ll use it during the opening ceremony.
Why didn’t he order one properly?
Why do we need to make it ourselves?
He thinks
making the camp banner ourselves will get us into the real camp spirit.
It’s a camp banner.
It isn’t for a sports day.
I can’t stop him, you know.
Who can?
Chain.
Huh?
You guys are making work for yourselves.
What do you mean?
We’re going to a volunteer camp,
so this is what we should do.
Exactly.
Since you’re studying Fine Arts,
you’ll paint on this canvas.
I’ve drafted some wording here.
Tan and I will make the name tags.
How about Chain?
He’s got class.
Why do our tasks seem so uneven, huh?
He’s getting on your nerves.
Making name tags is difficult. Right?
True.
How?
Well,
it requires my delicate handwriting, bros.
Why are you faking a handsome voice?
I’m cool.
- Go ahead. Do your best, guys.
- Take your colors.
I’m off to class.
See you.
Toey, help us.
What’s up?
Help with what?
Peem.
- What?
- Peem.
For what?
Hey, are you getting back at me?
You want this, right?
What?
Hey?
Slightly.
Pun, I started to believe you now.
Guys, you’re in for it.
Peem!
Why are you doing this to me?
Come!
No way!
He’s passing out.
Pun, wash yours.
Pun!
You want to play, huh?
You’re playing like a kid. Stop.
My whole face.
Q.
Peem, you feel hot?
Guys, Peem feels hot.
Look. I’m stained.
That’s just a bit.
- Look at my tee.
- Why does it feel so cold?
Pun.
Thank you.
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
I was just thinking about funny stuff.
You aren’t laughing at my face, right?
What’s that funny stuff?
Look at us.
We’re third-year students already, but here we are playing with water.
Crazy.
I didn’t play.
I didn’t get wet at all.
I didn’t mean it as an insult, you know.
I just like it.
I feel at ease being with you guys.
I can do whatever I want.
I can be silly if I want to.
I can act like a kid if I want to.
Ptooey.
Enough.
That sounds cheesy.
I’ll splash more water on you.
A little pat on your shoulder.
A little pat on your head.
I’ll give you an extra.
Is there something in your water?
I’m curious too. Why does my head feel hurt after drinking it?
I’ll try.
Go ahead.
That’s so hard, Peem.
Hey, your face looks so hilarious.
Q, bring it down a notch.
How nice.
When you guys are together, you look so happy.
Absolutely, bro.
Look that way.
But I haven’t drunk it yet.
It’s the happiness we’re offering you.
Tan.
I’ve assigned you all as heads of each department.
We’re both studying Fine Arts, but why are our duties so different?
Why does Peem get to teach the kids,
while I get to paint the wall?
I think
Pun is afraid you’ll make the kids cry.
You’ve gone too far.
You'll be the first kid to cry then.
I’m not a kid anymore.
Hey. I’m staying out of this.
Why are Mick and you on the cooking team?
That’s because of my excellent cooking skill.
You just threw water spinach into the pan the other day.
And the oil splashed on me.
We’ll have some food to eat, right?
Delicious one.
Don’t you worry, Peem.
With me and my beloved Fang,
I guarantee you'll be full.
I’ll just get desserts instead of food for sure.
No sugar needed.
Well, that’s it.
Let’s get to work.
Let’s go.
Cooking team, let’s go.
What? Are you cooking now?
We’re practicing.
We’re preparing ahead, you know.
Should we buy cheap or expensive ones?
Any will do.
Just get good quality.
Take as many as you want.
I’ll take 10 then.
Sure.
Even if you want to buy everything in this store, I can pay for you.
Excuse me, I’ll take everything.
Which color should we go with?
This one.
How about earth-tone colors?
That’s right.
Q.
Toey, what are you playing at?
You’re bothering the shop owner.
Fang, don’t. Don’t do this.
I’ll carry it for you.
I’ll push the cart for you.
What are we getting?
I’ll get it for you.
Fang, are you tired?
Let me do it.
This one?
The one on top.
Over there.
Enough.
Whoa. Time flies so fast.
We’re going to the camp tomorrow.
I feel like
Pun just twisted my arm to go only yesterday.
Damn it.
Anyway.
Let’s grab something to eat.
I’m not available.
See you.
Fine. I’m leaving.
I’m hungry.
Let’s grab something to eat.
Don’t you have other friends?
I do, but I want to eat with you.
Hello? What’s up?
(Are you free now?)
(Help me with something.)
Yeah. What do you want me to do?
(Meet me at the Student Society's Office.)
Alright. I’ll hurry there.
I’m not free.
I’ll get going.
Where are you going?
I’m going with you.
Head home already.
I told you I’m not free.
Phum, you’re here too?
Nice. I’m looking for someone to help.
Alright. Should we get in now?
Let’s go.
I’m working on it alone.
Help me organize these books for the volunteer camp.
There are tons.
I called others, but none of them answered.
I can’t handle it alone.
Don’t worry.
Just put them in the boxes, right?
Uh-huh.
I’ve already sorted them.
You just need to put them in the boxes.
What’s your plan after this?
We haven’t eaten anything yet.
I’ll buy some food for you, then.
Wait here.
It won’t take long. I’ll be right back.
I’ll choose the dish for you.
Okay?
Thanks a lot.
What’s up?
The professor asked for me urgently.
I’m sorry,
but can you handle this for me first?
I’ll hurry back.
Sure thing.
It’s no big deal.
Right?
Yeah.
Do what you need to.
Thanks, buddy.
I’ll be right back.
Come. Let’s eat.
You don’t like the leaf parts?
Fang doesn’t either.
I don’t like the stems.
Let’s exchange, shall we?
By the way,
when I told you I had fun when I was with you guys,
I meant it.
I know.
You’ve told me already.
I just want to let you know,
and I hope it will keep going like this.
When I’m with you, I don’t have to worry much about things.
I get to do what I haven’t tried.
I can do whatever I want to.
Sure thing.
I’m your slave.
That’s not what I mean.
I know. I’m kidding.
That sounds like you’re confessing to me.
Maybe I am.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Keep eating.
Why do you keep looking at me?
Eat already.
[For Donation]
Let’s go home.
How about Pun?
Don’t worry.
I’ll text him.
I’ll give you a ride.
Passing through that way again?
I can pass through that way every day.
Head home quickly.
I’ll pack my luggage.
I haven’t started yet.
If I call you, answer it.
Just talk right here.
Pick up my call.
I want to talk to you.
He was just saying that.
[Pun]
What’s up?
(Sorry, Peem.)
(I talked to the professor for so long.)
(Thanks a lot for helping.)
No worries.
Go to bed early
so you won’t feel tired tomorrow.
(Okay. I’m hanging up now.)
See you.
What’s with you?
You aren’t calling, right?
Why haven’t you called?
Hello? Why are you calling me?
I’m heading to bed.
Are you sure?
You’ve been waiting for my call, haven’t you?
Me? I’m going to bed.
So how is it going?
Have you done packing already?
(Yep.)
(So, what’s up?)
(Why are you video-calling me?)
Nothing.
I just want to see your face.
That’s it?
I’ll hang up then.
Hey, hold on.
Well, I’m packing my luggage now.
I want to ask what you’re bringing.
Just pack like for any trip.
It’s similar.
Nope. That won’t work.
Your trip and my trip aren’t the same, though.
You must bring comfy outfits.
Wear something suitable for working on-site.
What do you think about this one?
Is it okay?
Seriously?
You’ll be sweating a lot wearing this.
So, I can’t bring this one?
You can’t, of course. Why did you even ask?
I can’t bring that one.
What do you think about this one?
You need my answer?
The left one is okay, but the right one isn’t.
Your left or my left?
This one is alright.
Yep.
And these two?
- I think I’ll go with this one.
- I’ll let you figure it out yourself.
You were born in Thailand.
Think it over.
This one?
I think this one isn’t working.
Great job.
Eh? You’re sleeping already?
Goodnight.
So, I’m falling for you already, right?
Or am I not?
How could I say I’m not?
I freaking like you now.
NEXT EPISODE
We’re holding a volunteer camp here for two days.
Pass me the ketchup.
NEXT EPISODE
Besides our camp activities,
don’t forget that we’re on a mission too.
NEXT EPISODE
Are you feeling hot?
Let me wipe your sweat off.
NEXT EPISODE
I’ll handle other tasks.
Just express how you feel.
NEXT EPISODE
Or else, someone else could steal your thunder, and it can’t be helped.
What are you doing?
NEXT EPISODE
Let me give you a goodnight kiss.