Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series
are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
It seems Chain has already won your heart.
You told me to act like I usually do.
How could I stand it?
What are you doing?
Your hair smells good.
You freaking take advantage of me.
Let me have a goodnight kiss first.
Thank you.
Goodnight.
Phum, don’t.
Let me smell this side too.
Thank you.
Goodnight.
DIRECTED BY SIWAJ SAWATMANEEKUL
You’re up already?
Where are you going?
Feeling shy after hugging me all night?
Who hugged who?
Be clear.
Why?
You weren’t shy when you let me kiss you.
What was up with you yesterday?
You seemed really moody.
I just didn’t like it.
You didn’t like it?
You didn’t like what?
Just forget it.
Come on.
You didn’t like what?
Huh?
Face me.
You didn’t enjoy this camp or what?
That’s not it.
Then what?
Well…
Actually…
Peem,
you got up already?
Hey.
I made this for you.
Thanks.
I didn’t know you’re also here,
so I didn’t bring one for you.
I’m sorry.
It’s fine.
I’ll share with him.
Peem, why did you get up so early?
You too.
Hey, I’m going to shower.
Yeah.
What’s wrong with this guy?
Did I interrupt something?
You didn’t.
Can I ask you something?
Uh-huh.
What’s your relationship with Phum?
You don’t have to answer if you don’t want to.
There’s nothing between us.
We’re just close.
I’m close with everyone in this camp.
I see.
I still stand a chance, then.
Huh?
Nothing.
Oho.
Well, please take care of this for me, then.
Pardon me?
Where are you going?
You aren’t helping us?
I need to help Q with painting.
- I’ll get going.
- 	Pun!
See you later.
Tan, keep fighting.
See you.
See you later, Tan.
You picked an easy task for yourself.
Look at this mess.
Can we even finish it today?
Alright, guys.
Let’s get to work.
Let’s get it done quickly.
- Move it.
- 	Handle it for me.
Beer, start working.
Mick, go ahead.
Do you think we’ll get to go home?
Babe, just stand here.
I’ll do it for you.
Where should we start?
Hey? Why are you making my babe do this?
Move. Move.
Let go.
Leave it to me.
Are you sure you can handle it?
Yes.
Ouch.
Take this box, too.
How could you make time to keep fit?
Strong.
Ouch.
Hey. Are you alright?
I’m alright.
Let me see.
Dress your wound now.
It’s this small.
It’s fine.
Don’t worry.
I’ll take care of it.
Let me see.
What are you doing?
I’m alright.
It’s just a small cut.
Come with me now.
You’ll live.
Ouch.
Babe.
The paper cut my finger.
Eh?
So, can you tell me already what’s wrong?
I’m fine.
Come on.
Let me do it.
Cry out if it hurts.
It won’t.
Ouch.
Do it gently, will you?
There, there.
It will heal soon.
What did you just do?
I’m not a kid anymore.
If you aren’t a kid, why act like one?
What are you doing?
I’m comforting you like adults do.
I’ll get back to work.
Stay here.
Don’t go anywhere.
Don’t hurt yourself again.
Thanks.
What?
I’ll go with you.
Why? Didn’t you hear me?
I told you to stay here.
I don’t want to be alone.
Fine.
Come on, then.
Let’s go.
Come on.
You said you aren’t a kid,
but you can’t be alone?
Let’s go now.
What’s wrong?
Are you worried about Phum?
Peem is taking care of him now.
Don’t worry.
He’ll be fine.
Got it?
If you understood it, then…
Look at you. You’re frowning already.
Look at you.
Your boyfriend is standing right in front of you,
but you’re worrying about another guy.
Oh yeah right!
Phum is my brother.
Right.
Whatever.
Make up with me.
Do it.
Come on.
Make up with me.
Hey, guys.
I want to paint with you.
Sure, Pun.
But I think this is too plain.
Should we draw something on it?
Just paint.
No drawings.
Why, Q?
When the students walk into the school,
they’ll see some cute pictures.
Do you agree, Chain?
Good idea.
Toey, you asked Chain,
while knowing he never says no to you.
You’d better ask Pun if we can draw.
Go ahead.
I guess the kids will like it.
Let’s draw some pictures, Chain.
We can draw cute animals or flowers.
Sounds nice.
I don’t know how to draw.
Teach me.
Sure.
I want to draw, too.
Q, what should we draw?
Why are you asking me?
Whatever you want.
You’re alright now, right?
What took you so long?
I’m alright.
Peem already dressed the wound for me.
What a relief.
You worried my boyfriend.
Watch it.
I’m really alright.
Thanks a lot.
No problem.
I started to understand you already.
Your brother is really stubborn.
Phum, is your finger okay?
Do you need surgery?
Come on.
It’s just a wound.
My finger wasn’t torn.
I told you
he’ll certainly live.
Hey, don’t go.
I’ll hammer nails for you.
Come on, babe.
This is seriously a no.
Babe, if you do it, and it hurts your finger,
what should we do?
Babe, I’m worried about you.
Alright.
It’s just a small wound.
I can do it.
Nonsense.
Stay here and do nothing.
I told you your brother is stubborn.
Organize the books, and don’t hurt yourself again.
I’ll do it.
Listen to him.
Thanks a lot.
Still some more?
What?
Organize the books,
or else you’ll hurt yourself again.
Peem,
was Phum hurt a lot?
I already dressed the wound for him.
He’s fine now.
Thank you.
Chain, what do you want to draw?
I’ll teach you.
You draw.
I’ll color it.
Deal.
Chain, come with me.
Where to?
Just come. Follow me.
I have something to talk to you about.
Why don’t we talk here?
Just follow me.
You raised your voice at me, huh?
I’ll handle it.
Here we go.
A fight is about to begin.
Put your brush down.
Let’s watch them.
We can’t miss the climax scene.
What are you looking for?
What’s up?
What’s wrong with you guys?
Wanna see a fun match
between Chain and Q?
What are Q and Chain doing again?
If you want to know, check it out yourself.
I see.
Why?
What’s wrong with Toey and me?
Well…
If you have nothing to say,
I’m heading back.
Hold on.
You like Toey?
If I like him, then why?
I didn’t think you’d be serious about him.
Chain, you should stop.
What did I do?
You know Toey likes me.
And?
Why then?
If you don’t really like him,
stay out of this.
Please.
Please?
For what?
Begging?
To get Toey back
or to get your love back?
If you don’t have feelings for Toey,
you have no right to stop me, right?
I like Toey.
Huh?
What did you say?
I couldn’t hear it.
I like Toey.
Keep it down.
That’s it.
You’ve tired us out for ages.
Show yourselves already, guys.
Huh?
Buddy, it took you almost forever to say it.
Congrats.
Why are you guys here?
Gotcha.
How was it?
It’s a surprise from us.
You all knew?
Whose idea is this?
Pun planned it.
Without him, you wouldn’t speak the truth.
A plan?
I pretended to hit Toey
to push you.
Alright.
Let’s clear things up on your own, both of you.
Matt, bring Toey here.
Toey, come out and talk.
They’re asking for you.
What’s wrong?
Our defendant of love, come here.
Come.
Stand here.
Well, talk it over.
We’re leaving.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Matt.
What am I to you, Toey?
Well, I…
Did you have so much fun doing this?
You’re talking to me, so look at me.
Why?
You hate to see my face that much?
You’re teasing me, right?
Why?
Do you think you're the only one who can tease?
I can’t believe you’ve made me feel this much.
Q, I can’t breathe.
Thank you so much
for having done this much for me.
It wasn’t for you.
I did it for my love.
Q!
You’re teasing me again.
You’re fun to tease.
It took you ages to speak your mind.
I almost gave up so many times.
Really?
Q, don’t.
Honestly, I’m good at this.
I’m thinking about quitting the university
and turning into a cupid.
I think it works.
You’re the culprit.
Do you know how messed up I was?
Handle Chain first if you’re doing something to me.
Do I have something to do with this?
You do.
I was totally sold.
I’m a human, not an item to be sold.
It couldn’t be helped.
You were in denial.
Toey, grab some food with me.
Finally.
Has he asked you to become his boyfriend yet?
Nope.
There you go.
You slapped my head, didn’t you?
Stay here.
Are you helping or getting on my nerves?
Then, a baby frog tells its mom that
there’s a gigantic cow hurting all of its friends!
Fang, keep going!
The turtle wins!
Is there anything else you want to play?
Hey. Come.
It’s freaking beautiful.
Whose work is this?
I think mine is also beautiful.
So is yours
but not as beautiful as mine.
Mine is better.
Freeze.
Toey, be careful. You might fall down.
Got it.
Freeze.
You lost.
Everyone, thanks a lot for the past 2 days.
I hope you’re taking home good memories.
Tonight, I’ve prepared a special performance for everyone!
Pun, move.
So, these two are performing a special performance you mentioned?
Exactly.
I’m bored of them already.
Or do you want me to sing instead?
No, thank you.
Just sit down.
Let them perform.
That’s right.
I think you should do nothing.
Do you guys know which song we’re singing?
Gotcha.
That sounded grand like it was scripted.
Buddies, it must be such a special song, right?
It must be that Grilled Chicken song, of course!
Let’s go.
Ptooey.
I’ll countdown.
Help me sing, okay?
3.
Hold on.
We need some dancers for this song, don’t we?
Matt.
I’ll treat you to some drinks.
Don’t.
Dancing solo is lonely.
Get a friend to dance with you.
This guy.
Toey, go ahead.
Stand up.
Why must it be me?
Q is singing, so undoubtedly you must dance.
Q, we’re ready.
3,2,1.
♪ The grilled chicken is grilled ♪
♪ It will be put on the skewer ♪
♪ On the left butt and on the right ♪
♪ It feels so hot, super hot ♪
Watch me.
Music, please.
Let me sit with you.
Go ahead.
I think I’ve really made the right decision coming to this camp.
Really?
I’m glad you said that.
Your friends are funny.
Have you known each other a long time ago?
Q, Tan, Chain, Pun, and I have been friends since secondary school.
I just got to know the rest last semester.
Nice.
You guys seem close.
Stop.
Stop this.
I’m protective of him.
Stop dancing.
Sit.
Q, just sing.
Just sing and chill.
No more dancing.
I’m protective of him.
No more.
He’s tired already.
Fine.
I want to sing this song for one person
who’s my special someone.
Awww.
♪ Can I choose? ♪
♪ Is it possible for me to choose? ♪
♪ If I can’t have that luxury, ♪
♪ Then let me be your choice ♪
♪ My careless heart has a crush on you suddenly ♪
♪ So unexpectedly ♪
♪ Can I trade my heart for your number? ♪
♪ Falling for you, I became a music lover ♪
♪ Not joking, it’s the truth ♪
♪ I’m not an easy fool ♪
♪ It’s you and just you who make my heart tremble ♪
♪ Oh please send you to love me ♪
♪ Love love I need somebody to love ♪
♪ But that person must be you ♪
♪ I pray for us to be true ♪
♪ This is the love I’ll never hit undo ♪
♪ I will have only you ♪
♪ And everyday I will love you ♪
It’s from your special mentor.
[3 for 10 THB]
Ptooey.
Why are you playing a romantic scene here?
Keep the music going.
Let’s get hyped up.
Don’t overact.
What’s this, Q?
Why?
You don’t like it?
I’m not surprised it’s your doing.
Toey, you know what?
I once thought that
even if Milk Frappe Boy and you were two different people,
the only person
who can make me fall in love again must be you.
I’m sorry for hurting you many times.
It’s because I was such a coward.
I should have been braver,
admitting my own feelings
and recognizing that you’re special to me.
Stop saying sorry already.
If you say it again, I won’t love you anymore.
Can you do that?
I can’t.
But I’m just bragging.
10 THB for me?
Q,
do you really like me?
Why?
Nothing.
I was just asking.
I wouldn’t kiss someone I didn’t like.
I wouldn’t let someone who I didn’t like kiss me either.
Thank you for the flowers.
You’re welcome.
Why are you sitting here alone?
Does the wound hurt?
Let me see.
You don’t need to care about me.
If something’s bothering you, just tell me straight.
Are you two that close?
Huh?
What do you mean?
I saw Kluen and you stick together all day.
That’s why I asked if you two are that close.
Nothing much.
I guess we’re close.
He’s here solo,
and I’m the only friend he has in this camp.
But you’re my slave.
What’s that supposed to mean?
I don’t like seeing you with Kluen.
So what?
Does being your slave mean I can’t have other friends?
Being your slave doesn’t mean I have to do everything you say.
You heard all of that, didn’t you?
You’ve been his slave all this time?
Do you remember the time when I hurt him?
That’s when we started the deal.
When is this over?
But honestly, you don’t have to do it.
Or do you like Phum?
I don’t know.
I’m confused.
I think
I know how you must be feeling now.
Let’s go.
Don’t keep them waiting,
or they will complain about where we disappeared to.
Let’s go.
Is something wrong?
I ruined it again.
What do you mean?
I got mad at Peem because of Kluen.
I told him I didn’t like seeing them together
because he’s my slave.
Phum.
I told you to show how you feel
but not in the way you just did.
Peem and you aren’t dating.
It’s not wrong for Peem to get to know others.
Also, you shouldn’t have brought up that slave deal.
Yes. I know.
But I was upset then.
I didn’t know why I said such a thing.
What should I do?
Find a chance to apologize.
Good luck.
Has anyone here ever heard of the story called “Knock, knock, kkkrrr”?
It’s the story about
two female students who lived in the female dormitory.
One of them was sick,
so she asked the other to buy Thai Fried Noodles In Thick Gravy Sauce for her.
That friend agreed and decided to go downstairs to eat alone.
That sick friend waited.
One hour passed, and her friend hadn't returned.
Two hours passed, and she still hadn’t returned.
Then, she woke up again at around 10 PM.
She heard a sound from downstairs.
Her room was on the third floor.
It went like, “knock, knock.”
Then, the sound seemed to approach her room more closely.
The knock knock sound changed to “kkkrrr.”
She opened the door and found nobody,
but the noodle bag was hung on the knob.
Along the hallway,
there was a long line of water drops that went to the stairs.
After that…
Why did you hit me?
I was scared.
There, there.
Come on.
When are they coming?
What time is it now?
I don’t have a watch on.
I don’t, either.
How about you?
Here I am.
What’s that?
A swim ring.
You haven’t seen one before, Q?
I just asked Chain to blow it up for me.
I mean, why are you bringing it?
Pun said we’re heading to the waterfall,
so I’m all prepared.
You’re bringing a duck swim ring to the waterfall?
Fine. Whatever. That’s your business.
Since all of us are here, let’s go to the waterfall.
Yay!
Hey, walk fast.
Be careful.
Chain.
Pun.
Guys, let’s play in the water.
Oho. You’re taking off your tee now, Mick?
What are we waiting for?
Mick?
Q, hurry up.
Babe, what are you doing?
I’m playing in the water.
You’re playing in the waterfall, but why are you taking off your tee?
Don’t do that.
I’m protective of you, babe.
Jump into the water just like this.
Come.
Toey, you have a swim ring but are still hugging me?
Let’s go.
Alright. Let’s go.
Peem.
I’m sorry about last night.
I’m sorry for being that foolish to you.
I didn’t mean it.
Also, I have no right to stop you from being close to others.
I’m sorry.
Alright.
Apology accepted.
Wait.
Just like that?
Why?
You apologized, and I accepted it.
That’s it.
Or what do you want?
Do you want me to remain angry?
But can I ask for one thing?
Next time, if something’s bothering you again,
just tell me straight.
I don’t like it when you don’t tell me what’s wrong.
Honestly, I also have something to tell you.
I’ve been thinking about canceling our deal.
What do you mean?
You don’t have to be my slave anymore.
We can’t do that.
I mean,
we can’t do that
because I always keep my word.
I agreed to do it,so I must do it until the end.
I don’t want to owe you anything later.
I don’t want that to happen.
You said that yourself.
From now on, if you cry again,
it can’t be helped.
Cry? Cry for what?
It’s you who will cry.
Eh?
Why should I cry?
Why should I cry then?
Peem!
Help!
Alright.
I’ll help Toey.
How was it?
Did you talk it over with him?
Yes.
From now on, keep it up.
Thanks a lot.
Babe, I’ll carry it for you.
Hand it to me.
Hey, move.
Why are you so uptight, huh?
Why did time fly so fast?
Agree.
I don’t want to go back.
You said that because you don’t want to get back to work, right?
Come on, bro.
You know I’ll be stuck working late again after I go back.
You always want to hurt me or what?
It’s not just you.
Talking about meeting the deadlines,
Kluen and I understand how you feel.
Right?
But, babe,
no matter how much work you have to handle,
I’m always here to support you.
Let’s get on the bus already.
It’s hot here.
Fine. Let’s go.
Again.
Come.
Toey, come here.
Q, sit here.
Come on, Toey.
Since you’re not using me anymore,
you ditch me this easily?
Why?
Are you sulking?
It hurts here.
Stop the drama, Chain.
Just sit.
You took my seat, and now you’re shooing me away?
Hurry up.
Pun, I’ll sit with you then.
Why are you sitting so close to me?
Eh? The seat is small.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
See you again, kids.
Q,
I’m sleepy.
Can I rest on your shoulder?
Q.
It costs a lot to lean on my shoulder.
Do you offer a monthly buffet rate then?
That’s a flat rate for one hour.
Just one hour?
How stingy you are.
If you stop leaning on me,
then we need to restart.
Thank you, everyone.
Bye.
Thank you.
Make sure you’ve got your own bags.
Don’t take your friend’s.
Bye.
Safe trip home.
How are you getting home?
I don’t know yet.
I’ll figure it out.
Do you want me to give you a ride?
I’ll give you a ride.
Let’s go.
See you.
Phum.
If you want to say something, just talk properly.
Didn’t you see I was talking to Kluen?
I want to drive you home.
Let’s go.
Don’t be glum.
We’ve been on the bus so long.
I’m also tired from the drive.
Let me go in to grab some drinks.
Please.
Let me go in.
Auntie, I’m back.
Peem, you’re back?
Do you need my help?
No. You’ve just returned from the camp.
Take some rest.
You can head home now.
I’ll do some work.
Auntie, let me help.
You don’t need to.
Aunt Pui, hello.
Hi, Phum.
Can I help with anything?
No. You don’t have to help.
It’s alright.
Since I’m already here, let me help.
Which table is this order for?
Table 8.
Go ahead.
A moment, please.
Can you pass me the cleaning cloth, please?
Table 7.
Auntie, may I use the restroom, please?
The cafe’s are all full.
You can use the one in Peem’s bedroom.
Right?
(Please buy them, bro.)
(You can buy them for someone else.)
(Give them to your boyfriend.)
What are you doing here?
It’s taking you so long.
Why are you smiling?
You’re still keeping them?
I just forgot to throw them away.
I’ll throw them away soon.
Why?
Let’s go.
Head back already.
Where to?
Hang on.
Let’s go.
Hey.
What the heck did you do?
You finished it already.
Or did you tell me you haven’t finished it
because you want to have me around?
You didn’t agree to cancel our deal either.
Do you like me?
Nonsense.
I haven’t finished it.
It’s an art work, so it needs a lot of details.
Someone like you won’t understand this.
Don’t worry about the deal.
I always keep my word.
You really don’t like me?
I don’t know.
You don’t know about what?
You really don’t know?
Do you somehow know it now?
How about you?
Do you somehow know it too?
Are you ready to listen to my answer now?
Let’s go.
Let’s go already.
Cheers.
Peem, I like you.
Since you like me,
then…
Huh?!
What are you doing?
Phum.
You’re still using it?
My grandpa gave it to me.
How nice.
It’s nice.
It’s nice because I picked it up for you?
It’s nice you picked it up for me,
and it’s also nice having you here.