I'm going to be a little bit of a
little bit of a
little child
little baby
Buff...
Anyway
Annie
Mom
I hold you tight but you remain silent
Mother
What's wrong with my mother?
It's okay, Zhuyu
It will pass
Mother
Who are you?
Father
I didn't expect father to be a cat
I didn't expect the truth 18 years ago to be like this
Mother
Boss
You're awake
Where is she?
It seems that you have recovered
You are here to wait for me
I
Fifth Madam, please let her see you
Fifth Madam
Fifth Madam is finally fine
It seems that Changxi Palace is indeed in poor condition
Even the waist wound can be cured
I should be grateful
It's not the credit of Changxi Palace
It's because you are blessed
I asked you to come here earlier
But I didn't expect you to sleep for three days
She helped me so much
I have to thank her in person
Brother, he knows that you will recover
He is afraid that you will see him again when you wake up
He said that he knew his name and left
Fifth Madam
Fifth Madam, please wait a moment
I heard that you came to the shop when you were unconscious
You said that you wanted to practice the evil
This Changxi Heart-saving Pillar is the most important thing
I think that you won't have any conflict with the evil
Fifth Madam has just recovered
She still needs to be adjusted to the inner power
Maybe she can pay attention to you
Thank you
Take your time
The more you use this pen, the more you look for your name
Then the wind blows, then the moon falls, then you are gone
The long night is slowly falling into my dream
Then the heart moves, then the wind blows, then the wind rises
I am in the wild fire of the four seasons
The ugly thing over there is also yours
Once I won the second brother in a contest
The master gave me this clay doll
It's a reinforcement
It's pretty cute if you look closely
The real one is smart, the master is steady
The moment he moves, he is in front of the mirror
Your Majesty, our royal baby will be full of talent
Jinling Pavilion's real one, thin and crispy milk powder
This is prepared by the empress
90 kinds of full nutrition, super-rich in source, HMO
Full-fledged baby needs full nutrition
Jinling Pavilion milk powder, Chinese exclusive formula, baby super-rich in protection
Since the wife of Hu Zhu came to Changxi Palace
She hasn't been able to take a good look at us
Now that the boss is awake, I am happy
I just feel that Changxi Palace is not worse than the demon's room
Have you been well recently?
It's just that the boss is not here
The demon's room is busy
It is inevitable to neglect the business of Ruyi Pavilion
In the past half a month, a lot of profit has been lost
Ruyi Pavilion's business is so good
It's not bad at all
Why not?
I am going to be the first wife of Chang'an
I will feel bad if I am not as good as you
Yes, yes, what you said is right
If you earn money, you should be the first wife of Hu Zhu
You have a great ambition
You will definitely achieve your dream
When I became the first wife of Chang'an
Did you become a hero?
I will try my best
You are so confident
Actually, I also know that
In Changxi Palace, I entered the house first
And I have a good reputation
To be a hero
In the eyes of others, it is more like a daydream
But I always think about it secretly
There will be such a day
Be a cool and self-willed hero
The hero who will take over the world
The cultivator cultivates first
Since you have this intention
Then you should do it with your own thought
Don't care about other people's opinions
Why should you worry?
Thank you for your advice
Since it is so, I will give you a gift
What?
This is gold?
It looks like the gold of the previous dynasty
Good eyesight
But, can you take a closer look?
It is gold
It is war
The rich and the poor avoid disaster
The rich and the poor bury the gold in the mountains
Sometimes they forget where they bury
When time goes by, they turn into gold monsters
I found it when I was checking the accounts two days ago
This little guy knows how to hide
Get up
Don't bully him
My gold
Here
Get up
Why am I...
It was the fifth lady who invited me
This guy is acting again
Boss, this is not gold
This is gold crystal
The two generals brought it back to the demon world
Lady Hu Zhun
When the demon is back
Remember to clean it up
I know
Boss, did you clean up your luggage?
We should go
I will go
I have been bothering you
You are welcome
Let's go
Boss, why don't we wait for Mr. Mei?
I think we have more important things to do
Let's go
The Demon in the City
The demon in the city
Be careful
Be careful of the snakes!
There are snakes in the city!
In this winter, where did the snakes come from?
Brother, you don't know
I have been following this snake
to come here
But last night
I lost my big fish
I lost it
Are you serious?
Yes
What if it crawls into my house?
We are rich
Don't panic
I brought some firewood
You can burn it
near my house
to get rid of the snakes
Do you need money?
No, just to make it easier
for you to get rid of the snakes
Don't fight
Come with me
I have a big house
Come on, don't fight
Don't fight
You must burn it
near my house
Where are you going?
Go away
Do you understand what I said?
I don't understand
Don't fight
I won't
I don't understand
Don't fight
What's going on?
It's not a ghost. It's a snake.
What?
A snake.
They say that when snakes are introduced to Chang'an,
they all look for snakes to buy the sulfur.
From the east to the west,
they've been making trouble all morning.
It's winter now.
Snakes should be in the front.
But it's not wrong to buy more sulfur.
After all, they're going to break their hearts.
It's a bit of a shame.
Right?
Please, please.
Come on.
Don't snakes like to sleep in winter?
Emperor Liu?
Go!
It's very cold outside.
Are you okay?
My dear!
Stop the carriage!
I'm not stopping the carriage.
Go back to the mansion immediately.
Yes.
Let's go.
Go!
My dear!
The carriage is broken.
There's a snake!
What's wrong?
There's a snake in the carriage.
In the carriage!
Go and save the person!
It's in the carriage!
My dear, did the snake bite you?
Go and see!
I'm not afraid of snakes!
What's going on?
My dear!
Are you okay?
I'm not dead.
My dear!
The dead king and the six ladies...
What's going on?
The dead king saved the beauty!
My dear!
Stop!
You're not allowed to go to the palace.
But there's a snake!
What's the problem with snakes?
I'm happy to!
Take it away.
Grandpa, move aside!
What's going on?
Grandpa.
Take care of her.
I'll go get some water.
No, thanks.
What's going on with the four of us?
After all, we've been engaged for more than ten years.
Maybe we're about to get married.
Grandpa.
I'm sorry.
Are you done?
Thanks.
I didn't expect that the famous snake palace was so crowded by the six ladies.
You're fine.
I was lucky to not go out.
But...
You two are lucky to have met each other.
You should just make up.
You're not well.
Have a good rest.
I'm afraid there's something more important.
What is it?
Find out who's hurting me.
Someone's hurting you?
You mean...
someone designed the whole city to be haunted?
But even if someone did,
what's the use of the snake forest?
I don't know.
But the snake palace can't be left out.
I think we can find clues from the snake hunter.
It's only been an hour.
It's not hard to find the snake hunter.
Say it.
I saw the snake hunter's stuff before I entered the city.
Give me the money.
I saw his six statues before I got a cup of tea.
I know it too!
I saw it in the temple!
Don't rush.
One by one.
Please spare my life!
I heard you followed a big snake to the city.
What happened?
Where's the snake?
Snake...
The snake was in a low position.
It didn't catch the snake.
You look so timid.
You don't have many tools with you.
I don't think you usually see big snakes.
But you catch things like yellow gauze and mud.
But yesterday you claimed that you met a big snake.
You followed it to this place.
And you brought so many emeralds.
You lied.
Did you get an order from someone?
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
Yes.
I made the snake up.
Why did you make it up?
It's like this.
You saw it.
I'm not good at catching snakes.
I can't catch them.
I'm so scared.
So I had to scare the people.
After I'm done, I'll send the snake to the emperor.
And make some money.
Tell me the truth.
I'm telling the truth.
I don't have any money.
Is he a mortal?
What's behind him?
It's you.
You scared me.
Sir, you told me to send the emeralds.
I've done it.
Is there anything else?
Nothing.
You can go.
Okay.
I'll leave you alone.
I'm not drunk.
This way.
Slow down.
Your Highness.
Sir, my friends...
They left.
They left?
Where?
I didn't see the four-eyes.
But the young man was in a hurry.
I think something happened.
By the way,
I'm sorry.
I didn't see you.
By the way,
Lady Liu Jiang,
someone asked me to give you this.
The Demon Tree.
Where am I?
Who tied me up?
Who are you?
Did you tie me up?
Say something!
You're not a hero.
Your Highness.
Tianhui,
why are you here?
Elder Hui,
I should have asked you.
You're still alive.
Grandpa.
I asked Xuanhui
to be your friend.
Grandpa, I want to play with someone.
When did you come to talk?
But you pretend to be a ghost.
What are you doing?
I'm just making trouble for the demon.
Xuanhui,
have you forgotten
how you were so confident in the Demon Tree?
How I helped you escape from the Demon Tree?
And now,
you're facing an incompetent mortal.
You're so cruel and despicable.
Elder Hui,
it's my business whether I have any grudges.
It's not your turn to point out the bad things.
I promised you
to scare the cat in the Demon Tree.
I did it.
But I didn't promise you
that it would work.
As for him,
he's not an incompetent mortal.
He's my friend.
Grandpa.
Stop.
You're finally here, Lord Shen Gong.
Elder Hui?
You came back from your death
and must have spent a lot of effort.
Not only to bully an ordinary person
but also a demon who's only a hundred years old.
Me?
Of course it's because of you.
Lady Liu.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to make a deal with Lord Snake.
Just say it.
I want to use a snake scales on you
to exchange your lives.
How about it?
I'll do it.
The flowers of my heart are all withered.
The bitter memories are left.
The promise I made to you is like a wind.
How can I repay you?
The past is like a dream.
The most painful moment has changed.
I only want to be with you for the rest of my life.
But I can't.
The petals of the flower petals are falling.
What's wrong with falling in love?
The moonlight shines on the cold and cold.
I hold you tight, but you're silent.
But the petals of the flower petals are falling.
What's wrong with falling in love?
The eyes shine on the end of the memories.
How about it?
Goodbye.
Your look is like a wish.
Thank you for watching.