I'm going to be a little bit of a
little bit of a
little bit
of a
So
You can escape from the hell by yourself.
I underestimated you.
But what if you come out?
What can you change?
Lord Gui Ying will be reborn tonight.
You have Lord Gui Ying's yuan pellet in your body.
I'll spare your life for now.
But it's hard to say about the young man beside you.
Since he wants to die soon,
I'll be the one to blame.
Take the formation.
You want to be reborn tonight.
Why is your yuan pellet not working?
If we can't stop the evil spirits from destroying Chang'an,
we can't stop them.
Think of a way!
Tell me.
What did you do to Lord Gui Ying?
Tell me!
I only know that the cat knows the mouse.
The heaven knows the hell.
Do you really think that you can stop everything?
No!
Ya Chong?
This is my magic.
Why did you change my fate?
I didn't change your fate.
I am taking back what's mine.
Watch out for the slide.
Thank you.
Madam! Madam!
My family is coming for me again. I'll go first.
You have to be careful too.
Wait!
Your light is broken. I'll give it to you.
Thank you.
That lamp was given to me by my father.
There's a cat's bow inside.
Eighteen years ago, I chose you not because you passed by by accident.
It's because that lamp...
made him think of you as me.
I'm sorry.
Eighteen years ago, your fate changed because of me.
Fortunately,
everything was in time.
No!
If you want to stop this,
kill me.
No.
No!
Yi Huan.
I don't want to.
Don't hesitate.
I don't want to!
No!
Blood Slaughter Guiyin.
Resist.
Master!
It's useless.
I don't believe it.
I can't stop him.
I can't.
Except me, you're the only one who can take the bloodslaughter.
Hurry!
Do you know what you should do?
Eighteen years ago,
I finally came back.
Blood Slaughter Guiyin.
I can't do it.
As long as the world is not destroyed,
I won't die.
This time,
I can rebuild my demon world.
I'll show the important demons of the queen
that the new world I created
for thousands of years
is the new path of the human and demon I gave.
I'll show you the way.
Madam.
Are you really going to kill me?
I can't bear to let her go.
We can be together forever.
The Tao and the demon
are connected from the root.
They can't be merged.
If you learn it,
you'll be the first person in the world.
My wife just recovered.
She needs to be hospitalized.
This long-term heart-saving omen
is the most important thing.
Maybe it can help you.
The Tao and the Demon
You face the most difficult situation.
You face the choice you have to make.
At that moment,
you'll understand.
The Tao and the Demon
What's your name?
My name is Mei Zhu Yu.
You are so strong.
I'm so cool.
We are so different.
Aren't we born to be together?
You made me greedy.
You made me crazy.
Even if you lose your mood,
you'll be tired,
tired,
and bored.
You can't leave me.
I'll never leave you.
Really?
I won't let go.
Puzhen.
From now on,
I will never allow myself
or anyone to hurt you.
Mei Zhu Yu.
We are different.
I can't put you in a dilemma.
I'm so ashamed.
You took out the life of a mortal
and were with me.
And I...
I feel like I've only taken a part of my life
and I'm with you.
I'm so sorry.
You are Mao Gu.
I'm just sorry.
I'm really...
lonely.
I'm so sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Wang Jun.
Wang Jun, look at me.
Look at me.
Listen to me.
Look.
I bought it while passing by.
Shuang Jiang, the owner said
this is the first one in Chang'an.
Let me have a try.
It's not bad.
This lady Hu Zhu
is really good at business.
Unlike us,
who can't even eat
in Changxi Palace.
Everyone has his own...
Everyone has his own ambition.
Don't try to slander yourself.
Besides, we're going down the mountain to pick up the goods.
I've collected some demons recently.
I think I can hold on for a while.
Otherwise...
Shuang Jiang.
Take the fourth brother back first.
We can go to the next demon.
You've been working hard these days.
No need.
It's just some little demons.
They're not under the painting.
They're on my leg.
Steamed cake!
Delicious steamed cake!
One of a kind steamed cake!
Two steamed cakes.
You're right.
My steamed cake has just been made.
Master.
Please have a try.
One steamed cake is one yuan.
Two yuan.
Thank you.
Take care.
That one was really good.
Yes.
It's much more popular than the previous Xie Wu Lang's poem.
That's not Xie Wu Lang's poem either.
But I've read the new version of Demon Slayer.
Although there are some more demon paintings in it,
it doesn't seem to be scary at all.
That demon is a bit... how do you say it?
It's blood and flesh. It's heartwarming.
That's right.
Everyone, you've gone too far.
Da Qing, you've all seen it.
I didn't buy it.
Brother, I have a new one here.
If you don't mind, I'll give it to you.
Really? Thank you, Brother.
We'll be going now.
Goodbye.
Dishes are here.
Please.
Enjoy.
I'm sorry.
I was in a hurry. Did I break anything?
Fortunately, it's not your fault.
This is someone else's stuff. I have to return it to her.
I'm sorry.
The Demon Slayer
Where did you get this?
What do you think?
Not bad.
No, do you all like to steal stuff?
Is this a family tradition?
I won't talk anymore.
What did you come to buy?
I saw the Demon Slayer before.
Doesn't it have some herbs?
My father is not feeling well. I came to get him some medicine.
What's wrong with your father?
He's very angry.
His temper is getting worse.
Then, taking medicine is useless.
Are you sure you came to get medicine?
Where are you going?
I don't have any more. Do you want more?
Wait.
I don't have any more. If you want more, follow me.
Don't go. Don't run.
I told you many times not to run.
You forgot it so quickly.
I told you many times I'm not a dog.
I'm a snake.
Can you not drag my clothes every time?
Yes, yes, yes.
The only snake in the Demon Slayer.
It's so strong.
I'm getting goosebumps.
We are a family of dragons.
We don't care about you.
Thank you.
Let me introduce you to a friend.
I don't want to know.
No.
Let's go.
Stand still.
Little snake, no one is bullying you here.
Last time, a pig demon threw a stone at me.
But the hand-made sister has already told her father.
Father has already hit his ass.
No other little demons dare to bully me.
That's good.
Who are you?
Are you a dragon like me?
I'm not.
But I have a good friend who is just like you.
He is a very powerful dragon.
You do look a little bit old.
Your good friend may be my grandfather.
Slow down.
Lord Yagong.
I'm sorry.
I have to fold this line.
This is the key.
You are wrong.
You have to fold it in half.
Fold it in half.
Princess, be careful.
Be careful of your hands.
Or I will do it.
What do you want?
You do it yourself.
Come on.
Let me show you.
Look.
You have to fold it along the edge.
Along the edge.
Be steady.
How is it?
Is it good?
It's good.
You are so good.
You are so bad.
My job.
Anyway I got you a good heart.
Finally I have you.
fading away
You can't help화
It's been three months.
I haven't cleaned up the mess of the night.
Chang'an is peaceful now.
But you don't know
how many demons are making trouble outside.
Maybe I'll have to leave Chang'an in a while.
Are you up?
Yes, I am.
Mei Zhuyu, you've been sleeping for three months.
Even if you have a long life,
you can't survive the mess.
If you don't wake up,
I'll really be mad at you.
Fairy, come and have breakfast with me.
Coming.
Wen Hua, what do you want to eat this morning?
That guy...
He has already fallen in love with a girl whose ship I'm sailing right across the act of having a crush on.
Everyone has fallen for his affair now.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh
Oh
This is cherry peach filling sour sweet baked fruit ah salty baked there is also milk
The plate next to it is fried in a crisp oil with sesame seeds. Oh, it's so delicious
Oh
Sir, what kind of thing do you want to buy?
Wolfman wolfman you've been standing here for a long time. Which one do you want
Or
Oh
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I heard that there are autumn pear on the street. Mrs. Cui's wife is pregnant and loves to eat
Oh
Oh, so you're the secretary of the Xuanjian Temple
We've seen that
No
I said I'd let you get some face
Recently, Chang'an is on the wind
Said as long as in the hall of the Guangdong under the touch of his wife pregnant food love food will touch the Xuanjian Temple every time suddenly appear
Not so exaggerated
Hey, I'm serious. Although ordinary women have a happy time, their tastes will change a little more
But with your phoenix, you don't have to buy so much
I just want to be careful not to buy a little bit. Are you sure just a little bit
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
The woman
You're finally back. I'm so bored
Hey, wait a minute
Oh
That doll
I said I'd let you wait
Hey, wait a minute. Don't draw yet
I've been here for seven months. I've been here for seven months
I'm going to Ruyi Tower now
A big drink