If I ever need something,
can't you make it happen for me, son?
The moment H Group falls into my hands,
you won't get a thing.
Yai!
I could never leave such
an important position to a child of sin.
Tomorrow, I'll announce
that I've chosen Lek as the new chairman.
You've treated me like a dog,
a servant whose only purpose is to serve
the Hemaratsiris until the day I die,
just because
I'm not your flesh and blood?!
Grandpa!
Mr. Yai! Something terrible has happened!
Someone murdered your grandpa.
Whoever did this to Dad
is truly despicable.
I'll need to question each of you
at the station.
According
to the preliminary autopsy results,
the chairman
likely passed away last night.
May I ask, where were
you last night, Mr. Pramet?
I was at the penthouse.
My private floor.
Is there anyone who can verify that?
Last night, I was with Mr. Pramet.
Are you Mr. Pramet's wife, Ms. Nate?
Based on my intel,
Mr. Pramet hasn't registered
a new marriage certificate.
I'm only his mistress.
I'm not part of this family.
How was your relationship
with the chairman?
Met.
Who said you could bring
your illegitimate wife to this table?
- Dad.
- Get out.
- Get out!
I didn't get to see him often.
Most of the time, whenever Mr. Met
had to discuss business with the chairman,
he would go alone.
As the eldest son,
were you close with Chairman Preeda?
Do you think every son
has to be close to his father?
You have to marry Mei, no matter what.
I won't do it.
I've done everything
you've ever asked of me.
Can I have just this one thing?
I only want what's best for you.
Why do you have to be so stubborn?
You fool!
- You foolish son!
- Dad!
- Yeah!
I'm a fool!
No matter what I do,
it'll never be good enough for you.
Someone like him
wasn't particularly close
to any of his children.
Dad had a quick temper. He got mad easily.
No one could ever impress him.
You're incompetent!
You couldn't even handle
a simple task properly!
Don't ever expect
to rise to a higher position.
I just thought we didn't have to humiliate
our business partners like that.
We could have just collaborated.
How do you expect to run a business with
that kind of thinking? Enough talking.
You can just take care of the hospital.
I'll ask just one thing of you.
Don't mess it up.
I barely spoke to him.
My job keeps me busy.
With my position,
I only manage Heaven Hospital.
I'm always caught up with work,
and the only person I see
is my wife, who works there too.
The ones who clashed with Dad the most
were Mr. Pramet and Mr. Apapat.
And lately,
Mr. Apapat has been playing
a bigger role in managing H Group.
What is Mr. Apapat's position in H Group?
I'd really like you
to reconsider Parin's project.
I think it's very promising.
It'll generate a lot of profit.
Are you part of the company's management?
The data is complete nonsense.
Enough of this.
Stay out of my management affairs.
You're better off being a housewife.
I just don't want you
to make a rash decision.
But I've already made up my mind.
Stop bringing it up.
- But--
- No buts.
It's okay, Mom.
I respect Grandpa's decision.
That night, I locked up
the house at the usual time.
And once I finished up,
I went straight to bed.
I found out in the morning,
just like everyone else.
Do you know who was the last person
with the chairman that night?
I don't know.
The CCTV footage shows that the lawyer,
Pornchai, was the last person to see him.
But…
I don't see anyone else
entering his room after that.
The CCTV didn't capture it.
Is it broken,
just like in those crime dramas?
Someone intentionally turned it off.
Does the earlier footage show
who entered the control room?
It doesn't.
And where were you that night?
I was in the employee residence, as usual.
I'm Mr. Yai's personal bodyguard.
Among the family,
who did the chairman love the most?
I don't know who he loved the most.
It was probably Mr. Yai or Ms. Triprapa.
But as for who he hated the most,
I think that's pretty obvious.
I can't imagine anyone
doing something that horrible to him,
not after everything
he's done for this family.
Have you ever argued with the chairman?
Not even once. Dad was so kind to me.
If there was anyone
who clashed with him all the time…
Well…
It was Mr. Pramet and his son.
The only one who never disappointed him
was my son, Parin.
He's always been reliable and made
a huge profit for our business.
My dad died when I was young.
Grandpa was the one who raised me.
Did you ever have disagreements with him?
No.
I did everything Grandpa told me to do.
I never caused any problems,
unlike that detested grandson,
who only brings trouble.
Detested grandson?
It's Yai.
We're cousins, but we're not close at all.
We work in different businesses.
I run Heaven Home,
while he manages H Club.
H Club? The one
on your family's entertainment street?
Right.
He's in charge of it.
I think you get the idea.
People in power
never really value anyone. They just
keep causing problems for the family.
So, Mr. Mekhin
wasn't close to the chairman?
I don't know. I never cared.
But the person closest to Grandpa
must have been Triprapa, Yai's stepsister.
If I weren't so busy with work,
I would have been the one
taking care of Grandpa all the time.
You were also the one
who found his body, weren't you?
Yes.
I was bringing food to his room.
And that's when I saw him…
Other than Yai,
he was the one who always took care of me.
Dad.
Why did you have to take her in?
I didn't want her.
Her mom didn't want her.
Just leave her somewhere.
Shut your mouth.
You're testing my patience, Met.
Even if they only have
one drop of Hemaratsiri blood,
they're still family.
I won't allow anyone from our family
to be left on the streets.
So annoying.
What a burden.
Did you go to see him that night
before he went to bed?
I didn't.
Are you sure?
I am.
But when I walked past his room,
I saw Yai and Mr. Pornchai
going in to talk to him.
I heard Yai talking to him,
but I didn't know what it was about.
You heard it? It must have been loud.
Was there a problem?
It sounded like there was an argument
between Yai and Grandpa.
Yai doesn't talk much.
He has power and people under his control.
I don't know what he's thinking.
I don't really talk to him so often.
But Yai is really scary.
He's even stricter than Dad.
He must think he's better than everyone.
I don't know if he had the guts to do it.
But with his cold and cruel demeanor,
I wouldn't be surprised
if he turned out
to be the murderer.
Yes, I had an argument
with Grandpa last night.
What was it about?
Nothing important.
As always, we had some disagreements
about how to run the business.
He was very strict about work.
Everyone in the family knows that.
Was that all?
Does it need to be more?
That means you were the last person
to see the chairman alive.
It wasn't me.
When I left, Mr. Pornchai
stayed behind to talk to him.
Mr. Pornchai?
What are we supposed to tell everyone
about how Dad was murdered
in his own house?
Even when he was ill,
the board put a lot of pressure on us.
But now, a murder
has happened in the house.
H Group will be greatly impacted.
To protect Grandpa's legacy
and our family's reputation,
should we announce
that he died from his illness?
You're so smart. Good idea.
Everyone knows he wasn't well.
They shouldn't question it.
Would it be wise?
Wouldn't it be worse
if the murder were to be uncovered?
But if the stock price drops,
will you be able to fix it?
But Grandpa died--
The dead are gone,
but we're still here, alive.
Do we have to go down with him?
What do you think, Yai?
The stock price will drop
no matter what we tell them.
But death from illness
definitely sounds better than murder.
That's right.
If we tell them it was murder,
everyone will probably think
the killer is one of us.
What's wrong with that?
Anyone in this room
could be the murderer.
That's enough, Yai.
Let the police handle this.
How should we announce
Grandpa's health complications?
You're a doctor, aren't you?
Any ideas, Nuanchan?
I…
A sudden heart attack.
No one would doubt it.
Older people
tend to have this condition.
Right.
Let's go with that.
There's always trouble. What a headache.
I'm not comfortable with this, Yai.
It's not fair to Grandpa.
This is business, Tri.
We need to do what benefits us most,
even if…
it's not the right thing to do.
You've been using me.
You've been treating me like a dog,
a servant whose only purpose is to serve
the Hemaratsiris until the day I die,
just because
I'm not your flesh and blood?!
Sparing you
and your mother's lives that day
was already a great mercy.
Excuse me.
Is everything alright, Chairman?
I invited Mr. Pornchai here tonight
to draft my final will. Prin…
will be the new chairman.
And you will get nothing!
There's no update
on the shooter at the club, Mr. Yai.
The CCTV footage was lost.
I reviewed all the footage
from the area and found nothing.
We have a mole.
That's what I think.
Whoever wants you dead
probably has some power.
We need to find him.
I want to know
if he's part of this family or not.
Hey, watch this, guys. Come down, girl.
- Let go of me! Hey!
- I'll bring you to heaven.
- Let go! Get off of me!
- Let's go, girl.
- Let go!
- Don't play hard to get.
- Hey!
What was that?
Hey, softy.
Wait, Mr. Yai!
That's enough. I'm fine now.
MK 33 BANGKOK
Thank you for helping me.
You should take a few days off.
I'll talk to the manager.
He won't cut your pay.
He'll even cover your medical bills.
Wait.
What now?
It's pouring. You shouldn't go now.
It's dangerous to drive.
I'll be fine.
Wait for the rain to stop first.
Let's get inside.
Are you inviting me inside?
What? Don't get the wrong idea.
You saved my life,
and I just wanted to return the favor.
You're something, aren't you?
Go ahead, drive home in the rain
all you want. I warned you.
What?
Weren't you going to let me wait inside?
I was just asking. I didn't refuse.
Dry your hair.
I'm not that fragile.
I know. But you can still get sick,
whether you're fragile or not.
Just dry it.
Again, I appreciate what you did.
No need to thank me.
You're an employee of H Club.
As the owner, it's my responsibility
to take care of problems.
So…
We're even, after what happened that day.
No. You almost died that day.
How could you compare it
to your little act of help?
And where is everyone?
Aunt Jai's shop should still be open.
And Ti should be at the hospital,
working his shift.
What about your parents?
I don't have parents.
Aunt Jai is the one who raised me.
What is it?
I found Mr. Pornchai's car, Mr. Yai.
I'll be there.
Hey, wait. It's still raining.
Hey, you! Wait!
This is the CCTV footage from
the penthouse on the night of the murder.
That's…
Someone followed Mr. Pornchai
when he left the penthouse.
Then Mr. Pornchai
wasn't involved in the murder,
but he was abducted by someone.
He could already be dead.
Then we need to find his body.
Yes, Mr. Yai.
We haven't been able
to reach Mr. Pornchai.
What about his house?
We checked. No one was home.
There were no signs of struggle or any
attempt to escape. He just disappeared.
We figured he vanished
after leaving the penthouse.
Mr. Mekhin, are you aware
of the business he and the chairman
were discussing that night?
No idea.
I was furious,
so I stormed off before that.
Have you found any other evidence?
We're doing our best to gather more,
but we haven't found
anything else at the crime scene.
Also,
everyone in your family is a suspect.
I can't reveal too many details.
Then make it quick.
We don't want to be suspects
any longer than necessary.
We'll double our efforts
to find Mr. Pornchai.
He's probably the key
to understanding what happened that night.
BANG YI KHAN POLICE STATION
Someone is more interested
in the chairman's murder than us.
Tell our men to find Mr. Pornchai
before the police do.
He must be holding onto the will.
Before Grandpa died, he was drafting
a new will with Mr. Pornchai.
He would've definitely given you
the chairman position.
Don't worry.
We're not the only ones
looking for the will.
Tell our men to make fast.
I need to have the will
before anyone else.
Yes, Mr. Yai.
The police still
haven't found the will, Mom.
But I think it's with Mr. Pornchai.
I think Grandpa was discussing the will
with him that night.
It's serious now.
He was probably planning to appoint Yai,
his favorite grandson, as chairman.
Before Grandpa died,
he humiliated me and praised that jerk.
I won't let that happen.
Only my son can become the chairman.
I won't give it up either.
I've endured too much to get this far.
It's good that he's dead.
Now, the opportunity is ours.
You can't just sit around, Parin.
Don't worry.
I'll find Mr. Pornchai and the will
before the police do.
H Group's stock price dropped drastically
after news of the chairman's passing.
I think we should announce
the new chairman as soon as possible
to restore investor confidence
before we suffer irreparable damage.
He must've stated it in his will.
This shouldn't be complicated.
Well…
The lawyer insisted that
we can only read the will after 100 days.
Really?
Yes. Our family is fine with that.
We're still mourning Dad's death.
We're not ready
to focus on the will just yet.
I hope you all understand.
But it's impossible
to wait 100 days before announcing
the new chairman.
Then I think we should appoint
an acting chairman.
It should be someone with fresh ideas,
to give the company a more youthful image.
I disagree.
We should find someone respectable,
both in skill and experience,
to act as chairman.
We should consider Mr. Pramet
or Mr. Pramote.
I think Mr. Pramet is the best choice.
He's the chairman's eldest son.
People won't question his succession,
so we can avoid unnecessary drama.
Not to mention, we have Mr. Yai,
who built the business
into a success
and is there to support his father.
I personally have no objections.
I'm already overwhelmed
with work at the hospital.
So, I think Met is best suited
to be the acting chairman.
Are there any objections?
Well…
I need to thank
all of you for your support.
I promise
I'll lead H Group
through this crisis.
Thank you.
Oh.
Thank you for the nomination.
It's not a big deal.
We've known each other for a long time.
I'll never forget you. Thank you.
- Thank you. Okay.
- Enjoy your vacation.
I just realized that
this position requires connections.
I didn't have to do
any of what you're implying.
Just being here was enough to make
everyone believe I'm the right man.
Is that what you think?
For someone like you,
without a son like Mr. Yai,
no one would even care about you.
Your contribution to the family business
must seem like a few grains of sand
in the board's eyes.
What are you saying?
You're relying on your son
for everything you have today.
And yet you call yourself the right man?
What's wrong with relying on my son?
My son is good enough for me to rely on.
Unlike you,
who's desperate to rely on your son
but can't
because he's an idiot. You fool.
You jerk.
Asshole.
You should quit, Meena.
I'm worried about you.
Do as she says.
It's too dangerous to work there.
You should just help out at our shop.
But being a singer at H Club pays well.
I still don't have a permanent job.
I can't keep
living off your money.
And what if something
like that happens again?
You won't be lucky every time.
Since Mr. Yai handled it,
I don't think it'll happen again.
Trust me.
You shouldn't lower your guard,
espacially with Mr. Yai.
Ti, Mr. Yai may seem scary,
but he saved me.
And I don't plan
on doing this job forever.
I applied for an accountant position.
If I get the job,
I promise I'll quit the club.
That's good to hear.
You've been through so much.
You were always working part-time jobs
when you were in school.
I just want to earn good money,
so I can take care of you.
And I want to get Mom out of that house.
You still haven't given up?
How many times have you been hurt
because of what you've done for her?
This stubborn girl
will never listen to you, Mom.
It'll all go over her head.
- Hmm.
- Stop it.
That hurts, Ti.
INSTANT LOAN
- Take that.
- Ouch.
What's wrong, Mom?
Are you okay?
It's nothing. I'll just go to the kitchen.
Why are you siting here?
This table is for the bosses.
Oh, well…
Nate is with me.
I can tell her to sit wherever I want.
What is your problem?
Didn't Dad tell her not to sit with us?
Bringing someone like this to the table
just ruins our appetite, Uncle Met.
Bua, put those two plates away.
Put them away!
I can just eat in the kitchen.
No!
Sit down. I'm in charge here.
Anyone who has a problem can leave.
What the hell are you standing for? Sit!
Yes.
Pampering her like this,
you might as well make it public
that the acting chairman
chose a pathetic nobody as his wife.
I didn't ask for your opinion.
I can do whatever I want. Stay out of it.
Follow him!
Max, stay here.
Search for anything useful.
Right away.
Inthon.
Didn't you say you lost your appetite?
When did I say that?
Wow.
I never said it.
RUEANROT
What do you need to talk about?
I'd like you to be
in the Hemaratsiri house
as my fiancée.
What did you just say?
I want you to be my fiancée.
Are you insane?
We've only met a few times,
and now you want to get engaged?
When did you even fall in love with me?
You're nuts. Who said I love you?
Why do you want to get engaged?
It's necessary.
How is that necessary?
I don't want to marry someone
they arranged for me,
so I want you to pretend to be my fiancée
and get it over with.
I'm not asking you to do this for free.
Name your price.
I thought too highly of you.
Being rich doesn't give you
the right to look down on people.
I'm not lookng down on you.
I'm paying you to work for me.
Do you want a new house?
The one you live in is pretty old.
You're disgusting.
Not only are you looking down on me,
but you're looking down on my family too.
I don't need money
from this ridiculous job.
You're the one being ridiculous.
A job is a job.
Are you looking down on other jobs?
We need to get going, or we'll be late
for the chairman's funeral.
Think about my offer.
Chairman Preeda's funeral?
Please have some water.
Please.
Thank you for your time, sir.
Right. My condolences.
Please, have a seat.
- Nate.
- Right.
Careful.
Minister Ratthachai.
Thank you very much
for attending Dad's funeral.
I couldn't miss this.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Why didn't you practice
crying like that for a scene?
I don't see why
I should waste my time on that.
I'll never be able to steal the spotlight
from those foxes.
I'm sorry for crying too much.
Since the day he passed away,
I haven't been able to stop.
Why did you have to be clumsy now, Nate?
Clean it up. Quickly.
Mr. Yai, Miss Monmeena is here.
What do you want?
I'm Meena.
Monmeena.
I'm your daughter.
What are you talking about?
You've got the wrong person.
Mom.
I never blamed you.
I understand you.
I've always wanted to meet you, you know?
Mom, do you know?
I graduated. I have a job now.
Come live with me. Please.
I'll take care of you.
Why?
I don't see anyone in that family,
not even Mr. Pramet,
proud to have you as one of them.
Not a single one of them respects you.
Why do you keep tolerating them?
I don't understand.
- Please, Mom.
- What's wrong with you? Enough.
- What are you talking about?
- Mom.
I told you I have no idea who you are.
Don't ever let me see your face again.
How can you say that? I'm your daughter!
- Mom.
- Nate.
- Let go.
- Mom.
Nate!
Please, Mom.
- Where are you?
- Go away! Go hide!
I said hide!
Nate!
Why the hell didn't you pick up my calls?
What are you doing here?
I'm cleaning up the broken glass.
Mr. Met, you should go back inside.
They must be looking for you.
Next time, let me know
before going anywhere. Got it?
You need to be there when I call you.
Yes.
Follow me.
Now!
Dumbass.
Mom…
Don't!
- Don't do it!
- Silence!
Do you want to get hurt?! Quiet!
Hey!
What are you doing to her?!
What?! Run!
Aunt Jai! Aunt Jai!
Meena.
Aunt Jai.
- Are you hurt?
- I'm not. I'm okay.
- Let's go to the hospital, Aunt Jai.
- It's fine.
How is this fine?
I'm going to the police.
You can't do that. Don't, Meena.
Why not?
I told you not to.
Stop asking questions. Let it go.
Aunt Jai.
If you don't tell me what happened,
I'll call the police.
The police can't do anything.
These people are basically mafia.
The police are in league with them.
I owe a loan shark one million baht.
One million?
I only borrowed 400,000 baht from them.
But with interest piling up
over time,
it's turned into a million.
Aunt Jai, why didn't you tell me and Ti?
I… I didn't want to worry you both.
But we have jobs now.
It's okay, sweetie.
I'd just be a burden. Don't do this.
Aunt Jai.
Listen to me.
You're not a burden.
I'll take care of it for you.
You don't have to.
I don't want to drag you into this.
It's not a burden.
Not at all.
Sweetie.
I'm scared. They're dangerous.
What on earth makes you so happy
that you decided to drink here?
You brought your mistress to the funeral.
Do you care what people will say?
Wait for me upstairs.
You should keep that gold-digger
where no one can see her.
Who knows?
She might be hiding something from you.
Like…
Like what?
Like having had a child.
What are you trying to say?
I'm just warning you.
The moment
you make her your legitimate wife,
we'll have to share
our family fortune with her.
What if she has a child?
Why are you even
thinking about that nonsense?
I already told Nate
to cut ties with her old family.
There's no way they'd be part of this.
So that means she really did have a child?
How the hell should I know
if she did or not?
Why does it matter? I don't care.
Never mind.
Do whatever you want.
Just don't let it make the news.
Stop meddling in my life.
I'm warning you.
Be nice to me.
If you don't want trouble
with the chairman of H Group.
You know your time
in that position is limited.
You're so annoying.
Mr. Yai, there's a problem
at Miss Monmeena's house.
Will you say you love me?
Don't leave me hanging
Please hold me in your arms
Will you say you love me?
Don't leave my heart empty
Make my day turn out happy
Would you save me?
Please.
I thought I was clear
that I won't accept your ridiculous offer.
I didn't intend to insult you that day.
I'm sorry if it bothered you.
Is that all?
I'd like you to reconsider my offer.
- I said no.
- Don't you wanna see your mom?
Your mom lives in my house.
Am I right?
I think this offer is important enough
for you to reconsider it.
Think of it as a mutual agreement.
You get something out of it.
So do I.
Win-win.
I really have to go save my mom.
I'm sorry, Aunt Jai, Ti.
I'LL BE AWAY FOR SOME TIME
PLEASE DON'T CONTACT ME
Join us, Yai.
Who are you bringing with you?
This is Monmeena, my fiancée.
Fiancée?
Fiancée? What is this, Yai?
What game are you trying to play, Yai?
This is not a game.
Monmeena will live here as my fiancée.
We're getting married soon.
Mr. Yai, what wedding?
You said we were just getting engaged.
I hope all of you
will treat Monmeena, my fiancée,
as a member of the Hemaratsiri family.
Not a chance. I won't let this slide.
You can't just bring
some unknown woman into the house, Yai.
Why? Are you surprised?
I'm just doing what my "father" did.
- Yai, you…
- Uh…
Mr. Yai. Mr. Met.
You two should calm down.
You were always busy with work,
so how do you two even know each other?
Monmeena works at H Club.
The day I was shot, she saved my life.
And then we got to know each other better.
Love bloomed from helping each other
and getting close?
What's your job at H Club?
Uh…
I'm a regular singer at H Club.
So, she sings for a living.
You have good taste, Mr. Yai.
Well, you shouldn't
criticize his choices, Mr. Met.
Your son is in love.
You should be supportive.
After all,
Mr. Yai finally found
someone who suits him.
What nonsense are you babbling about, Pa?
If your mouth is empty,
stuff some pudding in it.
Why don't you do it yourself?
Don't you know I hate pudding?!
You dumbass.
Any more questions?
Mr. Mekhin.
Don't you want to explain
what you just said?
We agreed to pretend to be engaged.
We never said anything about a wedding.
I did it to make it convincing.
Once I become chairman,
our agreement ends anyway.
You won't be here long enough to marry me.
Yeah? Well,
I don't want to marry you either!
Once I get my mom out of here,
you'll never see me again.
Get your mom out of here?
How do you plan to do that?
I… I don't know.
I haven't thought about it.
Hey, can you take me to my mom?
Which floor is she on? I've met everyone,
but I still haven't seen my mom.
Don't be hasty.
It's not as easy as you think.
And did you forget our agreement?
If you want to see your mom,
you have to do everything I tell you.
Follow me.
What are you doing? I said follow me.
Right. I'm coming.
Here, we live on separate floors.
Each family gets their own for privacy.
This is my floor.
Over here is the living room.
The office and bedroom are upstairs.
And there's no one else living in here?
Normally, I'm here alone.
No one comes to this floor
unless I tell them to.
So, it's just the two of us
on this floor?!
Why?
I'm not going to do anything to you.
And don't think about
doing anything to me.
That means my mom is on the same floor
as Mr. Pramet.
Every floor has a security system.
Each one has different codes and keys.
So,
one wrong move
and it could be your last.
Just like Chairman Preeda, right?
They say he didn't die from an illness.
Is that true?
Just know that his death
is still a mystery.
But as you can see,
everyone in this house is a hypocrite.
Anyone can be a murderer.
Anyone but me.
Because if I were to kill someone,
no one would ever find out.
Well, at least
I'm not a fake fiancée to a murderer.
You have no idea what your mom
is going through in this house.
She's a mistress no one respects.
And she has to put up
with an emotionally unstable husband.
If I announce that I'm getting married,
the board will trust me more. And you?
You'll get closer to your mom.
I'll have to refuse.
I don't want to be part of your business.
Even without your help,
I'll find a way to get my mom out of here.
What about your aunt?
How are you going to help her?
I heard she owes
a loan shark a million baht.
Where are you going to get that money?
Let me tell you. These thugs hate waiting.
One day,
they might decide to hurt your aunt.
Now, follow me.
Wait for me.
Did you find anything?
I got the name of the guy
who abducted Mr. Pornchai.
Here.
His name is Ou. He's a gang leader.
He runs questionable jobs.
But we don't have much on him yet.
What are the police saying?
Our informant said
they've found nothing either.
As for the knife
used to stab the chairman,
there were no fingerprints.
It's going to take time
before the police find anything new.
Then we should lure Ou out
and take him down.
Get ready for that.
Right.
Mr. Yai.
Will it be okay
if Miss Monmeena finds out about this?
It can't be helped.
I need to get Grandpa's will soon,
no matter what.
If you keep acting recklessly like this,
you can pack up and leave in the morning.
You're just like Mei, your mother.
The audacity to look down on others.
A greedy coward like you
has no right to talk about my mother.
- You!
- What?!
It's good that
those two families are fighting.
This is our time to shine.
A speck of dirt belongs to the ground.
It can never be the star.
I can smell a gold-digger
from a mile away.
Don't be surprised
if there's a sudden wedding.
Mekhin.
You brought me here
to try on wedding dresses?
I thought we were faking our engagement.
Why do we need to do this?
I told my family I was going to marry you.
Monmeena belongs to me now.
I can do whatever I want with her.
Subtitle translation by: Anan Pratchayakul