Wang? What the hell are you doing here?
For an inspection
as one of H Group's shareholders.
I'll get more shares,
enough to make H Group mine alone.
Let him go and tell me where Tri is.
Then I'd rather be an ungrateful son
than your excuse to commit more crimes.
Let's not see each other again, Mom.
His descendants
are willing to kill each other anytime,
just to get what they want.
Mote!
- Die!
- Watch out, Mr. Yai!
- Meena!
- No, no, no.
If you can't make her happy,
then let her be with someone
who's ready to take care of her.
You're three months pregnant.
Your power really does keep you
from missing anything, doesn't it?
If you're calling
to cancel my wedding to Dylan--
You need to marry Dylan as planned,
and move to Chiang Rai like you wanted.
You're making me marry him,
even though you know
the baby is Mr. Yai's?
You're asking me to lie to your own son.
Dylan loves you.
If you marry him,
he'll accept the child without question.
But he's not the father.
How can I make him take responsibility?
Whoever the father is,
that child
carries Jong blood.
So, all you care about is the bloodline?
What about your son?
Have you ever once thought
about how he'd feel?
One day, everyone will know
who the child's real father is.
When that day comes, how will
Dylan and Mr. Yai face each other?
Why make everything so complicated?
You want to marry Mark, don't you?
Chairman Wang,
please consider Dylan's feelings too.
Soon,
Mark will become
the head of the Jong family.
He'll have countless responsibilities.
You and the baby
would only be a weakness for him
and for this family.
I won't let him be distracted.
This is madness! Stop doing insane things
just to preserve
your family's so-called legacy.
Marry Dylan.
Move to Chiang Rai.
And take care of my bloodline.
And if you tell Mark about this,
get ready to bury your parents.
You loved Mei, didn't you?
So much that you never
once saw me or my mother.
So, this is where you've been.
You leaked news that I'll be
the next head of the Jong family?
It's your duty.
The one who deserves
that position is Dylan.
He's been a part of this family
his entire life.
He's done everything
for you and for the family.
He should be the one to lead. Not me.
I've made my decision.
If you're choosing based on blood,
Dylan is the legitimate son
of your lawful wife.
Monmeena.
And what if that woman
is no longer in this world?
You can't do that!
Don't use her name to threaten me.
Are you sure…
you want her to spend her life
on the run forever?
Looks like…
the one who has a decision to make…
isn't me.
I'm not mad about the damn title.
You give your all
and still end up meaning nothing.
Just like with Chairman Preeda,
I gave everything
for Hemaratsiri.
I was willing to die for it.
But in the end, I was never chosen.
Just because I wasn't the right blood.
Stupid, isn't it?
Yeah. It's so damn stupid.
So, you're accepting the position
to protect Meena?
Do I have a choice?
And…
I'm sure…
you'll take good care of her.
Are you tired, Mei?
I am.
Then, come sit and take a break.
Wow.
Your painting is beautiful.
And this flower is gorgeous too.
I didn't think it would arrive
in time for your birthday.
Do you like it?
I love it.
But I love the giver even more.
If you like it,
I'll order them for you every year.
And I'll paint you like this every year.
How's that?
Then, when will we ever be able
to walk by the sea in public?
I'm tired of hiding,
painting imaginary oceans like this.
Soon, Mei.
Very soon.
I'll make sure
the two of us can be together,
and no one will ever
come between us again.
It's not just the two of us anymore.
Here…
Our third little someone.
You're pregnant?
I'm…
I'm really going to have a child?
I'm so happy, Mei.
If it's a boy,
he'll carry on the Jong family legacy.
He'll bring peace
between our families at last.
Do you think our child can really do that?
Of course.
He'll be even greater
than we ever were, Mei.
Yes.
He can do it.
Mei.
Our child can do it.
Thank you.
Alright.
How is it?
It's fragrant and creamy.
Oh, weren't you supposed to attend
the shareholders' meeting today?
No one really cares
whether I'm there or not.
There's one more treat
I bet you'll love. Just wait.
Auntie, can I have my noodle, please?
Thank you.
Don't tell me…
I had Auntie make it
with my secret recipe, just for you.
Chef Dylan, huh?
Try it. Let's see
how Chef Dylan's recipe holds up.
Let's see.
Thank you.
Will you let me be your chef
for the rest of my life?
I'm pregnant.
With Yai's child?
Does he know?
Chairman Wang stopped me from telling him.
At first, he wanted me to marry you
and pretend the child was yours…
but I can't lie to you.
I know how much pain he's caused you.
I can't hurt you too.
- Hello.
- Congratulations.
Alright.
Thank you so much. Please have a seat…
Sir, Mr. Dylan sent a message
that he won't be attending.
And Mark?
I'm sorry I couldn't accept your feelings.
I'm sorry for hurting you.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Just knowing you care
this much about my feelings
heals me more than enough.
Maybe I'm selfish…
but I still want you in my life.
You're the best friend I've ever had.
Come on.
If the mother is suffering,
the baby in the womb suffers too.
Smile.
Come on.
So, why haven't you told this to Yai?
- I--
- Was it because my dad threatened you?
That might be part of it.
But I don't even know
why I haven't told him.
Maybe I'm afraid of what might happen.
Maybe it won't turn out
the way I hope.
I didn't dare go against my dad either,
when I believed
I was the one who deserved
to be head of the family.
Why are we both like this?
Is this really for the best?
On the occasion
of the Jongtraipattana family's
100th anniversary,
today is the perfect opportunity
for everyone
to witness
the rise of the new head of the family,
Mark Jongtraipattana.
Mark.
Everyone's waiting to hear your vision.
I don't have a vision.
But I do have two questions.
First question.
Why me?
You already have Dylan. So, why me?
Because I'm the eldest son?
Is that all it takes for you
to accept someone as a leader?
Even if I were a total bastard
who's done nothing,
you'd still be okay with that?
Dylan's the one
who worked his ass off for all of you,
who brought JW to where it is today.
Is this really how you thank him?
- If you have nothing to say, sit--
- I'm not finished.
You're no different from the Hemaratsiris,
obsessed with bloodlines,
protecting one another in wrongdoing.
And in the end,
the whole family collapsed.
Same goes for the Jongtraipattanas.
If you keep this madness up,
you'll meet the same end.
Mark!
Second question.
It's something I don't understand.
Why would Chairman Wang,
a great patriarch,
let the woman he loved
marry Pramet
of Hemaratsiri?
Why did you let me and my mother live
under the Hemaratsiri roof for decades?
- I won't answer that now.
- What did you do to her family?!
If you don't answer me right now,
I'm walking out of here
and never coming back to this family.
I'm not someone
who worships bloodlines like you.
I'll destroy your dream
in a second if I have to.
Enemies.
The Jong and Song families were enemies…
but Mei and I loved each other.
Hey.
Business and massive profits
drove both my family
and your mother's family to dominate.
This is for crossing the line.
We always had conflicts.
But we never ordered a hit
on each other's heirs.
JONGTRAIPATTANA COLD STORAGE
Then came the assassination attempt on me.
My father lost all patience
to even breathe the same air as the Songs.
What?
Kill them!
Dad, no!
Let go of me!
- Dad, no!
- Go!
Go!
- Mei, go!
- Dad, no!
Hey!
- Go!
- Let's go, sir.
Hurry up. They're after us.
- Hurry up.
- Go.
- Mei!
Wang!
Boss!
- Boss!
- Mei!
- No!
- Wang!
And I never heard from your mother again.
By the time I found out Mei had married
the eldest son of Hemaratsiri,
you were already a grown man.
So, the Song family was wiped out
because of your revenge?
It wasn't something I wanted to happen.
And you expect me to be in the same family
that annihilated my mother's relatives?
But you carry the blood of both families.
You're the only one
who can reconcile us.
Reconcile?!
You already slaughtered her whole family!
I'll be the one to lead the Jong family.
If we're not talking about blood,
just qualifications, I'm the most
suitable person for the position.
Does anyone object?
I won't allow it!
That title belongs to Mark and Mark alone.
- I won't take it.
- Mark!
I'm so sick
of your obsession with bloodlines.
You have only two choices now.
Either let Dylan succeed you,
or watch this family fall apart
with no heir at all.
I'm sick of this too.
Fine.
If you don't want Monmeena to die…
Are you threatening to kill me now?
Meena.
No need for threats.
I came here to let you kill me.
But would you really dare kill me
along with your own family's bloodline?
Meena…
You're pregnant?
I didn't tell you
because Chairman Wang threatened me.
He wanted to push you into becoming
obsessed with leading the family,
a role he can't fulfill.
You're…
Listen carefully.
I'm no longer part
of the Jongtraipattana family.
And you have no right
to interfere with me or my people.
Is that clear?
No.
I won't allow this. I won't!
You will be…
Mark.
You're my blood.
You have to inherit this family.
You have to!
My name is Mekhin.
Mark! Mark!
Mark!
What are you waiting for? Bring him back!
Mark! Bring him back!
Bring Mark back! Mark!
Mark!
Meena.
Meena, I'm so happy.
We're having a child together.
From now on, it's just me and the baby.
I'll tell my child
that their father is dead.
If you really meant that,
then why did you come here?
I came here for Dylan.
I wanted Chairman Wang
to see Dylan's worth.
To see how much he loves his father.
And I came here for myself.
I don't want my child to grow up
not knowing who their father is.
And I will not live my life
hiding the truth
just to protect your hunger for power.
I'm willing to give everything up
for you and the baby, Meena.
When I begged you to be with me,
when I ran to you, you pushed me away.
But now that you know I'm pregnant,
suddenly you say
you're ready to take care of us?
Why? Because I'm carrying your blood?
That's not what this is, Meena.
You're no different from those you hate,
bloodline-obsessed tyrants.
It's too late.
From now on,
we have nothing to do with each other.
Once we reach the checkpoint,
a van from the casino will help you cross.
Don't stress.
Everything's been cleared.
You'll pass through.
Then drive faster.
Once we're across the border,
we'll fly straight to Europe.
Everything's already prepared.
Cops!
Damn it.
Drive faster!
Damn it!
Faster! Speed up!
We made it.
Come on, Dad. Let's eat.
Made it? You call this making it?
We haven't been caught yet. That's a win.
I'll find someone else tomorrow
to get us across the border.
The news is everywhere.
The police are hunting us down.
Who the hell would help us?
I told you we should've flown out.
I'd be sitting pretty by now!
You would've been arrested
the second you stepped into the airport.
Just eat something first.
We'll figure it out.
Screw it!
If I hadn't listened to you
from the start,
I wouldn't be stuck in this hellhole.
You're useless!
And if you hadn't tried to kill Yai,
we wouldn't be on the run.
If you think you're better than me, go.
Catch that flight.
We can split up right here.
I'm the son of a billionaire.
I have a lot of money.
So, why am I hiding
in a rat hole like this?
The money you took is still here.
We just need to get out of the country.
You'll be rich and comfortable again.
Just hang in there, Dad.
Alright.
Parin, the porridge is ready.
Parin?
Your porridge, darling.
Parin, aren't you hungry?
Porridge with shrimp,
just the way you like.
Parin?
Parin.
Arisa!
Parin…
Parin, my son.
Your favorite porridge…
Here.
Big shrimp, just how you like it…
MOTHER
If you want to call her, just call.
No need to overthink it.
I'd better not. I'm hungry.
Did you send your mom any pictures today?
All done.
Don't you ever want to go back
to Thailand and visit your mom?
I don't want to go back
to that same cycle of problems.
Life here might be demanding,
but I'm at peace.
And I get to be with someone I love.
Still, I feel sorry for your mom.
She's all alone.
Just like my dad.
You miss your father, don't you?
Ever since he sent me here,
I haven't seen him again.
When I'm ready,
let's go back together.
I want to meet Mr. Noppachai,
as his son-in-law.
Sure.
Risa…
What's wrong?
MP NOPPACHAI BUSTED - MORALIST ON
THE SURFACE, HUMAN TRAFFICKER UNDERNEATH
My dad was arrested.
- Alright.
- Here.
The fruits aren't big this year, huh?
Right?
CHIANG RAI - MAE SAI
Mom! Dad!
- Meena!
- Easy now. Walk slowly.
- Whoa.
Mom…
Just sit down and rest.
Slowly. Let me take this.
Mom,
I'm just pregnant.
I'm not that fragile. Don't worry.
Let me take care of you for once.
It took a long time for us to meet
and finally live together in peace.
- Drink some water.
- Alright.
Thank you, Dad.
I'm sorry for all the pain we caused you.
If I hadn't left your mother alone…
Don't blame yourself.
If I hadn't asked Pramet
to help with Meena's surgery,
none of this chaos would've happened.
But Mom…
That choice gave me my life.
I know
you both did everything for me.
It's because
you are the heart of our lives.
Then, please,
whatever mistakes we made,
let's leave them behind.
Let's cherish this moment,
now that our family is finally together.
The four of us. My grandchild is here too.
I missed you so much.
Mr. Yai.
Can I stay too, please?
Don't you feel any shame
coming all the way here like this?
I do.
I'm ashamed I ever used you.
Ashamed I hurt you.
That's why I don't want to be ashamed
of not being there for my child.
I never felt love from my father.
I know how painful loneliness is.
That's why I don't want our child
to grow up with that same emptiness.
Please give me a chance
to take care of you and the baby.
You never gave me that chance.
I was ready to stand by you.
- But you pushed me away.
- Because I was worried about you.
I didn't want you in danger,
in the madness
of that power-hungry bloodline.
I grew up in a broken home.
But I had Aunt Duangjai and Dr. Ti,
and my life turned out okay.
I'll give my child warmth and security.
Now I have Dad and Mom.
My baby won't be alone.
This thing between us is over.
From now on, we go our separate ways.
Mark.
Rest easy.
Your bloodline lives on.
Dylan and I, we're both your blood.
But we'll live our lives.
You might not like that…
but I want you to know
we'll live happy lives.
Mark… Mark…
Mark!
- Nurse! Quickly, help!
- Mark!
I won't be that kind of person.
This is my workplace.
Are you planning to be a farmer now?
I bought all this land.
I'm going to grow trees and flowers,
attract tourists.
While I win my wife back,
I should also learn
how to live like my in-laws.
Was this Dylan's idea?
Dylan is my little brother.
You?
You've only ever held pens and guns.
You think you can handle hoes and shovels?
Don't forget.
I was an executive.
Mr. Mekhin, we're ready.
- Head that way. I'll join you shortly.
- Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Let's see how long you can keep this up.
A lifetime.
I'll be watching.
Don't look away.
Yai.
Yes, Dad?
- Let's go.
- It's over there.
Dad?
He's been calling him that for a while.
You just never noticed.
Mom, you always take other people's side.
What other people?
He's my son-in-law.
Mommy!
FOUR YEARS LATER
Where have you been, sweetheart?
You're all sweaty.
KAMRAM YARD
Uncle Yai.
I took her to see butterflies and bugs.
Maysa,
tomorrow, Daddy…
Tomorrow, Uncle will come pick you up.
- See you tomorrow, okay?
- Okay.
Bye-bye.
Maysa, let's go take a shower.
Let's go.
One, two, three, alright.
You're getting heavy now.
How long are you going
to keep being this cold to him?
It's not even half of what
he made me suffer.
So, you're going to let
your pride get in the way
of your daughter
spending time with her father?
Maysa's growing every day.
Think it over, dear.
You're back…
Mark, my son.
The court sentenced
Mr. Noppachai to life in prison.
Father…
Obsession makes us greedy,
ravenous, blind, and leads us astray.
Families shattered…
separated, losing those they love.
Even losing their own lives.
The deeper you sink into delusion…
the more it haunts you,
like a nightmare.
Mote.
Dad…
You've embarrassed me.
You don't deserve to be my son.
You don't deserve to be a Hemaratsiri.
I am a Hemaratsiri.
I'm Pramote Hemaratsiri!
You don't deserve to be a Hemaratsiri!
I am a Hemaratsiri!
I'm a doctor! I'm Pramote Hemaratsiri!
I'm Pramote Hemaratsiri! Let me go!
It's like a dark shadow
that chases you wherever you go.
Police here!
Tri, run!
- Dad! Dad!
- Tri!
- Can you move?
- Dad, go!
Go!
Dad, go!
Dad!
It's tragic how people fight to the death,
only to end up with nothing.
Mom…
Parin!
Parin.
Parin, my son.
My son is back.
Maysa.
Maysa,
why are you sitting here
all by yourself? Where's your mom?
Mommy, Daddy Yai is here.
POVERTY DOESN'T ALWAYS MEAN SUFFERING
What did you just call me?
Daddy Yai.
What did you call me again?
Maysa.
Are you hungry? Come eat now.
Come to Mommy.
Are you hungry?
Come here. Let me feed you.
Good girl.
Take a big bite.
One, two, three.
Good girl.
One more bite?
No more?
It's a dinosaur! How does it roar?
How about a monkey?
Maysa, go play over there for a bit, okay?
Go on, good girl.
Are you thinking about me?
Meena.
You taught her to call me Daddy, right?
No way…
I didn't.
Thank you.
I didn't teach her.
They said the temperature's dropping
to 17°C tonight. Keep this on.
It's hot. Wear it yourself.
But I'm cold. I want to stay like this.
Like this, okay?
Please?
I've been cold for nearly four years,
and you never heard me complain.
Well, why didn't you tell me?
Every time I came near you,
you'd frown like you just got Botox.
Want me to frown again?
No, no.
Hmm?
I can't wait to fall asleep holding you.
Did I say you could?
You just did.
- Take this.
- Fine.
It's alright.
Whoa. Maysa's watching.
Maysa, come here.
Give Daddy a hug.
Let's hug, three of us.
You and our daughter
are the greatest gifts of my life.
Every time I look at her,
I'm thankful
for whatever brought you into my life,
for letting me know
how it feels
to be loved.
Even if it meant giving up
the leader position
of the family…
that you…
spent your whole life fighting for?
I don't regret it at all.
Yes, I used to be like that.
I wanted power. I wanted to lead.
But you, Meena…
You made me realize
people don't need much more than someone
who loves them for who they are
and stays by their side
until their very last breath.
I'm glad
to hear you say that.
I don't want you to end up
like Chairman Preeda
or Chairman Wang.
Consumed by ambition
until they forgot all their morals.
Hyah!
What is that?
What's that, Maysa? A tree?
What is it again?
Mountain!
Yes, good girl. Let's roll.
THE END
Be careful.
- Mountain and what?
- Let's go there.
What is this called in English?
- Tree.
- Tree!
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon