♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  You are the cutest in the world  ♫
♫  I give you the most sincere confession,  ♫
♫  send you all my love  ♫
♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  You are my cute fairy  ♫
♫  You are mine, you are my expectations  ♫
♫  Forever, mine, mine  ♫
♫  You are lovely, Pretty Girl  ♫
♫  I just want to hold our hand  ♫
♫  I apologize for writing too many love songs  ♫
♫  Even my head is not capable of comprehending the lyrics (you know)  ♫
♫  Hey, Girl, my words are not ridiculous  ♫
♫  It's enough to see you happy  ♫
♫  I just want to say to you "I love you so"  ♫
♫  Sending my love, Biu, Biu, Biu  ♫
♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  You are the cutest in the world  ♫
♫  I give you the most sincere confession,  ♫
♫  send you all my love  ♫
♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  You are my cute fairy  ♫
♫  You are mine, you are my expectations  ♫
♫  Forever, mine, mine  ♫
♫  I like you,  ♫
♫  when you're squinting and smirking while looking at me  ♫
♫  when the corner of your mouth raises when you are shy  ♫
♫  I like you,  ♫
♫  so quickly give me your hugs  ♫
♫  I like who you are,  ♫
[Assistant of Superstar]
♫  not just because it's you, but you can do anything  ♫
[Episode 8]
Mr. You.
You don't look like you slept well.
Did you stay up late to prepare for the exam?
No, I didn't.
Sister Yaoyao.
Brother You Xi, how's your preparation for the exam going?
With the help of Teaching Assistant Yuchi,
my preparation is going pretty well.
And you?
It's not going so well for me.
Don't be upset.
It's all about participation.
By the way, thanks, Sister Yaoyao.
She was on the phone with me for three hours straight last night.
Thanks for being so caring and encouraging.
I'd better head out.
Three hours?
You were on the phone with him for three hours?
You can't talk to him on the phone.
Why can't I?
Because you're my…
My full-time assistant.
What if I, your boss, have an emergency that you have to deal with?
So do you have an emergency now?
I mean, in case there's an emergency.
Yaoyao.
Dad.
It's almost time for the exam.
You're the supervisor. How come you're still outside?
We're all set.
Great.
Who is this?
This is…
Master, this is You Xi.
Yaoyao is currently his tutor.
I mean…
his assistant.
So you are You Xi?
Yes, Professor. I'm You Xi.
Pretty sharp-looking though. No wonder you're a popular star.
Good luck with your exams.
[Hurry and write your answers, Mr. You.]
[Meet me at the door.]
Do you know what you did wrong?
Dad.
You made it too obvious.
Wen Moxuan.
Yes.
Excellent job.
You've got all fill-in-the-blank questions of the Three Kingdoms correct.
As for the ancient poem's dictation part, you made a brilliant choice.
Good job.
"Not going so well," my ass.
Next. Student Pan Duo.
Yes.
You need to do better on the fill-in-the-blank section.
As for ancient poems, you chose "Quiet Night Thought."
This poem is a good one as well.
But your handwriting needs some improvement.
Sit.
[You Xi]
- Student You Xi.
- Here.
Student You Xi.
You didn't answer most of the fill-in-the-blank questions.
As for those analytical questions, you didn't answer in the designated areas.
However, you made a great choice for the ancient poems.
"Autumn is in the Air."
"Autumn is in the hearts of the departed."
"A glass of wine evokes many emotions."
"People tend to depart in the season of falling leaves."
How emotional, right?
But next time, don't use music lyrics.
However, I do appreciate Jacky Cheung's songs myself.
Sit.
Next. We'll first learn a poem by Cao Cao,
"The Longevity of the Tortoise,"
to help us truly appreciate the ambition of the people
during those troubled times.
Student You Xi, why don't you come up and recite it?
Me?
Yes.
Student You Xi, why are you still sitting there?
Hurry up.
What poem?
Come on up.
What on earth is going on?
Is he trying to make a fool out of me together with his daughter?
"Although long lives the wise tortoise,
in the end, he cannot but die."
Not bad.
"Rise…
the serpent in the mist."
Pretty good. Not bad.
You Xi, you did really well.
A true actor.
By the way, Cao Cao's poem, "The Sea," is one of my favorite poems.
You may recite it some other time.
I'd love to.
Professor Yuchi, after your class,
I now have a brand new understanding of this poem.
Perhaps, that's the so-called charm of literature.
For every time I read it, I feel something new.
It's good to feel something. Keep up the good work.
Watch and learn. Your dad is much more generous than you.
Mr. You, are you free tonight?
Why?
I want to ask you to go to the roof with me.
The roof?
Why the roof?
We'll have a very important moment tonight,
and I want to spend it with you, Mr. You.
Oh, you little dummy. You do remember my birthday just as I expected.
Is that okay?
Since you invited me so sincerely,
I'll…
Brother You Xi. Sister Yaoyao.
There's a meteor shower tonight. Let's go watch it together.
You heard about it, too?
Then let's watch it together, Mr. You.
So the important moment you mentioned is this meteor shower?
Yeah. The meteor shower in the constellation Lyra.
It's quite rare.
Yeah, Brother You Xi. Come on.
How boring.
Just go yourselves.
When is it going to happen?
I know. I've never seen it before.
Meteor shower.
There's no such meteor shower.
Liars.
What lies.
They must have nothing else to do.
Why is You Xi here?
I'll definitely make her pay for this.
There's no meteor shower.
There's nothing but mosquitoes. Forget it.
I'm heading back.
How dare you trick me?
Is anyone there? Open the door.
The heck?
Uncle Zou.
Now that I've found my book, you can lock the door.
Okay.
Take a look.
Take a look at this guy.
What did the girl ever do to you? Such an ingrate.
In return, he had an affair with her best friend.
He's a bad guy. Don't you agree?
Can't agree more.
Jerk!
Uncle Zou, I'm leaving now.
Right.
Now that the exam's already finished, why is the signal blocker still on?
No wonder I didn't snatch even one red envelope.
There's signal!
Not now, Pandora.
- Hello?
- Third Uncle, where are you?
Listen, Pandora.
If this wasn't an emergency, I would have thrown you into the lake.
Isn't it your birthday today? Do you have any plans?
Is my Prince Charming coming over?
Nope. Leave me alone.
Again? Always hanging up on me.
Uncle Zou. Well…
The director just told us. This signal blocker
needs to be on. It can't be turned off.
Okay, I'll leave it on then.
Right, I'm leaving now.
Yeah.
No signal again?
Pandora, this isn't over.
May I ask for an autograph?
Are you a fan of mine?
So I've got fans now. Is there a name for my fan club?
Can you get me in the club?
Of course, you have fans.
I've admired you for quite some time now.
Jia'er.
Well, you're mistaken.
Wait, don't go.
Right after I saw you just now, I'd decided to unfollow Zheng Jia'er.
From now on, you're my new muse. My dream girl.
You're quite casual, huh?
Beautiful, take a picture with me.
Since you're now a fan of mine…
Sure.
Here.
Who are you?
My idol.
What are you doing?
What am I doing? Why do you care?
Where did you put your hand?
Where did I put my hand?
Goddess, he's done me a great wrong.
No, he hasn't.
He is my Prince Charming. He's always right.
Thank you for coming, my idol.
He's bullying me.
I still stan Zheng Jia'er.
You have bad insight!
My idol. Thank you for coming here just in time and getting rid of the bad guy.
Can you use your brain?
A girl needs to learn to protect herself.
Even primary school students understand that.
Why can't you?
My idol.
You really do care about me, don't you? You've been stalking me.
You want to be my escort.
You're hopeless.
Prince Charming. In a few hours, Second Uncle and I will be celebrating Third Uncle's birthday.
- Why don't you come along?
- No.
Third Uncle would be pleased to have a huge gathering there.
Take a look.
Is that it?
Just keep an eye on it.
I'm so looking forward to seeing it.
Watching the meteor shower together is quite meaningful.
Oh right. It's Mr. You's birthday.
So, the important moment you mentioned was this meteor shower?
Yeah. The meteor shower in the constellation Lyra is quite rare.
How boring.
Just go yourselves.
Hello. The number you dialed is busy now.
Please wait…
How come there is still no signal?
I'm not going to spend the whole night here, right?
Sister Yaoyao.
This is for you.
For me?
Sister Yaoyao, when I first saw this hairpin, I immediately thought it'd suit you.
So, I'm giving this to you as a souvenir of our first time watching the meteor shower together.
I hope that I can watch all the meteor showers with you in the future.
Wen Moxuan, what kind of gifts do you guys like?
Perhaps,
the gifts that you can't get even when you've made every attempt.
Miss, I don't have money with me today.
As for the payment, I guess my handsome face will do?
I see.
Thanks, Moxuan.
I've got things to do. See you.
No?
Those shoes were launched a few months ago.
They are sold out. I'm so sorry.
Well, could you please check again?
Sorry, we really don't have them.
God, You Xi is so charming.
These shoes are a gift for You Xi. They're his favorite.
For You Xi?
You mean this You Xi?
Yes.
Go check the Chun Hua Road branch.
They're in a slump, so they must have some in stock.
Hurry up, before it's too late.
On it.
Wait!
I'll give you a ride.
What's wrong with him?
He's not in the dorm. And he's not answering the phone.
Why don't you try calling Yaoyao?
You're right.
Even Yuchi Yaoyao is busy.
They've disappeared together.
Second Uncle, could they be…
Pan Duo, stop! You're scaring me.
You Xi. You Xi.
You Xi, where are you?
You Xi.
My idol, wait up.
Stay at a distance.
My idol. Something just flew over there.
I'm serious. I'm scared.
I think I saw something over there, too.
My idol, I'm scared.
So the rumors are true.
What rumors?
They said a girl returned to her dorm after school.
She walked through this corridor.
And then…
Suddenly!
My idol...
I need to go to the bathroom.
My idol… I'm going to the bathroom.
Can you wait for me outside?
Okay, I'm going.
Please don't leave.
Please wait for me.
You have to wait outside.
Prince Charming,
are you still there?
If you are, can you say something?
Do you not want to talk?
If so, just clapping your hands will do.
Or just meow.
My idol.
I'm scared and alone right now.
Meow.
[Don't use this emergency route]
Thanks.
Don't forget to give the stuff to You Xi for me.
Sure.
Twenty missed calls?
- Hello?
- Brother Dazhuang.
Where have you been? Where's You Xi?
Mr. You?
- Isn't he in the dorm?
- He's not.
It's quite late now.
Where could he be?
How dare you ask me?
My poor You Xi.
He used to have grand birthday parties,
and he was always the life of the parties.
If it wasn't for you and the risk of you being fired,
he wouldn't have had to do this show.
He wouldn't have been this desperate.
And have a lonely birthday.
Listen! If anything ever happens to You Xi,
I won't forgive you.
I can't believe I'm the reason why Mr. You is training for this show.
Am I getting fired from the job?
You can't be fired unless I say so.
Then what is that?
A contract.
Since the truth regarding the perfume body spray came out,
there's been an increase in the number of endorsements and campaigns.
I went through them, and this was the one I chose.
If I write the word "answer,"
will you give me one point?
Fine.
Okay.
But the time is up.
You can't write anymore, Student.
- You!
Mr. You.
Mr. You, where are you?
- Are you free tonight?
- Why?
I want to ask you to go to the roof with me.
The roof?
Why the roof?
Mr. You.
Any recommendation for the best position to jump?
Don't.
Well, you only live once.
Don't even think about it.
So… like this?
Mr. You.
You are too handsome.
If you jump, your face will get damaged.
So, I'm handsome?
Yes, of course.
Then I'll jump like this.
Mr. You.
No matter what difficulties you're having,
I'll always be by your side.
Please, you mustn't.
Right.
Then, why were you on the phone with Moxuan for three hours?
He was having a hard time, so he asked me for help with his studies.
But you watched the meteor shower with him,
- leaving me alone here to—
- Mr. You.
Happy birthday.
This is for you.
For me?
Happy birthday.
[Happy Birthday to the most handsome man.]
And this… Did you write this?
No.
One of your fans wrote it.
She asked me to give it to you.
Thanks to her, I was able to get these shoes today.
That one's mine.
[May you have boundless happiness and a long life.]
What… do you mean?
May you have boundless happiness and a long life.
This is my birthday.
And this greeting is way too common.
It's worse than the fan's.
Mr. You,
I'm afraid you wouldn't understand if I wrote something too deep.
I've spent quite some time coming up with this.
I thought you'd understand.
Of course, I understand.
I do.
I just… Your handwriting is illegible.
Such ugly shoes. Why would you buy these?
Don't you remember?
Last time we went shopping together,
you were kicked out of the shop by the shop assistant.
And these were what you picked.
I thought you liked them.
They launched a few months ago.
They're long out of season now.
Sorry, Mr. You.
I don't go shopping that much.
No worries.
Who am I? A fashionista?
Even if it's out of season,
I can still wear them and make them popular.
It's comfortable.
They look good.
So… did you pay for it with your own money?
Yeah.
You didn't use the reserve fund?
What reserve fund?
Didn't Zhu Dazhuang give you the reserve fund?
No.
What do you mean?
So I've been spending your money for the past few days?
Mr. You, I've earned enough for you to spend my money.
No, I'm your boss.
I'm You Xi.
How can I spend your money?
In a couple of days, I'll give you my company card.
Look, a meteor.
I thought you said a meteor shower?
How come there's only one?
Mr. You, let's make a wish together.
They say wishes will come true when made under a shooting star.
How childish.
I hope next time we can still make a wish together.
Yuchi Mumu.
Look carefully.
You call that a shooting star?
Oh, it's a plane.
What a waste of emotions.
What's wrong with you?
Mr. You.
Wait up!
So she got him a present, and they watched the meteor shower together.
She's clearly coming on to my friend, right?
So you have a friend who shares the same birthday?
Well, that's not the point.
The point is, my friend…
All the things that he said thoughtlessly,
she took them to heart.
She even bought a birthday present in secret.
A pretty expensive one.
You're only overly polite to the people who you don't know well.
And with the people you're really close to,
you'll be more attentive with care.
Attentive is what she is.
She even wrote the card herself.
What did she write?
[May you have boundless happiness and a long life.]
I'm only asking you to resolve my doubts.
Now you're throwing cold water on me.
As far as I'm concerned,
you envy people who are in love with each other.
Going to stop talking to you.
I'm leaving.
Mr. You.
Here's the company card.
Well… I really don't need it.
What are you doing?
I'm writing a poem.
Do you want me to read it?
Just give me some advice.
But I know nothing about poetry.
It's fine.
You just have to tell me how you feel.
Okay.
"The light of the mountain county is hard to extinguish.
The wind is in my eyes.
The pleasant soil on the hillside.
The willow is smoky."
So, what do you think?
Mr. You.
I think it's great.
Good.
You are the first one to hear me reading my poem.
Where are you going?
The library.
You Xi.
Are you sure you've come to the right place?
This is the library.
Mr. You.
The next exam is in two days.
I can't believe you're still here playing with your phone.
Who says I'm playing?
I'm studying.
Liu Bei said.
Animated cartoons?
Romance of the Three Kingdoms.
What are you watching this for?
Those books of yours… I dozed off the second I read them.
I'd rather watch cartoons.
Here. Take this.
What's this?
It's an overview of the characters in the The Realm of the Three Kingdoms that I wrote.
I don't need this.
The life of Lü Bu.
Tailored for You Xi.
The one and only edition.
Three Heroes Combating Lü Bu.
(T/N: Three Heroes are Zhang Fei, Guan Yu, and Liu Bei)
"Zhang Fei stroked his beard and shouted."
"Lü Bu! You coward."
"You better not run away!"
"Zhang Fei was in high spirits.
He got in a fierce battle with Lü Bu.
They fought for more than 50 rounds
and ended in deadlock.
When Yun Chang saw this,
(T/N: Guan Yu also known as Guan Yun Chang)
he whipped his flying horse.
He waved his Green Dragon Crescent Blade, which weighed 90 pounds,
and attacked Lü Bu from the other side."
From the easy steps to the difficult ones, they turned complexity into simplicity.
[Relationship of Characters]
Lü Bu's adoptive father is Dong Zhuo.
(T/N: Eastern Han Dynasty Warlord)
Liu Xie is Dong Zhuo's master.
(T/N: Liu Xie is the last Emperor of the Eastern Han Dynasty)
Liu Bian is Liu Xie's brother.
(T/N: Liu Bian is the 13th Emperor of Eastern Han Dynasty)
Thinking outside the box gives you a memory trail.
Too easy, not on the quiz.
Too common, not on the quiz.
Too difficult, not on the quiz.
I don't know the answer. Hope you're not on the quiz.
So, not a single key point
for sixty years of the Three Kingdoms.
Identify the key points and clarify the misconceptions.
So uninspiring.
Now I'll be distributing the quiz papers.
Hey you. Now that you want to play Lü Bu,
can you tell me the meaning of "the slave of three masters"?
When Lü Bu was nine, his grandfather slaughtered a sheep.
Do you know the name of the sheep?
You Xi. What a wonderful counterstrike.
Students.
For the latest quiz,
the overall performance of the class
has improved compared to last time.
Among all, Student Wen Moxuan stands out.
Once again, he did pretty well.
In addition to his accuracy,
he even wrote down the answers in the Liu style
with a writing brush.
His calligraphy is vigorous,
having a style of his own.
That sounds exagerated.
In addition,
I've seen some of you make some huge progress.
You've made commendable efforts.
And by you I mean,
Student Pan Duo.
It's quite amazing how she herself
wrote a new poem on her previous work
on "Quiet Night Thought."
Elegant and refined.
It's a poem that I can relate to it.
I credit my bumpy relationship with this one.
What?
I'm humbled.
[Quiz Paper]
Mr. You.
What? Don't peep.
My score is confidential.
Well, I graded the quizzes.
Laugh all you want.
Your score was twenty times higher than the last one.
That's a huge improvement.
That's quite amazing.
You know what?
You're really bad at comforting people.
I do mean it. You've made huge progress.
As long as you keep working hard,
you'll definitely make greater progress next time.
Right.
This is what I call, a nice compliment.
- Hello.
- You Xi.
Did you watch the news?
- Why?
- Oh, sweetheart.
"Accidently Fall In Love With You," is on air tonight.
The countdown brought all your fans together on Weibo.
So you don't even bother to stay tuned to your own television series?
Tonight?
Where can I get a TV at your university tonight?
Why?
To watch a TV show.
♫  The world is so big,  ♫
♫  yet a word of love from you makes me melt  ♫
♫  Watching you decorate this little home,  ♫
♫  the overflowing happiness can barely be contained  ♫
♫  The noise of spring and autumn, the temperature difference between winter and summer  ♫
♫  they've all become picturesque  ♫
♫  Even if worries accompany sunsets,  ♫
♫  is there any reasons not to cherish the moment?  ♫
♫  I'll be with you when you cry  ♫
♫  I'll pamper you so that you won't ruin your makeup  ♫
♫  I will take you wherever you want to go  ♫
♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  I want you to be my goddess for the rest of my life  ♫
♫  I'll gently light the lamp in the quiet of the night  ♫
♫  I'll hold you in my arms and let you sleep soundly  ♫
♫  I'm your man  ♫
♫  I will take care of you with my all  ♫
♫  I'll silently follow the perfect script in your heart  ♫
♫  It's you who makes everything become possible and love to be flawless  ♫