♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  You are the cutest in the world  ♫
♫  I give you the most sincere confession,  ♫
♫  send you all my love  ♫
♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  You are my cute fairy  ♫
♫  You are mine, you are my expectations  ♫
♫  Forever, mine, mine  ♫
♫  You are lovely, Pretty Girl  ♫
♫  I just want to hold our hand  ♫
♫  I apologize for writing too many love songs  ♫
♫  Even my head is not capable of comprehending the lyrics (you know)  ♫
♫  Hey, Girl, my words are not ridiculous  ♫
♫  It's enough to see you happy  ♫
♫  I just want to say to you "I love you so"  ♫
♫  Sending my love, Biu, Biu, Biu  ♫
♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  You are the cutest in the world  ♫
♫  I give you the most sincere confession,  ♫
♫  send you all my love  ♫
♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  You are my cute fairy  ♫
♫  You are mine, you are my expectations  ♫
♫  Forever, mine, mine  ♫
♫  I like you,  ♫
♫  when you're squinting and smirking while looking at me  ♫
♫  when the corner of your mouth raises when you are shy  ♫
♫  I like you,  ♫
♫  so quickly give me your hugs  ♫
♫  I like who you are,  ♫
[Assistant of Superstar]
♫  not just because it's you, but you can do anything  ♫
[Episode 12]
Looks like it didn't work.
How do you have the nerve to say that?
It's all your fault for telling me to find a third party.
My idol, are you hungry?
Have some chicken wings.
Who did you find?
Pandora.
Who else can I find?
I'm sorry. I missed two words there.
Who did your friend find?
Third Uncle, you do have other intentions for Yaoyao.
You told me that your friend likes his secretary,
but in fact, you like Yaoyao.
You already knew that?
Was it obvious?
Your stupid advice was useless.
And you!
Don't focus on acting.
You only keep eating.
Third Uncle, since Yaoyao doesn't seem interested,
there's only one way to get her.
What is it?
You have to win her favor so that she'll grow to love you.
That never occurred to you?
How do I win her favor?
Third Uncle, you're a fool.
Don't you need an assistant right now?
I've been rejected.
There's someone who can help you.
Who?
There's nothing I can do about it.
You know Yaoyao's personality.
No one can change her mind when she has decided on something,
not even me.
Besides, she made that decision on her own.
I have no reason to stop her.
- Professor Yuchi—
- Enough.
Let's just leave it as is. Let's change the subject.
By the way, it's said that your costume drama will begin shooting soon.
It begins next week.
You Xi, Yaoyao has spent so much time
helping you understand this character.
You have to play it well,
or else she'll be the first one to be disappointed.
The first one to be disappointed.
Got it.
Professor Yuchi, thank you for the advice.
He's clever.
[Friends, help me and like my first post.]
[We will begin shooting next week and my character will be Lü Bu.]
[Little Wood]
Your exclusive WeChat Moments.
[Sealed]
[Little Wood]
Hello! Who is this?
Hi, Mr. You.
You?
Who is speaking?
Mr. You, I'm Yaoyao.
I saw your post on Moments.
You are calling me because you saw my Moments?
Mr. You, I wanted to tell you
Lü Bu was not a man who was just immersed in love.
He was a valiant, unconquerable,
battle-wise, and fearless hero.
According to the Biography of Cao Man,
Lü Bu is the best talent and Red Hare Horse, the best horse.
You told me all this,
but unfortunately, I don't remember.
Now I can play in whichever way I like.
It's none of your business.
I'll turn the historical drama into an idol drama.
And I'll make him look like a pick-up artist.
I must read the script now. Bye!
Why didn't Lü Bu just fight?
He was so awesome that he would definitely defeat them.
Mr. You, Lü Bu was not only brave and battle-wise,
but also resourceful.
He was not a simple warrior.
He knew that if the two sides had gone to war,
there would have been heavy casualties.
Why would he get into a fight
when he could handle things peacefully?
He did seem to be different from the Lü Bu I learned before.
Can I kiss you...
one more time?
[Dressing Room]
Third Uncle...
Here she comes! Here she comes!
She finally came!
Mr. You.
Why are you here?
I…
Third Uncle, Yaoyao worried that you would ruin the classic.
So she's here to supervise you.
How's my outfit?
Lü Bu held a halberd on the horse.
As a general, he had a commanding presence.
But don't you think that right now you look
a little too naïve?
What are you laughing at?
I wouldn't have called you if I'd known that.
You laugh at me as soon as you show up.
Besides, Lü Bu's weapon Sky Piercer
was used to kill enemies and render meritorious service.
Okay. I'll do whatever you say.
Yaoyao, look!
My Third Uncle definitely can't go on without your help.
Without you, he'd miss the essence of the character.
But as his assistant, should I be on standby and be with him all the time?
I still have to go to classes. The semester has already started.
Third Uncle's assistant doesn't have to be with him all the time.
You just need to coach him when you are free in your spare time.
Yaoyao.
Yaoyao, just say yes.
Look! I'll also play a role in The Realm of the Three Kingdoms.
If you just say yes, we'll see each other more often.
And you can coach me as well when you're free.
All right then.
Then I render meritorious service.
Duo Duo, what role are you playing?
I am playing… Diao Chan.
What is wrong with you?
Can you stop spinning?
I told you the role of Dian Chan would definitely be mine.
Sister, fighting me for the part?
You're too naïve.
My respects to you, General.
Get lost!
Is she nuts?
Uncle, is it true that you and my Second Uncle can't work in Shengguo Entertainment anymore?
Your niece's part was stolen by that girl.
You're not my real niece.
What are you upset about?
If she wants to play Diao Chan, let her be.
Anyway, she won't be popular.
Third Uncle, how do you know that?
Diao Chan is a peerless beauty, but whoever plays her would be reviled.
Wouldn't she be a target with her terrible acting?
Who else will they criticize except her?
Think about it.
Sun Shangxiang exists in both seasons
and her character is endearing.
Mr. You is right.
I've also read the script.
Sun Shangxiang's characterization is complete.
But Diao Chan is different.
She's just eye candy.
There is little room for the actress.
Just be good and listen to me, and play Sun Shangxiang.
If you can't be popular, blame me for it.
Third Uncle, you're really an old fox.
What did you call me?
Second Uncle, you'll be Third Uncle's biological child from now on.
What nonsense!
You Xi, Mr. Zhang's 50th birthday dinner party
will be held at 7:00 tomorrow night.
He has just invited you and a few other popular celebrities
and his closest confidants.
This is a top priority for Shengguo Entertainment.
You have to show up and be on time.
Am I the kind of person who likes to be late?
Good.
Wake me up at 2:00 tomorrow afternoon.
I will get a new hairstyle.
It's only five?
I did wake up early this morning, didn't I?
What is this dark thing here?
Is it eatable? How can it be?
Dinner!
5:00 p.m.
- Hello.
- Yuchi Mumu!
Didn't I tell you to wake me up at 2:00 in the afternoon?
Look what time it is now.
Sorry, Mr. You.
I'm a little sick today.
You… You're sick?
What's wrong? Have you seen a doctor?
I just feel a little dizzy.
I just need to get some sleep.
Hello?
Yuchi Mumu.
Yuchi Mumu!
Mr. You.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
How are you not feeling well?
I'm fine, Mr. You.
It's so hot.
Let's go! I'll take you to the hospital.
Mr. You, I don't have to go to the hospital.
I just have a few days like this every month.
Then you go back to bed.
I'll cook ginger soup for you.
That's the bathroom.
T-The kitchen is over there.
You have a fever caused by…
by your period.
Open your mouth.
Let me do it myself.
Hurry up and go, or you'll be late.
I'm not going.
You can't do that.
Mr. Zhang has specifically asked you to
sit next to him at his birthday party.
How can you be absent?
What can they do to me?
If you are not going, I won't drink this.
You…
Eat the ginger soup, and I'll go.
I'll show my face and be right back.
Lie down.
Wait for me.
Why isn't he here yet?
My dear, this is the hairstyle you've prepared for five hours?
Don't speak. Hurry up.
What's the plan today? I have to go soon.
Where are you going?
I'm in love.
You Xi, you're getting funny.
The plan for tonight is simple.
After Mr. Zhang makes a birthday wish, you'll congratulate him.
I wrote a speech for you.
Wait for me.
Thankfully, our company is really thriving this year.
The ratings for "Accidently Fallen In Love With You" have broken records.
In my opinion, there is no question that it will become the best of the year.
Good!
At present, "The Realm of the Three Kingdoms" will start shooting,
which has a huge investment and is a big-budget production.
And with the best actor and actress from our company,
as well as the popular celebrities,
it will be a hit.
Wonderful!
Thanks to the company's patronage for so many years,
we will continue to work hard in the future.
- Thanks.
- Great!
Today, in order to wish "The Realm of the Three Kingdoms" a smooth shooting and a great rating,
I've specially asked people to arrange the banquet here.
Look!
It's quaint, with a small bridge and flowing water.
It's very fitting.
- Third Uncle, when can I eat?
- when I'm in it… I want to recite a song
It'll be over soon.
As the ancient said,
enjoy yourself when you can,
and never waste the chance to drink under the moon.
Great!
Come on, Mr. Zhang. Blow out the candles.
Yes, yes, blow out the candles.
♪ Mr. Zhang, happy birthday to you! ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you! Happy birthday to you! ♪
Thanks, everyone!
Blow out the candles.
I hope…
Mr. Zhang, happy birthday!
Good! I hope we'll…
We'll… work hard together in the future.
Come on, Mr. Zhang. Here is a toast to you.
I wish you to be blessed and live a prosperous life.
Enjoy your dinner, guys!
Thanks.
Please, have a seat.
Help yourselves, guys.
You Xi, you are trying to leave so soon?
Mr. Zhang, You Xi has something to do.
If you want to go, give a toast to everyone here today first, and I'll let you go.
That's right.
Come on, eat, eat. Drink!
Come on, come on, eat. Drink! Come on.
Third Uncle, wait for me.
Walk slowly.
Hold on.
It's your turn, isn't it? Come on.
I-I-I can't drink.
Third Uncle. Sorry. He's drunk.
You may go. Go! Go! Sorry.
Third Uncle.
You Xi is counting on you for his publicity expenses this year.
Okay. Okay.
Second Uncle. Second…
Come on. Give a toast to Mr. Zhang.
Third Uncle. Third Uncle!
Little Wood.
[Pan Duo]
Hi, Duo Duo.
Yaoyao, come quickly! Third Uncle got drunk.
I can't move him by myself.
Mr. You got drunk?
I'll be on my way.
Third Uncle, you have to hide well.
Don't let me find you.
Duo Duo.
Why are you here?
Yaoyao, you are finally here!
If you didn't show up, Third Uncle would have killed me.
Where's Mr. You then?
Mr. You.
Maybe you didn't know. When Third Uncle gets drunk,
he behaves badly.
He kept chasing me and wanted to play the game of an eagle catching chicks with me.
I was afraid others might see, so I persuaded him to play hide-and-seek.
Mr. You, let's get up first. Come on.
What do you want?
She wants to take you home.
I'm not going home. I'm going to wait for Little Wood.
You are going to wait for Little Wood? Why?
I… I…
What do you want?
I'm going to ask Little Wood to be my girlfriend.
You'll ask Little Wood to be your girlfriend?
What if Little Wood refuses?
Duo Duo, stop kidding.
If L-Little Wood refuses, I won't…
I won't go home. I'll…
- Mr. You!
- Third Uncle, don't go.
Look! Little Wood is here.
Look! She's here.
- Little Wood.
- Here. Here.
It's really Little Wood.
Mr. You, let's go home, shall we?
Little Wood, will you be my girlfriend?
She's not saying anything.
She's not Little Wood.
Little Wood likes me.
I'll go to find my Little Wood.
Yaoyao, just say yes. Just say yes first.
He won't remember anything tomorrow morning when he wakes up anyway.
I'll be your girlfriend then.
Drink up! I can still drink.
Oh my god!
Isn't it my youth?
Isn't that You Xi?
You Xi, which You Xi?
Why does it sound so familiar?
Mr. Zhang, you're wrong. You Xi has long gone home.
Well, can't let them see you two here.
Quick! Quick! Hurry up and leave!
Stop! Don't run!
Second Uncle! I'm very… very dizzy. I'm drunk.
- Who's that girl?
- I-I-I don't know. I'm drunk.
I didn't see her clearly.
You Xi, are you all right? You Xi?
You Xi, what did she do to you? You Xi.
Duo Duo, you really didn't see the face of the pervert who kissed You Xi?
No.
Second Uncle, wait for me.
Third Uncle, do you remember that you asked a waiter for a toast when you got drunk last night?
No.
Do you remember you dragged me to play the game of an eagle catching chicks?
What about hide-and-seek? You remember hide-and-seek, do you?
I said I don't remember. I don't remember. I don't remember!
You're so annoying…
That's a great relief. Bye-bye!
She's so annoying.
Little Wood, will you be my girlfriend?
I'll be your girlfriend then.
She agreed to be my girlfriend!
[Little Wood]
[Good morning.]
[You Xi]
Yes! She replied back to me!
[Little Wood: Good morning]
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Why did you want to hang out with us today?
Great news. Amazing news.
Tell us after eating.
Brother Chao, come on.
It happened last night.
Last night?
Didn't you say you didn't remember anything?
Yaoyao agreed to be my girlfriend.
I have an errand.
I'll get going.
Yaoyao!
Third Uncle got so drunk last night
and asked me to play hide-and-seek with him for an hour, and my bones almost fall apart,
but he only remembers that Yaoyao said yes to him.
A boy who just fell in love for the first time,
he's bound to hit a few bumps.
Then, what about a girl who just fell in love for the first time?
Stop pretending that you are all right.
Say something or I'll head back.
Brother Chao,
I'm disappointed in love.
You haven't even been together.
Already disappointed?
She said that she had casually said yes
only because I was drunk.
Then what?
Then… I left.
I don't think Yaoyao finished what she had to say.
What do you mean?
Yaoyao is slow sometimes.
You have to be patient.
[If you weren't drunk...]
Little Wood, will you be my girlfriend?
[If you weren't drunk, I think I'd agree.]
[You Xi: Goodbye.]
[I'm so excited.]
[A birthday present from...]
[Thank you for not letting me down.]
It's okay now. It's okay now.
[Press Conference]
[This is just like when You Xi helped me with the book.]
[The Realm of the Three Kingdoms]
- Director.
- Is everything ready?
Yes. You can count on it.
All right, just pay attention to the details here and there.
Got it.
Here we are.
Well, where's the censer for the opening ceremony? Where do we put the incense?
Well… Director, don't worry.
I've got someone on it. It's a big movie studio.
There ought to be a censer that we can use.
[Torn Apart]
You didn't even prepare a censer for the opening ceremony.
It will be here right away.
What's going on?
[Torn Apart]
Here comes the censer.
I found the censer first.
Give it to me. We'll use it first.
I found it first.
Director, it's the only censer in the movie studio.
Director. I couldn't… I couldn't find a second censer.
W-Why don't we share it?
Are you nuts?
How can a censer be shared?
I found the censer first.
Give it to me. We'll use it first.
Why would I do that? I found it first.
Make way. Make way. Make way.
Director, look. Is it okay?
Perfect.
Give the censer to them.
Fine. I'll give it to you.
We don't want it.
This was ours in the first place.
We don't want it at all.
Why does the censer look so familiar?
I took it from your balcony.
I thought it looked pretty, so I planned to give it to my idol.
Pandora. You're so cunning.
Third Uncle. Third Uncle...
Do you know you have huge dark circles today?
Did you not sleep well?
Really? You're wrong.
♫  The world is so big,
yet a word of love from you makes me melt ♫
♫  Watching you decorate this little home,  ♫
♫  the overflowing happiness can barely be contained  ♫
♫  The noise of spring and autumn, the temperature difference between winter and summer  ♫
♫  they've all become picturesque  ♫
♫  Even if worries accompany sunsets,  ♫
♫  is there any reasons not to cherish the moment?  ♫
♫  I'll be with you when you cry  ♫
♫  I'll pamper you so that you won't ruin your makeup  ♫
♫  I will take you wherever you want to go  ♫
♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  I want you to be my goddess for the rest of my life  ♫
♫  I'll gently light the lamp in the quiet of the night  ♫
♫  I'll hold you in my arms and let you sleep soundly  ♫
♫  I'm your man  ♫
♫  I will take care of you with my all  ♫
♫  I'll silently follow the perfect script in your heart  ♫
♫  It's you who makes everything become possible and love to be flawless  ♫