♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  You are the cutest in the world  ♫
♫  I give you the most sincere confession,  ♫
♫  send you all my love  ♫
♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  You are my cute fairy  ♫
♫  You are mine, you are my expectations  ♫
♫  Forever, mine, mine  ♫
♫  You are lovely, Pretty Girl  ♫
♫  I just want to hold our hand  ♫
♫  I apologize for writing too many love songs  ♫
♫  Even my head is not capable of comprehending the lyrics (you know)  ♫
♫  Hey, Girl, my words are not ridiculous  ♫
♫  It's enough to see you happy  ♫
♫  I just want to say to you "I love you so"  ♫
♫  Sending my love, Biu, Biu, Biu  ♫
♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  You are the cutest in the world  ♫
♫  I give you the most sincere confession,  ♫
♫  send you all my love  ♫
♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  You are my cute fairy  ♫
♫  You are mine, you are my expectations  ♫
♫  Forever, mine, mine  ♫
♫  I like you,  ♫
♫  when you're squinting and smirking while looking at me  ♫
♫  when the corner of your mouth raises when you are shy  ♫
♫  I like you,  ♫
♫  so quickly give me your hugs  ♫
♫  I like who you are,  ♫
[Assistant of Superstar]
♫  not just because it's you, but you can do anything  ♫
[Episode 20]
Miss Pan Duo, this is the revised script.
Today is the first day back to filming.
Your scenes might be tough. Good luck.
That's fine.
Pan Duo, hello again.
Who wants to see you? Get out.
I'm here to congratulate you on your return.
Where is You Xi?
Oh, I forgot.
He is not the lead anymore.
And even his waiting room is now Zhao Yiling's.
Could you ask him for me?
What's life like after being cut off?
Shen Dazhi!
Try and call me that again.
Shen Dazhi. Shen Dazhi. Shen Dazhi!
What? Come on and beat me.
You can beat me!
Pan Duo, I'm not going to argue with you.
I'll show you something.
You took a sneak photo of me.
You were so happy over that ugly photo of me.
This is called payback in kindness.
I'm going to post it on Weibo now for all your fans to see.
You…
- Delete it.
- No way.
Delete it!
My idol. My idol!
Qi Chao?
What is your relationship with her?
Under this circumstance, it won't be a secret anymore.
I won't say it a second time.
No.
What are you going to do?
Maybe your money transfer to the arranger last time might not be evidence enough.
But...
This is a recording of your assistant and the arranger.
How did you get it?
As easy as pie.
Ask your assistant to be cautious next time.
Delete the photo. I'll let it go.
My idol, no. Don't worry about me.
Shut up!
What? Don't you want it?
You can't trick me. It's definitely fake.
Since you're willing to wager on this, I won't mind.
But I can tell you that your name will make the headlines in tomorrow's news.
Pan Duo.
You're lucky this time.
Get out!
My idol,
I didn't realize I meant so much to you.
I can't believe because of me, you gave her that important evidence.
There's nothing in it.
My idol is really smart.
You tricked Shen Yiling with ease.
By the way, why are you here?
You had a hunch I was in danger.
So you came to save me, right?
We do have chemistry indeed.
You left this in my car last time.
No wonder I couldn't find it.
Did you hide it deliberately to create a chance to see me?
My idol, you didn't have to go through so much trouble.
My idol, don't go.
Why don't you stay and watch me shoot the scene?
I have bed scenes today.
My idol.
Dear You Xi,
The most beautiful starlight can only be seen on the darkest night.
The most beautiful scenery can only be seen from afar.
The future is promising and wide
rather than plain and noisy.
Go across the Milky Way and the moon
to meet a better self.
I'm always here for you.
- Hello?
- Hey, You Xi.
I gave Xiao Qi a talking to.
Don't take this too seriously.
What are you talking about?
Those letters of your anti-fans.
What was up with Xiao Qi?
Why send those to your house?
If you get those letters, don't take them seriously.
They are just jealous of you. That's all.
Because of this, I scolded Xiao Qi.
There's nothing to worry about.
Don't worry, really.
We've been through a lot worse after all.
You loser.
Isn't it enough to be in so many bad movies?
Acting doesn't suit you.
Get out of show business quickly.
You don't care about the quality of the work.
You're only after money.
Boycott the king of bad movies.
Get out of show business.
Mr. You, we got a lot of letters from fans today.
Mr. You?
Mr. You, are you there?
Have you noticed that all the magazines have Wen Moxuan on the cover this month?
Yes, that's true. Look.
Let me see.
That's true.
Wen Moxuan is very popular these days.
He's got another play coming up soon.
- We can't miss it.
- Really?
[You Xi]
Excuse me. We need to change the sign.
[Wen Moxuan]
Cut!
You don't know your lines?
Think about it. How many mistakes have you made?
The whole crew is suffering because of you.
Sorry. Sorry.
Can you do it? Can you do it or not?
Study your script carefully.
I'm… I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
Such an easy line.
You still call yourself an actor?
I am. I am an actor.
I'll learn my lines.
It's fine. It's not his first time running away from home.
Mr. Qi Chao, is Mr. You going to be all right?
Don't worry. I know him.
But he…
There's nothing you or I can do for him.
He can only get over it himself.
You loser.
Isn't it enough to be in so many bad movies?
Acting doesn't suit you.
Get out of show business quickly.
I've liked you since your debut.
I now realized how silly I was at that time.
How could I like a good-for-nothing loser like you?
You Xi, stop making a fool of yourself.
If I were you, I'd be ashamed of myself.
You Xi is a has-been.
Here.
There are many idols I like.
Young and handsome.
Pick whichever you like.
This one is so handsome.
Such an easy line.
You still call yourself an actor?
I am. I am an actor.
I'll learn my lines.
♫  My memory fails as the wind blows passed me  ♫
♫  No one can understand my pain  ♫
♫  In the endless night sky,  ♫
♫  how I wish I could hold you in my arms?  ♫
♫  Thinking of your smile  ♫
♫  and the times you are being stubborn  ♫
♫  How many people keep wandering around us  ♫
♫  But I don't seem to care  ♫
♫  I have already given you my heart for safekeeping  ♫
♫  But I can't guess the sad future  ♫
♫  I'm not willing to let go of this love  ♫
♫  Just like a fish without water,  ♫
♫  it cannot exist  ♫
♫  I'm not willing to let go of this love even if it's a haze  ♫
♫  Remembering your goodness  ♫
♫  can only prove that you deserve it  ♫
♫  My memory fails as the wind blows passed me  ♫
[News update about You Xi.]
[He's made a decision about something.]
[Qi Chao]
Hello. Brother Chao.
Where are we going?
Aren't we going to class?
You wanted to hone your acting skills, right?
Forget about your old self and start from scratch.
Are you sure? No regrets?
Sure.
This is good.
The man I want you to meet today is a real method actor, an old stager.
Who? So mysterious.
Are you talking about yourself?
Don't worry.
Even if you asked me to come back, I have no time.
This man is my former teacher, Jiang Shaoyan.
Jiang Shaoyan?
The man that everyone calls the greatest actor?
Here.
Here?
Go in.
And you?
Mr. Jiang doesn't like spectators.
Brother Chao, come on. It's my first time here.
Go in.
I'll wait for you.
[Awards]
You Xi!
Mr. Jiang.
How dare you come in here?
You abandoned my daughter
- and killed her baby.
- Me?
Where were you when she was in the hospital
and needed you the most?
Mr. Jiang, I think there is a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding?
Can you swear in front of my daughter's picture…
swear to her picture
that you haven't done anything wrong to her?
This… This is a man!
The man…
He's my son.
What does your son have to do with me? Mr. Jiang…
You failed the entrance test.
What… What do you mean?
What entrance test?
You didn't respond to my acting.
As an actor,
you get put in prescribed scenes at any time.
You need to understand the character's mind.
No matter what stimulus other actors give you,
you have to respond. Got it?
Got it.
Really?
What did you get?
Whatever you say, I have to respond.
Fine. Let's try again.
Okay.
Mr. Jiang?
Sir?
I'm coming!
Welcome, Young Master You. Long time no see.
Look. If you're here for Lady Li,
she is fully booked today.
Would you like to see her?
Should I say yes or no?
I'm asking you.
Yes.
All right.
Lady Li, please.
What's going on?
How was it?
Mr. Jiang's class is really unusual.
It might come off as weird at first.
How about I get you another teacher?
Today's class was really...
Exciting! Exciting!
Let's do it once more. Let's go.
I can't cry.
Emotion.
Emotion, do you understand?
Do you know what emotion is?
Your tears, tears!
You Xi, you have to break yourself into pieces
and then put the pieces back together.
Come on, let's do it again.
My Dear,
is it true that I might never see you again?
My heart hurts so much.
I want you to remember that
I'll always be in your heart.
How should I respond to this?
The most fundamental quality of a good actor
is that he does not be affected by the mood and state of other actors.
Got it?
Again.
My Dear, is it true
that I might never see you again?
My heart hurts so much.
I want you to remember
I'll always be in your heart.
I…
I l-l-love you.
I am the prince of a renowned ancestry.
Illustrious name my royal sire…
Listen, reciting lines quickly
is the basic skill of an actor.
If you can't recite Lisao,
(T/N: one of Qu Yuan's work)
how will you learn lines in the future?
Memorize them by tomorrow;
otherwise, don't come back here. Got it?
Yes.
Get out!
"Since I have not realized my political ambitions,
I'll follow Pengxian to decide my destiny."
What is this?
"If farmers idly put their plows down,
the fields with weeds will be overgrown."
The farmer stopped working and began to slack off.
I see.
I haven't been able to sleep well in days.
Today in class, I recited Lisao so fluently
that I surprised my mentor.
This is…
Mr. You, I know you're working hard in class,
so I wanted to make you something delicious.
But…
Forget it. Don't eat it.
No, put it down.
I won't waste food. I'll eat it.
- It looks terrible. Don't.
- No. No. No.
It tastes... good.
Really?
Hold on.
You made it for me.
Only I can eat it.
Help yourself.
My girlfriend made me such delicious food.
Then I'll cook for you every day.
Tomorrow…
Let's discuss it later.
I have no classes tomorrow.
Let's think about where to go.
How about fishing?
Fishing?
Boring.
Can you think of something exciting?
Like what?
Such as bungee jumping,
underwater diving, or skateboarding.
Mr. You.
I… I don't know how to skateboard.
Let's do something else.
Mr. You, please. Put me down.
I've done a few rounds already.
You haven't moved at all.
Mr. You, I don't want to do this.
Help me down.
Okay. Then that'll be it for the warm-up.
Next, let's get to the real deal for today.
W-What are we going to do?
Bungee jumping.
Underwater diving.
And ghost adventure.
Let's go, Yuchi Yaoyao.
What? Come on, you're the lead actress.
But you are working so hard.
I'm not like you.
You Xi has been shelved.
You have nothing to worry about.
As for me, I still have an opponent to handle.
You mean...
Pan Duo.
As far as I know, she auditioned for Lady Xumu, the second female lead.
She is not a threat to you.
In my first movie,
I also auditioned for the second female lead.
But you know what?
I got the leading role in the end.
Letting your guard down is to give others chances.
I won't let such a thing happen.
Also, I want revenge for what she did to me.
What do you think? Were you happy today?
Yes.
But next time we go out,
can we buy insurance first?
What are you saying?
With me, nothing will happen to you.
I'll go cut up some fruits. And you can turn on the TV.
Let's watch a show while eating fruits.
Sounds great, right?
Good.
Awesome! Awesome!
The preparation work for Director Wei Ran's new film
is in full swing, catching the attention of many.
Who will be the leading actor and actress?
Please wait for…
Wait a second!
I'll be ready in a minute.
Okay.
You Xi, I have guests today.
Let's skip the class for today.
- I see.
- You see what?
Is he here to see you again?
Who are you talking about?
I really have something to do.
Step aside.
I'm really in the middle of something. Trust me.
I told him that I'll beat him every time I see him.
How dare he come here again?
- Are you stupid? You…
- You son of a... You…
Director Wei Ran.
Go on.
Goodbye, Director.
- Close the door.
- Okay.
Brat!
Is he your student?
Yes.
He sure does have the looks.
But his acting is also good. He is sensitive, as well.
Have you found the lead actor for "Zhongfu"?
You can give him a shot.
Tell me. Why did you want to see me?
Just to catch up with you.
After all, when I was in Shengguo Entertainment, you always looked after me.
Don't get me wrong, but I looked after you
because I was an artist agent.
And you were a signed actor of Shengguo Entertainment.
So stop playing the emotion card.
Get straight to the point.
What a sharp tongue.
Worthy of the nickname, the golden agent of Shengguo Entertainment.
Or should I say,
the former golden agent.
What are you implying?
Brother Morry, You Xi and I were signed actors of Shengguo Entertainment.
But I respect you very much.
If we two can work together…
Got it.
You want me to work for Time Entertainment
and to help you, right?
Everyone has the right to choose their own path.
But You Xi's career is ruined.
You don't have to go through this with him.
What's funny?
What's funny, you ask?
Song Qiege, I'm not a greedy and shameless guy
you might think I am.
Now is the time when You Xi needs my help and support the most.
You are asking me to betray him.
What makes you think I'll do that?
Brother Morry, you need to know.
It is You Xi who caused this situation.
Did You Xi think about you when he announced his relationship?
You don't have to think about him all the time.
With all the talk today,
Song Qiege, you must be very jealous of You Xi.
Am I right?
That's right. I know that
I am a considerate, smart, and talented agent, which is hard to find.
But working together also depends on the bond.
I am not an extraordinary man by any means.
But… I have nothing to hide.
I can't do anything at the expense of others.
I particularly don't do well with snobs,
because we don't match.
Do you know why you can't beat You Xi all the time?
The reason is simple.
You Xi has feelings.
He laughs and cries.
He's sincere.
He'll do anything for the people and things he loves,
while you have always been...
a cold commodity.
And you will always be a commodity.
It was good.
Thanks for the coffee.
I'll get going.
Also,
I prefer to be called Brother Dazhuang.
[You Xi's Script]
Mr. You, what are you doing?
My mentor said that I should study up on the roles I've played and find some shortcomings.
That way, I can find a breakthrough.
Sounds reasonable.
What did you get out of it?
Of course, why don't you take a look?
Sorry.
I'm a policeman.
My role was a policeman.
I found out that he was undercover.
He tried to intervene but I stood firm and stuck to justice.
But I think acting like this was wrong.
It should be…
Sorry.
I'm a policeman.
How was my acting?
Better than his.
- Next one.
- Okay.
Let's try this one.
This is it.
I discovered that the person who killed my father was someone I loved.
There should be agony, guilt, and self-reproach when killing her.
Look.
The way I was acting was so immature.
It's totally wrong.
Watch this.
Work with me.
I love you.
But… it's too late.
What do you think?
- Anything else?
- Let's see the next one.
For this one…
the girl I like misunderstood my relationships with other female friends.
I needed to kiss her to make her stay.
But I was being too rude.
It should have been...
like this.
I-I'll get the door.
Third Uncle, I've been blacklisted.
Yaoyao.
Third Uncle, tell me.
Is my acting that bad?
They scolded me instead of Zheng Jia.
I thought it was a big deal.
Listen. This will happen every day.
If you can't take it,
just go home early and sell barbecue.
You're a public figure.
Some people like you and some people hate you.
The internet just amplifies the voices.
Don't take it seriously.
- But…
- All right.
That's all for today's therapy.
Go home and sleep.
Forget everything.
We're going to watch a movie. Bye.
- A movie? I'll join as well.
- No.
Yaoyao.
With all that happened to me,
are you going to leave me alone?
Okay. We'll watch the movie together.
- You…
- Yaoyao, you are the best.
What movie are we going to watch later?
What do you like?
That one with superheroes.
Do you like it?
It's all right.
- Then, how about… a romantic movie?
- Duo Duo?
- There are some emotional scenes in romantic movies.
- Duo Duo.
- Or how about historical movies.
- Brother Chao.
Brother Chao? Brother Chao?
He loves being a listening ear.
If you go to him now, he won't say no to you.
And he also knows how to act.
You can practice with him.
Practice things like kissing scenes
or bed scenes.
My idol, I need comfort.
I don't want any.
My idol.
Is my acting good or Zheng Jia's?
- I never saw your acting.
- You haven't?
It's okay.
I'll show you.
Like a scene where a girl is proposed to.
I was like…
"I do.
Do you know how long I've been waiting for this moment?
I do. I do. I do."
She was like…
"Baby."
"Honey. Dear.
I do."
My idol, tell me.
Who is better?
You…
See?
My acting is better.
They all called me names.
I mean...
Are you done?
I am.
Let's move on to the next step now.
Next step?
My idol, practice with me.
There is a kissing scene.
I can't do it right.
This one.
My idol, can you teach me?
I haven't acted in a long time.
Why? My idol.
You are a movie king.
I didn't want to steal your third uncle's place.
That's right.
My idol, if you were in a popular drama,
there would be nothing to do with my third uncle.
At that time, you would be the leading actress
and I would be the leading actor.
The two of us working together would be perfect.
Get up.
My idol, I missed your bed so much.
♫  The world is so big,
yet a word of love from you makes me melt  ♫
♫  Watching you decorate this little home,  ♫
♫  the overflowing happiness can barely be contained  ♫
♫  The noise of spring and autumn, the temperature difference between winter and summer  ♫
♫  they've all become picturesque  ♫
♫  Even if worries accompany sunsets,  ♫
♫  is there any reasons not to cherish the moment?  ♫
♫  I'll be with you when you cry  ♫
♫  I'll pamper you so that you won't ruin your makeup  ♫
♫  I will take you wherever you want to go  ♫
♫  You are my girl  ♫
♫  I want you to be my goddess for the rest of my life  ♫
♫  I'll gently light the lamp in the quiet of the night  ♫
♫  I'll hold you in my arms and let you sleep soundly  ♫
♫  I'm your man  ♫
♫  I will take care of you with my all  ♫
♫  I'll silently follow the perfect script in your heart  ♫
♫  It's you who makes everything become possible
and love to be flawless  ♫