This series are new story, All story, contents and events created for entertainment purposes only. Viewer discretion is advised.
Here.
Thank you.
Aren't you dressed too well?
Do you want to be handsome for your customers?
No.
I want to dress for you.
So you can see that I also have a handsome side.
Yeah.
Hey.
When will you stop holding my hand?
If customers see it, they will misunderstand.
I don't want to.
No one saw us.
Oh, hey?
Nine.
I don't remember because your name was Mr. N.
Welcome.
Three months later, after The Air.
It's been three months...
since he hasn't contacted me.
When can I give up on you?
For those who can't move on from your love,
we have a solution for you.
Sometimes you have to delete all your memories with them
to create new memories.
It's hard to forget, isn't it?
He suddenly stopped contacting me.
He didn't reply to my messages.
Damn, he's really suck.
He didn't tell me his Facebook.
He didn't even tell me his Instagram.
Why am I so unlucky?
Hello.
Hello. Daonuea.
Hey.
It's not work time.
Calm down, Daonuea.
Tee wants a meeting tomorrow about the company.
Why didn't you tell me on Line?
Yeah.
I don't understand either.
Why don't you guys talk?
Why did he let me tell you?
No!
I mean you.
Oh, really?
Sorry, bro.
See you at 9 a.m. tomorrow.
Bye bye.
What's wrong with him?
[Have you slept yet?]
He read it, but he didn't answer me.
Maybe he's busy.
Daonuea.
Stop thinking about it.
He stopped contacting you for a long time.
For Pisces, your love is passive.
You still won't get what you hoped for.
You should care more about the people around you than the person.
Because the people around you may want to reconcile with you.
Are you coming?
Let's start the meeting?
Have you eaten? Daonuea.
Uh... not yet.
But it's okay.
I heard you have an urgent matter.
Yeah.
But I already bought some porridge.
Let's eat together.
Let's have a meeting after this.
So that we can come up with creative ideas.
Here.
Thank you.
Let's eat porridge.
Tee.
I forgot to tell you that I don't like eggs like this.
Really?
I'll boil another egg for you.
Aw...
Next time if you buy it, you should ask me.
So you don't have to boil it.
Okay.
Next time I'll ask you in detail.
Tee.
I like to eat a lot of ginger.
Next time, bring some ginger.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Calm down.
I thought you'd forget about it.
Forget what?
Nothing.
Hurry up and eat it.
The porridge will cool down.
Do you have anything else to do today?
I want to buy something for the office this evening.
If you have time, you can come with me.
Umm...
Okay.
I'll go with you because you bought me a porridge.
Eh...?
Or... the reason you bought me some porridge is...
because you need someone to go shopping with you, right?
Oh...
You're so cunning.
It's not.
I bought it because you haven't eaten.
I think it's right.
That's nonsense.
Why do you know better than me?
Am I wrong?
You're absolutely cunning.
You're like Loki in Marvel.
Sometimes I wonder,
if I wasn't here,
who would I be with
and what would I be doing?
Thank you.
Why are you thanking me?
Nothing.
I just want to thank you.
Umm...
If you want to thank me,
I want...
What the hell are you doing?
Aren't we promised that we're not dating?
Why don't you invite me to eat too?
What?
You are late.
Even if your home is not far from the company.
I'm not late, Tee.
Look at this.
Now 9 a.m.
Well.
I told you to find new employees, have you found them yet?
I didn't forget.
I think you forgot so I didn't find a new employee.
I'll find a new employee later.
But the porridge...
can I eat it?
It's right there. You can eat it.
Over there?
Then I'll eat it now.
I'll go now.
I don't want to interrupt you guys.
I'm going to eat now.
Please eat a lot.
Yeah.
I have to tell you that
after finishing the work last month.
There is almost no new work.
Now our company is almost unprofitable.
Of course.
Look at how bad the government of our country is.
Otherwise we would be able to continue working.
Who?
You want me to tell?
Yeah.
Why?
(I ask) because I don't know.
Let's continue the meeting.
Yes, let's continue the meeting.
We can't shoot a set that is far away.
We can't film if there are many people.
So we have to change our strategy.
Oh, Tee.
What about our old customers?
Now their old customers are all resting.
But...
You need to prepare a profile of our company
to prepare new client presentations.
Otherwise our company's finances will be bad.
Umm...
I think we should do an online profile?
In order to get more people to see our company profile.
Well.
Okay, good. Boat.
It's a good idea.
Then you are responsible for this work.
What?
Why me?
Why you not tell Daonuea to do it?
Boat.
It's your idea.
You should be responsible for it.
That's right.
Okay.
Daonuea, please contact the customer
and finish the work of the remaining old customers as well.
Sure.
I'll do it.
Don't forget our appointment this evening.
Okay.
Why do you guys have an appointment?
Don't tell me...
I go to work!
It's just working.
I have to clear the work.
Work, work, work.
I'm really annoyed with you.
Work...
Oh, okay.
Oh! Tee.
Do I have to do a profile?
It's okay if you won't do it,
but you won't get the bonus.
I don't have a choice, right?
Now we are at Breeze Cafe.
They say if you eat it, you want to come back here again!
With the person you came with?
What are you talking about?
It's all messed up.
I don't want to edit it.
Okay, sorry.
I'm not teasing you anymore.
Most importantly,
everyone look at this, it's very tasty.
It looks so soft and tasty.
You mean that dish or me?
I'll stop shooting videos.
Why are you being mean to me?
You came to this cafe because you're going to tease me, right?
No.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that.
I just want you to eat something delicious.
Be careful of the ice cream melting.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll eat it.
Even though he was the same as before,
why didn't I have any feelings for him?
But I thought,
if that was him,
what would it be?
Daonuea.
Bring the dish closer to your face.
Hurry up.
Closer.
Okay.
Smile.
I'll take now.
1,2...
One more.
Closer?
How close do I have to be to hold it?
A little bit.
Okay.
Does it work?
Will it fall?
It messes up your face.
Let me see.
Who are you missing?
You're not usually like this, are you?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Just...
I'm just space out.
What did you just say?
Oh, nothing.
I didn't say anything.
Do you want me to take you home?
It's okay.
I can go home by myself.
Anyway, I have a place I want to go after this.
Then...
Do you want me to go with you?
It's okay.
We are not dating.
If you do this,
people will think you took care of your boyfriend.
Be careful, you won't have a lover.
I don't think about other lovers.
So,
I'm leaving now.
Thank you for this meal.
I'll pay for the next meal.
Okay.
I think my friend has arrived.
I'll go now.
If you're home, please tell me.
What's wrong with him?
Why does he always act like this?
Boat.
We need to talk.
Daonuea.
Why did you take out my airpods?
What do you want to say?
Let's talk outside.
I have something to ask you.
About what?
I have to work.
You have to send it to the customer later.
I also had to promote in the evening.
Do you really need to speak now?
Really?
Are you working?
Yes.
I am working.
I see you dancing.
Well.
It might...
be necessary.
Be necessary...
However,
if I'm late for the work,
you're responsible for it.
Okay.
Let's go.
You promised.
I will help you.
Come with me.
Hey, Daonuea.
Calm down, I have to put the chair.
Hurry up.
Daonuea.
Calm down.
Boat.
Is it true that Tee will flirt with me again?
Please tell him to stop.
It's about both of you.
I'm not involved.
I don't want to be involved.
It doesn't matter.
Please tell him to me.
I don't want to be awkward like this.
Awkward?
I see you like it, isn't it?
I didn't like it.
Not at all.
He pushed me too much.
He also made that facial expression.
Is this a good idea?
You should date him.
No.
Now I don't want to date anyone.
Don't tell me
the reason you don't want to date anyone
is because you still missing of the person you met at The Air
as the person you used to…
Like that.
It's hurt.
Yeah.
As you said.
I won't tell you anything.
Do you know his name, surname, address, place of work?
No.
What?
How did you fall in love with him?
Or...
About...
It's hurt, Daonuea.
I didn't mean that.
Yeah.
It is a human right to fall in love with someone.
Actually,
if you can't give up on your love,
you should contact him.
You should ask him for a meal
or tell him exactly how you feel.
You don't have to think alone.
Be careful, you're going crazy.
I text him every day.
He didn't answer me.
As for finding out about him...
I searched for pictures of him
or searched on Instagram
but I couldn't find anything.
Did you fall in love with a ghost?
I got goosebumps.
It's not, Boat.
If it's impossible
or too difficult,
you should give up.
If you miss him like this,
when can you start a new relationship?
But...
Stop saying 'but'.
Do you know?
He texts me 24 hours a day where you go.
It's not right.
Wait.
What do you mean?
You and Tee have a secret plan about me?
No.
I didn't mean that.
No, not at all.
Don't make excuses!
You!
What?
I told the facts that I saw.
You don't see it?
He always asks you what you want to eat or where to go.
You're the one who keeps running away.
What if in the end the relationship ended the same again?
Daonuea.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean to do that to you.
Umm.
Actually,
I know you're talking to that person behind my back.
But actually...
We are in a talking stage.
You're not wrong.
That you talking to other people.
I really love you.
Otherwise ,
I don't produce,
don't do production here
and don't indulge you like this.
You can say it.
So should I talk to other people too?
Please, Daonuea.
We should go back to being friends.
We can be partners as before.
So we don't have an uncomfortable relationship like this.
Please.
Wait, Daonuea.
Listen to me.
You should give him a chance.
No one would want to make the same mistake a second time.
Yesterday you picked up the wrong bag for my shirt.
What?
Why don't you tell me?
I fell asleep as soon as I got home.
You can send me a Line message
if I pick up something wrong again.
It's okay.
It doesn't matter.
It's just a shirt.
No.
If you do this
I will...
Tee!
You know I don't like it.
If you do this, I won't be with you anymore.
Daonuea.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to tease you.
I just want to surprise you.
What's the surprise?
They don't usually give cakes at night?
It's noon.
What about candles?
Where is the candle?
I don't want to do like the others.
You're crazy.
Come on.
If there are no candles, you can blow fakes.
Here.
Yea~
Are you funny?
Huh?
If you want to blow out the candles,
would you like to blow out my candles?
You're cunning.
I'm just kidding.
Here.
Let's eat cake.
Okay.
I forgive you.
I will...
I'll call you to take it back.
Take you?
A shirt!
Are you thinking about obscene?
No.
I really didn't think that way.
I swear.
I not believe you.
Or...
Should I give him a chance?
Or should I just give it up?
Hello, for anyone who wants to give up on love, you should listen to me.
Don't miss out on the (not) secret tips from Kapper.
Don't wait anymore.
Can I believe him?
Hey.
My tips are 100% reliable.
Fu*k.
Does he know I'm listening to him?
Hey, listen.
The first step, don't let it last longer,
get rid of anything close to you
that reminds you of them first.
Not only is it good for you,
but you can quickly forget your old love.
The important thing...
You have to burn it!
Burn it!
Huh?
Burn?
That's right! You have to burn everything.
You will be able to forget them.
It's way too cruel.
So...
I'll keep it in the locker.
Okay.
I've done it.
The next step,
old surroundings remind you of old memories.
Why don't you try changing the atmosphere to make your room look fresher?
You can use exercise equipment as your loneliness companion.
It works.
The next step,
They say that changing yourself into a new person will make you remember who you are,
more than you think about that person.
New styles can help you too.
Wow.
Wow, Daonuea.
Why are you so cool today?
So cool.
Your hair is cool too.
Your pants are beautiful too.
Your shoes too.
Look at your hair.
Hey.
Continue your work.
You're so cool.
Okay, I'll continue to work.
Oh, right. Tee!
It's your bag.
Next time you'll have to call me
if I picked up something wrong.
Okay.
Did you change your dressing style?
It's not your usual style.
Yeah.
I just thought I should change something.
How do I look?
Do you like it?
I...
like it.
I've never seen you dress like this before.
You really like it?
If it's not good, you can tell me.
I'm not angry with you.
Hey.
I really like it.
Thank you.
What's wrong, Tee?
Uh...
Boat made a profile of our company
so I want you to check if it works.
Yeah. Okay.
Wait a minute.
Umm... okay.
Hey! He's very good at editing.
I remember this job because the client wanted the actor's face to be brighter
so we had to reshoot.
The last one.
Sometimes, being open to new relationships with the people around you,
may find someone who loves you.
And most importantly, it will help you forget your old love.
Tee.
Would you like to watch with me?
Yeah.
Okay.
How was it? Do you like it?
Yeah.
The editor is very skilled.
I think he's good at bragging.
Ahem.
I heard it.
If you will gossip about me, please lower your voice.
I complimented you.
I didn't gossip you.
Yeah, okay. You compliment me.
Have you uploaded it yet?
Oh, yes.
I uploaded it before you arrived.
Then I will send it to the customer.
I should update with them.
Okay.
Tee, are you not working?
Oh.
Do you have time today? Daonuea.
Do you want to eat together?
Or...
You can order delivery here.
It depends on your convenience.
Umm. I'm okay with all of it.
Okay.
So...
I'm going to continue my work.
Yeah.
Let's work.
You're good at other people's business.
I'm just worried about you.
Would you like to drink water?
I have a hand,
I can pick it up myself.
You are mean to me.
Your favorite brand of fried chicken has arrived.
It's delicious.
Where is Boat?
Did he not eat it?
Normally, if he knew we were ordering food, he would have run like lightning.
It's good, he should go home.
I can't pay him every meal.
Hey, Tee.
If you say so,
he will sulky.
After that, you reconcile him.
Aren't you going live?
Usually you always live.
I don't know.
I want a social detox.
Using social media for a long time is causing headaches.
Oh...
You're like a new person.
What?
I am the same person as before.
Please say it right.
Yeah.
Let's eat some chicken, it's getting cold.
Here.
I have a hand.
Oh.
Oh, it's hot.
You said you had hands, didn't you?
Take it.
You don't need to do this to me.
It's okay.
I'm willing.
If I don't do it,
will you eat chicken with me?
If you tell me, I have to eat it anyway.
You didn't tell me.
Hey.
What do you do?
Do you use your hand to hold the fried chicken?
You know? It takes me a long time to set my hair to find a look that works for me.
My hands are not stained.
Look at my hands. Is it stained?
Your hands are full of oil, hey!
Tee!
I'm just going to style your hair.
- I'm just going to style your hair.
- It's all messed up.
Tee! Stop!
I will take revenge!
Boat.
Yeah.
Come here.
Umm...
I want to scale up here.
- This file?
- Yes.
I think you have to fix 2 places here.
I think it's better than this one.
Ok, I'll fix it in the evening.
No problem.
Tee, do customers contact you?
Not yet.
We have to keep waiting.
Besides,
the economy is bad right now.
Not many people want to invest.
Fighting.
It's okay.
We will definitely have customers soon.
Our work is excellent.
Yeah. I think so.
You're awesome.
And...
Hey!
Someone contacted me by email.
Really?
Here.
Wow, really?
We have customers?
Umm...
Mister N... Are you sure?
Isn't it a scammer?
I think it's weird.
Umm...
Yes.
Notice from the way he writes,
I think it comes from a real person.
Umm... but I think...
He doesn't seem trustworthy.
Why does he have to ask for more information about our company
when we have a portfolio?
Moreover, his first and last name
was not written at all.
Wow.
But they say they will support our ad production.
But what does this mean?
They want to invest with us?
Okay,
we must meet with him
to be more confident and understand.
Okay.
Hey.
I want to high five with you.
Hang in there.
Daonuea.
Are you sleeping, right?
I'll blackmail you.
Black and white.
I'll print it.
Wow.
It's very similar to him.
The picture is very obvious.
Should I paste it here?
Here? No.
Here?
No.
Let's work.
What?
Where has Tee gone? Boat.
Tee... He went to do business.
I think he came back late at night.
And...
Have you reconciled?
Look at you!
Daonuea!
Why did you hit me?
Hey.
Why are you curious about other businesses?
Hey, hey.
When you guys are in love,
are you suddenly leaving me alone?
Leaving what?
That's nonsense.
I'll go home.
Oh.
Remember to turn off the lights and everything.
Last time, you didn't turn off the lights.
I will tell Tee.
Yeah.
Telltale...
I mean brothers, you and I are brothers.
You heard wrong.
I just forgot to turn off the light, why do you have to tell him?
He said he would eat with me today, didn't he?
I'll leaving now.
Let's continue work.
Hey.
Why are you in my house?
Wait.
Will you light candles and blow balloons?
The balloon will explode! Don't blow it.
Tell me what you will do.
Are you planning with Boat? Huh?
No.
I didn't do that.
I do it all alone.
If it caught on fire,
wouldn't my house burn?
What if you die?
I'm sorry.
I've made a mistake.
I say because I'm worried about you.
Don't do this again.
Okay, I'm not mad anymore.
Get up now.
What do you want?
I just...
want to have a relationship with you.
Are you okay with it? Daonuea.
Can we be the same as before?
When we weren't friends like now.
Okay.
What relationship status do you want?
Can I be your boyfriend?
Did you skip the relationship status?
Huh?
I don't want to waste my time with other people.
If I'm okay,
can I be your lover later?
Okay.
According to your comfortable.
Then...
Are we back in the relationship as before?
Yeah.
Here.
Keep fighting.
Don't worry.
I'll help you.
Thank you.
Oh!
Is he coming?
Mr...
Mr. N or something.
Oh.
He's probably on his way.
Then...
I'll make coffee for you.
Okay.
Keep fighting!
Hey, when will you stop holding my hand?
No.
No one saw us.
Hey, Nine.
I don't remember because your name was Mr. N.
Welcome.
How are you? Tee.
I haven't seen you in a long time.
Since when?
3 years ago?
When we were still studying.
Yes.
My friend and I can't contact you.
You don't use social media too.
You just post pictures of views when using social media.
So I don't know how you are.
For me it doesn't change.
I just want to find something to do lately.
Let's go inside and talk.
I forgot to introduce him.
This is Daonuea. He is...
Tee's partner.
Hey, Nine.
Did you know him before?