Hello, welcome to The Air Khao yai
I’d like to check in, please.
You first.
Thank you
I thought the two of you came together because you checked in together.
Oh no, I didn't come with him.
Please give me your ID card.
This is your room key.
Thank you
Excuse me?
This is your room key.
You look at him and it makes me think you're sharing the same room with him.
Sorry
I feel something
There seems to be a loud noise in the room.
Hello, mom!
I was taking a shower just now
You're there already, right?
Is everything okay?
It's very good, mom.
The resort is so beautiful.
The atmosphere is good too.
Where are your other friends?
Why does your surroundings seem silent?
Oh! My other friends are in different rooms.
There are many people.
You don't have to worry about me.
Okay
Bye
You lied to your mom.
Be careful, your mother will know about it.
Hey! You!
Oh?
You know me so fast.
Huh?
My name is Nine
When you say 'You' it's right. (Homophones)
'Hey, you'
And you?
What's your name?
Do I need to tell you?
You're not my friend
It's up to you
If your mom calls you again, don't ask me for help.
Be careful, your mother knows that you lied.
My name is Daonuea
Goat, eat this.
Strange guy, he can talk to goats.
What a strange person
Hello, my name is Nine.
I am a goat caretaker at this resort.
I really like talking to goats!
Because the goats say 'baa~'
baa!
Hello~
Now we are at The Air Resort @ Khao Yai.
I want to say that the atmosphere and location here are good
and the staff are very helpful too!
They are famous for this!
But now we live in Moroc @ The Air.
Here
So let's go check out.
Bye bye!
I told you that our love was impossible.
I don't love you anymore, Praew.
Please Praew, can you leave me alone?
Hello, mom!
How are you? Is the weather good at Khao Yai?
Yes, mom!
You don't have to worry about me.
But where are your friends?
I can't hear your friend talking.
You didn't send me a photo too.
Nine!
My mother called me.
Please talk to my mother.
Otherwise my mom wouldn't believe me that I was actually on a trip with friends.
Hello, mom
I'm Nine
Nine...
Who's Nine?
Daonuea has a friend named Nine?
Why don't I know you?
I feel offended to you, mom
Why can't you remember me?
I just didn't come to see you at home.
So you don't remember me?
It's okay
I might forget you because I'm old.
Please take care of Daonuea.
He's Allergic Rhinitis.
Don't forget to bring him an antihistamine.
Oh, I have one more thing to say.
Daonuea, he is not good with cold weather.
Don't turn on the air conditioner too cold.
Please take care of each other because both of you are in the same room.
Don't steal Daonuea's blanket.
Same room!?
Yes, mom
We are in the same room.
Don't worry, mom.
I'll take special care of Daonuea.
I will cover him with a blanket to warm himself.
Bye, mom
Bye
You talk like you're close to my mother.
You should say thank you to me first.
For helping you.
You ask for a debt of gratitude to me so well.
Okay
Thanks
But...
Why are you swimming alone?
Because I came alone.
So, why are you taking pictures up here?
I like to take pictures.
I like to keep memories
of happy times.
Happiness?
Yes, happiness
Why?
Oh
No
Nothing
It's good that you're happy.
Why should we want to suffer?
Yes
Nine
Let's swim together
Oh my god!
He took off his shirt and swam together.
Oh!
Excuse me?
Can I order 4 cans of beer?
With pleasure, our guest
I ordered a beer
You want 4 cans of beer, right?
Yes
About 4, right?
About 4?
What is wrong with you?
Why do you look tensed?
Oh
I'm...
This water is cold.
It's cold.
So I tensed.
Do you think it would be better
if the sun would always shine?
Yeah
Daonuea
Have you ever thought
that we can't always get what we want?
How is it?
It's like...
it's impossible for the good times to stay with us forever.
Just like the sun
which it has at sunrise
and sunset.
Just like now
But actually,
it's beautiful at night.
Because there are stars in the sky
and moon light.
If you don't believe it,
you can see it tonight.
It won't be long.
There are no stars in the sky today.
That's disappointing.
But...
Why are you traveling alone?
I just broke up with my girlfriend,
so I need some time to relax myself.
What about you? Daonuea
Why are you traveling alone?
I'm...
I've just been disappointed with something.
It must be similar to you.
That's love
When we are happy,
we are happy.
When we are suffering,
it hurts.
Hey, you're shivering cold.
We should just stop here.
You'll be sick.
Yes?
Can I take a shower here?
The water in my bathroom is not working.
I called the front of the resort and no one answered.
Okay
but...
Let me take a shower before you.
Why can't we shower together?
So that it doesn't waste your time.
Are you crazy?
Why do we have to shower together?
We're not that close.
What are you embarrassed about?
Or are you...?
you...
Okay!
I'm not embarrassed by you.
Please come in.
But...
why did you lie your mom about the trip?
Umm...
Actually, I don't want to lie to my mother.
I just don't want to stress my mom.
Maybe you don't want your mom to know
that you're heartbroken?
You know me so well.
You have a clairvoyant?
No
I can know, just by looking at you.
Your facial expressions are obvious.
Would you like to drink more beer?
If you don't drink it, I'm going to bed.
It's up to you.
I’m fine with either.
So...
That's enough for today.
Tomorrow I have to wake up to shoot video content.
Okay
I have no problem.
For tonight...
Good night
You just turn on the air conditioner at this temperature, that's enough.
It shouldn't be too cold.
Otherwise you might be sick.
Don't forget to take your antihistamine before you go to bed.
Are you ready?
What do you mean?
What?
You didn't say you were going to shoot a video?
Me
I'll go with you,
so you won't be lonely.
I didn't tell you that I was lonely.
Why did you wake up early today?
I usually wake up early.
Aren't you going to take your picture today?
I don't know what to shoot.
I don't know what I'm going to shoot.
Or... will you be my model?
My wages are expensive.
Do you know this?
You should hold me tight
If you're not careful, you'll get hurt.
Hello, today you guys meet Daonuea again.
Today we are still at The Air Resort.
This is a goat farm.
Let's go to see it!
The goats here are said to be very cute.
We can easily feed them,
and they are so tame.
I recommend that if anyone comes to the Air Resort, you can play with goats.
You can watch me play with them.
Hey, goat!
Oh
This way!
Here's your food, goat!
Goat!
Hey! Goat!
They're not tame at all.
I'll roast them all.
You can talk to goats too?
What?
You talk to goats too!
How do you know that I've talked to goats?
I'm...
That's day!
I happened to be riding a bicycle
and heard you were talking to a goat.
Are you sure you're just a coincidence?
We should go back.
It's raining now.
Hello, my guest!
There's a BBQ party tonight.
It's free, free, and free!
I invite you both.
Okay!
You guys look good together.
Oh, I'm so pleased
Bye bye~!
Let's go
Have you finished dressing yet?
We go to dinner,
not a fashion walk.
No, I'm afraid I'm not handsome.
It's a special occasion,
I should honor the resort.
It's up to you.
I'm sorry
I didn't mean to do it.
Let's go
I'm ready now.
Is he bipolar?
What did you say?
Oh, no
Nothing
I would say that your perfume...
smells good.
Do you like this scent?
You can smell it,
in case you can't smell it clearly.
We have to go now.
If we go late, there will be no food left.
Have you finished yet?
They've been waiting for a long time.
I feel embarrassed.
Go
What are you embarrassed about?
Hey! Our guest!
Hey, do you think our guests are handsome?
Welcome
The party has just begun.
I will introduce you to your neighbors.
Please come this way.
They are your neighbors.
Hey guys, are my guests handsome?
Yes
Hey, his head is red,
is it blood?
Excuse me.
Please come to this way.
Please sit here.
Please take care of them.
My pleasure
I'll be serving drinks in a moment.
Yeah, thank you
Hello
Well
What zone are you guys in?
Today I'm in Morocco 2.
Did the two of you come together?
Oh
We didn't come together.
Yeah
Our tents are next to each other.
Let's eat
Oh, yeah
Thank you
Have you guys eaten it yet?
- I already ate it
- The food here is delicious.
Your drink is ready.
Here you are
Thank you
- Excuse me.
- Yeah
Bye bye
Thank you
Well
Let's cheers
Okay
For tonight.
How are you?
Roasted pork
It's delicious
I think so
Wow
It's so delicious
Yes
Hey
Is everything okay?
Yes
Let's dance!
Hurry up, get up!
Okay
Let's go
Tonight is a happy night.
Yes
It's so fun~
Are you okay?
Yes
I'm so fine
Do you have a beer?
Here
I'm back tomorrow,
I don't want to back now.
We're not together tomorrow.
Hello
Was last night's party fun?
Today I'm here to provide you with a check-out service.
Thank you
Next time, please come back here again.
Has the person next to my room checked out?
Check out, please
Thank you
Next time, please come back here again.
Oh!
Excuse me,
I have to go serve another guest.
If there is another chance,
let's meet again.
Bye
Daonuea
Bye bye
Nine
Daonuea!
Can you give me your LINE?