Characters, actions, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series. Viewer discretion is advised.
Daonuea.
Yes?
I'll buy you ice cream.
Okay.
Hey, kiddo.
Why are you sitting here alone?
I'm waiting for my mother.
Look at you. Mosquitoes bite you.
Where is your home?
I'll take you to your home.
Daonuea.
Talk to me, please.
I'm sorry.
Daonuea.
Just tell what you want to say.
I can't take it any longer.
Daonuea.
I'm sorry for lying to you about everything.
I don't know how I should feel about it.
Should I be glad
you gave me money and the company
or should I be disappointed that you lied to me?
Why does being with you, it's make me so confused?
What should I do?
Daonuea.
I don't have secrets to hide from you anymore.
Don't leave me.
I can't live without you.
Umm.
Do you have any secrets?
Nothing.
I really told you everything.
Okay.
I'll assume you have good intentions.
In addition,
it's your money.
However,
it still circulates in the company.
You still haven't forgiven me?
I still haven't forgiven you.
Tomorrow,
you must apologize to everyone
in the office.
If not, I won't speak to you any more.
Okay.
Please come with me, Daonuea.
I definitely have to go with you.
What will happen at the office?
I can handle it.
You don't have to worry, Daonuea.
I'm not referring to you.
I mean everyone.
What will Tee and the others think
about what you're doing?
Huh?
Umm.
Tomorrow
I will definitely apologize to everyone.
Good.
Get back if you have nothing.
Don't pretend to want to sleep here.
I'm so tried.
I will rest here.
Hold on, Nine.
Hey.
Stop using this way.
I'm so sleepy.
Nine!
Huh?
You're... really...
[Lodestar Production]
Tee.
If you stay like this,
we probably won't be able to know
what we should to do next.
Yes.
You are the best boss here.
You have to make a decision now.
Alright.
I would like to ask your opinions,
what do you guys think about this?
For me,
Nine isn't that bad.
Why?
He gave me a chance to approach
Candy.
For me, actually...
Nine taught me a lot about how to use a camera.
He also knows how much I love to take pictures.
Ice.
If you want your pictures to look better,
you must change the lens.
Now you're using a normal lens,
change it to telephoto lens.
The telephoto lens will give your photos a more dimensional look.
The front is clear and the back is blurred.
It makes the product stand out more.
Ice.
Don't hesitate to start doing something
or fixing something.
Just trust your instincts.
Otherwise,
you'll stop loving your work one day.
Do you get it?
Have you ever thought
that what Nine did
was because he was deceiving us?
Uh...
If you think so,
it might be possible.
After this, he won't lie to Daonuea?
All that Nine did,
he just wanted to help you
and Daonuea.
Why
can good intentions
turn into deception?
Hey.
Nine.
Where have you been?
It's been several days.
I'm having some trouble.
Oh.
The other day I prepared a present for him,
have you brought it to him yet?
Yeah.
I already gave it to him.
Did he say anything?
I thought I would never receive a gift from anyone.
My name is Daonuea.
I'm Tee.
Please look after me.
Let's exchange contacts?
No.
He didn't say anything.
Really?
It's okay.
I'm just surprised.
So,
how does he look?
His face was nothing special.
I think you should focus on studying.
Be careful that you don't graduate.
Okay.
What part of your body will you exercise today?
I think I'll work out my shoulders.
Oh, okay.
[Are you really getting home with me? >_<]
I don't know either.
Are you guy meeting?
Oh.
Just about work.
Do you have anything to tell us?
Someone...
wants to apologize to you guys.
Come here.
I apologize to you all
for messed up the problem.
I apologize that I didn't tell you before, Tee.
I'm willing to take any punishment.
You can fire me.
It's alright.
Just you come to apologize, I'm fine now.
Nine sincerely apologize, Tee.
You don't have to bow that much.
If you get fired, who will help us?
We have a lot of work to do now.
Gosh...
The sky is beautiful.
Yes.
It's beautiful.
I mean the sky!
So
when will you accept my request?
Nine.
Let me ask you something.
Will we be lovers
or not,
is it that different?
Of course.
How is it?
If I were your lover,
I would be able to get jealous
when I saw you with someone else.
Including Tee.
And I can get mad
Ouch!
when you don't let me kiss your cheek.
Hey.
Please get more serious.
I'm sorry.
If we were lovers,
it would be a confirmation
that you will be with me forever.
Forever...
it doesn't exist.
So let's make it come true.
Huh?
It's evening now,
let's go downstairs.
Let's go.
[Lodestar Production]
Are you really going home?
Why are you so serious about how you look these days?
Are you okay, right?
Are you crazy? Ice.
You ask if I'm okay.
Why can't I dress nicely?
It looks good,
but before you dated Candy,
you never cared this much about yourself.
Ice.
This is the promotion period.
I need to dedicate myself to it.
Does dating someone
take this much effort?
Baby, I'm here.
Candy.
Wait a moment.
Just talk to Ice.
He's free now.
By the way, if you want to travel,
you can book through AirAsia Super App.
You can look up the places you wish to go.
You can choose them all.
I'll pay for you.
Huh?
Oh.
I forgot to shave.
I'll be back.
What happened to him?
I don't know either, Candy.
AirAsia Super App.
Hey.
AirAsia Super App can book flights,
or can book flights with hotels.
They have a food delivery service too!
They have messenger service too.
It's also cheap!
Wow.
Where should I go?
Candy.
Can you book a flight for me too?
Let Boat pay for it.
Okay.
Ice.
I can hear you.
Stop it.
I'll pay only for Candy.
If you want to travel, pay for it yourself.
Now you and Boat...
Yeah.
We are now in a relationship.
Oh, okay.
I never thought that you guys were dating.
Why? Ice.
Do you feel regret about me?
I'll tell you that the door to my heart is now closed.
I'm sorry, Ice.
Uh...
It isn't.
I'm just going to say that
it would be a good destiny
that you guys were dating.
You don't regret me?
You're so mean.
Candy.
I'm here.
Where are we going today?
I haven't eaten anything today, baby.
Can you take me out to dinner?
Sure.
Let's go.
What about you? Ice.
Do you want to join us?
Uh...
It's okay.
I'll back home soon.
Okay.
Then I'm leaving now.
Bye bye.
Don't regret me later.
This way, please. Baby.
Let's go.
Great!
I'm leaving now.
When can I have a date like this?
Tee.
Are you okay?
You can talk to me about anything.
It's nothing.
I just can't get over
to have a brotherly relationship with him again.
Also,
Daonuea is not working here anymore.
How can we stay together without being awkward?
It's good,
so that you can give up on Daonuea.
Umm.
I couldn't stand to see
Daonuea with Nine every day.
You will be able to forget Daonuea on your own
as time goes by.
Oh!
But I have another way.
You need to find a new love
so that you can forget Daonuea.
It's like focusing on things.
Let's say Daonuea is this pen
and you focus on it.
It's like you focus on Daonuea.
But if you focus the lamp over there,
the pen will get blurry.
What does it mean?
It means...
just finding a new love.
I'm old, who's interested in me?
Hey.
You're handsome, Tee.
Is there anyone who doesn't want to date you?
It has me, one person.
If I knew you were single, I would stand in line to flirt with you.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Nothing, I'm just saying that I've never dated before.
But you don't have to listen to me everything.
I'm just saying.
Hey.
It isn't.
I mean just saying goodbye here.
If you enter my room,
it will be as hectic as last night.
No.
What would happen if you were kidnapped?
Hey.
About 10 more steps, it will reach my house.
That's it.
This is another reason.
If you accept my request,
I will be able to enter your home.
It's not relevant at all.
Whether we are lovers or not,
I decide who I will let inside the home.
Alright.
If you say so.
What?
If you say so?
What does it mean?
Nothing.
I'll getting home now.
See you tomorrow.
What's going on with you? Daonuea.
Huh?
Just stop talking.
(There isn't a job that I want)
[Daonuea, help me!!!!]
Candy.
What's the matter?
Huh?
You want to meet me right now?
[Flann O'Brien's Irish Pub]
Candy!
Hey!
Please stop.
What makes you drink so much?
What about Boat?
I don't know.
I don't know where he is.
Huh?
So
you want to getting back?
No.
Why must all men in the world be evil?
I won't love anyone else anymore!
Hey, stop.
Baby.
I need to use the restroom.
Okay.
I'll be back.
[Irish Pub]
Huh?
Where did him go?
Oh.
I forgot my jacket, let me pick it up first.
What is this? Boat.
What does it mean?
Ouch!
I can't take it anymore.
Baby, let's...
let's talk later.
Ouch...
I have to go now.
I really can't take it.
Ouch...
Just go wherever you want!
Just do anything you want!
Really? Candy.
Does Boat really do that?
I tell you the truth about everything.
Why? Daonuea.
I can't trust someone?
I just want to have good love with someone.
Oh, it's alright.
Oh...
Umm.
I want to have a good love too.
Daonuea already has a good love, isn't it?
Actually,
I'm more afraid of being in love.
I don't know.
Perhaps it's like you,
who don't want to be left behind alone.
Hey.
You hit the nail on the head.
Oh, wipe it.
Candy.
Oh.
Here, napkin.
You want to blow the nose?
Are you feeling better, Candy?
I feel better now.
Yeah.
So
what will you do next?
Will you break up with Boat?
I don't know.
Perhaps.
You guys aren't going to talk?
I still believe that
Boat shouldn't do that.
He had promised me that
if he had a lover,
he would love and respect her very much.
For love, it's true.
But for infidelity, I can't take it.
I had a boyfriend before,
and eventually he cheated on me.
Fortunately, Nine helped me at that time.
Otherwise I would have slept like a dog on the street.
Uh...
What about you? Daonuea.
Why didn't you accept Nine's request?
I don't know.
I'd be afraid
when I bonded with someone
and we had to break up.
I would be very disappointed.
If you still don't believe in Nine,
I can testify to him
that his feelings for you are true.
Also, he's always missed you
since he came back from Khao Yai back then.
Daonuea.
Just trust in Nine.
His feelings for you are true.
Unlike Boat!
Look at him.
Our relationship had just begun
but he cheated on me.
Oh.
Calm down.
Uh.
Uh, is this good?
If you want to break up with him,
you should officially break up with him.
It's not a good thing to break up like this.
Believe me.
What do you want me to do?
Uh...
Oh.
Come here.
Great!
You're screwed.
[Lodestar Production]
1,2...
Please smile more, Tee.
1,2,3.
Tee.
I think you're still too tensed.
Hey, Ice.
I need some time to get better.
You want me to take a profile picture
to apply for a dating application?
It's very challenging.
Nowadays, it's normal.
If you're embarrassed,
you might miss the chance to meet someone.
Yeah.
It's true.
Come on, let's continue.
Okay.
Please relax more.
1,2,3!
That's great!
Just like that.
Please look the other way.
It's better, Tee.
Bastard!
What sound is it?
Boat might have dropped something again.
Just ignore him.
Let's continue.
Great.
One more picture.
Who pulled...
Oh...
My baby.
How did you get here?
Stop saying baby.
We need to talk.
So let's talk outside, shall we?
No.
Just talk in here.
Let everyone know that
you rode your motorcycle and bring the girl home.
Bastard!
You got it wrong, Candy.
He took her to the hospital.
What did you say?
Ouch!
Be careful.
Ouch...
Are you okay?
I'm hurt.
Which leg?
Right here.
I think you sprained ankle.
Let's go to the hospital?
I'll take you there.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
Ouch...
Calm down.
Hold my neck.
Ouch...
I forgot my jacket, please stay here.
What is this? Boat.
What does it mean?
I can't take it anymore.
Ouch...
I can't take it.
Baby, let's...
let's talk later.
Ouch...
Just go wherever you want!
I really can't take it.
Just do anything you want!
Ouch...
Are you okay?
Can you come on my motorcycle?
Ouch...
Really?
Yes.
Here.
Boat sent me a picture.
Why didn't you tell me earlier? Darling.
You blocked my number and Line in every contact.
How can I contact you?
You must tell me earlier, Darling.
I'm very sad.
Gosh... my baby.
Let's get back together.
Uh.
What happened?
This is your resignation letter.
You can sign it.
But I want to reassure you
that you won't really change your mind, right?
Yes.
I think
I wouldn't change my mind.
At least,
to make this company better
and to make you better.
For me, I have more time to myself.
Yeah.
I don't force you.
How is your relationship with Nine?
So...
it's okay.
It doesn't change.
Nine didn't disappoint you, right?
Tee.
Don't worry about me.
I think it might be me
that disappoints Nine.
But,
it's good that we're back in a brotherly relationship.
Tee.
Anyway, you're the one brother that I love the most.
Come on.
Let's hug.
Thank you.
Uh.
Excuse me.
I didn't mean to bother you guys.
Tee.
Please check the picture together,
I have to send the picture to the client now.
I will follow you.
See you again, Daonuea.
If you have some time,
I would like to invite you to the farewell party.
Sure.
Please contact me again.
I think our client have been waiting a long time.
Yeah.
I'm going now.
What is that?
[Impact Lake Front]
Wow.
This...
Nine.
What meal is this?
Why does everything look so expensive?
Just think it's the beginning of a new life after your resignation
after your resignation.
A new life?
Everything is the same.
I didn't even submit a job application anywhere.
You don't need to hurry.
You can rest first.
Or do you want me to take you on a trip?
It's okay, Nine.
The company is busy these days.
If we travel
and personal is missing one person,
it will make other people work harder.
Somehow other people can handle it.
It's not true.
Even after I resigned for a few days,
Ice still sent me a message for help.
So
when
can we start the new beginning again?
You have to keep waiting
for what will happen in the future.
Nine.
I also apologize to you
for my stupidity.
Actually,
I don't want you to be uncomfortable like this.
I'm not uncomfortable.
I just want to say that
you can tell me
if you are ready.
Okay.
Actually,
I can
be ready.
What did
you just say?
I'm ready.
Really?
Yeah.
Close your eyes now.
Close my eyes?
Close your eyes.
Hurry up.
Yeah.
Are you happy now?
Hey!
Don't move.
What are you doing?
Just stay still
and follow me.
Huh?
Yes.
Get up.
I'm scared.
Don't be afraid.
Well, walk up.
Watch out for me.
Go straight ahead.
Nine.
I'm scared.
Don't tease me, Nine.
I'm not teasing you.
Are you ready?
Huh?
It's so beautiful, Nine.
Do you need to overact like this?
Just show that
you're engaged now.
If someone sees it,
they will stop approaching you.
It means...
Please give me your hand.
Then...
What about you?
So no one will approach you either.
For fairness.
Will you wear a ring for me?
Yeah.
Bring me your ring.
Give me your hand.
This isn't official.
Okay.
Actually, this is boyfriend's stage.
It's not
that far.
That's it.
Why are you smile?
Nothing.
I'm just happy.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Okay.
Uh...
What do I have to say?
Cheers.
Do you like it? Daonuea.
Yes.
Daonuea.
[Lodestar Production]
Tee.
How was it?
The application that I recommend you?
Is it okay?
Oh.
Okay.
What are you guys talking about?
Just a game.
Y...y...yes!
It's a game, Tee just downloaded ROV game.
Soon we will be playing ranked together.
Really?
What rank are you in right now?
Tee has no rank.
He just downloaded the application today.
Alas...
If you want to
be as good as me,
you
can always tell me.
Because I
get conqueror every season.
Yeah.
You can help me later.
Okay.
Oh.
I ordered food before.
I'll get it first.
Hello.
Ice.
Is this application really safe?
The person we're talking to
isn't a robot, right?
It's not.
Believe me.
You said you've never used it before.
I checked it from the reviews.
Here.
Someone contacted me already.
Hey!
Really?
Just date with him!
What are you waiting for?
If he's not like the picture,
just get back home.
I'm afraid to.
You can do it.
Believe me.
So...
I'll pay you one day.
Please go on a date with me.
Huh?
You pay me to date with you?
It isn't.
I mean with me. With me.
Oh.
Okay.
But actually you don't need to pay me.
Then I will treat you.
Okay.
What time do you meet him?
This evening?
Yeah.
This evening.
[Breeze Café & Bar]
Keep fighting.
You are Tee, right?
Yes.
That's right.
Have you ordered food yet?
Yes.
I think it didn't take long.
It's okay.
I have nothing planned today.
Yes.
Thank you.
Is this your regular restaurant?
Yes.
It's near my office.
Besides, the food here is delicious too.
So I chose this restaurant.
That's great.
But...
what's your occupation?
Uh...
I opened a production house here.
Umm...
It's great.
I'll ask for your help next time.
Yes.
My pleasure.
Thank you so much.
Why are you thanking me?
You seem tensed, Tee.
Actually, I don't behave properly when I meet someone strangers.
So...
What do I have to do to stop being a stranger?
I don't know either.
Let's continue.
Thank you.
Hello.
Is this the number of the Portrait Live Love Dream contestant Ice?
Yes.
Ice.
Ice, you forgot to send me a copy of your ID card.
Please send it to me again?
It would be nice if you were faster.
Because it will close for applications this evening.
If your documents are missing, it's a shame.
Okay. Thank you.
Is it tasty?
Yes.
What are you looking at?
Oh, nothing.
It's like I saw an acquaintance.
Let's continue.
It's okay.
I'll treat you to this meal.
You come from afar, Oab.
I'll treat you to the next meal.
My pleasure.
Will you leave now? Oab.
Umm...
Yes, I think.
What about you? Tee.
Same for me.
Then...
See you later.
Okay.
Yes.
Oh, Tee.
Are we close now?
Maybe?
I shouldn't...
I shouldn't forget to send the documents...
Tee.
(Why am I...)
(suddenly so shy?)
(Actually,)
(our relationship moved so far,)
(but why am I so shy?)
The weather is good today, don't you think?
I don't know.
I might look for a series to watch.
Keep watching it.
Finally, I have a vacation.
I haven't watched many series.
Are you addicted to the series?
Yeah.
I said I didn't like it,
but I watched it till the end.
Do you get it?
You can see the opposite of feelings
with someone who has just been in love.
Why?
Nothing.
I'm just saying.
But if you say the opposite of feeling for a long time,
it's sad.
Why?
You're probably missing out on a lot of things you want to do.
Hey.
What do you mean?
You want me to invite you to my room?
No.
I really didn't mean that.
Swear with me.
No.
If heaven punishes me,
we won't be able to be together.
You're crazy.
Did you see?
It's thundering.
I'm
leaving now for today.
Yeah.
Nine.
Don't you accompany me into the house?
Okay.
Actually,
I'm willing.
It was true.
(People's life time)
(are getting shorter every day)
(If so,)
(I should choose to live with Nine)
Is the ring beautiful?
Yeah.
Uh...
Why don't you put on your clothes before you leave the bathroom?
Because
my shirt is here.
Oh.
Then
I'll clean it up first.
(It feels like my heart is going to burst)
Didn't you say you going to clean?
I'm pulling myself together.
Hey.
It isn't.
Uh...
After taking a shower and getting dressed,
you
can back home.
You really want me to leave?
We are together like this.
Yeah.
Getting back.