[Too Young To Love]
[Episode 2]
Everyone,
team up in groups of two.
The winners can skip the 800-meter run.
Pick your own partners.
The winners can skip the 800-meter run!
Come on, three groups for the first round.
Let's come up with a chant.
When we move the outside foot,
we shout "one."
When we move the inside foot,
we shout "two."
So it goes: one, two, one, two...
Three, two, one.
Go!
Come on!
Tong Xiaole!
One, two, one, two.
Awesome!
-So amazing!
-Go for it!
Come on, three more groups.
Hurry up.
I can get you out of the 800-meter run.
Ready?
Later you follow my call.
For the outside foot, I'll shout "one."
For the inside foot, I'll shout "two."
Come on. Three, two, one.
Run!
Come on!
One, two, one, two.
One, two.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
Yi Lan.
You're the best!
Give it to her.
Sorry about what happened just now.
Your stuff's blocking my view of my work.
Stand up.
Good morning, sir.
Luo Ningzi...
You're not going to defend her again,
are you?
Her playing skills are just average.
I'd even say they're bad.
Who's bad?
Just because I'm bad now
doesn't mean I'll be bad forever.
Luo Ningzi.
How could you say something so harsh?
We're all classmates.
I'm just telling the truth.
Do I
have to make up nice things
just to make you happy?
Why did you choose
the third movement
of Rachmaninoff's Symphony No. 2
as your life song?
It's in A major.
The melody is beautiful and melancholic.
The harmonies are rich and varied.
And it's one
of the most poignant
and aesthetic chapters in music history.
Is that it?
Leningrad was being bombed
with hundreds of tons
of explosives every day.
To pull people through,
musicians performed this symphony
for the first time right there in the war.
It made everyone believe
that they would win.
That is the power of music.
That's why I tear up whenever I hear it.
It's my life song too.
I thought that having the same life song,
we'd feel the same way about music.
But that doesn't seem to be the case.
Since you don't want to be friends
with me,
I don't want to be friends
with you either.
Faster.
You know what?
Joining the school orchestra
requires applying a month in advance.
Because you suddenly transferred here,
not only did you humiliate Yi Lan
in front of everyone,
but you also made her lose her chance
to audition.
Yet she didn't get angry about it.
Instead, she recognized your ability
and respected you.
But in my opinion,
your attitude right now
doesn't deserve to be respected.
This... I think
she meant to give it to you.
No wonder she doesn't have any friends.
You all look so lifeless.
It's time to switch seats, isn't it?
Groups 1 to 4 switch seats
with Groups 5 to 8.
Luo Ningzi,
you should be
in Group 5.
Five minutes!
Hurry up and switch!
Ning, let me help you.
You leg is injured.
You're in Group Five,
so you'll be Xiaole's deskmate.
Thank you.
Hi, deskmate.
Hi.
Are you free after school?
I want to ask you something.
Okay.
Traitor.
I'll wait for you at the school gate.
Shall we go?
School's over.
Aren't you going with your new friend?
So... you're not coming with us?
What would I do there while you two chat?
Good point.
I'm off then.
Go ahead.
You said it.
Yeah.
I'm leaving then.
Bye.
My new friend!
He's got a new friend now?
Do those two have some kind of secret?
Come with me.
Later, let's go eat malatang together.
My treat.
Can you slow down a bit?
Is your foot okay?
It's fine.
I can't hear them.
When did those two get so close?
They're even going home together now.
Why should I believe
what you just said?
I mean
why I should believe
that I took Yi Lan's spot.
The school orchestra
is basically run by students.
If you don't believe this,
you can go ask anyone.
Why aren't you this impatient
when you talk to them?
The way I talk makes you uncomfortable?
That's good.
At least now
you know how Yi Lan felt.
Childish.
Are you okay?
Yi Lan, Mengmeng,
what are you doing here?
You disappeared right after school.
Mengmeng insisted on coming here
to enjoy the view.
What's there to see?
It's really nice.
What were you and Mengmeng
furtively looking at just now?
We were enjoying the view.
The view?
What's so nice to look at around here?
It's quite nice.
What does it have to do with you?
Are you mad?
Why would I be mad?
I'm not mad.
I'm not mad!
Fine.
If you're not mad,
get on the bike.
Let's go home.
I have legs.
I can walk by myself.
You think those two legs of yours
can run faster than my two wheels?
Hurry up.
Leave me alone.
I can walk by myself.
You still say you're not mad?
You're clearly mad.
I said I'm not mad!
Can you stop making conversation
out of nothing?
Fine.
When did you
get so close to Luo Ningzi?
You know things between her and me
are awkward.
You're betraying me, you know that?
Do you still want to play cello with her?
What does it have to do with you?
Yeah.
It indeed has nothing to do with me.
Walk home by yourself then.
You're actually leaving?
Do you still want to play cello with her?
It's lunch break, right?
Alright, arrange your own time.
Don't erase the blackboard.
We'll continue this afternoon, okay?
Don't run around!
Class dismissed.
Come with me.
I need to talk to you.
Go eat by yourself first.
Qiao Mengmeng.
You lost.
That doesn't count.
Let's do it again.
Zhao Zhenghao, let me ask you something.
Are there auditions
for the school orchestra?
Why did you cancel Yi Lan's audition?
What audition?
Don't tell me
you're actually sympathizing with her.
It's not sympathy.
I want to compete fairly,
even if she still loses.
There's no such thing as fair competition.
I decide who it is!
Since you're the captain,
you should consider
your members' opinions.
Besides,
I was just nervous last time.
If you've got the guts,
let me play again.
Otherwise, I'll leave too.
Then let's just set another time.
Right?
Fine.
Since you want to prove yourself so badly,
I'll give you another chance.
Next Monday,
see you in the music room after school.
Thanks.
After school.
See you in the music room.
Why are you smiling so happily?
I'm happy whenever you're around.
The basketball!
Xiaole!
So you're at home.
Why didn't you answer the phone?
I called you so many times.
I didn't hear it.
Move over a bit.
You haven't eaten yet, have you?
No.
I'll cook for you in a bit.
I need to rest for a while.
Mom, I'm going out.
Why are you so inconsiderate?
It's already this late,
and you're still going out?
Your mom just said she'd cook for you!
Are you mute?
Say something!
Oh.
What kind of attitude is that?
You never answer your mom's calls!
Do you know how worried she was just now?
Alright, alright.
You always make such a mess at home.
Every time your mom has to clean it up
after she gets home!
It's fine, really.
Alright, alright.
Give it a rest.
Give it a rest?
Today, I'm going to let him know
that I am his father!
He can't just do whatever he wants
in this family!
So you do remember you're my father!
All you care about is your lousy money!
Have you ever cared about me?
Have you ever been
to my parent-teacher conferences?
Have you ever cared
about what I do
or what I eat at school?
Look at yourself!
What right do you have to lecture me?
Because I'm your father!
I work my ass off to support this family!
This is how you repay me?
Stop it.
Just get out.
Get out.
Who are you glaring at?
You ungrateful brat!
[Come get some fried chicken, same place]
[Come quickly!]
[Okay]
It's really boring, Yi Lan.
You're so boring.
How come you started eating without me?
It smells so good.
Try one.
Have a bite!
Are you okay?
I'm good.
I'm great.
He picks on me
every time he comes home anyway.
I'm used to it.
It's okay.
Don't be upset.
Your hands are all greasy.
So what?
Just come to me whenever you're unhappy.
Don't keep it to yourself.
I'll stay with you.
Really?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
You're in trouble!
Xiaole, you're back.
Yeah, I'm back.
Mom, I'm going to sleep.
You should rest early too.
Okay.
I'm here!
Didn't you say you were going
to do homework?
Why are you carrying your cello case?
I obviously need to practice hard.
I have to do well
at the school orchestra audition.
Fine.
Aren't you gonna help me carry it?
Just toss it in the basket.
There's some weird noise.
Let me check it for you.
Give it to me.
Make yourself comfortable.
Someone's practicing in there.
She doesn't even need the sheet music.
Pretty talented, huh?
Leave your cello here.
I'll let you know when it's fixed.
Thanks.
No problem.
Take care.
♪ Looking forward
to the next beautiful dream ♪
♪ I just want to be with you ♪
This girl
♪ To see the most romantic starry sky
together ♪
doesn't even like to smile.
♪ The evening breeze tells
heartfelt emotions ♪
♪ All the stars surround you ♪
♪ The moon smiles at you ♪
♪ I give you all the good things
in the world ♪
♪ And the light in your eyes ♪
♪ Shines like diamonds ♪
♪ Drawing an exclamation mark
in my world ♪
♪ The evening breeze embraces you ♪
♪ And I run towards you ♪
♪ I hear our passionate heartbeats ♪
♪ We borrow a dream ♪
♪ To build a castle ♪
♪ Every star is a romantic symbol ♪
Lan, that was beautiful!
♪ Let me find you ♪
Thanks.
Why work so hard?
You'll lose to Luo Ningzi anyway.
Shut your trap.
I was just joking.
Anyway, I just need to show
my true ability.
I don't care about the rest.
That's just beginner level.
With this,
she can get into our school orchestra?
Indeed.
Yi Lan, your level...
What do you say, Luo Ningzi?
Her understanding of music
is more than qualified
for your school orchestra.
What do you mean,
Luo Ningzi?
It's okay.
I know everyone's really good.
I don't care
if I can make it
into the school orchestra anymore.
Zhao Zhenghao, you're such a jerk!
Let's go.
Zhao Zhenghao.
The school orchestra
doesn't belong to you alone.
If the school orchestra
is full of people like you
who don't respect music
and are arrogant,
then I don't see
any point in this orchestra existing.
I... I didn't mean it.
Everyone, just keep practicing.
Sorry.
Mengmeng,
isn't this a bit too much?
You even got me a wheelchair.
Absolutely.
I'm terrified you'll get hurt again.
But Lan,
why didn't you join the school orchestra
in the end?
Luo Ningzi is indeed excellent.
But at least I've proved to her
that I'm not that bad. And that's enough.
Fine.
Anyway, you're the best in my heart.
You are so sweet, Mengmeng.
Of course, Lan.
Why does it take so long
for Chen Fan and Xiaole to buy skewers?
What exactly do you want?
Why are you always against me?
Don't tell me you want
to be the captain of the school orchestra.
I knew that was your plan.
You wanted to humiliate me
in front of everyone.
Are you questioning me?
Let me tell you this.
Without me, the school orchestra
wouldn't be what it is today.
I worked my ass off
to get every single instrument
in this orchestra.
To me, the orchestra
is my territory
and my king!
My kingdom!
How can you be so disrespectful?
Luo Ningzi?
Let's go.
Let's go have a look.
I am talking to you!
Stop it, Zhao Zhenghao!
Mengmeng.
You called for backup?
Zhao Zhenghao, I'm warning you.
Don't think just because we're off campus,
you can do whatever you want.
Exactly!
I never laid my hands on girls.
But you've gone too far.
You're practically forcing my hand.
What are you doing?
This...
Is anyone there?
Help!
-Help!
-Let go of her!
What kind of man
picks on three girls?
What does this have to do with you?
Mind your own business.
Of course it has to do with me.
They're all under my protection.
When you mess with them, you mess with me.
Fine.
Then let's fight like real men.
For real?
Come on.
He's so weak.
Captain Zhao!
Zhenghao!
Help me up.
Run!
Hurry!
Guys, what took you so long?
Where are they?
They called for backup too?
Zhenghao, they ran away.
Should we chase them?
Of course!
After them!
Quick!
Director Hu,
it's them!
they're bullying us.
Are you okay?
It's him!
You little brats,
stop right there!
You punks!
Which class are you from?
Don't let me catch you!
Stop right there!
Zhao Zhenghao!
Tong Xiaole, Chen Fan!
Come over here.
And you guys too?
Mengmeng,
you're such a traitor.
You ran off by yourself.
I just went to get help.
Look at you two.
Did you really become besties?
Luo Ningzi.
Although you don't like making friends,
you're still a good friend.
Can I invite you
to practice cello with me after school?
After school, I usually
practice in the school music room
for two hours.
Oh.
But the school doesn't say
only orchestra members can use it.
Then let's practice together from now on.
Together!
Let's go.
Director,
it was him.
He led
them...
these guys...
They cornered us after school.
And my leg
got injured
because of him.
It had nothing to do with those two?
Nothing!
Nothing at all.
Alright.
I've got the whole picture.
Tong Xiaole, Chen Fan,
you two are innocent.
You can go.
Thank you, Director.
Director, then we...
You can go.
Stand still!
You guys like causing trouble, huh?
Fine.
As your punishment,
you'll clean the toilets
for a week!
Try playing it first.
Let me take a listen.
Stop.
Count the beat in your head.
You have to keep up.
Da, da, da, da.
Keep the tempo steady.
Five, six, seven, go!
Da, da, da, da.
Stop.
You're falling behind the tempo a bit.
You might need to practice more at home.
Separate your second and third fingers
a bit more.
Curve your fingers.
Stop.
You still need more practice at home.
What?
Give me one.
This is not for you.
You have so many,
but I can't even have one?
Haven't you eaten enough?
Get lost.
Then it must be for me.
It's not for you either.
Then who is it for?
It's for Ning.
Ning?
You call her Ning?
This morning you called me Qiao Mengmeng!
Mengmeng.
She's your new friend?
She is my new friend,
but you are my best friend.
It's different.
Then where does a best friend
rank?
Ranked first.
First.
Only one.
Ning.
This nougat is really good.
It's for you.
Thanks.
This is
for you.
It's also a collector's edition.
[Rachmaninoff's Symphony No. 2]