(Names, businesses, products,
events and places are used fictitiously.)
(Episode 15: Period)
What should I do, Father?
Even now,
I still think about
what money is
several times a day.
And
I think that the person
who loves me the most
is the one who spends
the most money on me.
Like an old habit, I can't stop.
But sometimes,
- (Juhyeop Bank Deposit - 300,000 won)
- occasionally,
I sink deep
into the thought of what love is,
which is something
- I've never thought of before.
- (Jeong-woo, Min-su, Hee-sun)
- (Transferred-to Name: Lee Gang-jae)
- Not being at the receiving end of love,
but being the one to give love,
and creating space for
that person inside me.
The space grows.
How regrettable.
Then in the end,
I am filled with only that person.
I think about this kind
of listless pain.
Though I try hard to be alone,
I can't be alone.
I think about this kind
of sweet apprehension.
What can I do for that person?
What can I be for that person?
Maybe not being anything,
or trying hard to be something,
but rather being honest to myself
is the kind of love
that I can give.
We meet again.
In Seoul.
I'll buy this time, too. Let's go!
What?
Come on. Let's go.
I missed you, Ms. Lee Bu-jeong.
This reminds me of our past.
This is the first time
we're coming here.
How can this remind you of our past?
I leaned on you a lot like this.
At coffee shops,
on buses, and even subways.
I wanted it to last longer,
so a lot of the times,
I pretended to sleep.
Did you know?
I knew.
I think I wanted to torment you.
I wanted you to be upset because of me.
I know.
I don't know the psychology
behind that though.
Did you know that, too?
I knew.
What would people say about us?
That we're perverted?
Who cares?
As long as you're comfortable.
I feel like I'm going to cry.
I don't know what I'm feeling.
But
I think today will be
the first and last time.
Get some sleep.
I said let's just go home.
We came out to go to the karaoke room.
We can't just go back in.
Then let's go to the karaoke room.
You said you won't be able to sing
because your heart is racing.
What could be between those two?
It wasn't three or four people.
Just the two of them
going to a karaoke...
What do you think it is?
What about you?
An affair.
They could be just friends.
We also went to a karaoke room.
But they went toward a motel.
What?
Do you
still think that when you see...
That?
What are you talking about?
You know.
Go inside.
Hmph.
Were you drinking?
No.
You were.
I told you to leave it, but you took it.
I wouldn't have drunk a lot by myself.
Are you drinking with Gang-jae?
Oh, Gang-jae?
He left the moment he came inside.
Now he's not answering his phone.
Oh.
But eventually, he comes back.
Like a real estate agency dog.
A real estate agency dog?
That's what my grandma
used to say to me.
Because I'd leave,
go around the neighborhood
then come back when she starts worrying.
Oh!
You lived with your grandmother?
I guess Gang-jae never talked about me.
You know nothing.
My mom and dad were both busy,
so I lived with my grandma.
When I became a trainee,
I lived at the dorm.
9 years ago,
I almost debuted.
Several times after that, too.
But that time, it was for real.
Anyway,
things were hectic. They divorced,
each got remarried,
and then immigrated.
My dad took only my brother.
Hello? Are you listening?
Yes, I'm listening.
I have a web-drama audition on Monday.
Huh? A web-drama?
Yes.
The role is the girlfriend
of an agency's CEO.
Isn't it perfect?
Idol singers are
a good drama subject nowadays.
Since it's a national project.
Idol singers are a national project?
Oh, I'm not saying it as a fact.
I'm just saying it's that hot.
Anyway.
Can you pick what I should wear with me?
Tell me what's the cutest.
Me?
Hang up for a sec.
Wait here.
Is there an empty table for two?
- I'll have to clear that up.
- Okay.
I think they're full.
Let's go.
That place might seem hectic
but it's really good.
It was even more hectic today.
Do you know a place?
A place you went to often
when you worked at your office.
Or a place you want to try.
I don't know.
What do you like?
Oh, you said you don't like anything.
I like everything.
I like it all.
(Missed calls) (Mom)
Is it home?
You're awake?
Yeah.
Is it home?
It's Mom.
You're still a good son.
No, I'm not.
She still calls me bastard.
I love you, Jeong-su.
What?
Why, all of a sudden?
I deeply regretted not saying it
in the past.
I should've said it,
even if it were as a joke.
The day before my husband died,
I asked him.
I said there's a man
I've liked since I was young.
I asked if I could see him.
He started crying.
That means no, right?
(Mom)
Is it home?
It's Mom.
Why don't you answer it?
It may be urgent.
It's nothing.
She's just calling.
I don't know how others do it.
Do what?
Have an affair.
Many married people
meet other married people.
My heart sinks every time
you look at your phone.
How do other people have an affair?
I liked you the most, Jeong-su.
I still do.
Don't you have anything to say?
This might be the last.
Or not.
I still
use the same PIN number
for my bank account.
It's your birthday.
Since college,
I've never changed it.
Maybe you were too lazy to change it.
There's that, too.
You're needlessly honest.
Let's go.
Okay.
Where is everyone?
It's almost 11 o'clock.
My goodness.
What is she doing all day?
She got fired.
What does she go around doing?
Jeez.
Even if I try to be nice,
she's hard to like.
Her husband works hard even on weekends.
If she stays at home,
she should make pickled vegetables
and keep the place tidy.
Bu-jeong.
I'm going in here.
Yeah, I bet you're frustrated, too.
I wish I could understand you.
The fridge is too big.
I guess this is better than crying and
locking herself in her room,
not letting Jeong-su go out either.
Yeah, going out is better.
I wish I could understand you.
Should I give Chang-suk his right now?
It's too late, right?
(790425)
(Front door passcode)
(Ballroom Dancing Lessons
for Senior Citizens)
Bu-jeong.
I'm fine.
I'm okay.
Huh?
Do you want a drink?
Let's drink.
If I pour like this,
we'll drink it all with
two glasses each.
We have a long way to go.
I think this is the first time
I'm pouring drinks
off the clock.
It's true.
Okay.
It's an honor.
I'm telling the truth.
But
why did you tell me to meet you there?
It's near your father's place.
No reason.
That motel came to mind.
I remembered getting off the bus there.
I hesitated for a long time,
unable to cross
the crosswalk.
Why?
I don't know.
You must've been really hungry.
I didn't eat all day.
Why?
Well...
I was busy.
Doing what?
Oh, well, you know,
I want to imagine it
so I should know the details.
I think you wore those clothes.
Your shoes...
are heels.
What did you do?
On what I'm wearing now, I wore an apron
and peeled fruits.
I also put away dishes.
At the hospital.
Oh, the hospital.
Normally,
I'd go to my employer's house and clean
and cook, but she was hospitalized
so I had to go there to work.
I have to go a few more days.
You're thinking why
I'm dressed like this, right?
It looks uncomfortable
to work in, right?
Well, no, not in particular, but...
Is there a special reason?
I didn't tell anyone.
Not my dad
or my husband.
I dress and speak the same
just as when I went
to work at the office.
But I think they all know.
Before, they'd ask me
about my work and book.
But now,
no one talks about it.
It must be a coincidence.
Recently, he went to
my former workplace.
Who?
My husband.
You talked about
the pumpkin carriage, right?
About coming to reality
from an illusion.
Yes.
Actually, until recently,
for about a year,
I've been thinking that.
It's similar but a totally
different story.
What was before me
was the illusion.
In life, there are times
the word "reality" is
the worst word ever.
Sir!
Life before that moment was nothing.
It was a moment my effort
and sincerity vanished.
Thinking my life was okay,
that I was living better than most...
All of that was an illusion.
I realized that
in that moment.
What the hell are you doing?
What the hell?
Did you tell the baby's mama
to sue him? Huh?
No matter how hard
I tried to think good things,
to have hope in small things,
I couldn't see anything before me.
I was so distressed.
I wanted to be free from this nightmare.
(Lethargy / Relationships / Depression
/ Aftereffects of an accident)
But I couldn't wake up.
- I couldn't go back.
- (Hello, ma'am. How was your day today?)
I realized then.
Your comments are very well written.
That the past was a dream
and the present was my reality.
Life without an illusion
isn't life but rather
closer to death.
You included these in the bill, too?
Okay.
Where should we go?
I know.
How about life with an illusion?
Don't tease me.
I'm not.
I knew you'd tease me.
Where are you going?
Nowhere.
Oh, ma'am.
You're here early.
You said you were
stopping by your house.
I was just arranging things.
Is it raining outside?
It just started pouring.
You should've called me.
I was going home, but came here.
Because Mr. Seo is there.
Seriously.
I should change this habit.
That bastard doesn't deserve a title.
Anyway, that bastard's
at home waiting for me.
So I came straight here.
I see.
Do you have a pill for headaches?
Yes.
Do you always prepare like this?
What?
When I call, do you drop everything
and come here to set things up?
Oh, well.
I don't do much.
Since you're filming.
Did you see this
at my dressing room and copied it?
For my throat?
Yes.
I should've set it up sooner.
I wasn't thinking.
It must've been dry
and stuffy until now.
If you quit here and get married,
what will I do?
How can I get married?
Why can't you?
Bastards like Seo Jin-seop did.
Oh.
The photos of Writer Lee
that you gave me.
I sent them to her.
Did your conversation not go well?
It wasn't a matter of going well or not.
It's all over.
But
Her "holier than thou" act
struck a nerve,
so I sent them.
She should see the reality
and wake up.
She told me she prays every day
for me to die.
What are you thinking about?
Oh, no,
I'm not thinking about anything.
Remember
when I suggested we die together?
Yes, I do.
Do you remember you said no?
Yes.
You said your goal was
to live a long and mediocre life.
Is that still your goal?
Yes.
I see.
I'm kind of disappointed.
If you said you'd die with me,
it would've been great.
You should...
live with me.
Live a long and mediocre life.
Oh, my!
Why is it raining all of a sudden?
It's raining?
Yes.
First it was a drop,
and then it's suddenly pouring.
You should've bought
an umbrella on the way back.
Hey.
I could buy more soju with that money.
Look at you.
Jeez. You'll catch a cold.
Where are the towels?
There aren't any here.
No?
Hey.
Why are you over-reacting
all of a sudden?
You didn't bat an eye even when
I got hit by hail.
When did we have hail?
I'm just saying.
What?
Huh? What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Huh?
Since I'm soaking wet,
do I look sexy and all?
No?
Oh, no, that's not it. I was thinking...
Yeah?
...that's how I treated you, huh?
I never got you an umbrella
when it was raining.
When we've been
living together for 6 months.
What?
It didn't rain that much
during that time.
And I have a lot of umbrellas.
Some, you can fold. Others, you can't.
What? Did you do all that for Ji-yeon?
The glasses are inside?
I'll go get them.
You did, huh?
And you still got dumped like a fool?
That's not all there is in a marriage.
Hmph. Then what is marriage?
What is it?
Living with one person continuously.
But...
Some people find that stifling.
But isn't that why you get married?
Because you want to
be with them forever?
Right.
But...
Having been married,
I realized I didn't truly know.
What it meant to live with one person
for the rest of your life.
That's it?
That's it.
Goodness!
What brings you here at this hour?
You have an umbrella, right?
Can I borrow one?
Get an umbrella from under there.
And a pill to calm down.
That's why I'm here.
- A pill to calm down?
- Yes.
- Hold on.
- This is bad.
What should I do?
This is bad.
Can you
take me somewhere
in your car?
- Huh?
- Car?
My daughter-in-law won't pick up.
My bastard son must've
turned off his phone.
The dial signal goes, then stops.
Oh, okay.
- Hey, go home and get your car.
- Okay.
Ma'am!
- Ma'am.
- Yes?
- Sit here.
- Okay.
Calm down and tell me.
What's going on?
Oh, well.
Someone called me
at home on the landline.
- Landline?
- Yes, the landline.
I went home after going
to my son's place.
When I got in,
the phone rang in a million years.
Yikes!
Oh, my.
Who is it?
- My son.
- Your son?
He must be home.
I don't think so.
Is that you, Jeong-su?
Yes, Mom. What is it?
Why didn't you pick up?
Huh?
I called you so many times.
Someone called me
at home on the landline.
(Lottery Store)
Sir?
Sir, you can't go out!
Grab him.
Sir, please sit down.
It's okay. Sit down here.
Who is he? Why's he here?
He came in drenched,
asking about a payphone.
So I let him use my cell.
I think his mind has started to go.
Gosh...
After graduate school,
I finally landed a job.
But I was sick the whole
3 years I worked there.
In the end,
I called my dad to tell him I quit.
He didn't say anything for a long time.
Then, nonchalantly,
he said, "It's okay, Bu-jeong."
I thought he'd worry less
if I bought a place in Seoul.
So I pushed myself hard
and bought the studio.
For over an hour, he thoroughly
observed that small place,
then once again, nonchalantly,
he said,
"It's pretty."
It's pretty...
To my dad,
"okay" means he's worried
and "pretty" means he's concerned.
Father?
Father!
Why are you so wet?
Father.
How did you get here?
He told me
he walked.
Father...
Why buy me these?
I have nowhere to wear them.
Father, wear them
when something good happens.
Father.
Let's go home, huh?
Bu-jeong is waiting.
- Bu-jeong?
- Yes, let's go home.
Okay.
I'll help you up.
The towel...
Just take it.
Thank you.
I'll come back later
and thank you properly.
Thank you.
- Your father is leaving.
- Thank you!
Father!
Father, let's take a cab.
It won't cost that much.
We can't walk home.
You walked more than 10km.
Oh, right!
Jeong-su.
So...
Yes, that's right. I'm Jeong-su.
Jeong-su. Jeong-su.
Yes, I'm Jeong-su, Father.
I'm Jeong-su.
Jeong-su.
If you see my text, call me.
It's urgent.
My dad?
He has everything in his heart.
Law, philosophy, literature...
They're all in his heart.
No one taught him. He didn't learn them.
But they accumulated over time.
My dad is a one and only book of poems.
Father!
Father, wake up!
To Dad,
in his heart,
there are a lot more thoughts
than spoken words.
Excuse me, can you call an ambulance?
Father, wake up!
He mulls over numerous thoughts.
Father!
Sir, are you okay? Do something!
- Then chooses a few and voices them out.
- Father! Father!
I think he's unconscious.
Wait here for a sec.
I'll go get an umbrella.
Let's go home.
Take the call!
Where are you?
I called you so many times.
Oh.
Things were hectic
so I couldn't pick up.
What is it?
It's 5,000 won.
- You're all set.
- Thanks.
(Ms. Lee Bu-jeong)
(Something urgent came up
so I had to leave.)
Excuse me.
May I?
I'm sorry.
(Emergency Room)
Oh, no!
Mom.
How... how is he doing? Huh?
What do you mean?
He's doing well.
How's the situation inside?
He doesn't have a bed yet,
but he'll get one soon.
Oh, right.
The landlady said
he called the landline.
Yeah.
He remembered
only that phone number.
But he never actually called it before.
So if he had forgotten
that number as well,
they would never have found him.
Jeez.
It's sad
that he only remembers that number.
Why?
It means whenever
he missed his daughter,
he kept pressing that number.
But since it's his in-law's house,
he couldn't call.
I miss my mom.
Me, too.
Hey.
Why are you outside?
Oh, he's stable now.
I took turns with Mom.
What were you doing?
You couldn't even pick up?
You should've answered your phone!
Well...
The conversation got longer.
Did you have a drink?
What about Dad?
He was in a bad state at first.
He's conscious now, but...
He has acute pneumonia.
It could lead to sepsis.
You're his daughter.
What were you doing when
your father was in that state?
You don't even answer your phone!
Stop that, Mom.
She's the one that's most upset.
How's Father?
He wakes up for a minute,
worries about the bill,
and goes back to sleep.
Give me the pass.
I'm so upset.
Go inside.
Your father knows everything.
What's wrong with you?
I said your father knows everything!
Stop saying that.
Seriously.
Go inside.
Don't mind her.
Dad...
I'm here.
Bu-jeong is here, Dad.
Can you see me?
Yes.
Who am I?
Bu-jeong, of course.
That's right. I'm Bu-jeong.
Did you go somewhere?
Yes. I went somewhere.
I'm sorry, Dad.
You got rained on?
Yes.
Don't go around like that.
It's no picnic if you catch a cold.
Okay.
I...
I think I'm okay now.
Can I go home?
I'm so sleepy.
I fell asleep in front of
your mother-in-law.
His immunity has grown weak.
But his fever has gone down.
So we'll watch him for a bit more.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
Father won't be able
to leave his daughter.
His fever has gone down.
So let's wait and see.
Stop crying.
You'll wear yourself out.
Father will get back up.
Change your clothes before you sleep.
You'll catch a cold.
Even if you're young.
Okay.
Is this really for me?
Yes.
What's with the beer
instead of the usual milk?
No reason.
Mom.
What?
Have you ever
woken up from a dream?
Well, I...
I don't dream that much.
Not that kind of dream.
Someone told me
that living without a dream
is not living at all.
The wording wasn't like this.
But I changed it
so you could understand.
Hmph.
What was the original wording?
Originally, it was
"Life without an illusion
is closer to death."
You don't know what that means, huh?
I don't.
But I know what the illusion is.
What is it?
You.
Yuck. I should burn my ears.
I have to burn my ears.
Jeez.
You sounded like
an old man with that saying.
Where do you think? From you.
Mom.
What?
You don't have to send me money anymore.
Why not?
No reason. I just say so.
Okay.
Thanks.
You could at least pretend to refuse.
Why would I do that?
It's a gift from my son.
Jeez.
Good for you.
Don't expect to get
an allowance from me.
I don't. Just take care of yourself.
I am.
I can still come and
sleep over sometimes, right?
Of course.
You can come every day.
Why would I come every day?
(Ms. Lee Bu-jeong)
(Okay. Be safe. Call me later.)
Gang Min-jeong!
Yes!
Whoa, you're like
Frankenstein or something.
You're like a nightmare.
Potatoes again?
You can't cook them that well,
but you keep making this.
Don't eat it then.
Soon-gyu,
today is an important day for me.
So say only good things to me.
Why is it an important day?
I have my reasons.
Why's he in a good mood
these days? Creepy.
Hi.
Potatoes again?
Yeah! Potatoes again!
Potatoes again! So what?
Whoa, why are you getting mad?
I was just asking.
You ungrateful bastards.
Don't eat it!
I'll feed you.
Why are you refusing my help?
There's no need.
I have to move to get well.
Dad.
What?
Dad...
There you go again.
I'm not going anywhere. I'm here.
You only have me.
But I'm so lacking,
not giving you a grandkid
when you love babies.
Stop your nonsense.
I don't like babies.
Liar.
Have you ever
seen me hold a child?
You don't because
you're being extra careful.
You'd have loved your grandkid so much.
Were you upset because of that?
Of course I was.
Since you were upset.
I'm not just saying this.
but when I see babies on the street,
I don't feel the need for a grandkid.
I'm reminded of you.
How pretty you were.
Me?
Yes.
When you were young,
I left you by yourself so much
that whenever you saw me,
you wanted a piggyback ride.
I also went everywhere to find someone
to look after you.
Leave it up. Why shut it?
But you're going to sleep.
Pull it up. It's stuffy.
I'm going home for a bit.
Do you need anything?
No.
Oh!
You know the blue kimchi
container in the fridge?
I put my bankbook and
some money in there.
The PIN number is your birthday.
I'm paying with a credit card.
I don't need that.
Just know they're there.
Let me know again when we go home.
Okay.
- I won't be long.
- Okay.
What?
You're pretty.
Pretty.
I'll be right back.
- Bye!
- Bye.
I don't remember why,
but I didn't have a job for some time,
so there was no money.
I carried you on my back, trying to find
someone who'll care for you for a while.
What? But I'm your daughter.
Well, that happened.
Times were tough.
I even thought of leaving you
with someone and killing myself.
But then,
you woke up at the smell of bread.
I thought, 'Oh, no.
I should put you to sleep fast.'
But
you stroke my ear
like this and said,
"Dad...
When you earn a lot of money,
you'll buy me that, right?"
You were only three.
But you knew I was bad-off
and didn't whine.
Even though
you wanted to eat it
because it smelled so good.
I couldn't kill myself
and leave you alone.
You're precious to me.
Dad, when you earn a lot of money,
you'll buy me that, right?
(Lost)
Did... something happen
to the man living here?
I thought you were a scammer,
but you're a thief.
Even if you grill me, you should know
it's over between you two.
She has the photos.
You and Gang-jae are two of a kind.
Want to know a secret?
I...
I think I like someone.
What should we do?
Did you tell him?
I'm sorry, but can we turn back?
Even if you wait,
she won't call, Gang-jae.
She's married.
Subtitles from: iQIYI
Edited by: ayamefan13