(Previously)
Maey!
Last night
I saw creeping in the big house.
What are you doing?
This is downstairs!
Someone might see us.
No one will see us.
Ahem.
Are you trying to tell me something?
After this, if you must be strict,
then do so.
Because otherwise,
it's the people under your control
that will ruin the honor you've earned.
Can I ask something from you?
What is it?
Could you be my dance partner?
It's raining like this.
How is the party going?
Forget it, Jom.
Now there's only two of us in this house.
Ugh!
You're soaking wet, Khun Yai.
Why don't you let me undress you?
So you won't catch a cold.
There you go.
Let me do the same for you,
or you'll have a fever.
I love you, Jom.
I love you too, Khun Yai.
(I Feel You Linger in the Air)
(Episode 8)
Are you awake, Khun Yai?
So I'll put away your stuff there.
Jom, the sun hasn't yet risen.
Why don't you stay here a little longer?
Jom?
Do you see something?
No, I don't, Khun Yai.
It's nothing.
No matter what,
I will always be with you right here.
Khun Eeang Peung.
Maey.
I had a nightmare.
Oh! It will be all right.
It's all right.
It's nothing.
It was such a bad dream.
What was it like?
Please make yourself at home.
These vegetables and fruit,
you cut them all yourself?
No, I didn't.
These cut vegetables and fruit,
my daughter Eeang Peung did it all.
How exquisite!
Ah, eat up.
How do you find Robert
after having conversed with him?
He's like what you've said.
Hmh... He looks quite accomplished.
He is humble
and strong at the same time.
Yeah, right.
He has climbed up to become
a forest owner at such an age.
Not to mention his power
in business negotiation.
He's quite ambitious, isn't he?
By the way,
Robert, as a middleman,
could be of help to you,
who have just moved here,
in strengthening your power in
official and commercial affairs.
I think...
Mother, I overheard Father
and Uncle Dech talking.
It seems like they want me
to tie the knot with Robert.
We don't even know each other so well.
And they are talking about our relationship
and our marriage.
How would that be possible?
I know how you feel, daughter.
But it might not turn
out as badly as you think.
Take your father and me.
Our marriage was also arranged,
but, in the end, I just love him.
But the idea of marraige
is not yet my concern.
Also the idea of moving
out and being a wife.
You know that I want to further my studies.
I want to work in the
government services like Father.
But isn't it too unrealistic?
Women like us have been expected to
take care of households.
There's no room for us there.
So how would my life be afterwards, Mother?
What if the marriage came true?
Why don't you consider it
to be for your honor and your family?
Whenever you could no
longer endure your marriage life,
you would always have
some paths to choose from.
Mark my words, Eeang Peung.
Are you afraid of me, Eeang Peung?
No, I'm not.
I... I'm just...
Don't be afraid.
If you still distrust me,
it's fine.
I will never to anything to you
until you consent to it.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
Are you awake?
I really can't get rid of
this thought from my head.
It's all right.
Now you have me.
I will never let you
suffer all alone,
at least in this house.
I will cure your sufferings,
easing them off.
I love you so much, Maey.
I live you too, Khun Eeang Peung.
What the hell are you doing?!
Hey! Maey!
Maey!
You, get this harlot out from this house!
Now!
Yes! Ouch!
Maey!
Stop! Stop!
Khun Eeang Peung, please!
Maey!
Jom, come here.
What are you doing, Khun Yai?
Come on.
Trust me.
Wow! Did you prepare all these on your own?
Yes.
I noticed you were nervous about something,
something I can't percieve.
But what I could and should do
as your lover
is... to make you feel more relaxed.
Come on!
Are you sure this is for me,
not yourself?
For us, honestly.
Get rid of negative
thoughts from your mind.
Just at this time.
Your skin...
it's very smooth.
Thanks to your olive oil.
I knew it.
Khun Yai,
what makes you like plumeria?
Well, why are you asking this?
They're quite an unpopular
flower, aren't they?
Because the Thai name means misery,
which sounds quite inauspicious.
So try smelling it.
Its gentle scent makes me feel liberated,
and it's also enchanting.
I think, it smells like you, Jom.
♪ When our eyes meet, it's
like I've known you forever ♪
♪ Been waiting for us to be together ♪
♪ Dear, my dearest, I've
been defeated completely ♪
♪ Even in the afterlife,
I'll be loving you solely ♪
♪ When our eyes meet ♪
♪ It's like I've loved you forever ♪
♪ Been waiting for us to be together ♪
♪ Dear, my dearest, I've
been defeated completely ♪
♪ Even in the afterlife,
I'll be loving you solely ♪
May all curses disappear.
May all your ailments be cured.
May all dangers never befall you.
May you be full of happiness
and have a long live.
The Four Blessings:
Age, Skin, Happiness, and Health.
May they all befall
those who habitually pray
and obey the elderly.
I'll put them all away.
Thank you, Prik.
Thank you, Auntie Prik.
What's going on, provost?
Nothing.
I just don't think I've seen
this young man before.
This is Jom. He's just
lived here for a while.
You might not have ever seen him.
And I hadn't got up early enough to
offer food to monks for quite a long time.
You were not born and
bred around here, right?
Let's go.
Jom.
Eh?
What's going on?
Nothing.
Well, why did you, out of the blue,
take me to offer food to the monk with you?
I wanted us to make merit together,
so it might elevate our relationship
to the end of our lives.
Moreover, I don't know if you feel it.
But I feel such intimacy with you
as if we had met each other
and been together before.
Eh? Do you believe in
reincarnation, Khun Yai?
I had doubted it, actually,
until I met you, Jom.
But this hasn't made me
completely believe such a thing.
Because I don't even know how I can tackle
what's going these days.
Yeah.
Let's go home.
Have you got something, Chan?
I have got a little bit, sir.
This morning I saw Khun Yai and Jom
offering food to a monk together.
Khun Yai also held Jom's hand.
They were talking in
quite an intimate fashion.
They looked so close to each other, sir.
And...
Stop! I don't want to hear it any longer.
Keep watching over them.
If they ever cross the line,
inform me as soon as possible.
Yes, sir.
I think, if Khun Yai finds it out,
he won't be happy about it for sure.
So don't let it happen.
I'm putting a lot of trust in you, Chan.
Do you remember
how I have supported your family?
Don't let me down.
Yes, sir.
Eat.
No!
I will never eat anything
as long as I and Maey
are still under punishment
when we did nothing wrong!
So I will never eat!
How dare you talk to me
like this, Eeang Peung?
You said you did nothing wrong
when you and Maey were having an affair!
I and Maey, we just love each other!
We have loved each
other even before I met you.
So why are we wrong,
when, between us, it's been pure love?
Because now I'm your husband!
Why are you so heartless
to me, Eeang Peung?
I have loved you even since I saw you.
I have honored you even
since you became my life.
But you repay me with your cold heart.
You even suggested I have a second wife.
So you could stray with Maey, right?!
Yes!
I'm such an unfaithful
wife, according to you!
But has anybody asked me
what I want or don't want to do?
It's not me who has betrayed you,
but it's your own thoughts
that have made you think that
I can be someone you want me to!
Eeang Peung!
Come on!
Do it!
Just do it!
If you want to hit me
just like a slave, just do it!
As a woman, I've got no choice, haven't I?
However, it can never change the truth
that I never loved you.
When my love and respect for you
doesn't make you love me at all,
then I won't give them to you any more.
What are you doing, Robert?!
Let go of me!
What are you doing?!
No! Ouch! Help! Ouch!
Help!
No!
Let go of me!
Help!
Auntie, how is Khun Eeang Peung?
How is she doing?
How dare you ask about her at this time?
Why are you looking
at me like this, Auntie?
So what do I do?
Do you realize what you have done, Maey?!
Don't you ever learn to be humble
and know your own place?!
I love and care for you
just like my actual niece.
I have cursed Fong Kaew every single day
without evening realizing
that you would do such a lewd thing
to your own master!
But Khun Eeang Peung and I,
We have loved each other for so long.
We have done nothing wrong!
So you don't know that she's married?!
You don't know that her
husband is your master,
who has given you shelter and food?!
Maey, you could have
done it with anybody else,
not with Khun Eeang Peung!
Auntie!
Argh! Just eat!
And think of what you have done.
If you still have no brains,
then this is where you belong!
Auntie...
Eeang Peung,
I...
What are you doing, Fong Kaew?
I asked, why are you
still here at this time?
Sir,
I just came here to
clean the stuff as usual.
Aren't you already familiar?
How hardworking you are!
How strange! You have cleaned the room,
but why is there still
dust on my bookshelf?
Well, I mightn't have
cleaned it well enough.
So, thank you for your help.
But you don't have to do it any longer.
I will have someone else
clean this room instead,
so you don't have to be bothered.
Yes, sir.
So, please excuse me.
Fong Kaew.
Yes, sir.
Bring me some desserts in this room.
I think, from now on,
I will be working in this
room again for a while.
It seems like I have to take charge
of everyone's conduct here.
Yes, sir.
The lettuces are selling out.
Today we've got a good sale, mom?
Two items, and the cabbage, right?
Yes.
No change! Thank you!
Khamsaen, you've turned
over a new leaf, haven't you?
So take care of the stall.
- Yes.
- I'm going home.
You're selling them good today, right?
I'm leaving.
Yes.
Khamsaen.
Well, I...
I don' think we should be talking here.
I'm afraid that any of your servants
or acquaintances will see us again.
Go and wait for me at
the corner over there.
Be careful.
Go, and when my mom comes back here,
I will come for you as soon as possible.
Fong Kaew!
Auntie...
What are you doing here?
Well, I'm... I'm here to meet Khamsaen.
Why do you want to meet my son again?
He has become a better
person and moved on from you!
Better...?
Don't you know that he was such a drunkard,
losing his very sense,
just because you had dumped him!
So how dare you show up here again?!
But... I needed to do it.
I know you might have seen
me as an indecent woman,
but you know what I have
been through, don't you?
I know. I understand you, Fong Kaew.
And I know how your mom never learns
to keep her feet on the ground.
She still looks down on my family
as she has always done,
even now that she's
reached the nadir of her life.
I beg you, Fong Kaew.
Please let Khamsaen go.
Think that you are no longer meant for him.
Please... I want my son back.
- Mom.
- Hey, Khamsaen.
Help me sort the
vegetables out on the stall.
Ok, mom. Excuse me for a while.
Khamsaen!
Son! Khamsaen!
Fong Kaew!
Ah! Here you come!
What is so urgent that made you
invite me to your house like this?
Do you remember your
concern for me at the party
on the promotion day?
Yes, I do.
Well, is something else going on?
Not at this time.
But I think I've seen it coming
in the way you have foretold.
Hmh...
If you want to nip it in the bud,
you might have to do the same
as you did to your daughter Eeang Peung.
So who would be the right woman?
My daughter, Busabong.
They have known each other for a long time.
You wouldn't mind.
If we were to join our family trees, right?
Because I think that.
Yai has met her often since he was young.
I think this will be a good solution
for our families.
It sounds nice.
I finally want to settle
this once and for all.
Where are you taking me, Khun Yai?
Just follow my lead.
Stay here.
Yes.
I'll open the blindfold.
This is what I want you to see,
my favorite spot ever
since I moved to Chiang Mai.
Khun Yai, it's very beautiful!
I have watched fireflies
with my friends quite a few times,
but this is the very first time...
when I see so many fireflies like this.
So you remember another
thing about your past, don't you?
Ugh! Well... It's getting more and more.
There's a flash of a vision in my head
when I see a familiar scenario.
I'm so glad
to be here with you Jom
at such a special night.
Me too.
♪ Because my love is
endless, it goes on perpetually ♪
♪ Nothing can erase these
traces of love from me ♪
♪ Unlike a flower's scent
that can't be scented forever ♪
♪ Because my heart beats
persistently, only for you, tirelessly ♪
♪ This scent of love will
follow you indefinitely ♪
♪ This heart will search
for you, for always ♪
Jom.
Yes.
What's going on?
Well, I...
I think I see...
Ugh! Ugh!
It's raining, Jom.
Let's go home.
Well, yes.
Eh? It's stopped raining.
What are you laughing, Jom?
I think it's quite funny.
Last time we were running
for shelter from the rain,
just like this time.
Right. I already planned to make this night
our special night.
But it's raining again!
Huh?
What are you doing?!
You just said that
it's raining like before,
so now it's supposed to end with...
Stop, please.
Come on, Jom!
I was kidding. Please don't mind it.
Whenever I see you like this,
I really adore you.
Well, Khun Yai.
Do you feel like I feel?
These times,
it seems like someone is always spying us.
No, I don't.
Do you?
Yes.
Hmh... But when you don't feel it,
then it might be all in my head.
Huh?
What's this, Jom?
Can I ride on your back?
Ride on my back?
Yes.
My back?
Can't I?
Yes, you can.
1... 2... 3!
Ugh! Ugh!
Ouch! Oh!
How do you feel, Khun Yai?
So now you know how I feel, right?
Everytime you plead me to do stuff,
it's a real burden.
Are you getting revenge on me?
- Huh?
- Ouch!
Hey!
No, Khun Yai!
No!
Khun Yai!
Hey! Khun Yai! I'm gonna fall!
How was it? Do you still
want to ride on my back?
Aw! How wicked the boys are these days!
So, it's your bath time, right?
Eh?
Let's bathe!
Hey! I can walk! Khun Yai, stop!
Khun Yai!
No, it still doesn't work.
It's not quite an auspicious time.
And, based on their natal
charts, they're not a match.
Is there any solutions, provost?
Well...
I want them to get married
as soon as possible.
If you want to rush it,
there's a solution.
You have to hold an engagement
ceremony for them first.
Amen.
I will follow your instruction
as soon as possible.
Why are you being in such a hurry?
Now Yai is only
20 years old recently.
Isn't it too quick for him, sir?
Well, I've got something on my mind.
So I believe that,
if I get him to marry
Brother Dech's daughter before,
I will have nothing to worry
about in the future to come.
Your worry,
it has to do with the boy
who has just moved to your house, right?
How did you know that?
I might not perceive everything,
but I have to tell you something.
They were destined to
meet each other long ago.
And he is the one
who will bring change
to your house.
Tea, Khun Yai.
Are you all right, Jom?
What's going on?
Today,
you look quite unwell.
Well, I'm fine, Khun Yai.
I think it's sunnier than usual today,
so I might be a bit tired from the heat.
No worries.
But if something happens with you,
you have to tell me immediately.
Jom!
Jom! What's going on?!
Wake up, Jom! Jom!
Anybody's here?!
Help!
Jom!
Wake up, Jom! Jom!
Help!
Jom!
(Next Episode)
You still have a temperature, Jom.
Let me wipe your body to bring it down.
Khun Yai, you don't have to teach me now.
I just want to touch my lover's hands.
Yai.
I've made you a croissant.
I was told that you should like it.
Your father thinks this is the right time.
The engagement ceremony
for you and Busabong.
So why did nobody
tell me about it, Mother?
I want you to gradually
break off your relationship with Yai, Jom.
♪ Because my love is
endless, it goes on perpetually ♪
♪ Nothing can erase these
traces of love from me ♪
♪ Unlike a flower's scent
that can't be scented forever ♪
♪ Because my heart beats
persistently, only for you, tirelessly ♪
♪ This scent of love will
follow you indefinitely ♪
♪ This heart will search
for you, for always ♪