(Previously)
Khun Yai,
he is the son of Luang
Nititham and Khun Ying Kaekai.
No.
Go teach him how to work,
and let him start tomorrow.
Have you got a name, by the way?
It should be... Hope!
Why did you decide to join in?
It's the blessing ceremony for the
foreign master and his second wife.
It's like you've lost your blessing.
May your blessing come back to you again.
Hey.
Ohm.
Khamsan.
Fong Kaew.
Ohm.
How are you?
I'm fine.
You shouldn't have come here.
It's very dangerous.
I missed you.
Fong Kaew.
Why are you being so cruel to me?
If Boon didn't send word that you
were bought to be the foreigner's wife,
I would never have
known that you'd be here.
If...
If I told you,
you'd stop me from doing it.
I had to do it.
The reason I came to live in this house,
is because I want a
comfortable life for my mother.
After the store caught fire,
my family had nothing left to our name.
You know that.
Fong Kaew, I understand.
I understand everything.
But... now,
You should run away with me.
Go.
Fong Kaew!!
Right?
Go quickly!
Go on!
I asked who is it?!
Leave with me now.
Who is it?!
You go, I can't leave.
We'd be in big trouble.
If you won't worry about
yourself then please think of me.
Go! Go!
Go!
Is that Fong Kaew?
What?
Who is he?
What is it?
Oh, it's you.
What?
Fong Kaew? Is that really you?
What are you doing out here so late?
Why are you out here?
- I was just taking in some fresh air
and taking in the view. - What's here?
Nothing.
Where the hell did he go?
What are you looking for?
Is that a man?
There's no man there.
There! In the boat!
I can't see who it is.
What are you doing?
Who is he?
Hey, hey.
Who's there?
Is that Jom?
Jom! Stay there and don't go anywhere!
Hey, don't go anywhere!
Keep an eye on her and I'll...
Jom?!
- Argh, Auntie!
- Where are you running to?
What?
Let go of me.
Look, where did he go?
(I Feel You Linger in the Air)
(Episode 3)
Are you sure that you saw a man?
I'm sure.
I'm definitely not mistaken.
Fong Kaew was going
to run away with her lover!
That's not true.
She's accusing me.
I've just married into this
house for not over a day.
How could I do that to my master?
You liar!
Are you saying that I'm lying?!
I'm just saying what I saw!
Well, you don't like me, don't you?
Ever since I came here,
you've been glaring at me,
you don't like me, don't you?
What? So you're not going to tell
the truth and now you're talking back?
Khamthip! Stop!
Did you forget that Fong Kaew is my wife?
And she is also your boss.
I'm sorry master.
Are you sure that you saw a man?
Go find evidence and a witness.
Of course master.
I have a witness.
Who?
Jom, the new servant
of the House of Palathip.
I saw him there.
So I made him keep an eye on...
Miss Fong Kaew.
Maey, go fetch Jom now.
Yes, master.
Ming.
Jom, get up and look around.
Hey, Jom.
Ming.
Maey.
Maey!
Ming, come here.
What's going on?
Where's Jom?
Is he in the house?
Something big happened!
What happened?
Well, Jom...
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey, let me go!
Help... Help... Help...
Quiet, quiet, quiet, I'm not
going to do anything to you.
Be quiet.
Ohm.
Are you a servant of this house?
Huh?
And just now, it was you, right,
who secretly watched me at the pier?
You've got the wrong person.
It wasn't me.
I'm not wrong, I saw
you hiding behind a tree.
Come on, help Fong Kaew.
Don't tell anyone about what you've seen.
Otherwise, Fong Kaew
will definitely be punished.
This has nothing to do with me, let me go.
Wait, wait
I don't want anything with... you either.
Let me go.
Please, I beg of you.
Please.
Fong Kaew's life has already
encountered a lot of hardships.
Please.
May you have sympathy for our love, please.
Jom.
Where did you go?
I was looking all over for you.
Uh.. Nothing is going
on, I just couldn't sleep.
So I came out to walk
and think about things.
Damn, I really can't take my eyes off you.
Whenever I let my guard
down, there's always trouble!
What?
Master called you to go to the house.
Aunt Thip said she wants
you there as a witness
that you saw Fong Kaew secretly
having an affair, did you really see her?
Well...
I...
This time, I can't help you.
Go tell the master yourself.
Go hurry!
What?!
Master has called for
you for a long time, quickly.
Damn, hurry up.
Have you come already?
Master has already scolded us.
Oh.
Jom, go in first.
Aw, won't you go in with me?
Uh, you go first, I'll follow you.
Oh, Ming.
Jom.
Hurry up and go in.
Jom has arrived, master.
Where did you fetch him from?
Why were you so slow?
You can wait patiently
for a bit, what of it?
Weren't you expecting an answer anyway?
It's not their working hours anyway.
Lately you've been
opposing everything with me.
Master asked someone to fetch me
in the middle of the night like this.
Is there something wrong?
Kham Thip says
that you saw Fong Kaew secretly
having an affair at the pier.
So I want to ask you
whether you really saw it or not.
Tell the master.
You really are bad luck.
Wherever you go, everything goes to shit.
Why are you silent?
Aren't you fiesty?
Answer my question!
Answer me.
Whether you really saw it or not.
Jom.
Tell him.
Did you see what I saw?
Fong Kaew was secretly having
an affair at the pier, tell him.
What's wrong with you?
Why won't you answer my question?
If so I will punish both of you.
What?
For wasting my time.
Well, hurry up and say it.
Or we will all be in trouble.
Say it!
Jom.
I can't seem to agree with you, Robert.
Yai? Why are you here?
Well, this is a matter
related to my servants.
I had to come.
That's strange.
Before this, I had never
seen you interested in anyone.
Before, we didn't have any disputes
between these two houses.
But now it's different.
Well then, make him say,
whether he actually saw my wife
secretly having an affair at the pier.
So that I can let him go.
Well? Jom?
Did you see it or not?
I..
Speak according to the truth that you saw.
Jom!
Two years, I've been waiting for you.
Ohm.
I hope that you would find
someone better than me.
Yes, I saw them.
I saw that Fong Kaew was with a man.
See, I told you.
You see, I'm not lying.
Who was it?
It's true.
I saw them hugging each other.
Crying at the lake.
Sympathizing with each other.
Right, Jom?
But... I don't know who he is.
And I don't know if it was her lover.
I saw from afar.
That's all I know.
We're all done here.
I'm going to take my people back.
Let's go Jom.
I, too, will have to take my leave.
Apparently it's none of my business.
Let's go, Maey.
Yes.
Go.
Please excuse me.
Fong Kaew!
Eeang Peung.
What will happen to Fong Kaew?
I pity her.
I don't know how Robert will punish her.
Don't think too much about it.
I am afraid.
I like it more when you
have a smile on your face.
But if you smile and it's tiring.
You don't have to force a smile.
I understand what you're feeling.
But don't overthink it.
Because when that day truly comes.
I believe that there will be a solution.
Let go of me!
That hurts!
Who do you think you are?
Doing this to me?
Marrying you
means that I can't see anyone?
Don't change the subject!
If you didn't do anything
then why did you lie to me?
If I told master
then would master believe me?
Would you let me see him?
Stop calling me that!
Remember that
I am your husband!
Don't call me like those
other lowly servants!
I forgot, you aren't really my wife yet.
Or...
Should I make you remember that.
I'm your husband now.
Let go of me!
Oh, now you're playing hard to get!
Acting all innocent and jumpy!
But when you're out of sight
you present yourself to that low life thug!
Mr.Robert, please let go of me.
I'm beggin you.
Do you know that
the fact that I took you as my wife
I had to face the pitiful looks
from those foreign businessmen?
This is how I help you and your mother
and are you still going
to cause me trouble?!
Fong Kaew!
Let me go!
Please let me go!
Mr Robert let me go.
How was it?
It's all taken care of.
Jom, Robert didn't
do anything to you right?
I'm ok.
That's a relief.
I was on my toes outside.
I couldn't even go in.
Mr. Robert might think that
I called Kun Yai to help ypu.
But it's good that you're fine.
Thank you Kun Yai
for helping Jom again.
It's ok Ming.
Jom is my people.
What's more, I gave my word to mother
that if anything happened to Jom.
I'd take on full responsibility.
But I'm afraid that
if Jom continues to reside here
it won't be a good thing.
Could you look after Jom a bit longer?
If I can find a solution
then we'll talk.
Of course Kun Yai.
Let's go to sleep
it's very late.
There's trouble everyday.
Should we go get drunk?
Huh?
Yai?
Oh, mother.
Why aren't you in bed yet?
Oh..
Prik told me that.
Ming came to call you to that house
so I was worried.
It's nothing mother.
It was just a quarrel.
Kham Thip was telling everyone
that Fong Kaew, Mr.Robert's new wife
was having an affair.
And also said that Jom was involved.
Was that why you had to go over there?
Yes.
But it's nothing mother,
you don't need to worry.
Ever since they let him stay,
that house has seen nothing but trouble.
Many things aren't related to Jom.
Don't spread rumours.
Um.. Mother..
There's something about Jom that
I want to get your advice on.
Ming!
Where are you taking me? What are we doing?
Jom, keep your voice down
or my mother will wake up.
Then why are we sneaking around?
Sit down.
Stop standing over my head.
I'm not.
What's this?
At this time, you've been
getting alot of trouble.
Try it.
I marinated it myself.
No.
I don't want to have any of these things.
Jom, you act like you never drank.
The first time I met you,
the smell of alcohol was buzzing.
Come on.
Ming.
So, what will happen to Fong Kaew?
I don't know either.
Mr.Robert is a fierce man.
Erratic.
And another thing
this matter is serious.
If it was me, he would hit me
and beaten until there
were lashes on my back.
Well, but Fong Kaew is a mistress.
Oh I don't know
I can't guess.
Jom.
The man you saw,
what did he look like?
May you see my love for it.
Good, then drink up.
It's good stuff.
So, Ming, how did you
come live with Mr.Robert?
Where can I go, dammit?
In the past, my master
was a lord in Lampang.
But when power was consolidated,
my master's power declined.
Luckily, Mr.Robert came to the rescue.
Therefore, my mother has
been serving him until today.
That's all to our life.
First thing is our masters, next is booze.
In the morning you have to wake up to
go to work, when it's dark, drink liquor.
To forget the difficult things.
Finally end up sleeping.
Sigh, life just goes on and on.
Come on Jom!
I'll pour it.
Good, drink up.
You really are an acoholic.
Give me your glass.
Let me tell you.
Last night.
I saw Fong Kaew
get dragged into the room by Mr.Robert.
After the doors closed,
there was the sound of ruckus.
I'm so happy!
Fong Kaew must have
been beaten up by Mr.Robert!
Really?
Of course!
I was the one who heard the noise!
Bang, bang, bang! Like that!
You speak like you were
in the room with them.
He might have called for a massage.
You really like to make others look bad.
I'm your aunt!
Well, not by blood
but I raised you all these
years not to talk back at me!
Wait, please finish the story.
You should be interested like her!
Do you understand?
This morning Pun saw Fong Kaew
she was washing clothes
for Mr. Robert by the river.
What do you think happened?
You're full right? I'll put it away.
No, I'm not full yet.
I'm so happy!
Jom? Why won't you eat?
Uh..
Eat.
Jom?
Where are you going?
Jom!
I..
I didn't think it would turn out this way.
I'm not blaming anyone.
It's karma for women like me.
Hope, what am I doing here?
Geez.
That's perfect.
Uh..
Hope?
Mr. James.
Who named the pig that? That's a cute name.
Does it mean aspiration?
I don't know what it means.
I just think the word sounds nice.
Hmm.. Interesting.
What is the owners name?
I forgot to ask you the last time we met.
Uh.. My name is Jom.
But Hope is not my pig
he's the master's pig.
I was sent to train the pig.
Jom.. That's a nice name.
What does it mean?
Jom means a master in a topic of knowledge.
So Jom, can you tell me
some tricks for training Hope?
Of course.
I trained it with sound.
I use the bell to let him
learn when he hears the bell.
He will get food.
And when it hears the bell then
it will come running to me.
Someday, come and train my pig.
I would like to send some to compete.
Compete?
Yes.
At the Christmas party at the club.
The foreign tradesmen
often go to celebrate.
Oh... and Mr. James raises pigs as well?
Not yet, but I want to
for next year.
Next year.
Jom, will you help me?
Help me, Jom.
Uh...
Jom.
Kun Yai.
Kun Yai, it's as if you
knew that I was coming.
I was just... calling my people.
But what business do you have
to be able to come here?
I'm here to see Mr. Robert
but I ran into Jom first.
Please excuse me.
Please continue using
your people as you please.
See you soon Hope.
[in English] See you soon, Jom.
Hope or...
Kun Yai, do you need something?
Are you free this afternoon?
I'm free.
Kun Yai, do you want me to do something?
Ming told me that
you were practicing rowing.
How is it going? Are you able to row yet?
I'm getting the hang of it.
Where do you want to go?
Then can you take me to Kad Luang?
Why do you have that big
smile on your face, James?
Nothing.. Well, let's
just say I saw something.
How have you been Robert?
I've been quite busy,
still looking for a pig for the race.
Well, what about Christmas? The
people at the royal department of forests,
they've been asking me about it.
And obviously, all the guys at the Gymkhana
have talking on and on about their little
pigs all day, it's making me rather annoyed.
I'm still looking for
someone to train my pig.
I really want to win the bet this time.
I need more concession of the forest.
I want to shame them.
Well, Robert.. You know you don't
have to keep your secrets from me right?
I do know that you have a
very competent pig trainer.
Who are you talking
about? I don't have any.
Well, Jom? The domestic
servant from Palathip house?
Jom?
Who are you buying a shirt for?
It's for you.
Me?
Why?
In case you need to go somewhere
so you have something new to wear.
Out of this house.
This one doesn't look bad.
What do you think?
Do you like it?
That's so cool!
Cool?
Uh.. I mean..
This one is really nice.
Oh..
If you like this one..
I'll take this one.
Uh.. Could you get the
shirt from the merchant?
And just take a walk around here first.
I need to buy some things for my mother.
Of course Kun Yai.
Are you the one who told them?
I thought you that we were both slaves
that you'd be more sympathetic.
You're really ruthless.
Do you know what Fong Kaew wrote
in the letter she wrote me?
Do you know?
Fong Kaew told me to forget her.
In this life, she's compelled
to be that bastard's wife.
Do you see what you've done?
This is what you did?!
Do you see?
Don't fight in my shop.
You get out!
I will kill you!
Die!!
Why are you so selfish?
What else do you want from me?
Can you blame only me?
Well, it's because of all of us, isn't it?
When you asked for my help
for my sympathy.
Have you ever sympathized with me?
How will I feel?
Jom!
Kun Yai.
Kun Yai is...
I'm sorry.
In this life, if I and Fong
Kaew were not happy together.
Then don't expect that
you'll live happily ever after.
I said enough.
If you do anything to
me and my people again.
I won't stand for it.
Khamsaen, what the hell are you doing?
I apologize on behalf of my son.
When he's drunk, he likes
to argue with other people.
Don't mind him.
Saen! Let's go home!
Come back! Come!
Follow me!
Let go!
No!
Mom, let go of me.
Where are you going?
Ow.
Do you know what you've done?!
Out drinking all night.
When I came back and had you
watch my things for a moment.
You went around looking
for trouble with him.
Do you know who he is?
It's whoever it is.
I don't care.
I'm interested in Fong Kaew, you know that.
Learn to know your place.
Fong Kaew is already
in a good place in life.
Now her mother is wealthy.
But now you have to help me with
my daily work to have food on the table.
Do you understand?
I love her.
I love Fong Kaew, mom.
I know.
I've raised you since you were young,
why wouldn't I understand you?
But Fong Kaew
has gone on to live a good life.
You should let her go.
Saen.
What about me, mom?
What about me?
Saen.
It's just the way life is.
Make peace with it.
Saen.
What did I do wrong?
Forget her.
I love her with all my heart.
What's wrong with that?
Please may you have
sympathy for our love, please.
You are really bad luck! Wherever you go,
everything goes to shit.
I didn't think it'd be like this.
In this life, she's compelled
to be that bastard's wife.
This is what you did.
Let me.. Go home.
Please let me go home.
Jom.
Kun Yai.
What are you doing?
I... have no clue.
Jom.
Do you want to sit with me?
Are you thinking about
what happened this evening?
Ever since you came here.
I never asked you
how you are.
I'm... still trying to fit in.
Do you have a something
you want to tell me about Jom?
If not, that's fine, I understand.
Sometimes people have
stories that they can't tell anyone.
I'm just... confused.
I used to feel that way too.
And I always come
here when I feel like that.
So..
Have you ever been like me?
Feeling like you're in a
completely wrong place.
And I don't understand why
all the bad things
that're all happening now
have to happen to me.
Even though I didn't feel
that I had done anything wrong
but I don't understand.
Why do things like this
have to happen to me?
Did I do something wrong?
That I have to be here.
I do not understand.
Did what happened today
make you miss where you came from?
If it makes you miss it
and it makes you sick
then forget about it.
If remembering
makes you sad.
Just forget about it completely.
Let's start again.
Relax your heart.
Don't you love me anymore?
I still feel the same towards you.
I hope you find someone better than me.
Ohm.
Kun Yai.
Hmm?
Thank you.
It's ok.
Go back to your house and get some rest.
During this time, everything may have
changed from what you're used to.
Jom!
Yes?
May you be safe from misfortune,
even in your dreams.
Good night.
I think you've lost your spirit.
Let me help you bring it back.
I hope that your spirit
comes back to you.
Ever since you came here
I've never asked you how you were.
Do you like it?
It's good, right?
Eat lots.
Because I want you to know that
if from now on I can't be with you,
you might not get to eat
delicious food like this all the time.
Eat up.
Come on, quickly.
Where is Hope?
Oh, Kun Yai.
I just stopped by
to see if you're doing better.
But seeing you play with Hope
has really made me less worried.
Uh.. So why did you say Por
Jom? Why did you call me that?
I don't know
but it makes me feel at ease.
You don't like it?
No.
You haven't answered me yet.
Where are you going?
I'm not sure yet
that everyone still
wants me to stay or not
with everthing that happened.
Why would you think like that?
Before this,
you even said so yourself
that you don't want me to be here anymore.
But I'm afraid to let you to
continue to stay in this house.
It may not be a good thing.
I didn't mean it like that.
I meant that...
I was the one who brought you in.
Letting you live in Ming's home
which is that house's servant.
I see it as inappropriate..
Hope, were you the one who named it?
Yes.
You know what it means...
This isn't the first time I've seen you
different from others.
Since the first time you met Mr. James
at my brother-in-law's house.
I overheard you speaking in English.
So I want you..
to come stay with me as...
my majordomo.
Can you do that?
A ma...jor...do...mo??
(Next Episode)
We're finally living in the same home.
It's ok, Auntie.
I'm not hungry yet.
I'm not letting you eat it.
Staying at someone else's home,
you must know how to behave.
And only focus on what
you have to do after this.
Because if you can't
his lord won't probably
won't let you stay here
and waste rice.
How are you Jom?
Can you do it?
Kun Yai.
I'm very drunk.
I'm not phased by liquor
but taken aback by love.