- [CLATTERING]
- [AMELIA] Oh.
What was that?
Is anyone with you?
Uh…
No, Ma. I left in a hurry
while putting something down.
I might not have placed it correctly,
so it fell.
And, Ma,
make sure to message, text, or call me
before coming over next time
because Olivia and I might not be here.
I'll take care of this, Ma, okay?
I'll get a broom, Ma.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[VICTOR] Ma, let's go!
I'll take care of that.
I'm coming, son!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
All right. I'll get back to you soon.
Victor!
- Coach.
- Victor, I have good news.
The federation is permitting you to fight.
- R-Really, Coach?
- Uh-huh.
And the other camp just called.
They want you to face
their boxer for your first fight.
But the thing is,
they'd like you to make that fight
an undercard in Alex's match.
[CHUCKLES]
I just allowed you
to spend time with Abby,
and now you're going to ride my fame?
I'm the promoter of the match, Alex.
I can choose which undercards
are going to fight
before your match.
If I were you, I'd focus on your fight
so you don't lose.
You think I'll lose?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Your footwork's slow,
especially when you're charging forward.
Are you my coach?
I'm a boxer too, Alex.
And from what I see, in your condition,
you will lose your fight.
[BADONG] Victor is right, Alex.
You need to strengthen your stamina.
Do you think I'm dumb?
And stop being full of yourself.
What have you ever achieved in boxing?
I saw your title fight.
You headbutted your opponent,
that's why you won.
If I were you,
I'd use what Papa taught us.
It looks like you've forgotten about it.
- What did you say?
- [BADONG] Alex.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're my investment, Alex.
So, whether you like it or not,
I'll give you orders,
and you'll listen to me.
What if I don't want to?
Then we'll go to court.
Your former ring.
Is that what you want?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I can't afford to lose,
especially now that I'm under Victor.
It'll inflate his ego.
Why? You're not confident you'll win?
I am.
But I have a feeling
that jerk will embarrass me.
Who knows what stunt he'll pull
during my match?
Why should I help you?
So far, you have not shown me any evidence
of how Victor sabotaged my business.
What do I get out of this?
That's all the more reason
you need to help me.
I'm your only ally, Emilio.
All right, fine.
I'll see what I can do.
I've been doing you a lot of favors, Alex.
I hope that when the time comes
and I ask for repayment,
you'll be able to pay up.
Don't worry.
I'll make it worth your time
for all the help you've given me.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Alex!
What's up?
Are you high?
You might lose your license
if the boxing--
Relax, relax, okay?
It's still a long time until my match.
Anyway, uh…
These are Rachel, Jessie,
and Jenny, our round girls.
You've met them, right?
Yes, I know them.
Oh, here's yours.
Take it.
Don't take it then.
Come on, girls.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing?
I missed you.
Didn't you miss me?
[SMOOCHES]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
When will you visit me again at the condo?
I have a surprise for you.
This isn't it, right?
- No, Daddy, that's too sexy.
- [OLIVIA] Abby.
Take a look.
So, I got two options.
This one's cute, feminine, and bright,
and this one's more elegant.
What do you think? They suit you.
That's not what I'm looking for.
Oh.
Didn't you say you were
a princess in your play?
A warrior princess.
Um…
It seems like there are no
warrior princess costumes here, Abby.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I should have just gone out with Mommy.
Dear.
Dear, your Aunt Olivia
is just helping, okay?
Give her a chance.
Oh, is there a problem?
Oh, didn't you say you had an event today?
It ended early. Did you guys pick one yet?
Not yet, Mommy.
Okay, let me help you.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JULIANA] How about this one, dear?
You're looking for
a warrior princess, right?
[ABBY] Yes, Mommy.
[JULIANA] Look, it even comes
with a headdress.
Mom, the thing is,
but I still need a sword.
- [VICTOR] Hmm?
- Sword?
- You need a sword?
- Yes, Daddy.
- She's a warrior princess.
- Oh, look at this.
- Is it a sword?
- Yes, that'll do.
Or how about this?
That's better.
Hmm, doesn't this look real?
Yes.
Mommy, my costume's done.
We're not done yet, you still need shoes.
Wait a minute, dear.
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
- [DOOR OPENS]
Abby, I'll leave now.
Don't forget about my fight later, okay?
I'll see you and your mom at the arena.
Okay.
What is this for?
Oh, that's for our school play later.
Who bought this?
Daddy paid for it,
but Mommy picked the costume for me.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
It's good that your mom and dad
are on good terms now.
Do you guys go out often?
Hmm, whenever I'm with Dad.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR SLAMS]
Oh? Looks like you're packing
a lot of stuff.
It's always good to be prepared.
You sound nervous.
It's like you're the one boxing
instead of me. [CHUCKLES]
I don't know.
Maybe because this is your first fight
since we got married.
Hmm? Really?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
It really changes when you get married.
I used to be confident
when you had fights.
Now, I've got a lot on my mind.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Don't worry, I'll win.
Just as long as
nothing bad happens to you,
I'm good.
Liv, I promise…
I'll win.
When that happens…
we'll finally be able
to achieve our dreams.
That is, when Alex fails.
What do you mean?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Does it look good on me?
Oh, why are you still here?
Did you forget anything?
You should've just told me.
[GASPS]
Did you and Victor go out together
without telling me?
Huh?!
Alex.
Alex, it was just a coincidence.
I just tagged along with him and Abby.
Olivia was also with us.
How many times have you been going out
without me knowing, huh?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Answer me!
Alex…
Alex, I'm not doing anything wrong.
I know your tricks.
Didn't you also fool Victor before?!
Huh?!
Alex, please, please.
Please don't hurt me.
Y-You're the only one.
You're the only one I love.
No one else but you.
Don't think like that.
You're the only one.
You're the only one… The only one…
That's enough.
[SOBS] That's enough…
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BREATHING SHAKILY]
[BROODING MUSIC PLAYING]
We already talked about this, right?
You'll stay away from him.
If you do this again,
you're going to answer to me.
Mm?
- [BROODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BREATHING SHAKILY]
[CRIES SOFTLY]
[SOBBING]
- The Beast! The Beast!
I told you.
You're still The Beast
that I used to know.
Your opponent is down.
Now that you have proven that
you can do it,
we can easily find your next opponent.
Who knows? You and Alex
might end up fighting.
Lualhati versus Lualhati!
Ooh!
Congrats, bro.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
But it looks like
you're still far from my level.
You think you can handle me
in the ring, huh?
I don't back down from any fight.
Keep your arrogance in check
and make sure
those punches of yours stay in the ring.
Don't go hitting just anyone.
Are you implying something?
Just do well in your fight.
You're all bark.
[OLIVIA] Alex!
Alex.
It's time for you to prepare.
Let's go.
[BADONG] Let's go, let's go.
Boom!
Boom! [CHUCKLES]
You go ahead first.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGS]
Hello?
Is the plan all set?
You don't have to worry.
You'll definitely win.
[AMELIA] You can drop me off here.
Here's the payment.
- Thank you.
- [DRIVER] Thanks too.
Uh, miss, what is it? Why are you here?
Oh, Ma'am Amelia!
I'm glad I saw you.
It's me, Fely.
I used to be one of Sir Alex
and Ma'am Sylvia's maids.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, ma'am, I'm glad I got to see you.
- I just wanted to say goodbye.
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
Huh?
You see, Ma'am Sylvia is making us leave.
Why?
I don't know either.
Someone told me you moved here.
I just wanted to try my luck
and see if you needed any maids.
I'm sorry.
I don't live here anymore.
And from what I know,
they already have enough staff here.
So, you can go now.
Ma'am, please.
I'm in desperate need of money.
You need money?
- Here, I have money.
- Yes.
Take it. And after this,
- just leave, okay?
- Ma?
Dear?
There you go.
That's a lot. All right, you can go now.
What's happening here?
Huh? Oh… Well…
She asked for help,
so I helped her.
Uh, ma'am, that's not it.
I actually wanted to apply for a job.
I used to be one of Sir Alex's maids.
Don't mind her, dear.
I already gave her money.
She's done here, so she'll leave now.
You'll leave now, right?
Uh, how long have you worked for Alex?
Juliana, we're going to be late
for Alex's match.
Come on.
Ma, I'm still talking to her.
I worked for Ma'am Sylvia for a long time.
Until she died.
That means…
Seriously, miss? Can't you understand?
Didn't I tell you
that they don't need any more maids?
And you've already got money.
You can go now, right?
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
- All right, I'll go now.
- Okay, great.
Finally, thank you.
Liana.
What's going on with you?
I told you we're going to be late
for Alex's match, right?
There you go. We're all done
with your warm-up routine.
Just remember the techniques
that I told you, okay?
To avoid injuries.
Did you know that Juliana and Victor
have been seeing each other?
Yes.
I've been with them.
You've been with them?
Every time?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
You know, Juliana used to do
the same thing with me.
She'd meet with me secretly…
pretending that…
she needed some saving.
She's helpless.
Weak.
But turned out, she just wanted
to leave her husband.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Well…
that sounds like a problem with your wife,
not my husband.
I'm just letting you know.
Neither of us want to lose
our spouses, do we?
Maybe you want to work with me.
[REFEREE] Are you ready?
Are you ready? Fight!
[BELL RINGS]
[BADONG] Raise your hands!
Alex, raise your hands!
Alex, your hands!
[BADONG] Alex, defense!
Defense! Your left!
Raise your left arm.
Okay, okay, okay.
Defense, defense!
Don't lower your left!
[JIMBOY] Your hand, Alex!
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GROANS]
[CROWD CHEERING, WHISTLING]
[BADONG] Defense!
Try to recover. Deep breaths!
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [BADONG] Breathe!
- Hey! Hey!
- [BODY THUDS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Get up, Alex! Get up, Alex!
[CROWD CLAMORING]
[REFEREE] One! Two! Three!
- [JIMBOY] Get up, Alex!
- [REFEREE] Four! Five!
- Get up, Alex!
- Six! Seven!
[REFEREE] Eight! Nine!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Good thing Alex's opponent
didn't throw the game.
Why would he?
He won fair and square
and he even got a bonus from you.
Thank you.
If you hear anything about
Alex and Emilio,
tell me right away.
Alex was all talk
and no walk.
He got what he deserved.
What's your plan with him?
Are you going to drop him?
I need you to do something for me.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hurry up. Come on.
All right.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[AMELIA] Liana!
Come on!
Okay.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[AMELIA] Son.
Besides your shoulder,
does it hurt anywhere else?
No.
Do you want water?
I'll get you some.
[ABBY PANTING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[ALEX] Abby.
Uncle Alex, are you going to be okay?
[JULIANA] Dear, Uncle Alex will be okay.
Don't worry.
I'm already feeling so much better now
because you're both here.
But I'll recover more quickly
if I get a hug.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ALEX GRUNTS SOFTLY]
I was worried for you, Uncle.
[ALEX] You know, having you two
by my side is enough for me.
It's okay if I lose everything
as long as I have you both.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Will it be like this
every time Victor wins?
Where is Victor?
It's his first win, he should be here.
He should be enjoying
the food you prepared.
He's with Alex,
who's doing fine now.
Why?
Why does he need to be there?
Alex is one of his boxers, right?
So?
Can't Alex look after his own family?
I'm sure Juliana is there
- with Miss Amelia.
- Psst!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
But…
I guess he does need to be there
to comfort Abby and Juliana.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Don't worry too much, dear.
I'm just thinking about
how I got angry at Uncle.
When I found out something happened
between him and Mommy.
I feel guilty for getting mad at him.
What if something bad happened to him,
and I wasn't able to say sorry?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
Abby…
I'm sure your Uncle Alex understands that.
Don't beat yourself up over it, okay?
He acted as my father when you were gone.
He treats me like his real daughter.
He was the one who defended me
when I was bullied in school.
I don't want anything bad
to happen to him.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
How did that happen?!
I thought you told my opponent
to throw the match?
We had a clear agreement.
He might not have done it on purpose.
Did you watch the fight?
Did it look like he was planning to lose?
Well, it looked like he
was determined to beat me.
I'm not so weak
I'd get knocked down by a soft hit.
He won't get a single penny from me.
I don't know what happened.
He didn't follow our plan.
Only the two of us know about it.
I can't lose especially now
that I'm under Victor.
It'll inflate his ego.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why? You're not confident you'll win?
I am.
But I suspect
that bastard will do something
to embarrass me.
Have someone watch Norman.
Why?
Because he's the only one
who knew about our conversation.
I have a strong suspicion
that he's the mole.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GROANS]
- [DOOR OPENS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
What are you doing here?
Juliana might see you.
Babe,
don't worry.
I made sure they weren't here
before I went in.
Why didn't you just send me a message?
What you're doing will get me in trouble.
You're not thinking.
Are you okay?
How do you feel?
Why are you worried? We're not together.
[DOOR OPENS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- What's this?
Who is she?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Abby, you'll sleep over
at Grandma's tonight, okay?
Your Uncle Alex needs
someone to accompany him.
Okay, Mommy.
Come on. I'll drive you there.
Oh, Juliana, no need.
I know you have a lot to do
and you have to buy medicine.
I'll take care of Abby.
The taxi I booked earlier is already here.
Thank you, Kate.
I actually need to go home.
I'll have to bring what Alex needs.
Just message me when you get home, okay?
I'll message you.
All right. Bye-bye, baby.
- Bye-bye, Mommy.
- Take care.
- You take care.
Come on, Abby. Get in the car.
- Kate, message me, okay?
- [KATE] Yes, I'll message you.
Bye, Juliana! Take care!
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
- [CAR ENGINE REVS]
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[JULIANA] Who is she?
[ALEX] Health insurance agent.
Health insurance agent?
Mm-hmm.
My husband has medical insurance.
He doesn't need that.
Sir said the same thing.
Fine, I'm going.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
I think I've seen that girl before.
Oh, she's working for Emilio.
She also works as an insurance agent.
She's one of Ricky's girls.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
N-No… No… No…
[SOBBING]
- [SNIFFLES]
- [BREATH QUIVERS]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
Why are you looking at me like that?
Did you do what I asked you to do?
[SCOFFS, LAUGHING]
Would you like me to do it again?
So you can be sure.
Or do you want
his wife to catch us in the act?
No need.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's all there.
This is too easy.
Why?
You think I'm the only woman
Alex is fooling around with?
We round girls are like a buffet to him.
He's had us all.
I even thought that he liked me.
I feel bad for his wife.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SOBBING SOFTLY]
Liana?
Liana.
Are you okay?
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBBING SOFTLY]
- [SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING]
[SOBBING]
- [SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING]
[VICTOR] Don't worry, Liana.
I'm here for you.
I know…
it's hard to believe, but…
I wouldn't wish what I went through
on anyone.
Not even on my worst enemy.
Especially not on you.
["ANONG NANGYARI SA ATING DALAWA"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING]
Because you are the mother
of our daughter.
[SNIFFLES, SOBS]
What's your plan now?
Liana, if you need anything, anything,
just tell me.
[SNIFFLES]
You know,
the truth is…
I don't know.
I don't know what I'm going to do now.
I'm confused. I'm angry.
I don't know what I'm supposed to feel.
[SNIFFLES, SOBS]
Liana.
We both know Alex.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
And he can weasel his way out of anything.
He must not find out what you know.
If he was able to hide
his affair from you,
it means there's more
you don't know about him.
How well do you know your husband?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Where are Juliana and Abby?
Abby will stay at Ms. Pilar's for now.
Juliana went home to get your stuff.
Oh no!
I should've gone with her, she might…
She might what?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
What?!
Do you remember Fely?
She used to work for you and Sylvia.
She came to our house.
What did she need?
She wanted to work at the house again.
Well, what did you say?
I made her leave.
She was there the day Sylvia died.
She saw me arrive and we talked.
I don't know what else she knows,
or if she actually knows anything.
If she saw anything.
Juliana saw us talking to each other.
Alex managed to hide from you
that he has a mistress.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
And you believed that he loved you…
so you didn't see it coming.
That means, Liana,
he's hiding something else.
If we're going to talk about
Sylvia's death again--
Admit it, Liana.
Do you think it's possible
that Alex did something?
The night Sylvia died,
you brought me home.
You told me you were going to see her.
You were furious too.
Is it true that you never met that night?
Are you suspecting me?!
I just want to know the truth, Alex.
This is the truth!
The truth is, I know what you're doing.
You're turning this around on me.
You did something wrong,
so you're bringing up the past.
Aren't you afraid of what he might do?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
But…
there is no evidence
that will prove it was Alex.
[VICTOR EXHALES DEEPLY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I worked for Ma'am Sylvia for a long time.
Until she died.
That means…
Seriously, miss? Can't you understand?
Didn't I tell you that they don't need
any more maids?
And you've already got money.
You can go now, right?
But…
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What?
It seemed like one of their former maids
knew something.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
She came to our house.
She wanted to…
She wanted to work for us.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Did Alex talk to her?
Alex wasn't the one who talked to her.
It was Mama.
But I saw…
that Mama was nervous as they talked.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I told Juliana not to talk to her.
Even if she needs a job,
she shouldn't accept her.
Did she say anything about what happened?
We might get implicated.
"We"?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Alex.
I've been protecting you
even after everything you've done.
Whether you like it or not,
you're involved in what I did.
You hid the evidence,
fled the crime scene,
and didn't talk to the police.
You're an accomplice!
We're in this together, Ma!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I came in since--
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're leaving?
I am done playing the fool for Alex!
I… will file charges
against him and Juliana!
I'm not a coward like Victor.
What do you mean?
Victor dropped his charges
against Alex and Juliana!
I am still Alex's wife!
I will send them both to jail!
That's not the solution, dear.
Their child just died.
Have some compassion.
Why?!
Did your son have compassion
every time he cheated on me?!
I made this home for him!
I've sent away the household staff.
I'm taking all my things with me.
Alex will come home to nothing.
I am taking everything!
Dear…
Have mercy on my son.
Why should I have mercy
on those who ruined my life?!
He manipulated me!
Sylvia…
- Let's talk about--
- You may leave!
- Sylvia--
- I said leave!
Sylvia, let's talk about this.
You're not leaving.
You… You're not leaving, dear.
You won't file charges, and you won't--
Who are you to tell me
what I can and cannot do?!
Am I not doing everything, dear?
So you and Alex can make amends.
So you can save your marriage.
What more do I have to do?
Haven't I been kind to you?
The truth is, this is your fault!
You raised a liar and a cheater!
What kind of mother are you?!
Did you ever think…
that maybe you're the one who's at fault?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[AMELIA] Maybe the reason Alex
has been having an affair
is because of your shortcomings.
Shut up!
Maybe the problem is with you.
Huh?
[AMELIA] Don't blame
your problems on me, Sylvia.
Don't.
I'm just a mother
who will do everything for her son.
Leave.
[SYLVIA] Leave. Leave!
Get out!
I said leave! Get out!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Sylvia is furious.
She threatened that
if Victor couldn't do it,
she would send you and Juliana to jail.
What?
After everything she did,
she's the one who's furious?
Fine. Leave it to me. I'll talk to her.
Hurry! She's packing her things.
Thank you.
Wait for me here, Juliana.
I'll talk to Sylvia.
I want to talk to Sylvia, Alex.
Is that all you'll do?
What? Are you going to comfort her?
You'll console her after what happened?
You're going to calm her down, huh?
I understand you, Juliana.
Trust me. I'm angry too.
But our freedom depends on this.
We just made amends with Victor.
You think we'll ever
make amends with Victor?
He's going to take away my daughter, Alex.
Leave it to me.
Now go inside. You need to rest.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Alex.
- Where is she?
- She's upstairs.
I'll talk to her.
- I'll come with you.
- No. Go home.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ALEX] Sylvia!
Sylvia!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Where are you going?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm leaving.
Isn't this what you want?
Fine. If that's your decision, then go.
But we have to talk properly.
To find closure.
I know I've committed
a grave sin against you.
Oh no, Alex.
We're not doing that.
"Closure"?
Really?
[SYLVIA] Are you here
to ask for forgiveness?
And because you know
that I still love you,
you think I'll just accept everything?
Do you want me to leave without a word
and let you two live your lives?
Be the doormat that I've always been?
Those days are over, Alex.
Let's be adults about this, Sylvia.
[ALEX] Let us not be consumed by anger.
It happens, okay? People fall out of love!
But it doesn't mean
that anyone is at fault--
It does!
Someone's responsible
for our marriage falling apart.
And it's you!
Because you couldn't keep it
in your pants!
Because you had sex
with your brother's wife.
We didn't just "fall out of love," Alex.
You betrayed me!
Over and over!
All right!
Fine!
You're right. It's all my fault!
But I also lost a child!
Isn't that enough punishment?
Hell no!
You deserve a lot worse!
I've given you so many chances, Alex!
I gave up all the self-respect
and dignity I had left!
But I stood by you.
I endured it all
because I couldn't lose you.
It would've been the death of me, Alex!
It would've!
But what did you do?!
And even if we do part ways, Alex,
I'll make sure you don't end up together!
You will both spend
your miserable lives in prison!
And I'm going to make sure of that!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SYLVIA CRYING]
[LAUGHING MOCKINGLY]
Look at you.
Look at you!
You should see your face.
Your fucking face!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You're nothing but a scared little boy!
There.
[LAUGHS MOCKINGLY]
That's the real Alex!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
You know what?
You should be so thankful
that your son died
because you don't deserve to be a father.
No child deserves to have
a spineless, loser father like you.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
He's better off dead than with you.
[GROANING]
Alex.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
How can I fall in love with you?!
You're nothing to me!
You're just a worthless piece
of decoration!
You can't even bear a child!
You are useless! Worthless!
- [PANTING]
- [GRUNTING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[VASE SHATTERS]
[GROANS]
- [GRUNTING]
- [PANTING]
[VASE SHATTERS]
[GROANS]
[MUSIC TURNS SINISTER]
[SYLVIA WHIMPERING]
You monster! You monster!
[SYLVIA] You're going to kill me!
Bastard!
[ALEX] Sylvia!
[SYLVIA GROANS]
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ALEX GROANS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Sylvia!
[SYLVIA GROANS]
[SYLVIA GRUNTS]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sylvia!
[SYLVIA SCREAMING]
[ALEX] Come here!
Sylvia
[SYLVIA] No!
[BANGING ON DOOR]
[ALEX] Sylvia, open this door!
Let me help you!
[BANGING ON DOOR]
Sylvia!
[ALEX] Let me help you.
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BANGING ON DOOR]
Open the door, Sylvia!
Let me help you!
[ALEX] Sylvia!
SYLVIA, LET'S TALK.
Sylvia!
Yes, dear, I'm almost there.
Wait for me. Don't sleep yet.
Love you, dear.
[ALEX] Sylvia, open the door!
[BANGING ON DOOR]
- [BREATH QUIVERING]
- [LINE RINGING]
Pick up, Victor. Please.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [DOOR SLAMS OPEN]
- [GASPS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Who are you calling?
Get away from me.
- Get away.
- Answer my question.
- Get away from me!
- Who are you calling?!
Get away--Ah!
Victor?!
You can't talk to him!
Help! Aah!
Help! Somebody, help!
Aah!
Let go!
[SYLVIA SOBS]
Help!
[SYLVIA WHIMPERS] Help!
- Give me that!
- Let me go!
- Give it!
- I said let go!
[SYLVIA CRIES]
- Help me!
- Give me the phone!
Let's just see each other in hell!
- I said give it!
- Help!
Give me the phone!
Aah!
- [LOUD THUD]
- [GASPS]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SHRIEKS]
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[VOICE BREAKING] Sylvia…
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGING]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
- [PHONE CONTINUES RINGING]
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Alex?
Ah…
- Alex!
- [GASPS]
What happened to you? What happened here?
- What?
- It's Sylvia.
- Sylvia's dead?!
- No.
What really happened?!
I didn't mean to. We were arguing, and…
It was an accident. That's it.
That's all you can tell the police.
- The police?
- Yes!
Wait!
What do you think will happen?
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you think you'll get away with this?
No way.
I can't go to prison.
I thought you said you were innocent!
You said you were innocent.
Do you think I can explain this?
The police won't believe me.
We had a fight!
I hurt her!
Alex.
What's your plan?
Huh?
Do you think you can escape this?
Ma, it's just us here.
We need to leave. No one must talk.
We can't be seen here.
We need to go, Ma.
Sylvia called Victor.
What?
We'll be in deeper trouble
if we leave now.
I feel bad for your wife, son.
Sylvia is still your wife.
Will you leave her downstairs?
Be afraid of what you're doing!
This isn't right, Alex. This isn't right.
We're leaving.
We're leaving?
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
We are leaving.
Come on, Ma.
You should go home.
Hide this and burn it when you get home.
Shouldn't we just tell the police, son?
Come on, Ma!
Make sure no one sees you.
Do you understand?
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GROWLS]
[BREATHING ANXIOUSLY]
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
SYLVIA, ANSWER THE PHONE!
DON'T DO THIS, SYLVIA, OR ELSE YOU WILL
REGRET IT. DON'T MAKE ME ANGRY.
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBBING]
[WAILING] My God!
My goodness, son!
Alex!
How will you get away with this, son?!
How?!
[WAILING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Sylvia?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GLASS BREAKS]
Sylvia?
Sylvia!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sylvia?
Sylvia!
Are you here?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sylvia!
Sylvia, are you here?
Sylvia?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INDISTINCT NOISE]
Sylvia?
Let's just meet on Sunday.
Okay?
Huh? But--Wait!
- I have to go. Bye!
- [ZEUS BARKS]
Zeus!
- Zeus!
- [DOG BARKS]
What are you doing?
[GASPS]
[SCREAMING]
Sylvia?
Sylvia!
[MAID SCREAMING]
[VICTOR] Sylvia?
[ZEUS BARKS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[MAID SCREAMING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAID WHIMPERING, SCREAMING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
What have you done?!
[MAID SCREAMING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Security! I need help!
Security!
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC BECOMES DARK]
W-What happened?
Victor is already at the precinct.
He was arrested by the police.
Victor?
Why does Victor have to pay, Alex?
Why not?
I lost so much because of him.
My career as a lawyer,
my legitimacy as a son.
My child!
All of that is because of him.
It's not enough to pay
for everything he did to me!
Alex…
Son, why did it have to come this far?
Ma…
Everything you did was right.
It wasn't wrong for you
to choose your son.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you for everything
you've done for me, Ma.
Did you destroy all the evidence?
Sylvia's phone is missing.
Do you know where it is?
No. I left immediately.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What's on your mind, Ma?
You know what?
You're waiting to hear about my arrest.
I'll get you something to eat.
How oblivious do you think I am?
I was right to be suspicious of you.
No one could've taken
Sylvia's phone but you!
I had Matteo follow you
to confirm my hunch.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Your hunch was right, Alex.
You were going to give
Victor the evidence?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I can't do it, Alex.
I can't let Victor go to jail
for a crime he did not commit.
So you'd rather let me suffer
instead of him?
You meant to hide it from me.
But the evidence is gone, Ma.
You can't incriminate me anymore.
Alex…
[SOBS] Alex, please.
[ALEX] This is unforgivable, Ma.
But don't worry.
I'll still be in your life
to watch your every move.
But don't expect me
to treat you like my mother.
From now on, I call the shots.
You have no control over my life anymore.
[AMELIA] Alex!
Alex, my son…
You! Listen up!
You'd better help me.
You already betrayed me
for Victor once before.
Does he know anything about that maid?
No. Only Juliana and I saw her.
Victor can't find out about this.
What if he already knows?
Then find out!
[ALEX] Now is the right time
to ask questions.
Observe if he is acting suspiciously!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing here, hmm?
Don't you live over there?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What are you thinking?
If you know something, spit it out!
There's a unit next to Victor's house.
[AMELIA] It's always closed.
Uh…
[STAMMERS]
It's always locked.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[AMELIA] I don't know what's inside.
But…
I have a bad feeling about it.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]