[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
That was my chance
to make it up to your father.
Sylvia, can you talk to him again?
Please?
Sylvia.
You've been deep in thought
for a while now.
What's the matter?
Sylvia.
How important is it to you
that I give you a child?
Why are you asking me that?
If I couldn't give you a child…
would you still love me?
Of course.
Promise?
You wouldn't leave me?
Promise.
What's wrong?
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
I went to a doctor this morning.
She said it would be difficult
for me to get pregnant.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I might not be able to give you
the family you want.
Sylvia.
What do I always tell you?
What matters to me is you…
and that we're together.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sylvia, you're all I need.
[SNIFFLING, CRYING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[TRAFFIC NOISE]
Victor has a good point, Alex.
They're married.
The house is conjugal property.
Conjugal, my ass!
The down payment for that house
came from my own pocket.
It was my gift to Juliana!
Juliana just insisted on
paying in installments.
And now what?
Victor will benefit from it?
As Victor's wife,
Juliana is the one
managing their finances.
And besides, how are you so sure
that Victor's money
was not used to pay for it?
Wait, whose side are you really on?
Alex…
I'm just looking at all angles.
If I were you, I'd let it go.
What matters is that he doesn't
bother you anymore.
Let it go? I haven't even
gotten back at him yet.
He's the reason why
I wasn't appointed as judge!
Did you explain the situation
to your daughter?
Abby might think you and Juliana
are back together
because you're living in the same house.
Why did you do this?
Oh, I know.
You'll get back at Alex
by winning back your wife.
Do you want to get back together with her?
That's not it.
What they did to me
is too painful to forget.
I'm doing this to gather evidence.
I thought your application
was being processed again.
I can't rely on my father-in-law anymore,
so I'm going to ask someone else.
But that doesn't mean I'll let Victor win.
What's the plan?
He will regret living in that house.
I'm going to use that to prove
he can't support his family.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you expect to catch them
in the act again?
You've already caught them once.
They'll be more careful now.
Are you sure this is only about
getting back at them?
Or are you still hoping
you can fix things with Juliana?
What's left to fix?
Victor.
A person blinded by anger
tends to lose sight
of what's truly important.
I'm not saying you should
forgive them right now,
but I hope you'll keep an open mind.
Violence is not always the answer.
But that's something
you have to decide for yourself.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes, we're already here. All right.
- Good afternoon.
May we speak to the owner of this gym?
Uh, I'm the owner. Why?
This is a surprise inspection
ordered by the municipal government.
We received a report that
this gym doesn't have a permit.
That can't be right.
Our permit is hanging on that wall.
Where?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Is this it?
It's no longer valid!
I sincerely apologize, sir.
It expired just recently.
I'm working on it. I'm saving up money…
- …so I can renew it.
- Sir, that won't do.
This is a violation.
We have to shut down your gym.
Please don't.
Is there anything we can do
to fix this, sir?
We will give you a second chance.
But you need to renew your business permit
and settle the penalty.
Otherwise, we will order
the immediate closure of your gym!
Okay.
[JIMBOY] Coach Bads.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sylvia?
Get up already, dear.
You've been sulking for days.
I'm just not feeling well, Ma.
If you need anything,
just talk to the nannies.
I heard you and Alex talking.
Don't feel down.
There are other ways for you
to have a child.
What do you mean?
I have
a student who's pregnant.
But she doesn't want the baby.
And you want us to adopt her child?
Isn't it a good idea?
You can save the child
and raise it as your own.
Ma, I still haven't given up hope.
If it will come, it will come.
I don't want to force it.
I'm not saying
you should give up on conceiving.
I'm just concerned for you and Alex.
You need something like that
to save your relationship.
Don't you agree?
Ma, Alex and I need to discuss it first.
You said it yourself.
"If it will come, it will come."
Well, it's here,
although not in the way you expected it.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MATTEO] I've done what you've asked.
I took care of the gym where Victor works.
I'm sure they'll shut down soon.
That's not enough.
I need Victor out of that house.
Why? Did something happen?
I now know the reason
why he wanted to live there.
It wasn't to get back at me,
but to be with Juliana.
He wants them to get back together.
Well, it's not like
he can do anything about it.
Alex, Juliana is in love with you now.
I have to find a solution, Matteo.
I can't let him have Juliana back.
She's mine.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[GLASS THUDS]
[YELPS]
Alex. Alex.
Why are you here? How did you get in?
You still use the same lock.
Alex, you shouldn't be here.
Someone might see you. You have to go.
I saw Victor and Abby leave a while ago.
It's just the two of us here.
What are-- Just go, please.
Why?
Is it because you have
gotten back together with Victor?
I don't know what you're talking about.
[SMOOCHES]
Alex!
Alex, it's too risky. Stop it.
Please, Liana, I'm going crazy here.
You're so close, and yet I can't hold you.
I can't go near you. So, please.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[YELPS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh, why are you still here?
I thought you were heading to the gym.
I left my gym bag.
Were-- were you able to drop Abby off?
[CLINKS]
[VICTOR] I dropped her off safely.
You can check her school if you want.
Uh, Victor…
What?
Where-- where are you going?
I'm getting my gym bag.
I left it, remember?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why do you seem so flustered?
Um… it's nothing.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- Take those to the car.
- Yes, ma'am.
Sylvia.
I'm off to work.
Do you need anything?
All right then.
Uh, Ma…
Yes?
I've been thinking about it.
Can we meet with your student?
I've made my decision.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[KATE] Oh.
It looks like I arrived just in time.
Ah, yeah.
We have an event tonight,
so I might be home late.
You can leave Abby to me.
Um… where's Victor?
He was here a while ago.
Maybe he already left.
Could you wait for him
before heading to work?
Don't you have classes today?
My classes start tomorrow, so don't worry.
- [JULIANA] Okay.
- But, you know,
I'm more worried about you.
Why is that?
Isn't this hard for you?
Before, we used to be able
to watch over Abby
whenever you and Victor aren't around
while also keeping an eye on your house.
There's nothing to worry about here.
Plus, the security
in the village is tight.
- [JULIANA] And…
- Why not?
I already moved the car.
You know, Kate,
there's a vacant room upstairs.
You and Grandma can stay there.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
You seem to be making a lot of decisions
by yourself lately.
Don't you want someone here
watching over Abby
and the house?
You're not the only one busy with work.
I have my job at the gym.
It's better to always have someone
in the house.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What's the problem?
It's not like we're letting in strangers.
That's not the point.
You shouldn't be making decisions
by yourself.
You don't know how hard this will be
for Grandma.
She's lived in that house her whole life.
We've got visitors.
Good morning!
- Hi!
Mrs. Lualhati, right?
I'm Mrs. Reyes.
These are Mrs. Uychiat and Mrs. Soldao.
We're from the homeowners' association.
We've met once last year,
when you dropped by the office.
That was last year?
[REYES] Yes, it was around
a year and a half ago.
Oh, I'm Victor, by the way.
- Hi.
- Hi!
- [SOLDAO] Hi.
- I'm Juliana's husband.
We didn't know you were married.
And to such a good-looking guy too!
We thought you were just investing
in this property
and you weren't planning to live in it
since we rarely see you here.
Oh, you see, I just got back from abroad.
[UYCHIAT] Mm.
What brings you here?
I sent you an email
regarding the homeowners' association fee.
What's the fee for?
Um, it will cover the costs
of upgrading our security,
maintaining common areas, pest control,
and repairing our neighborhood streets.
I already emailed her the details,
but I haven't received a reply yet.
How much is the fee?
[REYES] With all of the amendments,
it's 18,000 pesos.
You're the only ones who haven't paid
among all of the homeowners.
Oh, it must have slipped our minds.
We'll pay the fee.
[REYES] No worries.
[UYCHIAT] Maybe we should
get together sometime
so we can introduce you to
the other homeowners.
And… we can get to know each other better.
By the way, you mentioned
that you'd just moved in.
Have you done a house blessing?
If not, we can help you organize.
- Uh, that won't be necessary--
- That's a good idea.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why not?
All right. Let's organize it.
- [REYES] Nice, nice!
- [JULIANA] Mm.
Right?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mama said you don't want to proceed
with your pregnancy.
Where is Ma'am?
Uh… She's still in an
emergency teachers' meeting.
So it's just the two of us for now.
Don't worry, you can trust me.
Here's your order, ma'am. Please, enjoy.
They say caffeine is not good
for pregnant women.
That's why I ordered a chocolate drink
instead, just to be safe.
Please, go ahead.
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CUPS CLINKING]
Uh…
Will you be adopting my child?
I will talk to your parents
and arrange everything.
I am willing to cover the expenses
for your pregnancy.
How?
I'm gonna give you 20,000 allowance
per month,
and I will take care of
your check-ups, vitamins,
and even the delivery.
I see.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I also want to continue my studies
after giving birth.
Yes, of course. No problem.
I will also take care of your tuition fees
until you graduate.
Thank you.
[SYLVIA] Oh, by the way…
I've read this book before.
It's an easy read and very informative.
But, of course, if you have questions,
just call me.
All right.
Thank you, Maricar.
I'll make sure that you'll have
a smooth and healthy pregnancy.
I'll be here for you all the way.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
You went out?
Yes. I just met with someone.
Who?
Mama has this student
who's pregnant.
She's looking for someone
who can adopt her child.
Adopt?
Wait.
You talked to her?
So, you've made up your mind?
Shouldn't we have discussed this together?
I want us to be a complete family, Alex.
We've talked about this.
The two of us are enough.
We both know that's not true.
I want this, Alex.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey.
Where's the matching cufflink?
I left it at the courtroom.
I think. It wasn't intentional.
What a shame.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
I'll just get you another one.
This time, to celebrate our family.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mostly, our agency
provides security services.
I don't have any problem with that.
I'm hardworking, strong-willed,
and resourceful.
I don't come in late or skip work
without a valid reason, sir.
I'll be honest with you, Mr. Lualhati.
You're a bit overage.
Just wait for our call.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Yeah, bro. It looks like a scam.
There's no such company here.
Any job will do.
You know I'm not picky
when it comes to work.
Okay, thanks.
[LOUD THUD]
[VICTOR] Oh my!
Hey, mister. Are you okay?
- [OLIVIA] Mister!
- Wait.
What's going on?
Are you okay? Here you go.
Hold on to this.
You good?
Oh no, you're injured.
My goodness.
V-Victor?
Thanks for your help.
Oh, don't mention it.
Anyway, what brought you here?
I tried to apply for a job
at the agency upstairs,
but I was rejected.
Oh, we have a job opening
- for orderlies.
- Huh?
Basically, you just have
to help transport patients
and assist the nurses.
I hope it's still available.
I'm sure it is.
That's great, but I'm not a nurse.
Don't worry. A degree isn't required.
If you want, I'll accompany you
to the HR department.
I just hope nobody has applied for it yet.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [VICTOR] Hold on.
[RINGING CONTINUES]
Hello?
Huh?
But I have an inter--
All right, fine.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Uh, Liv…
I have to go and fetch Abby.
Is it okay if I come back tomorrow
for the interview?
I might not make it if I come back later.
Okay, it's fine. I'll handle it.
- You'll still accompany me?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, thanks.
- All right, take care.
How can you decide to adopt
without even talking to me, Ma?
Wait, Alex.
I thought you and Sylvia had
discussed everything thoroughly.
If you both have decided to adopt,
there's nothing wrong with that, my dear.
Who knows? The child might
even fix your relationship.
We're fine, Ma.
That's not what I sense, Alex.
Not since your affair blew up.
Are we going to talk about this again, Ma?
Alex, I just want to help.
And I strongly believe
the child can do that.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Daddy!
- My dear! [CHUCKLES]
Yay! Give me your bag.
Mr. Lualhati.
- Hello, ma'am.
- Your daughter is so adorable.
Um, what did she do?
Abby helped her new classmate
to adjust in class.
Your daughter is very nice and friendly.
Her new classmate was able
to fit in well because of her.
She even invited the kid
to come over your house.
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- Huh?
Can we have a sleepover?
- [CHUCKLES]
- I'll ask your Mommy first.
You and your wife surely did
a good job raising her.
I have to go, Abby. I'll see you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow, Teacher.
- Buh-bye.
- Sir.
- Take care, ma'am.
Thank you.
You did well, dear. [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Where's Mommy?
She told me she would fetch me today.
Your Mommy is busy with work.
Really? That's too bad.
I wanted to show both of you
the stars I got on my homework.
You can show it to Daddy first.
I want to show it to both of you
at the same time.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
All right, this is what we'll do.
Since your teacher said that
you did a good job today,
I will…
give you a reward.
Come on.
Here. [CHUCKLES]
Ice cream?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, what's wrong, dear?
Mommy doesn't let me have that.
She said it might be dirty.
What?
We used to eat that all the time.
Wait here. I'll get you my favorite.
- Can I have one in a bun?
- Okay, sir.
- [METAL LID CLINKS]
- I'll get this flavor.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you, sir.
Here you go!
Ice cream in a bun?
Yes.
Go on. Try it, dear.
Wow. That's a big bite.
[CHUCKLES] It's good, right?
[CHUCKLES]
Is it good?
Thank you, Daddy.
I learned something new today.
Let's go, dear.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Is it good?
I've already sent you
all the vitamins you'll need.
The instructions are there too.
Make sure you follow them
to keep the baby healthy, okay?
Also, don't stay up late.
That's bad for you and the baby.
Just let me know
if you need anything else.
Uh, sorry. I'll call you back later.
I've been trying to call you.
I was on the phone with Maricar.
Are you planning to have
this room renovated?
Yes.
I want everything to be ready
before the baby arrives.
Why?
Don't you like the idea?
No, I do. I was just surprised.
I wanted to help you with it.
Really?
Don't worry.
There's still so much to do.
- Let's find time for it.
- Okay.
- [AMELIA] Alex.
- Ma.
Did you get my message earlier?
- What was it about?
- It's about Victor.
He's inviting us to his house blessing.
Why?
He said he wants to make amends.
[SYLVIA SIGHS]
- I don't think--
- We're all going.
Everyone in the neighborhood
knows Victor is my brother.
What will they think if we're not there?
I just think it's better
to avoid any potential trouble.
Mama is right.
What if Victor causes a scene?
Let him be. I'm not afraid.
He won't be able to provoke me.
If he wants to act crazy, let him.
He'll only embarrass himself.
We're all going.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MEMA] Thank you for
the invitation, ma'am.
Good thing you all made it.
Ma'am, this is for you.
A housewarming gift.
Oh, thank you for taking the trouble.
- You're welcome.
- Come in.
- It's lovely.
- [JULIANA LAUGHS]
Wow!
Your house is beautiful, ma'am.
Just like something from a magazine.
Juliana's house is beautiful, isn't it?
- [WOMEN] Yes.
- Too bad our relatives
from the province won't see it.
You know, Pilar,
they won't just be amazed,
they'll also be jealous!
[PILAR] All right, Abby, let's show them.
You know, your dance. Go ahead. Go ahead.
Count me in! I can do that too.
All right then. Show us.
- Oh… Oh… see? Oh?
- That's it!
- Oh! Oh!
- Wow!
- Whoo!
[WILLIAM] I thought this
was a house blessing.
Why does it feel like a circus?
[GUESTS LAUGHING]
Those are my grandma's friends.
That's just how they are.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[GUEST] Hey! Badong is here!
[VICTOR] Okay.
That's enough.
Who are they?
[GUESTS CHATTERING]
Just a moment, okay?
Who's going to sing first?
Olivia, of course.
She has a beautiful voice.
- Yeah!
- That's right.
Victor, come here.
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Where did you even get that?
I rented it. They want to sing karaoke.
This isn't a birthday party, okay?
It's a house blessing.
It's embarrassing for the guests, Victor.
Then we'll start later.
What are they doing here?
I invited them.
I'm glad you could make it.
Hi, Victor.
Juliana.
Uh… Where should I put this?
Give it to me.
Thank you.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Looks like we're late, huh?
Oh, not really.
We're still waiting for the priest.
Ah…
But why does it seem like
some guests are already drunk?
Not really.
They're just having fun.
It's a party after all, right?
[ALEX] Uh, Victor.
Thank you for inviting us.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[VICTOR] You're welcome.
Um, let's go. Come inside.
Victor, what did you do?
Why did you invite them here?
Did I do something wrong?
They're family, aren't they?
Don't make a fool out of me.
You and Alex aren't
having an affair, right?
It's just my imagination
that you're together.
It's all in my head.
Why are you so afraid now?
Because you always assume things.
I'm trying to avoid conflict, Victor.
Can't you see that?
Or are you just afraid of what I'll say?
What do you want?
Do you want me to tell everyone
that we're breaking up, huh?
It's up to you.
Just make sure you don't exclude Alex
from the story.
Go ahead and tell everyone,
even your grandmother.
Are you insane?
Liana, are you guys fighting?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
We're just talking.
May the presence of the Lord
guide the family to foster
understanding, harmony, empathy,
and above all, a deep sense
of love within their home.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Okay?
- All right. [CHUCKLES]
Oh, Grandpa.
I got you food
so you won't have to line up.
- What about you?
- It's fine. I can manage.
And Jimboy can manage just fine too.
- [BADONG] I'll eat outside.
- [OLIVIA CHUCKLES]
- You can do it yourself.
- Gee, thanks.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Auntie Liv?
Oh, Abby. How are you?
Let's play.
What do you want to play?
- Let's play boxing.
- Boxing?
Have you practiced? I might knock you out.
[CHUCKLES]
Daddy has been teaching me.
- Game?
- Game!
Punch hard.
- Mm! Wow, you're strong.
- [CHUCKLING]
You've learned well.
Go on. One more, one more.
Mm. [CHUCKLES]
- You're so good--
- Abby, dear?
Didn't you say you want ice cream?
The dessert bar is already open.
- You should go there.
- Okay, Mommy.
Auntie Liv, let's play again later.
All right. [CHUCKLES]
Um, Olivia, right?
Thank you for helping Victor
get the job at the clinic.
- Thank you.
- Oh. [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Don't mention it. I'm happy
I was able to help Victor.
[INHALES DEEPLY] I know that
he's doing everything he can
to provide for you and Abby.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You know what?
Even before, I remember how
he'll always sacrifice
for the people he loves.
Victor isn't the only one
who has sacrificed a lot.
Isn't that how a relationship
is supposed to be?
[CHUCKLES] You know,
it's not about who made more sacrifices.
It's not a competition.
You should be supporting each other.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY] Excuse me.
Geez, I look haggard now.
This is harder than our actual job.
It's okay. It's not like
we do this every day.
I remember I organized a party
while working on our presentation.
Do you need anything?
Need any help?
Uh…
We're good, Sylvia.
We can manage.
Thank you.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UTENSILS CLATTERING]
You know, this is my first time here.
You should give me a tour, Juliana.
Um, a tour?
Sure.
But we're still busy right now.
Maybe we can do it later.
You should've called me
so I could've helped you
decorate the house.
But don't worry.
I'll send you a new set of tableware.
We're also renovating our house.
We're preparing for something,
and Alex and I are so excited.
What-- what do you mean?
Well, I don't want to jinx it.
All I can say is that I can finally
give Alex what he has always wanted.
I'm sure you know what it is.
Anyway, it seems you don't need help here.
I'll go now. Okay?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [LADIES CHUCKLING]
- Oh, he's here.
Let me introduce you to my brother.
[CHUCKLING]
Victor!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I want to introduce you to our neighbors.
Oh, we've already been introduced.
Ah, yes. We've heard that you're a boxer.
Hm. Are you like Manny Pacquiao?
No.
Manny's on a whole other level.
My brother can't compare to him.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know what? After his boxing career,
he became a seaman.
[SOLDAO] Really?
My husband is also a seaman.
Are you a captain? Engineer?
He was a rust chipper.
Excuse me.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey, Alex. I don't think…
they know what the actual work is.
My job was to scrape off rust manually
to prevent corrosion.
[CLICKS TONGUE] I guess
that's why my biceps got bigger.
See?
Here, feel it. It's hard, isn't it?
[SOLDAO] Being a boxer really suits you.
Do you give free lessons?
We're getting tired of doing Zumba.
[VICTOR] Good thing you asked.
I actually teach boxing.
If you want,
we can start today or tomorrow.
Oh, and my boxer friends are also here.
Hey!
- Hey, Victor.
- Hey.
Those guys also teach boxing.
Don't try to overcharge them.
But then, I get it.
It's hard to raise a family
nowadays, isn't it?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come on, bro.
[VICTOR] Don't worry about us.
We're getting by.
That's one of the things
I learned from boxing.
Boxers don't back down from
any fight in the ring
or in life.
[REYES] What about you, Alex?
Do you also know how to box?
- Yeah, I do.
- [LAUGHS MOCKINGLY]
[ALEX] Our father taught us
when we were young.
But Victor was his favorite child,
so he let him do whatever he wanted.
He was a troublemaker.
But it's okay.
It was my choice
to choose a different path.
And now, I'm a lawyer
for the rest of my life.
You see, with boxing…
you can't really do it forever.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[VICTOR] Oh! Now that everybody's here,
will you all please gather around?
First of all, I want to
thank you all for coming.
And I want to give
a special thanks to some people here.
Without them,
we wouldn't have been able
to move into this house.
So, Sylvia and Alex…
thank you very much
for helping Juliana get this house.
[SIGHS] I really didn't expect you to
do that, so thank you very much.
- [APPLAUSE]
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, come on. Can we get a kiss?
- [MAN 1] Yeah!
- [GUESTS] Kiss!
- [MAN 2] Kiss! Kiss!
- [WOMAN] That's right!
[MAN 3] Kiss!
- [GUESTS CHEERING]
- [APPLAUSE]
[VICTOR] Hold on. Where's my wife?
Come here.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Victor! Victor, stop.
- Come with me, Liana.
- Come on. Don't be shy.
- [MEMA GUSHING]
Looks like my wife is getting jealous.
Victor, that's enough.
Are you jealous?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [WHISPERING] Victor.
- [BREATHES DEEPLY]
I think my wife wants you all
to tease us too,
so she can also get a kiss.
[GUESTS] Kiss! Kiss!
- [MAN 4] Just one kiss!
- Mm?
[MAN 2] Do it, Victor!
- [JULIANA] Victor.
- They said we should kiss.
- [GUESTS SQUEALING]
- Come on.
- [WOMAN SQUEALS]
- [GUESTS CHEERING]
- [APPLAUSE]
[MAN 4] Nice one, Victor!
[MEMA] That's so romantic!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[VICTOR] This way. Those are my co-boxers.
- Hey, Lei.
- [LEI] Hey.
[VICTOR] Attend to these ladies.
This is Lei, Leo, Kurt, and John.
This is Mister Badong, the gym owner.
- [BADONG] Hello.
- [VICTOR] Olivia, our PT.
She's his granddaughter.
She studied in the US.
And that's Jimboy.
Liana, how long will your annulment take?
It's a lengthy process.
But I'm doing everything I can
to expedite it.
You know, I just don't understand.
If you're separating,
why are you still living under one roof?
Victor is fighting it in court.
He says he wants to fix our relationship.
Does that mean he wants
to get back together with you?
Why do you have so many questions, Kate?
It's just…
It feels like I've seen this before
with Mama and Papa.
It's like a replay of everything.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
Isn't this hard for you, Liana?
Of course it is.
But sometimes,
Victor and I get along well.
He's kind to me.
Sweet, just like…
in the early days of our marriage.
But there are times when…
You saw what he did earlier, right?
That's why it's scary to be around
someone paranoid.
I mean, why would
he suspect that you and Alex
were having an affair?
Look. Alex and Sylvia
look so happy together.
I even heard that
they're planning to adopt a baby.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Is there a problem?
Problem?
You said we needed to talk.
I just want to know if you're okay.
When were you planning on telling me
that you and Sylvia are going to adopt?
Well?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Maybe Victor was right.
You're only leading me on.
What do you mean?
Alex, I broke my family apart
to be with you.
And yet here you are,
fixing things with your family and Sylvia.
Be honest with me.
Do you really plan on leaving Sylvia?
It's Sylvia who wants to adopt, not me.
I was just forced into it because of Mama.
You're just saying that.
We both know how much you want
to have kids of your own.
I'm not pursuing that anymore.
You can't take that back.
Liana.
Please.
I can.
Just trust me. I'll do something about it.
Alex.
- [SMOOCHES]
- [GRUNTS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Juliana?
Hey.
Juliana.
W-What is it, Kate?
Nothing. I saw you going here
and I thought you might need help,
so I followed you.
Uh…
Um…
What were you doing there?
I was looking for something.
What is it? I'll help you look.
No need.
I couldn't find it here.
I guess Victor took it already.
Let's go back inside.
We still have a lot to do.
Come on.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Alex?
Victor, have you seen Alex?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
He's out back.
He was there earlier.
Sylvia.
You should keep an eye on your husband.
Come on, Victor.
I found something the other day.
This belongs to Alex, right?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't know how your relationship
with Alex works,
or why you're keeping his affair
with my wife a secret,
but I'm telling you, Sylvia…
They're still seeing each other.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey, are you using the car?
I need to borrow it to go somewhere.
Why do you seem happy today?
[SIGHS] Because what goes
around comes around.
Aren't you going downstairs?
Grandma's waiting for you.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh. Grandma? Kate?
What… What are you doing here?
We'll be staying here.
W-What?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Put your things down, Grandma.
And…
I'll show you to your room.
[PILAR] Thank you.
Come on, Kate. Follow me.
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS, FADES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ALEX] Sylvia.
Sylvia.
I bought a stroller.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello, Maricar?
Why'd you call?
Is everything okay?
Sorry, ma'am.
I've decided to keep my child.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh, wait, Maricar.
Why?
I'm really sorry.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Alex, our baby.
[SOBS]
Our baby.
[SNIFFLES, SOBS]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
Kate, did Grandma get into
a fight with someone?
Why did you move here all of a sudden?
Why? Don't you want us here?
Uh-- No, that's not it.
I was just curious.
I was with you guys yesterday,
but you didn't mention anything.
I didn't know either.
Grandma just told me
to pack my things earlier.
- Can you finish up here?
- Okay.
I'll take the cooked dish outside.
I found some evidence, Attorney.
I have a video of them on my cell phone.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
All right. I'll be there soon.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PILAR] Liana.
Can we talk?
I'll be back, Grandma. I'll be back.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, taxi!
Taxi!
Follow…
- Follow the red car.
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[ENGINE REVS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Keep going straight, mister.
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
Mister, what happened?
How could we lose him?
Who are we following, ma'am?
Can't you just call him?
So we can find out where he's going.
No, I can't call him.
Just try to find him.
If you do, I'll pay you double.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello, Alex?
Hello.
Alex, it's Victor.
He has evidence against us.
What?!
I heard him talking to his lawyer.
I think he's going there now.
[ALEX] Where are you?
I was following him, but I lost him.
- [KEYS CLATTER]
- [SYLVIA] Where are you going?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh, I'm going to the office.
I have an urgent meeting.
About what?
I thought you were going with me
to talk to Maricar.
We could still change her mind.
I'll be back.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DRIVER] Should I go straight ahead
or turn right, ma'am?
[JULIANA] Um… Turn right, mister.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mister, please pull over.
[KNOCKING]
Are you following me?
What are you talking about?
Last time I checked,
this street was a public place.
Why are you here? Where are you going?
This isn't the way to Mister Badong's gym.
- I have an important meeting.
- [PHONE CHIMES]
I need to go somewhere. Take me there.
No. Do it another time.
I have much more important things to do.
Besides, you already have a cab.
- Thief!
- Juliana!
- Juliana! Give it back!
- Help me!
- Give me that!
- Help! Thief!
- Thief!
- Juliana!
- Cut it out!
- Thief!
Let go of me!
You're causing a scene here.
I'm not! She's my wife!
- She took my phone! Juliana!
- Call the safety officer!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THUDS]
- [GRUNTING]
- [THUDS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Excuse me, sir. Can we talk to you?