[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why the hell did you do that?!
[PHONE THUDS]
I'm sorry.
I let my anger take over.
If you had just lent me the car,
none of this would have happened.
Come on, Juliana!
You think you can fool me into believing
that it was just about the car?
Huh?!
You broke my phone
because you don't want
the truth to come out!
I don't know what you're talking about.
What the heck?!
Please, Victor, enough!
Stop it!
What is it that you want?
To get even? To hurt me? What?!
You really think I will do nothing
after everything that's happened?
You and Alex didn't just betray me,
you ganged up on me!
Even Mom! And Sylvia!
You all ruined my dignity!
If you had just accepted the situation,
none of this would have happened!
Why is it so hard for you to understand?
Your mother was also a mistress, right?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Go inside, baby.
What's happening?
[KATE] Um…
Let them talk to each other, baby.
Sometimes, parents need to do that.
You know, to be able to say how they feel.
So they can fix their problems.
But…
Why are they fighting?
I don't really know either.
What?
Is that why you cheated on me, huh?!
You think I will just accept that
because of what my mother did?
What kind of reasoning is that?
Is that what you will teach our child?
Answer me!
Fine!
I'll give you what you want.
But Abby will stay with me!
I won't let her grow up
with a woman like you!
You know why?
Because you're a good-for-nothing mother!
Take back what you said!
That's not true! Take it back!
Victor! Juliana!
Stop it! You're always
at each other's throats!
You don't even care
if your child can hear you!
Enough!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
He made a promise to the fairy
that he wouldn't lie anymore.
Oh.
Getting sleepy?
Well then, go to sleep, dear.
Let me take you to your bed.
[GRUNTS]
Daddy, wait.
What's wrong, dear?
Are you and Mommy fighting because of me?
- [SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
- What?
I heard you earlier.
What made you think it's because of you?
Because I insisted that
we stay together in this house,
even though Mommy is not okay with it.
- Dear.
- I thought you would
patch things up
if we all lived here.
But I was wrong.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
You two just fight even more.
Dear…
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Don't blame yourself
for what's happening, okay?
Your mom and I
just don't agree on some things.
Can't the two of you fix it?
What can I do to help you patch things up?
Please don't fight anymore.
Come here.
[GRUNTS]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HUFFING]
You told Maricar to back out, didn't you?
We're not above the law, Ma.
That's child trafficking.
It's clear as daylight.
[HUFFING]
Don't give me that daylight crap,
or I might just lose my cool with you.
Since when did you consider the law?
When you and Juliana fool around,
you always get away with it, right?
I'm doing everything I can
to fix your relationship with Sylvia,
and yet you keep screwing it up!
You're just making things complicated, Ma.
So, you don't want complications, huh?
Is that why you're sleeping
with your brother's wife?
Having an affair will do you no good.
And remember, karma bites back harder.
You are happy now
because you have them both.
But one day, you're going to wake up
with neither of them in your life.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You're fighting again.
I told you, Grandma.
Our relationship can't be fixed.
I guess so,
considering what I discovered.
By the way, thank you
for earlier, Grandma.
For coming to my rescue.
If it weren't for you…
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
…there'd be no end to our arguments.
That's too bad.
You had to stop arguing.
If not,
I might have done something worse.
To Victor?
- To you!
- [JULIANA GASPS]
You are such a liar!
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
I know why you and Victor
are always arguing!
It's all because of you!
You're the one
who's been having an affair, Juliana!
who's been cheating shamelessly!
You and Alex!
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't tell me you fell for that, Grandma.
Do you really believe Victor?
There's no truth to that.
Is that so?
[SCOFFS] Huh?
Hold on.
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
There's no truth to it? Then explain this.
You're still going to deny it?
Huh?
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PILAR] Watch it!
Explain this to me, Liana!
Huh?
Don't even think of denying this!
Huh?!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't you dare tell me
that you are just talking here
because you're clearly kissing!
I saw everything you did!
Grandma.
H-How…
"How?!" "How?"
That's all you can say?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I asked you several times, Liana.
I even defended you.
And yet you lied so many times!
Alex and I love each other, Grandma.
- [GASPS]
- I love Alex, not Victor.
Alex promised he would marry me,
and that we would correct
all our mistakes.
[JULIANA SNIFFLES]
That's why I asked Victor
for an annulment.
Alex said…
he's going to leave Sylvia.
[GASPS] You're such a fool!
And you really believed him?!
How could you let some man fool you, huh?!
That's exactly what happened
to your mother!
She went crazy for a man
and left her children!
I'm not like her, Grandma.
I will never leave my child.
You're just saying that now.
You'll go crazy over him.
You'll be made a fool of because of him.
I have to put an end to this.
I'm going to tell Victor.
Grandma. Grandma.
Grandma, don't.
Please.
I'm begging you.
This will work out
for all of us in the end.
Please, Grandma. Don't tell Victor.
I'm begging you, Grandma.
Please wait until
our annulment is finalized.
[SNIFFLES] Please.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[VICTOR EXHALES DEEPLY]
[CAR APPROACHING]
Why is Abby still here? Where's Liana?
I'm taking Abby to school today.
I'll do it.
It's rush hour.
It'll be hard to book a taxi.
You can come if you want.
Abby?
Abby, I think I forgot to check
if the door's locked.
Can you check it?
A wild animal might get in.
Okay.
All right, go on.
I can take my daughter to school.
Your pride won't get you anywhere.
I'm just concerned about her.
She's going to be late.
She's suffering because
of her father's stupidity.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
There are still seven minutes
before the taxi gets here.
You want to fight within
those seven minutes, huh?
Are you game?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[AMELIA] Sylvia…
I really tried to convince Maricar,
but she's already made up her mind.
I just don't understand
why she changed her mind.
You know, I have a suspicion.
I was thinking that maybe
a family member talked to her.
Well, teens nowadays are easily convinced
about these matters.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
W-What's your plan now, dear?
[CLICKS TONGUE] I don't know, Ma.
I feel like we've been facing
a lot of misfortunes lately.
[OBJECTS CLATTER]
And it doesn't help that Liana
and her family are close by.
I already told you
not to worry about that.
Don't mind them. Leave it to me.
I'll do something
to drive them out of here.
Uh, Ma…
Can I have a moment alone?
Oh, sure.
I'll just be outside, okay?
Thank you.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
You should keep an eye on your husband.
Come on, Victor.
By the way, I found something
in the house the other day.
This belongs to Alex, right?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
I don't know how your relationship
with Alex works,
or why you're keeping his affair
with my wife a secret.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
Hello, Dad?
I need to ask you a favor.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Thank you.
Hey!
- [VICTOR GRUNTS]
- [OLIVIA GIGGLES]
- It's just me!
- Don't do that.
- I almost punched you.
- Come on!
This looks nice.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[OLIVIA] This is the gym area
for heavy physical activities.
And then, this is the visiting area
for our patients' visitors.
Hmm…
Oh, this room is for checkups.
Our doctors and nurses can be found here.
So, if we ever need them,
this is where we go.
And then this is our rehabilitation area.
You'll find me here most of the time.
Are you excited?
Well, I'm a bit nervous, but I'm ready.
[OLIVIA] You can do this!
[VICTOR] Oh, slowly.
Slowly, slowly.
- Can you do it?
- Yes.
All right, just take it slow and steady.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [MAN GRUNTS]
- There we go.
All right, sir.
Kindly lift your right foot.
Now, lift the other one carefully.
[KIDS CHATTERING,
SHOUTING IN THE DISTANCE]
Abby.
Oh, hey. Give me your bag, dear.
[SNIFFLES]
This is for you.
Thank you.
How was your day?
I only scored 80 points
on our quiz earlier.
[SNIFFLES]
- [VICTOR] Eighty?
- [SNIFFLES]
Dear, don't belittle your score.
That's the highest score
I could get in the past too.
- [GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SNIFFLING]
Don't be sad, hm?
We're okay now.
You and Mommy aren't
the only ones fighting.
Mommy and Grandma are fighting too.
- [SNIFFLING]
- You mean Grandma Pilar?
[SNIFFLES] Yes.
I saw them fighting yesterday.
Grandma was crying while talking to Mommy.
[SNIFFLES, BREATH QUIVERS]
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Is that why Grandma left? [SNIFFLES]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Abby?
Do you want me to help you
with your homework
so you can get a high score?
You will do that, Aunt Olivia?
Of course.
And I'll also prepare
your favorite snacks.
Does that sound good?
[OLIVIA] Stop crying, okay?
It's okay, dear.
See? You've got lots of snacks.
You want to eat them?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Sylvia.
I'm glad you're here now.
I talked to your secretary,
but she said you didn't have any
meetings scheduled for today.
Why, did something happen?
Yes.
Your wife has been waiting for you, Alex.
Sorry, but what's happening?
I'm sorry. I wanted it to be a surprise.
Your wife is our newest associate.
Looks like we have
a new power couple in our firm.
What are you doing here?
Oh, don't worry.
I didn't come here to start a fight.
Actually, I want to help you.
That's new.
How long do you plan
to live in this house?
Why don't you ask Victor?
This was his idea.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I think we're on the same page.
Let's go our separate ways, shall we?
I have a solution.
But first,
you have to show me that you've changed
and that you're smart now.
Why didn't you tell me?
It just came to me.
Dad helped me out.
Actually, I was surprised
how fast it went.
I just had to submit my requirements.
That's how it is when you're a nepo baby.
- What?
- Nothing.
Don't you like it?
It's not like that.
Uh, I was just surprised.
I don't want to waste my degree.
I just wanted a change.
Since…
the adoption didn't push through.
Aren't you happy that
we'll be working together?
Won't it be hard for you?
I mean, it's been years
since you last practiced law.
You're here to guide me, right?
Don't worry, Alex.
You won't have any problems with me.
I know how to manage my time,
my work, and my personal life.
I won't neglect my obligations
to you as your wife.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm so excited.
You know, when Victor suggested it,
I was a bit hesitant.
But he's right.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
He's the one who convinced you
to go back to work?
My eyes were opened
to things I had never seen before.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
So I decided to expand my horizons.
I have to go.
I have other things to attend to.
[SMOOCHES]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, by the way…
You misplaced this.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ABBY] Grandma?
Oh…
Grandma, why did you come back here?
You don't have anyone with you.
Uh, dear, I'm just
taking care of something.
Come back to our house, okay?
I'm thirsty, Grandma.
Oh, go to the kitchen
and pour yourself a glass of water.
- Okay.
- You can do it, right?
All right.
I'll just put my stuff down.
[BAG THUDS]
Why did you leave without saying goodbye?
Did you and Juliana have a fight?
[PILAR SIGHS]
It's nothing. We just had
a misunderstanding.
That's normal.
[PILAR SIGHS]
Well, what happened?
Maybe I can help.
But how?
You two can't even get along.
But that doesn't mean
I'll just let your relationship
with Juliana fall apart.
Would you look at that?
Even if you're mad at her,
you're still thinking about her welfare.
I'm just worried about you.
You know that you're like a mom to me.
Victor,
if all your accusations
against Liana are true,
then why are you still together?
Can't you just forgive each other?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
You know, someone asked me earlier
why I still insist on being with Liana.
They said
that it can't be out of spite.
That maybe…
there's a part of me
that wants to be with her.
But how can I just let go
of all the resentment I feel?
How can I forgive Liana
after everything she did?
She ruined the family
I worked so hard to build.
You know how things are
between me and Mama.
All my life, I've just wanted a family.
A family that would complete me.
I thought Liana could give me that.
But instead, she ruined everything.
Victor.
I believe that there's still hope.
Don't give up
even if you only have a tiny bit of love
left for each other.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why did you and Liana fight?
Grandma.
Oh.
Come here.
Help me pack my things.
[PILAR] Come here.
[PILAR] Did you drink some water?
- [ABBY] Yes.
- [PILAR] Come help me.
[AMELIA] You won't have any problems
with this house.
It's spacious, the lighting is good,
and most importantly,
it's very quiet here.
This house is a good buy for you.
[HANDBRAKE CLICKS]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
I think they're here.
[PILAR] Let's go, dear.
[VICTOR] I've got it.
[PILAR] Thank you, Victor.
Did you like what you saw upstairs?
They still haven't seen the backyard.
- [AMELIA] Oh.
- Mommy?
Uh.
Abby, dear.
You were supposed to be home hours ago.
What took you so long?
We went to the gym,
and then we picked Grandma up.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Will you be staying
with us again, Grandma?
[AMELIA CLEARS THROAT]
Dear, greet your Grandma Amelia.
Abby, go wash up upstairs.
I'll be there in a bit.
Come on, dear. I'll help you.
I'll take that upstairs.
Just leave it there.
[PILAR] Thank you, Victor.
What's happening?
Uh, you mentioned you like to cook, right?
- Yes.
- Let's look at the kitchen.
- Okay.
[AMELIA] It's over there.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm selling this house.
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
Hey, Sylvia.
I didn't know you'd gone out.
You fetched Alex from work?
No, Ma.
We're colleagues now.
What do you mean you're colleagues now?
I'll be practicing law again.
Oh, that's good news.
You can put your education to good use.
And you'll get to spend more time
with Alex, right?
Yes!
Exactly!
Right, Alex?
I'll just get changed.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Dear, I have some news for you.
Juliana's selling her house.
They'll be gone soon.
You have nothing to worry about anymore.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Did you bring Abby to the gym again?
Didn't I tell you not to take her there?
I don't see anything wrong with it.
Victor, you're exposing her to strangers.
But you know the people I work with.
Are you saying they're bad people?
Sometimes, those who live in nice houses
are the worst.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you really sure
you want to sell this house?
Yeah.
Because I can't pay
for the mortgage anymore.
Is that the real reason?
I mean, I have a job.
Compared to what you were earning
on the ship,
you think the money you make now
is enough, Victor?
Is anything ever enough for you?
When were you ever content?
Fine!
I'm selfish.
That's what you're trying to say, right?
Why do you think I'm working so hard?
You think that's only for me, huh?
I'm working hard for our daughter!
To give her a good life!
You're not the only one
working hard for her!
The only difference is,
I still make sure
I spend time with our daughter!
You know what?
I'm so tired of you saying
I'm a bad mother
and a worse wife!
You know what? Fine!
I'll just quit my job.
That's what you want, right?
You want me to focus on
taking care of our daughter!
That's all you want me to do!
You think I don't want that? I do!
My life would be easy!
But you have to provide for us!
Now, you have to prove that
you have no shortcomings
as a father and husband!
[CHAIR THUDS, CLATTERS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I prepared new bedsheets for you.
I thought…
you'd need them.
[POUCH ZIPPER CLOSES]
Grandma, thank you for coming back.
[INHALES, EXHALES DEEPLY]
You know, earlier,
I wanted to tell Victor about what I saw.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I wanted to give him the video.
[SIGHS]
But I didn't do it.
It's not because I forgive you.
It's because I believe
you can still patch things up.
Juliana.
You promised you'd spend
your lives together.
That's the essence of marriage.
I don't want you throwing that away
just for your nonsense.
Think about your daughter.
You already got me involved in your lies.
So from now on,
I'll do everything I can
to fix your marriage with Victor.
I won't let you two separate.
[SOMBER MUSIC INTENSIFIES
THEN FADES]
[SPECTATORS CHEERING]
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[REFEREE] Break, break, break.
Back off! Back off!
Back off!
[REFEREE] One… Two…
[SPECTATORS CLAMORING]
Three…
[THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CROWD CLAMORING]
200,000.
So you can have money to buy medicine.
This is only if you agree.
If you don't, no hard feelings.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[CROWD SHOUTING]
[JULIANA SOBBING]
Son…
[SOBBING]
[JULIANA] Ever since Marco died,
I haven't been able to feel
your presence anymore!
You left me all alone!
Are you a captain? Engineer?
He was a rust chipper.
[JULIANA] Then prove that
you have no shortcomings
as a father and a husband!
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [CHAIR CLATTERS]
[CROWD SHOUTING]
[REFEREE] Break! Break! Break!
- Come on!
- Break! Back off!
- One--
- Come on!
- Back off!
- [CROWD SHOUTING]
[REFEREE] Two…
Three…
- [MAN] Get up!
- [REFEREE] Four…
["LABAN PA" BY KZ TANDINGAN
AND JAY R PLAYING]
Six…
- [OPPONENT] Come on!
- Six…
[SHOUTING CONTINUES]
Fight!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [CROWD CHEERING]
[BLOW LANDS]
[CROWD CHEERING, CHANTING]
Yeah!
[CROWD CHANTING] Beast! Beast! Beast!
- [CROWD CHEERING, CLAPPING]
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CROWD CHANTING] Beast! Beast! Beast!
So, are you going to fight again?
I'll think about it.
All right.
Long time no see, Victor.
It's been a while.
I see you're back in the ring.
What do you want?
You're just wasting your talent here.
You still have it in you.
You still have that fire.
Let me help you.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Why should I trust someone
who rigs fights?
Things have changed, Victor.
This time, I'll be your ally.
And you know what I can do
for people who sign with me.
All right?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Alex?
Why are you here?
I've been waiting for you a while.
So, you're selling the house?
I paid the down payment for it.
It gets sold, and then what?
Victor gets half of the sale proceeds?
Your mother convinced me to do it.
I also thought that
if we moved somewhere else,
we could somehow be at peace.
But Victor is against the idea.
Why does he have power over you
all of a sudden?
Why are you letting him decide?
[SCOFFS]
Why are you so pissed?
You both want the same thing.
I just don't want things
to get messy, Alex.
Do you know what Victor did to Sylvia?
He got hold of my cufflink
and he's using that
to put ideas into Sylvia's head.
So that's what you're mad about, huh?
Victor managed to outsmart you
and it's causing you
and Sylvia problems, is that it?
I don't want him
to have anything against me or us!
I'm only worried about us.
Do you know what I hate the most?
He's always taking what's rightfully mine.
That's all he's been doing.
He's tried to steal my family
and my father.
And now you!
I won't let that happen.
Who said I'd let Victor steal me?
Who said you're going to lose me?
Alex, we've already gone through a lot.
I'm not going to throw that away easily.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Have you talked to Grandma Pilar?
Yes.
She said she'll keep the video
to herself, but Alex…
Grandma won't take my side.
She doesn't approve of our relationship.
We don't need their approval, Liana.
What matters is how we feel
about each other.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[DOOR OPENS]
Where's Abby? Is she asleep?
Yeah.
Kate talked to me earlier, Victor.
Our fights have started to affect Abby.
I know.
Victor, please.
I'm begging you.
Never show Abby how mad you are at me.
I've never said anything bad
about you in front of Abby,
and it's not like
I want her to see us fight.
Hold on.
What happened to your face?
What did you get into this time?
I got back into boxing.
[SIGHS DEEPLY] Wait here.
[CABINET DOOR OPENS]
[OBJECT RATTLES]
[CABINET DOOR CLOSES]
Here. Clean your wound.
Thanks.
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
[VICTOR SIGHS DEEPLY]
["ANO'NG NANGYARI SA ATING DALAWA"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING]
Let me do it.
[VICTOR SIGHS DEEPLY]
["ANO'NG NANGYARI SA ATING DALAWA"
INSTRUMENTAL CONTINUES]
[VICTOR INHALES DEEPLY, SIGHS]
Apply an ice pack on this
so it won't get swollen.
I don't want Abby
to see your bruised face.
Anyway, I'm surprised that even now,
you don't know how to clean wounds.
It's because of you.
You're the reason why
I never learned how to treat myself.
Because you were always there
to treat my wounds for me.
After that, we would always eat
at your favorite restaurant.
What was your usual order again?
Two-piece chicken?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
You'd even go for unlimited rice, right?
Ow, that hurts. [CHUCKLES]
Our life was happier then.
Life was just so simple.
You were the only one
who was happy back then.
Because you were surrounded
by countless women.
Women would chase me,
but I never gave them attention.
It's done.
Wait.
[GROANING]
Here's the prize money I got
from winning earlier.
Use it for the expenses here at home.
["ANO'NG NANGYARI SA ATING DALAWA"
INSTRUMENTAL CONTINUES]
Get some rest.
[BADONG] I didn't take you in
and train you again
just so you could get beaten up
in underground boxing!
Nothing bad happened to me.
And I won't let myself lose.
What do you think will happen
if people find out that
you're involved in illegal fights?
I didn't do it just
for the heck of it, okay?
I needed the money. And I did that
because I wanted to help
with your problems here.
Victor, Grandpa, stop it.
Your tempers won't get you anywhere.
Victor, I know what you can do.
That's why I can't accept
what you're doing.
You're wasting everything
you've worked hard for!
What are you doing here?
I just want to know if
you've thought about my offer.
Victor, I assure you,
I will bring your career to new heights.
Have you forgotten
what he did to you before?
That man ruined your career!
I didn't ruin his career.
I gave him a chance
to save his son's life.
What happened after that
was out of my hands.
And now, I'm giving him another chance
to reclaim what is rightfully his.
Victor, I will clear your name.
I will find you formidable opponents
who will bring you
back into the spotlight.
I will fix your image
so you can regain your reputation
in the boxing world.
You won't have to wait long.
And I'll also get you involved
in international fights.
Victor, you deserve better
than waiting for so long
and wasting away in the underground.
It's an 80-20 split.
In addition to that,
I will give you a signing bonus
of 100,000 pesos.
You'll receive it right away.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Two hundred thousand pesos.
And I can leave your management
whenever I want.
What's the point
of having a contract, then?
I need to be sure that
I can trust you first.
Fair enough.
But I get 30% commission.
I need to earn as well.
You get 25%.
And I get to choose who joins Team Beast.
You won't regret having me.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
You won't sell the house?
I'm sorry.
I've already found a prospective buyer.
They're willing to pay
down payment in cash.
I hope you won't embarrass me.
Victor doesn't want to sell it.
Since when did you listen to Victor?
I'm just thinking about my daughter.
I don't want her to keep moving houses.
Besides, she likes it here.
How ambitious.
What did you say?
Oh, you didn't hear it?
I'll speak louder then.
I said you're ambitious!
Drop the act.
You refuse to sell this house
because you want
to appear well-off, don't you?
That's what you want, right?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Back then, you thought
Victor's boxing career
would make you rich.
But it didn't work out.
That's why you're going after my son now.
You've wanted him right from the start.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You think I'm in a relationship with him
because I want his money?
Well,
could you afford this house
with your salary alone?
And of all places,
you chose to move close to their house.
Do you think you're
on the same level as Sylvia?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I've never asked for money from Alex.
If I was only after his money,
I wouldn't ask for just a house.
How dare you! You really have no shame!
You're in my house
and you dare accuse me
of senseless things?
Please leave.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [VICTOR GROANS]
- Where are we going?
- Just come with us.
- Let me carry that.
This is for your daughter.
And for you and Victor as well.
Let's celebrate since Daddy
is going to be a boxer again.
[VAN DOOR CLOSES]
That's right, dear.
So where are we going?
And why are we bringing so many things?
How many days are we staying there?
We haven't even left yet,
and you're already
thinking about going home.
Stop asking questions. Let's just go.
- [ENGINE HUMMING]
- Let's go.
- Got everything?
- Yeah.
Are you leaving?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- We're going on a vacation.
- Auntie Sylvia! Auntie Sylvia!
Do you want to join?
As much as I want to, I can't.
Your Uncle Alex and I
need to go to the office.
Next time, okay?
Okay.
You have work on Saturdays?
Alex needs to meet an important client.
You should get going.
We don't want to bother you.
My family and I are going
to have some fun. Let's go.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, do you want to join us?
Too bad there's no room left for you.
Bye.
[VAN DOOR CLOSES]
[VICTOR EXHALES SHARPLY]
We can't leave if you don't move your car.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ABBY] Wow! It's so nice here,
Auntie Kate!
- [KATE CHUCKLES]
- [JULIANA] Be careful.
The ground is slippery.
[KATE] I told you it was nice here!
[SYLVIA] Are you okay?
Of course. Why?
You've seemed upset ever since
we saw Victor and his family.
Come on, Sylvia.
[SYLVIA] Okay.
Maybe I misread it.
But I really do hope
they're having a good time.
I hope they fix
whatever issues they're having.
Let's not… talk about them.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's go out.
Let's not waste the day.
Why are you suddenly being sweet?
When was I ever not sweet to you?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
- Like this?
I'm sure you'll learn how to swim soon.
Look at you. You're doing a great job!
Let's take a break, Abby.
You can ask grandma for some fruit juice.
Hold on. Wait for Daddy. [GRUNTS]
- [MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Oh. Uh, I'm sorry.
It's okay. How about you?
Uh… Okay. I'm okay. Thank you.
[WOMAN 1] You come here often?
[WOMAN 2] We are actually new
here in the Philippines
and we are looking for someone
that can tour us around.
[WOMAN 1] So far, I love the Philippines.
Especially the men.
- They're all very good-looking.
- Yes, I agree.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- I'm sorry, ma'am, but…
I am not available.
- Oh.
- Ouch. Okay.
What a loss.
- Bye.
- See you.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES, STOPS]
Having fun?
Huh?
Looks like you had fun back there.
You should've gone with them.
Are you jealous?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I've never given another woman
the time of day.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Abby.
I didn't know picnics were this fun.
Your grandma and Aunt Kate
do know how to make it special.
Come on, let's eat.
It's fun having picnics,
especially in spots like this,
where the air is fresh
and the scenery is amazing.
Did you and Mommy
use to go on picnics too?
Yeah, Abby.
Really? Where did you go for picnics?
Was it as beautiful as this place?
Tell me the story, Daddy, Mommy.
Um…
["ANO'NG NANGYARI SA ATING DALAWA"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING]
Well, Mommy liked being alone back then.
I'd always go to this place
not many people know about.
Turns out, your daddy
went to that place too.
I used to spend
a lot of time alone as well.
And when I went to that place one day…
I met your mommy.
That's where we became friends.
I realized then that
I didn't have to be alone.
I could have someone
to share my life with.
Your daddy and I would always meet
at that same spot.
That's where we had our picnics.
It was like all the problems
in the world vanished…
when we were together.
Is that where you fell in love
with each other?
["ANO'NG NANGYARI SA ATING DALAWA"
CONTINUES PLAYING]
E-Excuse me. I'll just go
find Grandma, okay?
Later.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you okay?
- Liana!
- [ABBY] Mommy!
- Mommy!
- Liana?
- Liana!
- Mommy!
[CRYING] Mommy!
- Wait, Abby.
- Mommy!
[PILAR] What happened?
I don't know. She suddenly
felt dizzy and fainted.
[PILAR] My god.
- Call a doctor now.
- [ABBY SOBS] Mommy.
[PILAR] Kate, hurry!
- Let me do it.
- [ABBY] Mommy!
[PILAR] Put a damp towel on her.
It might be a heat stroke.
[VICTOR] Got it. Liana?
[ABBY] Mommy! Wake up!
- [VICTOR] Liana?
- Mommy.
Is there no doctor here?
[ABBY SOBBING] Mommy!
- [VICTOR] Liana?
- [PILAR] Liana.
Mommy.
A-Abby?
Mommy, are you okay?
[JULIANA] Why? What happened? Sorry…
[PILAR] It's okay, Abby.
You fainted.
Huh?
Oh, Abby, come here.
Why are you crying?
[ABBY SOBBING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Mommy, Daddy…
- [VICTOR] Dear…
- Grandma said…
that dinner is almost ready.
Oh, okay, let's go.
Did you have fun?
Yes, I had so much fun.
Oh, before I forget,
let's take a family picture.
Don't you want to do it later
when the food is ready?
Let's take it now
so it's just the three of us.
Come on.
[GROANS SOFTLY]
All right.
- [HUFFS]
- [EXHALES SHARPLY]
Aren't you tired yet, dear?
You take the picture, Mommy.
My arms are too short.
[GIGGLES]
All right then.
- You do have short arms.
- Let's see.
But they're long for your age.
Your classmates have shorter arms.
[GIGGLES]
All right. Let's take a photo.
Am I doing this right?
- Oh. [CHUCKLES]
- Oh.
[SHUTTER CLICKS]
There you go.
Look at that.
- [SMOOCHES]
- [CHUCKLES]
["PAGBIGYANG MULI"
BY ANGELINE QUINTO PLAYING]
[TRAFFIC NOISE]
- Whee!
- [PILAR] Hey, careful.
- [ABBY, KATE GIGGLING]
Mommy! Daddy!
- Hmm?
- Yes?
Thank you again.
[CHUCKLES]
Did you have fun, dear?
I had so much fun.
[CHUCKLES]
I hope we can do it again.
I wish we could be happy
like this every day.
Let's go back there sometime.
Dear, oh, dear.
It will be a hassle for Kate's friend.
[PILAR] Give me your bag.
We'll take it upstairs.
Thank you, Grandma.
You know, it's better
if you get changed now.
Take a little rest,
and then we'll work on
your assignments, okay?
Okay, Mommy.
Look at you wanting to go swimming again
even though you haven't finished
your assignments yet.
- Hmm?
- Yes?
I love you both so much forever and ever!
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC STING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[CROWD REACTING]
[BADONG] Back him into a corner.
[JIMBOY] Victor, recover!
[CROWD CLAMORING]
You can do it!
- [JIMBOY] Go, Victor.
- [BADONG] Focus.
[CROWD CHEERING]
[REFEREE] Go. Fight!
[ALEX] Well? Did you have fun?
You looked so happy with Victor.
[SCOFFS] What do you want?
For me to say no to my daughter?
Just be honest.
You wanted it too!
You know,
I don't want to argue with you.
We're not done talking.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You didn't come here to talk, Alex.
You're here to pick a fight!
Isn't that right?
I'm sorry.
I really am.
I'm only acting this way
because I can't be with you.
Do you know how difficult it is
not to be with you?
Even if Victor were gone,
nothing would change.
Sylvia is still there.
I'd still have to wait.
This is what Victor wants.
For us to fight.
And he is succeeding.
He's driving a wedge between us.
Do you really think Victor still has
something to do with our fights?
Because I feel like he doesn't!
Victor has nothing to do with
our fights anymore, Alex.
[SIGHS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[BLOW LANDS]
[BADONG] Fight!
[JIMBOY] Watch your left!
["LABAN PA" BY KZ TANDINGAN
AND JAY R PLAYING]
[JIMBOY] Body! Body! Body!
[CROWD CHEERING]
[BLOWS LANDING]
- [BADONG] That's it!
- [JIMBOY] Yeah! Let's go!
[CROWD CHEERING]
[BLOWS LANDING]
Okay. Okay.
Steady. Body! Body!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [CROWD CHEERING]
[THUDS]
[CROWD CHEERING]
Let's go!
One, two, three, four…
five, six, seven, eight, nine…
- No, no, no.
- ["LABAN PA" CONTINUES]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[JIMBOY] Whoo! You did it! You've won!
[SCREAMS]
- [JIMBOY] You're the beast!
- [BADONG] Good job!
["LABAN PA" CONTINUES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- [VICTOR SIGHS]
- Perfect timing. You're here.
I've already prepared the food.
- Call Abby.
- All right, Grandma.
This will be perfect for our celebration.
Why?
Grandma, I won the fight.
Wow, congrats.
- [RETCHES]
- Hey.
- Oh, you okay?
- [PILAR] What's wrong?
Uh. Excuse me for a bit.
[JULIANA RETCHES]
I'll call Abby.
Okay.
[DOCTOR] Based on your ultrasound,
you're about eight weeks pregnant.
Congratulations!
I will just get
your prenatal vitamins, okay?
Excuse me.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Alex.
Alex, what should we do?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I don't know yet.
What?
You still don't know?
But didn't you say
you wanted to make sure?
Well, we are totally sure now.
Why don't you know yet?!
Come on, Alex.
This baby will be
the greatest evidence of our affair.
Alex, say something.
Why are you so awfully quiet?
I'm telling you everything
because you're part of this.
Now, tell me…
Tell me what to do
because I don't know what I should do.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS SHARPLY]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]