L-Let's talk about this
somewhere else, not here.
No! Let's talk here
so your son can hear everything!
Well?!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Fine.
- [PAPER RUSTLING, RIPPING]
Do you think tearing that
will change the truth?
The truth is… you're a mistress!
And you're a bastard!
Shut up, will you? Shut up.
- [SLAP]
- Shut up!
What?!
All my life, you've made me think
I was a product of sin.
That my mother committed a sin.
But the truth is, you're the mistress!
Stop it!
[VICTOR] What?
You want to know the truth?
Ask your mother!
Let's talk at home.
- Not here!
- Why? You're ashamed, huh?
Were you ashamed
when you took everything from my mother?
How could you stomach that?
How could you fool all of us?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
What's the truth, Ma?
Tell me, what's the truth?!
Ma!
What's the truth?!
Alex, I only did it because…
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Victor.
Victor, son.
From now on, you're going to live here.
Behave yourself, okay?
[SMOOCHES]
Oh. Amelia.
This is Victor.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[POUNDING NOISES]
[YOUNG VICTOR] That's a nice toy.
Hey! Don't touch that!
Do you know how to box?
Yes, I want to become a boxer like Papa.
- Are you good at it?
- Yes.
[MAKES WHOOSHING SOUNDS]
See? I'm good, right?
Alex.
Come here, son.
Listen.
His name is Victor.
He's your brother.
From now on,
he will stay with us.
You now have a training buddy, Alex.
Isn't that great? Come here, son.
[SMOOCHES]
I won't ask for anything more, Amelia.
All I want
is for you to be nice to Victor.
You know moneyis tight.
Why did you bring him here?
Doesn't his mother have any relatives?
No, she doesn't.
But I'd rather be with my son.
There were barely any people
at Leonor's funeral.
Don't mention her name.
It's not necessary.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Amelia.
Victor is a good kid.
It won't be hard to raise him.
Does he know?
We don't talk about it.
What about Alex?
He won't agree to this.
Amelia.
If it were up to me,
I'd want them to become friends.
I want them to get along as brothers.
That's all I ask, Amelia.
When are we getting married?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[YOUNG ALEX]
I didn't know you could box.
Who taught you?
Papa taught me.
How about we do some sparring?
Sure.
[SOFT THUDS]
Wait. Time out!
Boxers don't take breaks.
[AMELIA GASPS] Alex!
Alex!
Come on, dear.Stand up.
Get up, son.
What did you do?!
We were just doing some sparring.
I didn't mean to hurt him.
Why did you challenge Alex
to a sparring match?
I didn't. He did.
How dare you talk back at me!
It's okay, Ma. I just lost my balance.
No, dear. I know what I saw.
I want you to stop doing boxing, okay?
Do you understand?
Let them do boxing.
Boxing isn't for you.
[BADONG] Amelia!
Hold your T-shirt.
[KNOCKING ON METAL GATE]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey.
- Amelia.
- Yes?
It's Jessie.
What about him?
He suffered a heart attack
in the middle of the fight.
What?!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[AMELIA] Hey, Victor.
Now that your father is gone,
you better know yourplace here.
You'll help around the house
and take care of Alex.
Things are not the same anymore.
You can't just play as you wish.
Your father died before we got
the chance to get married.
I only did it because…
I didn't want you to feel
inferior to Victor.
[VICTOR SCOFFS]
I was just protecting you, dear.
Do you understand me?
I did it to protect you.
Alex.
Alex, hear me out first.
It's not--
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Is this what you want?
For me and Alex to fight?
You ungrateful bastard!
- You're ungrateful!
- Tell me.
Is that how you see me?
The child you took in
who should feel indebted to you?
I spent more than the cost
of that property to raise you!
What happened to the money
that Papa left us?
You used it all on Alex's education.
What happened to the money
that Papa left for me?
Alex is smarter than you.
You're nothing but a troublemaker.
And you got married early
so you didn't finish your studies.
You're no different than Liana.
Don't even compare me to that woman!
Why are you so mad at her?!
Yes, I was the mistress.
I was your dad's mistress,
but he loved me.
You're just afraid of your own ghosts!
When your father courted me,
I didn't know he was already married.
Our situation is different.
But why are you punishing me
for Papa's mistakes?
Huh?!
You never treated me as your son.
But I treated you like my mother!
I could have moved out of the house
if I'd wanted to.
I was old enough to.
But I didn't do it
because I considered you as family.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I waited for you to have
a change of heart,
but it never happened.
And even if I had known
all of that back then,
I would still have seen you as my mother.
But now, I don't care anymore
whether you accept me or not
because you kept reminding me
and throwing it in my face
that I was a bastard.
That it was all my mother's fault.
You even made me beg for
what should rightfully be mine!
Mine! They are mine!
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I don't care anymore.
And this time…
I'll now claim what I deserve.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Victor.
- [MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
All my life,
I've been living a lie, Liana.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Alex…
You didn't do anything wrong.
Her lies don't invalidate
who you are as a person…
and everything
you've achieved in your life.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
And most importantly,
it will not change my love for you.
I will make sure our child never feels
what I'm feeling right now.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
No one will ever call our child a bastard.
[ALEX] Liana, I promise you…
I will marry you.
I love you.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
We just need to get Victor
out of our lives.
Because that's the only way…
for us to be free and happy.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JULIANA EXHALES HEAVILY]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING]
- [BANGING]
- [SCREAMS IN ANGER]
- [STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Grandma?
Victor, we need to meet.
Okay. Why?
I have something to give you,
but it has to be in person.
Where are we meeting?
At the park, near the gym.
I'm on my way.
All right. Take care.
Grandma, you're leaving?
Uh, I won't take long. I'll be back soon.
You're meeting with Victor?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [AMELIA] Alex, son…
- [THUD]
Believe me.
I didn't do it to hurt you.
I would lie for you.
I'm begging for your forgiveness, son.
I will do anything.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Son--
[SOBBING]
Maybe it's best
if you go back to your own house.
After all, you sacrificed a lot
for that house, right?
Son…
I hope you understand that I only did that
to get on Victor's good side.
I'm a bastard because of you!
Shouldn't you have sympathy for me?!
You fell in love with a married woman!
My relationship with Juliana
has nothing to do with your mistakes!
Nothing!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, Kate. You're home.
No one was around when I got here
so I just made some snacks.
Where's Grandma?
She left. Didn't you know?
Why? Where did she go?
I heard her talking to Victor.
She said she had to see him
to give him something.
What time did she leave?
Just a while ago.
Did she say where she was going?
They'll meet at the park
near Victor's gym.
Why?
Not now, Sylvia. I'm in a hurry.
[YELPS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why?
You're off to see Alex again, aren't you?
Didn't he leave just now?!
You think I don't know?
You really can't get enough
of him, can you?
In case you've forgotten,
you're on my property, Sylvia.
So keep your mouth shut.
If there's something
that should be kept shut,
bound, and chained,
it should be your legs!
What do you want, huh?
I want to know how many times
I have to tell you
to stay away from my husband!
Where do you get the audacity
to keep doing this, huh?!
I swear, you'd better keep
your mouth shut, Sylvia.
Don't blame me if your husband
keeps coming back to me.
If you don't want him to do that,
tie him up!
It's not my fault your husband
doesn't love you anymore!
- [SLAPS]
- [GROANS]
- You flirt! How dare you?!
- [WHIMPERS]
- Come here! Come here!
- Stop it!
- Sylvia!
- Come here!
You're hurting me, Sylvia!
That's enough! Stop it!
Come here!
- Stop it!
- You slut!
Does it hurt that your husband
loves me more than you?!
Are you jealous, huh?!
- Sylvia!
- You whore! You whore!
- [SYLVIA GRUNTS]
- [JULIANA WHIMPERS]
[JULIANA] Ah!
You witch! How dare you?!
- I'm pregnant, you witch!
- [SYLVIA SCREAMS]
- I'm carrying a child!
- [SCREAMING CONTINUES]
- [KATE] Hey! Stop it!
- [JULIANA] You witch!
Stop it! Juliana is pregnant!
I strongly suggest that
you keep that home-wrecker on a leash
so she stops chasing after my husband
like a rabid dog!
I won't waste any more time
on you, Sylvia!
- Move!
- Juliana!
Move!
Hey!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Olivia.
Take charge here, okay?
I'll meet with Grandma Pilar.
- [METAL CLANGS]
- [MAN] Aah!
[SCREAMS IN PAIN]
What happened, mister?
[MAN GROANS]
- What happened?
- I have cramps.
Cramps? Let me help you.
Sit down first. Is it your right foot?
- It hurts here.
- Hold on.
I will stretch it, okay?
- Ready? Okay.
- Aah!
[GROANS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR HORN HONKING]
[GROANS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WHIMPERS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[BREATHING ANXIOUSLY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ah.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Grandma.
W-What are you doing here?
Grandma, why are you meeting Victor?
Don't wait for him.
Come on. Let's go home.
It's too late.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
What…
What do you mean?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SEETHING]
I now have strong evidence
against Juliana and Alex.
They won't be able to deny this.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HUFFS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[STIRRING MUSIC SWELLS]
Grandma Pilar sent me this.
She's given up.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
She couldn't condone
their actions anymore.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[VICTOR SIGHS DEEPLY]
Why do I feel this way?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
I knew that they were having
an affair, but… [SNIFFLES]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
It feels different
when it's right in front of me.
I don't know if I should be grateful.
[CRIES]
Because I've finally opened my eyes to…
[SNIFFLES]
…everything they did behind my back.
[INHALES, EXHALES DEEPLY]
[CRIES]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Or maybe…
it's all my fault.
Because everyone I loved…
didn't even think twice about
screwing me over.
How could you do this to me?
[CRIES] Why?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
- Liana.
- [JULIANA CRYING]
You know how much I love you.
[PILAR] But the way you are now,
I'd rather have Victor raise Abby
than let her grow up to be like you.
I didn't do this to hurt you.
I did it because
it's the right thing to do.
But I'm your granddaughter.
With what you did,
it's like you've just sent me to prison!
Is doing the right thing
more important to you
than saving your granddaughter?
How could you do it, Grandma?
What you're doing to Victor is too much.
Why did you do it, Grandma?
That will send me to jail!
[JULIANA SOBBING]
Liana, I just can't condone
your actions anymore.
[SOBBING]
- [GROANS]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- What's happening?
- [GROANING]
- Sit down.
- Grandma!
- Sit down--
- Let go of me! Let go of me!
- [JULIANA GROANING]
- Help!
- Hold on. Help!
- Let go of me!
Help! She needs to go to the hospital!
- [PILAR] Hurry! Be careful!
- I'm bleeding!
Be careful. Help us!
Liana! Let's hurry! Come on!
Mama, Alex…
[CRIES, SNIFFLES]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
…and Juliana.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
I tried to give everything I could.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INHALES SHARPLY, EXHALES DEEPLY]
But it's still not enough.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
It wasn't enough to make them give me
a little bit of respect.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
Victor.
There is nothing wrong or missing in you.
You simply fell in love.
[SNIFFLES]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I know it hurts.
I know you're hurting right now.
But I believe that…
you have to go through all of this.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know what? [SNIFFLES]
Only a few people…
are lucky enough to find
a beautiful truth.
[OLIVIA] More often than not,
the truth hurts.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
It's ugly…
and devastating.
[SIGHS DEEPLY, SNIFFLES]
[OLIVIA] But…
it's what will set you free, Victor.
[INHALES, EXHALES DEEPLY]
It's what will give you
the strength to move on.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SNIFFLES]
- [EXHALES DEEPLY]
And because of it,
you will find the right people for you.
It was true when I said that…
I'll always be by your side.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR OPENS]
[PHONE BUZZING]
GRANDMA PILAR
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SHOWER RUNNING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sylvia?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE BUZZING]
Hello, Grandma?
Hello, Alex?
Yes, I've been trying to call you
since last night.
What's wrong?
Something happened to Juliana.
She's in the hospital.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Make sure you eat a lot, okay?
Auntie, where are Grandma and Mommy?
Uh, they just went somewhere.
Do you want this?
Yes.
Will they be gone for a long time?
Can we go see Daddy?
Daddy's just in the gym, right?
Huh?
I'll ask your mommy first, okay?
Go on, eat up. Eat a lot, okay?
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello, Grandma? How's Juliana?
What should I say to Abby?
She's asking where her mom is.
How do I tell her
that she's in the hospital?
Mommy is in the hospital?
What happened to Mommy?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Liana.
[GROANS SOFTLY] Grandma?
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hold on.
I'll call the doctor.
G-Grandma…
How's my baby?
[BREATH QUIVERING]
W-Where's my baby?
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Grandma…
Grandma.
[SOBBING]
It's gone.
The baby is gone.
- What?
- The baby is gone.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
N-No, no. No. No…
Let's go see my baby.
Let's talk to the doctor.
- Grandma. No, Grandma!
- The baby's gone.
Don't say that!
Don't ever say that! My baby is alive!
Grandma, no. This cannot be!
I already lost a child once!
This can't be happening!
Let me talk to the doctor.
Let me talk to the doctor!
Grandma!
It's not true! It's not true!
Take back what you said!
It's not true, Grandma!
I have to go to Abby.
Kate called me.
She said the kid's worried.
They also went to the hospital.
Okay, but do you think they know
what Ms. Pilar did, Victor?
Maybe it's the reason why
Juliana is in the hospital.
I don't know why Juliana's in there.
I'm just worried that
you might bump into Alex there.
Juliana might not want you there.
Olivia, I'm not going to
the hospital to start a fight.
I also know how painful it is
to lose a child.
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm going there because Abby needs me.
I have to go.
You take care of things here.
Dear?
Say hi to your mom.
Uh, Liana. We'll leave you two alone.
Kate.
Mommy.
I came here with Aunt Kate.
Are you okay, Mommy?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Come here, dear.
[GRUNTS] Sit next to Mommy.
[SNIFFLES]
[JULIANA] Uh…
I'm not okay, baby.
[JULIANA BREATHES DEEPLY]
Mommy is sad.
Why?
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Because…
Mommy's baby…
is now in heaven with your brother, Marco.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mommy is sad because…
we lost the baby.
[SNIFFLES]
Don't cry, Mommy.
- I'm still here.
- [SOBBING]
I'll be your baby again.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES,
THEN FADES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[SULLEN MUSIC PLAYING]
[SULLEN MUSIC CONTINUES]
Juliana.
Alex… Alex.
[SORROWFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
[SOBBING]
Alex, our baby is gone.
We lost our baby.
- [SOBBING]
- [SORROWFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm sorry, Juliana.
[SORROWFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBBING]
I'm sorry.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Ms. Pilar?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUDS]
- [GRUNTING, SCREAMING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [KICKS LANDING]
- [SCREAMING]
- [BLOW LAND]
- [GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS] Aah!
Grandma gave Victor a copy of the video.
The video on her cell phone.
[BREATH QUIVERING]
It's proof of our relationship.
I went after Grandma, but…
I didn't make it in time.
Sylvia saw me while I was leaving.
That's when she attacked me.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBS]
[JULIANA BREATHES DEEPLY]
Alex…
[SNIFFLES]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Alex, I don't want to go to jail.
And most importantly…
I don't want Victor to have Abby.
My daughter is mine.
Just mine.
[JULIANA SNIFFLING, SOBBING]
[SMOOCHES]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
It's the result of your disbarment case.
[PAPER RIPPING]
[SCREAMS] Aah!
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[DOOR OPENS]
Alex…
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
What are you doing here?
Are you happy now?
Is this what you wanted?
I didn't want this to happen, Liana.
I once thought of your child as ours.
I could never take joy in this.
Even though it was the result
of your affair with Alex.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I know Grandma gave you
a copy of the video.
What will you do now?
You'll use it against us in court, huh?
Victor…
I've already lost my child, Victor.
Isn't that enough punishment?
Let's end this!
Let's end this now, please!
[JULIANA] Let me go!
Let's just live our separate lives.
Let me go!
[JULIANA SOBBING]
I'm begging you, Victor. Let me go.
Leave me alone. Let's end this now.
- [JULIANA SOBBING]
- [SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OBJECTS CLATTERING, GLASS BREAKING]
[SYLVIA] Alex!
Alex, what's going on?
[SYLVIA GASPS]
[ALEX] How dare you attack Juliana?!
How dare you attack Juliana?!
[GRUNTS]
Can you blame me?!
I saw you coming out of their place
in broad daylight!
You're still continuing your affair!
My child with Juliana is gone.
She had a miscarriage!
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Alex…
[SYLVIA GASPS]
Are you blaming me?
It was you who didn't honor our agreement!
You said you would stop
your affair with Juliana,
but what did you do?!
You didn't stop!
You didn't let her go!
[SYLVIA GASPS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SYLVIA SCREAMS]
- [VASE SHATTERS]
[GROANS]
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
Alex. Alex--
Don't touch me!
[SOBBING]
Alex, I'm not a bad person!
I'm not a bad person, Alex.
I just loved you!
You don't own me!
I gave you one last chance,
but you still chose that woman!
Maybe you deserve each other.
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SCREAMS] Aah!
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[KEYPAD CLACKING]
[LINE RINGING]
Attorney.
I want to talk to you.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Eat up so you can regain your strength.
Matteo said…
the result of your disbarment case
has been released.
Let's not talk about that.
What matters is your wellbeing.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
What are you doing here?
I'm here to clear things up
between the three of us.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
I'm ready to withdraw
the charges against both of you.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[VICTOR] As long as Abby stays with me.
And don't try what you did to me before
because I'm talking to you nicely.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Do you think I'll agree, huh?!
I don't want our daughter
to have a messy life.
I'm not going to take her
away from you, Liana.
I just want to be with her
until she grows up.
No!
My daughter stays with me!
I won't allow it, Victor!
If I present the evidence I have in court,
what do you think will happen to you?
You will go to jail.
And who will Abby go to?
[ALEX] Fine.
I'll prepare everything that's needed.
I'll file a petition in court
for you to get custody of Abby.
[JULIANA] Alex, what are you saying?
Abby is mine! My daughter
will stay with me! Stop!
That's enough.
This will settle things between us.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You won. You can leave.
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [JULIANA BREATHING HEAVILY]
Don't do that!
My daughter will stay with me.
Abby is mine. She's ours. Stop this!
Trust me. I'll take care of it.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[HANGERS CLATTERING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
No.
No!
No…
[SOBBING]
No, no, no, no…
- [STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING CONTINUES]
No!
No.
Thank you, Attorney.
Have you talked to your lawyer?
The transfer of Abby's custody
has been filed.
I've withdrawn the case.
How did you convince Juliana?
Don't ask too many questions.
Just don't talk to her about this.
Now, what?
You're free now.
Go get Abby.
From today on, I have no brother.
We're out of each other's lives.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why didn't you tell me?
Alex, what did you do?
Did you forge my signature?
Alex, speak up! What have you done?!
The important thing is that
Victor will withdraw the case against us.
We won't go to jail.
We'll get Abby back eventually.
Do you hear yourself?
I can't afford to lose my child
even for a second.
Alex, you don't understand,
I can't lose a child again.
You won't lose Abby.
She won't be taken away.
You can still visit her.
Abby is my daughter.
She's mine!
I won't reach the point of begging Victor
just to be with my child
because she's mine!
She's mine. I gave birth to her.
I brought her up. I raised her.
Just me, me, me!
Trust me on this one, Liana.
Trust me.
Victor may have won the battle
but not the war.
Please.
[JULIANA SOBS]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Just make sure you keep your promise.
Because Abby is important to me.
Abby is my life.
She's the only one I can call mine.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Alex, I'm fine. I can walk on my own.
It's for the better.
The doctor also said you need to rest.
Thank you.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
I've moved out.
I'm looking for a place where we can stay,
just like we planned before.
Alex…
At what cost?
We may be together, but…
we've lost so much.
Our child…
your career as a lawyer.
It's not the end of the world
now that I'm no longer a lawyer.
I can do many things, Juliana.
We'll start over.
Everything will be all right.
As long as we're together,
that's what matters.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
You know…
[JULIANA] I don't know what
I'd do without you by my side.
Forget about the thought of losing me
because it will never happen.
I will love you and stay with you
for the rest of my life.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JULIANA, ALEX CHUCKLE SOFTLY]
[SYLVIA] Victor.
[VICTOR SIGHS HEAVILY]
I'm ready to testify
against Alex and Juliana.
[SCOFFS]
I've already dropped the case.
What?
Why did you do that?!
Didn't you say…
we can't just let them be happy
after everything they've done?!
They deserve nothing, Victor!
Victor, don't be a fool!
They shouldn't get away with
what they've done to us!
They have to pay!
They have to go to prison!
Sylvia, can you stop?!
Do what you want.
But I won't help you.
I already have my daughter,
and that's all that matters to me.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING]
[BREATHING RAGGEDLY]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUESTS CLAPPING]
I can put up with you having an affair,
but Juliana?
Really?!
I will end things with Juliana.
The doctor said I'll have
a hard time getting pregnant.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I may not be able to give you
the family you want.
Sorry, ma'am.
I've decided to keep my baby.
Alex, our baby…
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBBING]
Am I really the father of
the baby Juliana is carrying?
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SMACK]
You knew I was the father
of Juliana's baby,
but you kept it from me!
Don't blame me if your husband
doesn't love you anymore!
[SMACK]
- [SMACK]
- [SYLVIA GASPS]
- You shameless woman!
- [JULIANA WHIMPERING] Stop!
You said you would end things
with Juliana!
But what did you do?!
You didn't stop!
You carried on with your affair!
[GASPING]
I will love you and stay with you
for the rest of my life.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING]
[AMELIA] If only you were alive, Jessie,
I would have someone
to share my problems with.
But I won't give up.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll do anything for Alex.
Just like I promised you…
I'm going to take care of Alex.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
How are you, dear?
- Don't worry, Dad.
- [THUNDER RUMBLES]
I'm fine.
You know my stand on this.
You don't have to stay with Alex, Sylvia.
You have nothing to worry about, Dad.
I know what I'm doing.
This problem will soon end.
Please trust me.
I just don't want you
to keep getting hurt.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll be fine, Dad.
Okay. I trust you.
Just call me if there's a problem, okay?
[SYLVIA] Dad…
Hmm?
[VOICE BREAKING] I love you.
I love you too.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You finally got custody of Abby.
You no longer have to worry that
she'll be taken away from you.
We'll help you so Abby can adjust easily.
Thank you, guys.
Oh, right. I'll pick up Abby later.
So, let's celebrate later?
- [OLIVIA] I'll cook.
- [CHUCKLES]
[BADONG] All right.
I'll buy beer.
- [LAUGHS]
- [OLIVIA CHUCKLES]
- Maybe just a few, Coach.
- [BADONG] Right.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
What if we just share custody of her?
So it will be equal.
This is not the right time
for you to haggle with Victor.
Let's plan things out
once he gets custody of Abby.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Abby?
I'm done packing, Mommy.
Just like Uncle Alex told me.
Grandma Pilar helped me as well.
Can't we just stay with Daddy, Mommy?
I don't want to leave you.
I promised I'd stay by your side.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Dear…
You're not going anywhere, okay?
You'll stay here with me.
Really?
But…
What about Uncle Alex and Daddy?
Wouldn't they be angry?
I don't care if they get angry.
I'll deal with them.
Don't worry, okay?
All that matters is we're together.
What's really going on, Mommy?
Why do I have to choose
between you and Daddy?
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I love both you and Daddy.
[BREATH QUIVERS]
Abby…
Stop crying, okay?
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Your daddy and I
may not agree on a lot of things,
but that doesn't mean we don't love you.
I… I don't want to lose you, dear.
Stay with Mommy, okay?
I love you so much.
[ABBY SOBBING]
I love you, Abby.
I love you too, Mommy.
- [BOTH SOBBING]
- [SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let's just meet on Sunday.
Okay?
Huh? But-- Wait!
- I have to go. Bye!
- [ZEUS BARKING]
Zeus!
Huh?
Zeus, what are you…?
[GASPS]
[SCREAMING]
- [DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MAID WHIMPERING]
[VICTOR] Sylvia!
[WHIMPERING]
[MAID SCREAMING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
What have you done?!
- [MAID WAILING]
- [DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]