Oh My Ghostess
Episode 12
Okay. I can't back down now.
Chef wants me to come. He's waiting for me because he's worried.
I like him so much. What it took to win his heart.
I'm only going to think about myself. Just this once.
I'm going to protect it no matter what, Chef's heart.
-Chef!
-Where were you?
What is it?  Because of you sleep is gone.
My goodness, this is trouble. Big trouble. You're completely smitten with me.
I suppose there is part of me that is hard to break loose from, once you've fallen for me.
I understand, so let go.
I don't want to. I don't want to separate myself from you.
What is this at the intersection? Are you in a manic episode?
When was it that you wouldn't even let me touch you?
It's your hobby to flip-flop.
So you want to stay like this?
Yes.
Oh My Ghostess
Episode 12
Officer Han!
Congratulations, for your release! Here.
What is it? What's with the tofu? Did I go to jail?
For a policeman, it isn't jail, but the hospital you're supposed to eat this when you get out. It's organic.
Organic?
Please give me your bag.
It's embarrassing the more I think about it? Attacking a policeman?
He got me off-guard. In any case, when I catch this guy I'm going to chop him up.
He smeared dung on the mighty Han Jin Goo's police life. I'm going to catch and kill him.
Aren't you hungry? You probably suffered eating flavorless hospital food.
-Hangover soup.
-Okay.
-I need to eat hangover soup.
-Let's go, to the hangover soup.
I can't stay in a hospital.
Here's the blood sausage soup.
Thank you for the food.
I was worried hearing you were hospitalized. But it's good to see you.
I'm glad to see you, too. Thank you.
Okay, eat a lot.
Take your time. Aren't you eating too quickly for someone who was just discharged?
Hey, have you tried hospital food? It's really bad. This tastes really good. I'm touched.
Here, more blood sausage.
-Hey, you should give me meat.
-I am giving you meat.
The more I think about it, the more sorry I am to Eun Hee.
You know that CCTV? In a hit and run with no other witnesses, that was the last chance.
And I get attacked, does that make any sense?
Not at all. You did the best you could.
That's why I deliberately didn't say anything to Eun Hee or her brother. Don't worry too much about it.
Can I do that? Eat up.
Yes, please eat.
Hey, hey!
Why are you carrying that? Ask the boys to do it. What if you throw out your back?
-It's okay.
-It's mine though.
What?
Take care of your body.
Yes, Chef. I'll keep that in mind.
And also, go to the market with me later.
Since they might think it's weird to always go to the market with you. When I give you a sign, say you're hurt and going to the hospital.
Yes, then where should I say I'm hurt?
Should I say I sprained my ankle ? Or...since it's summer, swelling?
Say anything. Anything.
Yes, anything.
Your mood is strange today.
This is not manic, maybe it's a little bit of a precocious child...
I find you most endearing when you're in the middle. See you later.
Yes, Chef.
Wow.
-What is it?
-Is everyone gathered?
What? What? What do we need to know?
Stay still. Our Chef and Bong,
I think the two of them are dating.
Why you! Saying nonsense from early in the morning.
Is Chef on drugs to date Bong?
Hey, Ji Woong. I really like you, but I don't think that's right.
Seriously, I really saw them.
When I was coming out of the restroom, Chef goes, "Bong,"
you're precocious. See you later."
Clear away that head. Clear away that head.
They probably ran into each other and bumped their heads. Who does this as a sign of affection?
Is it some kind of Kim Bok Nam's fashion show?
Oh man, you can be so dense. The vibe was like back when...it was vague.
Close that mouth! That mouth! Just make your debut.
This guy...if he is going to write a fiction, he should stick to what's possible.
Come here. Lately,
do you really not know who Chef has something like that with?
Who is it?
What's beneath the light is most possible.
What are we going to do with you? You'll have to let your goddess go now.
Goddess? PD Lee?
Ding, dong, deng, dong!
I had a feeling about the two of them.
When we went to MT, oooh~
The two of them were finally stuck together. That's why I brought Bong and put her in our car.
- Really?
- Isn't it your impression and not confirmed?
It's for sure. My feeling has never been wrong.
But, what? But, Chef and Bong?
Hey, punk. If Chef and Bong have that kind of relationship,
I'll live the rest of my life as an eunuch.
Oh, geez.
I'll be going to mise en place.
I'll going.
This is really annoying!
Hey, get up! Let's eat this.
I went to a funeral service and snuck some food out.
Stop feeling so sad about it, girl.
If you're here being lovesick, will that virile man even notice?
You should have stretched your legs where you're suited. Why did you get involved in an impossible relationship being a ghost and all?
I think we have to give up on getting rid of the virgin vexation.
Hey, let's just do the rite to heaven. I'll do it the least painfully,
I'll send you off quickly without it being too hard.
Hey, is your mouth glued shut? Someone who would chatter on and would never shut her mouth before...you should at least act like you're listening.
Whatever. Do whatever pleases you. Just lie there and become a fossil or not, I don't care.
Don't eat too much.
It's delicious. Seaweed.
-What is it? What is it? Who is it? Who is it?
-It's nothing.
You look like you're hiding something. Something good is going on lately, isn't it?
-What good thing? I said it's not.
-It's written all over your face.
I. am. dating. Is it that wonderful?
I said I wasn't.
You don't believe me. I'm done eating.
I'm going to the market, so get everything ready.
Yes, Chef!
-Ow!
-What is it? What is it?
I twisted my ankle earlier.
I hurt it pretty bad and I think I need to go see a doctor.
Oh, no.
There's so much to be done after eating, She-Bong!
Hurry up and and run there and back.
Yes, Sous Chef! I'm sorr... Ow!
It hurts so  much, what am I to do?
It hurts so badly.
Man, he bopped me in the head. Geez!
Wow, I'm getting goosebumps. She's acting, did you see her foot-acting?
When she said she was hurt, it was her left foot.
But when she was leaving, it was her right foot she was limping on.
Sous Chef, she's going after Chef, I'm telling you.
She's not. She's not.
How is he supposed to get through life without a clue like this?
-I really saw it!
-It's not, you Old Boy!
Oh, is it too dark?
There.
-Chef, give it here.
-It's fine. I'm strong.
See this. Touch it, try touching it.
-Where?
-It's no joke.
What do you mean where? They must be hiding today. It really is no joke.
After touching it again, I think they're there. They're really awesome.
-Right?
-Yes.
When we're out, you should wear your hair down. It's prettier that way.
Really?
There. It's pretty.
- Hyung!
- Ah, Joe.
Hey!
-Did you come to get groceries?
-Isn't that too much?
You don't even visit anymore. Your affection for me cooled off, did it?
I've been busy. Let's get together some time.
But why are you carrying everything? It's so heavy.
If you brought the pipsqueak, you should put her to work.
Ah, Chef, give them here. My arm fell asleep, but it's okay now.
Why don't you send her back and you and I can grab a bowl of shaved ice.
Don't you run a business?
You've just started your business! Instead of thinking about selling one more dish...Get going!
It's just that it's been so long since I saw you.
I'll see you next time. Just go.
Nagging the hell out of me when it's been a while since we've seen each other.
-Chef, I'm really okay.
-I know. Let's go.
Chef, let go of my hand.
There are so many people, and so many people recognize you.
Who cares? Is this a crime?
-You like holding my hand.
-Huh?
Chef, but where are we going?
Somewhere. Somewhere that you'll feel really moved by.
Why here?
We're here to eat, why, do you think I came to sell you at the blood sausage soup place?
I can't really eat blood sausage soup.
What are you talking about? It's your favorite food.
-Me?
-Yeah.
-Ah,
-It's here.
-Enjoy.
-It's perfect to eat now, isn't it?
Yes, please enjoy.
-Eat up.
-Yes, Chef.
It smells amazing, too.
This is the flavor, this flavor. It's good.
-Hurry up and eat.
-Yes.
-You liked it so much, why aren't you eating?
-I should eat it.
Ah, this girl.
Here.
-Don't you see my hand blushing? Hurry up and eat.
-Yes, Chef.
-Isn't it amazing?
-Yes, it's delicious.
The highlight is the intestines cooked with chives and soybean paste.
Eat a lot, Chef.
No, no. I ate a lot of mixed noodles earlier. You eat it.
-Yes.
-Eat a lot.
Yes, Chef. It looks tasty.
May I stop by the restroom?
Of course.
It's okay. This is the extent of it.
Yeah, blood sausage soup is helping me out, too.
It's good for clearing out the toxins.
You're okay, Na Bong Seon. You're doing well. You can do this.
What took you so long? Hurry up and eat.
-Ah, Chef, you ate a lot.
-I thought it wouldn't be enough so I ordered another serving.
-What?
-Isn't that good?
Oh, So Hyeong.
Yeah, friend. If I don't call, you never do. Are you going to be like this?
No, I'm sorry. I was busy.
I'm kidding, don't be nervous. It's just that an opportunity for a shoot came up.
I was thinking about going to your restaurant to take them. What do you think?
Ah. If you need to, you should. When?
Ahjumma, please bring the cooking shears.
I think tomorrow will work.
Oh, okay. Then call me.
Thank you.
You worked hard in this heat.
They're coming tomorrow to shoot Chef To Chef, so just know that.
Woohoo!
Please!
Overreacting like you're uncultured. Is a broadcast such a big deal?
Chefs shouldn't like being on TV too much. Then you'll turn out like Marco. A fame hog.
-Doctors can't even fix that.
-Yes, Chef.
Tomorrow's special will be the eggplant marinara.
-Na Bong.
-Yes?
-You give it a try.
-What?
M-m-me?
Why are you so surprised? How long are you going to wash dishes?
No, but still.
But, Chef. I don't think Bong is at the level to do that yet.
That's why I'm telling her to try. Am I going to leave it to her permanently?
You have to stretch your skills to improve them.
It's going to be a hairy day, so Joon should cover. The end.
Yes.
Whoa! Bong!
It's okay, you can do it.
Just watch out.
What are you talking about that you can't do it?
I'm still not ready. And I think it will harm the restaurant if I mess up.
You said you could do well before.
Didn't you say yourself that you wanted to chew gum? What happened to that self confidence?
Are you starting your coming and going again?
Th-th-that isn't it, Chef.
Hey, Na Bong Seon. You have talent.
You have plenty of ability and then some. You made the dried pollack rice soup and the buckwheat flour pancakes.
Am I someone who would give opportunities for my personal reasons?
I'm not. I gave you the chance because you deserve it.
Hmm? Why aren't you responding? You can do it, can't you, Na Bong Seon?
What?
I'll try my best.
-Okay.
-Yes.
You have plenty of ability and then some.
Is it going well?
Ah, Chef. Yes, I'm working hard.
You can't just work hard, it has to taste good.
When you're frying the eggplant make sure to rid of the oil. Since it'll absorb the oil.
-Isn't it difficult?
-Yes.
It has to be difficult for you to get a good result. What about the sauce?
Yes, it's boiling.
You don't have to slice the tomatoes this small. It's better to have some texture.
The flavor is good. Let's add a little bit more black pepper. To make it spicier.
Yes, Chef.
-You just have to work a little bit more.
-Thank you.
How wonderful. How did you live without enjoying such things?
What do you think? Do you want to try a bite?
You really  like pork slices.
If you don't eat it now, I'm going to eat all of it.
Are you really not going to eat? You're not hungry?
I guess sickness of the heart goes deep.
This girl who goes crazy over everything edible is refusing to eat.
Who is it? There's nobody who would come at this hour.
Who is it?
Dearie! I'm here!
What brought you here?
I was on my way home and thought of you.
I bought beer and soju. Isn't that good?
Oh my. You were drinking alone?
Meat and pancakes. You had a funeral ceremony, huh?
Why did you come without even calling?
I have a personal life, too.
I know you don't have a boyfriend. What personal life.
Be a drinking buddy for me today. It's because of my Seon Woo.
I feel uneasy, that's why.
Let's not talk about your son if possible.
I'm sure there is something going on with him and that Bong Sook girl.
But what you told me about that dead lifeline, it keeps bothering me. That something bad will happen to Seon Woo.
Let's go out and eat.
-Why?
-I think that would be better.
This is comfortable and there's plenty to eat.
There's a food tent out front with a good-looking man. He looks like Jang Dong Geon.
Jang Dong...really?
Come quickly.
Leave all this.
How old is he?
I miss you, Chef.
This isn't it.
Oh, I'm busy!
I said I really don't have any time!
Ow, hot!
It's hot.
Seriously! I'm going to go crazy.
No, no, Na Bong Seon. You have to have more grit.
This is nothing. Darn it. Darn it?
Darn it! Seriously! Who says I'm She-Bong?
I am Na Bong Seon!
I feel better now.
Yeah, just work a little harder, Na Bong Seon.
You're doing well. Just a little bit more.
Please. Please taste good.
I think it's okay.
Oh, you're here? You're late.
Oh.
There were so many civil complaints today. You didn't sleep?
How could I sleep first when you're not home?
Oh my, what happened to your hand? Did you get hurt?
Oh, a little. I was stopping a fight.
Oh no, you should be more careful. Let me see.
It's okay. It's not a big deal.
Let me see. Do you need to see a doctor?
It's okay.
I said it was okay, what's the fuss?
Seong Jae.
Sorry. I think I'm sensitive lately. I'm really sorry.
Don't worry and go to sleep first. I'll go and wash up.
Seong Jae. You can get irritable with me from time to time.
How can a person be angelic all the time?
But, don't get hurt. I don't like you getting hurt.
Oh. Okay. Go to sleep first.
Sounds tasty.
One eggplant special.
It's coming out!
One eggplant marinara, one special please.
One Shrek, one eggplant.
Yes!
One Shrek
and one eggplant marinara is here.
I think the eggplant is a success.
Yeah, the response is good. And there are a lot of orders for it.
I tasted it earlier and it was good.
Hey, Bong Seon you've improved a lot. Congrats.
Thank you.
All of this is what Bong learned over someone's shoulder.
If you didn't have an outstanding chef and outstanding sous chef, do you think this would be possible?
Hey, Bong. This isn't food on the pan. It's your face.
- Yes, Sous-Chef.
- Stop the chatter. Did Shrek go out to 10T?
Yes, Chef!
Then put a check on it!
Yes!
Concentrate on lunch!
Yes, Chef!
Give it here.
I told you that you can do it, didn't I?
Yes, I did it, Chef.
After just cleaning empty dishes, how does it feel to send out your dish? Doesn't it feel great?
-Yes.
-I still can't forget that first feeling, too.
You made it through your first dish. Good job, Na Bong Seon.
Yes.
You have to keep going with that confidence. Let's have a celebratory party after the shoot.
Yes, Chef.
Why do we have to do all this work for a restaurant shoot?
We could just film it in 6mm, why bring  me here-
It's a different picture with you shooting it, Director.
What picture when you're just shooting a restaurant?
I'll treat you to bean noodles after we're done.
-I'm not eating noodles.
-Soba?
-It's fine.
-Then cold buckwheat noodles?
Then I'll think about the cold buckwheat noodles.
Cold buckwheat noodles it is.
Let's hurry up and do this.
Welcome.
Hello.
Yes, welcome.
Welcome.
-Hello.
-Welcome.
Oh, so hot.
Hello!
-Chef Kang.
-Please look kindly on us.
Is there anything for me to do?
Unni, you look so cool.
Seeing you today, you look like a real producer.
Did I look like a fake producer until now?
That's not what I mean.
You should have come to a shoot earlier.
PD, PD.
Hello. You got prettier in the few days I haven't seen you.
You just need to wear a wedding dress in this state for the game to be over.
Thank you for the kind words, Min Soo. Please help with  filming today.
No problem. Just say it and I
will do my everything to do it.
Just a moment.
You had some beauty on you.
Jewelry is pretty.
Thank you. Please help us do well today. Bong Seon, have you been well?
Ah, you're here?
Do well today.
Yes.
What are you doing instead of getting ready?
Yes, Chef!
That kid, seriously...
I think you can just naturally follow the hall.
Later, please get a full shot of the kitchen.
Also, for the food, you can do a 6mm tight insert.
Ah, okay! Let's just get through this roughly. Roughly.
I didn't have to come to this site, but you  made me.
Director, why are you like that? You have to be here for the full picture to turn out well.
My goodness, you and your picture.
Hey, she wants a nice picture! Hoon, are you getting the setting well?
Yes, it's all ready, Director!
What are you doing there? What's ready? Clear away those things in the way.
And arrange the cords. Let's move quickly. It's hot and I'm getting irritable.
Yes, yes, yes.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Hey, Bong!
Shouldn't you give the cold water to the PD and the camera director first? Giving out cold water has an order.
-I'm sorry.
-Turn on some sense.
-Yes, I'll do it right away.
-I'll do it.
Yes.
Hey, and see this in the way? Clear it away quickly.
Yes, yes, Sous Chef!
I'll do it. Take care of the staff.
Ah,
It's sour! I won't drink.
Director, do you think it'll be alright without you looking over the white?
I saw it earlier roughly. Do you think I wouldn't do that?
Geesh.
So frustrating.
These young PDs don't know anything, but think they do.
Hey, Hoon!
Where did he go again? Are you somewhere texting again?
Just let me catch you! It's so hot.
Hey, bring me the battery box.
Me? The battery?
The battery box. No.
-This one?
-Not that one. The one in the corner.
Ah, this one?
No, the corner. Don't you know what a corner is?
Uh...
Is that the corner?
This...this one?
Yeah, that one.
There're others around, why are you making her do it?
Thanks a lot. There you go.
-Thank you.
-Give it here. I'm getting so annoyed.
How can you not know what a corner is? Oh, my nose is running.
Hey! Hey, hey. Bring that over here.
Yes? What is it?
-That...tissue!
-A tissue?
Don't you see that I have a runny nose?
Yes, I'll bring it right away.
There you go.
Is there anything else to be done?
No.
Go over there.
Don't do anything and just sit there and do what I tell you to.
-I'm okay.
-I told you to sit down.
You didn't even get to rest on your break. If it was going to be like this, I wouldn't have agree to do this broadcast.
Hey, Heo Min Soo! Aren't you going to look out for your family?
Because you keep looking down on Bong Seon, other people do that, too.
I'm sorry, Chef.
Who are you saying I'm looking down on?
You're making me feel bad.
What's wrong with borrowing some help, Chef Kang?
Why are you so irritable?
Are you two dating or something?
Yes, we are dating.
So please don't mistreat her.
Chef...
Wow. Big news.
Wow, how could such a big thing as this happen?
See? What did I tell you?
I told you so many times that the mood between the two of them was suspicious.
Why don't you believe me?
It turned out well. Just congratulate them.
What? Did you know something was up?
Roughly, I had a sense.
Oh, seriously.
You deliberately didn't say anything, did you?
You wanted me to get in trouble for abusing Bong,
so you deliberately didn't tell me, did you?
No, if the people involved aren't open about it, why should I say anything?
Open? It's close, you punk!
Hey, why are you being like that?
What?
What do I do? Do I have to quit now?
Why quit? What do you mean what do you have to do?
Hold him.
Joon, go get a knife and the cutting board.
Okay, Eunuch Heo, take it out.
It tickles! It tickles!
Oh, what is it? Do you want something to eat?
Tell me. Hurry up and tell me. I'll get whatever you want to eat.
I'll do it.
Do what?
I'll do the rite to heaven.
Did you make up your mind?
Just don't make it hurt too much.
Unni, do it well for me.
Okay?
Okay. Okay.
I'll muster everything that I can possibly muster.
I'll make it so you can go as quickly as possible. So it won't be too hard on you.
Don't worry.
Okay. Let's do it tomorrow. No need to drag it out.
Will you be okay?
Yeah.
I'll just go say my final goodbye to my father.
Chef Kang, sorry about earlier.
Bye!
You worked hard, Chef Kang.
You were pretty cool today.
Have I ever not been cool?
You were slightly more cool today. And romantic, too.
Love really must change a person.
Sung Gyu said so before that back when you were freshmen, if you have someone you like,
he would make flower rings to give while you just ignored them.
Why are you bringing up the past?
You're off work  now, aren't you?
Let's go. I'll buy. For Bong Seon, too.
Together?
Oh? What are you doing?
Hey, Bong, Bong! Wait a moment!
Hey, I'm going to do it!
This is my expertise.
Do it quickly. Must Bong Seon do this heavy thing?
Sous Chef, I can do it.
Hey!
Come with me.
Just come here.
Come and sit.
Just a moment. Have a seat.
Just wait there.
You know that I cherish you, right?
So I nagged you a lot in order to develop you.
And you know how I gave you a lot of work to give you experience?
-Me, too, me, too.
-Just stay still.
So you know how I feel, right?
Of course, I do, Sous Chef.
Oh, Bong Seon. When you smile, you're eyes do this and you look like a puppy.
It's so cute!
Not like a dog, you look like a puppy.
What is this?
I'll do better. I'll do my best.
Oh, no. I should do better.
No, no, I'm going to do better.
Come here.
Thank you!
Chef.
You were surprised, weren't you?
Ah, I wasn't planning to put it out in the open like that.
Are you okay, Chef?
Of course, I'm okay, kid.
But because I spit it out like that without talking to you, I feel a little bad.
But please understand me for acting so hastily.
It's okay, right?
Oh, yes. I'm okay if you're okay.
It's troublesome for me if you speak so sweetly.
So Hyeong wants to have a drink. With you, too.
What? Me, too?
She feels sorry and wants to resolve things.
Will you be okay?
Yes.
Okay.
What?
Do you want this, Chef?
Who gave it to you?
Sous Chef.
You really worked hard today.
Here.
Let's down our first glasses in one shot.
Yes.
Do you want some beer? Or soda?
Ah, no. I'll drink this soju.
This dimwit.
The one who is envious loses.
Truthfully, I envy you, Bong Seon.
Ah, no. You're so cool.
I've always been envious of you.
How can someone be so bright and confident and attractive.
-Really?
-Yes, really.
If she wasn't sincere, I could detest her.
But she's so sincere, I can't hate her.
I lost, Bong Seon.
Here, give me a glass.
Yes.
What's with the two of you?
Am I a ghost (as in invisible)? Seriously.
They're really treating me like a ghost.
Yeah, Brother-in-law.
It's me, Hyungnim. Where are you?
I'm drinking after work. Why?
Eun Hee went in for her treatment now.
But I got an emergency call, so could you take Eun Hee home?
Oh, really?
Okay, I'll go then.
Yeah, work hard.
What? Is something wrong?
My brother-in-law had something come up.
I have to pick up Eun Hee. What can I do?
Just go.
Aren't you too happy to get rid of me?
Because you need to go.
Don't drink too much.
And call me if she hits you.
Then I'll hit her, too.
She's the one keeping me in check these days, not the other way.
Stop that now and go.
Don't you see that my drink is waiting for me?
Bye, Chef.
See you.
Here.
Clink.
Now, carefully.
I feel so bad that you had to rush here for me.
Ah, not at all. It's okay.
You're my forever no. 1 priority. Aren't you moved?
There's a number 0 though, right?
Huh?
Ah, gosh.
I'm sorry. You were surprised, weren't you?
I don't know how it happened either. I feel like I was bewitched by a ghost, too.
It makes me realize that love can make even Kang Seon Woo to dance around.
Love? You're sounding too mushy.
It's true. I saw hearts shooting out of your eyes.
Since I liked Bong Seon from the beginning, I'll cheer you two on.
I earned a great backer. A great backer.
Oh, that's right. It's a secret from Mom. Who knows how she'll overreact.
I know.
But I think Mom caught on. She asked me how Bong Seon was?
Just tell her you don't know. You don't know anything. Just ignore her.
Okay, I'll ignore her.
Father.
Don't forget when you leave things on the stove.
And when business is done, make sure to turn off the gas.
See? Again.
I said turn that off first.
Oh, that's right. The gas.
You listen well, my father.
And don't carry heavy things.
It will be really bad if your back goes out.
And make Kyung Mo do whatever he can do for you.
Yes!
Hey, punk.
Father only has you now.
Grow up.
I know you're a good kid.
Take good care of father.
Kyung Mo.
Yes, sir!
Enough with the games.
Ah, you made me die!
Geesh, when are you ever going to grow up?
For the last time, just once.
Let me just see him once more before I go.
It's strange. If it's the second bottle,
I should be feeling buzzed,
but strangely I can't get drunk today.
Here.
-Drink up.
-One shot!
You drink so well.
Bong Seon, you could be my drinking buddy.
It tastes good.
Bong Seon, you're quite...
unique.
Sometimes we see this side of you,
and at other times, you're like something else. Seon Woo fell hard into this charm, didn't he?
Yes, I guess that's part of my charm.
-Are you already drunk?
-No.
I feel really good, but it's not because I'm drunk. I'm really okay.
Bong Seon, you're really cute when you're drunk.
In any case, please forget when I overstepped my bounds at your MT.
And make Seon Woo happy from now on.
Ah, yes, of course!
You're so cute! I can't hate you.
Me too, Unni.
Bong Seon, I said I'd take you home.
PD Lee, I'm really okay. I'm not drunk.
Do you want to see?
This...
Someone who's drunk can't do that, but see, I can.
Will you really be okay?
I'm really okay.
PD Lee.
People are all naturally selfish, aren't they?
When I'm up to my nose with problems and fire is at my feet,
there's no time to think about others, right? People usually don't do that, do they?
That's right, because they're human.
That's right.
Why? Are you sorry towards me?
Yes. I'm sorry towards you,
and I'm sorry towards the ghost and towards Chef.
I just want to ignore it this time.
I'll be going, PD Lee. Goodbye.
Be careful on your way!
I'll get scolded by Seon Woo.
Yes.
She gets really weird when she's drunk.
And I think I can understand why he fell for her.
♫ It's okay. It will turn out fine.
♫ There's a bright future for you.
♫ It's okay. It will work out fine.
Okay, it will turn out fine.
Have you ever been happier than this, Na Bong Seon?
What are you doing? Play with me.
I don't want to! I'm not going to play with you!
Why is Na Bong Seon always going around alone?
She can't talk, can she?
But she sometimes answers about as loud as a mosquito.
Stop caring. She's always dreary, it's annoying.
Me, too.
Okay.
It can't get better than this, can it? Yeah.
It's okay. It will turn out fine.
Na Bong Seon.
Wait! Wait a moment!
Didn't you come to see Chef?
No, I didn't.
I'm on my way back from saying my last goodbye to my father. Coincidentally.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Hey, you're lucky. You almost became my junior.
I saved you.
Watch out for cars.
It's your loss if you die.
-I'm going.
-Just a minute.
So,
I'm sorry.
And also, thank you.
You're saying things that don't make sense. Why would you be sorry?
Who's the one who caused a nuisance by possessing someone else's body? You're embarrassing me.
Na Bong Seon,
be happy. Please.
I'm really going. Eat and live well.
Isn't this the car from earlier?
Officer Choi?
Shin Soon Ae.
Hey, punk! Are you crazy? Get out here!
Hey! Get out now!
Get out, you punk!
Ah, you scared me!
You startled me.
Hey, did you see your father?
Did you say your farewell?
Hey!
What's wrong with her?
Is it because you're sad after meeting your father?
So why did you go to say goodbye? It only pains your heart.
Unni,
What?
I think I'm going to have to push back my rite to heaven.
What? Why now?
Is it because you can't leave your father as he's in your thoughts?
It's not that. Something is strange.
What's there to be strange?
Hey, you're the strangest one, girl.
No. He's not the person I knew.
The feeling. The feeling was strangely bad.
I don't think I can leave like this.
What in the world are you saying?
Are you making excuses because you don't want to do the rite to heaven?
If not, did you meet that virile man? Is it because you're wavering?
It's not that. That person,
that person is trying to kill Na Bong Seon.
Who is? That virile man?
No. Officer Choi.
If it's Officer Choi,
that virile man's younger sister's husband?
Na Bong Seon!
Yes, Chef.
Did you drink a lot? You didn't answer your phone.
My phone?
Missed calls
You look like you don't feel that well.
Did something happen with So Hyeong?
No, nothing happened. I feel fine.
-Really?
-Yes.
And here I thought....
Let's go in and try making something, I'm starving to death.
Ah, you haven't eaten yet, have you? What should I make for you, Chef?
Rice.
That fried rice you made.
Fried rice?
I thought you didn't eat rice.
Yeah, I didn't eat it, it's not that I couldn't.
I'm going to start eating it now.
Not eating it became a habit, so I get an upset stomach.
And you prefer rice. If I'm going to eat with you, I have to practice eating it.
-Hurry, hurry, hurry.
-Ah, okay.
It's done.
That smells reasonable.
I'm going crazy to eat it.
It's edible. Wow, indeed,
whose student are you?
Make rice for me. I'm going to try being Korean.
Yes.
Your expression is strange since earlier.
No, I'm okay.
You don't look okay. Did nothing really happen?
No, I'm just a little tired today.
I guess you had a lot of surprises today. I'm sure you're exhausted.
This won't do. Let me hurry up and eat so we can go out.
Where to?
To get some air.
Where are....
Don't you know by looking? It's Namsan.
You said you wanted to come here.
Well, people from the countryside only talks about Namsan Tower or Tower 63.
I did?
You said it last time at the playground. That there were so many things you hadn't done.
You haven't been to Namsan nor to a cruise ship. You kept on saying this and that, so I'm going to let you do it.
Since it's your wish.
I have a lot of sense, right? I usually just listen mindlessly to what people say.
But I especially remembered what you said. Aren't you touched?
You're not?
What?
No, I like it.
Then should we go there?
It is a little tacky, but there must be a reason couples die to go there.
I'm not the type who enjoys looking at the view like this.
But because of Na Bong Seon, I'm doing all sorts of things.
And when you come here, aren't you supposed to take pictures and stuff?
The view. Ready.
There.
Ah, it's cool.
It's really nice.
It's only nice because you're here with me. It's important who you come with.
I like it, too. Because I'm here with you.
Do you know when I was really thankful to you?
When my alumni came to my restaurant, I was a little crazy.
But when I came to my senses,
in the 33 years of my life, I was the most humiliated, pathetic and lonely.
Your buckwheat pancake from that day and you annoyingly talking to me was comforting.
It's not me.
I was alone since I was young,
so it became a habit to keep it to myself when I was lonely or sad.
But having someone by my side, just with that,
I realized that it brings comfort.
It's not me. Chef wanting to start eating rice, too.
The one who gave comfort to Chef, too, none of that was me.
Thank you, Na Bong Seon.
For having me do things I've never done.
And for being by my side.
It's not. It's not me.
Let's go.
Oh, we're going.
On the way down, the view looks different. It's fascinating.
We've done Namsan this time, so we'll go to a cruise ship next.
I can't help it if you're uncultured.
It's not me.
Okay, fine.
You're not uncultured. I was just kidding.
It's not me that you like.
What?
What are you saying? The one I like isn't you?
What are you talking about, Na Bong Seon?
It's a ghost.
Huh?
I said that it's a ghost that you like.
I... actually, I see ghosts.
And my body was possessed by a ghost.
Do you know the possessions that people talk about?
So, the one that you like,
is the me that's possessed by a ghost.
It's not me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Chef.
I can't understand what you're saying.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry, Chef.
Na Bong.
♫  The people I love so much, ♫
♫  the warmth that remains on my fingertips, ♫
♫  the glamorous memories in my mind, ♫
♫  I don't want to forget ♫
Oh my Ghostess
~Preview~
♫  The sun rises again and time flows, ♫
♫  Yesterday gets stained with today's life ♫
♫  I will also be forgotten and will disappear, ♫
♫ That's how everyone leaves ♫