[Lee Si-hyung Kong Mi-ri]
[Jeong Young-joo Qiu Qingzi]
[Kim Da-soon Park So-hee]
[Nanji loves Jun Ji-hyun]
[Zheng Sangxun and Park Seungho]
[Oh Dae-hwan and Noh Kang-sik]
["Housewives Detective Agency"]
stop
Wife
(Note: Approximately NT$105,000)
[5 million won has been transferred to Oh Hee Soo]
5 million won
What is this? What trouble have you gotten into?
I actually took over this cafe.
What
(Note: Approximately NT$1.05 million)
[The transfer fee for the cafe is 50 million won]
50 million won
50 million won is a bargain.
This location is very good and the business is super good
Nice shit location are you crazy
Just trust me once.
I've worked here and it really suits me.
He'll do well.
He worked as a trainee barista in our cafe.
The ability to accumulate experience has also been recognized
Especially Shenghao's vanilla latte is really good.
Vanilla Latte
What is your relationship?
Sorry I haven't had time to introduce myself.
My name is Wu Xixiu
Hee Soo
When I was a kid, I was a neighbor of Seungho.
Just... just neighbors
oh
It turns out you are Park Seung-ho's first love
Seungho, why are you talking about that?
My sister-in-law will misunderstand our relationship.
Return our relationship
We met by chance at the gym.
I heard she was running a coffee shop. I visited her several times.
Found a good atmosphere and many guests
Just then Hee Soo said
I'm planning to transfer the café. I said I wanted to take over it.
I don't want to hear about that.
This contract is void.
Wife
In this case, the 5 million won deposit will not be returned.
Is it okay?
Do you want to take 5 million won for nothing?
The seal is not dry yet.
What the hell are you doing?
It's not that I want to take it for free, but the contract is protected by law.
It is your freedom to cancel or fulfill the contract.
But the deposit cannot be returned to you
She said the deposit cannot be refunded.
You two can chat. I'm going to take a call.
Don't worry, Hee Soo will be fine with the contract.
His wife came over unexpectedly and almost messed up the contract.
We need to continue hiring people to pretend to be guests before they realize something is wrong.
Don't worry, the payment date has been brought forward.
You decide
Then find another gym
I am already in my forties
After teaching a few classes, my whole body feels like it's falling apart
I can't always be a fitness trainer.
Hyun-ji is also older
You should discuss this with me.
Am I still your wife?
I knew you'd be angry.
I didn't discuss it with you.
Look, aren't you so angry that you're jumping up and down?
We just didn't sleep in separate rooms.
In fact, emotionally speaking, it's no different from a divorce.
I will stamp the divorce agreement.
Just live a good life with your first love.
Wife
Let me go
Oh my god, I'm so scared.
Have you even prepared the divorce documents?
[Diagnosis: Erectile dysfunction]
I took medicine to keep in shape but it had side effects
I was also in pain during this period
To be honest, I don't want to exercise anymore.
I'm sorry for not being able to tell you in advance.
I'm really sorry
Park Seung-ho used to be so lively
So why don't you tell me?
The murderer who killed two girls in their twenties and abandoned their bodies
He was arrested by the police in a building in Guangshan District yesterday afternoon.
[Exclusive report: The serial killer in Guangshan District has been arrested!]
It is understood that the criminal is Park, who lives in the same building as the victim.
[This person and the victim lived in the same community]
When he attempted the third crime
He was subdued on the spot by other residents
Park kidnapped and imprisoned a female delivery worker who traveled to the community every day.
It has been confirmed that it is related to the two previous murders...
Who is he looking at?
[The serial killer was subdued by the residents of the community]
Who is that person behind?
[ep09 Community Dystopia]
Park Tae-hoon
You have been using a box cutter to attempt suicide since the 8th grade.
Two years ago, he was hospitalized in a closed mental hospital.
I also went to the outpatient clinic for treatment not long ago.
You know the Ribbon Killer? Where is he?
Where else can I be? I am the ribbon killer.
Even if this delays time
It's of no help to you or your mother.
Your mother doesn't even drink a sip of water now
Said I'd stand outside all night waiting for you to come out, brat
You're lying.
My mother should be busy now.
For her son who brought endless shame
Find a lawyer and fight for innocence.
Answer my question honestly
Why did you kill Kang Yoon-joo's puppy?
I didn't kill the dog.
Who killed that dog? Damn it.
My mother killed
My mother wanted to drive Yunzhu away
I killed the dog to scare her.
She raised the rent to get rid of her
Using all possible means in the community
But Yunzhu remained indifferent
Did you kill someone's well-fed puppy just because of this?
Ms. Choi Sun-ja, Chairwoman of Women's Association
To control his son
She can do even more outrageous things.
You and your mother are really amazing
I'm telling the truth
There's nothing special about this guy's call records. What should I do?
Whether it is the ribbon killer or the mastermind behind the scenes
[Call record details]
There is no doubt
No, I am the Ribbon Killer
Shut up damn it
First take out all your laptops and mobile phones for digital forensics
OK, I know.
You will regret it
What are you laughing at?
Is it fun?
nothing
Why do you always go to such dangerous places?
Is your dad back?
Maybe I'm worried that you'll go home depressed.
He's still drinking alone over there.
He has the nerve to drink alone
Secretly signed a contract to take over the coffee shop without authorization
He is really amazing that he quit his job secretly
This wine is so sweet
Park Seung-ho
[Coffee shop transfer contract]
From tomorrow you are the boss
I'm about to start the second chapter of my life
Wish me success
cheers
What can I do for you?
I'll look for Detective Noh Kang-sik.
Detective Lu?
Why are you here? Aren't you in the hospital?
Excuse me, can I see Park Tae-hoon now? Please.
We'll let you know when we finish our investigation.
Let's go back to the hospital first.
Detective Cui, please take her to the hospital.
Come on, I'll take you there.
That I...
I am the first witness of the Ribbon Killer
What
Do you remember 2003?
The first victim of the Ribbon Killer?
It was fished out from the Gangwon Province Deokjin Reservoir.
Uhm Ji-eun, a third-year student at Junghee Girls' High School
I was the one who went to the abandoned hospital with her on the day of the incident.
Scare me
How could you be scared by something like this?
Please finish the filming and go back quickly.
Otherwise you will miss the last bus.
I haven't finished shooting yet
How about this? I'll take pictures of the first floor and you'll take pictures of the second floor.
What? You asked me to go up to the second floor alone?
Well, we can finish the filming faster if we shoot separately.
knew
Then you have to sing for me when I'm on the second floor
What song do you want me to sing?
I won't be scared if you sing so funny
What to sing?
Kong Mi-ri will sing "Just a Feeling"
♪ Just a feeling, say it out loud♪
♪ Think about it ♪
♪ Don't hesitate ♪ You have to keep singing
♪ Just a feeling ♪ Can't stop halfway
♪ I'm ready♪
♪ Give you to me, I want to have you♪
♪ I want to get closer to you step by step, I want to have you♪
Ji Eun Uhm Ji Eun
Ji-eun
Uhm Ji-eun
If you come one step closer
Your friend will die.
Miri Save Me Miri
My friends were right in front of me, but I came out alive alone
You won't know
How have I lived till now?
If God could turn back time
I definitely wouldn't do that.
Even if it hurts him
Bite Him
I will protect her too.
Have a drink of water
Please let me meet Park Tae-hoon
I saw a suspicious man in the building before.
Park Tae-hoon still looked at him and smiled
Is he laughing?
He did smile at the man.
Maybe that man is the Ribbon Killer
We have to find the Ribbon Killer through Park Tae-hoon
I...
I must find the Ribbon Killer
Hello Yes
Park Tae-hoon hasn't come back yet?
Detective Wu is with him
Hello
What
How on earth do you do things?
This kid is in trouble.
What
Hurry up!
What trouble did you get into?
Come quickly
You wait here
What is going on?
[half an hour ago]
Criminal Police
You should know that you are violating human rights by doing this.
If you don't want to clean my ass
Could you please remove the handcuffs for me first?
I'll be out soon.
Tell me when it's over.
OK, thanks
Isn't it over yet?
Yeah, it'll take some time.
Hey Don
Dad is working?
Hey wife
that
Today is Don's birthday
But I'm not done here, sorry.
I will try to get off work early.
You wait a little longer
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey you kid
Hello, is there anyone outside?
Hey Mom
Hello
Just...let me...go
Tae Hoon Tae Hoon...
May 21, 2025 at 10:00 AM
Mr. Park Tae-hoon died
No no no Tae-hoon
Tae-hoon
how's it going
Dead
Kong Meili
I also said that Park So Hee has many secrets
You're better than me
We've all heard it.
It turns out that you are a friend of the first victim of the Ribbon Killer.
Do you need to be so exaggerated?
So corny
what to do
That guy is dead
Now there is no clue to catch the Ribbon Killer.
Hello
You are Hyun-ji's mother, right?
Please ask which
I am a resident of Room 1204, Building 213
What's the matter with you calling me so late?
I received a call from Fang Sulan
Fang Sulan?
I heard you were looking for me
I am the friend of Ji-eun's mother that you are looking for.
Minshan and I are neighbors living on the same floor as each other and call each other sisters.
[Recipient: Li Minshan]
Lee Min-sun
Her daughter died so early.
She has been living alone
One day I said I was going to see my daughter.
I thought she was going to the columbarium.
In the end, she really went to accompany her daughter.
Minshan used to live in the house where you live now.
[Special space for fire trucks]
Until death
Leave her alone. She must be in pain.
[No entry or exit cordon]
The hunter will not be the hunted
The hunter does not become the hunted, he just keeps hunting
He wants to be a real hunter.
Therefore, even when dying, I must choose a way to die that is worthy of being a hunter.
That is to end your life before becoming prey.
He kept imitating the hunter.
Refusing to become prey, dying a glorious death
It's time for the real hunter to show his true colors
Gods of Heaven and Earth
Please bring good luck and fortune to my brother's coffee shop.
Park Suzy, what are you doing?
I was worried because there were no customers.
If you keep posting stuff like that, you'll only get fewer and fewer customers.
This is a coffee shop, not a temple.
elder brother
I've staked all my fortune here.
If the cafe closes
I can't get married.
Good post
Also put it in the bathroom and on the coffee machine
Even on the dining table.
bring it on
What's this
I bought this from a very clever wizard.
Just post this and your business will be booming within a month.
Really
Certain
This is a really good location, right?
You're not being fooled, are you?
What nonsense are you talking about?
I not only did a survey beforehand
The number of customers was also counted by time.
But in broad daylight
Let alone people, I didn't even see an ant.
From one to twelve o'clock
At lunch time, customers will definitely rush in.
It's lunch time
So fast
From today on, I will start to lose weight and eat low-carb and high-fat food
Don't eat here
People outside will see it.
elder brother
I want a pretty girl to sit by the window
To attract guests
Who is the pretty girl? Hey, don't wave.
People will think this is a barbecue restaurant. Let's go.
Let me go and make me a cup of coffee
Go away go away go away
I want American
Auntie, it was you who led me to live in that house, right?
Why? Why did you bring me here?
[The late Lee Min-sun]
You don't want me to help you catch the Ribbon Killer, do you?
I want to catch him too.
But what should I do?
[The late Lee Min-sun]
Auntie, please help me
This thing is finally going to be returned to its original owner.
This is the sewing box.
When Min-sun's relatives cleaned up the house
Maybe he left it at the door and wanted to throw it away.
I put it away when I remembered Minshan.
I think you should keep it.
This is Minshan's work.
She would make dolls for fun
It is said that it can eliminate distracting thoughts in the mind.
How could this...
These are the scissors you asked me to buy.
This is the same pair of scissors Ji-eun bought that day
How come the scissors in Ji-eun's schoolbag disappeared?
Could it be that someone used it?
It should be Ji-eun and the murderer
One of the two.
Miri, what do you think about this?
I...
what to do
I have no idea
Your expression...
Did you also make this expression and beg him to spare your life?
sorry
I'm really sorry
Damn sorry sorry
You go
I don't want to see you again
I shouldn't have treated her like that that day.
Misato is so young, what did she do wrong?
Ji-eun
It's late but I still want to apologize to you
Miri, I'm sorry.
Can you forgive auntie?
Ji-eun
It's been more than 20 years since you passed away.
In a world without you, Mom has actually lived this long.
Is mom too heartless?
Tomorrow I will go to the flower market with my sister who lives in No. 1204
Take care of your children like...
She is the only one who can comfort me
Every time I think of my Ji Eun
[The 21st regular event of the Ribbon Killer Victims' Families Association]
They are the ones who stay by my side and give me strength.
Our precious daughter was brutally murdered.
But the police have not found a single clue yet.
Now I even have someone who treats me like his own son
No. 1204 Qing Shujie
We provide home delivery service
Not only is she beautiful
Ji Hyun, the kind-hearted owner of Gwangsan Supermarket
Oh, you're soaked.
Lao Jin, the administrator who helped me when I encountered difficulties
A very kind person
Is my depression getting worse?
If I take medicine, will the problem of doubting people disappear?
I want to find a way to dispel this doubt
I can't keep living in torment like this.
Who is she suspecting?
[There will be an event for the Victims' Families Association at 2pm on Friday]
[Went to the police station at 4pm to urge them to reopen the investigation]
Victims' Families Association
Is this the Ribbon Killer Victims' Bereaved Association?
What's this
torment
Can't hold on...
This is clearly a trace of what was written on the previous page.
Why is there no previous page?
Scare me
Haven't slept yet?
What's going on? Are you waiting for me?
Clang
This is your favorite snack. It's top grade.
[Sangju Dried Persimmon]
Super sweet premium persimmon cake Sangju persimmon cake
What kind of dried persimmons should we eat in our situation?
The thought of the loan interest is overwhelming.
Could you please stop reading?
You are so angry, I have been asking for your forgiveness
Running a cafe is not easy at all. I am dying of exhaustion.
No guests either
What
Didn't you say it was a good location?
You weren't deceived by your first love, were you?
What are you cheating about?
Stop before you continue to lose money
How can I stop that...
I know, I shut up.
My mother called me just now and asked me
Asked if the house sale information has been posted
I won't move.
Didn't you say the last landlord was your friend's mother?
The daughter was murdered and the mother committed suicide
Every corner of the house is filled with resentment
If you're scared, go to your mother's house.
Why do you want to separate from me just for such a small matter?
Sorry, sorry.
never mind
Wait a moment
It's my mom's phone.
Hey Mom
What's this
The house sale information has not been posted yet.
[Information]
Insider
I'm fine. I'm not afraid of ghosts.
[Bupyeong Cheolsan 2-dong Fengbo Apartment 301]
Fengbo Apartment No. 301
goodbye
[Fengbo Apartment]
Why did Auntie check my original address?
I want to formally entrust you with a task
I would like to know the information of the person who asked you to check this address
Tell me everything you know
I want to know everything for this little money.
My husband doesn't earn much.
Please understand.
Ouch
Name
Kong Meili
Oh, that's right.
[Bupyeong Cheolsan 2-dong Fengbo Apartment 301]
I wrote this for her.
Do you know how much I suffered to find this out?
Gangbuk DistrictDobong DistrictGwanak DistrictBupyeong
You've moved so many times.
How about you meeting that old man?
No, she died.
Was there an accident?
It's me...
Left
Suicide?
When did this happen?
February of this year
[Event Letter of Authorization]
[Provide Kong Meili's address to the client in January 2025]
I wrote this address for her in January.
It's exactly one month later.
Are you sure she committed suicide?
What
yes
People who committed suicide one month later
It is impossible to investigate others
Do you mean aunt?
In fact, the day I wrote down this address for her
[Bupyeong Cheolsan 2-dong Fengbo Apartment 301]
She asked me to check one more thing.
Please help me find someone for her.
Who did she ask you to check?
(Note: Approximately NT$2,100)
I can only say so much with 100,000 won.
I can't say it anymore. I can't say it anymore.
[The murderer who killed my son]
Oh my god, what is the murderer who killed my son?
That is to say
This is easy to wipe off, don't worry
Oh, what are you doing?
Wise
Mom, why did you come back just now?
What happened, sister?
Don't mention it
The Women's Association President said
We took our son away.
Make a lot of noise here
I was just taken away by the administrator.
Hyun-ji, you go in here first, mom will sort it out
knew
[The murderer who killed my son]
Thank you for coming.
The front door of my house and Ji-hyun's house
She messed up everything.
She said we killed her son.
Keep asking us to return the people.
In that case
Can it bring the dead victims back to life?
Why don't you think about the victim's family?
But the women's association leader said something strange before she left.
She said someone told her
Kim Kwang-kyu is the real murderer
Kim Kwang-kyu
Who told her?
yes
The police confirmed that he was not a suspect and he was living well.
Why involve him?
Kim Kwang-gyu
What are you doing here?
Scare me
Why is your house so empty?
It has everything it should have.
The Women's Association President suspects that you are the person behind Park Tae-hoon
Who do you think is the one who framed you for the murder?
If there was one, they would have been arrested and handed over to the police.
I thought about it carefully
Could the person who framed you be Park Tae-hoon's accomplice?
What's the meaning
That day
That was the day you were framed as the murderer and taken away by the police.
Park Tae-hoon was preparing for his third murder at No. 405
At that time, someone anonymously reported you as the murderer.
Report innocent people
Trying to buy time for Park Tae-hoon to commit the crime
And they are interfering with us who are looking for Suxi.
Oh my god, you really care about Park Tae-hoon's case.
I heard that you were a classmate of the high school girl killed by the Ribbon Killer.
Is that why you're so persistent?
How do you know this?
I was released from the police station.
I heard this when I visited you in the hospital.
I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
You must have felt heavy-hearted over the past twenty years.
If I could, I really want to catch him myself.
Maybe the Ribbon Killer thinks
21 years ago, he personally let that high school girl go
It was the mistake of his life.
Because the root of evil was not removed that day
Are you saying that I might die at the hands of that person?
If I were the Ribbon Killer, I would definitely do this
Is it me who dies or him who dies?
You have to try it to know.
He is old
And I am no longer a timid girl
I don't think Park Tae-hoon acted alone.
He should have been ordered to kill someone.
Or the person who led him to kill
You mean that person is the one who reported me?
He is the real Ribbon Killer
If it weren't for the Ribbon Killer himself
The one who was ordered by the Ribbon Killer
Let's make a deal
wrong
I think we should cooperate.
Cooperation?
Excuse me, uncle
[The murderer who killed my son]
Drink some of this before you do it.
Sorry for the trouble. Thanks.
Excuse me
Have you heard Auntie say who she suspects?
Even if someone doubts her, she will just keep it to herself.
I won't tell others easily.
Oh, there's something quite strange.
What is it?
On rainy days, you have to eat pancakes.
She hasn't come to see me for a while. What's wrong?
One day she came to me with a bad look on her face.
What's wrong
But she suddenly said
elder sister
If there is someone you want to kill
Will you kill him?
Someone you want to kill?
What happened?
I have someone I want to kill.
I must kill him myself.
I think it might be about the person who killed her daughter.
So I didn't continue asking.
Then a week later something happened.
It should be two days before the victims' family association meeting
Just leave it alone, I'll take care of it
I always owe favors to the residents
Always give back
I heard that the women's association president has been giving you trouble.
It probably won't happen after a while.
By the way, the previous resident of this house
Ms. Lee Min-sun
Ms. Li
I later found out she was my friend's mother
I just found out recently.
This is too coincidental.
yes
Are you familiar with her?
She is a very kind person.
I was told that I was a man living alone and gave me some side dishes.
Is a very good person
I don't know why I made such an extreme choice.
I also want to know
Wait a moment
Hello
Yes I know
What should I do? I have to leave first.
Oh, you are so busy, why are you still here to help me? Go quickly
Thanks for your hard work
So painful
I can't hold on any longer.
[It’s so painful, I can’t bear it any longer, I’ll go find you right away]
I'll find you soon
It's so painful I can't stand it anymore
[It’s so painful that I can’t bear it any longer. I want to be by your side...I want to rest]
I want to rest by your side...
Mom will come to you soon.
[I want to be with you...I will come to you right away after you have a rest]
Could this be...
It's so painful I can't stand it anymore
I want to rest by your side...
[It’s so painful that I can’t bear it any longer. I want to be by your side...I want to rest]
I'll find you soon
This is an incomplete sentence.
This is what my aunt wrote in her diary, and it's imprinted on the next page.
I copied down everything I could see.
Is this a suicide note?
So I want to confirm the contents of the suicide note, sister.
Come and see
This is the indentation where the words were written on the previous page
But the previous page is gone.
So sister, what you mean is that the page before it disappeared might be a suicide note, right?
But even if the previous page that disappeared was a suicide note
I always feel like something is wrong
What is a sister's suicide note?
What can
Aren't these the last words left before dying?
But you see, this is not the last page.
There is also something written at the back
Since it is not the last page
This means that this is not necessarily what was written before death.
That's right
I fully understand that you care about that person's death and feel sorry for her.
But you're wrong to suspect she didn't commit suicide.
What's wrong
If the death was caused by homicide
There will be traces left at the crime scene.
Such as the footprints or fingerprints of a second person
But there was no sign of murder.
That's why the police closed the case as suicide.
But now you doubt that it was not suicide
You are denying the police's findings.
It is also an insult to the Korean police.
I did not mean that
Maybe the police missed some clue.
so
You mean
South Korean Police
No, my husband who was in charge of the case at the time was a fool, right?
Oh, sister, why are you talking like that?
Qiu Qingzi, why are you so excited again?
Can't we do this in front of the police's family?
Raise reasonable doubt?
All right
If you disagree, stop talking.
elder sister
Are you really leaving like this?
Miri
I know you have a good sixth sense.
But don't trust that too much.
It might become a weapon to frame a good person.
elder sister
If you go over now, there will be another argument.
I'll go check it out
elder sister
It seems that Sister Qingzi is really angry
She seems to have misunderstood me.
Let her be
Even if she left in anger now, she wouldn't last more than a day.
Qiu Qingzi will never bear grudges.
What are these? So many
Everyone applaud!
I also want to find a woman with a good temper like my sister-in-law
What are you saying?
This seems a bit inappropriate.
But my sister-in-law is totally my dream girl
Really
Sister-in-law, I have something to give you
This is it
You lunatic, who are you competing with for love now?
Oh, but what to do?
My dream lover is Lu Kangzhi
What a shit dream girl
What does it mean to come here late at night?
Please do just one thing.
You must be asking me to do something weird.
Otherwise, they are threatening me.
What is the threat?
Everyone works so hard day and night.
How about this? Call over all the people who are working overtime.
Come on, everybody.
Team leader, Detective Jiang, please come over.
Suicide Note
I heard that the day when Lee Min-sun jumped off the building
Left a suicide note
There should be a suicide note in the case file.
Is it for this? Is it for this? To perform this act in the middle of the night?
Otherwise why would I do this?
So sudden and inexplicable in the middle of the night
Waste of money, time, energy
Why am I so tired?
I don't allow it because of my self-esteem.
Otherwise I wouldn't come to you.
Disclosure of case records is prohibited
You were a police officer, so why are you still saying this?
Go back quickly
no
It's all because Kong Meili said the old man's death didn't seem like suicide.
What does this mean?
She thinks he was murdered.
These aunties are addicted to the detective game.
There's no medicine for this.
And you think we only rely on a suicide note
Just close the case as suicide?
It was based on the situation at the time
Conclusions from the investigation and autopsy results
I said, of course I know.
I used to be a policeman.
So you say I can't be angry?
She said it was murder.
Not that you had 24 hours a day.
How could I not know if I was investigated day and night 365 days a year?
Don't touch me
It hurts my self-esteem.
Do you think it's reasonable to say that he killed me?
Didn't Aunt Kong Meili say it was murder?
right
I'm speechless.
She said he killed her.
You also feel hurt in your self-esteem, right?
Qiu Qingzi just knows how to control me
This is also a form of emotional blackmail
[Report on Lee Min-sun's suicide by falling from a building]
That's why I said my previous boss was terrible.
[The cause of death was a skull fracture and other fractures caused by jumping from a building...]
[Based on the suicide note in the house and the shape and direction of the indoor tow truck on the balcony, it is judged that the person jumped from the building spontaneously]
Hello sister
Miri
The old man once ordered dried persimmons
Order dried persimmons?
I know someone in Sangju
We started selling dried persimmons last year.
I now find that the elderly have ordered gift boxes of dried persimmons
[Reservation of gift box dried persimmons for Room 1004, Building 213, February 15, 2025]
[The order was cancelled due to the sudden death of the orderer.]
It was booked on February 15th this year.
She died on February 20th, exactly 5 days ago.
Auntie should meet me
That persimmon
It should be sent to me.
She said at the time
It's for an important person I haven't seen for a long time.
She still remembers that I like to eat dried persimmons
elder sister
Do you think your aunt really died of suicide?
Miri
if
What would you do if her death was not suicide?
Of course we have to find out the truth
I will find out the truth
Hello, this is the management office.
This is number 1104. My toilet is clogged.
Please call someone.
Who should I call in the middle of the night?
Lend me the toilet tool
How long will you live here?
There is still one month left before the contract expires
The rent has been paid
Is this your first time in the basement?
What's wrong? Is there anything here?
There is a musty smell that is so unpleasant
Return it after use.
I've been away from my position for too long. I'm leaving now.
Please help me check something through this person
Because he never told me
But this matter
Is it really related to the Ribbon Killer?
What you need to know if you want to find out the truth
There has never been such a service so far
I am the gossipy Director Jin.
Hey, this customer is calling so late, is there something wrong?
Usually the people who call at this time want to find out about an affair.
How about I check on your wife?
Guangshan Community Housing Building 213, No. 1004
Who is the person Li Minshan asked you to investigate?
Damn this gentleman.
This is not a case commissioned by a deceased person.
Why should I tell you guys who don't even know who it is?
Please cooperate while I am talking.
I know you are using your former police identity
Using connections to help people investigate
Do you not even want the civil servant pension?
You also charge high fees to the client.
Do you pay your income tax honestly?
I have a registered business license and I am doing business legally. What do you know?
Since it is so open and aboveboard
I want to investigate too.
Is it legal for you to investigate others?
Is that an illegal credit agency?
Hey, you dare to investigate me?
I've never seen a rogue like you.
Hello, who are you?
Please reply me as soon as possible
Hello
Ouch
recorder
For mini recorders
She even ordered fried chicken just to ask me that.
Oh, thank you.
There are coupons inside, please use them slowly
that...
Wait a moment
I want to trouble you with one thing
Why does she need a mini recorder?
So did you tell her?
It's not because she doesn't know how to shop online
So I bought her one.
I don't know what she's going to do with it though.
But I feel like she really needs that thing.
I'm leaving
Su Hee
Do you also think my suspicion is exaggerated?
If that's the case
Would I make this trip so late?
(Note: about NT$63)
I can earn an extra 3,000 won by running one more delivery.
I trust you
Good night, sister
Mini Recorder
She even ordered fried chicken just to ask me that.
Park Hyun-ji
Have you slept yet?
Don't forget to bring your sportswear again and run home. Remember to bring it with you.
Did you hear that, Park Hyun-ji?
Park Hyun-ji
What's this
boss
It's me
I just ordered a latte but it was not hot.
Usually drinks with milk are not too hot.
I often order this at other places.
But it's never been so cold
Wait a mininute
It's a bit cold.
I'll warm it up for you.
You already drank it
Me?
sorry...
This is my first time opening a shop. I will make you a new cup.
never mind
I'm sorry
I'm really sorry
OK...got it
Next time I come I'll give you a hot cup
No
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
It's all because of that spell.
You will be damned if you say that.
Hello Hyunji
The temperature is just right and the foam is dense. It tastes so good.
I told you not to come, why are you still coming?
Dad, haven't you had dinner yet?
This is the seaweed rice roll from the convenience store. It's not very hot.
Why buy this? Your pocket money is not much.
If you know, you can make more money.
Only daughter cares about her father the most
Not all cafes are open.
But why doesn't my sister-in-law come here once?
Isn't that too much?
So I'm here
Wife
Park Hyun-ji, why don't you come over to me?
It's because my mother didn't let me come here.
You are a student who doesn't study hard.
Why are you here so late?
I told her to come here because she was bored.
And why are you hiding? I can see you.
Mom, don't you think Dad is pitiful?
Your dad is really pitiful.
Pitiful
The most pitiful one is me who lives with your father.
Come quickly
Don't say anything, there are guests here.
A family should unite.
To save money
Dad doesn't hire part-time students, he does everything himself
Don't you think he's pitiful?
A man who ran out of money and took over a coffee shop full of flies
What's so pitiful?
The problem is there aren't even any flies.
Hello
Sorry, guest
We're so noisy. Sorry.
Oh... I will treat you well next time
Even the last table of guests has been sent away.
Park Seung-ho, do you really want to live such a humble life?
Why don't you listen to me?
Did I say stop before you lose everything?
I'm so sorry
I am helpless and hopeless, okay?
sister in law
Do you have to tell him off like this in a shop that's open for business?
Brother, where are you going? I don't know how to make coffee.
Mom, you're taking it too far.
Can't you forgive Dad?
What
Dad also wants to do business well.
Only then will I humbly cater to the guests.
What's wrong with doing something that hurts your self-esteem for your family?
Isn't this what parents are supposed to do?
dad
No one is on my side.
I don't know if the person who said he wanted to cooperate performed well.
[No. 1004 Miri Auntie]
Why don't you answer the phone?
Wow, delicious
Not with Ji Hyun
Why did you suddenly come here alone?
I provoked my husband and he sent this to me.
This is the content of Li Minshan's suicide note
Really
elder sister
Take a look
[It’s so painful that I can’t bear it any longer. I want to be by your side...I want to rest]
The handwritten suicide note found that day
Almost the same as the contents of the missing diary
[Mom will come to you right away]
elder sister
Auntie wrote it down at the back of this page
Activities of the Victims' Families Association and lunch volunteer schedule
She wrote this down to show that she would attend
Write down your suicide note on the first page and the activity time on the second page
This is contradictory.
It is true.
Even so, are you sure this isn't a suicide note?
Was it just a few words to vent my feelings at that time?
It was packaged as a suicide note by someone other than my aunt.
Attempted to disguise his murder as suicide
elder sister
A few days before my aunt passed away
Asked Suxi where to buy a mini recorder
Where should an elderly person in his seventies use it?
Gathering evidence
People like me who have doubts
But there is a lack of definitive evidence
Who is the person who has doubts?
Is this someone we know?
When I went in, I found it was a two-story house.
[The rough scene I saw was]
The scene I saw roughly was
The shelves have not been moved yet.
[I heard you want to explore abandoned houses?]
I heard you want to explore abandoned houses.
[I really want to go but I have a mock exam soon]
I really want to go but I have a mock exam soon.
[It was a close call]
It's a close call. If you were to compete, it would be too intense.
[If you are also involved in the competition, it will be too fierce. Where is the location?]
Is the location decided?
[Have you booked it yet?] [Someone I know recommended it but it’s a bit far]
Someone I know recommended it to me, but it's a bit far.
But that place is horrible
But that place is horrible.
Where is it?
[Where is it?]
But you really didn't tell your mother?
[But you really won’t tell your mother?]
[Are you crazy? Will my mom let me go? I want to go secretly]
Are you crazy? Will my mom let me go?
I'm going to go secretly
I'm almost there. I'm in front of the building.
Yes, it's almost here, sister.
elder sister
Su Hee
This is the same mini recorder I bought for the elderly.
After charging, just press the power button
Where is she going to use it when it's so small?
Did she record successfully?
Sister, have you found anything?
I asked my husband
He said that the old man's belongings
No mini recorder
If they had, they would have listened to it a long time ago.
Too
Sister, I have a plug-in
Thank you for contacting me tomorrow.
Hello, Mr. Kim
Ms. Kong Meili
You are really rude.
You're not doing this right, are you?
What does that mean?
That person actually evaded taxes by operating illegally
and civil servants' pensions openly threatened me
Who is that person?
Anyway, I told him everything I knew.
Don't look for me anymore, got it?
What is Kim Kwang-kyu doing?
Since it is a collaboration, any information should be shared immediately.
See how I teach him a lesson
The person my aunt suspected was...
[Graduation certificate]
[132, Seongyun-ri, Gundeokjeong Township, Gangwondo Town, Kimhyeon-deok]
[Dezhen Reservoir]
Gangwon Province, Gangwon Province
Kim Hyeon-deok's hometown where he lived until he was 9 years old
Ji-eun's body was found at
Dezhen Reservoir
[Dezhen Reservoir]
Is this your first time in this basement?
What's wrong
Is there anything here?
[Recipient: Li Minshan, Room 1004, Building 213]
How come this is here?
It seems that you like this place too. What do you want to say?
I'm here to return the toilet tools.
I heard she has a tape recorder, did you know that?
recorder
Elder No. 1004 bought a tape recorder a few days before he died.
I ask you
Is it me or that woman you want to help?
I want to help you, teacher.
Just like you helped me ten years ago
You're dead today, little bastard.
Please stop here.
Got him.
You are dead
What's up to here
I don't know how fast and skillful the teacher's movements were.
Old...Teacher, don't...
To be honest, I'm scared too.
Should I say it's a technique that looks like it's been done many times?
Even though you just made him faint
How are you
I'm fine
Kim Hyeon-deok, 54, was a member of the special forces
Ten years ago, my teaching career ended due to an ignominious incident.
I used to work as a truck driver and a deliveryman.
[Teacher, temporary worker, truck driver, delivery worker, administrator]
Then I came to Guangshan Community as an administrator
alright
Wipe it with this.
Thanks
I wonder if there are any clothes you can wear at home.
Oh, no need.
Auntie investigated and found out that the reason why he bought the tape recorder was
[Note: Commissioned to investigate Kim Hyun-deok]
Uncle Jin, the administrator who helped me when I was in trouble
He is a very kind person.
[Will my paranoia disappear if I take medicine? Is what I see real?]
It is wrong to doubt kind people.
[It is wrong to doubt kind people... It seems that my paranoia has come back again]
The kind person who always makes people suspicious
A few months before Minshan's accident
She was worried that the letters from the victims' families association had not been sent.
Letter?
[Association of Victims’ Families]
Victims' Families Association
Give it to me, I'll help you return it.
No return letter was found.
No return letter?
That letter
It's the letter from Lee Min-sun that was sent to my house before.
You said you would help me return it, remember?
Yes
I remember I returned it the next day.
The person who lied to me that he had returned the letter from the Victims' Families Association
Because they were too close, they didn't notice the criminal hiding right under their noses.
It turns out that he is the administrator of this community.
Jin Xiande
Brother
Park Tae-hoon's digital forensics results are out
One step late every time
His case was discontinued long ago.
What's this
[One month ago]
I can die I can die I can die
I can
It's because you're so useless
Only then will you be bullied by cats and dogs
What do you know?
You are a good prey.
You said I was prey
Next time you try to commit suicide, I won't stop you.
But since I was born in this world
Isn't it better to be the hunter than the prey?
[Since I was born into this world, it is better to be a hunter than to be the prey...]
It wasn't such an important thing, but he actually left it at the door and left.
The call you made was not answered
Why don't you answer the phone?
[Park Hyun-ji]
The call you made was not answered
Help! Help!
Mom, save me
[Thanks to actor Han Sangjin for his friendly guest appearance]
[Preview of the next episode]
Mother
I'm going to kill you myself.
Wise
This time, it's your decision.
Do you want your daughter to die or do you want to save her?
Go now
It's urgent.
Wise
No one gets out of here alive.
don't want
Your death is coming.
Wise
Miri
You've failed as a mother.
Wise
[Lee Si-hyung Kong Mi-ri]
[Jeong Young-joo Qiu Qingzi]
[Kim Da-soon Park So-hee]
[Nanji loves Jun Ji-hyun]
[Zheng Sangxun and Park Seungho]
[Oh Dae-hwan and Noh Kang-sik]
["Housewives Detective Agency"]