Visitors
Bring me a whip.
Queen
What mistake did my uncle make?
You punish me like this again
Jiang Qingyue
You are so brave.
How dare you pretend to be the disciple of Dr. Song He
This caused me and the Third Prince to lose face in front of the Queen Mother.
Did You Know
If you cause any trouble to the Queen Mother
Not only you and the Jiang family will be confiscated and exterminated
It will also implicate the Third Prince
Queen
I am really the disciple of Dr. Song He
Otherwise
How could I use this matter to deceive you and the Queen Mother?
It must be Jiang Qingyue
She framed me
Dare to quibble
If you are really a disciple of the divine doctor
How could I not even notice a small cervical spondylosis?
Instead, the princess cured him immediately.
I
It seems
The Prime Minister's Office didn't teach you well.
From today
I will personally teach you
Lord, save me
Lord
The Queen Mother cares so much about you
Thank you, mother.
Thank you, mother
I'd like to see
That bitch
What else can you do?
Go and invite His Majesty and the Seventh Princess and the Seventh Prince
Just say
Motomiya
Invite them to enjoy the flowers