Should apologize to him?
Damn girl
Ignoring me all morning.
Didn't even give me a chance to apologize
No
I gotta talk to her.
Hello?
The puppy is fixed
Are you free later?
I'll send it to you.
OK
How much? I'll transfer it to you.
I've done President Tang such a big favour
Aren't you going to thank me for that?
The company has just released some new limited edition products
I'll tell the marketing department to send them to you
I don't want any new products
Then what?
I haven't eaten homely food for a long time.
Why don't we go to your home later?
Let's try Chuxia's cooking
Will she mind?
OK
I'll send you the address
President Tang
This is a detailed list of the new products for the flagship store next week.
Please confirm and sign.
Wait a moment
President Tang
Any more instructions?
Miss Jiang is coming to visit us this afternoon.
Mrs. Sun has taken leave
Choose a favourite restaurant
Order a few dishes to be delivered to my home
Miss Jiang?
Then why don't you ask her what she likes to eat
She needs to stay in shape.
She can't eat much.
In the end, you'll have to handle the food.
Got it
There is an outsider today
Behave yourself later
Don't let people think we don't get along.
Miss Jiang is my friend too.
I'll behave myself
Hungry?
It's quite hard to find here
I was worried you'd get lost.
I used to come here to play with my friends before I went abroad
So I'm familiar with it.
Such a coincidence
Can I come more often in the future?
After the debut
I've almost lost touch with all my friends at home
Of course you can.
When did you become so close?
The secrets of girls?
Did Chuxia cook all these?
The future president's wife of Wanmao
is virtuous both inside and outside
I...
We ordered these at a restaurant
we often go to.
She is too tired to be my special assistant
I don't want her to bother with the housework too
Well.
I almost forgot the important thing.
What else are you bringing?
Why are you so polite?
Is this...
Thank you.
From now on
get along with it
Chuxia
Is this the worthless ornament you mentioned
and President Tang made a fuss about?
I didn't say it was a worthless ornament.
It's a gift from President Tang's family
It's important to him
How do you know it's from my relatives?
You said that before.
Did you forget?
Is it really from your relatives?
Chuxia
We are friends,
But this time I'm going to side with President Tang
As a qualified fiancée
You should care more about each other
Why don't you even know
such a little thing?
You're so careless.
Yes.
I was too careless
As your fiancée
I have to know you from others
Chuxia
Sorry
I need stay in shape too
I'm not eating
Enjoy your meal
Chuxia
The actress should control her diet too
Take care.
Aren't you going to see me out?
Don't you know this place well?
I have to go to Chuxia later.
Did Chuxia react that way
bacause she took me as a rival in love?
She's too careless.
Actually, Chuxia is very good
But as the future president's wife of Wan Mao
she needs to be more attentive
After all, President Tang, you are surrounded by so many temptations
I mean she's so careless
that she always trusts people so easily
She's not even aware of the crisis around her
Or maybe she knows I'm partial to her
So for the people who appear to me
She was always emboldened
She should be given a sense of crisis.
Take care.
You dummy
You thought Jiang Zhixi was genuinely trying to help you?
It was a deliberate attempt to step on you
to prove how good she is
and how well matched she is with Tang Jingxing
And you?
You can't even turn hostile.
After all, you're just an impostor?
What are you doing?
You're crying.
I didn't
I've just gotten sleepy.
Chuxia
I want to apologize to you
For what?
The thing with the puppy ornament.
I didn't tell you
what it meant to me
You didn't mean it either
So I shouldn't have gotten so angry with you.
Any more?
Except for this thing
What else should I apologize for?
Your secret affair with Jiang Zhixi.
When did I have a secret affair with her?
The puppy ornament thing
You tell her about the ornament but you don't tell me
You're jealous.
I...
I, as your fiancée
If you don't tell me these things
How can I act with you?
Good point
We should really learn each other in a deeper way.
Deeper?
How?
We'll see
In broad daylight
I...
I'm not ready yet