Hello?
Miss Jiang
Hey, Chuxia
I have a notice near Wanmao today
It is just finished. I'm exhausted.
I was going to greet you and President Tang
at noon
But I saw you were busy
I didn't even get to talk to you
Why did you go after seeing me?
So Miss Jiang wanted to see me too.
Why do I always get the wrong idea about her?
I saw you two talking about something
I didn't think it was a good idea to disturb you two.
So I didn't visit you
I went there for you
But you weren't there
I talked with President Tang
Let's not talk about that
How are you two getting on?
I don't know
whether our relationship has developed
I was too embarrassed to ask him directly
It's time to offer my second move
What is that?
Show yourself more
But I've been around him every day
Working hours don't count
You have to show yourself with quality and quantity in private
Think about it
What man can handle
a little clingy little girl?
OK, I'll
have a try
From the beauty of next door
It's the twenty-seventh letter of the month
It is only the thirteenth day of this month
Are you free?
Don't do this anymore.
You're so heartless
She has written you so many love letters
You didn't read a single word
I'm sick of these clingy girls.
Well
What type do you like?
Why are you asking this kind of question
that little girls would ask?
Did some
nymphomaniac
send you to spy me?
No, no, no.
I have a sister
She's quite pretty
Maybe it's your type
Wow
We've known each other for so long
You didn't even tell me you had a sister.
But
did your sister look like you?
You'll end up alone
Nothing to worry about
You are no different.
Brother
I'm the only one who can stay with Xiao Jing
Wanna eat grapes?
Not now.
Coffee?
Later.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
No, it's okay.
Are you trying to do Mrs. Sun's job?
I am
just getting some exercise
Exercise.
I acted on an impulse
Why didn't
I even think of an opening line
Should I ask him if he likes me?
The Matchmaker
Cupid
Please give me some inspiration
What are you hiding?
It's obvious that you are hiding something from me
Do you
Damn.
Will he find out that I have a crush on him?
want a promotion and a pay rise again?
What a straight man!
Of course, I'm a straight man.
Keep hiding
Tang Jingxing
I'm so virtuous
Can't you give me a compliment?
It's said that there's a veil between women and men
It's the Himalaya that separates us
The Qinghai-Tibet Plateau
What are you muttering about?
I'm sorry.
Mi Chuxia
Why do you touch my stuff?
I didn't do it intentionally
Get out!
It's just an ornament.
Why are you so angry?
Get out!
Miss Jiang
What happened?
I seem to have made him angry again
I broke something very important to him.
What is it?
Is it important?
Just a crystal puppy
But from his reactions
I think it's important
Should I apologise to him?
If you apologize now
that's like throwing gasoline on a pretentious fire
Just let him cool off.
Thank you for repairing the necklace you for me
It doesn't show any signs of damage.
I'm sorry.
I sent the wrong person
Hope I did not disturb you.
Can you give me the contact details of this craftsman?
I have something that needs him to repair.
Sorry.
He doesn't take orders anymore
But we had a good personal relationship
If you need it
You can ask him for help
in my name
Thanks. Miss Jiang
Why can't I find it?
Did the factory stop production?
Is it from his ex-girlfriend?
No.
He doesn't have an ex-girlfriend.
Why can't I find it?
Chuxia
Mi Chuxia