♪ Beautiful love ♪
♪ When you find it ♪
♪ You try to embrace it ♪
♪ You dedicate to it ♪
♪ You give it your all ♪
♪ So that it lasts forever ♪
♪ But sometimes
it turns into darkness ♪
♪ If you love so much
that it blinds you ♪
♪ Beauty can turn into pain ♪
♪ If love ends in vengeance ♪
♪ Will you still embrace it? ♪
♪ If love is gained
in exchange for someone's life ♪
♪ Will you still say this love
is what you wanted? ♪
♪ If love ends in vengeance ♪
♪ Will you still embrace it? ♪
♪ If love is gained
in exchange for someone's life ♪
♪ Will you still say this love
is what you wanted? ♪
Malai hasn't given me a child.
I had to find a solution.
That's a selfish thing to say.
What's the big deal?
Didn't you take me here
to be your wife?
Why haven't you fucked me yet?
What are you doing, Dech?
I'm gonna prove that I meant it.
If you want me to die,
I'll die to make up
for the wrong I did to you.
Goodness me!
Malai!
Chaem!
The tonic, ma'am.
Thanks, Fueang.
What medicine is that?
It's a tonic, my lord.
Count Phichit was kind enough
to bring it this afternoon.
But we have red cotton flower tea.
It works the same way.
It doesn't hurt to try, sir.
If it helps me conceive your child,
I won't turn away
any kind of medicine.
Then it's up to you.
What's wrong, ma'am?
What's wrong, Malai?
Why is it…
so sour, Fueang?
How can it be? I brewed it myself.
Are you sure
you brewed it yourself?
I'm sure, my lord.
May I taste it?
Why does it taste like vinegar?
She's probably choked on
vinegar to death by now.
Serves her right.
She's trying to have
the viscount's child before I do.
Your plan was so clever.
Fueang had no idea.
Someone like her is too slow.
No wonder she serves that toff.
Don't look at me like that.
I don't wanna see your face either.
Then why are you here?
Someone's here to see you.
They're waiting at the gate.
Did they say who they were
and where they were from?
I don't know. I've just got here.
How would I know?
It won't kill you
leaving the medicine pot for a bit.
-Go on then.
-Yeah.
Idiot.
I won't let you
boost anything, Malai.
This is the one.
Chaem, mark my words.
No matter what,
I'm gonna have the viscount's
child before that toff.
Of course you are.
And I'm gonna help you
any way I can, Ms. Ramphoei.
-By hook…
-Or by crook.
Thank you, my lord.
It's fine that
the tonic isn't drinkable.
You have red cotton flower tea.
There are some tonic herbs left.
I'll brew you a new batch.
I'll watch the pot
from start to finish this time.
Thank you, Fueang.
Yes, ma'am.
If there's nothing else,
I'll take my leave.
Goodness me, my lord!
Uh…
Ms. Ramphoei's sick again.
Again? What's wrong
with her this time?
I don't know either,
but she wanted to see you, my lord.
Where's His Lordship?
He said he'd come by.
-Really?
-Yes.
But you have to lie down
so it looks convincing.
Lie down, ma'am.
Please come in, Your Lordship.
Thanks, Chaem.
Fueang, who sent you here?
Where's His Lordship?
His Lordship sent me.
Who else could it be?
Where is he?
He's with Ms. Malai, ma'am.
He doesn't have time
to take care of you, Ms. Ramphoei.
Fueang, get out!
Get out of my sight!
Yes, ma'am. Yes, ma'am. Yes, ma'am.
I wish you a speedy recovery,
Ms. Ramphoei.
You'll get it.
Arrogant, both of them.
This must be Malai's doing.
His Lordship would never be
this heartless with me.
Right, Chaem?
Yes, ma'am.
So will His Lordship come back
to you, Ms. Ramphoei?
Is that your mouth?
I'll slap it off your face.
You don't need to.
I'll do it myself.
It hurts so bad, ma'am.
If Malai's waging war
against me like this,
I'll give her what she deserves.
This house will have
only one female master.
And that's me.
Malai?
Good night, Malai.
Oh!
Phoem!
I want to make magic love powder.
Use this for now.
(House of the Dark Shadows
novel: Phakhinai, screenplay: Wannason)
Come, Malai.
Come.
Sit down.
Thank you.
Is your master
feeling better, Chaem?
Oh, she is, my lord.
She's better,
but why hasn't she come down
to have breakfast with us?
I'll bring it up to her.
Whatever you do,
take good care of her.
Yes, my lord.
Fueang, prepare the breakfast
for Chaem to take to Ramphoei.
Yes, Ms. Malai.
Uh, that's okay, Ms. Malai.
I'll prepare it and bring it up.
Jeez, it's not a bother.
You're one of us.
Let's eat, Malai, while
the soft-boiled rice is still hot.
Yes, my lord.
-Oh!
Dech.
Ms. Ramphoei!
What are you doing here, ma'am?
It's dangerous for a woman
to be here alone.
It's none of your business
what I'm doing.
What are you doing here?
I'm here on
the viscount's business.
Would you like me to wait until
you're done and accompany you back?
No need. I can get back by myself.
Go on your way.
Yes, ma'am.
Out of all people
I had to run into.
-Oh!
-Hey.
Phoem!
What took you so long?
I saw you talk to that guy.
Who is he?
A servant at the house.
I thought he wouldn't leave.
I was thinking of killing him.
You can't do that.
You being a robber on the run
got me and Dad in enough trouble.
So what's going on
that made you called me here?
I want to make magic love powder.
Get me the ingredients.
How old is your husband?
Is he so old he's dying
and can't get it up?
He's still young.
Don't you insult my viscount.
Get me the ingredients I need.
Stop yapping.
Fine.
I was joking.
I've brought this with me.
I was planning to sell it
and get myself some food.
Use this for now.
I'll bring you more next time.
Good. As soon as I hook him,
I'll get you whatever you want.
That's what I'm talking about.
You really are my sister.
I'm gonna go.
Go on.
Ms. Ramphoei.
Why do I keep running into him?
Waiting for a hired boat?
Yes, Dech.
You can come with me.
I'm going back too.
Please come back together.
It'll be a while
before a hired boat comes.
Get in the boat.
Yes, ma'am.
Ms. Ramphoei!
Please sit down
or you'll fall over.
If I fall over, get in
the water and rescue me.
Actually, ever since
I came down from Lampang,
I haven't talked to you much.
I'm a servant. What would I have
to say to the viscount's wife?
Jeez, don't talk
like we're strangers, Dech.
You look like you're my age.
But I'm still a servant.
Please turn back around.
Ms. Ramphoei!
Ms. Ramphoei.
Ms. Ramphoei, don't play around.
Someone might see.
Jeez, I'm just joking.
No need to get so serious.
Or you already have a wife and
you're worried you'll upset her?
I don't have a wife yet.
But I'd like you to act like
you're the viscount's wife.
If that's the case…
you should get acquainted with me,
instead of acting like this.
I'm well aware
what is proper and what is not.
Hey,
I mean well.
If the viscount favors me one day,
I was gonna give you a big reward.
But why are you insulting
my kindness like this?
Keep your good intentions, ma'am.
I know how the viscount is.
That no matter what,
he'll never favor someone like you.
Dech, how dare you
talk to me like this?
Ms. Ramphoei, please sit down,
or you'll really fall over.
Sit down, ma'am!
Please, Ms. Ramphoei.
The viscount will fall head
over heels for me. Just watch.
I'm working. What do you need?
I saw you were working hard
so I've brought you some snacks.
Ms. Ramphoei made it
herself, my lord.
And what's that?
It's a frankincense pot, my lord.
I got my hands on
high-quality frankincense powder.
Its aroma is very relaxing.
You're well now?
I'm better now, my lord.
Good.
Don't you pull that prank again.
What prank, my lord?
I'm not stupid, Ramphoei.
You intentionally
pranked Malai yesterday
so she couldn't
attend the event with me.
I don't like shenanigans
in my house.
Goodness, my lord,
I was wrong.
I was just jealous of Ms. Malai.
Ever since I got here,
we haven't spent time together.
Ow, my lord.
Don't do that again.
Good women don't get jealous
or pull dirty tricks.
Yes, my lord.
Let's go, Chaem.
Don't bother His Lordship
while he works.
Yes, ma'am.
Ramphoei,
before you go,
light the frankincense for me.
You said it was relaxing.
Right away, my lord.
You smell so good, Ramphoei.
(House of the Dark Shadows
novel: Phakhinai, screenplay: Wannason)
Let's go, Chaem.
Don't bother His Lordship
while he works.
Yes, ma'am.
Ramphoei,
before you go,
light the frankincense for me.
You said it was relaxing.
Right away, my lord.
Ow, ow, ow.
Why did you hit me, Fueang?
When did you two get close? Huh?
We're not close.
I went on His Lordship's business
and ran into her.
I just accompanied her home.
That's all.
Unbelievable.
You know she's Ms. Malai's enemy.
Why were you nice to her?
Duh, I'm a servant. I can't pick
and choose who I serve.
Ms. Malai or Ms. Ramphoei
are the same.
Really, Dech?
How are Ramphoei and I the same?
You're screwed, Dech.
Are you hot, my lord?
Ramphoei.
If you're hot, unbutton your shirt.
Ramphoei, don't.
Hold on, my lord.
Where are you running off to?
Are you sick, my lord?
Ramphoei, don't.
Let go.
-I'll help you cool down.
-Ramphoei.
The frankincense
smells really good.
Smells good like you.
You smell so good, Ramphoei.
If I smell good, kiss me.
Kiss me more.
Kiss me more, my lord.
I will.
If you want to insult me,
be honest about it.
How are Ramphoei and I the same?
I never wanted
to insult you, ma'am.
As far as I know,
all Ramphoei and I have in common
is we're both women.
No.
We're both the viscount's wives.
I'd like to know
what else we have in common.
I was wrong, Ms. Malai.
Ms. Malai,
he just didn't think
before he spoke.
That's not it, Fueang.
Well, Dech?
Ever since I got here,
what have I done to offend you
and make you think badly of me?
It's not like that, Ms. Malai.
You've done nothing wrong.
Right, I've done nothing wrong.
But I haven't done
anything right either, have I?
That's why you have
a grudge against me.
Last time you took my floats.
This time you insulted me.
Ms. Malai,
I really didn't think that way.
But…
What's that?
It's from His Lordship's office.
Ramphoei.
-Malai.
-My lord.
Ms. Malai!
Wait!
My lord!
Let go!
Malai! Dech!
What are you looking at, Fueang?
Never seen a husband
and his wife have sex?
Leave me alone!
Calm down, Ms. Malai.
Running off like this won't help.
Did you want me
to watch His Lordship
being perverted with Ramphoei?
That's not what I meant, Ms. Malai.
I just…
Or did you want me
to see how worthless I am
in His Lordship's eyes?
You're happy now, aren't you?
You don't understand.
What don't I understand, Dech?
I understand
His Lordship doesn't love me.
He did that
in the middle of the day.
One day you'll understand
what I was referring to.
I don't understand
and I don't want
to understand anything else.
Go on, Dech. Leave. Just leave.
Leave me alone.
Leave!
Go!
I said leave, Dech! Leave!
Ms. Malai.
-Leave!
-Ms. Malai. Ms. Malai.
-I said leave!
-Ms. Malai.
-Ms. Malai. Calm down, Ms. Malai.
-Leave!
Ms. Malai. Calm down, Ms. Malai.
Calm down, ma'am.
Malai!
Hey, Malai!
Leave us, Dech.
I need to talk to Malai.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Malai.
Uh, Malai.
Malai, hear me out.
Malai.
Malai, don't do this.
It's unbecoming.
You never loved me anyway.
Goodness, Malai.
I married you in a big ceremony.
Acknowledged by everyone.
Ramphoei is just a mistress.
I'll never put her over you.
Don't make a mountain
out of a molehill.
Having sex in the middle of the day
is trivial you?
I can handle you having many wives.
But I can't handle you
being indiscreet.
Malai, hey.
I sincerely apologize.
I didn't mean for that to happen.
It already happened.
I promise it'll never happen again.
Please, Malai.
Forgive me
and let's go inside.
Please.
I can't do that, my lord.
I can't handle going in right now.
So what do you want?
You say no to everything.
I apologized.
Let me stay
with Bu-nga for a while.
Give me time to come to terms
with what you did.
Then,
take Fueang to serve you
so I won't worry.
That's okay.
I can manage with Bu-nga.
Thank you.
I said take it off.
His Lordship gave it to Ms. Malai.
It's not yours.
-Take it off! Take it off!
-Get off her!
(House of the Dark Shadows
novel: Phakhinai, screenplay: Wannason)
Whoa.
His Lordship was that fired up?
Your clothes are all torn up
like they were ripped by a beast.
I was surprised, too, Chaem.
I didn't expect him
to be that forceful.
So that means my master
pulled ahead of that toff.
Yes.
His Lordship's child
will come from me.
-Chaem?
-Huh?
You should have seen her face.
Pale like a boiled chicken.
She'd probably never seen it.
She acted like it was unacceptable
and ran off.
I hope she leaves for good
so I can rule this house easily.
I concur.
So no one will be
in my master's way.
By the look of His Lordship,
I didn't think he'd be so fired up
he tore up the clothes.
If it didn't come from you,
I'd never believe it.
I underestimated him.
I didn't expect that either.
You came to me yesterday crying,
so I was afraid to ask.
But is it a good idea
to run off like this?
Ramphoei must feel so arrogant now.
Why do you expect me to do, Bu-nga?
If I go back,
I'll feel uncomfortable.
That image is still in my head.
Don't give up so easily, Malai.
But what would
I fight her with, Ms. Bu-nga?
I married the viscount months ago.
But I still don't know
if I had sex with him.
That's the reason
you have to go back.
You can't just sigh and give up.
If Ramphoei gets pregnant first,
you'll be at a disadvantage, Malai.
The longer you stay with me,
the more you'll have to lose
It smells so bland.
No wonder it's hers.
You bland bitch.
Someone like her will never
win any man's heart.
Not with her bland taste.
You're right.
Oh!
There must be something good
in that chest.
-Get it out, Chaem.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Open it.
Move.
You were right, Chaem.
So beautiful.
If it's on your neck…
it'll be so much more beautiful.
So beautiful, Ms. Ramphoei.
Let's show it to His Lordship.
Come on.
What are you doing
in His Lordship's bedroom?
Ms. Malai's necklace.
Take it off!
I won't.
I said take it off.
He gave it to Ms. Malai.
It's not yours.
-Take if off! Take if off!
-Get off her!
Take if off!
I want you to love me
both body and soul.
Can you do that for me?
My wife's son
is nothing but a disgrace,
laying with men.
-Take it off!
-His Lordship gave it to me.
Take it off, ma'am. Or you'll die.
I want Malai to suffer,
dying on the inside slowly.
You got it.
You're a fighter.
Dech!
Help!
♪ Here's a heart
that's always faithful ♪
♪ Ready to be given
to you for good ♪
♪ Here's a life
that's still being offered ♪
♪ To you alone ♪
♪ You might be unaware
and still wondering ♪
♪ Why I'm willing to do
everything for you ♪
♪ Whatever you want ♪
♪ Everything I've done ♪
♪ What's it for? ♪
♪ I can't give you my reasons ♪
♪ Love has its own reason ♪
♪ I've only done
what my heart wants ♪
♪ All you have to do
is accept my love ♪