♪ Beautiful love ♪
♪ When you find it ♪
♪ You try to embrace it ♪
♪ You dedicate to it ♪
♪ You give it your all ♪
♪ So that it lasts forever ♪
♪ But sometimes
it turns into darkness ♪
♪ If you love so much
that it blinds you ♪
♪ Beauty can turn into pain ♪
♪ If love ends in vengeance ♪
♪ Will you still embrace it? ♪
♪ If love is gained
in exchange for someone's life ♪
♪ Will you still say this love
is what you wanted? ♪
♪ If love ends in vengeance ♪
♪ Will you still embrace it? ♪
♪ If love is gained
in exchange for someone's life ♪
♪ Will you still say this love
is what you wanted? ♪
"House of the Dark Shadows"
(Episode 6)
I heard that
someone stole a kiss from my friend.
Do you have any idea who it might be?
If I ever misbehave
towards Ms. Malai again,
I shall face a brutal death...
Mark my words, Chaem.
I will definitely succeed in
driving that Malai woman
away from this house.
- Eek!
- Hey.
Phoem!
I want to make a magic love powder.
Use this first.
You smell so good.
Wow!
Truly beautiful, Ms. Ramphoei.
Let's quickly show off to the Viscount.
Yes, ma'am.
Why did you enter the Viscount's room?
Ms. Malai's necklace...
Take it off now!
I won't take it off!
Take it off, do you hear me?
The Viscount gave it to Ms. Malai,
not you!
Back off!
Take it off!
- Back off!
- Take it off!
Hey!
Don't you dare give
that attitude to my master!
Don't go using my master's belongings,
without permission,
so I wouldn't have to say
that your master is
someone uneducated with unknown origin!
Seems like you need
to be taught a lesson!
I also have hands too.
Come at me if you dare!
Slap her, Chaem!
But she's incredibly strong.
I don't know how she's so strong.
Chaem, are you afraid of her?
What's the matter?
Not as tough as you made
yourself out to be?
Take off the necklace right now,
if you don't want to get slapped.
Or I'll report this to the Viscount!
- Take it off!
- If you slap me,
I will report this to the Viscount.
I am his wife,
and you are merely a servant.
Let's see whom he chooses to believe.
- Ramphoei...
- My lord!
Oww!
Want to get up?
Take that! How's that?
My lord!
Isn't it beautiful, my lord?
I bought this necklace for Malai
as a wedding gift.
Why are you wearing it?
Well, my lord,
I thought it looked beautiful.
Doesn't it suit me?
Take it off.
This necklace is meant for Malai.
It isn't appropriate for you to wear it.
Oh, my lord.
Well, Ms. Malai isn't
in this house anymore,
and she didn't take
this necklace either.
Who knows when it will be worn again?
Just give it to me, please, my lord.
Please, my lord.
Return the necklace, Chaem!
My lord,
I have something to report to you!
My lord, the thing is...
- Oww!
- Oops!
Goodness, Fueang! Are you alright?
Why are you running, Fueang?
What if you fall and hit your head?
My lord,
are you giving that woman...
Are you giving
Ms. Ramphoei the necklace?
Don't you feel sorry for Ms. Malai?
My lord.
- But this necklace...
- Hey!
Do as you please.
This is ridiculous.
I'll go and attend to my work.
Oww!
Hey!
That hurts!
Don't complain about this little wound.
Come.
This house is turning
into a complete mess.
Ms. Malai left abruptly,
that woman wore her necklace
without permission.
What are we going to do?
There's nothing we can do.
Servants must focus on their own duties,
and not get involved
in the master's affairs.
It'll only give you a headache.
Are you just going to
let the house fall apart?
When it falls apart as you say,
then I'll think about it.
Hey!
Where are you going?
I'm going to work.
I'm tired of listening to someone
complain so dramatically.
My, now you're acting so diligent.
If Kam and Aun were here,
I wouldn't have to
complain to you.
Hey!
Fueang.
My lord.
My lord, when did you arrive?
I've been waiting here for you.
I had no knowledge
of your arrival, my lord...
I didn't come here to
listen to your apologies.
It is I who should apologize to you.
What I did earlier,
I truly didn't mean it.
You know very well that I don't...
You don't need to apologize
to a servant like me, my lord.
I didn't take offense.
I came here to apologize
because I felt I wronged you,
but it seems like you
don't care.
Do I hold no value in your eyes at all?
That's not the case, my lord.
I am but a servant.
How could I be angry at my master?
Not to mention,
I owe you a debt of gratitude
that I can never forget.
Thank you.
Hey!
Move it!
Don't crowd in front of my shop.
Hey!
Oww!
Why did you shove my friend?
Leave!
Both of you are standing
in front of my shop,
no customers would dare come.
We're just looking,
we're not blocking anything.
Still arguing with me,
you beggars.
Go beg for spare change somewhere else.
I'm busy working!
Still not leaving?
Oww!
Hey!
Hey, Fueng, run!
You brats!
Stop where you are!
Hey, stop!
Hey!
Oww!
Stop, you brats!
- I'll hit you to death!
- Let's run!
Count, Viscount, Earl,
please save our lives,
and
we will gladly serve in
your households, my lord.
You've given me so many titles,
they're not even in the correct order.
Hey.
Young man.
I'm going to deal with
these beggar brats for biting me.
You're not relevant, so back off.
If I won't back away,
what are you going to do?
You commoner.
Hey!
Let go! Oww!
Oww!
How dare you swagger in front
of a government official?
Do you know who I am?
Do you know who my father is?
Do you wish to be imprisoned?
Well?
Oww!
My apologies, my lord. I was mistaken.
Leave.
Yes, my lord.
Make way!
Stand up.
Thank you, my lord, for your mercy.
Let's go.
Hold on,
didn't you say you would
become my servant?
But both of us are just beggars,
with no parents, my lord.
Do you want me to
take care of both of you?
Oh, Dech,
your debt to me is irrelevant here.
By now,
I'm sure you're aware
of what I desire more.
I want you to love me,
both body
and heart.
Can you do that for me?
Even if Malai doesn't want it back,
But if you ask me,
I think it's too valuable for you.
Seeing you wear it is an eyesore.
No! I won't take it off.
The viscount has already given it to me!
(House of the Dark Shadows
novel: Phakhinai, screenplay: Wannason)
Oh, Dech,
your debt to me is irrelevant here.
By now,
I'm sure you're aware
of what I desire more.
I want you to love me,
both body
and heart.
Can you do that for me?
My lord...
Dech...
What is it?
What are we gathering here for?
I have no idea,
but Chaem threatened us to come.
Threatened?
I will teach her a lesson.
Fueang.
Hey!
Sit down now.
Do you not respect your master?
You lot...
That goes for you too, Fueang.
Is everyone here?
Good,
now everyone will know.
Hurry up and tell us, ma'am.
You're wasting our time.
You're asking for it!
Watch your mouth!
Be quiet, Fueang.
She is the master's wife, after all.
From now on,
I am the sole mistress
of this household.
No matter what I order,
everyone must do as I say.
Don't complain, no exceptions.
And behind my back,
don't even think about
gossiping about me,
or else
I will report it to the viscount
and will kick all of you out.
Do you understand?
I said, do you understand?
Did you not hear me?
Answer!
Are you lot deaf?
Goodness gracious,
I thought this was a monkey show.
Ms. Malai.
Look, Malai,
a monkey who just got a taste of power.
This is my first time
seeing something like this.
Oh goodness,
I thought
Ms. Malai would never return.
Who gave you permission
to wear that necklace?
Who else but the viscount?
He rewarded me for
perfectly fulfilling my wifely duties.
Then
you can have it.
Is that a good idea, Malai?
That necklace is valuable.
It will only bring
satisfaction to that woman.
The viscount has already
given it to her, Bu-nga.
His lordship probably
thought she never had it,
and buying a new one
would be a waste of money
because she simply doesn't deserve it.
So,
he gave her a used one.
Malai!
A gun!
Don't even think about it.
I won't let someone like you
lay a finger on my friend.
Please back away, ma'am.
Even if Malai doesn't want it back,
But if you ask me,
I think it's too valuable for you.
Seeing you wear it is an eyesore.
Take the necklace off!
No! I won't take it off.
The viscount has already given it to me!
I said, take it off!
Otherwise,
I will report this matter
to the viscount's father.
Let's see
who holds the most power here.
Take it off!
Please take it off or you'll die!
Please take it off, ma'am!
Chaem, help me!
Hurry up!
Right away! I'm taking it off.
How do I take it off?
Hurry!
Yes! I'm taking it off quickly!
Hand it to her.
I want Malai
to suffer
and slowly die inside.
I'll make it happen for you.
(House of the Dark Shadows
novel: Phakhinai, screenplay: Wannason)
You have to be strong,
like you were today, Malai.
Without you, Bu-nga,
I don't think I can do it.
Oh, Malai,
even though I'm your friend,
I can't always be there to help you.
You must learn to stand up for yourself.
Do you understand?
Yes, Bu-nga.
No matter what,
you must take control of this household.
You must have the power
to handle that woman.
Don't be tricked by her deceitful words,
no matter what. Okay?
I will keep that in mind.
Excellent.
Value yourself above all else.
Without the viscount,
you won't have any assets.
Your siblings never cared for you.
The only one who can take care of you
is yourself, Malai.
I'm telling you out of concern.
I don't want you to
endure any hardship.
Do you understand?
Geez, come here.
Do you really want this?
Isn't it better to just kill her?
No,
I want that damn Malai to suffer
and be so embarrassed
that she desires death.
Would forcing myself on her
really torment her?
What if she gets addicted to it?
Absolutely not.
A snob like her, sleeping with
someone other than her husband
is like hell on earth for her.
I want to witness her
suffering
and slowly dying inside.
It's up to you, Ramphoei.
Whatever you desire,
I'll make it happen for you.
Why are you looking at me so quietly?
I didn't want to upset you, Ms. Malai.
Are you suggesting that
I'm short-tempered?
No, ma'am.
I find you to be more courageous
than I initially believed.
I'm truly not that brave.
All the servants were commending
your actions, Ms. Malai.
What were they saying?
They were expressing that
you conducted yourself admirably
as the primary wife of the viscount.
And I concur.
Thank you.
However,
I don't think it will be
resolved easily.
I concur, ma'am.
Yet, Ms. Malai's return
is already wonderful.
I will help you select.
♪ Beautiful love ♪
♪ When you find it ♪
♪ You try to embrace it ♪
♪ You dedicate to it ♪
♪ You give it your all ♪
♪ So that it lasts forever ♪
♪ But sometimes
it turns into darkness ♪
♪ If you love so much
that it blinds you ♪
♪ Beauty can turn into pain ♪
Water.
Father!
Don't approach me!
Just let me die in front of you both.
Father,
please don't speak such ominous words.
Why can't I say it
when I'll have no one to
carry on my lineage
even if I continue to live?
No need to frown like that,
Wisan.
I am trying, Father.
Please, Father, relax.
This kind of matter requires time.
Requires time...
Time to get over the fact
that a homosexual like you
wouldn't know how sleep with women.
Father...
I possess an immense fortune
that would not be depleted
even if I were reborn 10 times.
My mistress's son
just had to be infertile.
As for my primary wife's son,
the one who was supposed
to bring me pride,
only engages in shameful behavior.
You have the advantage
of being born male,
but you just had to be into men.
What a waste.
What will I do
if someone discovers this?
Wisan!
Why did you do it?
You ungrateful child!
You homosexual!
Do you want to be hit?
- Well?
- Please stop.
Please stop, Father.
Let me go! Why are you stopping me?
Leave!
What's wrong with you?
Why did you do it?
Father!
Phichit, release me!
- Release me!
- Please stop!
- Let go!
- Father!
Let go!
Rit!
Are you badly hurt? Rit!
- Wisan!
- Rit!
Right in front of me!
If you love him that much,
go and live with him!
Leave!
Father...
Are you hurt?
Please bear with me.
This medicine is very expensive.
It helps with internal bruising,
and you'll heal faster.
Is it so painful?
Mr. Wisan...
You shouldn't have to trouble yourself
and take care of me,
the master
will be even more upset.
I don't care
about that bigot.
You just recover first,
you and I
can escape and live to together.
I am educated.
Even if I don't become
a government official,
I'll survive.
Let's start a new life together.
Together.
Rit...
Rit!
I...
I fear I won't survive.
No, Rit.
Don't leave me!
Rit!
In this life, I'm fated by my past sins.
I'm denied the chance
to be with the one I love.
I wish Mr. Wisan...
to persist in living...
for me.
Rit...
Rit!
I apologize, my lord.
I am still not ready.
If you can't give me a grandchild
to continue the lineage,
I will give all of my assets
to the temples.
Just you watch!
(House of the Dark Shadows
novel: Phakhinai, screenplay: Wannason)
I admit to all of my wrongdoings.
Admitting or not,
they remain your wrongdoings.
He already repented,
please forgive him, Father.
No need to intercede on his behalf!
Rit...
Rit has already passed away, Father.
You no longer
have to be suspicious
that I might go out
with any man, Father.
Even if you can't forgive me,
at least,
consider it for
the sake of the late mother.
Please, forgive him.
I beg you as well.
From now on,
act like a proper man.
If you can't do it,
don't call me father,
go and become a beggar on the streets!
Thank you very much, Brother.
Don't overthink it.
Regardless of who you are,
I still love you.
Speak your mind.
No need to stare at my face.
It's nothing.
Mark my words.
If you can't give me a grandchild
to continue the lineage,
I won't give you a single coin!
I will give all of my assets
to the temples.
Just you watch!
Yes, Father!
I will rest now.
You two go wherever you want.
I don't want to see your faces.
I diligently studied and graduated,
served the government until
I achieved the viscount status.
But it's still not enough?
Why did Father...
You know
how serious Father is about
continuing the lineage.
He probably didn't want it to end
with his sons.
You've been married for quite a while.
You should already
give Father his grandchild.
If something were to happen to.
Father before he gives the inheritance,
you won't get the inheritance
that Father mentioned.
As a son of a concubine like me,
I have no rights to Father's assets,
as he intends to solely give it to you.
Brother...
But if you can't give him a grandchild,
you'll have to accept
giving all the assets to the temple.
It's a pity,
but I have no other means to help you.
Kam and I went to Ayutthaya
for just a few days,
and so many things
have already happened?
Indeed.
It's a shame you weren't here
to help me slap Chaem and her master.
If Ms. Ramphoei
were to have a child before Ms. Malai,
I dare not even think about it.
I only sympathize with Ms. Malai.
I wonder how long she can bear it.
You didn't witness what I did.
Ramphoei is truly difficult handle.
Malai.
Please let go of your anger towards me.
I have already instructed Ramphoei
not to cause you any more trouble.
Is that true?
Of course.
You are still
my sole primary wife.
Ramphoei...
Malai.
What's the matter, Malai?
I apologize, my lord.
I am still not ready.
It's alright, Malai.
When you are ready,
please let me know.
Thank you for understanding me.
Please rest.
I will continue with my work.
Please come in, my lord.
Dech!
What's gotten into you?
I hate him.
That Dech.
I hate you!
Help me!
♪ Here's a heart
that's always faithful ♪
♪ Ready to be given
to you for good ♪
♪ Here's a life
that's still being offered ♪
♪ To you alone ♪
♪ You might be unaware
and still wondering ♪
♪ Why I'm willing to do
everything for you ♪
♪ Whatever you want ♪
♪ Everything I've done ♪
♪ What's it for? ♪
♪ I can't give you my reasons ♪
♪ Love has its own reason ♪
♪ I've only done
what my heart wants ♪
♪ All you have to do
is accept my love ♪