Episode 16
Doctor, is there anything wrong?
Xiao Gang!
What happened?
Xiao Gang is awake!
Xiao Gang!
Fei request riddance 100 times
please go home
Go home who?
Brother
Take a photo with me.
It's me.
What do you want?
A'bao is your nephew
and my good brother.
Isn't it worth
a good chat?
You come in alone.
Wait for me here.
A'bao is still young.
He doesn't know what is good and what is bad.
That's why he was cheated.
What do you want to say?
You don't want to talk about A'bao?
Then let's talk about business.
I have nothing to talk about with you.
The 200,000 you gave A'bao
is just a business
that bribes people.
Lou Wei.
Sasha knows you are bad.
Otherwise, how could she leave you
and take the child away?
Sasha is a good girl.
She is so loving.
Shut up.
So many men want to marry her.
But she chose you.
Guess if she
regrets it now.
I will talk to her another day.
How dare you!
You gave A'bao
200,000.
You gave him 200,000.
You made him confess.
But you killed A'bao.
But you dare not to go to the police.
Because you were fired.
You hate the police.
But I don't care.
I can go to the police.
And I can get the bonus.
Sasha is from the old city district.
You married her.
You are her own man.
Your own man
will take care of her.
You should understand it.
I am going to give a big gift to Han Kuilong.
You'd better move faster.
I am a man of few words.
I will be the first one to give you a gift.
I don't know what will happen if I get angry.
Brother.
Doctor.
Can he hear us?
He can.
But he may not understand it now.
I will do it.
Brother.
I am Xiaolian.
I am glad you are fine.
I was worried about you.
Do you remember what happened?
You were riding a motorcycle.
Someone crashed into you.
Do you remember?
Do you have anything to say?
Brother.
Answer me.
You have been unconscious for half a month.
Calm down.
He just woke up.
It takes time to fully recover.
Doctor Tang is right.
We can't rush the patient.
Give him some time.
Take your time.
Sorry.
I was too excited.
Are these the
to make compensation to the victim's family.
And you can't make up for
the damage.
I believe
that as a mother,
you can understand
what the defendant did.
But you can't forgive him.
You have to pay for
what you did.
The judgment
is not only a punishment for the defendant.
It's a hope
that similar tragedies
will never happen again.
The judgment
is that all the four charges
of the defendant, Huang Juan,
have been established.
The judgment
is five years in advance.
Be careful along the way.
You're awake.
Aren't you happy?
I just woke up
and couldn't do anything else.
The doctor said
This can be done without any lip service.
Time is the problem.
Why did I let them arrest me in prison this time?
Because when I left,
the country I had conquered in the past decades was gone.
It even took advantage of the crazy Qi Changrong.
I promised to go to jail,
so that someone could take the credit and take the benefits.
I and them are on the same boat.
It's all a deal.
A deal doesn't need to be fair.
To win, it's not how strong you are.
It depends on who has the least bottom line.
You are a wolf, but compared to your brother,
your brother is more ruthless and ferocious than you.
You brothers can help each other,
but if you do something bad, let your brother do it.
As long as my brother can get better,
I don't care about anything.
Dealing with your brother is also dealing with the Han family.
The Han family?
You killed that thief
just to give them an excuse to let that crazy dog come to check.
Your brother has been living in the hospital for a while.
That crazy dog will definitely make trouble.
We must stop.
But we can't hurt Yuanqi.
I understand.
Take good care of your brother.
Come and take a look.
So many.
Do you like this?
Tell me, Shanbao.
This child is so pitiful.
He's only 18 years old.
I've known his mother for a long time.
I saw him this morning.
He cried so much that he couldn't open his eyes.
Who did it?
If I knew who did it,
he would have gone down to die with A'bao.
He's from your Jiucheng Gang.
Me? I don't have a gang.
Everyone living in Jiucheng District is a family.
I, Qi Changlong, like to protect children.
So cute.
Xiaojun.
Mom!
Xiaojun!
Give me back my child!
My child!
Do you have children?
No.
Madam is asking you now.
Not you.
The crime happened at 7 a.m. that day.
Where were you?
At home.
With my girlfriend.
Yes.
Do you want me to describe the details?
Did you ask me to keep you for 48 hours?
How many cases are you carrying?
You know it in your heart.
I can arrest anyone who comes out.
You should know who killed A'bao.
I know, so I don't need to call you.
You caught A'bao because he was hit by a steel.
Do you think he would let A'bao go easily?
You mean Ma Shanbao hit a steel?
Tang, don't pretend to be ignorant in front of me.
You police pretend to be righteous.
How many bad things have you done?
You know better than me who did it.
You bastard.
Don't go too far, Qi Changlong.
What?
Are you going to arrest me now?
If not,
I'll leave.
I told you to leave.
Leave.
Get up.
Han Ertao.
You are not a good aunt.
Why are you here?
Have you ever thought about your own mother?
I'm afraid she can't sleep well in the coffin.
If you are so filial,
then go down and be filial to your mother.
Be careful. Don't fall.
I'll deal with you.
Qi Changlong, don't make trouble.
Hello.
A'bei, they took Xiaoxuan away.
What did you say?
It's Qi Changlong.
Qi Changlong, I can bear the car he has.
Don't be afraid, Shasha.
Go home and lock the door and watch your daughter.
He will be fine.
I'll bring him back.
A'wei.
Wait for me.
Qi Changlong, come to me if you can.
Don't disturb my family.
A'wei, I told you I'm impatient.
I hate to coax kids.
If you coax them twice,
I'll slap you.
I'll help you steal and rob.
Let my son go first.
Look.
Who said we have no business to talk about?
We can talk about it.
Madam, come here.
Do you have paper?
Xiaoxuan.
It's okay.
I'm here.
Don't cry.
It's okay.
I haven't started yet.
I'm writing the words.
I saw Qi Changlong leave.
What?
The detention center is full?
I can't put him in.
You gave me some useful clues.
I'll open a room to take care of him.
Didn't the suspect who broke into my brother's room
get replaced by you?
The suspect is called Ma Shambang.
No.
We should change it now.
We should call the victim Ma Shambang.
For your brother, Han Gang,
you have a good reason to kill Ma Shambang.
Madam.
If you have any evidence,
you won't just call me back to ask questions.
Instead, you'll go to the Flying Tiger Team
and bring me here in the middle of the night.
No need to wait until the middle of the night.
If you want to go to jail,
I can send you in at any time.
I'm warning you.
Don't make things worse.
You're not your brother or your father.
Don't make yourself look so bad.
I want all the blood, violence and violence to stop.
That Ma Shambang,
are you sure he's the murderer who broke into my brother's room?
If it wasn't him,
why would someone want to kill him to avenge his death?
You're so capable.
Why did you let this person
break into my brother's ward last night?
He's from Qi Changrong?
He's not from Qi Changrong.
Are you sure?
The people from the Old City Gang
are all from Qi Changrong.
They're all from Qi Changrong.
The people from the Old City Gang
can smell the smell of their own body from afar.
Coach.
You're looking for me?
Qin Yiwei,
I was going to leave like this.
There's really no need to say goodbye.
Your problem,
your family's problem,
I really can't solve it.
I don't want it to end up being my problem.
You guys go find the Zheng family to help.
I'm leaving.
No need to say goodbye.
Don't say anything.
Just close your eyes.
Give me your hand, dear.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'll try to find the person who can help you.
I'm here.
Come with me.
Okay, you can sit down.
Yes, don't open your eyes yet.
So beautiful.
Wait a minute.
Very soon,
you can open your eyes.
Open your eyes.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you.
Come, make a wish.
Blow out a candle.
Thank you.
Hello, what's wrong?
Okay, you watch her for me.
I'll be right there.
What's the matter?
I've been investigating the fire in the wooden house.
I suspect that the person who died in the prison was a scapegoat.
There should be a black hand in the wood fire.
What's the situation now?
I know a person called Liu Mao.
We used to play together when we were kids.
Lin Jian said that she heard him bragging
that she had seen the real murderer of the fire.
Then she left the station and disappeared.
Someone told me on the phone
that she had seen him in the city.
Then go to the city.
Let's go.
Today is your birthday.
Birthdays can be celebrated anytime.
Hurry up.
You can only cut the cake when I come back.
Why?
Because if you don't wait for me to come back,
it will explode.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Okay, go.
Wait for me. Come back soon.
It's this person
who entered Han Gang's room.
Who is he?
Watch the next video.
This is the same person.
I didn't expect Han Lie to be good at drawing.
Who is he?
He doesn't look like a little mixed-race.
Of course not.
You know him?
Judge Qin, Tang Ducha is here.
Tang Ducha.
Can I have a word with you?
Sit.
Aren't you investigating the case of Ma Shanbao?
Do you have any clues?
Special Investigation Department is following up.
I came this time to ask you about something else.
How are you and your son?
Did you have a fight?
Nothing.
What's wrong?
He went to the hospital the night before.
I didn't hear him say he was not feeling well.
How did you know?
Because of Ma Shanbao's case,
when I was looking for Han Lie to enter the palace,
he told me that someone had entered his brother's ward.
So I went to the hospital to check the surveillance footage.
I saw this picture.
This picture?
And this one.
Judge Qin, I want to know
why your son went into Han Gang's ward
and wore a white coat.
This picture is from the night before.
I saw it.
It's a white coat.
This picture looks a bit strange.
I'll go back and ask.
This is Han Gang's ward.
The one who ran into Han Gang was your car.
Now your son is wearing a white coat to see Han Gang.
Do you really think there is nothing to do with this?
I dare not answer your question.
I'll go back and ask him.
The suggestion is that you should bring him to the police station
and let us ask.
Of course, you can investigate again.
This is your right.
This is the best way to get rid of his suspicion.
What suspicion?
You know what I'm investigating.
Okay.
I'll go back and arrange it.
I'll let you know again.
Okay.
I'll go back and ask.
I'll let you know again.
Yi Wei, where?
Have you dropped out of school? I'll pick you up.
Dad, do you remember the ice cream shop next to the gas station?
I do.
We used to go there every week.
I remember that mom loves to eat lemon ice cream.
She said that ice cream with no sugar is healthier.
But I don't like it. I like to eat sweet food.
I know.
But I also bought some ice cream.
Is it good?
It's so bad.
I also went there last week.
That shop closed down.
Where are you now?
Why did you go to the hospital?
Why did you go to Han Gang's ward the other day?
Someone saw you.
Someone found you.
I just want them to see me.
I'm so tired.
I can't hold on.
You haven't answered me.
Why did you show up there?
Mom never acts like you.
I'm not your prisoner.
I don't want to answer your question.
I'm sorry.
Let's go to Tony richer.
Look for ðŸ‘©ë¼ê³ à¤¸?
He went to work early today.
He just left.
ðŸ‘© corro
What's the matter
Thank you for caring for my brother.
This is my job.
I said
this is for you.
No, thanks.
I really don't need it.
Why is your son
in Han Gang's ward
and wearing a white coat?
I don't dare to answer this question.
I'll go back and ask him.
You should take him to the police station right away.
Let us ask him.
This is the best way
to clear his suspicion.
What suspicion?
You're back.
Why are you sitting here alone
and not turning on the TV?
I'm thinking about something.
Thinking about something?
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking
if I can really think about it,
it won't be hard to accept the truth.
Okay.
Let's not talk about the formula.
By the way, what are the arrangements today?
I've arranged everything.
First,
we'll go to eat
the self-serve meal that I've been looking forward to for a long time.
Then,
we'll go to sing K-pop.
You've been looking forward to
the self-serve meal that I've been looking forward to.
It's us.
You've been looking forward to singing K-pop, right?
It's not me who kicked it.
It's Brother Shi.
He said he wanted me to accompany you to go crazy.
He doesn't want you to know that
you're working all day
and thinking about something.
You're right.
Go and change your clothes.
I'll go after I wash my hands.
Okay.
The birthday gift is in the bag.
You can check it yourself.
Thank you.
Birthday gift?
This is my breakfast for tomorrow.
Sister,
you're just a nurse.
You gave such a generous gift.
Is it a high-level interview?
You violated the customs regulations.
No.
This is your birthday gift.
This is...
This is Han Lie.
He gave it to me today.
Han Kui Long's son, Han Lie.
His eldest brother lives in the nursing home.
He said thank you
for taking care of his brother.
Thank you for taking care of his brother
and giving you a watch worth more than ten thousand yuan.
I don't know either.
I just saw it.
You opened it.
I told you not to deal with people like him.
I didn't.
He gave it to me
at the subway station when I was off work today.
No need to say it.
Let's go.
Then you...
Change your clothes quickly.
Han Lie.
Tang Xuan.
Madam.
What's up?
Hongwawei's small square.
Can you get there in 15 minutes?
Okay.
That's it.
Hello?
Hello, Director Tang.
I'm Qin Yu.
I want to talk to you again.
Okay.
I'm at your house now.
Can we meet now?
I'll find you later.
I'm outside now.
Okay.
How is it, madam?
Did you find out who entered my brother's ward?
Tang Xuan.
Here's your watch.
I didn't give it to you.
I don't care what your purpose is.
Anyway, from now on,
stay away from him.
Why?
I don't want my family
to have anything to do with the Black Society.
How is the Black Society?
Dad.
Where are you?
I'm at the police station.
Why are you at the police station?
Can you pick me up?
Okay.
Don't go away. I'll be right there.
Be careful, mom.
оюke.
I'm back.
You can come at any time.
to see Hangang.
Do you really think
there's nothing to do with it?
You should take him to the police station right away
and let us ask him.
This is the best way
to clear his suspicion.
The police station
Dad.
Stop talking.
Eat something first.
Yi Wei.
Now we're here.
What we should remember
is the unhappy things.
If I want to leave,
you should stay with me.
Is it because of me?
Yes.
I won't be happy if something happens to you.
I also gave him a bonus.
If you really want to leave,
let's leave together.
Okay.
Man.
When will that end?
Tomorrow.
It still hasn't taken me this far.
It's time to eat.
Come on, it's delicious.
Delicious.
Eat some.
Here.
Eat some vegetables.
Thank you.
It's good that you're back.
This place will always be your home.
I'm happy.
Okay.
Eat.
Thank you.
Here.
Eat more.
Brother Wei.
Can you help me?
I won't make things difficult for you.
I don't need you to do it.
I will arrange it well.
Okay?
Today, I will return this favor to you.
Be careful.
Okay.
Brother Ying, what's wrong?
My stomach is growling.
No.
I need to go to the toilet.
Five minutes.
I will be done soon.
Okay.
Sir.
Do you know the air leak in the tire?
Air leak?
You don't ask why I came here?
I will tell you if you want to.
I think
there are some things you want to know.
Really?
Last night, around 7 or 8 p.m.,
I drove through a small square
near the house of Tang Ducha.
I saw him meeting Han Lie.
Tang Xuan and Han Lie?
Yes.
Han Lie was holding a very precious watch
in his hand.
You mean...
Han Lie seemed to be thanking Tang Ducha.
Actually,
it's obvious.
Tang Ducha hid the evidence
of Ma Shanbao's absence
because he knew Han Kuilong
would seek revenge from the Old City Gang.
In order to stop the assassination,
he leaked the news
to Han Lie.
He chose
to sacrifice Ma Shanbao.
He is a police officer.
Can a police officer
ignore the lives of ordinary citizens?
You said you saw them
meet in private.
You even saw Tang Xuan's meeting.
They just met.
Tang Ducha
could say that he was
seeking evidence from Han Lie.
He was holding a watch in his hand.
But it doesn't mean he accepted it.
If I were a judge,
I would say
that the evidence is not bad.
Then why did you
tell me about this?
The police can
find the truth
if they find the evidence.
Let me tell you my thoughts.
Okay?
Two weeks ago,
you introduced me to a client.
But you didn't tell me
that the client stole your car.
Then,
the client was involved in Han Gang's case.
You knew about this.
But you didn't tell me
anything.
Yes. You finally told me
that you had a way
to prove the client's innocence.
But what happened?
You saw it.
Then today,
you suddenly came to tell me these things.
Do you want to turn this
story that was not told
into a joke?
Or do you want to
know what I'm going to do
in the future?
Yes.
You guessed it right.
This matter
is indeed related to me.
A'Bing, thank you.
You have half an hour.
Enough.
Brother Wei,
I'm sorry.
I'll pay you back
in the next life.
SP650, please help.
We're being attacked in the city.
That's right.
This case
is closely related to me.
Because the person who hit Han Gang
was my son,
Qin Yiwei.
I didn't want to get you involved.
I just wanted you to help Ma Shanmao.
But what happened later
was totally out of control.
Judge Qin Yu,
you're the teacher
I taught at the law school.
You taught me
what is law,
what is justice,
what is law
that you can't bow to.
I've always respected you.
Let's go.
Bastard, he said he has half an hour.
Police!
Don't move!
Don't shoot!
I don't want to force you.
You can choose not to help me.
Or you can just pretend
nothing happened.
Even if you think I'm a bad person,
you can tell me.
I won't help you.
But I won't choose to escape.
You want to know
that I'm going to punish you, right?
You're a judge.
You can judge
if you're guilty or not.
But I don't want to hear from you.
I'll use my own method
to clear Ma Shanbao's name.
Luo Wen,
I'm sorry.