♪My heart flipped when a dynamic
flashed between us someday♪
♪Guided by instinct♪
♪We feel the same reason,
harboring a special feeling underneath♪
♪Amidst the ecstatic shock♪
♪I begin to doubt what I see♪
♪I can't believe you made me compromise♪
♪The world you're sick of♪
♪I look into it thoroughly♪
♪How lucky I am to console you♪
♪When you suffer alone♪
♪Yet I realize♪
♪I cannot let go
of the love I hold onto tightly♪
♪As I venture into the world
from a mundane life♪
♪You show up at the exact moment♪
♪My ambition♪
♪Puts an end to this aimless journey♪
♪The familiar light of pursuit
shines into my heart♪
♪From the starting point♪
[South Wind Knows]
[Episode 28]
Grandma and Grandaunt are so nice.
They've given us so much.
Sis,
you must take care of yourself.
I got it.
You have rheumatism.
You should keep warm.
It's an old condition of mine.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of yourself.
You
have to take care of your health.
I won't bring you
any cake from Kaisiling next time.
Your blood sugar level is so high,
and you're always eating something sweet.
Okay.
I'll listen to you.
Don't worry.
I hate to see you go.
Grandma and Grandaunt,
look here.
Let's take a picture together, okay?
- Sure.
- Come on.
Alright, look at here.
Three, two, one.
Okay.
Alright, I'll get going now.
Grandaunt, we're leaving.
Be careful, Grandma.
Just go back.
Be careful.
Okay, come on.
Good.
Remember to call me.
I got it.
Let me put this on your feet.
[Nurse Station]
Dr. Zhu,
what brings you here?
Aren't you off today?
I'm a little worried about Meng.
How's she?
Don't worry.
Dr. Ji has been to the ward several times.
She's got a better appetite today.
But she kept mumbling,
"Where is Madam Zhu?"
"Why hasn't Madam Zhu come to see me?"
I'll go check on her.
She's not awake yet.
She's still asleep at this hour?
I'll wait for her then.
Do you want to get some rest
in the office?
It's okay. I can just wait here.
Mr. Gu.
Good morning.
Hi, Ms. Jiang.
Mr. Gu,
I have to apologize to you.
Why?
Xizhou has upset Ruanruan.
I'd like to apologize on his behalf.
It's normal for a couple to have a fight.
They're getting divorced.
I'm afraid it's not as simple as a fight.
Who says they're getting a divorce?
Ruanruan said it herself.
Ruanruan
has adored Xizhou since she was a child.
If she weren't heartbroken,
she wouldn't have asked for a divorce.
This is our family affair.
Ms. Jiang, please don't worry about it.
Feelings are unpredictable.
Who knows what will happen in the future?
Gu,
whatever Fu Xizhou promised you,
my son will give it to you
when he takes over the company.
Ms. Jiang,
I'll make my stance clear today.
I support Xizhou
not only because he's my son-in-law,
but most importantly because
he's better suited to manage Lingtian
than Yunshen.
[Civil Affairs Bureau]
Hello, where are you?
I'll come to you.
I'm here.
Come here.
Come here, quick.
What took you so long?
- I'm sorry.
- Do I look good today?
You're so pretty today.
We're finally married.
One, two, three.
Ruanruan.
Let's go.
The marriage certificate is missing.
Why didn't you tell me
something so important?
Can't you call me beforehand?
It's because it's important
that I wanted to tell you in person.
Fu Xizhou,
do you think it's funny to make fun of me?
How could that be?
It's really missing.
Maybe you're the one who lost it.
If you don't believe me,
you can go home and look for it.
Then, let's get a new marriage certificate
before we get a divorce.
Well, I...
I've been working on
a lot of projects
and having a lot of meetings lately,
so I don't have much time.
Call me when you're available.
I...
Ruanruan.
What's wrong?
Dr. Zhu, quick!
Something's happened to Meng!
Family members are not allowed in.
Meng!
Doctors, save my child!
Don't worry. Doctors will try their best.
[During The Operation]
She's in cardiac arrest.
Prepare for resuscitation.
Mask ventilation.
Come on, defibrillate.
Okay.
Defibrillator's here.
Clear.
Again.
Epinephrine.
Dr. Zhu.
[OR Center/Anesthesia Dept]
Dr. Zhu, how's she?
I thought you said her surgery
was a success.
Where is Meng?
- I'm asking you, where's Meng?
- Meng!
Meng, come out!
I'm waiting for you here, Meng!
Return my daughter to me!
- Calm down!
- Let me in!
- Calm down.
- My daughter is in there!
- This is the hospital.
- Let me in!
Calm down.
Meng!
Where's she?
- I'm waiting for you here!
- Calm down.
Come out, Meng!
Calm down.
Meng!
[Hospital]
Mom.
Zhizhi.
What brings you here?
You've lost a lot of weight
since you've been working nights.
I made you some soup.
Really?
Mom, how did you know I am hungry?
I'm your mother.
Of course, I know you well.
It's my favorite black chicken soup.
It smells so good.
Have more then.
Okay.
That's the taste.
Tell your supervisor
not to put you on the night shift
all the time.
Look at your face.
your skin has lost its luster.
Mom,
I'm not the only one
who works the night shift.
We all take turns here.
Everyone works the night shift.
It's so tiring.
Why don't you just quit your job?
We don't live on your salary.
Mom,
I like this job.
Marriage and family are still
the most important things for a woman.
Zhizhi.
I know
you've been reluctant
to go on a blind date
because of Yunshen.
It's got nothing to do with him.
If you can't let go,
be proactive.
Mom,
he already has a girlfriend.
He's not even married.
It's not a big deal.
Mom,
I'm full.
I'm going to get back to work.
I'll walk you down.
I really have to get back to work, Mom.
Alright then.
Remember to eat it later.
Hello.
Hello, Shuning.
Are you free at noon?
Let's have lunch.
Okay.
See you later.
[Congratulations to "Soft Congee" on
its second anniversary, from Two Dimensions]
♪I'm wondering what I've lost♪
♪Our love is still drifting♪
♪It drifts past
the doorstep of happiness♪
♪Into the depths of my heart♪
♪And brushes against your silhouette♪
♪When the sunlight is cast upon me♪
[This is my heart. Please accept it.]
I'm sorry.
I lied to you.
Today's not my birthday.
it's the day we first met.
It's been 6,570 days now.
I've wanted to marry you
since I first saw you.
♪It's my fault♪
This is my heart.
Can you accept it?
♪What makes your heart♪
♪Stone cold?♪
♪To put on this act♪
♪Saying more♪
♪Making me even harder to believe♪
♪Losing you without precaution♪
♪Is more sincere♪
♪Than holding onto you tightly♪
Mr. Fu,
our Singapore market
has seen a decline in sales this month.
Chenghuan.
How can I win a girl's heart back?
Well...
The first step in courting a girl
is to give her flowers.
[1. Give flowers]
Who's there?
Delivery.
Hi,
are you Ms. Gu?
Yes, I am.
Here are your flowers.
[Don't be mad anymore. Come home! From F]
I don't want them.
You can have them.
[3. Watch a movie, 4. Candlelight dinner]
Fu Xizhou,
what do you want?
I thought if I was going
to ask you out to dinner,
you wouldn't go.
So I brought the food.
I remember you said
your mom wouldn't let you eat junk food
when you were a kid.
Whenever you had a craving
for instant noodles,
you hid and ate them.
I bought every flavor
and you can pick the one you like.
I don't think
instant noodles are nutritious, either,
but I'll eat with you
if you want.
Can you carry that?
Yes, I can.
Don't worry. Go ahead.
Hi.
You are
Meng's parents, right?
Yes.
Who are you?
I've heard
that your child's death
wasn't an accident.
What did you say?
It wasn't an accident.
It was medical malpractice.
As you know,
the surgery was a success.
I've heard
that the attending doctor was careless
and used the wrong medication
after the surgery.
Really?
But Dr. Zhu said
it was because Meng was too weak,
so she...
Do you still believe
that doctor at this point?
Will she admit she was wrong?
It's a life.
She might go to jail for this.
Wait, who are you?
How did you know all this?
My daughter works at this hospital.
I shouldn't
be telling you this.
But
I can't stand it.
After all, the kid was so young.
What a poor girl.
I'm a mother too.
I can understand your feelings.
I knew something was wrong with them.
What...
What else did your daughter say?
What kind of medication
did they get wrong?
Who should we go to
for this kind of matter?
There's no use
making a fuss over this kind of thing.
I suggest you hire a lawyer
and take the doctor
and the hospital to court.
Hire a lawyer?
We've spent all our money
on treating Meng.
How can we afford a lawyer?
It's okay.
I can refer you
to a lawyer who specializes
in medical litigation.
He's a lawyer in legal aid,
and he'll help you for free.
Free?
Well...
Why are you helping us
when you're not related to us?
As I said,
I'm also a mother.
I can understand your feelings.
Besides,
I am not asking you to do me any favors,
am I?
Don't worry.
I'll take you to the lawyer first.
You'll have to sign an agreement
if there's a lawsuit.
It's in black and white.
Okay.
I'll come with you.
Get in the car.
Call me if there's anything.
Mint.
What's the matter?
Meng's family is here again?
No.
Director wants to see you.
Okay.
Meng's family filed a lawsuit against me?
They won't accept our test results.
I'm sorry
that Meng couldn't be saved.
I feel bad too.
But given a second chance,
I'd do the same thing.
Well,
you should go home and rest
for a few days.
You're suspending me?
Just avoid the situation for a while.
Avoiding it means I'm guilty.
Will they believe you
if you explain it to them now?
Alright.
You may leave now.
[Director's Office]
What did the director say?
He told me to take a few days off.
He's suspending you?
I don't think so.
He's just giving me a few days off.
I agreed to Meng's surgery,
and we were both in the operating room.
I should be the one
to be held accountable.
I'll talk to him.
Don't.
The department is so busy right now.
What will happen to the other patients
if you're suspended too?
Stop arguing.
Okay.
Thank you.
Mom.
The court has sent the lawsuit
to the hospital today.
Mr. Wang just faxed over
a copy of the proxy agreement.
He's an expert in this field.
Shuning,
don't worry.
[Recording]
I know.
Alright, I got it.
Mom.
Zhizhi is back. Let's talk later.
Why are you back at this hour?
Don't you work the night shift today?
Mom,
the lawsuit you just mentioned
is not the lawsuit of Meng
from our hospital, right?
I don't know what you're talking about.
[Litigation Proxy Agreement]
Don't touch my stuff!
Mom.
What's this?
It's none of your business.
Give it to me.
For the past few days, Meng's parents
have been coming
to the hospital to make a fuss.
Did you instigate them?
Don't talk nonsense.
That has nothing to do with me.
I just introduced a lawyer to them.
I feel sorry for them
for losing their child.
I help them fight for their rights
and seek justice. What's wrong with that?
Mom,
the medical board has verified
that there was nothing wrong with Meng
from the surgery to the healing process.
You don't know anything.
Do you know how serious
medical malpractice is?
How can you just
make things up like that?
Do you want justice,
or do you want to frame someone?
Zhou Zhizhi,
do you know who you're talking to?
Are you saying I'm framing someone?
How rude you are.
Mom, do you have any idea
that because of you,
a doctor is now facing a lawsuit
and will probably
be suspended from her job
and even the profession?
A pair of parents
who have just lost a child
are likely
to be in a great deal of trouble.
Mom,
how can you be
so dismissive of other people's lives?
Who are you defending?
Useless.
I'm doing this for you.
I don't need you to do this for me!
Mom, I beg you, okay?
Don't meddle in
my affairs with Fu Yunshen again.
I can't afford your love for me.
You and Ms. Jiang should
stop it as soon as possible.
I'm warning you.
If you really want to be with Fu Yunshen,
don't be so stupid
as to tell him!
Do you understand what I said?
Grandma,
come on.
It's time to eat.
Again, huh?
I'll join you today.
Why do you have time to eat with me today?
You're wearing your own clothes?
Are you off?
I'm off today.
Yeah.
Grandma,
there will be hair loss
during the course of treatment.
This is very normal.
Don't worry.
I've brought your favorite food today.
Take a bite.
I don't have an appetite.
You must eat something.
You must boost your immune system
so you can have the surgery.
Okay?
Have some.
I'll listen to you.
I'll eat.
Okay.
I'll get it for you.
Liu,
did you get a copy of Grandma's case
I asked you to make for me?
Yes.
Thank you.
Grandma,
I got off work early today.
They say these plums are very delicious.
Try it.
I haven't finished this one yet.
That's why you should try this.
Thank you.
You're supposed to be hanging out today.
Zhu Jiu is off today.
She's off?
She said she was off.
Yunshen,
I don't get it.
Zhu Jiu said
she was off today.
But someone from the department
called her away.
What's going on?
There's nothing.
I think she's got some issues.
You...
You go
and check on her.
Okay?
Sure, Grandma.
Don't worry.
I'm going to check on her right now.
Go and look for her.
Get some rest.
- Okay.
- And try it.
Okay.
(Being entrusted with health)
(and life.)
(When I entered
the sacred medical school,)
(I solemnly swore)
(that I would dedicate myself
to medicine,)
(love my country,)
(be loyal to the people,)
(and abide by medical ethics.)
(I am determined to do my best
to cure human diseases,)
(to help the perfection of health,)
(to maintain the holiness and
honor of the medical profession,)
(to save lives and to help
the sick and the wounded.)
What's on your mind?
Yunshen,
I'll become a good doctor.
Dr. Zhou.
[All recordings]
(For the past few days, Meng's parents)
(have been coming
to the hospital to make a fuss.)
(Did you instigate them?)
(Don't talk nonsense.)
(That has nothing to do with me.)
(I just introduced a lawyer to them.)
(I feel sorry for them
for losing their child.)
(I help them fight for their rights)
(and seek justice.
What's wrong with that?)
[Shen, Yunshen]
Grandpa,
you wanted to see me?
I heard that Redstone Investments
is going to acquire Lingtian.
Do you know about that?
Come on,
have a seat.
I just found out about that.
But I think it's a diversion.
What makes you say so?
Logically speaking,
investment firms should know
that our family
has absolute control over Lingtian
when they do their preliminary research.
I've asked around
and found out
that Redstone is also in contact
with other pharmaceutical executives,
so we may not be their target.
So you're saying
they're using false pretenses
to confuse others
when, in fact, they have other plans?
Grandpa,
that's just my assumption.
You're an experienced businessman.
Don't investment firms do that
all the time?
The acquisition of Company A
is preceded by a deliberate announcement
of the acquisition of Company B
in order to lower the price.
There is such an approach.
Grandpa,
don't worry.
As long as we work together as a family,
Lingtian will be fine.
Your mom's the one who initiated this?
And Yunshen's mom.
Ms. Jiang is involved?
Yes.
What are you going to do?
When I first
found out she was involved in a lawsuit,
I gloated a little bit.
I wanted to
listen to my mom
by feigning ignorance
and watching her get ruined.
But I realized I couldn't.
I've tried to delete the recording
so many times.
I'm too troubled to sleep.
But I knew
that if I did it,
I'd become the person I hated the most.
Zhizhi.
I'm going to give the recording
to Yunshen.
But she's your mother.
And Yunshen's mother is involved too.
I know.
That's why I'm really sad.
However,
if I were you,
I'd do the same.
Zhizhi,
why didn't you come to my office and talk?
It's fine.
Let's talk here.
Okay.
Yunshen.
There's been some rumors about Dr. Zhu
at the hospital lately.
I don't know if you've heard about them.
Since they're just rumors,
she won't care.
But I think it's not that simple.
(For the past few days, Meng's parents)
(have been coming
to the hospital to make a fuss.)
(Did you instigate them?)
(Don't talk nonsense.)
(That has nothing to do with me.)
(I just introduced a lawyer to them.)
(I feel sorry for them
for losing their child.)
(I help them fight for their rights)
(and seek justice.
What's wrong with that?)
I'm sorry, Yunshen,
for not telling you this sooner.
But it's related to my mom.
Don't be sorry, Zhizhi.
I understand.
Thank you.
It's not easy for you
to let me listen to this.
I know Dr. Zhu is in a difficult position.
I can give you this recording
to prove her innocence if necessary.
I have something else to attend to.
I'm heading back to the hospital now.
Okay, thank you.
Bye.
Mr. Wang,
Mr. Fu is here.
Hi, Mr. Fu.
Hi, Mr. Wang.
Please come in.
Have a seat.
What kind of case
did you want me to help with?
I'd like to talk to you
about Meng's medical litigation.
Mr. Fu,
are you the defendant's lawyer?
I'm the defendant's family.
So what do you want to talk to me about?
Who is the one who hired you?
The patient's family, of course.
Mr. Wang,
I've already asked around.
You're an expert in medical litigation.
You charge a fortune.
Given Meng's parents' financial situation,
they wouldn't be able
to afford to hire you.
Mr. Fu,
this is my client's privacy.
It's not relevant to this case.
I'm sorry, I can't say anything.
I've got some work to do.
Please excuse me.
Mr. Wang,
maybe this is something that I...
[Chen Le]
Boss,
I've got the address of Meng's house.
I've sent it to you on WeChat.
Okay.
Coming.
These are Meng's favorite things.
Dr. Zhu packed them
and asked me to give them to you.
♪I see you in a dark corner♪
♪With vulnerability overwhelming you♪
♪Biting your lips
and facing away from me♪
♪You break the walls of stubbornness♪
♪Once more, another sundown
swiftly passes by♪
♪Love is like a lie at the end
of the century♪
♪That almost fools me♪
♪A kiss can heal this wrecked world♪
♪If there is a slight possibility
of avoiding loneliness♪
♪Let me endure the heavy rainfall
with you♪
♪If there is a slight possibility♪
♪The moon that once shone for me
should stay radiate♪
♪You'll regain happiness
when you are true to yourself♪
♪You feel my pain♪
♪No reason for those meaningless winds
to pass by me♪
♪When the meaningless things hit me♪
♪Why must we miss out on each other
when our hearts are broken?♪
♪Imitating others who flinch and escape
after love sparks fade away♪
♪All I yearn for
is the warmth deep within you♪