♪My heart flipped when a dynamic
flashed between us someday♪
♪Guided by instinct♪
♪We feel the same reason,
harboring a special feeling underneath♪
♪Amidst the ecstatic shock♪
♪I begin to doubt what I see♪
♪I can't believe you made me compromise♪
♪The world you're sick of♪
♪I look into it thoroughly♪
♪How lucky I am to console you♪
♪When you suffer alone♪
♪Yet I realize♪
♪I cannot let go
of the love I hold onto tightly♪
♪As I venture into the world
from a mundane life♪
♪You show up at the exact moment♪
♪My ambition♪
♪Puts an end to this aimless journey♪
♪The familiar light of pursuit
shines into my heart♪
♪From the starting point♪
[South Wind Knows]
[Episode 7]
You sure know how to make the plan
for me.
Come with me, then.
No, thank you.
That's your area of expertise.
My place is in the laboratory.
By the way, Xizhou.
The type of herb I'm looking for
is limited.
When you talk to them later,
can you ask
if large-scale cultivation is possible
in the future?
Okay, I'll handle it
as soon as possible.
The company's financial report
for this quarter
doesn't look good.
Grandpa and the shareholders are waiting
for some good news from us.
Got it.
The photo you took
really captures
their customs and habits.
You did a pretty good job.
Doctor,
please check on the child.
Let me take a look.
Mr. An, what's this?
Mr. An,
please tell this lady
not to worry.
This can be treated.
Have some water.
I heard you were shocked today.
I wasn't shocked.
Don't worry about it.
That skin condition
is actually quite common.
But he's still so young.
Did you see how it covers his neck?
It does look pretty scary.
But this disease
mainly affects children.
It's rare in adults.
It usually clears up
in five to seven days with medication.
So don't worry
because it won't leave scars
or any adverse effect
on his future life.
Fortunately, you're all here.
Yeah.
Luckily, we're here.
But if those in the more remote areas
don't get proper treatment,
the mortality rate can be quite high.
I can't do anything to help at all.
Yet, here I am, being fascinated
and taking photos
all over the place every day.
Ruanruan.
To be honest,
I think what you're doing
is very meaningful.
Look, you're taking photos here.
When you return,
you can share these photos
with everyone.
Then, when people see these photos,
they will pay attention to this place
and these children.
You're right.
I came here
mainly to investigate
immune system diseases.
Well,
how about this?
Maybe you can take
more candid photos
of life here tomorrow.
That's a good idea.
Sure, I'm good at curating.
Later on,
I can organize a photography exhibition
for the children.
Maybe we can even raise some funds.
You know what?
To me,
even though photographers
can't heal people,
they can inspire many with their photos.
Ruanruan,
I truly think
what you're doing is meaningful.
Thank you for your encouragement.
By the way,
look at the photos I took today.
You really have talent.
Dr. Zhu,
thank you
for coming to comfort me today.
But I still can't like you
because I'm Zhou Zhizhi's best friend.
Professor Hans.
Uncle Hans.
How did it go?
There shouldn't be any problems now.
I'm glad to hear that.
I have good news.
The results from both laboratories
are out.
The Perdo extract is indeed effective
against the virus.
Really? That's fantastic.
We need to conduct further research
and synthesize the antiviral medication
as soon as possible.
But
the amount of the herb you've found
is too little.
It's not enough
for me and Mr. Fu.
Uncle, don't worry.
Yunshen has been with me
during the research.
He's very familiar
with the situation here.
He'll definitely prioritize
the children's lives.
Really?
That's great, then.
I'll go and talk to him.
All right.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- I'll get going now.
You sure packed up fast.
Why did you want to see me here?
Why?
Can't I reach out to you
unless there's a problem?
Sit down.
Let's warm up by the fire together.
I have good news to share with you.
Go on.
Uncle Hans said
he sent the blood samples
from the sick children
and the Perdo extract to the laboratory.
They got the results today.
We were right.
These children can be saved.
Zhu Jiu,
you knew my purpose here, right?
Of course, I knew.
That's why I'm here
to ask for your favor.
Can you let the professor
have the medicine?
You also know how unfortunate
these children are.
I can't make
this decision on my own.
My brother has been negotiating
with the Chief
for harvesting rights
these past few days.
Harvesting rights?
Are you saying you want
to monopolize these herbs?
I came here specifically for it.
If you take those herbs,
what will happen to the children?
I can apply
for additional medical funds for them
from the company.
Funds?
Do you think they need money?
They need life-saving medicine!
Zhu Jiu,
calm down.
Don't confuse things.
In medicine,
finding a research direction
is one thing.
Developing medicine to save lives
is another.
Even if I give up the herbs
to Professor Hans,
do you know how long it'll take for him
to develop a new medicine?
It could be three or five years.
Or even eight to ten years.
By that time,
- it'll only end...
- What are you trying to say?
These children
will have already died, right?
Don't misinterpret my meaning.
How is every word I say
misinterpreted your words?
Zhu Jiu,
I have my tasks and responsibilities.
The entire company and team are waiting.
Besides, I can use Perdo
to save lives as well.
Yes,
I get that you also develop medicine.
But don't you know
that this might be the only chance
for these children?
In medicine,
there's something called "priority".
Fu Yunshen,
can you help them?
I see...
Zhu Jiu.
Can you try to put yourself
in my shoes?
I can.
I can understand
where you're coming from.
But asking me to give up everything?
I really can't do it.
I can't pretend I never came here,
never did the research.
Pretend not to know
these children
might still have a chance to live.
I really can't do it.
[Chapter 1, Overview
of Antihypertensive Medications]
Sit.
What's up?
What is it?
Xizhou,
can we allocate
some of the plants we found
to the professor for research?
He can use them to synthesize medicine
to help the sick children.
You mean the sick children
in the village, right?
You saw them?
I heard about them from Ruanruan.
She went to take photos
of those children during the day.
Those kids...
Grandpa and the board of directors
won't agree.
I'll talk to Grandpa when I get back.
Just give me your support
when the time comes.
Xizhou,
you don't agree?
Yunshen,
I understand your desire to save lives.
Those children are indeed unfortunate.
Not only are they unfortunate,
but they might also not even make it
to adulthood.
Yunshen,
you also know
the company's current situation
isn't great.
When you first proposed this project,
Grandpa and I
wholeheartedly supported you.
To provide you with sufficient funding,
I didn't hesitate to cut the budget
for my department.
Now, you're saying
you're not going to do it?
You,
me,
Grandpa,
and even your mom
will all be held accountable
by the board of directors.
I know.
That's why I suggested allocating some
to Professor Hans.
I'll also work hard
on developing my new project.
You make it sound easy.
Starting a new project
isn't that simple.
And the current project
has significant commercial value.
The company also needs some good news.
Xizhou,
you know
I'm in pharmaceutical research
and development
is to save lives.
Yunshen,
let me ask you this.
How many children in that village
are sick
in total?
Five?
Ten?
Or twenty?
Do you know
how many employees Lingtian has?
Over five thousand.
Xizhou,
giving up some herbs
might slow down our progress.
But it could give those kids
a chance to survive.
This project
is currently the company's hope.
Yunshen,
if the financial reports
for the next quarter
still don't look good,
the company will have to
undergo massive layoffs.
The first to be let go
will be the older employees.
They have families to support.
You're right.
Illness is painful.
But unemployment can push
many families into despair.
Xizhou,
I get it now.
I'll think it over.
Xizhou,
can you put off
the harvesting rights issue for now?
I need more time to consider.
All right.
By the way,
the helicopter is arriving tomorrow.
We'll leave together then.
About tomorrow,
I won't go back for the time being.
I'll stay and talk to Professor Hans
to see if there are other options.
All right, then.
Take care of yourself.
Get some rest.
Don't wander around in this place.
If you need anything,
remember to find Yunshen.
Although I'm reluctant to see you go,
I'm a bit happy to see
how worried you are about me.
I'll get going, then.
When you arrive, remember to call me
on the satellite phone.
You must call.
I'll miss you.
You must miss me too.
Three times a day.
Don't forget.
Come back
after you're done taking photos.
I know.
See you.
Xizhou,
safe journey!
Dr. Zhu, Boss.
This local freshly baked bread
is delicious.
Here, try some. Try some.
Let me break off a piece for you.
Hey, guys.
We need to leave here right away.
Did anything happen?
Na Lu is unconscious.
Several children have high fevers
that won't go down.
I suspect it's a viral infection.
What's the situation?
I'm not sure yet.
The medical conditions here are limited.
I want to take these patients
to Naotao Medical Station
as soon as possible.
But those children are so young.
Can they handle such a long journey?
She's right.
Professor,
let's go by water.
We'll ask Sen to find a boat now.
All right. The faster, the better.
All right.
- Come on.
- Okay, let's go.
All right, here we are.
Be careful, everyone.
One at a time.
Madam, be careful.
Watch your step.
Be careful.
One at a time.
Give me the luggage.
Professor Hans.
Professor.
How is it?
The test results are in.
They're infected
with a virus called V-Four.
Dr. Zhu.
Le,
why are you so early?
I went to bed early, so here I am.
My boss couldn't finish his breakfast
and left some for you.
Don't waste it.
It's a shame to waste food.
That's right.
Boss spent all night on...
Okay.
I'll take them.
Thank your Boss
for his well-balanced
leftover breakfast.
Boss,
Dr. Zhu says thank you.
I think Dr. Zhu
isn't mad at you anymore.
Look, she even finished the breakfast.
No wonder they say
it's good to date a science guy.
Boss, you're amazing.
Enough talking. Let's go.
Wait,
where are we going?
We're helping the villagers
with indoor disinfection.
where are we going?
We're helping the villagers
with indoor disinfection.
After that, we'll go up the mountain
and see
if there are any usable medicinal herbs.
We've only slept
for a little over two hours.
Aren't we going back
to sleep a bit more?
Didn't everyone only sleep
for about two hours?
Are you talking about Dr. Zhu?
I'm not sleepy. Are you sleepy?
Yes.
No, I'm not.
So, am I sleepy or not?
No, you're not.
Wait.
I'm not sleepy.
But I'm just worried about you.
Lack of sleep
can weaken your immune system.
And then we might get infected
by the virus.
No, you won't.
You've been vaccinated
against every disease in the world.
Boss,
I can stay awake.
Can you make me a sandwich
to replenish my energy?
Sure, I'll make one for you.
Yes!
(The V-Four virus spreads
through respiratory droplets.)
(People with weakened immune systems
are more susceptible.)
(After infection,)
(the main symptoms
include respiratory issues,)
(persistent high fever,)
(coughing,)
(shortness of breath,)
(and difficulty breathing.)
(Severe infections
can lead to pneumonia,)
(acute respiratory distress syndrome,)
(and liver and kidney failure.)
(If not treated promptly,)
(it can lead to death.)
(So, those who have close contact
with the patients)
(must be quarantined.)
(Our medical station has limited beds.)
(So we've set up
a temporary quarantine area.)
(in the school classrooms.)
(All students and parents
who have been in contact with Oscar)
(will be quarantined here together.)
(What we can do now)
is to prevent the epidemic
from spreading further
while waiting for the antiviral serum
to arrive.
Guys,
I'm counting on you.
Danmin.
[Hope]
[Quarantine. No Entry]
Miss,
how's Danmin?
Did I infect him?
Don't worry.
He's fine.
You have to get better soon.
So you can see him, okay?
Okay.
Have a good rest.
Thank you.
Uncle Hans,
how's Danmin doing?
Oscar is worried about him.
Here is his test report for today.
Danmin has shown
some symptoms of V-Four.
His white blood cell count is too low.
At the time, Danmin cried
and wanted to go back to school.
He said he missed his classmates
and teacher.
I let them talk on the phone.
But Danmin didn't cooperate.
Oscar couldn't bear it.
So he came to the hospital to see him.
Even if it's not this virus,
any bacteria in the air
could take his life.
But
Danmin's mother and Anson understand
and don't blame Oscar.
After all, he's also seriously ill.
Aunt Addy,
why haven't we seen
Oscar's family here?
His wife recently went
to another village to teach.
We've already informed her.
Okay.
Hello?
Hello, Dr. Ji.
How's the situation on your end?
We've mostly identified those
who have had contact with the patients.
It's better than I expected.
That's good.
Hopefully,
it would stop spreading.
Mint,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's just that the aid station
is a bit short-handed.
So it's quite busy.
Even if it's busy, you need to rest.
Only by maintaining good health
can you work well,
understand?
Don't worry about me.
Take care of yourself too.
I'll leave the tribal area to you.
Okay.
Stay in touch.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Let's cooperate happily.
What's wrong?
The minister is asking about the progress
of the supply and medicine distribution.
There's nothing that I can do
if the road is closed.
There are nosy foreign journalists
who want to go to
Naotao and Ninggu Village
to report the epidemic.
I have already released
the medicine and supplies.
Aren't we waiting for the good weather
to fly?
Tell the minister not to worry.
They can't get into Naotao and Ninggu
without an airplane.
We won't let them report it.
What happened in Naotao?
Nothing.
Just a wild outbreak.
That can be treated.
We just have to send medicine.
How long has it been?
A couple of days.
Sir,
I need your help.
Morning.
What are you doing here?
This medicine looks very familiar.
There are many antiviral herbs here.
What you're making looks
just like the traditional herbal pouch
my grandmother used to make for me
when I was a child.
Are you trying to use it
to treat V-Four?
Just taking a shot.
The roads are blocked,
and even the helicopter can't get in.
Waiting isn't an option.
What are you looking at?
Handsome, right?
I usually look pretty handsome
when I'm working.
Imagine me
holding precision instruments.
It's not something
ordinary people get to see.
Yes, it's especially handsome.
Your weather forecast
may not be accurate.
But the herbal pouch
will definitely be useful.
Dr. Zhu,
Luca has a fever.
Come and take a look quickly.
Follow me to the examination room.
Fu Yunshen.
Xizhou said
you weren't answering the phone.
You should call him back.
Ruanruan, where's your camera?
I'm not taking photos for now.
They need extra hands here.
Yes, Xizhou?
There's an outbreak on your side.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I want you
to bring Ruanruan back with you now.
You'll come back to Shanghai with me.
It has been raining here
and the roads are blocked.
We can't get out.
The weather is already improving.
The government has sent a helicopter,
medical teams, and serum.
Both of you will fly back to the capital
on the helicopter.
I can't, Xizhou.
I need to work with the medical team
and do some handover.
Hand over what?
You're not a doctor.
Do you want me to go
with the medical team
and drag you back here?
Xizhou,
don't exaggerate
just because you heard
about the outbreak.
We've already kept it under control.
The infected villagers
have all been isolated.
So I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
With the serum,
there won't be any more problems.
So don't worry anymore.
Yunshen, can you listen to me once?
Just for once!
Hello?
Xizhou, the signal is bad.
By the way,
I entrust you
Grandpa and Madam Jiang's matters.
Keep this a secret and you know why.
Hello?
Fu Yunshen lied to you.
The signal is good here.
Ruanruan,
the medical team here
might go over at any time.
If Yunshen doesn't come back,
you should come back first.
I'm staying too.
Why are you causing trouble too?
Gosh, I'm not.
Before coming here,
Zhizhi prepared various medicines for me.
So don't worry.
I haven't married you yet.
How can I die just like that?
Are you really worried about me
right now?
Then you better keep worrying about me.
I want to enjoy
this special treatment longer.
Hello?
I guess the signal is really bad here.
What are you doing?
You've never seen the cutest person
in the universe?
If Fu Xizhou dares not to marry you,
I'll sever ties with him.
Righteous man.
Just being wise.
I'll get going.
Bye-bye.
Be safe.
Dr. Zhu,
where's Professor Hans?
He's busy inside.
Are you looking for him?
- This is...
- Dr. Zhu,
I'm Oscar's wife.
Is my husband okay now?
I'd like to see him.
He has an infectious disease.
You can't see him now.
I'll be careful.
I will wear protective gear.
Can I just take a quick look?
Please!
Mint,
Oscar is experiencing
a hyperactive immune response.
The conditions here
make it difficult
to provide further treatment.
What do you mean?
What happened to my husband?
This won't do.
I have to see him.
I must see him now!
If you go and see him,
you could easily get infected.
It's too dangerous.
Please.
I'm not afraid to die.
I can sign an agreement.
My decision has nothing to do with you.
Please take her away.
This is the quarantine area.
It's too dangerous.
Get her out of here quickly.
Ms. Xu, come.
Please take care of her.
What happened to my husband?
Ms. Xu,
go home first.
The doctors said
they would take good care of them.
When can I see him?
I believe it will be soon.
Uncle Hans!
Uncle Hans.
If...
I mean
if there is any possibility
that I could help her take precautions
so they can meet for a moment?
We don't have any antiviral serum
right now.
We can't let her take that risk.
I understand.
But if we watch her
and don't let them
have any close contact,
just let them meet once.
Or perhaps say a few words,
- Oscar's condition might...
- Mint.
You're a doctor.
You must be responsible for every life.
You can't let your emotions
get the best of you.
Yes, I know.
Have you ever thought about it?
If Oscar were to die like this,
they might not even have a chance
to say goodbye.
Mint,
I'm disappointed in you.
- I must see him today!
- You can't go inside!
If I don't see him now,
it will be too late.
This is the quarantine area.
- You can't!
- I must see him!
Xu Li!
Calm down!
Didn't we agree beforehand?
If you don't let me see him now,
can you guarantee he'll be able
to stand in front of me
without harm after this?
We'll take good care of him.
I can't leave like this, Dr. Zhu.
I have to go inside now.
I have something to say to him.
We had an argument
before we left previously.
I said a lot of things I shouldn't have
and hurtful things.
He must be feeling terrible
all alone in there right now.
I have to go in and be with him
to tell him
that I miss him
and I love him.
We've been together
from university until now,
for most of our lives.
I can't let
the last thing he heard from me
was I hate him.
Hello?
Hi, Dr. Hans.
Tomorrow morning,
the medical team
will fly the serum over.
That's great.
That is good news.
So you guys hang on
and wait for us, okay?
Okay.
Thank you. Thank you.
[Hope]
Honey,
are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry
to have left you alone.
How did you get in?
Aren't you afraid I will infect you?
That would be great.
Then I can lay next to you.
This is great.
I was just wishing
that I hope I can see you
when I open my eyes.
If I can see you one last time,
I can die happily.
No, you can't, Oscar.
I can't live without you.
Don't say that.
You will be sad in the beginning.
Don't stay here alone.
You have to go back home
and let your family and friends
to keep you company.
Eat good food,
travel,
and do things
that you have always wanted to do.
But don't forget me too soon.
Remember me for a few years
before you change to a handsome guy.
I love you.
I will always love you.
♪I see you in a dark corner♪
♪With vulnerability overwhelming you♪
♪Biting your lips
and facing away from me♪
♪You break the walls of stubbornness♪
♪Once more, another sundown
swiftly passes by♪
♪Love is like a lie at the end
of the century♪
♪That almost fools me♪
♪A kiss can heal this wrecked world♪
♪If there is a slight possibility
of avoiding loneliness♪
♪Let me endure the heavy rainfall
with you♪
♪If there is a slight possibility♪
♪The moon that once shone for me
should stay radiate♪
♪You'll regain happiness
when you are true to yourself♪
♪You feel my pain♪
♪No reason for those meaningless winds
to pass by me♪
♪When the meaningless things hit me♪
♪Why must we miss out on each other
when our hearts are broken?♪
♪Imitating others who flinch and escape
after love sparks fade away♪
♪All I yearn for
is the warmth deep within you♪