♪My heart flipped when a dynamic
flashed between us someday♪
♪Guided by instinct♪
♪We feel the same reason,
harboring a special feeling underneath♪
♪Amidst the ecstatic shock♪
♪I begin to doubt what I see♪
♪I can't believe you made me compromise♪
♪The world you're sick of♪
♪I look into it thoroughly♪
♪How lucky I am to console you♪
♪When you suffer alone♪
♪Yet I realize♪
♪I cannot let go
of the love I hold onto tightly♪
♪As I venture into the world
from a mundane life♪
♪You show up at the exact moment♪
♪My ambition♪
♪Puts an end to this aimless journey♪
♪The familiar light of pursuit
shines into my heart♪
♪From the starting point♪
[South Wind Knows]
[Episode 13]
Yunshen is away,
so it'd be great
if you could watch it for him.
Is Yunshen...
How is he lately?
Haven't you talked to him?
I called him,
but he never picked up my call.
He never replied to my messages.
He's not doing very well.
Does he still refuse treatment?
Given Yunshen's condition,
he really needs a caretaker.
But he wouldn't stay in Shanghai
and refused to let me stay
with him in Heidelberg.
I am truly concerned.
Wouldn't it be great
for him to have a doctor like you,
who is kind and thoughtful,
by his side?
Madam Jiang,
I get where you're coming from.
I've mentioned to Yunshen
that I could go to Heidelberg
and look after him there.
But he turned me down.
And you just gave up after one attempt?
But given his condition,
I don't want to upset him further.
I...
Zhizhi.
Sometimes, men don't like women
who do as they are told.
You've been in love with Yunshen
for years.
Why haven't you made any progress?
This is a chance.
Make the most out of it.
How about this?
You're taking an annual leave next week.
Go to Heidelberg and bring Yunshen back.
It's easier for you to look after him.
What do you think?
I see, Madam Jiang.
Eat up.
Yes.
Come, cheers.
(Zhu Jiu.)
(I've been following up)
(the matter with Perdo.)
I'll do my best
to get some for Professor Hans.
Just like you,
I hope what happened to Danmin
will never happen again.
Hello? Yunshen?
What's wrong with you?
You finally answer my phone.
Hello.
Hello?
May I know if this is
Fu Yunshen's phone number?
Yes.
I'd like to speak to Yunshen.
Could you pass the phone to him?
It's late.
I'm afraid it's not very convenient.
Yun...
The medicine is ready.
Mint.
Are you going home?
The medicine is ready.
Heat it up for him tonight.
Are you coming tomorrow?
I don't know how to prepare the medicine.
I'm afraid of bugs.
I must get going.
I read all his files.
But for specific decisions,
I have to see the patient.
I understand.
Neural damages are best
to be treated within two years.
The prognosis will be worse
for your friend
if there is any delay.
He has tried many treatments,
but none of them worked.
He can try olfactory ensheathing
cells transplantation.
I looked into this procedure.
But it's still in the clinical trial.
The risk is unclear.
Yes, but there are also successful cases.
You can read this
and think about it.
Okay, fine.
Thank you.
Wutong?
What's wrong? Wutong?
Yunshen! Yunshen!
Let me help you up.
Yunshen.
Get out.
Please, Yunshen.
Get out!
Yunshen...
Now!
Linda!
Mint.
How is he?
He's all right.
He didn't get hurt.
Mint.
You don't have
to prepare the medicine tonight.
Mr. Fu wants me to tell you
to move out.
I expected this.
I don't know how much longer
I can take this.
Linda.
Don't worry.
I'm never leaving.
Really?
Thank you so much.
I should get to work.
Mom.
I'm hungry.
What would you like?
Soup?
I'll ask Miss Tao
to bring you chicken soup.
That should replenish your strength.
I knew my son
wouldn't be defeated so easily.
Mom.
Don't worry.
I'll receive the treatment
and get well.
I'll return to the company.
I have so many ideas for my research
that haven't been realized.
If you get well,
you will have
my full support.
Come, follow me.
Pretend you're feeling it moving.
Move harder,
even if you can't feel it.
Madam Jiang,
what happened?
Fracture in the leg.
He's going through surgery.
How did it happen?
The doctor said Yunshen
overdid it during his therapy.
Can my son still stand?
The result of his treatment
is lower than our expectation.
Are you using the right method?
We've tried all of our methods on him.
The treatment he's receiving
is the best solution we have.
But it's been so long.
Why hasn't he made any progress?
We've done our best.
Would you consider transferring him
to a different hospital?
The doctor says
the wound has healed.
You can take a bath today.
The water is ready.
Leave.
But how do you take a bath on your own?
Besides,
I can't just leave you here alone.
Leave.
Boss.
You can't take a bath on your own.
You need help with it.
Leave!
If you need help,
just call me.
Boss, be careful.
The floor is very slippery.
Boss?
Are you all right?
I told you you'd need help.
Let me give you a hand.
Don't touch me.
Boss, just listen to me.
Don't touch me!
Boss.
Come on.
Listen to me.
Don't touch me!
Will you cut it out?
Stop it.
Do as I say.
How is it, Boss?
Is the water warm enough?
Here.
Body wash
and shampoo.
Let me help you with it.
Come.
Boss.
You don't have to do this.
Your legs
will get well slowly over time.
Right?
Give it a wipe.
Get well.
Come on, clean yourself!
Fu Yunshen!
Are you still the man I once knew?
Look at me!
Stop acting this way!
Get yourself together!
Fu Yunshen.
Look at me.
Where is your confidence?
Get yourself together.
Yunshen?
Yunshen? Yunshen!
- Not me!
- Yunshen?
Yunshen,
you're safe now.
Was it a nightmare?
What are you doing here?
I heard some noises,
so I came to check on you.
Have some water.
I'm fine now.
You may leave.
I have an idea.
Let me tell you a bedtime story.
Okay?
I'm getting into the mood.
Wait a moment.
There it is.
Long ago,
there was a big rabbit
and a small bunny.
One night,
the two of them
were gazing at the moon on the roof.
The big rabbit said,
"Look!
The moon is big and round."
Then, the bunny said,
"Round."
I'm speechless.
What's wrong with the story?
It has a place, time, and characters.
All right.
I'm sleepy.
I need to sleep.
You may leave.
Would you like me to read
from my mom's storybook?
Never mind.
I'm going back to sleep.
Goodnight.
Goodnight, Fu Yunshen.
Just how many tonics have you bought
for Fu Yunshen?
Are these even going to work?
No idea.
Just give everything a try.
Yeah.
You gave up
on taking the corporate title exam
to see him in Heidelberg.
I don't know if Yunshen is touched,
but I'm moved to tears.
Ruanruan.
Do not tell Yunshen.
As for the examination,
I can retake it next year.
Ruanruan.
You always told me
that I should be braver
and more proactive.
I've made up my mind.
This time,
I'll fight for my chance.
Once you've decided,
give it your best and see it through.
You'll always have my support.
Thanks.
All the best.
I'll wait for your victorious return.
I must get going.
Text me as soon as you arrive.
Bye.
Have you lost your mind?
Not your concern.
Can you not be such a nuisance?
You're only a doctor I hired
to get me healed.
You have no right
to intervene in my life.
Fine.
You want to get drunk?
Let's do it together.
Fu Yunshen.
I've put up with you long enough!
Are you ignoring me?
You're ignoring me
on purpose, aren't you?
Because I am simply too charming.
You...
You're ignoring me.
You refuse to look at me.
What is the meaning of this?
Seriously, I've put up
with you long enough!
Who do you think you are? A vampire?
Why is your room so dim?
You know what?
Back then,
you said
I was your family doctor.
You...
Linda, get over here.
What?
Gosh...
Mint, good morning.
Good morning.
Are you all right?
Not bad.
You skipped dinner last night.
I bet you're starving.
You need something light after a drink.
Here.
Have some porridge.
Thank you.
It smells great.
Don't thank me.
Mr. Fu ordered me to prepare this.
Mr. Fu is actually a nice person.
But he has a bad temper.
However, given his condition,
it's understandable.
Here.
Thank you.
[Lingtian Pharmaceutical]
Come in.
Mr. Fu.
We received news from Singapore.
Somehow, Luo Jiang managed
to bypass the staff
and meet Mr. He directly.
How capable of him.
But it doesn't matter.
He works for Ms. Jiang.
Besides, the deal from Singapore
is pivotal to you.
I fear he might...
I could come up with an excuse
to transfer him away.
That won't be necessary.
I've talked to Mr. He.
It wouldn't be easy for
Luo Jiang to get the contract
from Mr. He.
Yes.
Understood.
I'll follow up.
[Sun Cheng]
Speak.
Hello?
Mr. Fu.
The Chinese female doctor
I mentioned to you the other day
moved into Fu Yunshen's house.
Run a background check on her.
Yes.
I'll send you photos of her right away.
Did he leave?
Fu Yunshen?
He hasn't left.
Keep watching.
Xizhou.
What brings you here?
To pick you up after work.
I found a great restaurant.
Treat me to dinner.
No.
I have work to finish.
Another time.
Not this again.
You've been working overtime
and having meetings.
We haven't gone on a date for long.
I wonder if I'm still in a relationship.
How about this?
I have a day off next Sunday.
Really?
We can go swimming in the morning.
Then, we can watch a movie
and go shopping in the afternoon.
At night...
What's wrong?
Gastric pain?
Did you skip your meals again?
It's all right. I took my medicine.
We should go to a hospital.
Never mind.
No.
You need a break now.
Your dark circles
can almost outshine pandas'.
Lie down.
- What?
- Lie down.
Why am I lying down?
Take a deep breath.
Relax.
Close your eyes.
Your body is heavy.
You need a good sleep.
Xizhou?
He fell asleep so quickly.
Dad, Xizhou, the food is ready.
Coming.
Mr. Wang is cunning.
He won't make a stance
until the final moment.
I think
I should ask Mr. Wang out
for a game of golf.
You should join us.
Sure.
Okay, all the dishes are ready.
This is the last.
We're having a feast here.
Xizhou.
Here, have a prawn.
I bought them this morning.
They are fresh.
Thank you, Madam.
You love the wings.
Your favorite, the ribs.
Xizhou.
You two have been engaged
for over a year.
When are you getting married?
Mom.
Xizhou and I have discussed this.
He is still mourning the passing
of his mother.
We can't hold a wedding.
Sir,
Madam,
if I can have your permission,
I'd like to get registered with Ruanruan.
We'll hold the wedding three years later.
Really?
I don't think it's adequate.
It's too casual.
Xizhou.
I'd love to leave Ruanruan in your care,
but she is the only child we have.
My wife and I
would like for Ruanruan
to have a grand wedding.
Let's wait.
Dad, Mom.
I never planned to have a wedding.
I attended
a friend's wedding recently.
The process was so cumbersome.
It was exhausting.
And the parents were just as tired.
I don't want to trouble you.
Ruanruan,
your dad and I don't mind it.
Mom,
you've always told me
what matters in a marriage
is the one next to me.
I am certain
Xizhou is the right one.
Ruanruan.
Mom,
this is what I want.
♪I see you in a dark corner♪
♪With vulnerability overwhelming you♪
♪Biting your lips
and facing away from me♪
♪You break the walls of stubbornness♪
♪Once more, another sundown
swiftly passes by♪
♪Love is like a lie at the end
of the century♪
♪That almost fools me♪
♪A kiss can heal this wrecked world♪
♪If there is a slight possibility
of avoiding loneliness♪
♪Let me endure the heavy rainfall
with you♪
♪If there is a slight possibility♪
♪The moon that once shone for me
should stay radiate♪
♪You'll regain happiness
when you are true to yourself♪
♪You feel my pain♪
♪No reason for those meaningless winds
to pass by me♪
♪When the meaningless things hit me♪
♪Why must we miss out on each other
when our hearts are broken?♪
♪Imitating others who flinch and escape
after love sparks fade away♪
♪All I yearn for
is the warmth deep within you♪