Shen.
I think I touched something.
Be careful.
The Guiku Sect is full of traps
and very dangerous.
Qiqi,
why don't you stay here
and wait for news from Feifei and me?
Why can you two go
but I can't?
I, Zhu Qiqi, am not a coward.
Having one more person to help is always good,
isn't it?
Fine. Let's go then.
Shen.
Stepped on another one.
Shen,
what's going on?
This time, please be very careful where you step.
It seems Tie Huahe was prepared.
The Guiku Sect's traps
have been rearranged.
Six Jia, nine chapters. Heaven is round, Earth is square.
Four seasons, five elements. Blue, red, white, yellow.
This stone forest array mimics celestial movements.
To break this formation,
one must first break through the eastern gate where the sun rises.
I received an invitation from Fugui Manor
and came today specifically to help Brother Shen
with my humble abilities.
Brother Shen's brilliant reputation
is confirmed upon meeting you today.
This person's eyes...
seem familiar.
Thank you for your kind words.
Besides being skilled in both civil and martial arts,
you're also versed in the art of divination.
Such cleverness and wisdom,
such literary talent and charm,
under heaven,
could only belong to the Man of a Thousand Faces, Wang Lianhua.
Brother Lianhua.
You flatter me, Brother Shen.
Everyone in the martial world says you're both wise and brave,
yet you can't even break through this small stone forest array?
It seems I've arrived too late.
So you're the one
who's rumored to be constantly attracting admirers, Wang Lianhua?
This young lady has such rosy lips and white teeth,
with a perfect figure,
clearly from a noble family.
I've heard that Brother Shen is close with
the Zhu family's daughter, Qiqi.
So this must be
Miss Qiqi, isn't it?
So everyone in the martial arts world knows
that Brother Shen and I are close?
What exactly do you all say about us?
In the martial arts world,
they say Miss Qiqi
once saved Brother Shen's life.
They say you've known each other since childhood,
growing up together like childhood sweethearts.
What else?
Well,
they also say you two are a perfect match.
A match made in heaven.
You're so young,
yet you've mastered the Five Elements.
This interest of yours
is rather unusual.
Your hands are so delicate and soft.
They seem perfect for threading needles
and embroidery.
What are you two talking about?
I don't understand any of it.
Thank you for your help today, Brother Lienhua.
But now that this formation is broken,
why can't we see the entrance?
Brother Shen, please be patient.
What have you done?
Feifei.
Miss Feifei.
There are some grudges between us.
But we came to Guiku Sect
without interfering with each other.
You wouldn't take my life, would you?
You fell down here with me.
If anything happens to me,
you'll be implicated too.
If you die,
it would naturally be the Guiku Sect's doing.
What does that have to do with me?
No.
You...
I swear I never told anyone about your identity.
No.
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have used
that despicable Mind Control Dream Inducing technique on you.
Wrong.
I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
No,
sis,
I'm your brother.
His son
deserves to die even more.
Chai Yuguan also deceived my mother.
I will definitely kill him too.
Shen.
Don't
be afraid.
It's okay. I'm here.
I'll protect you.
Good thing I'm here, right?
Otherwise, it's so dark,
you'd be scared to death
and how would you find anyone?
What's that?
Qiqi.
I wasn't scared at first,
but in this tomb passage,
there seem to be many corpses.
If you keep getting startled like this,
I,
will be frightened to death by you.
This person died mysteriously.
If they were killed by someone,
there's not a single wound on their body.
Yet only on the wrist there are overlapping old and new scars.
If they wanted to commit suicide,
why would they cut their wrists repeatedly?
Shen.
Tell me.
Why are there corpses
in this haunted cave?
There's one here too.
Qiqi.
If you're really scared
and can't help but scream,
you might as well call out
for Lienhua and Feifei.
Maybe we'll find them sooner that way.
Feifei!
This is the Heart-Devouring Pill.
It takes effect once every seven days.
You know what you should say
and what you shouldn't, right?
Are you hurt?
It's only been a moment since I last saw you.
How did you two end up like this?
Especially you.
And also,
why did you dig such a big hole?
Planting flowers.
Brother Lianhua, you're in good spirits indeed.
In such dire circumstances,
you still remember to engage in refined pursuits.
Don't tease me, Brother Shen.
How was your journey?
You all missed out on quite a treat.
All the way here,
you didn't get to hear Miss Zhu's beautiful singing.
It seems Tie Huahe already knew we were coming
and set up traps for us.
Since everyone is fine,
we should quickly find a way
to escape from here.
Wait for me, Shen!
Wait for me!
Shen,
I'm scared.
It's alright.
The trap map indicates
there are hidden arrows here.
Everyone step back.
These traps
haven't been triggered.
Could the traps in this haunted cave be broken?
Their inner strength is weak
and their meridians are in chaos.
They're all at the end of their rope.
These are all disciples of the Ghost Cave Sect.
These are medicine people.
Medicine people?
It's an evil martial art.
They draw power from living people's blood while practicing.
And those who are kept
to provide blood are called medicine people.
So many medicine people died here.
Could it be Tie Huahe
practicing the Invincible Mirror technique?
I thought
this Invincible Mirror that everyone in the martial world covets
was something extraordinary.
I never expected
it would be such a cruel and vicious martial art.
Martial arts are just skills
with no inherent good or evil.
It's just that...
It's the people who are evil.
To achieve mastery quickly,
they're willing to use their own disciples as medicine people.
It's a pity my disciples are so disappointing.
However,
the perfect test subject
has delivered himself right to my doorstep, hasn't he?