[English subtitles are available]
[Rising With the Wind]
[Episode 29]
[All animals in this show were filmed under safety guidance]
[Do not imitate]
That's because
when we were little,
you always packed up pancakes.
I had to seize the chance
to eat more.
That scallion pancake smelt so good.
Yes.
I miss it.
Do the pancakes made by Yang Jian smell bad?
You witnessed
my first step towards being a designer.
I hope
I can share every happy moment
with you in the future.
[Teng Yue]
Hello.
You're still up?
Yes.
I knew it.
Is it because of tomorrow's event?
I want to win.
But I'm more afraid of losing.
Failure is not necessarily a bad thing.
At least
you can gain valuable experience from it.
As long as you are confident,
you'll have a chance to make a comeback.
You've been an investor for so many years.
Have you never failed?
I'm not a god.
Of course there were times
when I misjudged.
It's normal to win or lose, right?
Tell me.
How many people
can have a big victory in the end?
The standard for a big victory
is gaining profits of more than 20 times.
Only 1% of the investment activities
can achieve that.
I think you really
want to be part of the 1%.
That's why you are so nervous.
Don't you want me
to be part of the 1%?
I told you
I'm not a god.
I can accept failure.
My dad was a god.
But he failed.
Little Butterfly,
whether you win or lose,
I will always be by your side.
Sleep early.
Good night.
[Teng Yue Shoes]
Hurry up.
35.
Are they all here? Let me see.
Make sure the number is right.
There are 20 pairs in total.
Okay.
Ask them to put them in order.
How many?
Check them all.
Ten pairs for each.
Okay, thank you.
Be careful.
Okay.
Make sure of it.
All here?
It's correct.
We have loaded the four trucks.
Check them if you have loaded the trucks.
The cargo will be delivered if there's no problem.
Okay.
You have to be sure.
Okay. Go. Go.
[Lidu Department Store]
[Teng Yue]
Come on.
Take a look at Teng Yue.
Come on. This way, please.
This way, please.
Have a look.
Take a look at our products.
Come on. This way.
Teng Yue has spent 30 years on these products.
It's trustworthy.
Come and take a look.
Take a look. Take a look at our shoes.
Come on.
Come on. Everyone, brace ourselves up.
Thank you.
None of them has been given out?
It's okay.
Everyone, smile. Smile.
Come on. Smile.
How can we win?
It's okay. Come on.
Brace ourselves up.
Take a look at Teng Yue's products.
Have a look.
It's okay.
Come on.
Good. Good.
Miss, take a look.
Come on.
Please take a look, okay?
This way.
Brace ourselves up.
Okay. Come on.
I think it makes sense.
What is Teng Yue doing?
They are betting on nostalgia.
It's obvious that they don't have enough budget.
Can we win?
Definitely.
We must attract
all the onlookers here in the mall.
It's best that our place is crowded with people.
We spent a lot of money this time.
You have to make it count.
Just wait and see.
I can't guarantee that it's worth everything.
But at least
it's worth something.
Come on.
Don't... Don't do this.
Stop mumbling.
Be more sincere.
Mr. Xu.
Please.
Come on.
Welcome.
What do you
think of our exhibition booth?
Boss, you are here.
Sorry for not going out to welcome you.
You're increasingly glib-tongued,
just like Jiang Hu.
I think it's good.
It's very exquisite.
It feels like we're back in time.
Yes.
We...
used the Chinese fashion style
when... we designed it.
-Good.
-But we...
have been outshone by Free Unicorn, which has enough budget.
Well...
Don't undermine our own power.
It's okay.
It's been a long time
since Free Unicorn
held a marketing event with so much budget.
It's good.
Just let them be.
-Right.
-Where is Jiang Hu?
She hasn't... arrived here yet.
It's already 10:30 a.m.
She hasn't arrived here yet.
Yeah.
If she is not here,
we can't get it started.
Today,
Jiang Hu has to be here.
I think I know
where she is.
Me too.
I'm gonna go find her
and take her back as soon as possible.
I'll leave you to it.
Okay. Okay.
Well,
we'll be waiting here.
Take her back as soon as possible.
Take a look, okay?
Teng...
Teng Yue's shoes.
Do you want to buy them?
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Sorry.
I just remembered
today is your father's birthday.
It's already a great comfort
that someone still remembers it.
You know what?
When I just took over Teng Yue,
no one had faith in me.
Everyone advised me to give up.
I felt upset every day.
Only when I was here
could I calm down to think.
From now on,
Teng Yue will be different.
Running against the wind.
Beginning with Jiang Hu.
This is what my dad told me.
He always said
a girl
should live a carefree life.
But I think he also wanted to see
when I face challenges,
I can go against the wind
instead of retreating,
so that I will not disgrace him or the Jiang family.
You've already done a good job.
I will do better.
Let's go.
Uncle. Auntie.
[Tombs of Father Jiang Qisheng and Mother Pei Zhijian]
You can rest in peace.
I will take good care of Jiang Hu.
Let's go.
What's so attractive?
Stand properly. Stand properly.
Come on.
Smile. Smile. Smile.
Good.
What's so attractive over there?
Ours is the most attractive.
We need to brace ourselves up.
Okay.
Brace ourselves up.
Mr. Zhang.
What do you think?
Jiang Hu can change her name into Jiang Lang.
She is at her wits' end.
Their event is so boring.
I overestimated her.
No matter how good the creativity is,
it's important to have enough budget.
This is called
you can't make bricks without straw.
It's already noon.
Are we...
going to do it or not?
Xu Si and Jiang Hu are on the way.
They'll be here soon.
Will it be too late?
Whether it's too late or not,
everything goes as planned.
Yes.
Okay.
Tell the staff
to get ready.
Okay.
When do you plan
to tell me the answer to the riddle?
What do you mean?
The event.
Apart from the design style
of the 1980s
and Xiang Zhaoyang's freehand painting livestreaming show,
you still have a trump card, right?
What's your purpose
of going to the Studio City?
You'll know soon.
So mysterious.
There are really more people
compared with this morning.
Of course.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have decided
to do it at this hour.
During the lunchtime,
there will be customers
coming here to have lunch.
It's the perfect time to draw public attention.
You're so meticulous.
Look.
Ours is over there.
Yes. Go take a look.
Teng Yue.
[Victory Leap
Blooming with Each Step]
Hello, everyone. I'm Xu Ling.
I'm Mo Xiangwan.
Hello, everyone. I'm Lin Xiang.
I'm Song Qian, an actor.
Hi, everyone. I'm Fan Mei, an actress.
I like Teng Yue
because
I can feel the craftsmen's professionalism
from every detail.
Everything bright
will fade with the elapse of time.
As time goes by,
what still remains
is what we have gained.
I'm glad to see
that Teng Yue with a 100-year history
is in the public eye
to shine again.
Teng Yue
has accompanied me since my childhood.
Congratulations to Teng Yue.
Happy 100th anniversary.
If you ask me
about comfortable shoes I've worn,
I would say I've worn many comfortable shoes.
But Teng Yue's shoes
have left the deepest impression on me.
On a rainy day,
an enthusiastic fan
waited for me for the whole day
just to give me a pair of Teng Yue's shoes
when I was discharged from the hospital.
She said
when she first saw me
on the screen,
I was playing
a nameless supporting role.
At that time,
I was wearing a pair of Teng Yue's shoes.
Although
it's been a long time,
she still remembers
the original me.
I think
the pair of Teng Yue's shoes
I received back then
is very, very precious.
The craftsmanship is meticulous.
Here,
congratulations to Teng Yue on its 100th anniversary.
I wish it can continue to progress.
I wish Teng Yue
can develop by leaps and bounds
in the current prosperous era.
Keep meticulous craftsmanship forever
and introduce more exquisite products.
See? See?
It's our creation.
We should
cheer for Teng Yue.
Come on.
Teng Yue's booth is over here.
Yes.
Please come and take a look.
Welcome.
Teng Yue's booth.
Is anyone interested?
Go to Teng Yue's booth to take a look.
Teng Yue has many new products.
Come.
Welcome. Welcome.
Take a look at our shoes.
Come.
Teng Yue
has spent over 30 years...
Come.
Hurry up.
Go.
What about the atmosphere?
Liven it up.
Rotate the lights now.
Music.
Louder.
Let me introduce.
This pair of shoes
is a new product of Teng Yue.
You can take a look.
Okay.
Do it!
Let me tell you.
The biggest highlight of these shoes
is strong brand influence.
Whether you give them to your friends
or you wear them yourselves,
they make you very dignified.
So
you made great efforts
to treat Mo Fei to a meal
and ask about Mo Xiangwan's whereabouts,
and you disappeared for two days
and almost got lost in the middle of nowhere
in the suburb
just to invite them?
Are you
surprised?
No,
I'm not.
You tricked me and Fei.
Thank you.
[The revival of Chinese fashion
Congratulations on the grand opening]
Louder.
Hurry.
Can you make it much louder?
I...
Move. Let me do it.
Hurry.
What are you doing?
Uncle.
You're here.
You're back.
This one.
Let me introduce this to you.
This is...
Hurry.
This is an old brand.
Push it!
What are you doing?
♫The evening wind caressing willow trees, the sound of the flute piercing the heart♫
♫The sunset over mountains beyond mountains♫
♫At the brink of the sky, at the corners of the earth♫
♫My familiar friends wander in loneliness and far from home♫
♫One more ladle of wine to conclude the little happiness that remains♫
♫Tonight my dreams of parting leave me cold♫
♫At the brink of the sky, at the corners of the earth♫
♫My familiar friends wander in loneliness and far from home♫
♫One more ladle of wine to conclude the little happiness that remains♫
♫Tonight my dreams of parting leave me cold♫
♫Outing in the garden♫
♫Outing where were the flower scrawl♫
♫Even me found love from the blossom♫
♫There's just one that I adore♫
♫No matter where I travel♫
♫You're what I'm singing for♫
♫I'm singing of your high mountains♫
♫Singing of your land and rocks♫
♫Sing of hometown, the big or small♫
♫Sing of them once more♫
Bravo. Bravo.
Step onto the stage. Step onto the stage.
[I want to go against the wind]
[Teng Yue
Reviving Chinese fashion]
Let's welcome Miss Xiang Zhaoyang.
Xu Si,
I really want to rent the factory.
Offer me a solution
to revive Teng Yue,
and we'll talk about it then.
Teng Yue! Teng Yue! Teng Yue!
Teng Yue! Teng Yue!
[Lidu Department Store]
Mr. Xu.
Mr. Gao.
Let's talk.
This is the third batch
trucked to Lidu, right?
Yes.
I think we need to transport a few more batches.
I think they are gonna be hot-selling.
The online store's customer inquiries
have also surged.
I can barely feel my hands.
No wonder Jiang Hu
asked us to stay here.
So she knew
the offline event
will boost online sales.
She's really thoughtful.
I admire her.
You have become Jiang Hu's fan again.
Go help them.
Jie.
You scared me.
Didn't I ask you
to wait in the canteen?
Why are you here?
Isn't it normal
that a boyfriend picks up his girlfriend from work?
What boyfriend?
[Teng Yue Shoes]
[Celebration Party of Teng Yue Shoes]
[Grow stronger]
Everyone. Everyone.
Attention please.
Come on. Let's applaud.
♫Fly, even though it's dangerous ahead♫
Okay.
♫I'll still fly♫
♫Only brave people can understand♫
Everybody,
today, Teng Yue's booth
♫What freedom♫
in Lidu Department Store
won a big victory.
♫Feels like♫
We have also
♫Beautiful, only by being yourself♫
impressed the industry.
Our creativity
♫Can you be beautiful♫
really surprised them.
♫Even if my body has withered♫
It evoked a great response
♫And the whole world is against me♫
and has been widely recognized.
In the future, Teng Yue...
♫I just spread my wings♫
The industry is also optimistic
about our future development.
♫And fight against my destiny♫
So from now on,
as long as you
♫Ignore the darkness and run♫
♫Towards the vast distant world♫
work hard
and do your best at Teng Yue,
I will make sure
you get enough benefits
and bonuses.
You'll get more.
♫Time passes by and stars fall♫
What do you think?
Great!
♫Riding the wind and flying high♫
Of course.
Of course. Of course.
Today's achievement
♫Growing recklessly♫
is
♫A little wish♫
thanks to
our big boss,
Mr. Xu Si.
♫Even if we're surrounded by dangers♫
♫Never compromise or retreat♫
And Ms. Jiang.
♫I didn't fulfill my wish♫
♫I've been wandering in a dream♫
We made the achievement
under their leadership.
Why don't we invite them
♫The faith guides me♫
to say something to us?
♫No one can stop me♫
Good idea.
♫I shout, whether noisily or lonely♫
I'll pass.
♫I keep going without hesitation♫
You go.
♫The faith guides me♫
Go.
You really are not going?
♫The victory is waving at me♫
Let's welcome Ms. Jiang first.
Okay.
You want me to say something.
I'm gonna say a few words.
Thank you very much for today.
I will still count on you
in the future.
Well said.
♫Fly, even though it's dangerous ahead♫
♫I'll still fly♫
Okay, that's all I want to say.
♫Only brave people can understand♫
What?
♫What freedom♫
Well...
That's all?
♫Feels like♫
That was really a short speech.
You...
♫Beautiful, only by being yourself♫
You are wearing long pants today,
not a short skirt.
That was too short.
♫Can you be beautiful♫
♫Even if my body has withered♫
Long story short.
Everything is understood between us.
Well said.
♫And the whole world is against me♫
Everyone,
♫I just spread my wings♫
do you think
she can walk off the stage like this?
No.
♫And fight against my destiny♫
Do you agree?
No.
♫Ignore the darkness and run♫
Well, they don't agree.
Do you want her
♫Towards the vast distant world♫
to say more?
Yes.
What do you say?
It's
what everyone wants.
♫Time passes by and stars fall♫
What you just said is not enough.
♫Riding the wind and flying high♫
I'm gonna sing a song.
Okay.
♫Growing recklessly♫
♫A little wish♫
Ms. Jiang.
-Ms. Jiang.
-I'm going to pick a song.
Yes, yes.
Be careful.
♫Even if we're surrounded by dangers♫
Ms. Jiang
is definitely better at singing than giving a speech.
♫Never compromise or retreat♫
♫I didn't fulfill my wish♫
♫I've been wandering in a dream♫
This is great.
Mr. Pei.
♫The faith guides me♫
Where's Zhaoyang?
She... She said she would be here later.
♫No one can stop me♫
♫I shout, whether noisily or lonely♫
What's up?
Nothing.
♫I keep going without hesitation♫
I'm going to welcome her.
Okay.
Okay. Go.
♫The faith guides me♫
♫The victory is waving at me♫
Mr. Xu,
a toast to you.
♫Protect your true self♫
Thank you for your support for Teng Yue.
I should thank you,
Ms. Yue.
When Jiang Hu was having her hardest times
and when everyone
gave up on her,
you still stood by her side
unconditionally.
I watched her grow up.
Of course I should help her.
No matter what the reason is,
I should thank you.
Thank you.
She's here.
Bravo.
♫If pride hasn't been washed away callously♫
♫By the billows of reality♫
♫How could we understand♫
♫How harder we need to try♫
According to Jiang Hu's personality,
♫To reach the target afar?♫
she doesn't like
songs like this.
♫If dreams haven't fallen off a cliff by a hair's breadth♫
She's doing this
to get closer to the employees.
♫How would we know those who are perseverant♫
In the past, Jiang Hu
♫Have invisible wings?♫
would never
care so much about the employees.
Her father used to take good care of her.
♫Swallow tears in the heart♫
She was a princess in a castle.
♫And they will bloom into flowers of bravery♫
She could have
everything she wanted.
♫When you are weary♫
But it's different now.
♫You can close your eyes and smell a fragrance♫
She has no one to protect her.
She can only rely on herself.
♫Just like you've had a good sleep till dawn♫
She has to overcome all the obstacles on her own
and create a new life.
♫And you can hum a song while walking♫
♫With light steps♫
She has already done a good job.
♫When we are upset♫
♫We feel lonely easily♫
♫I really wish those who understand me♫
♫Could comfort me and lend me a shoulder♫
Xu Si,
♫I'm so glad that we've had a tactic understanding all this time♫
as Jiang Hu's aunt,
I think I can call you that.
♫After going through the wind and making a turn, our hearts are still connected♫
Sure.
In my eyes,
she's still a child.
♫Just as usual♫
But she
is carrying a heavy burden.
♫The original dreams are firmly held in our hands♫
What she needs now
is someone
who can share the burden with her.
Do you understand what I mean?
♫If that's the place we desire to go the most♫
I'll always be by her side
♫How could we return halfway?♫
and accompany her.
♫We will definitely achieve our original dreams♫
♫Only by realizing true desires♫
♫Can we say we've been to the paradise♫
She sings so beautifully.
Join me.
Come on, Uncle.
Come on.
Come on, Master Zhang.
Come on. Let's sing together.
Come on.
♫When we are upset♫
♫We feel lonely♫
♫Easily♫
♫I really wish those who understand me♫
♫Could comfort me and lend me a shoulder♫
♫I'm so glad♫
♫That we've had a tactic understanding all this time♫
♫After going through the wind and making a turn♫
♫Our hearts are still connected just as usual♫
♫The original dreams are firmly held in our hands♫
♫If that's the place we desire to go the most♫
♫How could we return halfway?♫
♫We will definitely achieve our original dreams♫
♫Only by realizing true desires♫
♫Can we say we've been to the paradise♫