I, Yue Jingzhe
today
am going to propose to the girl I love, Zhong Xin,
today.
Zhong Xin
Will you marry me?
What are you looking at?
We're all just people.
Don't be like this.
No.
A Zhe
Get up first.
I'll get up if you put it on.
Stop messing around, get up first.
I told you to get up, so get up.
Don't you understand what I'm saying?
What are you all looking at? Move along.
Move along, move along, move along.
Let's disperse.
Why are you angry?
Is it because of the sense of ceremony?
Then I'll come up with a new one for you.
And I'll make you cry your eyes out.
Can you say yes first?
Please?
A Zhe
I'm sorry.
I know you really like me.
I do like you.
But liking is just liking.
Marriage is marriage.
But if you like someone,
isn't it to marry her?
And spend your whole life together?
I've already decided to go abroad.
Next month.
I'm leaving next month.
That's fine.
I can wait until you come back.
I'll get you a bigger diamond ring.
Once I leave, I'm not coming back.
You know.
You know too.
So all of you knew?
So I'm the only fool here, is that it?
Do you want it?
You don't want it.
If you don't want it, I will.
No, no, no.
A Zhe, A Zhe, A Zhe!
Spit it out, A Zhe!
Hurry, spit it out!
Go after him, quickly!
A Zhe!
Sis.
Let's go, let's go.
Stop buying, stop buying.
Go, get out.
No business today.
Hurry up and leave.
Go.
Get out.
Where did you all come from?
So annoying.
Get out of here right now!
Get out.
What are you doing?
Why are you getting physical?
Lin Sufen, right?
That's me, your auntie.
Let me tell you all something.
I've seen plenty of thugs like you.
Get out of here now.
Or else...
I'll call for help.
Take a good look.
Your daughter borrowed money in your name.
I'm here to collect the debt.
Lin Xiaoxiao
Have you thought about the transfer?
Come out.
Auntie.
Xiaoxiao had something to do and went out.
She told me.
You can just sign the contract with me.
This is such a big matter.
Can a little girl like you make the decision?
Auntie.
You can't say that.
I am indeed young.
But since I’m here,
it means Xiaoxiao trusts me, right?
That Lin Xiaoxiao, such a brat.
She’d rather trust outsiders
and not even
give her own aunt a hand.
When you took advantage of her,
did you ever think she was your own niece?
Watch your mouth.
About this contract—
No.
My shop is so big,
and you’re only giving me this little transfer fee?
Sign it if you want.
No, no, no.
Don’t be like that, I’m just asking you.
Sis, you’re here.
Lin Sufen signed the contract without saying a word.
Yeah, the contract is right here.
She was so quick to sign for a business that doesn’t make money.
That’s not like Lin Sufen at all.
Who are you people?
How did you get in?
Who are you?
Why do you care who I am?
Cut the nonsense.
Move, move, move.
We’re not leaving until we clear this up today.
No one is leaving.
You think you can bully us because you have more people?
Fine.
Take a good look.
Lin Sufen owes me money.
She mortgaged this shop to me.
It’s written in the agreement.
It’s all clearly written in black and white.
This is indeed Lin Sufen’s handwriting.
She mortgaged the shop to you.
But we have a transfer contract.
We were all deceived.
You say she borrowed money, but did she really?
I had no idea about this.
Who knows where you got
this worthless IOU from?
Are you here to scam me?
Fine.
I’ll go to Yangcheng right now.
And find Lin Xiaoyan.
Don’t go.
Lin Xiaoyan
She’s just a student.
She doesn’t have any money.
If she has no money, she still has people, doesn’t she?
Let your daughter keep my guys company for a few days.
Then the debt will be paid.
I’ll pay, I’ll pay.
I’ll pay.
As long as you
don’t go after my daughter,
I’ll pay even if I have to sell everything I own.
Alright.
I’ll give you three more days.
If you can’t pay in three days,
don’t blame me for what happens next.
That Lin Sufen is such a wretched woman.
She actually dared to sell the same shop to two people.
Boss Wang,
we're all just doing business here.
There's no need to get upset over Lin Sufen.
Harmony brings wealth, after all.
How about this:
Give us three days.
We'll find Lin Sufen.
You get your money,
and I get my shop.
How does that sound?
Another three days?
You said it.
Three days.
Just three days.
I'll go check the old Lin family house.
Brother Xiao Wu,
you have a lot of connections.
Send some people to ask around the streets.
See if anyone has seen Lin Sufen.
Alright.
Let's go.
Yue'er,
don't just stand around.
Go check all the inns and guesthouses.
Who knows if she's hiding in one of them.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I've been really busy.
I haven't seen you lately.
Alright.
Let's head back to the dorm first.
Sure.
You guys go ahead.
Mom.
Why are you here?
I'm at school, studying.
You need to use your brain.
You should eat more eggs, okay?
When you're growing,
you also need to eat more vegetables.
Don't skip them.
Yan'er.
This is all money.
Mom got it from that brat Lin Xiaoxiao.
It's all for you.
Why are you spacing out?
Hurry, take it.
Mom.
The fact that you're wanted for fraud
has spread everywhere.
How do you still dare to come see me?
I don't care whether it's a scam or not.
All I know is I got the money.
It has to be sent to my daughter.
Now there's money.
Only then can my daughter go to school with peace of mind, right?
She'll have a bright future.
And find a good family to marry into.
Hurry, take it.
Mom.
Don't worry.
I definitely won't let you down.
When I graduate,
I'll make sure to take good care of you.
Our Yan'er
is the most filial.
Good child.
Mom, you sit here for a bit.
I'm going to the restroom.
Okay.
Then go quickly, go on.
Don't leave.
Wait for me to come back.
I won't leave.
I'll wait for you.
Lin Sufen.
That's you, right?
You are suspected of commercial fraud.
Please come with us to assist in the investigation.
Take her away.
Get in the car.
Let's go.
Go inside.
Xiaoyan,
your performance in the trade courses you majored in these past two years
has been outstanding.
So the school has decided
to recommend you to
intern at a garment trading company.
This is to
prepare you for entering society
and lay a solid foundation for your future.
Thank you, Director.
But this company
has very high requirements.
You must go through a round
of strict interviews.
Also,
your internship performance
will be directly linked to your graduation results.
How you perform during the internship
will become
part of your comprehensive graduation evaluation.
So
you must give it your all.
Don't worry, Director.
I definitely won't let the school down.
Excuse me, hello.
I'm Lin Xiaoyan, recommended by Yangcheng University.
I'm here for the interview.
Students from Yangcheng University really are different.
We've already heard about your excellent grades.
Come,
I'll take you upstairs.
Thank you.
Lin Xiaoxiao?
What are you doing here?