My girlfriend's here to work, not to be harassed by you!
I just want the kind of love that makes me feel at ease.
Marry me, Rose?
Use a vibrator next time.
That stuff only needs a battery.
It doesn't have feelings you can hurt.
But right now, what you love
is about to stop you from actually living.
Don't be a coward.
I want to ask you out.
Before I can give you an answer,
there's something I need to prove first.
I can't be anything more than this with you, Tony.
Isn't this Mr. Saran?
Why is there a photo of Mum and Mr. Saran?
Why do you want to know what his connection to your mother is?
Why can't you tell me?
Are you keeping something from me, Dad?
You don't need to pay him any respect.
He left your mother before you were even born.
Saran...
is your biological father.
Your mother was an amazing person.
She got a scholarship to study medicine abroad.
She was dating Saran at the time.
I was her best friend
when we were in medical school.
The reason she was concerned about your sex life
was because she was afraid you'd end up like your biological father.
She was afraid you would get some woman pregnant.
It could ruin your and her bright future.
But why?
Why did you never tell me any of this?
Does it matter?
Do you really want to get to know
someone who hurt your mother like that?
But do you even realise that
my life is a mess right now because of Mum?
What are you talking about?
Your life is great.
Don't dig up the past.
Just live your life.
Let the past stay there.
Your mother wouldn't want you unearthing a buried past.
What?
Are you saying, now that you know the truth,
you won't think of me as your father anymore?
You're my only father, Dad.
Thitipoom Techa-apaikhun
Yongwaree Anilbol
Harit Cheewagaroon
Ployshompoo Supasap
Chanunphat Kamolkiriluck
Apichaya Saejung
Archen Aydin
Pusit Dittapisit
Thinnaphan Tantui
Phuwin Tangsakyuen
Chaleeda Gilbert
Pavida Moriggi
Pakin Kuna-anuwit
Jira Charoenthamasuk
Directed by Tichakorn Phukhaotong and Pinya Chookamsri
Okay.
Good class.
Goodbye, everyone.
Bye.
Good day.
(Birth Control Methods)
Oh, Alex?
Why are you here?
I've missed you.
It's been a while. You look amazing.
Having a trip down memory lane?
No.
I'm here to talk to you.
So, what do you want to talk to me about?
About this.
Can you explain this?
Well?
I know you're my biological father.
My dad told me everything.
You knocked my mother up
and left her for my dad to take care of.
You were so concerned for me when I was a student here...
Were you just trying to make up for it?
I'm sorry.
I was very young.
I really wasn't ready.
So you were just gonna act like my father when you got older?
I'd been trying all this time.
Your mother always turned me down.
I tried sending you birthday presents every year.
But she never took it.
Presents?
You sent me birthday presents?
Yes.
But one year,
she finally accepted it.
But it never reached you because
your mother...
got in an accident.
But I still wanted to give you that gift
so I left it on your doorstep
when you were turning 18.
Was it an instant camera?
Yes.
Back then,
I loved photography.
And your mother
was my favourite model.
If she was still alive now,
I'd love to apologise from the bottom of my heart.
Same goes for you.
I don't need your apology.
The only person who could forgive you is her.
But she's no longer here.
So you can live with this guilt for the rest of your life.
Alex.
Alex, wait.
Can I ask you something?
How many friends with benefits do you have?
Right now?
One.
Just you.
(THAT NIGHT)
I got you hooked, didn't I?
Ridiculous.
Of course not.
I just don't want to get tied down to anyone.
They all want to date eventually.
But not you.
You're not the romantic type or anything like that.
We screw.
We're done.
We go home.
That's only because I haven't shown you my romantic side.
If I do...
you might want me to ask you out right away.
No, thanks.
What if your fans find out about this and I get dragged?
I want to just be a nobody and live my life the way I always do.
Fine. Up to you, then.
Just come and go all your please.
But if you ever get lonely,
give me a call.
I don't want you to treat me like I'm just your bed buddy.
I can be anything, you know?
I can be your chauffeur,
your cook,
or your...
My what?
Your whatever.
You decide.
Then, can you be the...
room service for now?
I'm starving.
Let's order something.
Please?
Of course.
Didn't we finish your training?
Is something the matter?
Are you really going to be like this?
Are you really not going to open up to anyone?
You think you're so high and mighty,
think you really can raise a kid on your own?
I've put on a brave face to be here, you know?
Do you need me to spell it out for you that I'm still in love with you?
That I am so happy to get to spend time with you again?
We can spend time together as friends.
God, Nim.
Stop it.
What freaking friends?
We've never been friends.
When I put that sticker on you on Valentine's Day,
I didn't do it as a friend.
I don't know, Mollie.
I just think this won't work.
Oh?
Is that so?
Is that all you think of me?
I get it now.
I apologise, then.
The problem seems to lie with me.
What a damn fool I am.
Enjoy your life.
I won't bother you again.
It's not like that.
The reason it won't work is because of me.
I just want to live my life without having to care about someone else.
Okay, then.
Be my guest.
Enjoy your solo life.
Holy crap.
Your life is more epic than a fantasy movie.
So the power in the camera
was born from your parents' love in the accident.
I still haven't solved the whole thing.
There's my photo and Jean's.
These two are still the same.
I think
you need to find a way to get closer to Jean.
Find out what makes her cry like she does in the photo.
I have a feeling that both of your photos could be about the same thing.
What do I have to do?
I think you need to try again.
But it has to be all-or-nothing this time.
What else can I do?
I went to see her at her workplace last time
and she slapped me right in the face.
Talking about having a life like a fantasy movie...
Jedi's wedding.
Ask her as your date to Jedi's wedding.
The theme is prom night.
So take this chance to win her over.
If you get her to kiss you,
the curse will go away.
Maybe you can orgasm again after that.
Oh, yeah.
But I think, if you're going after her again,
you might need to go big this time.
Fine.
I'll try asking her out.
But if she says no,
I'll go alone.
Go alone?
Army just broke up with his boyfriend.
I'm sure he can't find someone to go with him.
He'll be alone, too.
Hey, hey, hey.
As if someone of my calibre
would ever go to prom alone.
What will you do, then?
What? Take yourself out to the damn dance?
I guess you all have heard about me.
Your parents are afraid I would turn you into something like me.
Some of them even think I'd violate you.
But let me ask you honestly,
ever since I've become your coach,
have I ever made any of you feel uncomfortable?
No, sir.
Have I been a good coach who teaches you how to play football?
Yes, sir.
Does my liking men
compromise my ability to be your coach?
No, sir.
Then I guess it won't be a problem.
If you're feeling uncomfortable with this,
just come talk to me.
You can also quit the team, of course.
Because I don't think I can change who I am.
The only thing I can do is
promise you I'll do my best as your coach.
I'll turn you into a great football player
and send you to nationals.
I'll show you that
sexuality has nothing to do with footwork.
Alright?
Yes, sir.
Give it a go.
Can I join you, Coach?
What the hell are you doing here?
Don't you see I'm in the middle of teaching here?
I'm here to ask for another chance.
I'm sorry
for using my own standard to judge you.
You're not a coward.
You're just waiting for the right moment.
Yeah, okay.
Is that all?
Go back now.
Hold on. I'm not done.
Don't rush me off like that.
Just say what you're here to say.
Look.
My athletes are waiting to try out the penalty kicks.
Huh?
Will you go to prom with me?
Prom?
What prom?
We graduated ages ago.
No. It's...
Jedi is getting married.
The theme of the wedding is prom night.
You know, I...
I need a date for that.
So I thought I'd ask.
Will you go with me?
I don't want to go solo. That's too lonely.
If you want me to go with you,
I have an offer.
You have to play my game first.
Sure.
Tell me.
If you can kick the ball to hit the crossbar,
I'll go to prom with you.
Hold on.
Isn't that, like, impossible?
The crossbar?
You know I'm not easy to win over.
Fine.
Brush up your tuxedo.
Crap...
I have to go to prom alone?
I know.
I missed it.
Bye, then.
You're just gonna give up easily like that?
Huh?
What do you mean?
I'll give you another shot.
And hey...
Don't you dare miss this time.
Joe.
I won't miss.
Will you go to prom with me?
Okay.
Drink!
Drink for the past we should have forgotten!
Only fools
would go back to the very thing that keeps hurting them.
Love with all your heart.
But never make a fool of yourself.
It's time to move on.
Jean?
Jean.
Jean, can you come out?
Who's that?
I don't know.
Some next-door neighbour?
Jean.
I need to talk to you.
I don't.
Just go home.
Will you go to prom with me?
Jedi's wedding, I mean.
I just want to tell you how much I like you.
I like that you have dreams.
You're a film director now.
I admire your strength.
You always fight for what is right
without caring what anyone thinks of you.
I adore your free spirit.
Your independence.
You do whatever you want
but never cause anyone trouble.
I feel really bad about this.
I didn't want to be that wound in your heart.
There should be, like...
a million more people like you in the world.
The world doesn't need someone like me.
But it needs someone like you.
Jean...
Will you go to prom with me?
Give me another chance.
I promise I'll be the Alex you used to like.
Jean.
Jean!
Look at the camera.
Of course.
- Congratulations, man. - Congratulations, man.
Thanks.
You gotta be in sync, huh?
Alright.
Here we go.
Well, Nim.
Thanks for coming with me.
I would have to come alone otherwise.
Ew freaking came here with Liu.
He doesn't care about me anymore.
Yeah.
Sure.
We're the only two people no one wants anyway.
That may be true for me personally.
You, however, turned them down.
What's with you?
They tried to make up with you.
What's with your stone cold heart?
None of your business.
Focus on your damn self, man.
Well?
I guess you'll have to adapt
to the life of celibacy for all eternity now.
I really think Jean won't ever forgive you.
I'm gonna go get drinks.
What the hell, Nim?
Where's my encouragement, man?
Nim.
Like, honestly?
Are we the only two people who are here with their friend?
Everyone else brings their date.
You said no to Alex yourself, though.
I can't help you with that.
He was putting on a full Romeo-and-Juliet performance.
And you were still mean to him?
Yeah.
Honestly, is there absolutely no way
you and Alex could be something more than this?
Something like what?
Like friends.
How could we be friends?
We had a crush on each other once.
We screwed once.
And he thoroughly hurt my feelings...
You think I can be friends with someone like that?
Bottoms up?
Please welcome the bride and the groom!
First of all, thank you everyone for coming to my wedding.
I've got nothing to say except that
I threw a prom themed party only because
I want to reminisce about the first days I fell in love with her.
Well, we're still very much in love.
And as you can all see...
Rose will always be the Prom Queen in my life.
That was as sweet as honey.
What about you, Rose?
Do you have anything to say to the groom?
I know we fight along the way,
but I am always so happy to have you by my side.
And...
You'll always be the Prom King to me, too, Jedi.
This is the perfect timing for the Prom King and the Prom Queen
to open the floor with their first slow dance.
Everyone else is welcome to grab their date
and celebrate this lovely occasion.
Come on.
Stop being so afraid.
I'm...
I'm not afraid.
I'm just not used to being so open.
Well, get used to it already.
'Cause I'm going to tell everyone,
and show off to everyone that you're my boyfriend.
You know what?
I'm going to shout here in the middle
of the damn floor that we're dating.
Listen up, guys—
Hold it.
Don't.
I won't.
As long as...
you dance with me.
Please?
I just want to have a slow dance with someone I've...
always had a crush on.
I mean it.
Trust me a little, will you?
Fine.
I'm not good at this, though.
It's alright.
I'll teach you.
Babe, what are you doing?
Why are you on your knees?
Babe, no.
I want you to be my Queen, too.
No, babe.
This is their wedding.
Don't steal the spotlight from Rose and Jedi.
But I want to be in this atmosphere,
like when we were in school,
when we first met.
There's not a lot of people who understand me for who I am.
I may not be your King, Liu,
but I'll try to be everything that you want.
You don't have to be anything.
Just be my good old See-ew.
I like you like that.
Marry me?
Hey.
Do you want something like that?
I'm all in, you know.
Nope.
You and I will never get to that point.
We haven't even started.
Don't be so pessimistic.
You don't think we're perfect for each other?
Sure.
But I need more time.
My heart's seal shut.
I'm not in a hurry.
I can wait.
Dudes.
How was it? Huh? Huh?
Was that romantic?
Huh?
Bad timing, man.
You stole the limelight.
Well, sorry.
She's the right person, and the timing was perfect.
When everything feels right,
you just gotta go for it, you know?
Let's talk about you guys.
Why are you two here together?
Oh...
Are you going for Alex now?
As if I would ever.
It's not like that.
Nim had a fight with Mollie
so she asked me to come with her.
Hold it right there, Alex.
That was full of crap.
It was you who asked me.
And why?
Because Jean turned you down, big time.
You hired a freaking fire truck to apologise and all, right?
Just shut your trap.
That was some melodrama bullcrap.
Alright. Enough, both of you.
My heart is full of love tonight.
You two need to try harder.
I want you two to be happy the way I am happy.
Put your glasses down and come with me.
Come with you where?
Ew, where are we going?
- No, Ew, don't. - What the hell?
No, Ew.
Hi, Jean. Hi, Mollie.
My two friends here happen to be looking for a dance partner.
Idiot.
Sorry.
Can I borrow that?
Excuse me.
I thought you wanted to dance?
No.
I just needed to get you out of there so Jean could be alone with Alex.
Mollie.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I still haven't sorted things out with myself.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
It's up to you, isn't it?
You want to be alone.
You want to raise your baby alone.
Who's gonna stop you?
Your life, your choice.
But I don't think I can take it
if you're gonna keep changing your mind.
Mollie.
To tell you the truth, I've never changed my mind.
I miss you all the time.
But you know how I am.
I'm freaking stubborn.
I–I don't know.
I think I'm afraid.
I'm afraid...
I will get hurt again.
But you gotta try, right?
Is there anything in this world that is 100% safe?
There's none.
But at least,
you can be sure of one thing...
If you take my hand,
I'll make sure I won't hurt you.
Fine.
Let's give it a go.
Will you dance with me?
Just this once.
I won't ask for anything ever again.
What I said the other day...
I mean every word.
I'm so freaking proud of you, Jean.
I remember everything that happened that day...
the day we went around school, taking photos.
You told me you wanted to be a film director.
And you're one now.
You said you wanted to be a... photographer.
How come you're a gynaecologist now?
A lot of things happened along the way.
You probably won't believe me if I tell you.
I don't remember a lot of things that happened.
Everyone around me has all changed.
But my feelings for you...
I remember that.
And I feel awful.
Very awful.
Everything I do right now,
I do it because I want you to have the life you once enjoyed.
I want you to be happy again.
Will you give me another chance, Jean?
Jean?
Jean!
Wait, Jean!
Jean.
Jean, why are you crying?
Enough.
Enough already.
I thought I could forgive you, but I can't.
I understand.
But I still want to try—
Don't.
Alex, you don't have to.
Please.
Just let me live my life.
Trying to get me to forgive you...
I keep replaying that night in my head.
Nothing has changed.
And do you know...
what happened after that?
I got pregnant.
We were both drunk.
You didn't use a condom.
I wasn't ready to have a baby
because I had dreams and a lot of things I still wanted to do.
And I had no one left I could talk to,
because if I told them,
all they would say was that I brought it on myself.
So I went alone to get an abortion.
Where were you, Alex?
Where were you back then?
It's too late now.
Why didn't you tell me?
If you had told me, I would have stayed with you.
You wouldn't.
- No matter what you decided, I would have stayed. - No, you wouldn't.
You loved being in the middle of the spotlight
because you had sex one time with a girl at a party.
I am so sorry.
I didn't know what horrible things you had to go through.
I'm really sorry.
Tell me what you want me to do.
I will make it up to you.
Please, just tell me.
Enough. Stop saying sorry, Alex.
You've said sorry one too many times.
You don't need to say it anymore.
From now on,
don't see me again.
If you want to fix things,
there's only one way.
Go back to the past.
Maybe you might change something.
Maybe, then...
I might be able to forgive you.
Jean...
Why?
Why can't I fix these two damn photos?
Why...
Mum.
You brought me here because you wanted me to see, didn't you,
how I've ruined Jean's life?
I saw it.
I saw everything.
I know now.
I will repent.
Just tell me what you want me to do and I'll do it, Mum.
I just want to...
turn back time and fix everything.
I just want Jean's life to be good again.
Look.
I put it back on, your ring.
Why... Why won't you care?
Why are you doing this?
You know, don't you?
Your curse is ruining my life!
Alex.
Mr. Saran?
Why are you here?
I always come here.
Your mother used to love coming here with me.
Do you realise
you and your present
has ruined a woman's life?
What are you talking about?
This stupid camera
brought me here
to face this issue I will never be able to solve.
And it makes me feel eternally guilty.
Alex,
does the issue
lie with this camera
or with you?
The guilt you're talking about,
I've lived with that my entire life.
That's why I've done everything I can to fix it.
I've done everything to make it up to you.
I just want another chance
to be your father.
I only have one dad.
You will never forgive me no matter what?
Can you turn back time?
I get it now.
But at least...
Can you keep this camera?
It's the last thing
that connects me to you...
and your mother.
Can I take a photo of you with this camera?
Do you really want my photo?
Stand here, please.
This is the place
I gave Mum my promise.
Directed by Tichakorn Phukhaotong and Pinya Chookamsri
(EVERY PUZZLE IS SOLVED?)
(OR WILL ALEX REPEAT THE SAME MISTAKES?)