《Meet You When the Bitter Orange Ends》
I hope you guys listen to me and I'll say it again
I did not have sexual relations with Ms. Lewinsky
I never let anyone...
The strongest wind
Start from the fist
Episode title: "The Wind Has Passed, My Heart Is In Trouble, My Emotions Are Agitated and I Can't Calm My Heart"
Nothing can resist the wind
I'm so innocent.
Looking up at the sky I...
Have a clear conscience
why is that?
Why am I no longer the president and am I forced to abdicate?
Hello Park Young-ran
Come here
Are you ignoring me too?
I called you over here
What do you do at home all day?
Spending my money on white rice
But you can't even control your children?
That damn girl is just following you
I know everything!
Go to sleep when you are drunk!
What the hell are you doing, little brat?
Whose child are you?
- Whose side are you on?
- Dad, do you know how old I am?
Hello!
You little bastard!
You never came to my sports meet.
Maybe it's because you never thought of me as your child
While you are wandering around in the world of romance...
“Wandering around”?
Mom never forgets a day
Pack us a hot lunch
Hello!
Who brought this stepmother home?
The stepmother can be replaced at any time
But you and I are blood relatives!
- If you two separate me and my mother
- What are you talking about, little brat?
I just live with your mom because of you
I treat you as my father
Bring the broom
Where is the broom?
Wu Cheng, go back to your room.
You shouldn't talk like that.
Break up with him! What are you lingering on about?
Mommy wants to be with Daddy
I want to be with him
hateful!
you do not say!
You can't live without me
You guys eat so well at my expense.
Isn’t it?
You can even have white rice!
Life must go on
I have to go on with him.
hateful!
I want to spend the rest of my life with him
See the end of everything
(Knock on the door)
go out
You little...
I really want to kick you away
I told you to get out!
Seriously
Oh my god
mom!
If you were a Korean, I would have beaten you up a long time ago.
You know, right?
You look like an army sergeant.
Are you dating?
Why do you still have photos of Huang Xinhui?
You have to be born again to be like her.
Get out of my room!
How did you get involved with that family's son?
You idiot, her mother and we...
- Damn it
- What happened to his mother?
You can't be together anyway.
You'll be embarrassed to death later.
Stop messing around while I'm still polite.
Why can't we be together?
Go tell him...
If I see him again I will kill him
Let's break up
No I don't want it! Why?
Is it because of those two bastards Wu Cheng and Han Yin?
Or is it because of my dad?
My dad is my dad but I am me
I never listen to him.
Listen, stop telling people you're my girlfriend.
Don't cut in line in the cafeteria and think I'll protect you
If you go ice skating, just go to the rink at Twin Peaks
No, I will
You can't date anyone but me.
If you date someone else I'll beat them up
Do you think I won't?
I know you will
No, I can't break up with you.
I don't want
- The last thing is that my husband is virtuous
- What?
Take care
They cried
You fucking bastard!
Don't let me see you again
I'm going to kill you!
You're breaking up with me just because I got beaten up
I'll tell them to keep beating you!
I’ll beat you every time I see you!
You have no idea how much it hurts!
We can avoid them
Don't let them catch you
Amusement park ice skating rink urban area
I can't go anywhere
Your brother's friends keep showing up
I got on the bus yesterday
The driver is also their friend.
He forced me to sit until the terminal!
Damn it! How am I going to survive?
I have my own life too
Then run away
Let's escape
- What?
- I can't stand it anymore
My dad even took down my bedroom door
Do you want to escape?
My dad said if I see you again
He shaved my hair and sent me to the temple
Do you believe him?
Then all your friends are nuns now
So should we escape?
Do you want to escape or not?
I don't know a damn thing!
Keep honking the horn
Oh my god they look
Like the middle part of the Korean flag
Come on, everyone is like this when they are young!
Apparently this is the spring of their lives
Is it because spring has arrived or is it genetics?
I love you
I love you too
Looking back, spring is like a feast
Welcome home son
But for Sprout it's a battle
Hello
Do you come here often?
The new sprouts are experiencing the test of breaking through the soil
You can't even serve soup.
Didn't your mother teach you?
It's just the kelp tangled together.
Don't use your hands!
Our family wouldn't be like this.
You are all here
Happy birthday indeed.
There is only one happy person in that family
All kinds of cinnamon are delicious
It's hard to find good cinchi in Seoul
I'm not saying that all the Xinqi in Seoul are bad.
This is bought
I haven't had home-cooked food for a long time.
I feel like I can eat two bowls
We eat less at home.
Do your parents know that you often go to men's apartments?
She doesn't come here often.
I asked her to come today because it's my birthday.
I didn't ask you
Jin Ming
This is not Yingfan's apartment. It's mine.
I bought him the apartment.
I don't want you to come to my apartment too often.
- Mother
- This is my apartment.
I don't want you here
Of course you guys keep dating.
Taste the ups and downs of love
I told you I was planning to marry Jinming...
Quiet
You want a place near the school?
The result is this...
this
You are my pride
Now my pride is damaged
Everyone's heart is shaken by love
A storm swept through their hearts
Is your family a big chaebol?
Samsung or Hyundai?
How much richer is your family than mine?
We went to the same school.
I am just as precious to my parents.
Why should I be ashamed of not being able to serve soup?
Are you good at serving soup? Did your mother teach you?
I'm not good at serving soup either.
It's so unfair
I hate all of this
I feel like a cheap clown.
I can't stand being in front of people who look askance at me.
No matter what I do, I can't please you
I hate this so much!
(Stomachic and digestive beverage)
How do you eat so much?
Of course I want to please her.
Of course I did!
Who doesn’t want to please their boyfriend’s mom?
Who would want to marry a mama's boy?
You choose
Being a good son or a good husband?
You can only choose one
I don't want a man who has to please everyone.
Forget about the proposal.
Decide this first, then talk about the rest
Who in the world can choose one and give up the other?
No one will...
My dad
What?
That's what my dad did.
I see
Let me make it clear first
I won't marry a mama's boy
It all felt so genuine.
Like a little owl
Cried all night in the breeze
I am Kim Ki-duk from "Two O'Clock Date"
I believe the 90s were a pop culture renaissance
The wind of change is coming
I like this picture
I don't think he's Picasso anymore.
Did you see it?
You can do a good job
The theme of the movie is clear
Just seeing this makes me want to dance the lambada
here you go!
That old lady is here again
She always knows when a movie is coming out
Where did she get the resale tickets?
I never sold her a ticket.
Maybe a fake ticket?
We don't buy
No that...
- We don't want to resell tickets
- no…
Does that look like Choi Jin-sil?
- I think she looks like me.
- The painting is really good.
- Feel sorry?
- Is it bad?
No, I don't think so.
I heard that it was painted by a college student majoring in fine arts.
So that's it
Why don't people watch it?
Is everyone busy?
Everyone went in without even looking at the paintings.
It really makes me a little sad.
It's really sad.
Picasso lived in the basement of the Cannes Theater
For some people
This theater is their Louvre
Stop scalping tickets! Stop it!
Scalpers are a social nuisance!
Ticket scalping is prohibited!
I told you not to sell it!
Does he really think I'm a scalper?
Since you're here, it'd be nice to watch a movie.
I heard that the movie that will be released in two days is good.
(Promotional ticket)
It was rerun because it was popular.
You shouldn't give your ticket to anyone else.
But you are not ordinary people
This is an employee benefit given by the boss himself!
Come on Monday afternoon at 2pm and there's usually no one there.
It feels like a packed house.
I hope you don't tell my son.
I came here to see his paintings.
Chung-seop doesn't know I'm here
He went out with his lunch box and came home covered in paint
Never say what you painted or where you painted it
Because he was embarrassed
Not everyone can draw such a big picture
- Anyone who can draw is a painter
- Yes.
He draws really well. I really want to see what he draws.
I have seen everything Chung Seob has drawn since elementary school.
That is my happiness
Now the movie release day is my happiness
(Promotional ticket)
Without Painter Park, our theater would be finished.
Boss, you are not from Seoul, right?
Really
- Wow
- Wow!
What happened this time?
Yinming is selling things at school again?
Yinming's mother
Don't call me that anymore.
Then call you Jinming Mom?
Didn't Seoul call?
I said Jinming has a boyfriend.
She has forgotten her parents
Oh my god, this is annoying.
Let her call us first.
Just like giving us more face
Children are only children when they are in the nest
Once I leave the nest, I am busier than the president
My kids are the busiest people in the world
Why are you having a nightmare again?
Why did the school call you this time?
He's at the bottom again?
He was never the last one.
There is Zhelong in that class
Cigarette related
You said you wouldn't tell anyone.
Does that bastard smoke?
He doesn't smoke
He sells cigarettes
- He sells cigarettes
- Wow
(Auntie Seafood House)
He's really good at it.
In my opinion, selling cigarettes is better than smoking.
He cheated the old man in the grocery store
Said the cigarettes were bought for us
I bought cigarettes and delivered them.
They say he'll put a markup on the price when he resells it.
I really want to know more than Jin Ming
What will Yinming become in the future?
Have you asked him why he did that?
what why?
Adolescent anxiety is lawless
I mean, have you asked him?
Why do you want to make money so much?
I don't know why he is so obsessed with money!
That's why you ask.
You gave him life but his mind is not yours
You know you can't help Jin Ming
So he was very strict with Yinming.
Jin Ming is a tough guy
You always treat her like soft tofu
Yinming is easy to get along with but you treat him like a carrot
Jinming is a bit sensitive like me.
Yinming, you know...
Easy to talk to?
I don’t think so!
A carrot may seem to be fine no matter how many times it falls.
But no matter how strong the carrot is
It may be hollow inside.
Don't treat children differently
Children
Remember everything
Because I'm sad too
I can't help but get even more angry at my weakness
So this matter
And Jinming makes you proud
Is it okay if Yinming embarrasses you?
So what? Am I a saint?
What can I do?
...maybe a rising star
Advanced Selection
High-performance Elantra
so…
I owe you a favor again.
I don't know how to repay you
It's fine
But I still want to...
When you are free
Can you draw something for me?
This way I can sell it for a good price later
Heard about Picasso's works
It became more valuable after his death.
But who can guarantee that I will die first?
- Are you kidding?
- Yes
- I should go back to the ticket office.
- good…
What's wrong?
Thank you so much
It's okay. I didn't pay for it myself.
No, I mean my mom...
(Cinema Paradiso)
This is her first time watching a movie in a cinema
Uncle! You have to run!
No, you have to run!
Although she watches "Weekend Classic Movies" every week
I guess
I've been too focused on my own life.
Everyone is shaken by the love in their heart
Did you know?
I cried when the projectionist came in wearing sunglasses
Alfredo?
Why isn't there a fire extinguisher in the screening room?
Why put out the fire? He should save his own
He should jump out of the window.
That would only break your legs.
I wonder what he will do if he loses his job as a projectionist.
Maybe Toto will send him money because he is so kind.
You cried because you thought
Could Alfredo be broke?
You know Toto
Reminds me of you
Toto is like my son
What did you want to give Miss Liang?
I'll bring it back to her
You said you were an English major?
Yes
(copy printing and binding)
You can count on me until graduation.
These are all in English and people just don't buy them
(1984 Gyeonggi Province High School Painting Competition
Park Chung-seop)
It would cost a fortune to buy them all.
English is more expensive
There are some study notes in it
I'm not sure I can take all of this.
No wonder parents like their daughters.
I've been here forever and every day feels the same
The only special thing is to see new paintings on the premiere day
But thanks to you, Ms. Liang
I am really happy today
I think I will remember this day until I die.
Listen to you say
Makes me feel
I did an amazing thing
Mom, that's enough.
How could she lift it?
She can't carry it alone.
She can't hold it
How about a drink?
Have a drink…
- Shall we have a drink?
- For you
It’s a bit…
Oh well
You know...
What's wrong?
If you really appreciate me
Maybe you should clarify this for me.
Instead of treating me to noodles?
My landlord's daughter
Always kicking the shoes I left outside
She knows there's nothing between us.
I think
She wants to get married with peace of mind.
So you want your girlfriend to marry someone else?
You must be a
saint
She's going to marry the noodle shop owner's son
Can you make a fortune by selling noodles?
Bidong Noodle Chain
Who wouldn't want to marry into a good family like that?
But she
Can't make up my mind
Then keep her.
If she dumped Picasso
It's her fate to marry the guy from the noodle shop
You need to tell her in person.
"You can leave if you want.
This is your loss, not mine!"
You should bring a gift set and say:
"Please let me marry your daughter"
At least you won't regret it.
How do you know I'm better than the guy in the noodle shop?
You don't understand me
You are your mother's precious son.
So you can draw whatever you want.
That's the feeling in my bones, you know?
I am also my parents' baby
I just want
Live with your head held high
Let our family live with dignity
At least that's what I think
You know
You don't have to stand up for someone you barely know.
How come I don't know
After all, people are the same
No, everyone is different
After all, everyone has a bad side.
In that era, stranger danger
The kindness of strangers is also dangerous
13-year-old child killed in Hwaseong serial murders
Less than three months later...
Oh my god, I'm so sorry.
(Apgujeong kidnapping case becomes an open investigation)
Please tell me. Sorry for the trouble.
Those bastards deserve to be cut into pieces!
The phrase "a thousand cuts" is so true.
How could someone be so bad?
Really? OK, I understand.
Wait for Jinming to come back
Can you ask her to call me back...
OK, thanks
Kidnapping a child
That's equivalent to taking three lives instead of one.
What should parents who lost their children do?
I mean, losing a child is devastating in itself.
But losing a child like that...
Oh my god
What happened? Jinming is late again?
I don't understand why she's out so late
I told her to stay home tonight.
What's wrong? Do you always have nightmares?
About what?
You may feel this way because it is almost time to pay homage to your ancestors.
When you were a child, something strange happened during ancestor worship.
The Ekishan incident?
We were all there, right?
Oh my god, I shudder just thinking about it
I still remember the taste of that day
hurry up!
They would put the meat on the sacrificial table.
Dad will leave it all to my brother
Only humans can see black dragonflies
They say other dragonflies can't see them
Why?
Because this is the Death Dragonfly
We humans can't see the god of death, right?
What? You wanna catch it?
You go first
let's go!
Wait till I catch it
It can't kill other dragonflies.
The little dragonflies also want to live with their parents
Dad is going to scold you again
Is this what is called upper body?
I don't know why I chase it.
(Ekishan Bus Station)
I want to take the bus but my legs hurt
Can you go to that store?
Would you like to change this into a ten-won coin?
What does the owner say?
They said they would not change coins.
- Did he scold you?
- No
But he did glance at me.
Sorry for bothering you
You are really kind and gentle.
Are you very obedient?
But
You don't have to give me this
Could you give me some more change?
I have to take two buses.
Since the store owner is unwilling to change the coins
Then you go to the alley behind the telephone pole.
Find the cabbage vendor driving a truck
Can you get some change from that man?
Then I'll give you another
My legs really hurt.
What are you doing?
- Mother
- what are you doing here?
- What's wrong with you, mom?
- What is this money?
- Uncle!
- What's wrong? Do you know that guy?
There was an auntie here just now
Guangli said her heartbeat accelerated
But she didn't say anything for fear of scaring you.
But why are you here, mom?
What a strange coincidence.
I'm in a neighborhood I've never been to before.
Met a mom who wouldn't be there
You don’t know yet?
Your mother went out to look for you that day
Thanks to your sister-in-law, I don't have to collect firewood.
Stop calling her sister-in-law.
We still have the firewood you brought earlier.
She can do these things.
Her children have been living and eating here for free for several years
You should pay some child support.
Don't let Aichun carry firewood
Replace sake with makgeolli
Han Kyu prefers Makgeolli
What about Aichunren?
Today is her father's memorial day, but she just wants to go out
Where is Aichun? There is broth here. Where is she?
She went after the Death Dragonfly
What?
My mother's intuition is terrible.
It is said that she climbed over a mountain in one go.
You should drink the broth made for your dad
Why run around?
For Mom
Why? This is mine.
This is unlucky
How did you know I was here?
I have eyes on the back of my head. All mothers are like this.
Do you think the aunt will come back to ask for money?
- Love Pure
- What?
Did that lady see your face?
I see
What does she look like?
She looked pale and had a strange...
Do you think your mother will let you go?
Someone who bullied her child?
Come and see!
(Fresh Caught)
Come and have a look! We have preferential prices and all are fresh goods
3 50 won for you
I don't care
Give me another one.
Please, we worked so hard to get these.
That's fine.
Oh my god!
Oh My God!
Hello! The wrists of every woman in Jeju Island
Do you want to check them all?
Oh my god!
You scared the customers away by pulling their wrists.
Are you selling conches to catch criminals?
That bitch saw Aichun's face
I want to buy some conch
These are free!
What's your asking price?
What is your bid?
Hey, I sent the boat back.
Why do you always look for children?
Is there an age limit for begging?
If you touch it, you have to buy it, okay?
The older you get, the less obedient you become.
Kind and gentle children are the best
That girl is perfect.
what the hell?
- What's wrong?
- Please!
Before you pull her wrist
Let me do my business first!
Auntie, you must be crazy.
Are you crazy? Let her go!
What the hell? Why are you so energetic?
I'll beat you to death, you bitch!
You want my daughter to beg, don't you?
These bastards! Catch that bastard!
They must be killed!
Come here, bastard!
Bitch!
what happens?
Fairy tales back then didn’t have open endings
What else could she do when she was about to beat her to death?
She beat her to death?
Those bastards deserved to be beaten to death, right?
Don't come back here asshole!
Go to hell you bitch!
The country had no legal system at that time.
So if you hit someone who deserves it
The police won't say anything.
Even if you beat a person half to death
The police will also clean up the mess and take the person away.
The police used to beat people themselves.
It just so happened that day was Han Kyu's memorial day.
Your mother said it was your father who saved you
But I don't think so
Your mother saved her child.
There's nothing like a mother's intuition.
Oh my god
Grandma is still awake so late
She can forget everything
I just can't forget the day when my eldest son came back.
There's nothing like a mother's intuition.
My mother said to me at that time
The back of the mother's head
You need to have two eyes
Hello, there is a phone call for you
good
Oh my god
Don't people in Jeju Island watch "Eyes of Dawn"?
She always calls when this is on TV
Yeah, everything is fine.
What can happen in a day?
(Eye of Dawn)
Do you have to call me every time you dream?
Why do you always come home late?
Where do you hang out every night?
I didn't hang out
Have the lights in your alley been repaired?
The world outside is dangerous, go home early
You must sleep at home
Don't spend the night outside
I'll know if you do that.
You call every night
Is it to see if I'm playing?
You don’t have a partner, right?
I can't bear it if you disappoint me too
You are the pride of your parents.
All my hopes are placed on you
If there is a problem with the support...
Damn pillars...
Is I the only one in your life?
Don’t you have your own life?
Even if I stay out all night
You can't do anything there.
If I want to deceive you, I can deceive you a thousand times
You are awesome
So don't worry about it, please.
You have to live your own life
Wait until you have a child
Wait until you have a daughter like you before you say that!
You wear these hairpins every day
Throwing it everywhere every day
Why should I buy it for you?
You lose it every day anyway.
She thinks she is amazing
I saw this at the hardware store and bought one
You go to Seoul and see her install it.
Since she is so good, she can definitely install it herself.
I'm the only one worrying stupidly
A child is only a child when he is in your arms
She feels she has grown up, but I don't.
She's still a child to me.
Is it because of that dream?
What do you always dream about?
Why don't you say anything?
Are the nightmares this period that bad?
Not a nightmare
nothing
mom!
mom
Didn't I say I'd give you candy after you finish the noodle soup?
Why don't you listen to your mother?
Mommy, hug me
Aunt Wu! Jin Ming had an accident!
Is she bleeding?
Didn't I say I'd give you candy after you finish the noodle soup?
Why don't you listen to your mother?
Another nightmare?
Oh my god
What dreams did you have recently?
...I'll give you candy after you finish the noodle soup
Aunt Wu! Jin Ming had an accident!
Is she bleeding?
baby
Mother…
I'm going to pick up your sister and will be back in a while.
Okay?
I'll be right back
Wait till I come back
I give you candy every day
Okay?
Mom is unlucky
I've suffered a lot
So she is more worried.
She believes that if she keeps worrying
It can even prevent those unfortunate
Jin Ming
baby
baby!
No God
My baby, oh my god
Help!
baby
What's wrong with him?
doctor
Call a doctor
ambulance
The ambulance called...
Kuan Zhi called an ambulance
Why didn't anyone call an ambulance?
Jin Ming
Help!
Help! Ambulance!
Someone call an ambulance!
ambulance!
baby!
Look, you can't just walk over here...
What's wrong?
She inhaled gas
What? No!
No. 108, Bongcheon 5th-dong
No. 108!
Number 108! Yes!
No, there are no steps!
The car can't drive up
right
That’s when true kindness was frozen…
Oh no
Baby mommy is here
Mom is here
...the year when Korea's three major unsolved crimes occurred
Mommy would be on the 9 o'clock news every night.
Call me
Here we are!
Her endless worrying is annoying.
Doctor! Please help us!
but
It is this annoying worry
Saved my life again
Why is it so quiet?
baby
No baby!
Baby oh my god
Are you okay? Oh my god.
Just like that she saved me time and time again
No!
No dear!
- Are you okay?
- When you grow up, you must be kind to your parents.
You're so likely to get into trouble
Do you want to be some great person?
Will it leave scars?
Are you worried about her getting a scar?
I'm lucky it's not worse.
Who would believe you caught it?
A child jumping from the roof
Mom and Dad
Oh my god
How did she get on the roof this time?
She always said she was a magpie
My baby got stitches
I can't imagine how painful it is.
Until much later
When I no longer receive her calls
I deeply miss her endless worry
sorry
I'm sorry, baby. I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter
Her delicate heart sank countless times
I wish I had
I can express my gratitude to her more.
Regret comes too late
(“Ready to go, give it your all
Dance with the moment")
Subtitle translation: Mateo