《Meet You When the Bitter Orange Ends》
Hello
Wow you are beautiful
Can you help me? Oh my god.
Really good
- Help me
- good
Here it comes
(Yalashan Film Club)
one two three
I'll take another photo
Smile
one two three!
What does I can't go mean?
tonight
It's our last night.
Your last night before enlistment!
I really want to...
Do you want to die?
Hey who knows what will happen?
People say you don’t know until you walk on the red carpet
Wait till you see me in a wedding dress
Here we come!
So beautiful
I should cover this up.
I did what I said
Oh? Hey over here.
Hey!
We don’t know who we will meet again or for the first time.
Rapid heartbeat
Oh my god!
I didn't break it on purpose.
…my feet feel like they are floating
Episode title: Such Unequal Love
Another life entered my mother's world
A chubby little guy
(Happy 10th birthday
(Presented by Lian Bingzhe and Luo Minyu)
Even though two generations
He is a strange being
But inexplicably lovable
No matter how cute your grandchildren are, don't take care of them.
I only feel cute when I see you once in a while
Don't be a parent to others until Jin Ming gets married.
Carefree and soaring into the sky
Everyone says the child's eyes look like mine
But the mouth is like fuck...
The chin
Where are your family members? Aren't they coming?
That you know...
I wouldn't want an unemployed son-in-law.
What about your brothers?
They just said
Roll as far as you can
- Walk
- What?
How far to go
- How far?
- How far to go!
How far to go
This one has 19 grams.
Oh my god, they're on the phone.
I mentioned "19 grams" dozens of times.
They said before that I could use this to go to college
Oh my god, that stingy old man
Hasn't he heard of inflation?
He should pay the market price for college tuition
They have money anyway, don't they?
He makes money by selling rice cakes.
Did you buy this for us?
right
The one he showed off was a Mercedes, right?
Of course, everyone eats rice cakes.
- But this job isn't cool enough
- "cool"?
Let's go
(Liang Jae-il’s first birthday)
Is this appropriate for you now?
I'd do anything for him.
You always mess around on my birthday
- At that time, we could only...
- I understand
Only my birthday was miserable
How are you going to support your family now?
Do you plan to live with us forever?
- I'm working on a business plan.
- Business?
With Zhelong?
I told you not to open a pawn shop
Life is just waiting for an opportunity...
I should beat the shit out of you.
Others become mature when they have a family.
Why are you still chasing after nothingness...
I don't need your help
Do I expect too much from you?
Let’s get up early first!
Go find some work at the docks or something.
- Go get a job!
- Seriously
Do you want me to live like you?
Do you really want that?
dad!
You have to turn the tap on completely.
To fill the bucket
Patching up life will never achieve anything great
You also understand this principle
Don't just count on Jin Ming.
Just wait and see what I can do!
I'm not the type to go out to eat.
The dad who only ordered three servings of meat
I want to be the dad who orders five or six servings of meat.
Why did you do this to your dad?
As people get older, their hearts become softer.
Even a heart of steel will bear scars
Na Jinming's mother
Can comfort Jinming's father
Oh my god
Why are you becoming more and more difficult?
To be honest, you should be grateful that I have become more mature.
How sensible a child is depends on how much you trust him
Jinming is sensible because you trust her completely
You always doubt me, so I'm only this tall.
You little bastard!
Can you hug him? My arms hurt.
Oh my god
Give me Zaiyi and you two go in.
Give him to me quickly.
Honey, come here.
Oh my god
I never thought my daughter would be like this.
I feel betrayed
It feels like the whole world is falling apart
I really can't tell
How sorry I am and...
Oh my god, if you get pregnant first and then get married
Not even a brass ring
Not to mention gold.
I didn't even have a wedding.
She will never wear a wedding dress.
Yinming may still be trying to figure it out
But as a human being...
I have no problem with Yinming
How to say it?
They say sons resemble their fathers.
I have always envied your life more than anyone else.
You are the wife of a rich man.
At the children's sports meeting
I was alone with three children in the hot sun
Then I saw your husband
Fan you to cool you down
You are always good at observing these things.
I cried.
I want to know how you are so lucky.
Being treated so kindly
What did I do to step on such a pile of shit?
that
Is Xianshu okay?
She can't do anything
If she doesn't, you scold her.
Scold her till she cries
I won't scold her.
I won't scold her until she cries.
I won't give Hyun-suk a brass ring
Okay?
If you want to see your eldest grandson or Xianshu
You can come visit them anytime.
Or call me out
The children are ours
So let's face it together, okay?
Oh my god, how does he look?
Exactly like my daughter?
Oh my god
It seems that you can't beat your daughter.
My mother once wrote a poem...
It's called My Damn Child.
(My damn child)
What's the big deal?
Oh my god!
You little bastard!
Is she going to defend her country or to explore the business world?
Pull it down and give it to me
Why would anyone buy a bottle of Chivas?
A first birthday gift for your child?
Zhelong must be crazy
Because you and dad look down on me
Jin Ming celebrated her only nephew's first birthday like this
Your sister isn't having a good time either.
Her company is in bad shape.
She works in a big company and acts superior.
But who is taking care of you and dad?
Who takes care of you when you are sick?
You talk as if you can take care of people!
Take care of yourself first
Don't be too hard on him. Even if a tree grows crooked, it can still provide shade.
Rumors are even more shocking when they come true
(Kia Corporation is in substantial bankruptcy)
This could have far-reaching consequences for our economy
By Kwon Jae-hong
Kia's main banking partners this afternoon
Korea First Bank
(18 Kia subsidiaries initiate bankruptcy protection)
Announced at a press conference
18 of Kia Group’s 28 subsidiaries…
This is a harvest season
Whether it is the Golden Toad...
Post-dated cheque
- Stop layoffs immediately!
- Stop layoffs!
- We're not leaving like this!
- We won't!
- Stop layoffs immediately!
- Stop layoffs!
(Stop layoffs!)
- We're not leaving like this!
- We won't!
(We can't stand it any longer)
The Asian financial crisis is destroying businesses
Causing widespread unemployment
(Assistant Manager of Overseas Business Department)
A particularly unforgettable winter is coming
34th largest company: Danong Group
In addition to Meduba
They have essentially dissolved
Among the four subsidiaries protected
Only Meduba is resurrected
Danong Limited goes into receivership
Danong Heavy Industry and Metro Products...
Everyone can get approved! 100% approval for credit cards!
Shuanglong Development Company applied for settlement yesterday
(Use credit cards to get through this difficult time!)
Declared bankrupt
Thai-Japanese Group in financial trouble
Designated for bankruptcy protection today
Debts of Tairi and its subsidiaries
Total 970 billion won
Chohung Bank and other bond holders
The meeting will be held on the 24th...
Stocks plunge again, KOSPI index falls…
First of all, thank you for giving me a chance during this difficult time.
Difficult situation...
first
Thank you for giving me a chance during these difficult times.
I do…
Experiencing severe financial difficulties
After barely holding on for a while
Hitech Group officially filed for bankruptcy today
This toothpaste is exported to Northeast Asia
Often in short supply
(Recruitment Position)
But due to the bankruptcy of the manufacturer...
This toothpaste alone can treat
Common tooth decay
and gum disease
Whitens teeth
This product is a collaboration with American Toothpaste Company
Results of technical cooperation
Recognized by the World Health Organization
The new core group of the 25th largest company filed for settlement
Declared bankrupt today
Dear Audience,
The government has decided
Apply for assistance from the International Monetary Fund
(Interview cancelled at 9 am on the 21st)
Although South Korea was once known for its economic boom
Now forced to admit national bankruptcy
and seek assistance from international organizations for recovery
The government's goal is to minimize
IMF policy intervention
Even if South Korea receives aid
(Permanently closed)
The next stop is Xinlin Market, formerly known as Cannes Theater
(Cannes theater closed in December
The last screening is free and first come first served)
(Cannes theaters will be closed on December 1
Cannes has been in Xinlin, thank you all)
When a door closes...
Another door will open
(Cinema Paradiso)
(Ticket A 17)
Hey can't you just sit anywhere?
(A-17)
This is not a leg rest, it's an armrest
Here is the handrail
People need countless reincarnations of fate
To meet once in a lifetime
It is rare to encounter it three times.
Hey, did you see her?
Did you see her?
- What?
- Didn't you see her?
Who asked you to clean these up?
I have already paved the way for you.
You still missed the target
If you fail the third time...
You have to wait until next life.
Jin Ming!
Last time it was Seo Taiji
This time it's HOT
Jin Ming!
Only then did he understand
You only have three chances
If no one scores in extra time
It will go into a penalty shootout
Stop!
master!
When a door closes
Another door will open
How about taking the next one?
Really
thank you
If the IMF crisis had not occurred…
If I hadn't lost my job...
If the theater hadn't closed down...
If anything goes wrong...
Everyone got off and arrived at the terminal.
...maybe this moment will never happen
Is this a dream?
Is it a dream?
Yes
I started chasing you from the cinema
Run as fast as you can
I can't let you slip away
Even if I run until I can't breathe,
Are you
Going to the theater alone?
- Yes
- I see
- Are you also...
- Yes
finally
We can use
The word "finally"?
Why do you keep laughing?
You look totally different now.
It seems that you are no longer Picasso
I haven't changed
I am Picasso from the Picasso Institute of Art
Without me, our college will close down.
They pay me a lot.
Really great
real
Me too
Really great
Why are we all at the theater today?
In fact, I go there every day
in case
I really miss you
I miss you so much
So now we can...
Now?
Isn't it possible?
Give me a drink
Or is it not possible?
We can order drinks now.
Let's have some beer
Just beer?
（Jinro Soju）
etc.
Why are you staring at me?
It drives me crazy.
Right?
I also
I'm going crazy
- Oh my god
- Oh no
I don't usually get drunk easily.
You will hurt yourself
Lift your feet higher.
Your voice sounds like my dad's.
What sound did you just make?
Are you bleeding?
I think I got it cut.
I think I need to stop the bleeding.
But no bleeding
Precautions
how so?
I thought I was going to die suddenly...
"sudden death"?
When I helped you get those books
I just kept thinking
“I want to hold her hand”
But we were...
Right?
That's why I said
“Everyone has a dark side”
...is no longer innocent
I think I've become darker.
We dated like adults...
Not the cheap IKEA feel
But the kind of expensive home
Are you crazy?
What's wrong with your expression? And your hands?
Come on, don't make that face.
Come on, you're like Titanic
Are you drawing me?
Come on, how can I
Paint you like Titanic?
Different models, different situations
"Condition"?
Okay, so what kind of situation would be appropriate?
Wow
- Please Putoto
- "Pu To To"?
What should the situation be like then?
Toto is being naughty again, isn't he?
Oh my god, really
Please how could you spit in my face?
Don't call me Pu To To!
Why do you like Park Toto so much?
I thought you never laughed
Toto and I have the same sense of humor
You influenced me
I started talking like you too
In this adult world where we learn to fake smiles
That's an incredible energy.
Don't make me laugh when we kiss
I can't concentrate
Baby, laugh together every day
Harder than kissing every day
So we are a good match
- Don't add the garlic now.
- good
Do you really like eating raw fish?
You always eat
Yeah, I like it.
Hey, do you want to eat?
Real amberjack?
- Real amberjack?
- right
Real amberjack
finally…
Finally the two men met
hateful
Amberjack shit!
Where did this damn saury come from?
Hey Dad
Why are you looking at him like that?
This will make him uncomfortable.
Finally one day
I stand with other men instead of my dad
That's how I look at people
Could you be nicer to him?
People living on the peninsula are not used to taking a boat
Did you adapt right away from the start?
- right
- That's right.
Did you let them go because they were too young?
You are such a kind fisherman.
Your father
Really kind
These are baits and we are leaving them to die.
Now that's not kind, is it?
Okay stop staring at him and catch me an amberjack
I brought him here
Just to eat real amberjack
Why do you keep following her?
She just went to the toilet
Just sit down and eat the amberjack and remember to pay
(Auntie Seafood House)
Selling rice cakes!
(IMF crisis Jeju Island residents half price
Eat together and live together)
Selling rice cakes!
Who will buy her rice cake?
Why doesn't anyone buy her rice cakes?
Selling rice cakes!
(Collecting gold from home to boost the national economy)
Are they playing a game where whoever speaks first loses?
(Gold Collection Movement Participant)
But why don't you sit over there?
Why do you ignore them?
Maybe she doesn't like him
Yeah?
What do you think of him?
I?
Get your head off my shoulders!
So why did you come here? Why did you come to Jeju?
Are you playing 20 questions?
I told you not to do this
You can't speak or ride a boat.
You don't even drink, right?
Then why should I hand my daughter over to you?
If you were me would you?
I'm really angry for no reason
Even now you are not willing to make an effort
Even though I want to impress you
But if you don't like me...
No matter what I do...
He won't like you anyway.
So you don't try hard?
Who do you think you are?
You are such a rude boy.
Letting go
Nineteen Eighteen…
What about seven six five four three two one?
I said let go
What do you think of him?
Um
You know...
Do you have anything to say?
If you have something to say, just say it.
Really
His family members...
Speaking of his family...
I mean
I'm trying my best to impress you.
What did you do?
I didn't see anything.
I don't normally eat this much but...
Sorry for asking you to prepare so much food.
Be careful
I almost beat you up.
Don't stare at me
Why did you get up again?
Why do you keep following her to the bathroom?
What do you want to do?
What are you doing in the dark?
You are dead
It's dark so I have to...
Notice!
It’s cold so…
Why is this brat so dull?
What if Liang Jinming likes him more?
If I make a big deal out of it...
Did you just call your brother-in-law a brat?
"Brother-in-law"? So you recognize him?
You selfish child, don't just eat the shrimp by yourself
Peel some for him!
Wait, why? What's so good about him?
Seriously why?
Oh My God
Why do you keep following her?
She just went to the toilet
Just sit down and eat the amberjack and remember to pay
Oh my god, why do you keep...
I'm afraid she'll fall.
Afraid that Jinming would fall
You think I would let my daughter fall into the water?
You should worry about yourself.
Notice!
But I still have to protect her so...
I'm worried so...
I don't stand a chance.
How can I impress him?
Do you know, baby?
You were a little dull just now
that
I want to impress him.
But that's how I am so...
So this is your nature
I don't know what to do
It's hard to do something I don't do often so...
So you think
I am the kind of person who likes to please others.
The one who changes his voice in front of your mom?
Let me be frank. I am...
- Are you listening?
- exist
I am my father's daughter
If you can't get past my dad, then you can't get past me.
- Can't get married
- baby
baby
Wait, why do you approve of him?
Then why didn’t you recognize my wife at the beginning?
I will never allow anyone to treat my virtue differently
Go away, go away
Hey Hyun-sook knows you were in kindergarten
Shit in your pants?
Does your Chung-seop know that you use my razor?
- Let me go
- Uncle!
Oh my god
uncle
uncle!
I can
Can I peel shrimp for you?
You peel it yourself
He got drunk and acted weird.
Look at him.
He really likes Jinming
But you know what, his mother also likes Jinming
She said she really likes Jinming
Interesting, right?
Yeah, it's very interesting.
You must have cried, right?
How is that possible?
Who in this world doesn’t like Jin Ming?
You cried
Is this real wild honey from Hallasan?
Are you going to give this to his mother?
You know
Chung-seop's mother gave me a gift first
She was literally bribing me.
Not everyone does this.
Do you know what I received yesterday?
What treasure?
What is it
Let her wrap it so tightly?
Why let him sleep here?
We should book him a hotel room.
How can we let him stay in a hotel?
I already feel guilty about him sleeping in the living room
How could I sleep under the same roof with Park Jong-seob?
Why can’t I sleep?
Just can't
Seriously, don't go out to see him.
He won't sneak into Jinming's room.
How dare he if you stare at him like that?
Don't go!
Let me go hey
Sit down! Oh my god!
Uncle, why don't you go to bed?
Instead, it keeps coming out?
What about you? Why aren't you asleep yet?
Why aren't you sleeping? What are you doing?
What are you going to do?
What? What's wrong? Is there a problem?
I picked the best persimmons when I went home in the fall
Thinking of you preparing for the whole season
I put my heart and soul into it
Every day I look at it and think of the lovely Jinming
I like Jinming very much
(From Chung-seop's mother)
Maybe mom
(I like Jinming very much)
Been waiting to hear these words.
Are you going to stay up all night?
If he went to Jinming's room
What are you going to do?
Then he's dead.
What can you do?
You never beat Jinming, right?
Let her be
Your partial love
Mom knows...
This day will come sooner or later
Laugh Show! I am the host, Kang Seok
The crisis of the International Monetary Fund has led to
Lots of sad words, right?
The "early lost" refers to
Most of the unemployed people are in their twenties.
(Closing Sale)
"38th parallel" means you have to quit your job at 38
"Winning the lottery" means retiring at 45 like everyone else
"Job thief" means working until age 56
Equivalent to a thief
No one can laugh these days.
Listen to an inspiring song
I flew away from the nest.
Like a blue bird flying over the bare hills
Flapping wings with excitement
Full of confidence
Don't laugh too much today.
It will make your dad angry.
Mom, don't be like this today.
Please don't cry like that, okay?
alright
You're going to ignore me once I get married?
You're not my mother anymore?
Listen carefully
I am still Liang Jinming, not Park Jinming
What are the last few digits of my pager?
Isn't that his home number?
Or is it our 3312?
Then whose family am I?
I know I won't give my daughter away.
So don't cry
If you cry I will cry too
The wedding photos will be ruined
Let's keep calm
Okay?
Oh my God! Why are you two here?
How could I miss your family's happy event?
The girl who is getting married...
Can you hold this open?
…The one who loves caramel, right?
Yes, Jinming, you always give her free caramel
OK, please go forward.
You are so beautiful today
- Hey, where's Joo Kyung?
- Juqing?
- How could the photographer be late?
- She's here
- Hey!
I shouldn't have come.
- Juqing!
- Hey!
- hurry up!
Please hurry up
Hey, hurry up.
What's going on?
She looks so beautiful
Hey, photographer, don't be late.
You should start filming when I get off the car
Are you happy? What a confident bride.
- bring it on
- Start shooting from here
good
So beautiful
Let's go over there
Go to the stairs
The stairs there
Does everyone marry their most passionate lover?
The scale of love is the same but the temperature is different
You gave us so many oranges.
You don't have to buy oranges anymore.
It's that kind of temperature that allows me to be myself
Did you say hello?
I found my prince
A match made in heaven
You taught him to be so cheesy.
Or is he just like that?
He is my favorite student
So cute
Next the groom enters
The groom enters confidently
Please welcome him with applause.
I didn't say
Do I hate it when brides cry at their weddings?
Don't cry for me, Dad.
I'll be very angry if you cry
Forget it, what?
Don't look into my eyes, okay?
Jin Ming
You're going to be fine, right?
If something is wrong, forget it.
Come back to me directly
Okay?
Can you really eat this?
If you don't like it, forget it
Can you spit it out?
Oh my god
(Liang Jinming)
Is it suitable?
Say "Hello, teacher"
Hello, teacher
Oh my god
I said I can't send her to school yet.
Let's send her there next year.
Do you want her to stay home forever?
How are you going to marry her off in the future?
You are so stupid. Is he really stupid?
Jinming, do you think you can go to school?
I can go there too.
What does it matter if he goes?
I don't want you anywhere near Kim Jong-gun.
I want to go to school
Then go now. If you don't like it, forget it.
Can you please run home? I'll be waiting for you here.
- Okay?
- good
Jinming, I'm sure you'll be able to run well tomorrow, right?
I think I can get first place
First place?
- Ready... No.
- run!
Can you run when you hear the word “run”?
But you don't have to be first.
If you fall, come to me.
I'll be behind you tomorrow.
Okay?
good
- Prepare...
- run!
Oh my god
(Aim for high scores!)
(University Entrance Examination Admission Ticket)
come on!
You can do it!
Come on Wuyi High School!
We're too early again.
Seriously
Why is our family so hardworking?
What kind of life do you live that causes you to be like this?
Jin Ming
- Can you guess it?
- Please
Why should I guess the answer?
Dad, I am Liang Jinming
you're right
I know you've been here for these years.
You do everything well
Your dad, who is good at everything, now knows
So you're saying I'm good at everything?
Just let me forget it without saying anything?
But if you have a headache and really can't do it
That's fine.
Then run out and I'll wait here for you, okay?
You always have my back, right?
Are you sure you don't need some herbal remedies to calm you down?
(Liang Jinming)
(The pride of Dodong-ri!
My daughter will definitely pass the imperial examination! )
Every time I walk on the tightrope
Dad is standing there holding the net
"Even if you fall, I will be there"
I really wish I had told him
How comforting his words are.
Even once
He stood there
The snow seems to fall only on my dad
The bride is about to enter the red carpet
Jin Ming
What's wrong?
Dad is still here
Just do whatever you want to do.
In my dad's winter
I grew into a lush green
Feeding on their youth
Grows into a tree
If Chung-seop makes you angry, forget it.
Is it okay for Dad to be here all the time?
No, don't say that now.
You're annoying, dad.
Welcome the bride
Please welcome her with applause
Guangli must be grinning from ear to ear
She is finally happy.
Uncle Aichun was at the wedding
When I walked down the red carpet holding Aichun's hand
I thought I would die of heartache
Daughter's decent life
Like a medal for a mother
So she kept laughing
To prevent the bride from crying
Can't get to the front
The groom ran to greet her.
Please give them a big round of applause again
We agreed to keep calm
Why are you crying like this?
Aren't we going to get married? Should we cancel it?
No, I want to continue
Let's go
The day before my dad left me
I apologized hastily
"Dad, I'm so sorry."
My father told me at that time
Since the day I was born
He's been living in heaven.
I'll just say it
Your dad cries harder than your mom
My dad is crying?
I didn't expect your dad to be like that.
Why do men say that in front of their son-in-law?
Always want to act so tough?
Why drink too much?
Dad wanted to see if he would behave strangely when he was drunk.
Who is weird now?
- Hey Dad
- careful!
What did your mother say?
What?
Does she like Jin Ming?
My mother keeps nagging me for a daughter.
So she likes Jinming more than me
No
- What?
- She's my daughter, not yours.
She will always be my daughter
Yes, of course.
- Park Chung-seop!
- At Uncle
Do you know what you took from me?
What?
I give you...
My Paradise
You didn't do anything for her.
30 years passed like this
All right
I heard that my aunt is the one with literary talent.
Hey Beam Heaven
Get Your Own Honey
Dad's partial love
We now invite the bride and groom
For the bride's parents
Bride and groom please bow to the bride's parents
Oh my god, the bride's father is crying oh my god!
Be quiet
The father of the bride must love his daughter very much
Kuanzhi's most precious thing was stolen
He was robbed!
Even if his mother remarried, he wouldn't cry like this.
I wish you happiness.
Next the bride and groom will bow to the groom's mother
That's enough, okay?
It's really embarrassing.
Bride and groom please bow to the groom's mother
Who is it?
Who is looking for you?
Who is this?
I don't know either
Didn't I tell you
Did you dye your gray hair before going?
Jinming is nagging me again
Obviously compared to her
Or am I better able to take care of my husband?
She now has her own husband to take care of.
Life never allows us
Really enjoy these moments
Liang Yinming
I?
Happiness is coming
But trouble always sneaks up from behind
Where is Park Cheol-yong?
You know, right?
I?
When mom tells me not to hang out with a certain friend
There is always a reason for everything
(“If you can’t do it, forget it
We are always behind you")
Subtitle translation: Mateo