WHEN LIFE GIVES YOU TANGERINES
The strongest wind is one
that blows within one's fist-sized heart.
Nothing could withstand such wind.
I'm completely innocent.
Looking up at the sky, I have…
no shame, you know.
So why?
Why am I no longer chief
and just put out to pasture?
Hey, Park Yeong-ran.
Get over here.
Are you ignoring me as well?
I said get over here.
What the heck do you do at home?
You eat white rice with my money,
and you can't even handle one kid?
That brat definitely takes after you.
I know everything!
Just sleep if you're drunk!
What was that, punk?
Whose kid are you anyway?
-Whose side are you on?
-Father, do you even know how old I am?
Hey!
You punk!
You never once came to my sports days.
Maybe you never saw me as your kid.
When you're fooling around enjoying
spring flowers and snowy mountains…
"Fooling around"?
Mom never missed a day
packing us a hot lunch.
Hey!
Who brought your new mother
into this house, huh?
Your stepmom can be replaced anytime,
but you and I are family by blood!
-If you two split up, I'm going with Mom.
-What was that, punk?
I'm only treating you like a father
because Mom lives with you.
Fetch the broom.
Where's the broom, huh?
Oh-seong, go to your room.
You shouldn't talk like that.
Split up with him!
What are you holding onto?
I'm going to stay with your father.
I'm staying with him.
Darn it!
That's right!
You'd never survive without me.
You all eat well, thanks to my money.
Don't you?
You even eat white rice!
I have to stay.
I have to live with him.
Goddamn it!
I'll spend the rest of my life with him
and see how it all ends.
KNOCK
YOU BETTER KNOCK
Get out.
You little…
I wish I could knock you out
with a flying kick.
I said get out!
Seriously.
Oh man.
Mom!
I'd have given you a beating
if you were Han-eum. You know that?
You look like an army sergeant,
and you're dating?
Why do you even have
this actress's picture?
You'd need to be born again
to look like her.
Get out of my room!
How are you involved
with that family's son?
You fool. You know, his mother and our…
-Damn it.
-What about his mom?
You guys won't work out anyway.
You'll be mortified later.
Stop this bullshit
while I'm still being nice.
Why won't we work out anyway?
Go tell him…
I will kill him if I ever see him.
Let's just break up.
No, I don't want to! Why?
Because of those bastards
Oh-seong and Han-eum?
Or because of my father?
My father is my father, but I'm me.
I never listen to him anyway.
Listen, don't go around
saying you're my girlfriend anymore.
Don't cut in line at the cafeteria
thinking I've got your back.
Only go to the roller rink in Ssangbong.
No, I'm still gonna do it.
You can't date anyone but me anyway.
If you do, I'll beat them up.
You think I won't?
I think you will.
No, I can't break up with you.
I won't.
-One last thing, Bu Hyeon-suk.
-What?
Stay healthy.
They're crying.
You son of a bitch!
Don't ever let me see you again.
I will kill you!
You're breaking up with me
just because you got beat up?
I'll tell them to keep beating you up!
Every single time they see you!
You don't know how much it hurts!
We can just run away from them.
Make sure they don't catch you.
The arcade, the roller rink, downtown.
I can't go anywhere.
Your brothers' friends keep showing up.
I got on the bus yesterday,
and the driver was one of their friends.
He told me not to get off the bus
until the last stop!
Damn it! How can I keep living like this?
I have my own life too.
Then run away.
Let's run away.
-What?
-I can't live like this either.
My father even removed my bedroom door.
You want to run away?
My dad said if I see you again,
he'll shave my head
and send me to a Buddhist temple.
You believe him?
Then all your friends
would be Buddhist nuns by now.
Do we run away or not?
Are you going to run away or not?
I don't know. Damn it!
Keep honking.
Keep honking the horn.
Man, they look like
the center of the Korean flag.
Come on. Those were the days!
Apparently,
this is the spring of their lives.
Is it because it's their spring,
or is it in their blood?
I love you.
I love you too.
Looking back, spring was like a feast.
Welcome home, son.
But for the budding sprouts, it's a war.
Hello.
Do you frequent this place too?
A trial for the new buds that push
their heads through the concrete.
You can't even use the ladle properly.
Your mom didn't teach you?
It's just that the seaweed is all tangled.
Don't use your hands!
We don't do that in our family.
You're really both here.
This really is a happy birthday.
Only one person was happy in that house.
The kimchi tastes so good.
Good kimchi is hard to find in Seoul.
I mean, I'm not saying
all kimchi in Seoul is bad.
I bought it.
I haven't had a homemade meal in a while.
I feel like I can eat two bowls.
We're light eaters.
Do your parents know
you frequent a guy's apartment like this?
She doesn't come over often.
It's my birthday, so I asked her to come.
Did I ask you?
Geum-myeong.
This isn't Yeong-beom's apartment.
It's mine.
An apartment I got for him.
I don't want you frequenting my apartment.
-Mother.
-It's my apartment.
And I don't want you here.
Sure, keep dating.
Learn how relationships work.
I told you. I plan to marry Geum-myeong--
Quiet.
You wanted a place near your school,
and it was just for this…
Just for this.
You are my pride.
Now my pride is bruised.
Each had their heart rocked by love,
and a storm swept through their heart.
Does your family own a conglomerate?
Like Samsung or Hyundai?
How much richer
could your family be than mine?
We go to the same school,
and I'm just as precious to my parents.
Why should I be ashamed
that I can't ladle soup?
Are you better at it?
Did your mother teach you?
I'm not good at ladling either.
So unfair.
I hate everything about this.
I feel like I've become a cheap clown.
I can't stand groveling
in front of a person
who won't like me anyway,
no matter what I do.
I hate it so much!
DIGESTIVE DRINK
Why did you eat so much?
I wanted to impress her.
Of course I did!
Who wouldn't want to impress
her boyfriend's mother?
Who would want to marry
the pride of his mother?
Just choose one.
Be a good son or a good husband.
You can only be one.
I don't want a man
who's just a little nice to everyone.
Forget the proposal.
Choose one first before anything else.
Well, who in the world
would choose one over the other?
No man would--
My dad.
What?
My dad did.
I see.
Let me make myself clear.
I won't marry your mother's son.
It was a time
when everything felt so sincere,
like a little owl crying all night
at the slightest breeze.
This is Kim Gi-deok on Two O'clock Date.
I believe the '90s are truly
the renaissance of pop culture.
The winds of change are here.
I love this painting.
I guess he won't be Picasso anymore.
See?
You can do your job properly.
It's so obvious what the movie is about.
Just looking at this
makes me want to do the Lambada.
Great job!
That lady's back again.
She somehow always knows the release day.
Where does she get the resale tickets?
I've never sold her any tickets before.
Maybe they're counterfeit?
We don't want any.
No, that's…
-We don't want resale tickets.
-That's not…
Does that look like Choi Jin-sil?
Does it look like Choi Jin-sil?
-I think it looks like her.
-It's a job well done, then.
-Sorry?
-Or is it bad?
No, I guess not.
Apparently, it was painted
by a college art major.
Right.
Why do people go in without looking?
Is everyone busy or something?
It makes me a little sad that people
don't even glance at the painting.
It really does.
A Picasso lived in the basement
of the Cannes Theater,
and for someone,
this theater was their Louvre.
Stop selling resale tickets!
I said stop it!
Scalping is a nuisance to society!
No resale tickets!
I said no!
Does he really think I'm a scalper?
Since you're here,
it would be nice to watch a movie.
I hear this movie
coming out in two days is great.
It's being rereleased
due to its popularity.
You shouldn't give out tickets to anyone.
But you're not just anyone.
This is an employee benefit
offered by the owner himself!
Come at 2:00 p.m. on Monday.
It's normally empty then.
It'll feel like you rented the theater.
I'd prefer it if you didn't tell my son
I came here to see his paintings.
Chung-seop doesn't know I come here.
He leaves with his packed lunch
and comes home covered in paint.
He never tells me what he paints or where.
He says he's embarrassed.
Does just anyone get to paint
such big pictures?
-If they paint, they're painters.
-Of course.
He painted that so well.
I'm just dying to see what he does.
I've seen everything Chung-seop
has painted since elementary school.
That's been my joy.
These days, movie release days are my joy.
PROMOTIONAL TICKET
Our theater would be ruined
without Artist Park.
Sir, you're not from Seoul, are you?
Honestly.
-Wow.
-Wow!
What is it this time?
Did Eun-myeong sell something
at school again?
Eun-myeong's mom.
Don't call me that from now on.
Should we just call you Geum-myeong's mom?
No calls from Seoul?
Geum-myeong has a boyfriend, I swear.
She's forgotten Mom and Dad already.
Goodness me. It's so unfair.
It's as if she's doing us a favor
by calling us first.
They are only children
when they're in your arms.
Once they leave,
they're busier than the president.
My children are
the busiest people in the world.
What, did you have another bad dream?
Why did the school call you this time?
Is he bottom of his class again?
He's never bottom of his class.
Cheol-yong is in that class.
It's about cigarettes.
You said you wouldn't tell.
Does that little punk smoke?
He doesn't smoke!
He sold them.
-He sold cigarettes.
-Wow.
AUNTIES' SEAFOOD HOUSE
He really is something.
Isn't the seller more impressive
than the smoker?
He lied to the old man at the variety shop
about the cigarettes being for us,
then bought them
and basically made a delivery.
They say he sold them at a markup.
Personally, I'm more curious
about what Eun-myeong will become
than Geum-myeong.
Have you asked why he does it?
What do you mean "why"?
He's just an angsty teenager
acting entitled.
I mean, have you ever asked
why he desperately needs money?
I don't know why he's obsessed with money!
That's why you should ask.
You gave birth to his body, not his mind.
You know,
you're helpless with Geum-myeong,
but a boss to Eun-myeong.
You handle picky Geum-myeong
like soft tofu,
and easygoing Eun-myeong
like a radish being tossed around.
Geum-myeong takes after me
and is a bit emotionally sensitive,
and Eun-myeong is, you know--
A pushover?
I don't think that!
A radish may look fine
no matter how many times it falls,
but even the sturdiest radish
can crack inside.
Don't treat your children differently.
Children… remember everything.
It's because I'm upset too.
I can't help but get more mad
about the one I worry about the most.
So it has nothing to do
with Geum-myeong making you proud
and Eun-myeong embarrassing you?
So what if it does? Am I a saint?
What could I possibly do?
…may be the star of tomorrow.
A choice ahead of its time.
High-performance Elantra.
So…
I'm in your debt once again.
I don't know how I'll repay you.
There's no need.
But I'd still like to…
Then could you paint something for me
when you have time?
So I can sell it for a high price someday.
I heard Picasso's work
became more valuable after he died.
But there's no guarantee I'll die first…
-Was that a joke?
-Yeah.
-I should go back to the box office.
-Well…
What is it?
Thank you, really.
There's no need.
I didn't spend my own money or anything.
No, I mean, my mother…
It's her first time
seeing a movie in a theater.
Mister! You have to run.
Oh no, you have to run!
Even though she watches
The Weekend Classic Movie every week.
I guess
I'd been so focused on my own life.
Each person was swayed
by the love in their heart.
You know what?
I started crying when the projectionist
walked in with shades on.
Alfredo?
Why wasn't there a fire extinguisher
in the projection room?
Why put out the fire?
He should've saved himself.
He should've jumped out the window.
Then he would've only broken his legs.
I wonder what he did
after losing his projectionist job.
Maybe Toto sent him money
because he's kind.
Did you cry because
you thought Alfredo might be broke?
You know, Toto
reminds me of you.
Toto is like my son.
What did you want to give to Ms. Yang?
I'll give it to her.
Did you say you're an English major?
Yes.
PHOTOCOPY, PRINTING, BINDING
You can rely on me until you graduate.
These are all in English.
People just won't pick them up.
It'd cost a fortune to buy them all.
English ones are even more expensive.
There are some study notes in here too.
I'm not sure if I can accept all of these.
So this is why parents love daughters.
I'm here all the time,
so every day feels the same.
The only special thing I did
was to see new paintings on premiere days.
But I was truly happy today,
thanks to you, Ms. Yang.
I think I'll remember this day
until I draw my last breath.
Hearing you say that
makes me feel like
I've done something extraordinary.
Mother, that's enough.
How can she carry them all?
She can't carry them alone.
She can't.
How about a drink?
Well, a drink…
-Maybe we shouldn't?
-Here you are.
Yeah, that's a bit…
All right, then.
You know…
Yes?
If you're grateful,
maybe clear my name
instead of buying noodles?
The landlord's daughter
keeps kicking my shoes outside my door.
She knows that there's nothing between us.
I guess
she wants to get married
without feeling guilty.
So you're sending off your girlfriend
to marry someone else?
You must have
a really big heart.
She's marrying
the son of a noodle shop owner.
Do they make a fortune selling noodles?
The Pildong Noodles chain.
It's a perfect family to marry into,
but she can't
bring herself to do it.
Then just hold onto her.
It's her fate if she dumps Picasso
and goes to the noodle guy.
Tell her to her face,
"Leave if you want.
It's your loss, not mine."
You should bring a gift and say,
"Please let me marry your daughter."
That way,
at least you won't have any regrets.
How would you know
if I'm better than the noodle guy?
You don't know me very well.
You're really precious to your mom.
That's why you paint everything
however you please.
That's just deeply rooted guts, you know?
I'm precious to my parents too.
I'd just like to think
that holding my head high
and living my life
is what keeps my folks' pride intact.
At least I'd like to think so.
You know, you don't need to take sides
with someone you barely know.
It's not like I don't know.
People are the same, after all.
No, they are different.
Everyone has a dark side, after all.
It was a time
when strangers were dangerous,
and kindness from a stranger
was dangerous.
Less than three months after a 13-year-old
was killed in the Hwaseong serial murders…
Oh my. I'm so sorry again.
Yes, please let me know. Please.
Those bastards should be beaten to death!
The phrase "beaten to death"
exists for a reason.
How bad must they be?
Is that right? Okay, I see.
When Geum-myeoung gets back,
could you please ask her to call--
Yes, okay. Thank you.
When you kidnap a child,
you're taking three lives, not just one.
How can parents cope with losing a child?
I mean, losing a child
is devastating in itself,
but to lose your child like that…
Goodness me.
Why? Is Geum-myeong out late again?
I don't understand
why she's out so late at night.
I told her to stay home at night.
What's wrong?
Do you keep having bad dreams?
About what?
Maybe you feel that way
because the ancestral rite has come up.
Something odd happened to you
at an ancestral rite as a child.
On Aegi Hill?
We were there together, right?
Goodness, just thinking about it
gives me the chills.
I can still remember the smells
from that day.
Hurry! They put meat
on the ancestral rite table.
My father will give it all to my brother.
Only people can see that black dragonfly.
They say other dragonflies can't see it.
Why not?
Because it's the Grim Reaper
of dragonflies.
We humans can't see
the Grim Reaper either, you know.
What is it? Are you going to catch it?
You go ahead.
Let's just go!
If I catch it,
it won't be able to take
the other dragonflies.
Baby dragonflies would want to live
with their mom and dad too.
Father is going to scold you again.
Is that what people call being possessed?
I don't know why I chased it.
AEGI HILL
BUS STOP
I need to take the bus, but my legs hurt.
Could you go to the store
to exchange this for ten-hwan coins?
What did the store owner say?
That it's not his job to change coins.
-Did he scold you?
-No.
But he did give me a side-eye.
For your trouble.
You're really kind and so gentle.
You listen well, don't you?
But
you don't have to give me this.
Then, can you do it once more?
I need to take two buses.
Since the store owner
didn't like giving change,
you can find the cabbage truck vendor
in the alley behind the telephone pole.
Could you get some change from that man?
Then I'll give you another one.
It's just that my legs hurt.
What are you doing here?
-Mom.
-What are you doing?
-What about you, Mom?
-What's this money?
-Mister!
-What? You know that man?
That lady was just here.
Gwang-rye said her heart was pounding,
but she said nothing
so she wouldn't scare you.
But, Mom, what are you doing here?
It was such an odd coincidence.
I was in a neighborhood I'd never been to,
and I ran into my mom,
who would never go there.
You still don't know, do you?
Your mother went out
to look for you that day.
I don't need to get firewood,
thanks to you, Sister.
Don't call her sister anymore.
We still have the firewood
you brought before.
It's the least she can do.
Her child has been living and eating here
for free for years now.
She should at least do that
for child support.
Don't make Ae-sun carry wood.
Replace the jeongjong with makgeolli.
Han-gyu likes makgeolli better.
Where's Ae-sun?
It's her father's ancestral rite,
but all she cares about is going out.
Where's Ae-sun?
There's meat soup. Where is she?
She went after a Grim Reaper dragonfly.
What?
A mother's instinct is a scary thing.
Apparently, she ran over a mountain
in no time.
You should be the one
eating Dad's meat soup.
Why wander around instead?
Give it to me.
Why? This one is mine.
It's bad luck.
How did you know I was here?
I have eyes in the back of my head.
That's what it takes to be a mom.
Do you think she'll come to get her money?
-Ae-sun.
-Yes?
Did she see your face?
Yes.
What did she look like?
She had a pale face,
and on her wrist, something strange…
You think your mom would let someone off
for messing with her child?
Here, check it out!
Come see! We'll give you the best.
Fresh from the haenyeo!
Three for 50 hwan. Here you go.
I don't care.
Just give me one more.
Come on,
we put our lives on the line for these.
Forget it, then.
Goodness me!
My goodness!
Hey! Are you going to check the wrist
of every woman in Jeju?
Seriously!
You're driving all our customers away
by yanking their wrists.
Are you selling conches
to catch the culprit?
That bitch saw Ae-sun's face.
I'm going to buy some conches.
They're practically free!
What's your price?
What's your offer?
Hey, I sent the boat back.
Why do you always go after the young ones?
Is there an age limit for begging?
You touch it, you buy it. Okay?
They don't listen as they get older.
Kind kids who are so gentle are the best.
That girl was just perfect.
What the hell?
-What is it?
-Come on!
Let's make a sale
before you yank her wrist!
You must've lost your mind.
Are you out of your mind? Let her go!
What the hell? How are you so strong?
You should be beaten to death, bitch!
You were going to make my daughter
beg for money?
These scumbags! Get that bastard!
They need to be beaten to death!
You bastard, get over here!
You bitch!
So what happened?
There were no open endings
in fairy tales back then.
She beat her to death. Obviously.
She beat her to death?
Those scumbags deserved
to be beaten to death, didn't they?
Don't ever come back here, you bastard!
Die, you bitch!
At the time, the country didn't have
much of a legal system,
so the police didn't say much
if you beat up those who deserved it.
Even if you left someone half-dead,
the cops would clean up the mess
and take them away.
The cops themselves
used to beat people up.
It happened to be the day
of Han-gyu's ancestral rite.
Your mom said that your father saved you.
But I don't think so.
It was your mom who saved her child.
Nothing beats a mother's instinct.
Oh dear.
Mother wakes up this late.
She may forget everything else,
but she never forgets
the day her eldest son visits.
Nothing beats a mother's instinct.
My mom told me back then
that you need eyes
in the back of your head
to be a mother.
Hey, you have a call.
Okay.
For goodness' sake.
Do people in Jeju not watch Eyes of Dawn?
She always calls when this show is on.
Yeah, everything's fine.
What could possibly happen
in just one day?
EYES OF DAWN
Are you going to call me
every time you have a dream?
Why are you always home late these days?
Where do you go wandering every night?
I don't go wandering.
Did they fix the light in your alley?
It's a scary world out there.
Be home early.
Make sure you sleep at home.
No staying out overnight.
I'll know if you do.
Do you call every night
to see if I'm only having fun?
You're not seeing anyone, are you?
I won't be able to handle it
if you upset me too.
You are your mom and dad's pride.
All my hope is in you,
so if the pillar starts acting up--
That damn pillar…
Am I everything in your life?
Don't you have a life of your own?
Think about it.
Even if I stay out all night,
you can't do anything from there.
If I wanted to fool you,
I could do it 100 or 1,000 times.
Good for you.
So stop fussing over it, please.
You need to live your own life.
Wait until you have a kid.
Wait until you have a daughter
just like you!
You wear these hairpins every day
and lose them every day.
Why do I bother buying them for you?
You lose them every day.
She thinks she's the only great one.
I saw this at the hardware store,
so I bought one.
Visit her in Seoul
and install it yourself.
I'm sure she can do it herself
since she's so great.
I'm the only fool for making a fuss.
They are only children
when they're in your arms.
She's the one growing up, not me.
My heart is still the same.
Is this about that dream?
What is this dream you keep having?
Why won't you say anything?
Is the dream that bad these days?
It's not a bad dream.
It's nothing much.
Mom!
Mom.
I told you I'd give you candy
after you finish your sujebi, didn't I?
Why don't you ever listen to Mommy?
Mommy, give me a hug.
Ms. Oh! Geum-myeong was in an accident!
Is she bleeding?
I told you I'd give you candy
after you finish your sujebi, didn't I?
Why don't you ever listen to Mommy?
Another bad dream?
Oh dear.
What dreams have you been having lately?
…I'd give you candy
after you finish your sujebi.
Ms. Oh! Geum-myeong was in an accident!
Is she bleeding?
Baby.
Mommy…
is going to get your sister
and come right back.
Okay?
I'll go get her.
When I get back,
I'll give you candy every day.
Okay?
Mom, by mere coincidence,
has lost immeasurable things.
That's why she fussed even more,
believing that restless worry
could prevent even coincidences.
Geum-myeong.
Baby.
Baby!
Oh no. Good heavens.
My baby. Oh my God.
Help!
Baby.
What's wrong with him?
The doctor.
We need to call the doctor.
An ambulance.
An ambulance. Call an…
Gwan-sik, call an ambulance.
Why won't anyone call the ambulance?
Geum-myeong.
Help!
Help! Ambulance!
Someone, call an ambulance!
Ambulance!
Baby!
Look, you can't just be walking
through there like this…
What?
She's inhaled coal gas!
What? Oh no!
San-108, Bongcheon 5-dong.
108!
108! Yes!
No, there are stairs here!
You can't drive up here.
Yes.
It was a time
when genuine kindness froze over…
Oh no.
Baby, Mom's here.
Mom's right here.
…the year Korea's three major
unsolved cases occurred,
Mom called me every night
after the nine o'clock news.
Here, we're over here!
Her relentless worry was tiresome.
Sir! Please help us!
But… it was the same relentless worry
that saved me again.
Why is it so quiet?
Baby.
Oh no, baby!
Baby. Oh dear.
Are you okay? My goodness.
Just like that,
she's saved me time and again.
Oh no!
Oh no. Honey!
-Are you okay?
-You better be a good daughter.
What great person are you trying to be,
causing trouble so well?
Will it leave a scar?
You're worried about her scar?
She's lucky it wasn't worse.
No one would believe it if you said
you caught a kid jumping off the roof.
Mom, Dad.
Oh dear.
Why was she on the roof this time?
She kept insisting she was a magpie.
My little baby got stitches.
I can't even imagine how much it hurts.
It was only much later,
when I could no longer answer her calls,
that I deeply missed her relentless worry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, baby. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Her delicate heart sank countless times.
I wish I'd shown her
a bit more appreciation.
Regret arrived too late once again.
"JUST GET READY AND GO,
RIDE THE MOMENT WITH ALL YOU HAVE."
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang