I know who killed Divine.
We'll drag you
down with us
because you
were a part of it.
Divine killed herself.
End of story.
The police arrested her.
Liv killed Edward.
This is such a huge
relief for our family.
I'm begging
each one of you.
We can't have any more
scandals in our family.
We were given orders
to let her go alive.
What if she reports us
to the authorities?
She'll attend to something
else instead of doing that.
I know Bingo paid
for all of this.
Miss Cathy paid him
a huge amount
to help train Ling.
You used me for money?
Ling, I'm sorry
I didn't tell you.
It's okay.
- I'll walk you to your car.
- It's okay, Bingo.
That is understandable
because Bingo
needs the money.
Can't the reason
I'm hurt be because...
I thought he
was different?
I thought he really
cared about me.
But now, I don't
know, Jersey.
You can't just tell her
things like that.
You got paid
for doing a job.
There's no problem with that,
unless you love Ling
and you feel
bad about it.
I like her, okay?
I don't want her to think
I'm using her for money.
Then the problem here is
your feelings, not my big mouth.
Damn it!
She's mad at me.
I'm sorry
I made you wait.
It's nice to meet
you, Caroline.
["YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE"
BY MOIRA DELA TORRE PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Bingo.
Are you and Ling fighting?
No, we're not fighting.
Hmm...
I know you.
And I also know Ling.
Tell me, what is going on?
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
I've been trying
to call Ling,
but she's not answering
my calls.
Bingo...
I don't want to
assume anything,
but I can feel that...
you've done something
to hurt Ling.
Fix it.
Don't let it go
on for too long.
Got it?
That's exactly
my plan, Grandma.
Okay, very good.
Hmm?
- I love you.
- Love you.
[SMOOCHES]
Fix it.
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
- [LINE RINGING]
- [SIGHS]
Please, Ling,
answer the phone.
[RINGING CONTINUES]
Here.
Um, what am I going to do
with those?
Of course, you'll eat it.
This is food.
This vegetable stew is healthy.
And the chicken stew
is good for your...
Your...
What the hell?
You're giving me chicken stew
so you can score with me?
- Of course not!
- [QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
My mother said moringa leaves
boost breast milk supply.
I am not... pregnant.
I'm not pregnant.
It's not in my plan
to get pregnant, okay?
You had an abortion?
That's against the law!
You could go to prison.
- Plus, I'm against it.
- Snoop.
S-Stop! Stop it, stop it!
Don't be overdramatic, okay?
I don't want to talk
about it. Period.
Wait--
You forgot your stew!
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
Jersey.
[LINE RINGING]
What?
Jersey?
Are you with Ling?
And you think I'll answer
your question?
Come on, Jersey.
It's important.
Call her.
She's not answering.
So that means...
she doesn't want
to talk to you, okay?
[SIGHS] Jersey.
You see, Bingo,
I was rooting
for you, okay?
How could you do
that to Ling?!
Of all people,
you dare hurt Ling!
Just because my best
friend is from a rich family
doesn't mean you could treat her
as some kind of investment!
I so want to strangle
you right now, Bingo!
As in you've no idea!
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello? Jersey?
Jersey, are you
still there?
Jersey...
I want to talk to Ling.
So please tell me
where she is.
No.
I won't tell you.
Jersey, please.
Come on.
Until now,
I use the car
that Papa gave to me.
So for my birthday,
I've decided
to get my own.
And that's why you've
taken an interest in our car.
But, it's not for
sale, my dear.
I'm not here to make
an offer, Miss Annie.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you want me to call
my dealer for you?
I'm sure he knows more
about the car.
I'm actually here
to get your opinion
as an owner.
Of course, if I ask
the car dealers,
they'll mention all the
good qualities about the car.
It's still different...
...hearing the owner's
experience.
Because they won't
hide anything.
They'll tell you everything.
The whole...
...truth.
Of course.
You'll know the whole truth...
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
...about the car.
By the way,
how did you know
that I own one?
There are only few cars
like that in the Philippines.
- And for...
- [CUTLERY CLINKS]
people like us,
it's not that hard to track.
Right?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
You're right.
People like us.
Okay, about the car...
I like it because
of the smooth ride.
It's a head-turner.
Others even ask for a picture
as if it's a celebrity.
Mmm. [CHUCKLES]
Actually,
that's why it caught
my attention too.
I saw that type of car at...
...the Evergreen Haven Park.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Have you ever been there,
Miss Annie?
No.
Since I came back
to the Philippines,
I've been to many places
here in Manila.
I don't think so.
Well, it's actually near
my sister's ex-fiancé's place.
You might know him.
Edward...
Liao.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
It's done.
I took care of everything
you asked me to do
to carry out the hacking.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
That settles our
family's debt to you.
[ANNIE] Edward...
...Liao, did you say?
No, I don't think
I... I know him.
Anyway, about the Royce,
I'm surprised that a Tiu
doesn't own one.
You know my family?
I know that...
GLC is owned by the Tius.
Yeah.
You want some tea?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Tea?
Truth?
About my family?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Tea, as in a drink.
Would you like some?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
All I know is that
Wilson Tiu is the CEO.
And he has lots of kids.
Who's your mom, by the way?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Her name is Divine.
Oh.
[MOUTH CLICKS]
Divine... [SIGHS]
May she rest in peace.
[EXHALES SOFTLY]
You know her?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[JERSEY]She told me she has
a meeting at Waheet Palace.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes.
I've worked with her.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ling looks sad.
She's acting on her own again.
[HOSTESS] Um, sir...
We have a dress code here.
What?
Oh...
Right.
I understand, I'm sorry.
What else do you know
about her, Miss Annie?
[CAROLINE SIGHS]
Where did you work together?
That was a very long time ago.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOUTH CLICKS, SIGHS DEEPLY]
I remember she had a building
that was being constructed
for her food business.
Did you talk to her?
Before she--
[PHONE RINGING]
- I'm sorry.
- [PHONE RINGING]
I have to take this call.
[RINGING CONTINUES]
Hello?
[SHERWIN]  She's free
now, Miss Annie.
[ANNIE] Okay.
I'm sorry, Caroline,
but I have to go.
I have to attend
to some matters.
But if you need something
or anything else,
just call my assistant,
Nanny Lyn.
Miss Annie.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
And...
Please say hi to Gina
and Cindy for me.
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
[MUSIC STOPS]
No, she's bluffing.
She doesn't know anything
about Divine's death.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[GASPS SOFTLY]
- Ma'am.
- [SIGHS]
- Can you get me another glass?
- Yes, ma'am.
Hurry up!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
No.
I can't go to jail.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Here you go, ma'am.
- [LINE RINGING]
- Go, go!
[RINGING CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
This is all your fault.
I hate you for
introducing me to her.
No, Gina. You don't
get to blame me for this.
Did you know that I have trouble
sleeping last night?
She's like a ghost from the past
that continues to haunt us.
You know what?
Instead of blaming me
for Annie's return,
why not think of how we can
shut that mouth of hers!
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
- We need to get ahead of Annie.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
Ling, I have nothing else
to say but sorry.
I-I was wrong
for not telling you.
But I want you to know
that everything I showed you...
can't be bought with money.
All of it is true.
[CAR HONKS]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[CAR ENGINE RUMBLING,
HANDBRAKE RATCHETS]
Ling.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Everything I showed you
is real, Ling.
Okay?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [THUD]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
[HANDBRAKE RATCHETS]
- [GROANS]
- [CAR DOOR OPENS]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[ANNIE'S DRIVER] Hey.
Are you stupid?
You're blocking the way.
Hey, drop the act already.
It won't work this time.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let's go.
Sure, ma'am.
At least I'm right.
She knows something about Mama.
I need to get to know her more.
[PHONE CHIMES]
[PATO] Caroline,
this is Pato.
Someone kidnapped me,
but they let me go.
We need to meet up.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
[PATO] Caroline.
Caroline.
Can you hear me?
It's me, Pato.
Pato, where are you?
Let's meet.
Are you okay?
Please, g-get my bag.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh.
Here.
Here's some cash.
Ma'am, don't!
He might be a thief.
It's okay.
Go to the hospital,
get yourself checked.
I'm so sorry.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Here.
Are you okay?
Just get yourself checked--
Did you hit your head?
- I've got it, ma'am.
- Get up.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm sorry.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Papa said you're leaving us
for money.
Why'd you have a kid if you
won't take responsibility?!
- Bingo! What happened?!
- What happened?!
Bingo got into a fight.
Irresponsible parents
shouldn't have children.
What happened to you?
I've been looking for you.
Before they kill me,
I need to tell you
the whole truth, Caroline.
I'm giving you
this one last chance
to tell me the truth
about my mother.
- I'm so sick and tired of you--
- No!
You're not going to
walk away from this.
Never again!
Caroline, move on!
I will not move on!
Because I know the truth.