Mister Ibe's target
is not the GLC.
He wants revenge on the Tius.
It means Ling's life
is in danger.
Especially now that her wedding
is fast approaching.
Ling is getting married?
Why is she marrying another man?
Isn't this partnership
for the Mabenta Box?
Then we need
a picture together.
Haven't we talked about this?
I am already married.
I can't see you anymore.
I can meet with anyone I want
with just one press on my phone.
I heard her talking
on the phone.
I'll find out
who she was talking to.
We can't trust anyone right now.
Boy, your plan's working.
He got spooked and bolted.
- [GLASS BREAKS]
- Whoa! What...
- What was that?
- Stay put. Don't go outside.
- Be careful.
- Hey!
You're my mom's killer?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BREATHES DEEPLY]
Hey!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOG BARKS]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[GROANS]
Who are you?
Who sent you here?
[GRUNTING]
[BINGO]
You'll pay for what you did.
Your day is coming.
I didn't see anything suspicious
in your Aunt Cindy's phone.
Even in the call logs?
But I swear I heard her.
I checked everything, emails,
messages, but I found nothing.
Don't worry,
I'll keep an eye on her,
while the investigators
handle Gilbert.
Oh my god.
Could it be him?
Bingo?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAROLINE] It could be him that
Auntie Cindy was talking to.
You told me he paid off
Toni Alumahan
to incriminate Miss Annie,
and now, I'm not even sure
if he's telling the truth
about being with Auntie Cindy
the night Mom died.
Pa, I need to do something
about this.
I need to know the truth.
I have people working on that.
I won't stop, either.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't know, Pa.
Maybe it's just wedding jitters,
but I need to get this
out of my system.
I can't just sit around
and do nothing.
This is not only for Mama.
This is also for Miss Annie.
For Bingo.
Caroline, you'll be placing
your life in danger.
Pa...
Do you really need
the Tanhuecos?
It's still your decision,
Caroline.
[SNIFFLES, SIGHS]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
[RINGING STOPS]
[LEAVES CRUNCHING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
- [LINE RINGING]
- Ling, please pick up.
[PHONE VIBRATING]
- Caroline.
- [VIBRATING STOPS]
Stephen.
What are you doing here?
I know it's not good to see
each other before the wedding,
but I just can't help it.
You're just checking
if I haven't escaped yet.
[SULLEN MUSIC PLAYING]
Caroline, I trust your word.
And I know you'll be honest
with me if that's your plan.
So...
are you going to escape?
I will see you tomorrow,
Stephen.
[SIGHS]
[VIBRATING]
- [LINE RINGING]
- Come on, pick up.
Caroline...
thank you for trying your best.
[SIGHS]
I have so much love for you,
and I'm going to do everything
to make you happy as my wife.
[SULLEN MUSIC CONTINUES]
[VIBRATING]
[LINE RINGING]
[CRASHES]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
If you're going to hinder
our plans,
- [GUN COCKS]
- you might as well die now.
You got goons, you bastard?
[GROANS]
[GUNSHOTS CONTINUE]
[GROANING]
[GROANS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE ROARING]
[FOOTSTEPS FADING]
[GASPS]
[RINGING]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
[RINGING CONTINUES]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE TURNS OFF]
[LINE RINGING]
Pick up!
[RINGING CONTINUES]
[GASPS] Wilson?
What's happening, Cindy?
What are you doing here?
Wilson.
[LINE RINGING]
I knew it. You're still up.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
I'm glad you're here, Jersey.
Of course.
[SIGHS]
I'm sleeping over, okay?
The wedding is too early,
and I can't be late.
Let's go.
- Jersey.
- Yeah?
Bingo was calling earlier.
I couldn't answer it
because I was with Stephen.
And now, I've been calling him,
but he's not answering.
Caroline...
your wedding is tomorrow.
And if you're having
second thoughts,
you have the whole night
to decide.
I just want to talk to Bingo
to have a proper closure
with him.
- That's it.
- [SIGHS]
Jersey, he's been so nice to me.
He at least deserves
an explanation
as to why I decided
to marry Stephen, right?
Okay, I understand.
If that's your way
of moving on, fine.
Hopefully, you'll get
to talk to him.
But please,
think about it carefully.
Come here.
Caroline.
It's not impossible
to fall in love
with someone like Stephen.
But at the same time,
it's possible
that your love for Bingo...
That love?
It's never going to fade.
Like they say,
love is a choice
that you make everyday.
So whoever it is you'll choose,
choose him
over and over again.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Okay.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
I already admitted it, right?
That I ordered Gilbert
to ruin Divine.
Because I was so afraid
you're going to leave us.
But, Wilson,
there's no other reason.
You have to believe me.
Then I tried
to cut ties with him.
But he's blackmailing me.
Money is no longer enough
for him.
If I don't agree to see him,
he'll ruin everything.
Wilson, I understand
if this is unforgivable to you.
But I swear to you,
I swear to you, Wilson,
may lightning strike me down
if I'm lying,
I did not kill Divine.
I did not kill her.
I...
You have to believe me.
If that's the case,
we're going
to face him together.
But he's dangerous.
Gilbert is a dangerous man.
And we need to leave now.
Let's go. We have to go.
Call him!
We'll settle this right now.
[PHONE RINGING]
Jimmy?
[BREATHING NERVOUSLY]
[BETTINA]
Papa, what's happening?
Why the additional security
at this time of night?
After I received your call,
I can't help it.
I need to be here.
And wherever
my son goes, I'll go.
So now, Wilson,
tell us everything.
Because we have
to be extra-careful.
Starting tonight,
no one can leave the house
without my permission.
Why?
Because someone
is after us.
It's Gilbert Bautista,
the main suspect in the murders
of Annie and Divine.
Whoa. We found the killer?
He's alive?
[CAROLINE] Pa.
So we were right all along?
It's really Mister Ibe?
I've had him investigated,
and the police reported to me
just a few minutes ago
that he's now targeting Bingo.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
What?
Is he okay? What happened
to him? What did Mister Ibe do?
What about Grandma and Papi?
[WILSON]
It's been taken care of.
His family is safe.
But Gilbert got away.
They're looking for him now.
I will use all of my
connections
to help in the search.
[CHARLESTON] This is serious.
We need to be careful.
But why is he after us, Papa?
According to the police,
Gilbert's motive
is to seek revenge on the people
who destroyed his life.
First, it was Divine.
Then Annie, who was his
accomplice in a scheme.
It's also possible that he might
target me or you father next.
Or he could hurt you
to get revenge on us.
So please, everyone, Caroline...
I told you
he is a dangerous man,
so please listen to me
this time.
I want to keep you safe.
I've talked to the Tanhuecos.
Tomorrow, we'll be
on heightened alert.
And I'll make sure
that none of you gets hurt.
And I promise you,
I will not stop
until Gilbert is arrested.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
- [LINE RINGING]
Hello?
Hey, relax.
Don't get mad.
Listen to me first.
[SIGHS, CLICKS TONGUE]
It's not over yet.
We can still carry out
your plans.
We will succeed.
["IYO" BY DARREN ESPANTO
PLAYING]
[GINA] Let's go.
[CINDY] Girls, come on,
let's do this.
Let's go.
We're going to be late.
- Where's your sister? Irene!
- Good morning, good morning.
What's taking you so long?
Hello, you looked
very stressed.
I know.
Stressful day. Let's go.
Let's have our pictures taken.
- Boys over there.
- [IRENE] Morning.
[CINDY] Where's the
photographer? Come on.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Photographer, hello?
Come on.
Let's have our pictures taken.
Okay.
- Okay.
- [CAMERA CLICKS]
- So... It's done?
- We're done?
- Our turn.
Sir, you can take
a picture of these now, okay?
- Make it good. I trust you. Go.
- [CLAPS]
[CAMERA CLICKS]
[JERSEY]
Okay, let me check first.
Let's take hers next.
Wait a second. I'll check.
You're so beautiful.
["IYO" BY DARREN ESPANTO
CONTINUES]
She's here.
Let's do the photo shoot.
Come on.
Let's go. For the family photos.
- Let's do this.
- Let me fix your gown.
Photographers,
we'll take it here, okay?
Where are they?
Let's do this. Come on.
Hurry, guys.
Can you take the photos, please?
Let's go.
Are you ready?
[CAMERA CLICKING]
- Is it done?
- [JERSEY] Yeah.
- Yeah, that's enough.
- Yeah, let's go.
Ling must be
so beautiful right now.
["IYO" BY DARREN ESPANTO
CONTINUES]
Wearing a gorgeous dress.
A gown that's beautiful
from top to bottom.
With embroidery
fit for a bride like her.
[SNIFFLES]
Maybe she's at the altar
right now.
But not with Bingo.
[SIGHS]
Nene, unfortunately,
there are people
who are destined to meet
but are not destined
to be together.
You know what? That's not really
what I wanted to say.
Forget that. Let me try again.
Bingo and Ling...
they've lost their chance.
But the two of us?
There's still a chance.
What did you say?
There's still a chance
for the two of us, right?
Of course, there is.
Did I ease your sadness somehow?
Yes.
But...
I'm still sad because...
...Bingo and Lingling...
...it's over for them.
[SNIFFLES, SOBS]
["IYO" BY DARREN ESPANTO
CONTINUES]
[INAUDIBLE]
Careful.
[CHUCKLES]
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Yes, sir.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[BODYGUARD] Yes.
She's in the car.
We'll be right behind them.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'll make sure Bingo won't
cause trouble at the wedding.
This wedding will save
our legacy.
So why does it feel wrong?
A person's worst enemy
is always their conscience.
Caroline isn't here yet.
She's not picking up.
Miss Caroline
has been kidnapped.
- What?
- You didn't go after her?
- Oh my god!
- She's really not picking up.
Sir, I think we're going
the wrong way.
Stephen, you are not
going anywhere.
Stop the limo!
Hey, we're going the wrong way!
What do you want from me?!