I just came to ask you
where I can find
Engr. Gilbert Bautista.
I need to talk to him.
Son...
This is all I ask of you!
All my life I've worked hard
to support myself!
You won't say anything?
La Sinfonia.
You'll find
Gilbert Bautista there.
- I can take care of those.
- I'm just preparing them
because you will become COO.
If I'm being honest, I don't
know if this is a good idea.
What if this nomination
just makes everything worse?
He's been using you
all this time!
Ma!
Can you please shut up?!
I get it, alright?!
Charleston is cunning!
You're meeting up with me
in an empty street
just to tell me Auntie Cathy
is transferring you to Bulacan?
I still need you
to buy me alcohol.
Why don't you find
a new supplier there?
You don't want
five thousand a week?
Five thousand a week
just to see you?
Okay, fine. Deal.
Okay.
Oh, Bingo!
I didn't notice you come in.
Don't stare too much,
or you will be entranced
by her beauty.
Here's a counterspell.
Grandma, what are you doing?
I'm good.
I bet you are. [CHUCKLES]
I found a town near the farm.
La Sinfonia.
They have products that
we can use for Mabenta Box.
- That's good.
- Mm-hmm.
Should we go there?
Sure. When do we leave?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[NENE] What?
You're going on a honeymoon?
Your Papi should
know about this.
You have to tell him
these plans of yours.
Grandma.
We haven't even tied the knot.
Bingo!
I'm just messing with Grandma.
The other day,
she was saying we eloped.
Now she's talking
about honeymoon.
She'll start asking
about our wedding plans soon.
You really enjoy
teasing me, huh?
You're the one who said
that you two are going
to a far away place.
Isn't that what people do
on honeymoons?
Grandma, it's purely
for business.
You're going to the farm
that produces that jam?
We're going to drop by there.
But we'll stay in La Sinfonia.
Aside from fresh air
and nice views,
there are also products there
that we can check out
for our business.
Right, Ling?
[NENE] Alright.
Go ahead and have fun, my dears.
Don't hesitate to mix
pleasure and business.
- Grandma!
What?
[NENE LAUGHS]
Let's just eat.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
I really want
to get this over with.
Have you convinced Bettina
to sell her shares?
Not yet.
We'll have to wait until
she loses the COO position.
You should've been there.
I was her only ally
in that meeting.
After she loses the election,
she will be so pissed.
She will hate her own family.
And then...
she will turn to me.
Just make sure you'll get
Bettina's shares
once she gives up on GLC.
I can't wait to witness
that family's downfall.
They're the reason
my relationship with my son
fell apart.
They deserve to suffer
the same fate.
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'll go home first.
What for?
We're heading out tomorrow,
remember?
Just stay here.
Bingo, I need to pack
for this trip.
And I still have to arrange
the van that we'll be using.
There's no need for that.
You don't want me to go home?
Yeah.
You already have me.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
What I mean is...
I'll prepare everything we need.
I got you.
You got me?
Yeah.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Whatever you need...
I'll get them ready.
You need clothes?
I'll get you some
from our inventory.
Shoes?
We've got them, too.
What else do you need?
Shampoo?
Well, I might have
to buy some for you.
Bingo, are you sure?
Ling, don't worry about a thing.
You know what they say.
"Traveling unprepared allows for
the most unexpected adventures."
Just trust me on this.
But, Bingo--
Ling.
I got you.
Okay.
I trust you.
Alright! I'll take you
on a wild ride.
Okay. Strap me in.
Huh?
W-What straps?
That sounds a bit inappropriate.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
What do you mean?
I said, strap me in.
Please don't say that.
Just say, uh...
"Yes."
Just say, "Yes."
"Yes, Bingo.
I'll leave it all to you."
Yes, Bingo.
I'll leave it all to you.
There we go!
["YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING]
- Whoo!
- [EXHALES LOUDLY]
[IRENE] What?
This place doesn't even
have an AC!
What is this life?!
[HUFFS]
This is so much worse!
[MAN] Irene Tiu.
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[IRENE] Yes?
You know me?
Of course.
[IRENE]
Well, who wouldn't know me?
I know you!
Aldrich Co.
Student council member,
Debate Club president,
captain of the football team,
and valedictorian of your batch.
- So, you know me.
- Yeah, of course.
Hello? Who wouldn't know you?
Aren't I three years
ahead of you?
So?
Look at you now, though.
- What do you mean?
- You've changed so much.
L-Like what? You think
I'm not gorgeous before?
No, no.
I mean...
You're even more gorgeous now.
I know, right.
So, Aldrich...
You're the guy Auntie Cathy
assigned to train me.
Yep.
Well? Are you ready?
- Hell yeah!
- Alright, let's go.
Follow me.
Okay.
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Where's Caroline?
She didn't come home.
Do you want me
to ask Ma'am Cindy?
No need. I've got it.
Thank you.
Okay.
- [HUFFS]
- [LINE RINGING]
Come on. Pick up!
[RINGING CONTINUES]
[PHONE BUZZING]
Stephen.
Finally!
I'm at your house.
Where are you?
You weren't answering my calls.
I'm going out of town
with Bingo.
What?
Just the two of you?
Yeah.
Why are you going out of town
with him?
It's a business trip, Stephen.
Well then, let me come.
Not this time, Stephen.
I need to do this for myself.
At least let me know
where you're going.
Up north.
Okay. Where exactly?
La Morado for the jams.
And then La Sinfonia
for more business ideas.
Anyway, I have to go.
I'm still packing. Bye.
- [LINE BUSY]
- C-Caroline.
Caroline!
Bingo!
[HUFFS]
Who called?
Stephen.
[MUMBLING] Oh, the nuisance.
What?
That was the guy
who serenaded you, right?
He's good.
Hey, don't worry about me.
Auntie Cathy trained me well
back at the resto.
It's the same system here,
right?
Whatever the customer wants,
I'll give it to them.
They order pork buns ,
I'll serve them that.
If they want nails,
I'll give them nails.
"What sizes do you have?"
"How much for a kilo?"
"Is it for wood or cement?"
What?
You'll be getting
those questions quite a lot.
So, you need to know
the materials we have
in case the customers ask.
Wait. You want me to memorize
the different sizes of nails?
Uh-huh. As well as the sizes
of plywood and steel wires.
What? Was I hired to be
a construction worker?
[CHUCKLES] No.
We won't ask you
to build a house.
Effective leadership,
customer focus,
adaptability,
and problem solving.
That's what you need to develop
as per Auntie Cathy.
I think you'll learn in no time
once you get the hang
of working here.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
What's with the sigh?
You want out?
No. I'm not backing out.
Who says I'm backing out?
I'll memorize the sizes of
all hammers here if need be.
I'll learn all the skills
that could be useful
once I become CEO of GLC.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh my god.
You find it funny that I want
to take over our company.
No, it's not that.
- I'm just amused--
- Whatever.
It's just my first day.
- I'm trying to familiarize yo--
- Shh! Okay!
That's too much for today.
I need to recover.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE BEEPS]
[CATHY] How's it going there
at the hardware?
Poop?
Poop!
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Here. Look.
I got the 19 percent from
the stakeholders for you.
Thank you, Sherwin.
- It means a lot.
- Of course.
But these are just
predictions.
It doesn't include the
votes from other stakeholders,
but the way I see it,
that's the percentage of votes
you and your siblings will get.
No matter what I do,
I still won't win.
Because Papa will vote
for Charleston.
Then talk to your father
about it.
Do everything you can to get
the remaining 20 percent.
The election hasn't
started yet.
But Papa nominated Charleston.
Bettina, you still have
a chance.
Up until the last minute,
you should make sure
that Charleston won't get
the COO position.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Charleston will be
our next COO.
That's for sure.
I had a hard time
convincing others,
but at least I was able
to get him another 9 percent.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CATHY] Give the COO
position to Caroline.
Even though
she's the youngest,
she will lead your company
with that heart of hers.
Wilson?
Yes?
Well, as I was saying,
the election tomorrow
will just be a formality.
Our eldest son
will have that position.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm sorry, Ling.
The bus has no AC.
It's okay, Bingo.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- I'm really sorry.
- I'm alright.
This is what traveling is like.
[PHONE BUZZING]
It's fun, right?
[THEA] Miss Caroline, I just
want to remind you
that the COO election
is tomorrow.
Who was that?
It's Papa's executive
assistant.
She texted to remind me
about the COO election.
I know it's impossible
for Papa to notice me
and consider me
as COO of GLC.
But I want to prove to them
that I can stand on my own.
We can do this.
Right?
Yes, we can do this.
You got this.
The business grant from
Jonathan will help us a lot.
We need funds
for our business, Bingo.
I don't want to ask
for Papa's help.
We got this.
["YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING]
Oh my.
You're tired, aren't you?
You need some rest.
You should take a nap.
Here.
Rest your head right here.
You'll act as my pillow?
Yes.
I'll be your pillow.
Pillow... activate!
[CHUCKLES]
Thank you.
This ride is going
to take several hours.
["YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE"
INSTRUMENTAL CONTINUES]
[SONG FADES]
[SNOOP] Sorry, come again?
Did I hear it right?
It's not just a business trip?
Yeah, but I'll tell Ling
some other time.
I have to get to know
the guy first.
Oh, boy.
Last time, you were
acting like a CSI.
Now, you're looking for
a missing person.
What's his name again?
Gilbert what?
- It's Gilbert Bautista.
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
This is for Ling.
She needs some answers.
Especially about her mother.
Oh, I see!
That's good, then.
You really are the man.
I'll root for you, okay?
You just gave me
a year's worth of butterflies.
[SNOOP LAUGHS]
Bingo!
Anyway, I have to go.
Love you. Bye.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Is that everything?
That's a lot.
- This one's really good.
- [SIGHS]
Purple yam jam.
[EXHALES HEAVILY, SIGHS LOUDLY]
It's a good thing
they're easy to talk to.
We even got a lot of freebies.
Yeah, we can share this
with the others in Manila.
The owner offered us
a big discount
if we buy their products
directly from them
for our bestseller box.
You're very good
at negotiating, Bingo.
You know, I was thinking,
in the future,
we should make something else
other than a curated box.
You know,
we have to innovate.
What else can we include
in our bestseller box
that will make us
interesting and unique?
If only the people in GLC
can hear you right now,
I'm sure they'll also
be impressed like me.
["AUTUMN" BY BEN &amp; BEN
AND BELLE MARIANO PLAYING]
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Oh, wait. Someone's calling.
Miss Girlie, hello.
Yes, we're on our way.
Okay. Please inform
Mister Ibe.
Okay, bye.
- They're in La Sinfonia.
- Alright.
Let's go.
- You need help?
- No, I can manage.
Here, let's ask her.
Miss.
Hello.
Is Miss Girlie here?
- [VENDOR] Are you Bingo?
- Yes.
Miss Girlie is already
waiting down there.
They're waiting for us.
Thank you.
You can leave
your things here.
- [BINGO] Here?
- Yes.
Thank you.
- Down there, right?
- [CAROLINE] Thank you.
- Yes, down there.
- Okay, thank you!
Let's go.
["AUTUMN" CONTINUES]
Wow.
Bingo, this place
is beautiful.
[BINGO] Right?
[CAROLINE]
Is this place even real?
Wow.
Bingo, you know, I've been to
so many places around the world.
But this one...
- It's like I'm in a painting.
- [BINGO CHUCKLES]
[BINGO] We're not
in a painting.
We're in La Sinfonia!
["AUTUMN" CONTINUES]
- It's so beautiful.
- Why go abroad
when you've got a view
like this in the Philippines?
Let's take a photo.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Here. Okay.
- Want me to take it?
- Yes.
There.
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
- Okay, your turn.
- A solo picture?
- Yeah.
- Seriously?
- I'll send it to you.
Yeah.
- Mm.
- No, don't do that.
Pose like this.
Look here.
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
- Okay, my turn.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Smile!
Raise your arms!
- La Sinfonia!
Woohoo!
[CAROLINE] Wow.
Let's take another selfie.
Selfie!
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
- Include the view.
- [MUSIC FADES]
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Papa, I'm begging you.
This position will
make me whole again.
Let's vote for the next
Chief Operating Officer of GLC.
Welcome, welcome to
our humble garden.
- Thank you.
- Wow.
These cabbages
look like roses!
It's so fragrant,
Miss Girlie.
Lavender.
We can do so many things
with this fragrance.
Living here must be nice.
You can start a family
and lead a simple life.
Thank you for
bringing me here.
It means a lot to me.
I needed this.
I needed this too.