Am I in heaven?
- Grandma, Grandma!
- Ma, Ma!
- Grandma, can you see us?
- We're over here.
Bingo.
- Ma! [LAUGHING]
- Grandma!
You can see me?
I can see you, Ling.
I'm glad you're okay.
I'm okay. Yes.
There's a big possibility that
she's involved in the hacking.
And then kidnapping
Caroline and Irene.
That's her, too.
I was there when Ling
was kidnapped
at the yacht.
What?!
But I wasn't the kidnapper.
I swear on my life,
I didn't know there
was a kidnapping.
The Tius are not easy opponents.
But I am here now,
and I will do everything
in my power
to get her out of jail.
Now that the nightmare
is finally over,
can we start over as a family?
Of course.
That's everything.
They're now yours, Andrei.
This house deed,
plots of land,
and even all the businesses
of GLC.
All of them are
now yours, Andrei.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
We're here.
Be careful, Ma.
There you go.
Good morning.
It's so nice here.
Wow!
Let's go up.
There's even a fountain.
Andrei.
Grandma Nene, Sir Papi.
Oh my.
- Please come in.
- This is Nanny Lyn.
- She's like a mother to Mama.
- Hi, how are you?
I'm good.
Oh, come on in.
Wait a minute.
I'll make you some snacks
then I'll have them bring
your things to your room.
- Oh, we can manage.
- Wait a second.
Bring their luggage
to their rooms.
We'll just do it ourselves.
They're not heavy.
Oh, let us do it.
We're happy to serve you.
Yeah.
Alright.
Wait, I'll just prepare
some snacks.
- Thank you.
- I'll be back, Andrei.
Mama wanted you
to feel at home.
Don't worry, someday
Annie will be with us too.
She's always in our prayers.
- Come on, let's have a tour.
- Okay, let's go.
- I'll show you around.
- This house is big, right?
- [NENE] Oh my.
- This is Mama's piano.
[NENE] Wow, a piano.
I still can't believe
she hugged me.
Finally.
You know what?
I feel like crying, too.
Well, at least
it's finally over.
Your mom's true killer
is now in prison.
Stephen, she may be in jail,
but she's still denying it.
[STEPHEN SIGHS]
Maybe let's not talk about it.
Yeah.
Let's not talk about it for now.
The case? Yeah, I'm sorry.
But the question is,
how are you and Bingo?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
We're okay.
I think.
[LINE RINGING]
- Sir, let me.
- I'll do it.
- No, sir, let me.
- It's okay, Cris.
No, sir, it's my job.
[BINGO] I'll do it next time.
It's no big deal.
- [CRIS] Okay, sir.
- Oops, stay put.
I can do this alone.
Now, don't laugh at me.
I'm just not used to this.
I'm not laughing at you.
I'm actually glad
to see you like this.
It has always been your dream.
And now... wow.
Look at you.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
I wanted to fulfill that dream
through my own hard work.
Not like this.
[SIGHS]
Ling, I hope you're okay
with all of this.
Of course.
I am.
I'm not used to it.
But they're forcing it on me.
They want this.
Really, Bingo, it's okay.
Well, then, shall we eat?
I'm starving.
My treat.
Okay.
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
We have lots to talk about.
And I have something
to tell you.
By the way, the Mabenta Box...
Looks like I can finance it now.
I have the funds for everything.
Yes, you really can finance
your own business now.
Our business.
- Come on. You can ride with me.
- Let's go.
I'm going to show you
the Kuliglig 2.0.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
- Let's go.
- You start it up like this.
Oh, really?
Shall we, sir?
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BINGO CHUCKLES]
Take a load of this view.
- Watch your step.
- Thank you.
Wow, it's so beautiful.
[CAROLINE CHUCKLES]
[BINGO] Now, I can say this.
- Order anything you want.
- Mmm...
- Not just coffee.
- [GIGGLES]
Alright.
You know...
this reminds me of La Sinfonia.
Where you can vent out
your problems at the sky.
[SIGHS]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Mm. So, what is it
you want to tell me?
Ah.
I'll tell you later.
Let's grab a bite first.
- Come on.
- Okay. Chow time?
You're learning. [GIGGLES]
- You've got the munchies?
- I do.
- Then say it.
- I've got the munchies.
This way, please.
- Thank you.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SPOON CLATTERS]
Bingo, I think
we should leave.
Why? Don't you like it here?
- Let's go to another place.
- Why?
Let's just go.
- Charleston--
- You have the nerve...
flaunting our wealth!
That you only got through
your mom's scheming.
- Charleston.
- Watch your mouth, bro.
Not here. Please.
Why? It's the truth.
And you, stop being stubborn.
I told you to stay away
from that man.
- Let's go.
- No.
- Let's go!
- Bro, that's enough.
- Let's go.
- I'll see you at home.
- Caroline.
- I'm serious, Caroline!
I said I'll see you at home.
- Bingo, I'm so sorry.
- Ling, I'm not a scammer.
I've never swindled anyone
my entire life.
Don't listen to him.
I'm sorry, Ling.
I forgot they're still
your brothers.
Maybe they're still upset
about what happened to the GLC.
I'm just respecting
my mother's wishes.
Just like you guys do
with your parents.
Is it wrong?
Is it my fault, Ling?
You've done nothing wrong.
It's not your fault
that you're her son.
Let's go.
Are you hurt?
- I'm alright.
- Here?
Let me give you both
some privacy.
Thank you, Sherwin.
[IN ARABIC] Thank you.
[SIGHS] Ahmed.
I'm sorry for asking
your help with this.
No problem, Annie.
I want to help, okay?
But is Fatima okay with this?
She knows.
She just wants me
to call her "every day."
I'm happy to know
you two are getting married.
But first, I have to take you
out of here.
[SIGHS]
I'm so grateful that you're
still helping me even though...
we're no longer together.
We both dreamed of this day,
when you could be together
with your son.
[SULLEN MUSIC PLAYING]
And that dream
took me away from you.
It's okay, Annie.
The love we had was beautiful.
I learned a lot
about life from you.
All I want
is to see you and your son
spend some time together again.
Thank you.
How much longer
are we going to stay here?
All of our hard work
amounted to nothing.
Felix is just rotting in jail.
Don't worry, Boloy.
We'll get out of here.
But how?
Are we breaking out?
He promised me that
he'd get us out of here.
Who are you talking about?
Balong. You have a visitor.
[GATE LOCK CLANGING]
Told you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Aldrich.
Irene.
Is this for real?
You're seeing another woman
while we're still together?
Well, in that case,
we're breaking up.
Hey, I'm being serious here.
This is grounds for a break-up.
So we're done.
We're good. Bye.
Irene.
- What?
- Meet my sister.
- [QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
- Irene, finally.
Your sister?
She's not your number two
or number three?
She's not your other girl?
No.
I'll make it up to you, Ling.
I'll take you
to a fancy restaurant.
Bingo, this is good.
Fishball, duck egg, blood sauce.
Coconut jam boogers. [CHUCKLES]
This is perfectly fine.
About the other thing
I wanted to tell you...
You should hear it
from me first.
Sherwin is handing
the COO position of GLC to me.
He said he'd train me.
Of course.
Your mom
is the major shareholder.
This is so ridiculous!
I know it's bad news
for you and your family.
But it's different for them.
And it's different
for us, right?
["YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE"
BY RICO BLANCO PLAYING]
Even though our lives
have become more complicated...
my wish is still simple.
Because I know what I want.
And that's to be with you.
Not only in business...
but here as well.
Ling...
on my arduous road
to one million...
I made a wrong turn
because of you.
It got me to unexpected places.
But taking that wrong path...
felt so right because
you were with me.
You're the best surprise
that's ever happened to me.
I love you with all my heart,
Caroline Tiu.
Hey, say something.
Did I upset you?
I'm sorry. I just couldn't think
of any other way to say--
I love you, too.
["YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE"
BY RICO BLANCO CONTINUES]
[BALONG] Where are we going?
[OFFICER] Stop asking
and just do as you're told.
[BALONG] You?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
So then...
can we be a couple?
Will you be my girlfriend?
[SNIFFLES]
If you had asked me earlier...
my answer would've
been yes, Bingo.
Yes.
But?
But is this really
the right time for it?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
You're still dealing
with problems.
I am, too.
Both of us and our families.
I get it.
Point taken.
But, Ling...
whatever you want us to be...
I'm fine with it.
What matters
is we don't give up.
We're not going to let go.
We'll keep on fighting.
You're my business partner.
My friend.
The only person I could ask:
"How are we going
to do this life?"
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're my person...
...Bingo.
And yes.
We'll keep fighting for this.
["YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING]
And someday,
once this is all over...
once we've solved all
of our problems...
nothing's going
to stop us, then.
[SIGHS] Yes.
I promise.
One day...
...when everything's okay...
...we're going to be together.
I love you so much, Ling.
Remember that.
Don't ever forget it.
["YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE"
INSTRUMENTAL CONTINUES]
I'll get straight to the point.
I know you're just a goon.
What do you want me to do?
Become a witness.
We need someone
to bring a person down.
That depends.
What about my protection?
We'll give you everything
you need to start a new life.
You can live anywhere
far from here.
I've now been approached
by two of Wilson Tiu's children.
This must be a big job.
Who am I testifying against?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
The moment I announce
that you're the GLC's new owner,
your decision will be the
most important in the room.
They're looking for loopholes
in Ms. Annie's ownership of GLC.
My mom is still in jail
and they're filing another case?
We are not going to acknowledge
the new owner,
because I have plans
to get the GLC back.
The Tanhuecos.
What are they doing here?
We may get the chance
to regain back control of GLC.
They agreed to help,
but they'll only do it
if she agrees to marry Stephen.