You're breaking up with me
to be with Gilbert?
- [SCREAMS]
- I'm going to kill you!
I backed away
when I heard Wilson
threaten Divine's life.
But when I returned for her,
Divine is already dead.
That's why I promised myself
that I would become
more powerful than them.
And when that day arrives,
I can finally fight Wilson Tiu.
Bingo, why didn't you tell Ling
about what Annie said?
She was really troubled when
her brother became a suspect.
What more if it's her father?
Trust in what
your heart tells you.
Who would've thought
that Ms. Irene Tiu
would be the one selling
her shares to our people.
Fifty-one percent, Miss Annie.
You're now the GLC's
major shareholder.
Annie Al Juffali?
You know Annie?
She's the woman Sherwin's
been talking to.
Oh my god.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Miss Annie?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Caroline.
Nice to see you again.
Wait, you know her?
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Everyone,
meet Ms. Annie Al Juffali.
Also known
as Ms. Annie Mariano.
You're Annie Mariano?
Yes, I am.
Ah, whatever.
I think Ling deserves to know.
[SIGHS]
Who's this woman?
Because, dang, she's hot.
Who am I, she asks.
Sherwin, tell them.
Miss Annie holds the majority
of shares in GLC.
Her ownership
surpasses the combined total
of everyone else's.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHARLESTON]
My shares went to her?
- Charleston!
- Charleston.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Cindy.
Gina.
I won't make this long.
As Sherwin said...
I have majority of the shares.
Now, let's proceed
to the million-dollar question.
I'm sure every one of you
is itching to ask:
Why am I doing this?
Because I want to destroy
your lives
like how you destroyed mine.
I want to see
all of you in vain!
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- What the hell is this? Huh?
What's this? What's happening?!
Why don't you ask
your mother, Bettina?
I'm sure she and Atty. Gina
can tell you everything.
Right, girls?
Shut up, Annie!
Wow.
Fierce.
But is "shut up"
all you can mutter now?
That's not the woman
I knew back then.
Back when you and Cindy used
to threaten my life
if I failed to follow
your bidding.
Annie, I am sure we can talk
about this in private.
[ANNIE]
But why do it in private?
It's better to reveal
my big revelations
out here in front of everyone.
Revelations?
What revelations?
Which one do you want?
How about when Cindy and Gina
set Divine up to take the fall
in the Orchid Place's collapse?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
That's what
Engr. Gilbert told me, too.
[WILSON] Caroline.
I chose to stay quiet because
I know no one would believe me.
Well, now, you have someone,
because I'm here.
I'm the one Gina
and Cindy coerced
into doing what they wanted.
Liar!
Are you talking about yourself?
Don't you dare walk out.
Don't you want to know
who really killed Divine?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know?
You know who killed my mother?
I do.
And it's someone
you know very well.
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Look familiar, Wilson?
It must be.
I was with Divine
the day she bought it for you.
And you dropped it the night
you killed Divine!
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
You're crazy!
You were threatening my friend.
You almost choked her
to death out of rage.
You can't deny this.
I saw it with my own eyes.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Divine!
You're leaving me
to be with Gilbert?
Wilson, please.
Will you stop it?
Not only have you stolen
from me,
you've also been cheating on me.
- [GRUNTS]
- [GLASSES CLATTER]
How dare you accuse me
of such things?!
Here.
Look at the actual reports.
The ones that aren't falsified.
You're breaking up with me
just to be with Gilbert?
Answer me!
I don't want this
anymore, Wilson!
I've had enough!
- I'm leaving with my daughter.
- No!
You are not leaving
with my daughter!
You will not bring Caroline.
I am leaving with her!
- [GRUNTS]
- [SCREAMS]
[GROANS] Wilson.
You are not leaving me!
I won't allow it!
- You're hurting me, Wilson!
- Over my dead body!
- Wilson, stop!
- I'm going to kill you!
- Please stop!
- I'm going to kill you...
It's true, isn't it?
You were the last person
who was with Divine.
You hurt her
and threatened to kill her.
[SULLEN MUSIC PLAYING]
Pa...
Is that true?
[ANNIE] It's true.
[SOBS]
You know what happened next?
I ran outside to ask for help,
but someone tried
to run me over.
And those people followed me
because they wanted me dead.
That's how horrible
they were, Caroline!
No. No.
[SOBBING]
[ANNIE] Money.
Money.
Your entire life
revolves around money.
That's why this...
This is my victory!
Taking away all
of your sources of money!
- [DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS]
Pa?
- Pa? Papa?
- Wilson!
Wilson!
- Help!
- Thea!
- Wilson!
- [CARLO] Pa!
- [IRENE] Thea!
- Help!
[OVERLAPPING SHOUTING]
- Thea!
- [CINDY] Wilson!
- [CARLO] Pa!
- Pa!
- Wilson! Thea!
- [IRENE] We need some help!
[CARLO] Pa!
Please call an ambulance!
[BETTINA] Call an ambulance!
Papa's having a heart attack!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[IRENE] Thea!
Thea!
[OVERLAPPING SHOUTING]
[BETTINA] We need an
ambulance now, Thea! Come on!
I can now face my son.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Where's the ambulance?
How many minutes?
How long will it take?
- Hello, doc?
- You need to hurry up.
- He said 15 minutes.
- Fifteen minutes, doc.
I'm going to sue her! She's not
going to get away with this!
- Pa, just hold on, please?
- [CINDY] Where is the...
Is there any help coming?
Can you move faster, please?
Here, Pa.
Go, go, go.
Move. Please move.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
MJ, what happened to Sir Wilson?
I don't know, but that's
Miss Caroline with him
in the ambulance, right?
- She was crying.
- [SIREN WAILING]
Let's ask them what happened.
[LINE RINGING]
- [LINE RINGING]
- Ling.
[SIGHS]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BANGS]
- [CINDY] Charleston.
[IRENE] Charleston.
Doc? How is he?
We are prepping him
for angioplasty.
We have to unclog his arteries.
And we need to do this
immediately
so it won't get any worse.
Okay, doc. Just do
whatever you need to do.
- [DOCTOR] Excuse me.
- [CINDY] Thank you.
Papa...
[SNIFFLES, SOBBING]
Okay. Now, hand it to me.
It's still too warm.
Let's go to the table.
Alright. Careful.
Take it slow.
Go right.
Right...
- There you go.
- [KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Hello?
[NENE] Someone's here?
Ma'am Annie?
- Ma.
- Huh?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma'am Annie?
This is all my fault.
This is my fault.
I didn't know all my shares
will go to Annie.
That witch!
There's no point in blaming
yourself, Irene.
Okay? All of us...
All of us were deceived.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ling, where are you?
[PHONE RINGING]
Grandma?
She...
Annie's here.
She's picking us up.
What?
[SULLEN MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR CLICKS]
You're happy now?
- Auntie--
- Answer my question.
Are you happy now?
This is what you want, right?
This isn't what I want.
If you want to believe
Annie, go ahead.
You're free to go.
And stay away as far
as you can from us.
Don't ever come back.
You wouldn't stop.
You wouldn't let
anything stop you...
until something like this
happened to my family.
You're right.
You're a constant nuisance
in our lives.
And you've proven it
once and for all.
[SULLEN MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Grandma.
Andrei.
Andrei, it's done.
I've had my revenge on the
family who broke us apart.
Now's the time we enjoy
the fruits of my labor.
GLC is now yours.
What?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
The Tius have lost their power
in the GLC.
It is what it is.
You think I'm the only one
who got used?
You're just a freaking puppet!
This is your plan all along.
I didn't do anything!
You even used my sister.
He's not that type of person.
It's still his mother.
Now you choose:
This family or theirs?
Why is this happening to me?
We were destined to meet
just to make each other suffer.