♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 13=
(Male and female are equal)
(Main Hall)
Stop crying.
All you do is cry.
What's the point of crying?
Crying will not bring Xiaoman back.
You're the best.
You know what to do
yet you couldn't come out
from the prison on your own.
The daughter has to
bear it for your sake.
I...
Xie Li is here.
Father. Mother.
I've brought sister home.
Father.
Mother.
Where have you been?
Why didn't you inform us?
I'm very worried.
Mother.
Don't cry.
I'm doing just fine.
Not at all.
You lost weight in a few days.
I'm extremely worried about you.
I'm very concerned.
Mother.
Man'er.
I let you down.
I'm useless.
Father.
That hurts.
I'm Li Su.
It's pointless to hit yourself.
She is home.
Look.
I'm Xiaoman's senior from the academy.
We met at Yuyangli Village as well.
Thank you for the cakes and repairs,
aunty.
Have you forgotten?
Mr. Li.
May I speak to you in private?
Man'er.
Take a break.
Go on.
Mr. Li.
What should we do now?
If the Commandery Prince sells her off,
my daughter would suffer.
My daughter doesn't deserve
this mistreatment.
Do not worry, elders.
Although His Highness
and I do not get along,
the man he selected
is bonded with my father.
I came to an agreement with them.
If Xiaoman was sold,
they'd redeem her freedom for us.
However,
Xiaoman's reputation
would be tarnished.
It's going to be fine.
My poor child.
Lady Xie, are you feeling better?
By the way,
you asked
what happened at
the Commandery Prince's Mansion today.
Shi Deng'er told me that
Commandery Prince's brother...
I don't know what he's called.
Duke of Yongguo.
Yes.
Duke of Yongguo's birthday is coming up.
Around this time of the year,
the Commandery Prince's mansion...
has to pay memorial to Duke of Yongguo.
Did you know?
After the Qixi Festival
comes my brother's birthday.
Principal Yang once said
my brother and I are
completely different.
Both of us entered the palace together.
My brother was reliable,
and I was stubborn.
Everyone thought
my brother would emerge
as the next Emperor.
I've never thought of
competing with my brother anyway.
All I wanted
was after my brother
becomes the Emperor,
I'll head to the borders
and protect the state for my brother.
Unfortunately,
I was exiled from the capital.
Even worse,
he no longer exists.
Lady Xie.
A student from Bailu Academy
is at the main corridor.
The student calls himself
your classmate.
His name is Wang Weicheng.
What's he doing here?
Are you here to collect the goods
after receiving the deed
from Zhao Xiaoqian?
No.
That's not true.
I...
I do not intend to purchase you.
What are you doing here then?
Let me be honest with you.
I grew up with Lang Mengzi of
Jingnv Pavilion.
I promised her I'd never
marry a concubine.
Don't
even dream of entering my household.
Also,
by His Highness' orders,
he wants me to collect your deed
after the polo tournament
and release you.
He also wants me to
pass you a title deed.
I'm still troubled.
Mengzi misunderstood me.
I can't go on with this anymore.
Anyway,
I'll leave everything to you.
Resolve it among yourselves.
I'm leaving.
That fool.
Idiot.
Lady Xie.
Wick.
Head to Minggu
and tell her to join me at the market.
Do it now.
He mistreated you.
Are you still going
to buy him something?
Besides,
the Commandery Prince's Mansion...
has no use for these.
Miss, what do you need?
Shopkeeper,
I would like
some cloth and bamboo splint
for kite-making.
Do you sell them here?
Yes.
It costs ten cash in total.
Thank you, miss.
I'm repaying the favour.
Repaying the favour?
Let's go.
Take care.
Your Highness.
Why is Your Highness drenched?
Shi Deng'er, what were you doing?
It has nothing to do with them.
Your Highness.
Do not follow me!
Mr. Liangji.
Where is Mr. Zhong?
Besides Mr. Zhong,
nobody else can persuade His Highness.
Mr. Zhong is at Mount Han Temple.
It's Duke of Yongguo's birthday.
He's off to light the lanterns.
Let's talk to Zhu Momo instead.
I don't want to be reprimanded.
You go instead.
You, come here.
Tell me.
What's going on?
(Xiaoqian.)
Brother.
A partridge flew by the city gate.
(Zhao Xiaoqian at young age)
I asked Fuweng to catch it with me.
(Zhao Xiaoqian's brother, Zhao Xiaojie)
I'm not allowed to leave Wude Palace.
Otherwise,
the Empress would be upset.
It doesn't matter.
We can have fun here the same.
I want to go out there.
I don't want to drink tea in here.
It's bitter.
We can't do that yet.
Yesterday,
you knocked over Her Highness' tea cup.
Her Highness was enraged.
You should obey and stay put here.
I'll get Fuweng
to have some noodles served.
You should warm yourself up.
Tomorrow,
you shall learn " The Great Learning"
with Her Highness tomorrow
to cheer Her Highness up.
Is that all right?
Will Her Highness allow us to leave?
She doesn't like me.
I just want to fly a kite.
I want my kite to fly the highest
to show father and mother.
Once they see it,
would they come to visit us?
If father and mother saw your kite,
they'd lecture you for fooling around.
A few days ago,
did you break a wooden sword again?
I hate them for showing me an attitude.
They call me playful and mischievous.
Everyone thinks badly of me.
No one likes me here.
I want to go home.
Hide your treasured belongings well.
No matter what happens,
do not break them.
Despite the contempt they show you,
these things will keep you company.
I'm right here, too.
I'll not mistreat you.
The wooden swords and kites
will not mistreat you either.
We will always stay by your side
forever and ever.
We'd watch you grow old
as you live a happy life.
Isn't that good enough?
I'll take you there right now.
Come on.
Your Highness.
It's cloudy today.
Why would anyone fly a kite?
Brother.
Your Highness.
Xingzhou.
Xiaoman came by just now
and left this to me.
She said
she made this kite herself
in hopes to comfort
your yearning for Xiaojie.
It's Xiaojie's birthday today.
I guessed you'd be...
Are you speaking on her behalf?
Like I said,
I do not want you to regret anything.
If Xiaoman was truly sold,
would you be happy?
Would you be able to forgive yourself?
Before Xiaoman left, she told me
the Zhao Xiaoqian she knows
never worried about a single thing.
Where is Hanchen?
Why isn't he here yet?
I stopped him from coming.
What?
How will we proceed
with the competition?
(Mulan)
The time for the polo tournament
shall begin soon.
We're going to give
a leeway of 30 minutes.
Absentees will be considered
as voluntary withdrawal.
I'm heading over.
Sure.
Ladies of Jingnv Pavilion,
you're all respected opponents.
If I do not show up,
it's a disrespect towards
your effort and ambition.
Xie Xiaoman,
this is your test.
You should see it through.
I'll be right here.
I'm not going easy on you.
Let's get it started, guys.
All right. Come on.
Move it.
Lady Xie,
quit standing around.
You should head inside.
His Highness is waiting for you.
What are you doing?
What are you trying to do?
I'm about to return as
a daughter of nobility.
You went against your words
and harassed me.
Yes.
I've decided not to let you go.
Why not?
We agreed beforehand.
No means no.
You're quite talkative today.
Xie Xiaoman,
are you pretending to be
dumb or are you blind?
Don't you see
everything I've prepared for you?
That's another matter altogether.
My deed is important.
You should be a man of your words.
♪Listening to your wonderful voice♪
♪When I close my eyes♪
♪You dance like the cloud♪
♪We grow old together slowly♪
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have said that
I wanted to sell you off.
I found out.
Wang Weicheng told me everything.
You didn't mean to sell me.
You wanted to free me.
I'm not freeing you now.
Are you a dog?
You can't just retract your words.
I...
What?
I like...
What do you like?
Dogs.
I like dogs.
Can't I?
♪Seek no more as it'll always be you♪
Will you
forgive me?
♪I'd only tell you my feelings♪
♪When I close my eyes♪
♪You dance like the cloud♪
♪We grow old together slowly♪
(Prince Pu's Mansion)
About travelling to Wujiang Prefecture,
I already spoke to father and mother.
By the reason of visiting relatives,
I'll depart tomorrow.
As for the matters at the capital,
I'll have to trouble Your Highness.
Hanchen has always been headstrong.
If he upsets you
after your arrival at
Wujiang Prefecture,
do not worry.
I'm on your side.
(Brothel)
Yanniang.
What are you...
Congwen,
I've decided to marry Squire Wang.
I invited you here
just to bid you farewell.
Do you remember back then
when we first met
at Yanliu Forest?
The red peach blossoms flutter gently
as the east wind blows.
The heart aches for whom?
The anguish of a woman, forced
to marry a man she doesn't love.
As passion fades,
she was shrouded
by the memories they shared.
It was drizzling that day.
You took shelter under a pavilion.
I was playing the song, The Hidden Moon.
I have three wishes.
One, for my lover to live a long life.
Two, for a healthy body.
Three, to be like
the birds of the forest.
I'll meet you in my dreams.
Mr. Li.
Your father and I were
officials of the same age.
We could be considered colleagues.
Today,
let's be honest with each other.
Do you know why Courtesan Zhu's
appeals were
constantly deterred?
I know.
Since you're aware,
I hope you will not make
things difficult for me.
Lord Yan.
Is there
any other way?
As long as you remain
as the guarantor of Courtesan Zhu,
she will not be able to
regain her freedom.
She's just a courtesan at the brothel.
Your father would never
allow you to marry a frivolous woman.
Not to mention,
a man would like to act as
Courtesan Zhu's guarantor.
Mr. Li, consider letting her go
so she could find a man to rely on.
(Bailu Academy)
(Jingnv Pavilion)
Stream of Bian flows.
Stream of Si flows.
They flow towards
the ancient port of Yangtze River.
Congwen.
Longing and hatred.
There's no end until your return.
Holding each other under the moonlight.
Although the structure
of this piece is short,
with the form of repetition,
it expresses the endless longing.
The pain of longing and
the agony of separation
were portrayed vividly.
All right. You may all take a break.
Thank you, Congwen.
Don't you think
Congwen is rather strange today?
(She stands in a daze among
the flowers while swallows fly in pairs.)
You're walking like my father.
Both hands on your back.
I like it.
Right.
The old men are often arrogant.
It's a good thing that
I'm behaving more mature.
Sure.
You're always right.
Actually,
it feels pretty good
to put my hands behind.
Xingzhou.
Try it out.
We went through the entire street.
We've been looking around.
What exactly are you looking for?
I have a confession to
make to Xie Xiaoman.
After contemplation,
I need to buy a gift
and come up with an excuse.
What's the matter?
Are you going to confess your love?
You should consult me in this regard.
I'm the perfect person to ask.
Fine, enlighten me.
All right.
Recently,
a trend has been going on
in Wujiang Prefecture.
A poem is hidden in the lantern.
It's not visible during the day.
However, once it's lit up at night,
the poem would be displayed.
The Ghost Festival is around the corner.
The stream will be filled with lanterns.
You may express your feelings this way.
What do you think?
No.
This feels obscure.
It doesn't fit my personality.
As long as it works, am I right?
Many gentlemen
express their love with this approach.
It works for many of them.
How did you know that?
I...
I've been writing
to an old friend of mine.
That's what she told me.
A man like you has a pen pal?
Aren't you worried she
could end up as an old hag?
Don't be ridiculous.
I asked.
She's 16 years old this year.
On the day of Ghost Festival,
take me to the lanterns.
The civil examination is coming up.
I need to prepare for it.
Let's do it some other time.
Don't be mad.
Listen to me.
It wouldn't make a difference
to go next time, right?
What's wrong?
Hanchen.
(Lotus Garden)
Stream of Bian and Stream of Si flow.
They flow towards
the ancient port of Yangtze River.
Longing and worries...
What in the world is this?
Read it properly.
I don't understand
a single word.
Congwen always
teaches you difficult materials.
No wonder Courtesan Zhu left him.
What did you say?
You heard about what
happened between
Courtesan Zhu and Congwen as well?
Yes.
I was out eating noodles in the morning.
The owner of Da'e Noodle House said
Courtesan Zhu is getting married.
She's going to be married to a squire.
Apparently,
he owns tens of hectares of farmland.
He's wealthy.
Could that be true?
Courtesan Zhu is getting married?
Did they mention Congwen?
I'm not sure.
Well, everyone thinks
Congwen is just a poor scholar.
It's a good thing Courtesan Zhu
isn't marrying him.
I think so, too.
If I get to choose,
I'd marry the squire
and be an owner of land.
Congwen is a poor man
who enjoys poetry.
He gives me a headache.
Don't be ridiculous!
Did they mention
the courtesan being
forced into the marriage?
What happens if the squire
seized her by force?
Congwen is a mere scholar.
He will not be able to win.
I haven't heard of that.
Do not enter.
Enter.
No.
Shi Deng'er.
Enter.
Do I enter or not?
Do not enter.
You...
His Highness is here.
Who's here?
- Who is it?
- Shi Deng'er.
Shi Deng'er.
His Highness is here.
Why are you pushing me?
(Lotus Garden)
What are you doing here?
This is my home.
I can go anywhere I want to.
Your words are hideous.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
I'll teach you Su Calligraphy.
Do you know how to write it?
Of course I do.
Who am I?
The well-rounded Commandery Prince.
You're one lucky girl.
Tell me.
What does holding each other
under the moonlight mean?
Under the bright moonlight,
two lovers should enjoy it
by holding each other
to properly appreciate its beauty.
You enjoy writing poetry.
Do you like poetry
hidden in the lanterns?
Oh, right.
Let me ask you.
Do you think
a man would forcibly
marry a woman of another man?
Should I stay the night?
Lecher!
Your Highness.
What do you intend to buy?
We left abruptly.
I haven't finished my rice cakes.
Sir.
Would you like a lantern?
These two are rather exquisite.
You have a keen eye, sir.
These two
are different from the rest.
Look at this one.
"Cut all ties" is written on this one.
They are
used by the ladies to reject men.
What about this one?
This is great.
Look.
"Lover on the other side."
This lantern
is one of our best sellers.
This is the last piece left.
Really?
This one it is.
How much does it cost?
Ten cash.
Your Highness.
Wait up.
(Brothel)
I loved the lady for a long time,
but she had no idea.
"Dew becomes frost".
Tell me.
What exactly is going on
in a woman's head?
"Dew becomes frost".
I told you the story of
Minggu and I.
Please advise me.
("Dew becomes frost")
Hold it.
What are you doing?
Let go.
"Dew becomes frost"?
Which lady are you writing to?
Are you thinking about ladies already?
Are you fully grown?
Mind your own business.
Give it back.
You...
A letter written to a lady.
I'm sure the letter
consists of things you don't
want others to find out.
How about this?
I'll charge you 20 strings of 1000 cash.
and act as your pigeon
to deliver the letter.
20 strings?
In your dreams.
I don't have money for you.
Fine.
I'll order a few servants
and have this letter
duplicated in hundreds.
I'll stick them all over Bailu Academy.
How dare you?
Why not?
I cannot allow Ming...
Ming?
What are you talking about?
Quit yapping.
I have no money for you.
I can't be bothered.
By noon tomorrow,
at the entrance of Bailu Academy,
if I do not receive the money,
I'm going to stick your letter
onto the notice board.
Let's go.
Xu Shu!
You...
You rascal!
Qiongqiong.
Burn them all.
(From Congwen)
Sister,
I do not understand.
You clearly have feelings
for Mr. Congwen.
Why would you agree to
Squire Wang's proposal?
Burn these letters first.
Sister, I can't burn them.
The letters consist of your poetry
written with Mr. Congwen.
You have yet to pass them to him.
You can't burn them.
Enough.
Congwen and I are over.
Since it's over,
it's pointless to keep these around.
Sister.
Your heart still yearns for Mr. Congwen.
I've made up my mind.
Do not try to convince me.
Burn the letters.
Tomorrow,
we're leaving.
(Bailu Academy)
Lady Xie, please hold on.
Qiongqiong?
Lady Xie,
I have a favour to ask.
Take your time.
I'll take a walk at the Shi Alley.
Is this about Courtesan Zhu?
Is she really getting married?
Was it out of her own will
or was she extorted by the squire?
It was out of her own free will.
Lady Xie.
You may not have known.
Since the courtesan told Mr. Congwen
about her marriage,
Mr. Congwen never stepped
foot in the brothel.
I'm certain
that she still yearns for Mr. Congwen.
I'm sure Mr. Congwen
feels the same as well.
However, we're leaving tonight.
I just
wanted them to meet for one last time.
Perhaps, things will turn around.
Even if nothing changes,
at least they could
have bid each other farewell.
Sister kept everything to herself.
I'm concerned about her.
One last time?
This
was written by her and Mr. Congwen.
It's called the Sapphire Song.
Mr. Congwen wrote the first verse
while she wrote the bottom half.
She hasn't shown it to Mr. Congwen yet.
Once he sees this,
he'd definitely come to meet her.
Since Courtesan Zhu has
made the decision on her own,
there's nothing I can do either.
My apologies.
Lady Xie.
It's fine if you wouldn't
pass it to Mr. Congwen.
I
said what I needed to say.
I shall return to pack our belongings.
Qiongqiong.
At 9.45 p.m. during
the Ghost Festival tonight,
Squire Wang's carriage
to pick Courtesan Zhu up
will be passing by the market on Leqiao.
I'll be waiting for your reply.
You...
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪