♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 19=
(Living in a poor environment
makes me lonely at night)
Take a look at this.
This was written by my student
in the capital
for my entertainment.
Now, it's known across
the entire capital
the Prince Pu's Mansion
who broke off the engagement
is again connecting with Shen Family
through marriage.
Moreover, an order has been
issued at the imperial palace.
Why did Her Highness agree to it?
How could Her Highness wish
me to marry the daughter
of Shen Family?
The balance of interests
in the imperial court
changes frequently.
Shen Family is on Her Highness' side.
If you marry their daughter,
and go to the capital,
you'll be within her control.
I'll reply them
the same thing.
I won't marry Shen Zhaowen.
All I'm thinking is to help Xie Xiaoman
to be conferred as Noble Lady Wuguo.
I know that, in Wujiang Prefecture,
you're the only person
who isn't under the control
of Prince Pu's Mansion.
Please pass this to the Ministry
of Imperial Affairs on my behalf.
I don't believe that
after Shen Zunfu saw this,
he'll still entrust his daughter to me.
So you're going to go against
the Prince Pu's Mansion?
That's right.
Let me be the Prince Pu's Mansion's
good-for-nothing son until the end.
Such a pity.
For this matter,
(Commandery Prince of Julu's letter)
I'm unable to help.
Principal.
Submitting a memorial
is beyond my power.
That being said, here's an idea.
Duke Teng of Tongzhou has
resigned from his position,
so he isn't controlled
by any of the parties.
If he's willing to help,
you will have a bigger chance.
Thank you for your help.
Take care, Your Highness.
Why did you help His Highness?
Whenever the roc flies into the sky,
thousands of miles will be passed by.
How did it go?
I don't think I can go
with you to the exam hall.
I have to go to Tongzhou
on a quick horse.
I understand.
Don't worry about the exam.
Take care on your way there.
(The deserter of Shenwu Army, Huang Liu,
will be beheaded in seven days)
What exactly happened to you?
He and Shen Zhaowen are engaged.
They might
get married soon.
Xiaoman.
(Zheng Hai's wife, Ming Yue)
Xiaoman?
Ming Yue?
Xiaoman.
Save me, Xiaoman!
Save me!
She's Ming Yue,
my childhood friend in Yuyangli Village.
We grew up together.
Since the day you left,
our family got poor harvest.
At the same time, my brother fell ill.
We had no money to hire him a physician,
so they arranged me to get
married here in Wujiang Prefecture.
The matchmaker said
it's a wealthy family looking
for a second wife.
I only found out upon arrival
that the man's a local hooligan.
Not only does he not work,
he'd even hit me
whenever things don't go his way.
He even hit you?
Xiaoman,
I want to go back to Yuyangli Village.
I want to go home.
Get up first.
It hurts.
How can he hit you like this?
All these were his doings?
Xiaoman,
I pleaded with him to let me go.
I pleaded with everyone around me,
but as you can see,
in the end,
I got beaten even more badly.
I've used up
all the cash gift I took from my family.
There's no way I can escape.
I'm trapped here forever.
It won't happen, Ming Yue.
Don't worry.
I'll help you.
It's not a big deal.
He just wants money.
I have money.
I saved up a lot.
I'll give you all my money.
We can't do that.
He won't let me go.
Nothing is predestined.
Don't worry.
I won't let you live like this.
I resign to my destiny.
I'm not like you.
I've always been timid
since I was little.
So what if I leave his side
and return to Yuyangli Village?
I'll still be
an old maid who can't get married.
Xiaoman,
I'll only bring you trouble.
Just let me be.
Ming Yue.
There are really ladies in this world
who will remain at their husbands' side
even if their marriage is a mistake?
I think
that's the majority.
How did it go?
(The deserter of Shenwu Army, Huang Liu,
will be beheaded in seven days)
Speak.
Xiaoman...
Xiaoman didn't come.
She isn't willing to help?
Aren't you two childhood friends?
She...
She's having some trouble lately.
So she won't help you?
Maybe...
Maybe it's because we haven't
seen each other for a long time.
She...
What else did she say to you?
Nothing.
You're useless.
Try again tomorrow.
If it still doesn't work,
I can only use brutal force.
Tomorrow, you all will follow Ming Yue
to Bailu Academy
to kidnap the Commandery Prince.
A life for a life.
I'm going to save Huang Liu.
But Zheng Hai,
last time, he...
Zhao Xiaoqian
doesn't seem to be in
Wujiang Prefecture currently.
He's not in Wujiang Prefecture?
Then we'll get hold of his weakness.
What...
What weakness?
Commandery Prince of Julu's concubine.
But...
That's it.
Year after year,
we already have four children.
If you don't pass the exam,
how can we carry on then?
This time it'll be all right.
Just stay at home to
look after the children.
I'll definitely pass the exam this year.
Xingzhou,
don't be anxious.
Just do as
you normally would.
I agree.
You seem to be more anxious
than Xingzhou.
Go away.
A time will come to ride
the wind and cleave the waves.
I'll set my cloud-white sail
and cross the sea which raves.
Xiaoman,
Hanchen is up to something lately,
but no worries.
You two can talk about it
when he's back.
(Wujiang Examination Hall)
Examinees, please enter the hall.
Good luck.
Okay.
Xingzhou,
my father said,
bring a cicada with you during exam.
If the cicada sounds,
the examinee will get the first place.
Take it.
Thank you.
Minggu,
I have to go.
Where are you going?
I'm going to look for Congwen.
He said he has something to tell me.
Don't you think
Xie Xiaoman and Zhao Xiaoqian
have been acting weird recently?
You don't know anything.
It's not for you to gossip.
I don't.
You're the one who's been weird.
Xingzhou's taking the exam.
And you
gave him a cicada as a gift.
If the invigilator heard the noise,
what's our Xingzhou going to do?
Our Xingzhou?
What do you mean?
Xingzhou isn't your son.
Someone's coming.
Xiaoman,
you're here.
Congwen,
you're teaching here?
Yes.
I'm teaching general knowledge.
Since you're here today,
you can teach the ladies a chapter
from Examples for Women.
Me?
I can't do it.
Who knows.
You'll never know unless you give it a try.
Children.
Today, I invited
a female teacher here to join us.
This is Teacher Xie.
Greetings, Teacher Xie.
Before this, Teacher Li taught you all
"Women's Analects".
What do you all think of it?
I didn't understand it.
When I was reading at a younger age,
a farmer's proverb from our village
would always come to mind.
Seedling frame tall in the field
vines coiled by itself.
Under the regime of powerful forces,
the disadvantaged will be
suppressed and exploited.
At that time, I thought
the "Women's Analects"
is all about instructions
for the ladies.
In terms of morality, words,
appearance and power,
there are demands for
the ladies to follow.
But why
there aren't demands for men?
And we ladies
have to be like the vines
on the seedling frames
to be cooped up at one place?
I also heard that
in the past,
if a woman gives birth to a daughter,
she'll be given a spindle
to weave all day.
If she gives birth to a boy,
she'll be given expensive jade
which represents her jade-like virtue.
Spindle and jade
are of course non-comparable.
However, this goes on to show
the world's contempt for women.
My teacher, Liu Huaiying,
once taught us,
as a human,
we don't need to devote to everything,
but one must have high ambitions.
Teacher, what do you
mean by high ambitions?
Boys have their own high ambitions,
and girls
also have girls' high ambitions.
Just like my high ambition
is that you all will grow up quickly.
I know.
Boys and girls are both kids.
Boys can attend
the imperial exam in the future.
We girls can also do other things.
I want to plant sweet potatoes
in the field with my father.
If I grow large, tasty sweet potatoes,
I'll be able to make a living.
Isn't that right, teacher?
You're right.
Being poor
doesn't mean we forget
about our ambitions.
You all need to be like that as well.
Whether it's attending imperial exam
or growing sweet potatoes,
we need to look ahead
to score better in the imperial exam
and grow larger sweet potatoes.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You did a very good job today
as if you're really a teacher.
Congwen, you're making fun of me again.
I won't become a teacher.
I'm serious.
A teacher
must have
something they believe in.
All these years,
I've been to many places
looking for a belief.
I didn't find it,
but you did.
But I don't understand
what I'm going to be like in future.
These few days, Teacher Liu
told us to write about our future,
but I couldn't think of anything.
Especially after teaching here today,
in fact, I'm even more confused now.
Although, today
I talked about "Women's Analects",
if I
really come across
the problems in the books,
I might not be able to
think them through.
Just like
Zhao Xiaoqian and I.
We always worry or fear
over something that has yet happened.
However, future is
like this wheat field.
It may seem far
and vast,
without a direction.
But as you said,
a person's high ambition
doesn't have to be a clear goal.
Sometimes, as you walk down the road,
you'll find another path.
At a secluded temple made of bamboo,
I listen to the speeches
of Buddhist monks.
At the hall in winter season,
I play a game of chess with
the woodcutter for fun.
Wearing slippers made of hay,
I stride across shrubs
climb steep cliffs,
cross uneven terrains
in search for seclusion and beautiful
scenery of streams and rocks.
I can reach the furthest place.
When I arrive, I sit down,
have a chat and drink with friends
whom I haven't seen for so long
to get drunk.
When that happens,
I'll climb high and shout
and let the eye travel
over the great scenery.
When I go to sleep at night,
the dream will reflect the same.
Could it be...
Could it be
you're "Lunatic of Wild Dreams Hall"?
I have to thank you for this book.
Why?
To be honest,
actually, that day at
Mount Kunyan Temple,
I was going to bring my
broken scroll that no one cares about
to leave Wujiang Prefecture
and return to the capital.
Really?
Back then when I left home,
I was thinking
to lead the kind of
life I always wanted,
and never muddle with the affairs
of my father's generation.
However, after all these years,
I've somehow forgotten
my intention back then.
My long-time friend
parted ways with me,
and the manuscript I wrote with
passion was despised by others.
Sometimes, I even doubt
whether I chose the right path,
or should I turn around
and choose another?
Luckily...
Luckily, I have you by my side.
You read that book
and you understood it.
Sometimes, even one reader
will become the author's
motivation to keep going.
I'd never thought
I'm the one who made
"Lunatic of Wild Dreams Hall" stay.
I'm still waiting for you
to publish another book.
Teacher.
Greetings, teacher.
As long as someone by our side
is supporting us,
it'll give us utmost confidence
to move on.
You're that person.
But now,
I also have a friend
who wants to take a step forward,
but she's afraid of how
people will see her.
Congwen, do you think
I should help her?
What do you think?
Thank you, Congwen.
(Lonely Boat At Night, volume four)
Lady Xie.
What do you want?
The nourishment has
been sent to your house.
Is it not enough?
I am not here for that.
I came here to look for you.
My lady would like to meet you.
Why did you bring me here?
What exactly are you up to?
To show you something good, of course.
Go away.
So clumsy.
Wait on the side.
Sorry, sir.
I'm sorry.
Mother.
Didn't you say
His Highness isn't willing to marry me?
Today, I'll show you
even if His Highness isn't
willing to marry me,
you'll never become his wife.
Do you know
the imperial palace has agreed
to grant Hanchen and me marriage?
Someone,
pour me a cup of tea.
Coming!
Your tea is here.
What are you doing?
Lady.
You can't blame others
for certain matters
because Hanchen doesn't
belong to you in the first place.
Are you aware of his identity
and your identity?
Are you also aware that,
even without me,
there'll be someone else.
Commandery Princess of Julu
will never be someone
from your background.
You'll forever be a concubine,
a servant.
Your son
won't call you mother in the future,
and will instead call you nanny.
Your parents
will also be inferior to others.
You don't even know how to pour tea.
You peasant!
Mother.
Is staying in the inner courtyard
for the rest of your life
what you want?
For so many years,
that's what women have gone through.
What?
Do you think just because
Zhao Xiaoqian's in love with you,
he'll guarantee your safety?
Zhao Xiaoqian will take care of you,
but what about Princess Consort Pu,
Her Highness
or the imperial palace in the capital?
Lady.
I...
Is your hand all right?
I didn't do it on purpose.
Do you know who I am?
My lady is
the Commandery Princess Rong'an.
She'll marry
Commandery Prince of Julu in future
as his wife.
She isn't someone you can offend.
You're Lady Xie's mother.
I'm not mistaken, right?
It's my fault that
I failed to recognize you.
It's my fault.
I'm really sorry.
What do we do with your hand?
In a royal or nobleman's family,
a concubine
is just a
doll.
Lady.
Here.
Take this.
When your lady is married
to Commandery Prince,
my daughter will need
your care.
My daughter is kind,
with no underhanded
tricks up her sleeve.
She won't cause trouble for you.
Please
don't make things difficult for her
and let her stay.
Did you see that?
You'll forever be
a concubine who's inferior to others.
Even your mother...
This slap
is for my mother.
And this slap is for me.
Lady.
(Tongzhou)
Duke Teng.
Good child.
Come and have a seat.
Have a seat.
So,
what brought you here today?
I'll cut to the chase then.
(Commandery Prince of Julu's letter)
I have a concubine
named Xie Xiaoman.
I'll bring her to meet you next time.
Lady Xie is gentle,
modest and courteous.
I want to help her get conferred
as Noble Lady Wuguo,
but people at Wujiang Prefecture
will gossip.
That's why I'm asking
for your help, Duke Teng.
Don't worry.
I don't have tricks up my sleeve.
I just want the woman I love
to have a status.
I don't plan to marry again either.
Ladies
prefer to never be apart, right?
Duke Teng, if you will agree to it,
and Lady Xie also agrees to it.
Wife, kids and a warm bed.
I'll have everything.
I won't intervene
with what's going on in the capital.
It's fine if you like her,
but will she become your wife?
You know, for someone
with your identity,
you'll have a wife eventually.
Favoring the concubine and
doing away with the wife
are great taboos.
I know.
I won't get a wife.
Childish.
Even if you don't want a wife,
but will the Prince Pu's Mansion
allow it?
Will His Majesty allow it?
Do you plan to defy the imperial order?
If you insist on this,
it'll only do her harm.
I'll do anything
for her sake.
Even defying the imperial order?
You're muddle-headed.
Hanchen,
with the forthcoming battles
at Baichuankou,
are you really going to remain at
the tiny Wujiang Prefecture
as the sluggish prince
for the rest of your life?
May I ask
do you know
a lady called Ming Yue?
She lives nearby.
No.
You're looking for Ming Yue?
Yes.
I'm her friend.
We know where she is.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's go.
Who are you people?
(Zheng's Mansion)
Please let her go.
I'll do anything to repay your kindness.
Shut up.
We'll sort out with you later.
Xiaoman.
You're Xie Xiaoman?
You're Zheng Hai?
That's me.
I've long heard about you
and wanted to meet you this way.
Tell me.
If I slash your beautiful face
with a knife,
perhaps you won't be
so sharp-tongued?
What are you trying to do?
Zhao Xiaoqian.
If it wasn't because of him,
my brother
won't be arrested
by the magistrate office
or set to be executed a week later.
I'm worried about my brother,
isn't that right?
You've got the wrong person.
I'm nothing
at the Commandery Prince's Mansion.
Zhao Xiaoqian won't risk himself for me.
Doing so
not only won't help your brother,
but bring then more troubles.
Xiaoman, I'm sorry.
I brought this onto you.
Shut up, woman.
Inform the Commandery Prince's Mansion
to come and get the hostage tomorrow.
Xiaoman.
You knew he's going to kidnap me.
That's why you tried to approach me,
is that right?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you'd come.
Come out quickly!
Search quickly! Hurry!
Search carefully!
(Lotus Garden)
She isn't here.
The front courtyard.
Search the front courtyard.
Okay.
Oh, right.
Did you ask Su Family?
Yes.
They said she wasn't
seen the entire night.
It must be Shen Family.
Shen Family must've harmed Lady Xie.
We've asked Shen Family.
They didn't see Lady Xie.
Ridiculous.
Shen Family must've kidnapped Lady Xie.
Mr. Liangji.
Someone said
she knows where the lady is.
Who is it?
Ming Yue?
Is my lady with you?
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
What's going on?
(Commandery Prince's Mansion)
It's Zheng Hai.
Zheng Hai kidnapped Xiaoman
so he could threaten
Commandery Prince of Julu.
- Your Highness.
- You're back, Your Highness.
What did you just say?
It's Zheng Hai,
a local gangster at Xushui, Wazi.
He kidnapped Xiaoman
to exchange for terms with her life.
It's him?
Quickly inform Arms Instructor Qin.
Your Highness!
Your Highness mustn't go.
They're after Your Highness.
Let me tell you.
Zhao Xiaoqian will never come.
Just give up.
(Zheng's Mansion)
If Zhao Xiaoqian doesn't come,
you and I will have a
good time together.
I'm in need of a lady
to warm the bed, too.
Apart from you,
I still have other ways
to teach him a lesson.
(Zheng's Mansion)
You're here so quickly.
Zhao Xiaoqian, are you an idiot?
Why did you come here alone?
Say it.
What do I need to do
so you'll release her?
Now you're negotiating with me.
That day
when you stepped on me,
that's not how you spoke to me.
The tone I'm speaking now
isn't much better either.
If you act this way,
our deal
won't be so easy.
If it wasn't because of you,
my fellow brother won't be arrested
or set to be executed a week later.
If you want to save her,
the conditions now
are that I'll beat you up
and you'll get my brother back
uninjured
to exchange for her.
That's right.
Release Huang Liu.
If it wasn't you,
he wouldn't have been arrested.
Desertion is a capital offence.
The army has ironclad rules.
Justice is military law.
What's wrong with it?
Huang Liu's mother passed away.
He went home for the funeral
which was later blamed by
his superior for desertion.
That's what you mean by justice?
A royal's life is life
and our commoners'
are nothing?
Xiaoman,
close your eyes.
I'll bring you home soon.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Come on.
What are you waiting for?
Hit him!
Hai!
Hai, are you all right?
Hit him!
A bunch of useless people.
Stop!
Let's see who dare move an inch!
Bring them away!
Great.
Come on!
Not bad.
You terrible woman!
Let's go.
You betrayed me!
Your Highness, let's go.
Xiaoman,
I'm sorry.
You should come with me, too.
Are you all right?
Does it hurt?
In the future,
don't do this on your own.
You have a husband.
I'll help you with everything.
I know you and that lady
are long-time friends,
but now she's been sent to prison.
Do you want to visit her?
(Prison)
Ming Yue.
Xiaoman.
Xiaoman,
I'm sorry for lying to you.
I got you involved.
I'm sorry.
Yes,
it's your fault.
Because of you, my husband was injured,
I was kidnapped
and you're jailed.
But at the same time,
you've helped me.
Didn't you defy Zheng Hai
for my sake?
Also, you admitted
your wrongdoing to Zhao Xiaoqian.
I blame you,
but more than that,
I want you to be all right.
I'm not here to seek revenge.
You left the lady at home
to come and meet us here.
Interesting.
Which camp is he in?
Third Commander of Shenwu Army,
Huang Liu, a scout under
General Meng Liang,
is here to greet Your Highness.
Shenwu Army is stationed at Gu City,
a part of Zhending Prefecture's
army camp.
It was once led by General Xu Zi.
Am I correct?
Yes.
Zhending Prefecture is
situated near our enemies.
Five years ago, there was
the battle at Heyuan.
There was a severe drought in Zhending
and the army lacked food supplies.
However, General Xu Zi
led the soldiers to fight
the enemy for three months
and killed 40,000 of the enemy.
More than 300 of their leaders
were captured as prisoners
along with 3,000 soldiers
and more than 10,000 weapons.
More importantly,
they took back Shun City
so the people didn't lose their homes.
Am I correct?
Yes.
Did you know
I've been dreaming of being
a soldier all my life
yet you
deserted.
No matter what,
the battle at Heyuan
was a significant battle of the nation.
I respect that.
A true man has nothing to hide.
I won't make things
difficult for you today,
but what lays before you
other than returning to Wazi
to keep on being a gangster,
there's also another way.
Huang Liu,
I'll give you one more chance.
General Xu's going to Zhending
again three months later.
You're allowed to join his army.
A man like you,
hiding your identity
in the black market at Wazi
and fighting with others every day.
If you have this kind of energy,
why not return to the battlefield
to carry out a man's duty?
Zheng Hai
doesn't fear power
for the sake of his brother.
He differentiates love from hatred.
However, he isn't aware
of the severity of his actions
and acts frivolously towards ladies.
After three years of conscription,
I'll also allow you to join the army
and go to the battlefield
with your comrades.
What do you think?
We wear gold armors to go
through hundreds of battles.
A sparrow cannot understand
the ambition of a swan.
If you two are swans,
then don't let me down.
If you're willing to join
General Xu's army,
toss your cup in an oath.
I'm willing to go!
I, Zheng Hai,
have always done things
my own way since I was a kid.
I've never thought of
doing something great or noble.
Since you think so highly of me,
I'll go ahead and do it.
I wish for your victorious return.
By telling us these,
it seems Your Highness
aren't entirely disinterested
in joining the army.
So, why do you choose to stay
at Wujiang Prefecture?
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪