♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 20=
(Laughing my way out to the street,
with talents nowhere to perform)
(Prison)
Do you still want to divorce Zheng Hai?
I don't know.
I don't know what's going to happen
after the divorce.
Why are women treated so unfairly?
The world treats women unfairly
because we
did not fight for our own justice.
Perhaps we could take a shot with
what we have.
My cousin Su Wei's
grandmother lost her husband back then.
She raised her daughter up on her own.
However, she was surrounded
by the entire clan.
They intended to seize
all her possessions.
Alone,
she knelt outside
in the snow for three days.
She called for justice every day.
That's how they ended up
with the tradition of female shopkeepers
of Su Chang Ji at Wujiang Prefecture.
A widow who was raising a
daughter could achieve that.
Why should we fear?
What about you?
I will do the same.
I'll fight for my way.
(Prison)
I need to talk to you.
There are things
I've wanted to tell you.
I can finally tell you now.
Once upon a time,
there was an arrogant
and domineering Commandery Prince.
He forced a lady commoner to marry him.
The lady commoner
did not want to marry into
the Commandery Prince's Mansion
as a concubine.
She had her own ambitions.
All she wanted was to retrieve
the title deed of her family's field.
She wanted to spend the rest of
her life back at the village.
However, she was just a peasant.
Neither her nor her family
had the means to
go against
the almighty Commandery Prince.
In the end, they got married.
The lady
did not enjoy such a life.
The Commandery Prince was
always on the high horse.
Being in the company of a king
is like living with a tiger.
She can't
stay by his side at ease.
However, one day,
the Commandery Prince told the lady
that he wanted to spend
the rest of their lives together.
However, she knew
the favour of His Highness
is limited
and transitory.
Most importantly,
if she stays with him,
she will remain a concubine forever.
She will
remain inferior to others forever.
Isn't that right?
I can resolve this.
What are you going to do?
Tell me.
Can we disobey the imperial edict?
Even without Lady Shen,
it would have been someone else.
Your first wife
will never be me.
Isn't that right?
Just trust me this once.
I'll definitely resolve this
as long as you trust me.
It's pointless.
Let me go.
Can you please stay?
I've already found someone I love.
From the moment
I've learned how to love,
she's been residing in my heart.
She is not from a family
as noble as yours.
She isn't as knowledgeable
and refined as you are.
She isn't as generous as you,
but she's the best
in the world.
Do you know how it feels?
When she's mad, she'd bicker with you.
When she's shy, she blushes.
She has many excuses,
but none of them
makes sense.
I've once imagined a life
without her.
However, I can't do it.
(I can't live without her.)
(I can't love you.)
(I'm sorry.)
Discussion of policies.
For today's question,
discuss the theory of punishment.
(Head of Nencao Hall)
(Theory of punishment)
You may begin.
(Wujiang Examination Hall)
Cheating in the examination
is a grave crime.
Before the essay examination,
the topic was leaked.
Who wrote the article for you?
Tell me the truth.
It's the Head of Nencao Hall.
The Head of Nencao Hall
wrote this article on my behalf.
(Zhong Ziyan)
Zhong Ziyan?
(Wujiang Examination Hall)
Examinee Zhong Ziyan
cheated in the examination.
Take this to Prince Pu's Mansion.
Hurry up.
Yes.
(Accurate fortune-telling)
How did it go?
Will he emerge as the first
in the provincial exam?
Three suns and two moons.
What's the reading of the hexagram?
Twelve.
Divine obstruction.
The malevolent has its way
while the good is precarious.
A huge effort, but a little gain.
It's not looking optimistic.
What do you mean by
the good is precarious?
The heavens are above, the earth below.
Heavens represent the good
while the earth represents the vile.
Heavens are outward
while earth is inward.
This reading shows
the vile entering the palace
while the good remains in the wild.
What?
Stop mumbling on.
I don't understand.
Just tell me directly
what I should do right now.
Pay me a tael of silver
to eliminate the calamity.
A tael of silver?
Fine.
Minggu,
what are you thinking?
This is clearly a scam.
Why do you buy a lie?
I'm spending money to
buy a sense of relief.
It's none of your concern.
Go away.
Go.
A tael of silver, right?
There you go.
I'm taking this with me.
Hanchen,
look at her.
She is crazy.
This is clearly a scam.
We could have had a great meal instead.
By the way,
why isn't Xiaoman here today?
Are you sure this would work?
I have things to attend to. I'm leaving.
Thank you.
You're welcome. Take care.
Why did Zhao Xiaoqian leave?
He's surrounded by too many women.
He's probably exhausted.
Unlike me,
I'm a lone wolf.
A lone wolf?
Minggu.
I intend to compile the Biography
of Legendary Women of the History.
But the work is complicated.
I'm afraid I'll not be able
to handle that alone.
Principal Yang gave me a suggestion
to organize an examination
for the female scholars
of Jingnv Pavilion as well.
The best scorer shall
join my endeavour
in the compilation.
I wonder if you're willing to join me.
I'm willing.
Me, too.
- Me, too.
If that's the case,
in three days,
the essay examination will
be held at Tingtao Pavilion.
I look forward to your performances.
(Delicacy Restaurant)
Teacher Liu is organizing
an examination for the ladies.
Besides Lady Shen,
who among us would
emerge as the best at Jingnv Pavilion?
She was taught by
the Imperial Grand Tutor.
Our participation
will be a stepping stone for her.
Who said so?
I think Xie Xiaoman
has the prospects of competing with her.
Xiaoman,
during the Qixi Festival,
I forgot to pass Xingzhou
the poem I wrote.
Should I
leave my poem in this
and give it to him after
the examination?
What do you think?
Do you want him to know
or do you not want him to?
Honestly, I'm not sure.
Minggu.
Xiaoman.
What's going on?
Are you eating?
It's delicious.
Hanchen.
Have you heard that Jingnv Pavilion
will host an examination
for the ladies?
I'm eager to participate.
However...
I'm done. I'll get going.
I don't know how to
write a discussion essay.
Hanchen, please help me.
All right.
Hanchen.
Wait for me.
Xiaoman.
Congwen.
Have a seat.
Teacher Liu told me
you registered for the examination.
Previously,
you took me out of the city
to attend one of your classes.
I'm thinking of
becoming a teacher just like you
and Teacher Liu.
It's a noble job.
Thus, I would like to give it a shot.
However,
I don't know if I'd pass.
How about this?
I heard there are still a
few days left to prepare.
I'm available during the afternoon.
I can help with your revision.
(Dongguan Building)
Xiaoman,
are you here to study as well?
There's a seat here.
Come and join us.
It's fine.
I've made plans with someone.
Lingniang extended her kindness to you.
Lady Xie, you're rather
impolite.
Thank you, Lady Shen.
I'm grateful.
Xiaoman.
Congwen.
Let's go.
My neck.
Hanchen.
Who offended you this time?
You look pretty upset.
Writing a discussion essay is different
from composing poems or odes.
Bombastic expressions and
formats are unnecessary.
Address the issue
and lay down your opinions
comprehensively.
Express a critical point of view.
Is something going on between
you and His Highness?
It seems like
something has happened.
We've decided to opt for a divorce.
I'm waiting for him to issue
the letter of annulment to me.
Divorce?
Why?
It's often said in the books.
As a woman,
one is often left with no choice.
He's leaving Wujiang Prefecture soon.
This may be
a good thing for me.
In a few days,
I would like to give you something.
What's it?
After your examination,
I'll give it to you.
You will find out then.
(How I wish you could understand
my feelings for you.)
(Wujiang Examination Hall)
Xingzhou.
Why are you here?
How did the examination go?
Did you catch a cold?
Did you starve?
Mr. Zhong.
Thank you.
The carriage is over here.
Over here.
I'll make a move first.
Are you Zhong Ziyan?
Scholar from Wujiang Prefecture,
Zhong Ziyan,
is involved in bribery and
disclosure of examination topic.
He was caught cheating
with a fellow student.
His qualifications
shall be revoked from
participating the examination
permanently.
Xingzhou!
I got all excited that
I forgot to pass him the amulet.
I forgot to pass him the food as well.
I'll just give it to him next time.
Let's go.
Xiaoman.
Xiaoman, look.
This belongs to Xingzhou.
Has Xingzhou completed his examination?
He finished it early this morning.
I went to pick him up.
But I forgot to pass him the pouch.
It's fine.
We will see each other tomorrow anyway.
Xiaoman.
Do you think
Xingzhou
would stop coming to the academy?
He must have passed the examination.
From now on,
would he still come to the academy?
I guess so.
I thought so, too.
Initially,
I wanted to confess
my feelings to Xingzhou
after the examination.
It seems like there's
no need to do it hastily.
Look.
Xingzhou dropped this.
He folded it so nicely.
I bet he finished the exam
early back at the hall
and folded this out of boredom.
Look at
the wings
and the neck.
Xiaoman, take a look.
It's exquisite, isn't it?
Please leave me alone.
Minggu.
Yanwan, let's go.
(Jingnv Pavilion)
(Personal profile)
Personal profile?
Eat properly.
Look at you.
Father.
Do you know what a personal profile
of the examination is?
You don't know that?
It's a verification for the participants.
Yes.
Your mother is right.
During the examination,
the students' identity are
verified with that.
After the examination, they will
be submitted back to the facility.
What happens if they aren't submitted?
That means they did not participate
in the examination
or something went wrong
during the examination.
What could possibly go wrong?
Things like cheating.
By the way,
a few days ago,
I told you to withdraw
some cash from the bank.
Is everything done?
Yes.
I placed them in your chiffonier.
When the new store launches,
you may take it.
Father. Mother.
I'm done.
I shall excuse myself.
What?
You barely ate anything.
What...
Is she ill?
It's good that she's gone.
Nobody wants to hear
the problems of the business.
Su Tingshan
opened a new store at Tongzhou
before us.
He's planning to meddle in
Wujiang Prefecture as well.
This time, Su Chang Ji must
acquire the store first
in order to let him know that
Wujiang Prefecture
isn't a place he could
meddle in as he pleases.
That's right.
The side branch of Su Family
has been coveting Su Chang Ji.
I'm telling you.
He
had better not show up in Wujiang Prefecture
or I'll beat him to pulp.
Listen to you.
Why are you so happy?
Stop reading. Let's eat.
Come on.
Let's eat.
(Wujiang Examination Hall)
Lady,
this is the examination hall.
The examination is over.
There's no one in there.
Please leave.
Fellow guards,
it's urgent,
and I need to talk to the examiner.
Please let me in.
I said,
the examination is over.
The results will be
released after a while.
You may inquire the examiner then.
This is extremely urgent.
Please let me in.
What's going on?
Let me in!
Lady!
Sir.
She barged in.
I couldn't stop her.
You're dismissed.
Yes.
What's the matter?
Sir,
I would like to find out,
among those who failed to submit
their personal profile,
is there a man by the surname of Zhong?
I think so.
What's the matter?
Did something happen
that he failed to submit his profile?
He cheated during the examination.
He
is banned from taking the exam ever after.
All right.
I shouldn't have told you so much.
Hurry up and leave.
Sir,
did you make a mistake?
Zhong Ziyan is an upright man.
He'd never cheat, sir.
Sir, it must have been a mistake.
Sir, please investigate the matter.
I'm sure you made a mistake.
I'm begging you.
He'd never cheat,
sir.
(Brothel)
The raging wind blows,
and the clouds are enmeshed along.
Sir.
After achieving triumph and peace,
I returned home in glory.
Seeking a hero to protect
all corners of the state.
Xu Shu!
Lady!
Get out of the way!
You can't go in there!
Xu Shu!
You can't enter!
Why did you frame Xingzhou?
Lady Su!
Get out of the way!
You should return!
Why did you harm Zhong Ziyan?
That's enough.
Get lost!
Do you know how important
the examination is to Xingzhou?
Why did you frame him?
Xingzhou?
Zhong Ziyan is the Head of Nencao Hall.
Xingzhou had no idea.
Go with me to clarify the situation
in the examination hall.
Come with me.
Why should I?
I'm not allowed to undertake
the examination myself.
Why should I help him?
Lady Su,
the examination is important
to your Xingzhou.
What about me?
My father has no expectations for me.
Look at me now.
I am not even as valuable as a dog.
Sons and daughters of
noble households like you
would never understand
what I go through.
Whatever you said
has nothing to do with Xingzhou.
He was unaware.
He had no idea.
He worked all his life
for the examination.
His whole life is ruined by you.
Please help him out, okay?
I'm begging you.
Please help him out
and clarify the situation
in the examination hall.
I'm begging you.
He accepted my money.
Therefore, he must do his job.
Since I've failed,
he
should suffer with me.
Hold on.
Tell me.
What will it take
for you to help Xingzhou?
Fine.
Give me 500 strings of 1,000 cash.
I'll testify for his innocence.
500 strings of 1,000 cash?
Fine.
I'll bring you the cash tomorrow.
You're coming with me to clarify
everything in the examination hall.
Hold on!
Lady Su.
What's your relationship
with Zhong Ziyan?
I'm in love with him.
Pass the cash to Madam Su later.
All right.
Watch it closely.
Lady Xie.
Why do you come home so late?
I was studying at the academy
and lost track of time.
Where are my books?
Zhu Momo came back this afternoon
and took the books by
the Commandery Prince's orders.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Lady Xie.
(Sleeping Room)
Your Highness.
Mr. Zhong is not like himself today.
The civil examination has just ended.
He should be elated.
Why is he drowning in wine?
He's probably exhausted.
I shouldn't have taken him out
for a drink.
By the way, Your Highness,
Zipei came to the mansion
to borrow some books.
Zhu Momo sent her to retrieve
them from Lotus Gardens
and said it was by your orders.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Why did you take my possessions?
Why did you take my books away?
Lingniang asked for them,
so I gave them to her.
What's wrong?
Lingniang wanted them,
so you gave them to her?
Yes.
She's my fiancee.
Whatever she asks for,
no matter what it takes,
I'm willing to do it for her.
Since you have no feelings for me,
why do you care?
Fine.
I understand.
Stand right there!
This isn't a place for you to
come and go as you please.
Help me get changed.
You shall serve me in bed tonight.
What?
Since you've not left,
you're still my concubine.
Carry out your obligation.
What's the matter?
Are you afraid?
Let go of me.
Why are you so eager to
participate in the examination?
Are you doing this to leave me?
Yes.
I want to leave you.
I'm doing this to leave you.
Who do you think you are?
Who do you think you are
to play around
with me?
Do you find it fun?
As you watch me
wag my tail like a dog and beg
for your attention repeatedly?
Do you find it fun?
Yes.
Isn't it great that you'd end up
being with Shen Zhaowen?
Since you grew up together,
since you both are of equal positions,
since you're both engaged,
isn't it great that you end up
being together with her?
Why did you mess with me?
Keep this in mind.
Even if I marry Shen Zhaowen,
I'd never allow you to leave me.
Even if I turn Wujiang Prefecture
upside down,
you're not allowed to take
a step out of my mansion!
In the summer of first year of Jianxing,
Zhu Bao led a rebellion to
conquer Zangke Prefecture.
The uprising begun with
Yong Kai of Yizhou County.
Governor of Liu, Zhang Yi was exiled.
He refused to yield.
Prince of Yi led an army
of rebellion and triumphed.
By the end of the year,
Daughter of Zhang Clan
was titled as the Empress.
Lady Xie.
(To Xiaoman)
(Lonely Boat At Night, volume four)
Fellow students,
the discussion of policy
for today's examination
centers around the diplomatic mission
of Princess Consort Ming.
Please rise to deliver your insights.
After the speaker sits down,
the rest may rise to
voice your opinions.
You may begin to
express your opinions.
The discussion begins.
Back then, State of Han and
the Xiongnu Empire were in dispute.
The entire state was exhausted.
The people were suffering.
Princess Consort Ming, Zhaojun,
volunteered to marry Huhanye.
She spent the next 60 years
in the north.
She developed Xiongnu and
the people lived in abundance.
Peace reigned for three generations.
Wars ceased and the people have peace.
Such political insight
and noble sacrifice
should serve as an exemplar
to the ladies of this age.
Xiaoman.
Xiaoman,
it's your turn.
Zhaojun ventured into
a diplomatic mission.
She deserves the respect and
admiration of the posterity.
However, I believe it was
inferred by causality.
In my opinion,
Princess Consort Ming
volunteered to the north
not necessarily to
quell the war between both nations.
It was but a game of fate.
She was forced by the circumstances.
Recorded in the Book of Later Han,
Zhaojun spent years in the palace
without meeting His Majesty.
Grudge and dismay were accumulated.
From this, one could imply
that she was long tired of
living her days like a caged bird.
On one hand, it's the perpetual solitude
of 20 years in the harem.
On the other hand, it's being 3,000
miles away from her motherland.
Princess Consort Ming chose
the latter opportunity for herself.
Princess Consort Ming's
departure up north
was praised as a virtue for generations.
How dare you proclaim such presumptions?
You show contempt
for a lady's sacrifice for the country.
You show contempt towards the noble
sacrifice Princess Consort Ming
made for her people.
Princess Consort Ming's departure
was praised and respected.
However, in my opinion,
the people of Han betrayed her.
She was forced to give up her happiness.
Her free will to control her life
was diminished.
However,
by her strong will and tenacity,
coincidentally,
she saved an entire nation.
As a delicate woman,
Princess Consort Ming
was forced to marry
a foreign man she has never met,
and forced to spend the rest
of her life with him.
After she passed away,
she could only be buried in the desert,
forbidden from returning
to her homeland.
To Princess Consort Ming,
isn't it a great sacrifice?
If what you uphold is true,
Princess Consort Ming was tired of
living her life as a caged bird,
so she volunteered to embark up north,
why were the songs of grievances
sung through the ages?
From the palace to Xiongnu,
isn't that just moving from one cage
to another?
Lady Xie,
do you concur?
Spring is everlasting.
The willows never sleep.
The lonely moon lit up the skies while
the stars kept each other company.
In the future,
dreams are far from reach,
remaining in Yuyangli Village.
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪