Until two months ago, my life was smooth sailing.
"Gift yourself an affluent tomorrow."
But out of nowhere, I was laid off
and divorced.
[Divorce Forms]
Losing both my job and family
somehow landed me a job as a caretaker.
- Who are you?
- He's our caretaker.
- You're...
- Hold it!
Nishijima has been pushing herself lately.
I wish to date Nishijima.
Excuse me?
I won't lose to you.
Why does this man consider me his rival for this woman?
Please take good care of Nishijima.
H-Hold it!
One thing before you go.
This is all a misunderstanding.
"A misunderstanding"?
Let me set things straight.
I don't feel...
- anything for her─
- Really?
Yes.
She's just one of the residents.
I was serious... about my confession earlier.
Good night.
Hey─
I'm back.
Then, if you'll excuse me.
Itsuka-san's co-worker has declared his affection.
What?
I happened to witness his confident confession.
He shall now be called "the communicative co-worker."
[Maison Ginseiso]
It's 38.7 degrees.
Every try comes out the same.
My head hurts.
I have chills too.
You definitely have a cold.
Maintaining your health is part of your job as a businessperson.
Having people take time off
decreases the efficiency of the company and leads to loss.
Still, you can't help catching a cold.
I'll go get your medicine.
Hello, Nishijima?
I saw your message. So it's a cold?
Yes.
[Katori Shun]
She has a fever and a cough.
What are you doing there?
She says her throat hurts, and it's difficult to talk.
You haven't taken advantage of the weakened Nishijima, right?
Of course not!
[Unexpected - Love Story in Maison Ginseiso]
Timing and subtitles brought to you by
🧺 The Housekeepers Team 🧹 @Viki.com
Sister Nao,
about my offer at Pegasus Beer...
Oh, that.
You failed, didn't you?
How did you know?
If it had gone well, you'd tell me immediately.
At least I don't need to find a new caretaker now.
If anything, I'm thankful you didn't get hired.
Sorry.
Anyway, you'd better remain aware of your job as caretaker.
Don't take advantage of vulnerable resident girls.
I already said I'd never-
I want to eat some clementines.
I'd like some seltzer.
Oh, no!
My humidifier ran out of water.
I'm coming in.
Hey, what are you doing?
Exactly what you think I am.
I want to win this competition, no matter what.
Why are you so particular about Kazuki Beer?
[Design Plans]
It's almost like you're avenging your parents.
In a way, I guess I am.
I remember now!
You said your co-worker once messed up a presentation, right?
Are you avenging that person?
This isn't a period drama, you know.
If it were,
then an evil magistrate like you
(T/N: the typical villain in Japanese period dramas)
would be punished for sure.
How am I the evil magistrate?
You sure hold your grudges.
That's the last thing I want to hear from someone who was fired.
You're bothering me.
Please leave.
Ever heard of the saying, "Rest is the best medicine"?
Jeez, she's so stubborn.
Hot!
Oh.
Hello.
I've come to check up on Nishijima.
Please come in.
You really didn't have to visit.
But people get especially lonely when they're sick.
Besides,
I'm concerned about a few things.
"A few things"?
Remember that Chinese place we used to eat at
back when we were new hires?
Well...
Zukyu Hanten?
Yes.
Anyway, I went and asked them to make you a batch of this.
Congee?
And just the way I like it too.
Here's your tea.
Your throat hurts too, right?
Here.
I bought you some propolis spray.
(T/N: bee-produced substance believed to be anti-inflammatory)
And this jar is manuka honey.
I thought these would help out.
Thanks. They will.
Sorry, you should go get some rest.
I'll take her from here.
Please don't let us interrupt your work.
Let's go.
My porridge isn't so bad, either.
Nishijima, why are you working?
Because...
I can't push all the work onto you.
Well, I welcome it.
After all, we're a team.
Thank you, Katori.
What could those two be talking about?
Impossible, I am worried about her?
No, it can't be.
I'm only like this because my workload will increase
if her cold is passed on to the others.
According to our last meeting,
the overall concept will be as follows.
This direction looks good to me.
The reason why you're working so hard
is because this competition is run by Kazuki Beer?
It's because I don't want to experience such misery ever again.
If only our client this time
was the one who critiqued you two years back.
Why?
Because then you'd be able to prove yourself to him.
How long is he planning on sticking around?
No. He won't ask to stay the night, will he?
It's me.
I'm coming in.
He's the one taking advantage of a sick girl.
Is everything all right?
Yes.
One thing before I go.
That was a misunderstanding.
Pardon?
I would never take advantage of a vulnerable girl.
O-Oh.
I see.
Excuse me, but haven't we met somewhere before?
Sorry?
No, I've mistaken you for someone else.
In that case, I'll be back, Mr. Caretaker.
You have no right to call me "caretaker"!
Oh.
Oh, the communicative co-worker.
Pardon?
May I have a moment of your time?
- Why?
- Have you observed any of the following:
obsession with Itsuka, increased heart rate,
loss of sleep or appetite?
What?
Seeing as my only data regarding romance are two-dimensional,
I couldn't help but be curious.
Excuse my rudeness for asking.
Am I... a research subject?
I came to visit Nishijima.
Welcome in.
I got these since they were cute.
Please come in.
Wait, look. Isn't this a typo?
- I'll fix it.
- I'll do it.
- No, it's fine.
- I insist. Besides, I type faster.
It's fine, really.
Seriously, give it a-
You have a package, Sir.
Oh, hello.
I made you some porridge.
It's 38.5?
It hasn't gone down.
You're getting your priorities mixed up between work and health.
Or maybe you're just too giddy that he asked you out?
Even if I was, that's none of your business.
He made me his rival
and caught me up in all this.
It's a real pain.
Your snide remarks are only making this cold worse.
Eat up.
What?
Don't expect this any other day.
Here.
It's warm.
I'm full.
Sleep for now. You still have a fever.
To tell you the truth,
I haven't gotten any sleep.
What?
The competition weighs on my mind,
and I get anxious.
Can you stay here until I fall asleep?
[Maison Ginseiso]
But I didn't... ask him to clean my room.
You'll catch... a cold.
Congratulations on your recovery, Itsuka-san.
[Unexpected - Love Story in Maison Ginseiso]
- Thank you.
- I'm glad you've gotten some rest.
You look much better.
Who nursed you back to health?
Let me guess. Your boyfriend?
Maybe he caught her cold for her!
How dreamy!
Stand back. You two will catch it, too.
- Yes, Ma'am.
Do you want to celebrate your recovery tonight?
That's strange.
I'm making no progress in my chores today.
I still have to sun-dry the futons
and buy ingredients for dinner.
It's no good, I'm losing strength...
Why hasn't our caretaker
[I don't need dinner tonight.]
read my message yet?
Let me know if you're going to be late.
The person you've called is currently unavailable.
Nishijima, is something wrong?
I just need to run to my place really quick.
I'll be right back.
♫ If we could rather look into each other's eyes, embrace ♫
♫ and say it's love ♫
♫ This is love! Is this love? ♫
Hey, Mr. Caretaker?
♫ If only those two could be more honest ♫
♫ Surely then they'll cherish ♫
Mr. Caretaker?
Are you not home?
Mr. Caretaker!
He's...
He's dead!
I'm not dead.
But...
I have a headache
and chills.
What did Itsuka say?
[Sorry! Our caretaker caught a cold. Can we reschedule today?]
She wants to reschedule our plans today
because her caretaker has a fever.
Seriously?
Would Itsuka go that far for him?
- Do you know him?
- I more than know him.
He's the one who gave her a hard time, right?
What?
[Maison Ginseiso]
[Unexpected - Love Story in Maison Ginseiso]
A cold? You really aren't managing your health well.
I caught yours.
"Having people take time off decreases the efficiency of the company"
"and leads to loss," right?
- I'll make dinner.
- No need.
Nao-san will get takeout tonight.
We ran out of detergent for the bath, and I didn't buy it.
Suzu-chan will get some on her way home.
- I need to clean the vent.
- It doesn't have to be done today.
Sure, but I'll feel bad.
I've accomplished my tasks daily, without fail.
"I need to do this."
"I'm the only one who can."
Pardon?
Hasn't that always been your mindset?
Why this method? Surely there must be something more efficient!
I'll do the rest myself.
[Juntaku: The Affluent Ale. Gift yourself an affluent tomorrow]
Even when you were struggling
or at a standstill,
you always told yourself you could handle it alone.
In fact...
- I did that.
- That's only because
you assume that relying on others is a loss.
You don't want to be a burden.
Kou-chan!
You've convinced yourself to be alone.
Am I wrong?
If anything ever goes awry,
don't just bear with it.
Instead, ask us for help.
You should try relying on others for a change, Mr. Caretaker.
Remember, you're no longer living alone.
What?
Oh, no.
This is not good.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by
🧺 The Housekeepers Team 🧹 @Viki.com
Mr. Caretaker?
Laugh all you want.
[Shitara Kouichi]
[Kazuki Beer: Shitara Kouichi]
Kazuki Beer's Product Planning Department?
The client you struggled with two years back may be in charge again.
Don't worry. He's...
He's long gone.
♫ The noisy city comes to a halt ♫
♫ Your scent when you pass by makes me involuntarily turn around ♫
♫ As if I want to dive headfirst into a troublesome problem ♫
♫ When we meet by chance next time, I'll do something about it ♫
♫ If we could rather look into each other's eyes, embrace and say it's love ♫
♫ This is love! Is this love? ♫
Why am I crying... in front of this woman?
♫ Surely then they'll cherish whatever tomorrow brings ♫
♫ This is my life ♫
[Preview]
What is this feeling?
[Is this anxiousness "love"?]
Please take care of me from today.
[A rival joins their humble abode!]
Are the leeks ready?
[The new guy is a puppy-like, high-achiever guy.]
Why am I helping him?
Mr. Caretaker, do you like me?
[Our former elite finally confesses?]
So, I mean, I...
What is she doing in a place like this?