ROMANCE IN THE HOUSE
Louder than your friend.
-One, two!
Strong enough to break down the wall.
Good job.
Master, show us a flying kick.
-That's random.
-It'll look cool.
-Show us, Master.
-A flying kick!
-Show us!
-All right. Quiet down.
-I'll show you only once.
-Okay!
Master, you use a flying kick
to fight the villains, right?
What?
What on earth is it?
What's the reason, you bastard?
I told you to let go. Let go!
Get your hands off right this instant!
Honey!
Well…
JPLUS
Is there an event in the store today?
There's an event, indeed.
Look over there.
-You're so cool.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Please use a cart next time.
Excuse me, would you please get me
that item down from the shelf?
He teaches children
at a taekwondo gym in the evening.
And he's 28 years old.
How do you know that?
He's well-known as Mr. Handsome Back
in the company.
It's all thanks to you.
Me? Why?
Remember when you passed out?
-Oh, no.
-Ms. Byeon.
What should we do?
Excuse me, please help us.
-Hurry up.
-Carry her.
Be careful.
Ms. Byeon.
Oh, no.
Where did Superman suddenly come from?
Thanks to him, everyone has forgotten
all about what happened
with your obnoxious ex-boyfriend.
Excuse me.
I have something to tell you.
That day, your parents…
JPLUS
SECURITY, NAM TAE-PYEONG
Mr. Nam Tae-pyeong,
I have a favor to ask of you.
What is it?
Please don't talk about
what happened that day in the mart.
If anyone tells my mom
about what happened that day,
I'll think that you spread the story and…
And I'll get you fired
with the authority of the head office.
"The authority of the head office"?
Well…
I wasn't going to talk nonsense.
I wanted to apologize to you
for kicking your father.
I'm sorry.
No need to apologize for that.
It was satisfying.
"Satisfying"?
Monthly rent.
That'll be free for you.
Why isn't she… There she is.
Just a moment.
Hello, we're here to view Unit 102.
-Okay. Let's go inside.
-Okay.
-Hold on.
-Hello.
Hello.
We're sorry,
but we're no longer showing our place.
-What?
-Excuse me?
Gosh, what are you talking about?
We're not moving.
EPISODE 3
THE GREAT BYEON-SBY'S SECRET
You fell for his promise
to waive the rent?
We pay 700,000 won a month.
That's almost 10 million a year.
There's no need to waste
your hard-earned money for rent.
It isn't a waste.
It is one of the reasons I work so hard.
Exactly. We can save up more for key money
and move to a better place.
We can take out another loan.
I promised to find a way.
We already got loans
to pay the key money for this place.
We can't take out another loan.
Realistically, it's impossible
to move right away.
Mom, are you in your right mind?
Yes, I am.
You'll live with Father?
In the same building?
He's the one who bought it and came back.
Why should we move out?
We can live with our eyes and ears shut.
I can do it.
So can you.
Do you know what our neighbors
are saying about us?
They've always gossiped about us, okay?
Those things don't scare me at all.
Money scares me.
-Are you getting swayed?
-By what?
By Father, who is suddenly rich,
and begging for you back.
Hey, Byeon Mi-rae.
Say that again.
What's swaying me?
The leaves are swaying.
Gosh, it must be windy.
In any case,
that's how it'll be.
Understood?
That's what I'm talking about.
All right.
Who is it?
Can I come in for a second?
I guess your mom accepted my offer.
If you want to be on a power trip
over rent,
just give us the money instead.
Right.
You didn't give a dime for alimony
when you got a divorce.
My mom was only left with a wedding ring.
-Give it to us now.
-I don't want to.
What on earth do you want?
I'm going to seduce your mom again.
Did you remarry several times
after the divorce?
Did those women refuse to live with you?
-Do you want my family register?
-Are you deathly ill?
My medical report too?
Or did you commit a terrible crime?
I just want to live with my wife,
that's all.
She's my mom. I'll live with her.
Byeon Mi-rae, are you anxious…
that I'll steal her from you?
Are you filming a drama?
-Want to make a bet?
-On what?
Want a drink?
What are you doing?
"Pledge."
"If I, Byeon Moo-jin,
fail to seduce…"
"Seduce" sounds a bit… Woo? Reconcile?
Okay.
"…fail to reconcile with Geum Ae-yeon,
I will pay the alimony owed."
How much do you think?
Considering the inflation rate
and overdue interest of 11 years…
You should give us the villa.
Okay.
"As alimony, I'll hand over ownership
of the villa to Geum Ae-yeon."
-And the time limit?
-Four weeks.
Like the consideration period
when getting a divorce.
BYEON MOO-JIN
Sign it.
BYEON MI-RAE
You know that it's legally binding, right?
Of course, I do.
One more thing.
If your mom and I get back together,
you know that you and Hyeon-jae will come
as a bundle, right?
Let's say we get the villa.
You know that you have to pack up
and leave, right?
You can do it!
You can do it, Geum Ae-yeon!
Just focus on the rent.
Money is what's scary.
Byeon Moo-jin is nothing.
My goodness. Hello, sir.
Have a seat. What brings you here?
I want to change the door lock.
Which lock do you want?
Well, a sturdy one that can't be picked.
Do you have trouble sleeping these days?
Your face is pale.
Can I get it changed today?
Of course.
What? It's President Byeon.
What?
Perfect. The landlord should pay
for the door lock.
I'll talk to him for you. Please wait.
President Byeon.
Mr. Jang, do you make signboards too?
Come on, I make everything.
Do you want a new signboard for the villa?
The broken sign proclaims
that there was a fire.
Good idea. That way,
the property value will go up
and you'll make more money.
So tell me.
Where did you invest your money?
Just tell me.
I thought…
that bet was over.
Right.
What kind of sign do you want?
Right. While you're at it,
get a new door lock
for the semi-basement unit.
Here.
Sir.
-What?
-The man from our semi-basement unit?
I had it notarized.
You can't pull out now.
It's our rent for this month.
Take it.
You took cash out for this?
I didn't know your account number.
Is there anything you want to add?
Anything else you want from me.
As for that, I already told you
a long time ago.
Get lost.
Stay away from my family…
until you die.
I guess you forgot.
Seeing that you came back like this.
The promise from 11 years ago
should've been the priority between us.
Since he broke our promise and came back,
he should pay the penalty
as well as all the interest.
Hello, I'll have one iced chocolate--
And an iced Americano
with five espresso shots.
And the biggest size for the Americano.
Okay.
It's on me.
-Because you feel bad?
-Yes.
And to silence me?
That's right.
To repay you for the hospital bill,
I'll buy you a drink
whenever our paths cross.
Here's your Americano.
Wouldn't that kill you?
I drink this to live.
I need caffeine in my blood.
How arrogant of him to buy up the building
just to get back together with Mom.
Let's have another great day.
I'll show him,
make him surrender, and win.
So we can get
our peace back.
Byeon Moo-jin, are you out of your mind?
I did get roped into it.
It's not too late to revoke this.
I'll find out what can be done legally.
I can't revoke it now.
I have my pride.
Byeon Moo-jin, can't you get a grip
of your situation?
Even the greatest love
can't withstand the test of money.
But the two of you…
God… You really think this will work?
Forget it. I'll take care of it,
so just sit still.
Give it back.
I said, give it back.
I have no other choice.
I've already come this far.
I can't back out now.
I have to take it to the end.
Sir, are you home?
Gosh.
-Mr. Jang, what brings you here?
-Hello.
To change your door lock.
Gosh, I'm so forgetful these days.
-How much is it?
-It has already been paid for.
-By whom?
-President Byeon.
President Byeon?
Sir.
My goodness, I forgot my toolbox.
Let me get it from my car.
What? Wait…
Gosh.
Sir.
Yes?
You told me that I looked familiar.
What?
I have something to say.
Sir.
Wait…
Yes, he's better now.
I don't know what got him so startled.
I think he's becoming senile. Yes.
Don't worry. Okay.
Sir, please tell me.
What's so dangerous?
I promise to protect you,
so don't worry, and tell me, okay?
You guys said…
that the new landlord was suspicious.
I think you guys were right about him.
Sorry?
Yes.
I saw
the new landlord.
I saw him the night before the fire.
GANGNAM HOF
I've known President Byeon for years.
He isn't like that. For goodness' sake.
Didn't you see Mr. Choi's reaction?
He's acting that way
because he saw something.
I mean, why would the old landlord
and the new landlord drink together?
If President Byeon knew the old landlord,
why hasn't he said anything?
See? Everyone brushed off my theory.
So…
Did anyone else see something that day?
Anything suspicious.
Perhaps Unit 301 did.
She's just across the hall.
I'll ask.
Hello, Jeong-in.
Yes.
Something suspicious?
Noise? I don't know.
Right. One time, I woke up at night
to the sound of the door slamming shut.
Did you hear anyone's voice?
I heard a young man's voice.
When… When was that?
Wasn't it the day before the fire?
What? Was it?
I think so.
-It was that day!
-See?
Okay. Have a good night.
-My goodness.
To be honest,
I saw something recently.
-President Byeon?
-I've only seen such a tattoo
-in gangster movies.
-That's right.
Never in real life…
But still, since he was Ae-yeon's husband,
I told myself that I was being ridiculous.
In that case,
what I saw suddenly seems very suspicious.
Did you see something too?
Hey! It's Mr. Poop.
Mr. Byeon came out of a police station
and entered a soft tofu restaurant.
It's customary to eat tofu
after serving time in prison.
Hey, that restaurant has…
tasty food.
-It's a well-known restaurant.
-It's true.
But when we put together all the stories,
it's a bit suspicious. Don't you agree?
That's nothing.
To tell you the truth,
I witnessed a decisive scene
on the rooftop this morning.
Hey, Unit 202.
I'm here to hang my blanket.
What are you burning there?
Traces.
After moving to the crime scene,
he brazenly destroyed evidence there.
He's a bold man.
So you got soot
all over the blanket we just washed
and picked up these stupid matches?
No.
This isn't from today.
-What?
Then…
Right after the fire,
I found it on the villa's flower bed.
Does anyone in the villa use matches?
Have you seen anyone use them?
He's the only one!
-Goodness!
-You startled me!
The previous landlord said
that he'd never sell the villa
when he was alive.
-Gosh.
-It's true.
He said that he needed to keep it,
or else his children would abandon him.
Could that be the reason why…
That's why
he set the unit on fire…
and killed the landlord?
You guys must be having a drink.
-Alcohol is going in
-My goodness.
-Hey, Ae-yeon.
All right. Let's take a love shot.
Are you guys dating?
My goodness.
Eun-woo, your grandma
is really drunk today.
Everyone knows my grandma
can drink anyone under the table.
The grilled chicken must be all out.
Yes.
Well, then. Enjoy the food.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Bye.
-She left.
Despite the divorce,
they're still family and have children.
They might be on the same side.
Oh, no. My goodness.
Such a criminal and my Eun-woo
are living in the same building?
I'm more disappointed in Ae-yeon.
We've been neighbors for so many years.
We only have circumstantial evidence.
Until we find hard evidence,
watch your mouth and stay safe.
You should be careful.
Stop asking him how he earned money.
It'll get you seriously hurt.
No way.
My father got you rice cakes
as the new member of the villa.
Okay. Please thank him for me.
It's my first time receiving
moving-in rice cakes in a box.
Grandma, won't we die if we eat this?
Thank you.
-Enjoy.
-Okay. Take care.
Eun-woo, close the door.
Heave-ho.
Carry this. It's yours.
YONGYONG RICE CAKE SHOP
It's the moving-in rice cake.
You liked their sirutteok.
Geum Ae-yeon.
You haven't aged much.
You're still pretty.
And you…
are ridiculously the same.
You'll be in your fifties soon,
but you haven't matured at all.
Thank you
for not moving away.
Mr. Byeon Moo-jin, don't be mistaken.
I'm not living there because of you.
It's because of money.
Don't forget that.
-Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
The PR team's meeting is at 3 p.m.
Let's hurry.
I need to use the restroom.
-Please get the elevator for me.
-Okay.
Ms. Byeon.
-You lunatic!
-Father!
Isn't that Mr. Nam, our CEO?
Ms. Byeon!
-Look…
-Then take care, sir.
Wait…
-Hello.
FATHER
What did I tell you?
I told you not to take
that lousy security job!
Yes, all clear.
How will you
keep the tteokbokki girl quiet?
I'll look into it.
-Had you listened to me--
-Yes, sir.
Ta-da.
It'll take me forever to eat this
by myself.
I'd prefer a discount
on the management fees.
Hey, when will your dad come out?
I still haven't even seen his face.
Right now.
Father.
I'm done. Let's go.
Father, she's Aunt Jeong-in of Unit 301.
We're like family.
I bought some rice cakes.
Please enjoy them.
Okay, thank you.
We're going to eat out.
Let's go, Father.
Well, then.
Bye.
Let's go.
GANGNAM HOF
I guess it's a nice spot.
Any business that opens there
has been successful.
Hyeon-jae, you were
in elementary school back then, right?
Yes.
I was young, so I don't remember much.
Does your mom work
at Mi-rae's company now?
Yes, she works at the free sample booth.
Mi-rae wanted to keep Mom from working,
but Mom insisted on doing something.
So she just works part-time.
Does Mi-rae like her job?
Does she have a boyfriend?
No.
She always says she'd rather use that time
to make more money.
I bet she's never had one.
By the way,
why did you guys stay
in this neighborhood?
Why didn't you start anew somewhere else?
They wanted to show
the people of Yongdong-dong
that we could get back up on our feet.
You know how unyielding
Mom and Mi-rae can be.
Hyeon-jae, take this
and go to the department store.
Buy the most expensive fruit baskets
and give them to all the neighbors.
What? Really?
You guys
have done enough.
From now on,
I'll show them.
Father.
You're like Gatsby.
No.
You're the Great Byeon-sby.
Father.
Hey, Hyeon-jae.
Hello.
It has been a while, Hyeon-jae.
You're all grown up now.
Come by for some barbecue sometime.
I didn't know that bastard still ran
a restaurant in this neighborhood.
Who is he?
After we moved out of a gukbap restaurant,
we rented a semi-basement room.
And that bastard was the landlord.
Did he treat you badly?
He hit on Mom.
What?
He always called Mom
behind his wife's back
and kept trying to barge into our house
when he was drunk.
I seriously wanted to kill that bastard.
Do you know how much you spent
in a single day?
You are neither a philanthropist
nor a billionaire.
I spent it for a good reason.
I know that you'll increase my fortune,
Jae-geol.
Bye, then.
I won't say anything.
Especially not to Ae-yeon.
We're…
complete strangers, okay?
How's your health?
Are you all better now?
Who is it? Is it someone in the company?
Or is it someone we know?
My ear is bleeding.
Come on.
You deserted your colleague and ran.
Sharing information
is the least you can do.
-I'll get going.
-Okay.
-Take care.
-Ms. Byeon, come on.
What are you pestering Ms. Byeon
all day long about?
I think
the CEO's son works at this company.
-Really?
-Are you serious?
But only Ms. Byeon saw the son.
And she won't tell me who he is.
I'm so disappointed in her.
Can we talk for a second?
Why don't you buy me dinner?
Your order is here.
Enjoy the food.
Thank you for the food.
-What you saw earlier--
-Kind indifference.
"Be kind to the customer.
But after receiving the money
and serving their coffee, be indifferent.
That way, the customer
will relax and enjoy their coffee."
It's the secret behind the success
of coffee chains in the US.
It's my workplace motto too.
So please don't explain anything to me.
I really don't want to know about
the company owner's family affairs.
I just want to work in peace.
It really is kind indifference.
Well, we now have the dirt on each other,
so I feel more relieved.
Were you really worried
that I might tell the mart employees?
No.
That's why I wanted to ease your mind too.
Let's continue to be indifferent
and pretend not to know about each other.
Can we, Mr. Nam Tae-pyeong?
Let's do that, Ms. Byeon Mi-rae.
To be honest, it'd be a lie
to say that I'm not curious at all, but…
"You're leading a more tiring life
than I expected."
I'll leave it at that.
And…
And I'll get you fired
with the authority of the head office.
Gosh, it's so embarrassing.
AMILY VILLA
What's this?
A dining table. You said
it was time for a new one.
Really? How much was it?
It's cheap
since it's ready-to-assemble furniture.
Let's go.
Be careful.
What is all this?
Air purifier.
Massage machine.
Coffee machine.
Robot vacuum?
Don't worry about it.
We're returning everything.
Byeon Hyeon-jae!
I'll pull out all your hair
if you miss a single item.
Okay.
I'd like a refund for the fridge too.
Yes, the one with four doors.
I'll keep the tablet PC and smartwatch.
That crazy bastard.
Why did he give the kid his credit card?
-No, it doesn't fit.
-Why not?
Geum Medal, move out of the way.
We don't need four chairs.
Three chairs are enough for us.
-Cheers.
It's nice and comfy.
By the way, tables always come
with a set of four chairs.
Is it what's considered normal?
Who cares?
Once I become an assistant manager,
I'll buy you a new fridge.
Deal.
Let's split the cost
and get one with four doors.
I withdrew my installment savings.
What? Has it already matured?
You don't need to know the details.
-Cheers.
Gosh, my back hurts.
You worked hard.
I want to get a massage.
Mom, shall I give you a massage?
Sure!
Medal, Mi-rae's going to
give me a massage.
Isn't it great?
Cheers.
He gave gifts to everyone
in the neighborhood.
It's a ploy to clean up his image.
Just in case, make sure
you don't touch the rice cake and fruits.
I already threw them away.
He could've poisoned them.
I ate them.
They were perfectly okay. I'm fine.
Perhaps we're overreacting here.
He doesn't seem like someone
who'd do such a thing.
Don't you think he's just a nice landlord?
Haven't you seen photos of criminals?
No one had "criminal" written
on their faces.
Right.
How much longer do we have to
walk on eggshells around them?
I doubt we'll find additional evidence.
Really?
The landlord
got into a fight with someone
in the neighborhood yesterday.
He beat the man to a pulp.
What?
The landlord must really be a criminal.
Maybe that was why
Ae-yeon from Unit 102 divorced him.
Maybe he beat her up.
Gosh, I was really wrong about him.
I feel so bad for Ae-yeon, Mi-rae,
and Hyeon-jae
for having such a man in their family.
I pity ourselves more
for having such a man as a landlord.
Our lives are in danger.
What are we going to do?
Enjoy a free sample!
Really? Okay.
Are you here to get groceries?
Ae-yeon.
Did Mr. Byeon really set
the old landlord's house on fire?
What?
Is Mr. Byeon really an arsonist?
You knew all along, didn't you?
What are you talking about?
Where's the tteokbokki?
What? You jerk.
Hello.
Do you also work here
with my wife and Mi-rae?
Yes.
I'm really sorry about that day.
I misunderstood.
Okay. At least you know now.
I know that
a simple apology isn't enough, but…
I'm truly sorry.
I accept your apology. You can stop now.
Why are you asking me that?
You said that you'd move,
but you're still living there.
-So many things are suspicious.
-Move aside.
I'm not being dramatic.
I can't stand
that such a dangerous man is living
in the same building as my grandson.
I live in fear because of you people!
Excuse me?
Come with me.
Let's talk outside. Come on.
Where will you take me?
What will you do to me?
-Excuse me, call the police.
-Come on. Let's go.
-Hurry up.
-Call the police.
The police.
Please let go of me.
Please call the police.
What are you doing?
Why are you asking Mom about a stranger?
A stranger? This is about your dad.
He's a stranger.
This is obstruction of business.
Do you want to embarrass yourself
by getting dragged out?
Leave.
In the end, Mr. Byeon did it again.
He made the business go under.
What did Mi-rae's mom say?
She called me yesterday,
but I didn't pick up.
I thought she'd ask me to lend her money.
Don't get involved with Mr. Byeon
ever again, understood?
We'll never see him again anyway.
Isn't that right?
-That's right.
Apparently, her husband took out
private loans.
-I feel so bad for her.
-The snack bar was doing so well.
It can't be helped.
-What was that about?
-How scary.
Ms. Byeon, you can work with your mother,
but you can't bring family affairs
to workplace.
I'm sorry. It won't happen again.
You didn't get into too much trouble,
did you?
He just gave me a warning.
Don't worry. Let's go inside.
Tell us the truth now.
-Stop--
-As tenants, we have the right to know.
Stop!
You're all too scared to ask the landlord,
so you pester me,
since I'm the easy target.
Moo-jin set the villa on fire
in order to purchase it?
If he were that daring,
I would've stayed with him.
Let's go.
Why did you talk to her?
Is this what you came back for?
I don't need a pledge
or anything else. Just…
get lost.
Why are you asking Mom about a stranger?
A stranger? This is about your dad.
He's a stranger.
I don't have a dad now.
From today onward, my dad is dead.
Stay away from my family until you die.
Get lost.
Who is it?
It's me, Hyeon-jae!
Why are you so drunk
this early in the evening?
Father.
Father, come here.
Come here.
I…
brought something very important
that could prove your innocence.
Here.
Answer my questions truthfully.
Is it true that you went berserk
while drinking
and beat a man to a pulp yesterday?
Is it true that you have
a huge carp tattoo on your arm?
What?
Is it true that you use matches?
Is it true
that you were with the old landlord
the day before the fire?
Is it true that you were
at the police station due to the fire?
Is it broken?
Father.
Who are you?
FIANCÉ SALON
BYEON MOO-JIN
Ae-yeon.
I'm sorry.
I'm hanging up.
People won't pester you about me anymore.
I'm here regarding the fire that broke out
on the third floor at 83-1 Yongdong-dong.
Sorry? What did you just say?
Yongdong-dong's Family Villa Fire Case.
I came of my own volition.
Two hours have passed,
but it's still quiet.
-I don't see a police van yet either.
-Then go inside and check.
That'd be too dangerous!
I'll wait a few more minutes and…
Oh! He's coming out.
We should sit down and talk.
-I don't have time for--
-The police serve the people!
He's yelling at a police officer.
I think he's resisting arrest.
Let's go to Yongdong-dong.
Just leave, okay?
What?
What was that?
Why did the police officer go in alone?
I'm… I mean…
I'm sorry.
Tell everyone to gather around.
Right now.
So I'm on my way to Gangnam Hof.
What does Father want to talk about?
No way.
He wouldn't, would he?
Father!
Where's Jeong-hyeok?
I don't know.
He hung up after saying that.
Perhaps that jerk lost his temper
and killed my husband!
Come on.
I'll end him!
No way, that can't be it.
Father.
-Honey!
-Are you okay?
I was going to get some help
from governmental authority.
But they're busy serving the public.
"Governmental authority"?
Wouldn't it be the opposite?
So let's use this opportunity…
to put an end to all.
President Byeon, let's calm down.
Because of this…
I've always been a fan of Chow Yun-fat.
I was being pretentious.
So you found this
right after the fire and before I moved in
in front of the villa, right?
Yes.
But
shouldn't you be more suspicious about
how I bought the villa
that was never on the market
as soon as the owner passed?
Father.
The man who was with the old landlord
before the day of the fire
-was me, indeed.
-What?
And I did visit the police station
because of that.
I got interviewed and gave them my alibi.
Why?
What did you do to him that night?
I mean, what did you say to him?
I tried
to persuade him to sell the villa to me.
There was a reason why
I had to purchase this villa
out of all the properties out there.
You know the reason already.
If you were so curious about
whether or not I was the arsonist,
you should've asked me directly.
Why pester someone
who had nothing to do with it?
Bring out some alcohol.
What? Well…
Oh, okay.
For goodness' sake.
President Byeon.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
I, of all people, should've trusted you.
Hurry up and apologize to him!
-My goodness.
-Okay.
Here you go.
What do you think you're doing?
Are you kidding me?
You asked me to bring some alcohol.
Oh, you want soju? Soju and beer?
-Bring enough alcohol for everyone.
-What?
If you leave this pub sober
and walking on two legs,
I'll end you.
I…
will pick up the tab.
What?
-My goodness.
-You're the best.
Father!
-Honey.
-Gosh, President Byeon.
-Hurrah.
-You're ridiculous.
Hurrah.
-Please adjust the price.
-In that case…
LANDLORD
Please excuse me.
A PRANK WITH THE CANDLE
THAT NEVER GOES OUT
What's this?
A PRANK WITH THE CANDLE
THAT NEVER GOES OUT
I'm sorry.
I refuse to get lost.
-President Byeon, we love you so much!
My goodness.
EPILOGUE
I didn't know that bastard still ran
a restaurant in this neighborhood.
Did he treat you badly?
He hit on Mom.
He always called Mom
behind his wife's back
and kept trying to barge into our house
when he was drunk.
You can take it easy.
I'm trying to remove the knots.
What the…
They say a leopard can't change his spots.
What do you think you're doing?
You know what? Bastards like you
are the most sickening.
Bastards like you only harass young women,
single mothers, and weak people!
But I'm strong and rich.
If I see you again
around this neighborhood,
I'll kill you.
ROMANCE IN THE HOUSE
She's the spitting image of her father.
I plan to change my last name.
I'll be Geum Mi-rae.
Bring it on.
When did they become so distant?
A rival you never wanted to lose to.
Who on earth is the CEO's son?
-Why do you ask?
-Must you ask?
I'll seduce him.
Byeon Moo-jin?
Still, I have to do it
if I want to score big.
You won't tell me, right?
I'll ask him then.
Your mom disappeared.
What did you say?
Subtitle translation by: Park Dong-joo