♪Suddenly, you showed up♪
♪Who stole away those years♪
♪Oh, night and day♪
♪Oh, it's been a long time♪
♪Pass through the bustling world
in the daytime♪
♪Circumvent love at night♪
♪Day after day, year after year♪
♪I wake up and close my eyes
before it gets dark♪
♪But when the day breaks into the night♪
♪It makes me believe
that there's still love♪
♪If you want it, if I want it♪
♪It's a vow of night and day♪
♪It's a vow of day and night♪
[Blooming]
[Episode 25]
Tantan, I'm really happy
that you come back with me.
Then let's collect
the lotus seeds together,
liquidate the Demon Lord,
and take revenge for you.
You've traveled all day.
It's time to rest.
Prepare two guest rooms,
one in the front yard
and one in the back.
Yes.
Stay with me in the front yard.
Well...
Cui Chen and I are far apart.
We haven't seen each other
for a long time.
Don't you want to talk to me?
I do, but...
Tantan.
Let's listen to the host.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll go ask out about the lotus seed.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
Miss Feng.
I have something to ask you.
I have nothing to say to you.
We didn't know each other
before the Changluo Town.
Why do you
have such deep prejudice against me?
Heartless people are forgetful indeed.
I'm asking you to leave.
I haven't finished my question yet.
Where did you get
the jade pendant you gave Tantan?
Of course it's mine.
Have you seen it somewhere else?
My late friend
had a same one.
She treasured it a lot,
and said her best sister also had one,
but she never told me her name.
Now I know who that person is.
Looks like I was careless.
Lian Wen did like you a lot back then.
She even showed you her jade pendant.
Did you give it to Tantan
because you think she's Lian Wen?
Well,
if Tantan is Lian Wen,
do you want to kill her again?
Feng Bao, what happened back then
was a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding?
You had the sword,
and I saw her die by it.
How was it a misunderstanding?
I don't have to explain it to you.
You don't want to or you can't?
You brought us to Wanfang City.
What's your purpose?
What do you think?
I don't know what your purpose is.
But I'm warning you,
Tantan is Tantan,
and Lian Wen is Lian Wen.
She's not a substitute for anyone.
I won't let you hurt her.
How ridiculous.
A heartless hypocrite
actually said that to me.
Aren't you afraid?
Afraid of what?
Afraid that Tantan is Lian Wen,
and she'll remember everything.
I'll say it one last time,
what happened back then
was a misunderstanding.
I didn't do anything wrong
to Lian Wen.
Afraid that Tantan is Lian Wen,
and she'll remember everything.
(Tantan, if you are Lian her,)
(will you hate me?)
(Will you believe the truth I tell you?)
What's wrong? You look mad.
Here.
Have a candy.
These are peanut candies
specially prepared for you.
Cui Chen said there is a lotus seed
in Wanfang City. Is it true?
Looks like you know it.
Over these years,
I've been absorbing
the spiritual power of the lotus seed
to increase my magic power,
so that I could lead the people
to rebuild the city.
I've been looking for the lotus seeds
for so many years,
but you've been keeping it from me.
A hundred years ago,
we saw how scary the Demon Lord was.
A single lotus seed can't hurt him.
Now the people of Wanfang City
need this lotus seed even more.
What about the hatred
of the past hundred years?
I'm sorry.
As the guardian of the city,
my duty is to ensure the safety
of Wanfang City.
Fine.
Do your job well as a guardian.
Revenge is not your concern.
Tell me where the lotus seed is.
I can't tell you.
If you won't say,
then stay out of my business.
Feng Bao, why did you bring
Cui Chen and Zhao Tantan
into the city?
She's Lian Wen.
Lian When?
She died a hundred years ago.
She is Lian Wen.
She just lost her memory.
I brought her here this time
to revive her memory,
then we can seek revenge together.
Feng Bao.
Before Uncle Feng died,
he told you to lead the people
to live a good life.
If you keep living in hatred,
you'll be exhausted.
But my father and sister died.
The Demon Lord and Cui Chen
destroyed my life
and my family.
I must avenge this.
Cui Chen?
He's the one who killed Lian Wen.
Cui Chen and Zhao Tantan
are skillful in magic power.
You mustn't do anything reckless.
Otherwise, you'll not only hurt yourself,
but also bring disaster
to the people of the city.
Don't worry, I know what I'm doing.
I only need to keep Cui Chen away,
then I can make Tantan
realize she's Lian Wen.
How are you going to do it?
Stay out of it.
[Feng Mansion]
Miss Tantan.
Who is it?
It's me, Agua.
Lady Feng asked me
to take you to see Uncle Song.
Who is Uncle Song?
Lady Feng said he's the one here
who is most likely to know
where the lotus seed is.
Let's find Cui Chen and leave together.
Lady Feng has sent someone
to inform Mr. Cui.
You can go first.
Okay.
Tantan.
Where's Tantan?
Come with me
if you want to know where Tantan is.
Uncle Song?
Are you looking for the lotus seed?
Yes.
I heard there's a lotus seed
in Wanfang City.
Feng Bao said you're most likely
to know about it.
Choose one.
Choose what?
The jade.
I don't like jewelry.
It's for carving.
Can I not carve it?
That's my rule.
I'll choose this one.
Tantan is in there.
If you want to see her, follow me.
(There is the scent of the lotus seed.)
Where's Tantan?
I have my plans for her. Don't worry.
You should think about
how to beg me to let you out.
Well,
is the esteemed Mu Bai Zhenren
also scared?
You tricked me into coming here.
What's your purpose?
[Spirit Tablet of Lian Wen]
Cui Chen, you keep saying
it was a misunderstanding back then.
Do you dare to say in front of Lian Wen
that you didn't kill her?
Of course I dare.
I've been an honorable man.
I said I didn't kill Lian Wen.
That means I didn't kill her.
Lian Wen, this is the man you loved.
I clearly saw him
plunge his sword into your body,
but now he won't admit it.
Sometimes, what you see may not be true.
I used Dongxu Skill...
Enough.
You just stay here
and explain it to Lian Wen.
Polishing jade requires patience.
First, rough polishing,
then fine polishing, washing,
and finally applying oil and wax.
Just being a human being.
You need patience
and endurance to achieve great things.
Do you remember?
Remember what??
I'm not carving anymore.
Do you know it or not?
I'll leave if you don't know.
What do you want?
Where is the lotus seed?
I didn't know
there are so many secret books
of various sects in Wanfang City.
Lian Wen,
what else did you keep from me?
There's something in the jade trowel.
The lotus seed's scent
becomes strong suddenly.
It must be here.
It's the lotus seed indeed.
This jade trowel has a spirit.
Are you the Feng Zhai,
the late Lord of Wanfang?
That's me.
Tell me
how you released me.
I used the Qingyuan Sect's
out-of-body power.
I'm Cui Chen of the Qingyuan Sect.
You killed my daughter, my Lian Wen!
Elder Feng, there's a misunderstanding.
There are so many secret books
on magic arts.
You should have heard of
Qingyuan Sect's Dongxu Skill.
You can have it.
Why are you giving this to me?
Besides, jade is fragile.
Can a trowel made of jade be used?
Jade is fragile,
but it can nourish plants and trees.
I'm done carving.
It's been a day,
but it's still not finished.
Go get some rest.
We broke Father's favorite jade trowel.
We should be punished.
I'll buy him ten trowels.
Jade is fragile,
but it can nourish plants and trees.
The purpose of polishing jade
is to refine your characters.
Father.
Why do you have to tend plants
with jade?
Won't it be easily damaged?
I'll get you an iron one.
The more precious something is,
the more careful you should be.
Feng Bao, you're unsettled.
How will you be able to take on the role
of being the leader of Wanfang?
Father.
Feng Bao just wants to make you
a better and stronger trowel.
Feng Bao.
Lian Wen.
They're family.
Lian Wen, are you remembering something?
I'm not Lian Wen.
I'm Zhao Tantan.
The situation was urgent back then.
I wanted to pass my sword
through Lian Wen's body
and kill the assailant behind her,
and then explain to her
that Dongxu Skill
wouldn't hurt her at all.
Maybe it was my hesitation earlier
that made her stop trusting me.
She hated me so much
that she wanted to take revenge on me
with her life.
As spirits, we have our own destiny.
Lian Wen had been a stubborn girl.
No one can stop her
from what she wants to do.
After Wanfang City was destroyed
by the Demon Lord,
the two of them stayed
in this secret chamber
and studied all the secret books
I collected.
Lian Wen learned the Xilan Flower Curse
during that time.
I apologize on behalf of my daughter.
Elder Feng, please rise.
Elder Feng, then how did Lian Wen
get to the Qingyuan Sect?
They found the secret
of the Seven-Leaf Lotus
in one of the books
and wanted to use this divine treasure
of the Qingyuan Sect
to take revenge on the Demon Lord.
Lian Wen.
I'm useless.
Now you have to go to the Qingyuan Sect
to steal the Seven-Leaf Lotus.
Feng Bao, what are you talking about?
That's what I should do
for Wanfang City and Father.
Besides,
I'm naturally able
to conceal my demonic aura.
I'm the perfect one
to go to the Qingyuan Sect.
Speaking of that,
you must always remember
not to show your demonic token
when you're out there,
or you'll be in danger.
See,
you revealed yourself
once I mentioned it.
You must remember,
you're different
from the other lotus spirits.
They have five petals,
but you have seven.
That's why you can't be found out.
Okay.
I got nervous when you mentioned it.
And then I revealed it.
Don't worry.
Father taught me
how to hide my demonic token.
I still remember.
If only
they hadn't walked out of here,
Lian Wen wouldn't have died.
Lian Wen!
Are you Lian Wen's older sister?
That's right. You finally remembered.
I trusted you so much.
Why did you deceive me?
I'm sorry, Lian Wen.
I wanted to tell you a long time ago,
but you've been rejecting
everything about yourself,
not to mention the fact
that you are Lian Wen.
That's why...
So, you've been so good to me
only because you see me as
Lian Wen's substitute, right?
You've recovered your memories.
Why are you afraid to admit it?
That's not my memory.
It's an illusion
that you made me see with magic.
That's not true.
It's your real memory.
If you don't believe me,
you can look into the Mirror of Truth.
The True Mirror of the Tianyin Palace?
Yes.
It can reveal the demonic token
of all spirits.
Lian Wen.
I'm not Lian Wen,
and I won't look into it.
I'm not a spirit either.
Master never said I'm a spirit.
You have to be brave and face yourself.
You are Lian Wen.
I didn't know
how long they had been gone.
One day, Feng Bao came back and said
that Lian Wen was missing.
She cried in front of me
for three days and nights.
She kept saying that she harmed Lian Wen
and didn't deserve to be her sister.
Elder Feng.
Actually,
on the night before the wedding,
Lian Wen told me she was a spirit.
If I had asked one more question
and known about her heavy past,
maybe all this wouldn't have happened.
Mu Bai.
Will you always trust me?
Why are you asking it?
Nothing.
I just want to know
if you'll always trust me
no matter what happens.
I'll always trust you
Mu Bai.
I'm a lotus spirit.
You...
I see.
You can't accept it.
I'll leave the Qingyuan Sect tonight.
I only have one question.
Do you really
want to marry me?
Of course I do.
Then it's good.
Everything else can be solved.
Really?
Really really.
But what happened on the wedding day
was unexpected.
It's also my fault
that it has come to this.
Maybe being locked
in this secret chamber by Feng Bao
is my punishment.
I know about Feng Bao.
Cui Chen, I've lost a daughter.
I don't want to lose Feng Bao.
Consider it compensation for Lian Wen,
can you take me out with you?
Elder Feng, I'm duty-bound to do so,
but I'm also trapped in this chamber.
I can't find a way out either.
Over these years,
you're the only one
who released me from the jade trowel.
And I'm the only one who can save you.
This secret chamber can only be opened
by our family's spell.
But I don't have a physical body.
I can't perform the spell.
I need you to do it for me.
Please tell me what to do.
All you have to do
is to carry me with you.
Elder Feng.
Sorry about this.
Tell the patrol
to check the barrier of the entire city.
Yes.
Let's go.
Cui Chen.
How dare you break into
the Feng Ancestral Hall?
You even stole the lotus seed.
Feng Bao tricked me into going in there.
Feng Bao?
This thing.
You must know what this is.
The late Lord wants to talk to Feng Bao.
Feng Bao's father died
over 100 years ago.
How can he talk to Feng Bao?
I have my own way.
Tantan.
You've been wondering
why you can see Lian Wen in your memory.
The Truth Mirror
can answer this question now.
Why hesitate?
This mirror can only show
the demonic token.
How can it prove
Lian Wen and I are the same person?
The seven-petal lotus flower
on Lian Wen's forehead
is one of a kind.
If you show the same token,
it means you're the same person.
Why are you forcing me
to do something I don't want to do?
Is this your so-called sisterhood?
You want to deny my whole life
with just a mirror
and turn me into someone else.
Don't even think about it.
No matter what,
I'm going to prove that you're Lian Wen.
Xie Yu, why did you let him out?
Miss Feng.
Do you remember this?
How dare you touch my father's relic?
How dare
you disturb the late Lord's soul?
Feng Bao.
Uncle Feng wants to talk to you.
Cui Chen
can release his spirit from the trowel.
How can you believe such nonsense?
You can hold it yourself.
There is nothing to worry about now.
Raise the trowel.
I'll use the Qingyuan Sect's
out-of-body power
and release Elder Feng's spirit.
- My Lord.
Father.
Look who she is.
Lian.
Elder Feng, I'm not Lian Wen.
I'm Zhao Tantan of the Qingyuan Sect.
This is our father.
How can you forget that?
The lotus token is too special.
Don't reveal it easily.
Feng Bao.
Lian Wen.
These two jade pendants
will be the symbol of your sisterhood.
From now on, you two
should share everything.
You must love each other
and support each other.
Tantan.
Lian Wen, what else did you see?
Feng Bao, stop pushing her.
You're a murderer.
You have no right to talk.
Feng Bao, stop.
It's been over a hundred years.
You're still so impulsive.
Don't force your will on others.
Father.
How am I forcing her?
She is Lian Wen.
She should bear her responsibilities
and seek revenge
against the Demon Lord with me.
And Cui Chen.
He killed your little daughter.
What's wrong with you?
Are you being threatened?
Why aren't you angry at all?
Feng Bao.
Cui Chen has explained it to me
in the Ancestral Hall.
There was an attacker behind Lian Wen.
In order to save her,
Cui Chen used Dongxu Skill,
passing his sword
through Lian Wen's body,
to hurt the attacker but not her.
Father.
How can you believe such nonsense?
Cui Chen, prove it to us.
I trust you.
Don't worry.
I'm the Light of Qingyuan now.
This won't hurt me.
If you don't do it,
I'll have to do it myself.
No.
Don't!
That's enough.
I don't want to prove anything anymore.
Let's find a place to talk.
Okay.
Dabai.
Who am I in your heart?
In my heart, you're a heroine
of the Xinhuai Village.
You're my junior who caught
the hamster spirit with me.
You're the one who I confessed my love to
in Zhu village.
You're Zhao Tantan,
the one and only Zhao Tantan.
Okay.
Take out the True Mirror.
I want to see
what the relationship is
between me and Lian Wen.
Have you decided?
I've decided.
Well,
even if Lian Wen and I
have the same unique demonic token,
she's still my past life.
Based on your descriptions
and my sporadic memories,
we are different people.
I don't care about her past.
What I care about is our present.
You forgot to keep your distance again.
Take it out.
I'll look into it
and give an explanation to others.
Okay.
It's just as I thought.
But it still feels incredible
when I see it myself.
Tantan.
I'm fine.
I'm just a little emotional.
I never expected someone
who passed away over 100 years ago
to have such a connection with me.
Let's talk about something happy.
By the way, I have good news for you.
Look.
A lotus seed?
Where did you find it?
In the Ancestral Hall of Wanfang City.
Well,
is this what they call
"Misfortune may be a blessing
in disguise"?
Well done.
You're getting more knowledgeable.
Master would be very happy to know that.
Touch it.
After you touch the lotus seed,
you'll be able
to reach the Divinity Phase.
Really?
If I touch two more,
will I be able
to reach the highest level
in the Qingyuan Sect,
Dacheng Skill, just like you did?
Maybe.
Who do you think you are?
You won't have a future together.
What happened?
What did you see?
I...
I just saw
some memories of the massacre,
and it scared me a bit.
Really?
Really.
Don't worry.
I'm now a high-ranking cultivator
of the Qingyuan Sect.
I won't be scared easily.
Tantan.
No matter what scary memories
you see next time,
you can tell me right away.
I'll be there for you.
Okay.
Let's go find Feng Bao now
and tell her the result
of the Truth Mirror.
Father, rest assured.
I'll avenge your death
and Lian Wen's death.
Bao, it's time to let go of the hatred.
The people of Wanfang City
are waiting for you to grow up.
Father, I'm sorry.
I failed to fulfill your instructions.
I didn't guard Wanfang City well.
I've been wandering around
all these years,
looking for a chance to take revenge,
but I forgot
my most important responsibility.
Good girl, you're doing well now.
Besides, I have a son-in-law.
You two can join hands
to protect our people.
Father, what are you talking about?
We're not married yet.
Then keep an eye on him.
Don't let anyone steal him.
Or you'll come back
to the secret chamber
and cry in front of my tablet.
I can't stand that.
Father, why the tablet?
Can't Cui Chen make you stay forever?
Silly girl, this is just my spirit.
I have to leave.
Father, don't leave.
I've been missing you
for over 100 years.
My Lord.
Cui Chen, do something.
Make my father stay.
He can't go.
Brother, save my father.
Save him.
The power of the Qingyuan Sect
can only summon Elder Feng's spirit.
Now his spirit is dissipating.
I heard you call me father again.
That's enough for me.
When you miss me in the future,
just look at the sky of Wanfang City.
I'll be protecting you from above,
and protecting Wanfang City.
Don't leave, please.
Father.
[Adapted from Han Yishui's book
on Shuqi Reading Platform, "Blooming"]
[Produced by]
[YOUKU Information Technology (Beijing)]
[All rights of network communication
reserved by YOUKU]