♪Suddenly, you showed up♪
♪Who stole away those years♪
♪Oh, night and day♪
♪Oh, it's been a long time♪
♪Pass through the bustling world
in the daytime♪
♪Circumvent love at night♪
♪Day after day, year after year♪
♪I wake up and close my eyes
before it gets dark♪
♪But when the day breaks into the night♪
♪It makes me believe
that there's still love♪
♪If you want it, if I want it♪
♪It's a vow of night and day♪
♪It's a vow of day and night♪
[Blooming]
[Episode 29]
(If there were no such thing
as turning into a demon,)
(would Dabai be waiting for me)
(at the back side
of the mountain like this?)
Go back.
She's not coming.
Why not?
We said we'd meet here today.
I've prepared so much
to give her a perfect proposal.
Why is she not coming?
Maybe
it's not that she doesn't want to come.
She just can't come.
We love each other so much.
Why can't she come?
In this world, there are many things
that can't be helped.
Do you think she might be
watching me
and smiling at me in some corner?
Maybe.
Then I'll show her
the surprise I prepared.
[The Light of Qingyuan]
It's really a surprise.
I used to think they looked like flies.
[Chen Tan]
Can you hear it?
I want to take you as my wife.
Will you marry me?
(Dabai.)
(I will.)
Tantan.
Dabai!
Wake up.
You're awake.
Who are you?
I...
You...
I'm Zhao Dahua. Do you remember me?
Who's Zhao Dahua?
The one
who fell off the cliff
and was saved by you.
Get up.
Are you okay?
That's good.
Since you've recovered,
you should go back.
I've been living alone for a long time.
I like quietness.
You should hurry back.
Or your family will get worried.
I...
Say no more.
You're a little girl.
You shouldn't stay deep in the mountains
with a grown-up man.
Just leave.
But...
Why aren't you leaving?
You little girl.
I kindly took you in,
but now you're stuck with me.
You've taken care of me for so long.
I haven't figured out
how to return your favor.
Your leaving is the best way
to return my favor.
That will save me rice, wine and salt.
Just go.
[The Light of Qingyuan]
I want to take you as my wife.
Will you marry me?
Dabai!
(His spiritual power has dropped again.)
(Should I leave?)
(He's lost so much spiritual power.)
(What if he's in danger after I leave?)
(What's going on?)
(He remembers that he has magic arts.)
Tantan.
We're both miserable.
The first time I proposed,
I watched you cry in the rain
from the corner
and couldn't come out and hug you.
The second time,
you stood by my side,
but I had to pretend I didn't know you,
acting toward the sky.
Do you think there will be a third time?
(So,)
(when he proposed yesterday,)
(he remembered everything.)
Tantan! Tantan!
Tantan.
Master has been looking for you
for a long time.
What are you doing here?
Look, Feng Bao is here.
Something happened in Wanfang City.
Tantan!
Sha, I've remembered everything.
You just told Tantan
something happened in Wanfang City.
What happened?
Senior Mu Bai, you heard it.
Don't worry about it.
Master and Tantan will handle it.
You should recuperate
in the Peach Blossom Valley.
Although my spiritual power
has decreased,
I still know martial arts.
Don't worry about me.
Something happened in Wanfang City.
Does the Demon Lord send people
to harass them again?
We can't hide anything from you.
Yesterday, someone named Feng Bao
came to our sect
and said she's Tantan's older sister,
the Lady of Wangfang.
She said Wanfang City
is surrounded by the Demon Lord's army,
and the barrier can only hold
for ten days at most.
She wanted you and Tantan to help.
Let's go there
and gather some information first.
Senior Mu Bai, but your memory...
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
I won't become a burden to you guys.
Elder Qing.
I thought
Tantan had restored the Seven-Leaf Lotus
and lifted
Cui Chen's Xilan Flower Curse,
so I wanted them to help me
rescue Wanfang City.
But I didn't expect
that Cui Chen lost his memory
and Tantan went missing.
Such twists of fate.
Elder Qing.
I won't bother you anymore.
Please let me immediately
if there's any news about Tantan.
I'm leaving now for Wanfang City
to fight against
those demonic cultivators.
Hold on!
Don't be impulsive, young girl.
I've written
to all the cultivation sects.
Tomorrow at noon, those with
noble aspirations will gather here,
and we'll go to Wanfang City together
to help you break the siege.
Elder Qing, thank you for forgiving me
for what I did to Cui Chen.
I want to thank you
on behalf of the people of Wanfang City.
Please rise, Miss Feng.
It's the Qingyuan Sect's duty
to eliminate demons and uphold justice.
Not to mention you're Tantan's sister.
Now Wanfang City is in trouble,
and Tantan is missing.
Why do these things happen
at the same time?
I've been looking for her.
Don't worry too much.
She is a lucky girl.
She'll be fine.
Master!
- Master!
- Tantan?
Master!
She's back.
- Feng Bao!
- Tantan!
Feng Bao!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
We were just saying you're a lucky girl,
and you're back.
Master.
I'm sorry that I made you worry.
By the way, what happened
to the Wanfang City?
How did you know about it?
Sha told me.
What? The Demon Lord has sent people
to surround the city?
Does he want to repeat the tragedy
of 100 years ago?
I won't let him succeed.
Feng Bao, you know what,
I have Dacheng Skill now.
Let's go back together
to protect Wanfang City.
Let's go.
Stop.
Why are both of you
so impulsive?
The more dangerous the situation,
the more necessary to remain calm.
Didn't I teach you that?
Elder Qing said
he's informed all the sects,
and we'll set out
when they're all assembled.
It's decided.
You two haven't seen each other
for a long time.
Take your time to chat.
I'll go back first.
Master.
I have something to ask you.
Feng Bao, have some rest first.
Elder Qing, I'll leave then.
Go ahead.
What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Have you found the Longgu Herb?
Master.
Do you know about
the Peach Blossom Valley?
The Peach Blossom Valley.
How do you know about it?
Not only do I know,
I've been there these days
in Cui Chen's room.
Master, tell me the truth.
I'll tell you.
When I went back to the library
with Zi Meng that day,
I ran into him.
Cui Chen.
You're awake.
Everyone
is in the library making medicine
for you.
I'll go get them.
Master.
I heard what you said yesterday.
My spiritual power is slowly decreasing.
No one knows if I will turn into a demon
or become a mortal
and die of old age immediately
in the end.
I don't want you to worry about me
or become a burden on you.
I want to leave the Qingyuan Sect
and go to a desolate place.
If it doesn't go well,
I'll end my life.
Nonsense!
Tantan, the whole Qingyuan Sect, and I
are all trying to save you.
But you've become so degenerate
and trying to escape.
Master.
All right, say no more!
I'll send you to a place,
where no one can find you except me.
Go there and recuperate for a while.
I'll visit you regularly.
But remember,
you mustn't have that idea again.
Do you hear me?
Yes.
You're the reason why he blossoms.
I sent him to the Peach Blossom Valley
to separate him from you.
If you know where Cui Chen is,
can you resist the urge to see him?
Tantan, you must know
that not all relationships
in this world
can lead to a happy ending.
Some choices, no matter how difficult,
must be made early
to avoid more trouble later.
Now, we're faced with a formidable foe.
You can't be indecisive.
Tomorrow,
we'll go to rescue Wanfang City,
and I'll go myself.
You stay in the Qingyuan Sect.
Why?
I'm the most powerful person
in the Qingyuan Sect.
Fighting off the Demon Lord
is no easy task.
It's only right for me to go.
Master, you're an old man.
Don't get yourself involved.
Just because
you're the Light of Qingyuan,
you should stay.
The future of the Qingyuan Sect
rests with you.
If anything happens to you,
what should we do in the future?
Master.
If you and my juniors risk your lives
fighting against them
and I hide in the mountains,
when others know it,
the title of the Light of Qingyuan
will become a laughingstock.
Besides,
I'm more familiar with Wanfang City
than anyone else.
I'm the most suitable person to go.
I won't let you go.
You...
Master, with my magic power now,
you can't keep me here.
I know you're doing this for my good.
But Feng Bao and I
are like real sisters.
I can't ignore Wanfang City's troubles.
You stubborn girl.
The Demon Lord might be coming for you.
Me?
Why didn't he come
to capture me earlier?
The timing wasn't right.
What timing?
Earlier, you were not powerful enough.
He didn't worry about you.
In just a few months,
you've progressed
from Foundation to Dacheng,
becoming the Demon Lord's
number one threat.
If you go there now,
aren't you falling into his trap?
Let go of the rope.
Master, you're right.
But,
what if
the other cultivators won't come?
For my sake
and for the noble reason
of eliminating demons,
they will surely respond actively.
Okay. I'll wait for one more day.
If they don't come,
I'll have to go myself.
Come in.
If there are no reinforcements tomorrow,
help me persuade Tantan
to stay in the Qingyuan Sect.
Master, forgive my foolishness,
but this battle is already challenging.
If you don't bring
the most powerful cultivator
of the Qingyuan Sect,
it will truly
become a perilous situation.
I suspect that the Demon Lord's attack
on Wanfang City
is just a plan to attack reinforcements.
His real target
is Tantan.
Tantan?
Lately, I found a book in the library
about the history of the Qingyuan Sect.
It says that 20,000 years ago,
the Seven-Leaf Lotus once
transformed into a human.
It took the cultivators
from various sects thousands of years
to recover the lotus seedpod, the seeds,
and the lotus flower
that transformed into a human,
and restored the Seven-Leaf Lotus.
We already have the seeds
and the lotus seedpod.
As for the lotus flower
that transformed into a human,
where can we find it
in the vast world?
Moreover, the human
transformed from the lotus
must be a virgin,
otherwise, the Seven-Leaf Lotus
can't be restored.
It's been 100 years.
It's not easy to find this person,
and that person must be a virgin.
Saving Cui Chen is so hard.
That's why I think
the human transformed from the lotus
is Zhao Tantan.
Hold on.
No wonder
when I first met this girl,
she was clearly in the Foundation Phase.
Then I gave her the lotus seed.
One day later,
she reached the Virtuoso Phase.
That's right.
Although the lotus seeds
can temporarily boost
everyone's spiritual power,
the external power
can't be immediately internalized.
But when Tantan touches the lotus seeds,
her power will immediately advance
to another phase.
I...
The lotus seeds.
Lian Wen.
The Seven-Leaf Lotus.
The Demon Lord has been coveting
the Seven-Leaf Lotus for 100 years,
but we've never noticed it.
Take Qiu Yuebai for example.
He continuously provided information
about the lotus seeds to Tantan.
Clearly,
there is a mastermind behind him.
Is it possible
that they only want to use
the power of Cui Chen
to find out the lotus seeds?
It's not that simple.
The Demon Lord was tyrannical
100 years ago.
But recently,
Feng Bao has led the spirits
of Wanfang City
to stay hidden in the woods
and pay no attention to worldly affairs.
The Demon Lord's attack on Wanfang City
is completely unprofitable.
They massacred the people
of Wangfang City to catch Lian Wen.
That's right.
He should have known about
the relationship between Lian Wen
and the Seven-Leaf Lotus.
His recent attack on Wanfang City
likely indicates that he has found out
Tantan is part of the Seven-Leaf Lotus.
Otherwise, why would Feng Bao
be able to break through layers of siege
and bring the message
to the Qingyuan Sect?
You're right
We can't let Tantan go to Wanfang City.
I won't let Tantan go,
not just because
she is my disciple
and I don't want her to get hurt,
more importantly,
we can't let the Demon Lord
have the Seven-Leaf Lotus.
Otherwise,
if he summons the power of the universe,
I'm afraid this world
will become a purgatory.
So, I'm the reason
why the Seven-Leaf Lotus
can't be restored.
Cui Chen.
I finally found a way to save you.
Master.
What did they say?
Most cultivators,
led by the Tianyin Palace,
think the spirits in Wanfang City
should perish together
with the demonic army.
The disciples of the Qionghua Sect think
it's a losing proposition
and are unwilling to participate.
But Zou Manqian and Su Zhinan
are willing to fight in their own names.
They're loyal friends indeed.
Tell all the disciples
that we'll leave for Wanfang City
in four hours.
Yes.
Wait.
Don't tell them yet.
I have something to discuss with Master.
You can leave.
Okay.
Tantan.
This battle is crucial.
I think it's best
for our
esteemed and respected Master Qing
to lead the way in person.
That's right.
You're the Light of Qingyuan.
You should stay and familiarize yourself
with the affairs of the Qingyuan Sect.
Master.
I have a plan.
We don't need to leave the Qingyuan Sect
to help Wanfang City.
Tantan, what's the plan?
To announce my wedding with Dabai
to the world.
What?
But
what does your wedding
have anything to do
with saving Wanfang City?
If he wants the Seven-Leaf Lotus,
he'll come to my wedding.
Master. Uncle.
Am I right?
Tantan.
You...
Do you know it?
I didn't say it.
Master.
It has nothing to do with Uncle.
I overheard you two talking about it.
Tantan.
What's going on?
Feng Bao.
My virginity
is crucial for the rebirth
of the Seven-Leaf Lotus.
If we announce my wedding with Dabai,
no matter
how far away the Demon Lord is,
he will come before our wedding night.
I don't agree.
Xiaobai.
- Xiaobai!
- Senior Mu Bai!
I'll go get Huai Meng.
Hurry.
Uncle, no need.
It's a residual effect
of the four blooming petals.
He'll be fine in a minute.
Sha, why are you two here together?
When you left,
he had recovered all his memories.
I know.
He never remembered he had magic arts.
But on the day I left,
I secretly saw him using it.
But the thing is,
if he regained his memory,
he should be more reluctant
to come back.
He overheard our conversation,
knowing something happened
to Wanfang City.
He wanted to help.
So,
he insisted on going to Wanfang City,
and I went with him.
How is the situation?
When we arrived at the laurel tree,
we found that those demonic cultivators
were only surrounding but not attacking.
They seemed to be waiting for something.
Yes, they were also like that
before I left.
It seems my guess was right.
Their goal is Tantan.
Cui Chen.
He's awake.
Yeah.
Where am I?
Who are you?
Well...
Who am I?
What's wrong with Senior Mu Bai?
What's going on?
[Look at your chest]
(You're Cui Chen of the Qingyuan Sect.)
(The purpose of your return
to the Qingyuan Sect)
(is to help Wanfang City
fight off the demonic cultivators.)
(Stay away from Zhao Tantan.
Don't fall in love with her.)
This is the Qingyuan Sect.
I'm Cui Chen.
Right.
I'm your master, Qing Zhufeng.
Greetings, Master.
No need for that. Please rise.
You're Zhao Tantan.
I'm Zhao Tantan.
What's on that sign is right.
You can't fall in love with me.
But
to save Wanfang City,
we have to put on a show.
What show?
A wedding.
Okay.
But let's get one thing straight,
it's just a fake wedding.
After the plan is completed,
we'll have nothing to do with each other.
Okay.
All right, guys.
Our Turkey Shoot Plan
is officially starting.
The goal is to lure all the demons here
and then use our magic instrument,
the Demon Purifying Shield,
to round them up.
By the way,
tomorrow, ask all the disciples
to send these to the major sects.
Remember, the more high-profile,
the better.
Do you hear me?
Okay.
Go ahead.
Master.
Well, a few days ago,
we just sent letters to them
and invited them
to fight against those demons.
Now we're sending them
wedding invitations.
Will they come?
It doesn't matter if they come or not.
What's important is
they must know about this.
My Lord.
We've surrounded Wanfang City.
The demonic cultivators inside the city
are also ready.
When shall we take action?
Wait.
The important person hasn't arrived.
Yes.
My Lord.
Speak.
Zhao Tantan and Cui Chen
will be married in three days.
What did you say?
The Qingyuan Sect
has announced to the world
that Zhao Tantan and Cui Chen
are getting married in three days.
Wanfang City is in crisis now,
and news of Zhao Tantan
and Cui Chen's wedding has spread.
There must be something fishy going on.
Have they found out our true purpose?
No matter what they know,
they can't get married.
Find where Qiu Yuebai is
and make sure
the Demon Purifying Shield is destroyed
before the wedding night.
Yes, My Lord.
Tantan.
Have you really decided?
Although it's a fake wedding,
I know
you're taking it seriously.
I've thought it over.
Cui Chen and I
are meant not to be together.
As long as there is a wedding,
whether it's real or fake
it's enough for me.
(I'm Cui Chen,)
(a disciple of the Qingyuan Sect.)
(My mission)
(is to have a fake wedding
with a person named Zhao Tantan)
(to lure the Demon Lord
and destroy him in one fell swoop.)
(After it's done,)
(I'll never see Zhao Tantan again.)
What was that?
Master.
- Master.
Why are you two back?
We heard that Tantan and Senior Mu Bai
are getting married,
so we immediately left work
and rushed back.
Yes.
Master, what were you doing?
Do you need our help?
No.
It's the thought that counts.
Master.
We're not the same as we used to be.
Except for alchemy and demon hunting,
we can handle everything else.
Yeah.
Well...
Master, please assign us a task.
Yeah.
There is one thing
I don't know who can do it.
We're willing to share your worries.
Qiu Yuebai, time to eat.
Qifang, Xianfang.
Do you know us?
You're the shareholders
of Crab Noodle Restaurant.
Everyone knows you.
But why would the owners
of the chain store
bring me food in person?
Tantan is getting married. Everyone
in the sect has been busy lately.
We came back to help out.
That's right.
We came here with no other intention.
It's a big deal for Tantan
to get married.
What's the rush?
Senior Mu Bai is not in good health.
So the wedding has to...
I thought you're just like me,
not valued by our master
and ending up delivering food
to prisoners.
Has the esteemed Mr. Qiu
also experienced such a low point?
Haven't you heard of it?
I used to be your senior,
but I had to leave
because Cui Chen ostracized me.
But we heard
that you turned to
the Demon Lord yourself.
A hundred years ago, Cui Chen and I
were cultivating in the Qingyuan Sect.
Because he was better looking than me,
I was always overshadowed by him.
Later, he was hailed
as the Light of Qingyuan,
while I had nothing.
I also had to take orders from him.
Until I met the Demon Lord
who gave me a new appearance
and a career.
When I had a career, I realized
I didn't need to bend myself
to please others.
I wish
we had heard your words earlier.
That way, we wouldn't have endured
so much humiliation.
It's not too late now.
I once bought a piece of land
in Yunzhou.
I wanted to open a big restaurant.
Unfortunately, I'm locked up here now.
If we can work together,
we can surely make a lot of money.
Really?
Mr. Qiu, I also think so.
Mr. Qiu.
Although we are greedy for money,
we still have bottom lines.
No matter what price you offer,
we won't betray the sect
and let you out.
Let's go.
Hurry.
Tantan's wedding
is the most joyous occasion
in Qingyuan Mountain.
Yes!
We must make it lively.
Let's start rehearsing now.
Get all the musical instruments ready.
The first rehearsal
for Tantan's wedding music
begins now.
Whether the wedding tomorrow
is real or not,
I'll wear this wedding dress for you.
[Adapted from Han Yishui's book
on Shuqi Reading Platform, "Blooming"]
[Produced by Youku Information Technology
(Beijing) Co., Ltd.]
[All rights of network communication
reserved by YOUKU]