♪Suddenly, you showed up♪
♪Who stole away those years♪
♪Oh, night and day♪
♪Oh, it's been a long time♪
♪Pass through the bustling world
in the daytime♪
♪Circumvent love at night♪
♪Day after day, year after year♪
♪I wake up and close my eyes
before it gets dark♪
♪But when the day breaks into the night♪
♪It makes me believe
that there's still love♪
♪If you want it, if I want it♪
♪It's a vow of night and day♪
♪It's a vow of day and night♪
[Blooming]
[Episode 11]
Is the gold here also yours?
Lemon spirit?
Yes.
I'm a lemon spirit.
You really are a lemon spirit.
You tricked me.
This is called 'All is fair in war.'
I was just a lemon
without life.
But luckily, I grew on a spiritual land,
then I gradually developed
a human form.
However, due to my special nature,
I emit an acidic smell,
and those who smell it become jealous
and even engage in fights.
Because of this,
the people around me
gradually distanced themselves from me.
Become jealousy
and engage in fights.
Did you hear that?
Senior Zou just said thank you to me.
To both of us.
Yes.
Did she say that to you?
Don't flatter yourself.
Senior Zou said thank you to me.
Look how smug you are.
Can you be less cheeky?
Stop staring at her.
You're drooling over her.
Me?
I haven't mentioned
the way you looked at Qiu Yuebai.
We were just acting.
Acting?
I think you're trying to make it real.
Turns out it's because of
the lemon's acid.
No wonder
I've been feeling strange lately
and getting jealous at times.
I also feel...
So, those who are close to you
will be affected by your acidic nature
and get jealous and competitive.
That's not entirely the case.
If the person
doesn't have similar thoughts,
there won't be an impact.
(Bai looks cute when he's asleep.)
(It won't work if the person
doesn't have similar thoughts.)
(Then I was affected because...?)
Go on.
Later, I heard that the medicine
of Central Plains is advanced,
so I came here to improve my nature.
I didn't expect
that I would end up
at the Qionghua Sect.
Can a lemon spirit join
the Qionghua Sect?
I cast a spell on Mr. Su that day
and hid it from him.
With Mr. Su's spiritual power,
do you think he couldn't tell it?
I don't know.
But since I joined the Qionghua Sect,
he has treated me well
entrusted me with important tasks.
I was all alone before.
The Qionghua Sect
and Mr. Su
are warm presences for me.
I swore to serve him with all my heart
without any other thoughts.
But as time went on,
I began to think of him
in a way I shouldn't have.
I know
that in his eyes,
I'm just a capable assistant.
I often remind myself
that due to my nature,
there is no chance for us
to be together.
To be honest, I thought
as long as I can stay by his side,
I would be content.
But that day, he said
that all beings are equal,
which gave me hope again.
So, I put my nameplate
into the Marriage Tripod.
We all fear
disappointment after having hope.
The night before
the Gathering of Fated Marriage,
Mr. Su decided to send me away,
and I couldn't stay by his side anymore.
I didn't want others to see me sad,
so I came here alone.
It's all my wishful thinking.
If you gave me hope,
why did you let me down?
I was just
a carefree lemon.
Why turn me into a spirit
and give me feelings?
Now I end up like this.
Oh, no, what should I do?
My goodness.
You melted a whole box of gold.
How many tears have you shed?
Looks like you really care about
Mr. Su.
I'm sorry.
You came at such an opportune time.
I had to put the blame on you.
It's okay.
Wait,
did you make
the Marriage Tripod leak
with your tears?
Oh my, you must have felt really awful.
Now that we know the truth,
let's go see Mr. Su.
I...
I dare not.
Why not?
Are you afraid
he'll ask you for compensation?
She's a lemon spirit.
If Mr. Su finds out the truth,
do you think he'll keep her with him?
Whether Mr. Su minds it or not,
she's been in charge of
the treasury vault.
You must come forward
and give an explanation
to the Qionghua Sect.
I understand.
I've been here for so long,
but I've never faced
Mr. Su and my fellow disciples
with my true identity.
It's unfair to them.
Besides, it concerns the reputation
of the Qingyuan Sect.
I should step forward.
Aren't you afraid
that Mr. Su will handle it impartially
and expel you from the Qionghua Sect?
Then you won't have any chance
to be by his side.
I didn't expect Senior Zou to be...
Stop calling her that.
She's a lemon spirit
who orchestrated the whole thing,
melting gold
and destroying the Marriage Tripod.
She doesn't deserve
to be in the Qionghua Sect!
- That's right.
- Yeah.
- She should have been kicked out
long ago.
Are you done?
She never hurt you guys.
How can you say that?
Everyone.
We've found out the truth
about the theft of the gold.
The gold melted
because of Zou Manqian's negligence.
It has nothing to do with
these cultivators from the Qingyuan Sect.
Here, on behalf of the Qionghua Sect,
I'd like to apologize to Miss Tantan,
Mu Bai Zhenren,
and Mr. Qiu.
I have decided
that this matter
won't be revealed to the public.
It will be settled
within the Qionghua Sect.
May I ask how you want to resolve it?
Zou Manqian is a lemon spirit.
Her acidic nature
will only bring more disasters.
That's right.
Zou Manqian is a thief,
and she framed others.
We can't keep such a person
in the Qionghua Sect.
Listen to me.
Zou Manqian is certainly at fault,
but she's admitted it.
Do you have to be so aggressive?
Tantan and I have forgiven her.
There's no need to bring it up again.
I can give you two boxes of gold
for Miss Zou.
Is it okay?
It's
the Qionghua Sect's internal affairs.
You have no right to interfere.
- That's right.
- Yeah.
That's right.
Enough.
Regarding the theft of the gold,
Zou Manqian was negligent
and shifted the blame onto others.
She should be punished severely.
But you've seen her contribution
to the Qionghua Sect over the years.
Her faults are offset by her merits.
Let's end this matter here.
Master.
I've decided.
There's no need to say more.
I'll take Zou Manqian
to the reflection room
where she'll reflect on her mistakes.
[Qionghua Sect]
Master.
Mu Bai Zhenren has arrived.
Mr. Su.
Mu Bai Zhenren, please.
Okay.
Mr. Su, I'm here
for the treasury vault.
Tantan and I were too rash,
and I apologize to you for that.
You don't have to apologize.
But when you broke into
our treasury vault,
it wasn't for
any of the treasures, right?
No wonder you're the leader.
Tanta and I came here
for the lotus seed.
That was also my guess.
The lotus seed of the Seven-Leaf Lotus
belongs to the Qingyuan Sect
and it should be returned to you.
Before you came,
I've ordered my disciples to bring it.
Thank you, Mr. Su.
If I had known earlier
that you are such a magnanimous man,
Tantan and I wouldn't have
wasted all this time
and caused you so much trouble.
As for the gold in the vault,
Manqian did it wrong
and made you suffer injustice.
Miss Zou has admitted her mistakes.
She is brave.
She's a good girl, but unfortunately...
You already knew
that Miss Zou is a lemon spirit.
All beings are equal.
What does it matter
whether I know or not?
Master.
What's wrong?
The lotus seed is missing.
What?
Mr. Su seems quite nice.
Why is he so mad this time?
Besides, you shed tears because of him.
How could he treat you like this?
If it wasn't for him,
I would have been expelled
from the Qionghua Sect by now.
Are you saying
he is protecting you?
Manqian.
What's going on?
The lotus seed is missing.
Because of the gold incident,
everyone in the sect suspects you.
Master sent me here.
Mu Bai Zhenren and him are waiting
in the treasury vault.
Hold it back.
The lotus seed
has been in this box all these years.
No one has ever touched it.
If it wasn't for this time
If it wasn't for this time,
to get the lotus seed for Mu Bai,
I wouldn't have known it was lost.
When Tantan and I first entered
the treasury vault,
we felt a strong scent
of the lotus seed.
Now, there is only
a faint scent of it left.
Master.
Senior Zou has arrived.
I didn't take it.
I don't know when it was stolen
and who did it.
But the treasury vault
is a forbidden place,
and the treasure has been kept
by Senior Zou.
Even when the disciples went in and out
to move things,
they did it
under Senior Zou's supervision.
Besides,
Senior Zou is different from us.
We're human beings.
You're a lemon spirit.
We're too species.
What's more, that lotus seed
isn't an ordinary item.
Anyone who gets it
can use it to increase spiritual power.
Am I right?
Since I joined the sect,
I have been diligent
and never coveted anything
from the sect.
It was an accident
that the gold disappeared.
But I had nothing to do
with the loss of the lotus seeds.
Could it be that your tears
melted the lotus seeds too?
You...
You're making baseless accusations.
Where's the evidence?
Mr. Su.
Are you mute?
Can't you say something?
It's our sect's business.
You have no right to interfere.
You...!
Are you the one
who conspired with her
to steal the lotus seed?
Shut up!
Finding out the truth needs evidence,
not speculation.
Anyone who breaks the rules again
will be punished.
Miss Zou doesn't have
the scent of lotus seed on her.
Why should we believe you?
I think we should tie her up
and search her all over.
Do you know who he is?
He's the famous Mu Bai Zhenren.
With his relationship
with the lotus seed,
what he said can be trusted.
Mr. Su, what do you think?
Of course, I believe
Mubai Zhenren's words.
But if we don't find the lotus seed,
she's still a suspect.
That's easy.
Check all the disciples
of the Qionghua Sect
one by one.
What nonsense
are you talking about, old man?
Except for Zou Manqian,
everyone in the Qionghua Sect
is an honest cultivator.
Except for you, a lemon spirit,
who else would covet the lotus seed?
Show.
Thank you for teaching
my incompetent disciple a lesson.
But it couldn't have been
one of our disciples.
They don't know about the lotus seed.
Even if they obtained it,
their spiritual power would change,
and I would surely know.
The disciples of the Qionghua Sect
couldn't have done it.
Zou Manqian couldn't have done it.
The participants of the gathering
couldn't have found
the treasury vault so easily.
Then the only one left is...
- Hu Meng.
No wonder
I haven't seen her these days.
Turns out she ran away
after stealing the lotus seed.
We even helped her in Yunlai Town.
Who's Hu Meng?
The relationship lecturer
hired from outside for the gathering.
What kind of
relationship lecturer is that?
You're just making things more difficult
to charge exorbitant fees.
What's more, she's a golden fox.
She's very cunning.
How could this happen?
Lu Yi!
Wasn't he just here?
Go find him!
- Yes.
Wait,
find Hu Meng too,
and bring them to me.
Yes.
I'm sorry for what happened
in our sect.
On behalf of the Qionghua Sect,
I apologize to the Qingyuan Sect
and Mu Bai Zhenren.
Give me three days.
I'll find out the truth.
You don't have to say that, Mr. Su.
It's our lack of consideration
that allowed her to use us.
When I catch her, I'll make her suffer.
[Qiye Inn]
Tantan, don't be sad.
Eat something.
I'm not in the mood.
The lotus seed is lost.
It's the first time
I've cooked something myself.
Eat a little for my sake.
What happened to your hands?
It was my first time, and I was clumsy.
I'll do it better next time.
Thank you, Qiu.
Bai, how is it?
Mr. Su said
the two of them disappeared.
There's no trace of them
in the whole city.
He's sent people to find them
in every direction.
What should we do?
Mr. Su said
he will send more people soon
and expand the search range.
He told us to wait for his news.
Within three days,
he'll give us an answer.
Are we gonna do nothing
and wait around?
I've sent Mo Yan
to inquire about it
at the Qiye Inns across the country.
Qiu, you're thoughtful indeed.
Doesn't Uncle Zi Meng have
a team of little toads
who gather information
and record events for him?
They're good at it.
I bet they're better than your Qiye Inn.
I've sent them out.
Uncle Zi Meng.
That's impressive.
Wait.
What?
I'm hungry, and no one's eating it.
I made it for Tantan.
Eat banana.
The banana is...
I made it for Tantan.
I'm your future senior master.
Your future master won't mind it.
I'm glad you didn't eat it.
It's not good at all.
You need to improve your skills.
Be grateful to have something to eat.
Why do you have so many opinions?
Qiu.
I'm sorry.
If you cook for me next time,
I'll drink every drop of the soup.
I've lost my appetite. It's too salty.
Why do you have so many problems?
That's tense.
Oh, the jealousy.
Why aren't you in the reflection room?
I'm here to apologize and bid farewell.
But I've never wanted
to expel you from the Qionghua Sect.
I lied to you
and brought shame to the Qionghua Sect.
I feel too ashamed to stay here.
Manqian.
Actually, since the first time
I saw you,
I knew your identity.
Master.
These are the new disciples
we recruited.
(Why is there an acidic smell?)
(A lemon spirit?)
My wife is pregnant,
and she feels sour in her stomach.
We don't know what to do.
I heard from my mom
that she had the same problem
when she was pregnant with me.
Then she ate sour plums
and felt better.
From today on,
buy some plums every day
and deliver them
to Zou Manqian's room on time.
Yes.
(Why is there such a silly person?)
I wanted to use plums
to change your nature
and reduce the impact on others
due to your acidity.
But I didn't expect...
I like you.
Since I joined the Qionghua Sect,
you've been taking good care of me,
which gave me fantasies
that I shouldn't have.
I even want to...
I want to be with you forever.
I know it's impossible.
I thought...
As long as I don't say it,
I could be with you.
But my love for you has grown
day by day,
and I'm overwhelmed by it.
Today, I finally said it.
Now, I realize
I have to do this
before I give up.
I'll voluntarily leave the sect
tomorrow.
Manqian!
Well,
I'll let the gold incident pass.
Don't talk about leaving again.
I'll let you keep guarding
the treasury vault
as a way to make amends.
Are you willing to do it?
Yes.
[Marriage Stick]
Are you thinking about a boy?
Forget about me.
Look at yourself.
It's rare for you to smile like this.
Did you...
Don't overthink it.
It's not what you think.
But Mr. Su asked me
to stay and help him.
You've finally melted
half of such a big iceberg.
Keep it up.
What about you?
Me?
What about me?
I saw it. Don't hide it.
It's about your destined one, right?
Lu Yi is gone. Who is gonna
to interpret the stick for me?
I don't have to know,
but I just feel uncomfortable
when there is something unsolved.
Mr. Su.
Our Master
is an expert on stick interpretation.
He's accurate.
[Dew turns into frost since tonight.
The moon at home is more bright.]
Interpret it.
My friend, is this
how you ask a favor from someone?
If it weren't for the problems
within your Qionghua Sect,
would I need you to read the stick?
It's my mismanagement
that gave room for a traitor like Lu Yi
who used our business to make money.
All right.
It scared me
that you're apologizing
so formally.
I don't know
what Zou Manqian likes about you.
I'll interpret the stick.
Okay.
Your stick says,
'Dew turns into frost since tonight.
The moon at home is more bright.'
The 'dew' here refers to the White Dew season,
which is autumn.
No way.
It's Qiu and Bai,
[*Qiu means autumn; Bai means white.]
and Yue.
[*Yue means the moon.]
Could it be...
The key point of this stick
is the character 'Bai'.
No way.
How am I gonna face him?
I'm his master.
Zhao Tantan, your destined one is...
I know.
(How is it possible?)
(How could it be?)
(How could it be Qiu?)
Well,
could it be that Mr. Su made a mistake?
That's impossible.
Mr. Su is one of the best
stick interpreters
in the cultivation world.
Most cultivators are no match for him.
All right.
I know you like him.
We can't say anything bad about him.
No, he's really that good.
All right.
Your master is great.
But what should I do?
He's my disciple.
What's wrong with that?
You don't have the problem
that we have.
But Bai said
the Qingyuan Sect doesn't allow
disciples of different ranks
to be together.
Since he hasn't become your disciple,
then don't take him.
No.
Our relationship
is not that kind of relationship
that you and Mr. Su have...
Well,
do you have someone else in your heart?
What are you talking about?
I've never liked anyone in my life.
Really?
Real...
Really.
It's true.
Stop looking at me.
I know I'm pretty,
but stop looking at me.
Cheers, Mr. Su.
Mr. Cui, what are you gonna do?
I don't know
what the Xinlan Flower will bring.
In order not to involve her,
I'll pretend I don't know anything.
But Tantan is a good girl.
I know that.
What about you?
What can I do?
There's a gap between us
that can't be crossed.
Well, Mr. Su, you can interpret sticks,
but you're trapped in it.
There's a saying,
'A healer doesn't heal himself.'
Though I know my destiny,
I can't change
my unfortunate fate of love.
Cheers.
I've specially prepared a meal for you.
It's been hard for you guys
in the last few days.
(Is it really him?)
Tantan.
Come over and eat.
I...
I'm not feeling well.
You guys eat. Don't worry about me.
What's wrong?
Your face is red.
Your head is a little hot.
Are you not feeling well?
I'm fine.
You guys eat first. Don't mind me.
Let's eat.
[Dew turns into frost since tonight.
The moon at home is more bright.]
How could Qiu be my destined partner?
It's so annoying.
I wish Xueyi was here to talk to me.
Tantan.
I have something to tell you.
(Does he also know)
(that we're destined to be together?)
(Oh, no, how are we gonna
face each other?)
(It's so embarrassing.)
Tantan.
Tantan?
What do you want to say?
I said I have something to tell you.
Do you have to tell me now?
Before
the Gathering of Fated Marriage...
(The Gathering of Fated Marriage.)
(Why does he mention that?)
(Could it be about destined partners?)
I thought about it.
No matter how complicated the rules are,
as long as you take me as your disciple,
I'll be satisfied.
Well,
I have something to do.
I'll leave first.
Wait.
Tantan.
- Don't chase after me!
- Tantan!
What's happening?
I don't even dare to go back to my room.
Zhao Tantan,
you're too much of a coward.
Xueyi?
Tantan.
Xueyi!
I'm here.
Tantan.
You're finally here.
[Marriage Stick]
You're destined to be together.
No one can separate you two.
It's destiny.
You're destined to be together.
What?
Is your destined partner
someone I don't know?
Can you keep it down?
It feels good. Keep doing it.
Who's it?
Qiu Yuebai.
The one you cooed to me,
just the one...
The one who wants to be your disciple?
How embarrassing.
How can I be a destined couple
with my disciple?
If it gets out,
how am I gonna be the light of Qingyuan?
I've read something similar in a novel.
It's about a love story
of a stupid master
and a warm-hearted disciple.
But it's pretty good.
I've told you many times
to stop reading such novels.
It'll make you stupid.
Who is becoming stupid?
Me? I'll leave then.
Don't.
What should I do if you leave?
Come on, believer.
Tell me what's bothering you.
Although it's the master
of the Qionghua Sect
who interpreted my marriage stick,
I've never liked anyone.
I don't even know
what it feels like to like someone.
Do we really like each other
as a man and a woman?
I'll tell you how it feels
to like someone.
It's like eating candy one moment
and drinking vinegar the next.
Which novel did you read that from?
My novel...
Who said I read it from a novel?
No way.
I just left not long ago,
and you have someone you like.
It happens fast when you like someone.
Tell me who he is.
Is he handsome? Is he tall?
He's the one you brought back
to the back side of the mountain.
The one I brought back?
Oh my God, it's Huai Meng!
You...
When did you...?
How can you be sure you like him?
Look, I didn't know at first.
But when I saw him, my heart raced.
It was pumping fast.
Then I wanted to talk to him,
but every time I opened my mouth,
I got snippy.
What are you doing here?
I...
I'm tired of flying and taking a rest.
Smell it.
You've got a muscle strain.
Lift your little arm.
I'll apply the medicine for you.
You...
It's none of your business.
What's wrong?
It seemed to be true.
If that's the case,
why are you still hesitating?
Just be together with Qiu Yuebai.
It's not Qiu.
It's...
Your face is red.
Your head is hot.
Are you not feeling well?
Who is it?
It's Bai.
Aren't you two enemies?
That was a long time ago.
We've been getting along better lately.
But I don't like him the way you said.
Besides, I'm destined
to be with Qiu Yuebai.
Do you have any other way
to confirm my feelings?
There's another way.
What is it?
Remember.
When another woman approaches him,
your heart gets...
It's like...
It's like
this.
Got it?
Yes.
Stop staring at her.
You're drooling over her.
Why am I thinking of him again?
Don't tell me
you're thinking of Senior Bai again.
Is there really something
going on between you two?
No.
Last time, it was because of
Zou Manqian's acid.
Trust me. That must be the reason.
Well,
have you ever got jealous
because of Qiu Yuebai?
I don't think so.
It's okay. We have one last method.
The last one will definitely work.
[Adapted from Han Yishui's book
on Shuqi Reading Platform, "Blooming"]
[Produced by]
[YOUKU Information Technology (Beijing)]
[All rights of network communication
reserved by YOUKU]