♪Suddenly, you showed up♪
♪Who stole away those years♪
♪Oh, night and day♪
♪Oh, it's been a long time♪
♪Pass through the bustling world
in the daytime♪
♪Circumvent love at night♪
♪Day after day, year after year♪
♪I wake up and close my eyes
before it gets dark♪
♪But when the day breaks into the night♪
♪It makes me believe
that there's still love♪
♪If you want it, if I want it♪
♪It's a vow of night and day♪
♪It's a vow of day and night♪
[Blooming]
[Episode 18]
Although the love between Hu Meng
and Zhu Yan is lamentable,
at least Zhu Yan is a faithful man.
Hu Meng's love for him is not wasted.
Cui Chen, on the contrary,
is full of righteousness and morality,
yet he treats love so casually.
You don't deserve this.
I don't care. Why are you so angry?
I've made up my mind.
From now on,
I won't be upset about him anymore.
Tantan, it's good that you think so.
As long as you're happy, I'm happy.
Tantan, you...
Don't get me wrong.
I didn't.
I...
I just think I'm so lucky
to have met a man as kind as you.
That's not true.
In fact, I have a selfish motive.
I did it all for you.
I'm the future Light of Qingyuan.
That's not selfish to help me.
We can almost think
you
are enterprising in cultivation.
Tantan,
I'm different from Cui Chen.
All he thinks about
is helping the world.
But I only want to be with you,
like now,
having fun with you, laughing with you.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
Thanks, Qiu.
Tantan,
I mean,
I don't want us to be just friends.
I want us to take it to the next level.
You...
Do you understand?
The next level?
OK.
Great idea. I agree.
Really?
I'll tell you what, I've decided
that from tomorrow on,
I'll teach you mental methods
and mnemonic rhyme.
What do you mean?
Are you saying...
Didn't you suggest
we take our relationship
to the next level?
Look,
the weather, air,
and moon are all perfect today.
Let me take you as my disciple.
You...
To take our relationship
to the next level,
do you mean to take me as your disciple?
Yes.
If I take you as my disciple,
you won't just
be there for me as a friend.
You will
be there for me
as my glorious first disciple.
Tantan, actually...
Let's formalize
our master-disciple relationship.
But
I've seen others taking disciples.
Disciples are supposed to burn incense,
bathe, and kowtow.
Why don't you go and get ready?
Forget it.
Come on.
No.
Get up.
Qiu, you know what,
I'm so grateful to you.
You've helped me find my goal in life.
From now on,
I won't be concerned with love.
I'll focus on my career.
Tantan,
I don't think we should rush
into taking our relationship
to the next level.
No rush.
I tell you what,
we're in a rush to find the lotus seeds.
Let's wait until I pay homage
to my grand master,
then we'll go over the details...
Don't bother.
Your grand master listens to me.
Come on.
Hurry.
I don't think
it's that urgent.
Some other day.
Next time.
Qiu, don't leave.
- Next time. I'm off.
- Don't go.
You asked to be my disciple.
Come back.
Next time.
He's so weird.
Didn't he ask to be my disciple?
Everyone in the town is sleeping.
Do you think we can get the new quilts
from the silk shop now?
I guess so.
The boss's wife told us yesterday
that they were going to
deliver new clothes to Mr. Wang
in the next town over at noon today.
They should be awake by now.
How was your conversation
with Qiu Yuebai yesterday?
Pretty good.
I've decided to take him as my disciple.
Disciple?
[Zhou's Silk Shop]
Tantan.
They're still sleeping at this hour.
Aren't they going to
deliver clothes to Mr. Wang?
Madam.
Go and pick for yourself.
I'm sleepy.
Sir.
Sir. Wake up. Sir.
Leave me alone.
They are fast asleep.
Aren't they afraid of being stolen?
We'd better not wake them up.
Let's pick quilts ourselves
and leave them the money.
OK.
Don't take this one.
I'll pick one for you.
This one.
This one is soft, silky, light,
and dense.
It should be cozier.
You know what,
I used to play in the mountain
behind the Qingyuan Sect.
When I was tired,
I'd just find a tree to sleep in.
I was a wild girl.
How can I recognize a good quilt?
But I'll listen to you today.
I'm going to enjoy the good quilt.
Go.
We each take our own.
OK
Go.
Why did I
fall asleep last night?
If I'd held on just a little longer,
this wouldn't have ended up like this.
That's true, Uncle.
Cui Chen had worked so hard
to make the arrangement.
And what happened?
Qiu Yuebai took advantage of it.
I'm so pissed.
Huai Meng.
What are you talking about?
Did Cui Chen
decorate the courtyard last night?
You're right.
He prepared the candlesticks, flowers,
and two bottles of wine.
Darn it.
In the end...
It was so cold last night.
Exactly.
Cui Chen
worked his butt off.
He even caught a cold
and couldn't get out of bed.
Uncle.
But no one's been to see him.
What?
Shouldn't we defend Cui Chen...
Morning.
What are you doing here at this moment?
Didn't you say he caught a cold
and couldn't get out of bed?
Cold.
Poor kid.
Cui Chen.
Look.
What's wrong?
Why did you come at such a bad time?
What happened?
Gosh.
Cui Chen, you made me speechless.
Could the new quilt
really attract the spirit?
I don't know. Give it a try.
Cui Chen.
Tantan.
Don't leave me, Cui Chen.
Don't leave me.
What's that smell?
Herbal ointment.
The spirit made you sleep just now.
It was a white mist.
It escaped through the door.
How dare it stab me in the back?!
Go!
Hurry.
Cui Chen is running
after the white mist.
Go.
Tantan.
Cover it with your toad coat.
This is...
Quilt?
Could a quilt become a spirit
these days?
As far as I know, it's a succubae.
Probably, it's a cotton spirit.
Reaching a certain level,
it can weave itself into a quilt,
so that the cotton gathers
and won't fall apart.
You're bullying me!
What kind of immortal is this?
Immortal?
This little thing
is 300 years old at most.
In terms of seniority, I'm her ancestor.
You're bullying me!
What's going on here?
Has the cotton shrunk in water?
Stop crying.
I was trying to help you,
but you treat me badly.
You're so mean!
Look, you've hurt me badly!
Though children speak the truth,
you should speak from your conscience.
Look, the whole town can't wake
from a long sleep because of you.
You call this helping them?
I'm trying to be nice.
Why are you scolding me?
You're injured.
Let me apply medicine to your wound, OK?
Come with me.
Come on.
Little girl,
my name is Qiu Yuebai. What's your name?
Bai Diezi.
What did you mean when you said
you were helping them?
They said it themselves.
They can't get out of their quilts
in the morning.
When they get home at night,
they flake out in bed.
They wish they could stay in bed
all day.
Some adults suffer from sleeplessness.
They can't sleep
even though they want to.
So I feel sorry for them.
I let them have what they want
and sleep all the time.
It seems that
we should really thank you.
What's this?
No.
Don't touch it.
Little girl, this is so beautiful.
May I have a look at it?
No.
No way.
May I have a look at it?
Lotus seed.
Well...
No wonder she can
put the whole town to sleep.
It turns out she has a lotus seed.
Baby girl,
who is so good
and can knit a quilt
at such a young age of 300 years old?
You're amazing.
Come on, let me look at...
No.
Fine.
Bai Diezi,
where did you get this lotus seed?
I found it
when I was playing by the lotus pond.
Isn't it pretty?
Cutie pie,
this lotus seed is very important to me.
Would you give it to me?
I'll trade this for it, OK?
Tacky!
This is my second favorite thing.
The wimpy kid doesn't know what's what.
I won't give it to you anyway.
Kid,
give us the lotus seed,
or I'll beat you up.
Come on. Beat me up!
You...
I'm not afraid of you!
Wimpy kid.
Little girl.
Do you want to fly with me?
What's fun about flying? I can fly.
Wimpy kid who's never seen the sky.
Little girl,
I can...
Huai Meng, come out!
Say, what does it take us
to get the lotus seed?
You play with me.
You play with me!
Throw the hankie.
Tantan, why don't you come and catch me?
Tantan, come and catch me.
Bai Diezi,
we've been playing with you all night.
It's light already.
Why don't you leave us alone?
No. I want to play.
Honey, we can't play anymore.
Last night,
I've been playing your son.
Let's stop playing.
I've missed my beauty sleep.
You...
You play with me.
The kid is a tough nut to crack.
Listen to me, your...
Don't touch it.
Bai Diezi,
I'm super good at playing chess.
What's fun about chess?
It's boring when adults play chess.
Bai Diezi.
Sandbag!
I saw kids playing with sandbags,
but they wouldn't play with me.
Let's play with Tantan, OK?
OK.
Come on.
I'm joining you.
You're so boring.
I don't want to play with you.
Sir.
Sachets.
Sachets for sale.
Here you are.
Look,
after you take back
your spiritual power,
everyone is back to their normal lives.
It's great, isn't it?
I want this.
Do you want this?
How much for one?
Two coins.
It's OK. Give me.
Here you are.
Be careful. It's hot.
I want a string of candied haws.
Bai Diezi,
you've got a drumstick in your hands.
Can you still eat the candied haws?
Yes, I won't get stuffed.
Really?
I'll get some.
Sir, two strings.
OK.
How much for one string?
Two coins.
OK.
Bai Diezi,
since Yuebai bought you candied haws,
could you give this to us?
No.
Yuebai, she's bullying me again.
She's just kidding.
Here you are.
Tantan.
Tantan, have a try.
It's sweet.
Look at this happy family.
They're all good-looking.
It's too late to be envious.
Besides,
we can't be born again.
Shut up if you can't speak properly.
How do you like it? Is it sweet?
Yes.
It's all over your lips.
Tantan, it's fun over there.
Let's go over there.
Tantan, let's go.
Ignore him.
Let's go.
It's fun over there.
Tantan.
How long are you going to be mad at me?
Tantan, don't mind him.
Let's go.
Don't leave me
or go with this bad man.
What a heartless woman.
Look at this cheating woman.
She's already had a daughter.
No. Let me explain.
It's not what you're thinking.
The little girl is crying.
You stalked me?
Let me explain.
Don't go.
There, there. Don't cry.
You guys go first.
Give us a minute.
Don't go.
Here you are.
Thanks.
Tantan.
Let's bury the hatchet.
What happened before was my fault.
Your fault?
What was your fault?
Putting a tracker on me
or using me as a substitute?
I admit
that when I first met you,
I thought you were Lian Wen.
But the more I spend time with you,
the more I realize
that you two are completely different.
Every day I'm with you,
I've never thought of you as her.
I swear.
I don't believe it.
Tantan,
I'm sorry.
It was all my fault.
I can't change what happened.
But let bygones be bygones.
At present,
in the future,
you're the only one in my heart.
You're the only one
I love, Zhao Tantan.
Tantan, this piece of tangram
is too lonely.
Would you reunite it with the other six?
It's not that easy
to reunite the tangram.
We'll see after we get the lotus seeds.
OK.
As long as you forgive me,
I'll do whatever you want.
Walk slowly.
Be careful.
Here.
Yeah.
Naughty girl, you scared me.
Yuebai, were you upset
because of Tantan?
Why do you know everything?
Because I care about you.
You're the best to me.
Really?
Yuebai, how I wish you and Tantan
were my parents!
I've never seen them.
Bai Diezi, it's OK.
Now you have me, right?
In fact, I've also
lost my mom since I was a child.
We're fellow sufferers.
It's OK.
Yuebai,
let me help you.
Help me?
How do you do that?
I'll steal Tantan for you.
You two can be my dad and mom.
That way, we both have a family.
You're full of wicked ideas.
Wanna play a little longer?
Yes.
Go.
Be careful.
Walk carefully.
Uncle,
how do I coax a little girl?
I can manage with older ones.
But I don't have any experience
with little girls.
Ask him.
Uncle,
my Xueyi is different from Tantan.
She's smart, kind and gentle.
She's easy to coax.
Not Tantan. I'm talking about Bai Diezi.
Bai Diezi?
She is little indeed.
I tell you what,
I'll look it up
in the Strange Tales in the Secular World,
OK?
Here it is.
(To make a child happy,)
(use food.)
(It should be tasty)
(as well as cute and pretty.)
Bai Diezi.
It's time for breakfast.
Why is it you?
Where is Yuebai?
Why is your voice hoarse?
Don't touch me.
I know you don't like Yuebai.
So I don't like you either.
I'm going to find Yuebai.
Look.
Why don't you eat?
It will get cold.
(How can I be bribed so easily?)
(I'm going to help Yuebai.)
(Piggy buns, when Yuebai and Tantan
become my parents,)
(I'll come back to eat you.)
This is a piggy bun.
Don't you like it?
This is a little hedgehog bun.
Since you don't like them,
I'd better give them to someone else.
No.
I'll give them to Uncle Zi Meng.
Here.
Yuebai hasn't brushed my teeth,
washed my face and combed my hair yet.
I can't eat now.
Go get him for me.
You don't need him. I can help you.
Come on.
(The second step
of coaxing a little girl,)
(make her pretty by all means.)
Can you do it or not?
If you can't, go get Yuebai.
I'm in a rush to have breakfast.
Don't doubt me. I can make it.
I can do much better than Qiu Yuebai.
What's wrong?
Yuebai, Tantan,
he's so clumsy.
He made my hair ugly.
I didn't.
It's OK.
Let's ignore this clumsy man,
OK?
OK.
Yuebai, would you brush my hair?
Go.
Tantan, I want to eat
while having my hair combed.
Clumsy.
OK.
You clever little thing.
Why do you have so many ideas?
Is it flying high?
It's high.
I want it to be higher.
Higher?
Bai Diezi, I'll give it to you.
You mustn't lose it.
Let me try.
Ready?
This.
Here.
- Cui Chen.
- What's this?
Peaches.
(Tantan doesn't like Yuebai.)
(I must find a way to help him.)
Let's clean these peaches.
Tantan,
don't you want my lotus seed?
Bai Diezi, why are you talking
about the lotus seed suddenly?
Don't get us wrong.
We do
want this lotus seed.
But we also like you
and want to play with you.
I know you are good to me.
I like you too.
Yuebai likes you too.
If you agree to be with Yuebai,
I'll give you the lotus seed as a gift.
That way the three of us
will be together all the time.
Bai Diezi, listen to me.
You're a little girl.
You don't know about relationships.
You can't be with someone
just because you want to.
Adults always make simple things
complicated.
We've had so much fun these days.
I want Yuebai to be my father
and you to be my mother.
That would be great!
Bai Diezi,
I can be your father too.
Yes, you can.
Look, good girl.
I didn't care for you in vain.
But you can only be my godfather.
I didn't tell her to say that.
Yeah. It has nothing to do with Yuebai.
It's my own idea.
Am I not as good to you
as Qiu Yuebai is?
No bad guy is as good as my father.
You just can't.
Why can't I?
Today I must let you...
Enough.
Why are you arguing with a kid?
I think it's a good idea.
An innocent child
is the best judge of human nature.
She knows who's good to her.
That's right.
Isn't a godfather a father?
Senior Mu Bai,
why are you so calculating?
An innocent child is easy to be fooled.
Mr. Qiu,
you don't think that if you
use the lotus seed as a threat,
Tantan will give in, do you?
Mr. Qiu, how could you do that?
Xueyi, cut it out.
Why can't I say it?
Don't talk bad about Yuebai!
Don't!
Enough.
Stop arguing.
Come here.
Bai Diezi, listen to me carefully.
I just think of Yuebai
as a friend.
It won't change.
If you must
ask me to be with him,
I won't accept your lotus seed.
Tantan.
Tantan, don't go.
What's wrong with Qiu Yuebai?
How could he use a child?
Exactly.
Bro, I'm telling you,
you're in trouble.
If you don't get the lotus seed,
then
Tantan won't make up with you.
But Bai Diezi was right about one thing.
Adults always make things complicated.
As long as Tantan likes Cui Chen,
whether he gets the lotus seed or not,
Tantan will make up with him.
Is it really that simple?
It won't be that simple.
Believe me,
Qiu Yuebai won't stop so easily.
Gosh.
Uncle,
how many women have you dated
in your 5,000 years of life?
Properly speaking,
I've had about 50 true loves.
Why are you asking me this?
Gosh, Uncle,
I know you too well.
Bro, don't be afraid.
You mustn't give up on Tantan.
Don't let her go easily.
Go straight to her
and say what's on your mind.
You know what,
though she likes you now,
she may dislike you
and be disappointed in you at any time.
Who hasn't been in a relationship?
But I agree with you on this.
The best defense is offense.
Let's be patient, OK?
A long delay means many hitches.
He must act fast.
Bro, you must listen to me and Hu Meng.
You must listen to me.
- Listen to us.
- Listen to me.
Listen to us.
I'm telling you, he must listen to us.
Do you know
how many times I've been dumped?
You deserve it.
What's wrong?
Something on your mind?
I'm sorry.
Did I wake you up?
No.
I woke up when I turned over.
You're worrying about something.
Why don't you tell me?
I may give you some advice.
Actually, it wasn't me.
It's a friend of mine.
Classic beginning.
No.
She's really a friend of mine.
OK, a friend of yours.
Then what?
This friend of mine
met someone earlier.
A man?
At first,
she thought this guy was nasty.
He had better magic arts than her,
better perception than her,
and constantly bullied her.
But then she realized
that whenever she was in danger,
that guy always stepped forward.
He seemed to be good to her.
Then...
Then they got together.
But...
But they broke up afterwards?
Because I...
No, the friend of mine.
She realized one day
that all that guy had done for her
was because she looked like
his ex-girlfriend.
Then she started quarreling with him.
But it didn't work out.
Does it bore you?
No.
I'm not bored.
So,
do you still like him?
I...
I suppose so.
How could you trick me?
I didn't.
Sit down.
Let me give you some real advice.
What did he tell you?
He said he never thought of me
as a substitute.
But I don't feel good about it.
I feel jealous.
You feel jealous
because you don't trust him.
Because he isn't doing the right thing.
You'd better forget about the man
who treats you like a substitute.
Such kind of man
doesn't deserve to live.
OK.
Don't be mad.
I recalled my best friend.
She sacrificed her life
because of a man.
I won't allow you
to make the same mistake.
By the way,
I always carry this jade pendant
with me.
It means a lot to me.
I want you to have it.
No.
It's precious to you.
I can't take it.
Don't you consider me a good friend?
I do.
Then put it on.
Thank you.
Tantan,
have you ever considered other men?
Other men?
Like
Qiu Yuebai?
I've been observing him
over the past few days.
I think he has a good character
and career.
And he risked his life
to save you in the quicksand pit.
Above all,
I think he loves you with all his heart.
But, I...
But I don't love him.
You can spend more time
bonding with him.
You can try to accept him.
I...
Don't rush into any decisions.
Think it over.
[Adapted from Han Yishui's book
on Shuqi Reading Platform, "Blooming"]
[Produced by]
[YOUKU Information Technology (Beijing)]
[All rights of network communication
reserved by YOUKU]