[theme music]
You can have him.
Please take him as yours.
-[Mali gasps]
-You don't care about me at all,
not now or ever. Am I right?
[Horathibodi] Today, the French envoy
is to see the King.
Tell me who you are thinking of.
Go look in the looking glass.
[Narai] Rit Kamhaeng
named you as the envoy.
Will you do it?
[Sorasak] Let me tell you.
The King also has another son.
[tense music]
[Phetracha] Though the King
hasn't given the order
and Khun Pan hasn't accepted
Constantine's proposition.
Your uncle is smart enough
to sense danger.
What danger?
That the western scum would convince
the King to give a royal command.
[Phetracha] His lordship will have
to be an ambassador
to appear before the King of France.
He can't refuse, Duea.
I loathe him so.
How can the officials in Ayutthaya let him
gain such an advancement here?
He was a lowly commoner
in his own country.
But here, he's bestowed with eminent power
and the title Earl Rit Kamhaeng.
He can visit the royal court
as often as he pleases.
He always gets his way with the King.
The speaker isn't the one
who dictates what happens.
It is also decided by the listener.
[sighs]
Why is the King so gullible
as to put blind faith in that scoundrel?
[Sorasak sucks teeth]
Duea.
What is the matter?
[inhales sharply]
Father.
I am your son.
But the truth is,
I am the secret son of the King
and his concubine. Is that right, Father?
If it is so,
I would like--
[Phetracha] Duea, my son.
So much time has passed
and you are now a grown man.
[Phetracha] I have raised you as my own.
Hereafter,
whatever that you are entitled to,
you shall have it
as the son of Earl Phetracha.
You are not the son of King Narai.
[somber music]
What astounds me is that,
if that commoner worships
the King of France so much,
why doesn't he go there himself?
[dramatic music]
[dramatic music continues]
[Dech] Henceforth, we have to study
the French language.
The missionary Pierre Langlois
from Saint Paolo Church
offered to teach us.
Lady Karaked,
can you be our interpreter?
[Karaked] No problem, sir.
[light music]
Hurry up. Do not take time.
Pick the big and fresh ones for me, Prik.
-Yes, my lady.
-See? This one is small.
[Champa] Hm.
[light music]
My lady.
What are you looking at?
What is that tree? Is it a kapok tree?
It is, my lady. It's ripe with kapok pods.
Whoa.
What are you thinking, my lady?
[lively music]
[scoffs]
[Prik] Listen. Clean up after yourself
once you're done.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[tranquil music]
[Prik] Good grief.
I've never seen such a large pillow.
Won't our heads disappear into it?
I've never seen such a thing.
-Of course, you have.
-From where?
Here.
[gasps, scoffs]
[both chuckling]
[calm music]
-Waen.
-Yes, my lord.
-Where is her ladyship?
-[Waen] She's sewing a pillow.
"Sewing a pillow."
-She is sewing a pillow?
-Yes, my lord.
Her ladyship always prepares tea for him.
She's not here today, so...
[light music]
[clears throat]
I'm thirsty.
I'm so thirsty.
Khun Pi, go drink water if you're thirsty.
[Dech clears throat]
I said I'm thirsty.
[sighs]
Get yourself some water.
Do you want to drink kapok?
[Karaked] Stuff it firmly.
Boong, stuff it properly.
I will leave now.
Yes, sir.
-Stuff it well, Chuang.
-Yes, my lady.
You too, Chik. Make it firm.
Yes, my lady. The pillow is very big.
It's not big. It's the right size.
Hey.
[scoffs]
[Prik chuckles]
[light music]
My lord, here's your tea.
[sighs]
I don't want it.
[playful music]
[door closes]
[knocking on door]
Choi, I said I don't want it.
Do you want a slap?
No, sir.
[sighs]
Here's your tea. I heard you were thirsty.
Suit yourself.
[romantic music]
[lively music]
[lively music continues]
It's finished, my lady.
[playful music]
[playful music continues]
Oh! Her ladyship wouldn't listen to me
when I said the pillow was too big.
[Prik] How can we rest our heads on it?
It's enormous.
You really can, Lady Champa.
It's comfortable too.
[Prik scoffs]
[quirky music]
[grunts]
[romantic music]
[romantic music continues]
[laughing]
[Champa] Lady Karaked.
You're laughing for no apparent reason.
Do show some manners
since you're about to be married.
You embarrass yourself time and again
wherever you go.
[sighs]
[Dech laughing]
[chuckles]
[playful music]
[calm music]
The moon here is so big.
Do you want to hear a song, Lord Hora?
What? A song?
What song?
-[laughs]
-[Horathibodi] Ah. Ah. Ah.
I don't want to hear
a series of songs, Karaked.
I'm feeling drowsy.
I might fall asleep mid-song.
Let me sing to you, Lord Hora.
I guarantee it will wake you up.
Very well.
-I'll start now.
-Okay.
âª The moon is shining brightly âª
-âª The sky... âª
-Very well.
Your song really did wake me up.
-Really?
-[Horathibodi] Yes.
Is it beautiful, Lord Hora?
Yes.
[laughs]
Whose song is this?
I've never heard it before.
[Karaked laughs]
What kind of song is that?
It sounds peculiar.
Is it beautiful, Lady Champa?
Hmm.
It is, but it's unlike songs
from Ayutthaya.
Is it a song from your home
in Song Kwae, Lady Karaked?
Yes, my lady. It's a song from my town.
Hmm...
I've listened to songs from Song Kwae,
but they're different from yours.
[Champa sighs]
Come, Prik. Chuang.
I'm going to my chambers.
-Yes, my lady.
It's a modernized version, Lady Champa.
Okay.
[clicks tongue]
Is it a beautiful song, Khun Pi?
His lordship wasn't listening.
He is busy working.
Choi.
You are dismissed.
Yes, my lord.
[soft chuckle]
[Karaked scoffs]
[romantic music]
[romantic music continues]
It's the sweetest song I've ever heard
to praise the moon's beauty.
Did you hear me sing?
Every word of it.
I sang my song for you.
Next time, you will have to sing for me.
Indeed. I should be the one singing.
-Why?
Uh...
It's a song to praise
Karaked's beauty, Father.
-I see.
-[Dech chuckles]
Then, you must learn to sing it.
Yes, Father.
[chuckles]
-You can go, Muang.
-[Muang] Yes, my lord.
[Horathibodi] I'm going to bed.
[romantic music]
-Are you sleepy?
[both chuckle]
Khun Pi, I want to visit a temple.
Can you--
You've been to every temple here.
Where else do you want to go?
I think you must know Ayutthaya
better than me by now.
Your curiosity is impossible to satisfy.
[groans]
There's no other temple here.
Why don't we go to Lavo?
[dramatic music]
Lavo!
[Karaked] You are so kind, Khun Pi.
I want to see
where the King keeps his telescopes.
Where are they?
[Dech] At Kraison Siharat Palace
and Saint Paolo Church at Thale Chup Son.
[Karaked] Yes, sir. I want to see them.
[dramatic music]
[light music]
[light music continues]
I'm here to see Madam. Is she here?
She's making desserts inside. Follow me.
He thinks himself
equal to the King, my lady.
His audacity will be his downfall.
Who do you mean?
His home is as grand as the King's palace.
No one is as shameless as this westerner.
Buildings in his homeland
are built with concrete.
He must be used to it.
Plus, this building may be used
to welcome western guests
and make known the glory of Ayutthaya.
Don't think too much into it.
But it is still wrong.
No one would dare put themselves
on the same level as their masters.
[servant 1] It is uncustomary, my lady.
The King favors this westerner.
[Abb] The person who criticizes him
may be punished instead, my lady.
Abb, you're so nosy.
I want to see Lady Tong Guyomar's son.
You look so pretty, my little Jorge.
[chuckles]
[Karaked laughs]
-[Jorge coos]
-[chuckles]
Where's the other one?
[Mali] Here.
-[Karaked smooches]
-[Mali giggles]
I had no idea you were pregnant
with your youngest son.
Are you okay, Lady Mali?
I'm fine.
My youngest is called João.
He's still a baby.
I breastfeed him myself,
and without a wet nurse.
[Karaked] But you still find time
to make desserts.
[João coos]
[gasps]
[Karaked] They look appetizing.
[Mali] Take João to bed.
Jorge.
[smooches]
[Karaked] What is this, Lady Mali?
[Mali] I came up with the recipe,
but it doesn't have a name yet.
It's made from duck egg yolk and flour.
I figure that if I simmer the sugar,
it will make the desserts last longer.
[clicks tongue]
You have found your calling.
My calling?
What do you mean?
Well...
It looks appetizing and smells good.
[Karaked] It should taste delightful.
Let's give it a try.
[sucks teeth, yells]
[yelling]
It's hot.
-Lady Karaked.
-Goodness.
[dramatic music]
[dramatic music continues]
I have an idea.
Poom, follow me.
[light music]
[light music continues]
[Clara] It is so pretty.
What is it called, madam?
I call it
thong...
thong jeeb.
[groans]
Do you think it sounds like
the Chinese sweets?
Then, I will call it...
thong yip.
[laughs]
That's it.
I put more flour in this one.
I will call it thong yod.
The dessert over there is made
by dripping batter into boiled sugar.
I call it thong pae.
That's not good.
I think foi thong sounds better.
Oops.
Foi thong? I love this name, Lady Karaked.
You are so creative.
[laughing]
[lively music]
What's wrong, baby?
[laughs]
Come, Jorge.
I'll visit you again
before I leave for Ayutthaya.
Yes, Lady Karaked.
[light music]
My lady, aren't they back yet?
I'm sitting here with you.
How would I know?
But you're his lordship's mother.
Huh? You speak like
you have never had a child.
Don't you know that
mothers and sons live separate lives?
Prik did have a child, my lady.
-Chuang.
-[Chuang] It's true, Prik.
-My lady.
-Yes?
Prik used to keep...
-[giggles]
-Chuang.
-She called it her baby.
-What did she keep?
Don't you dare.
She kept a dog.
[laughing]
-She called herself its mother.
-[women laugh]
[Chuang] No.
My lady, dogs are more loyal than people.
I would rather have a dog as a child
than a human being.
You already have one indeed, Prik.
[Chuang] Hey!
[giggling]
They are back, my lady.
[Champa] Go eat something.
I already ate.
I couldn't wait for you two.
Where are you going this afternoon?
[calm music]
Thank you.
I want to go buy spoons and forks.
[laughs]
Do as you please.
Once we are married,
I will let you be
the principal mistress of the house.
I don't want to be a principal wife.
[Dech] You won't have to be.
Because I will not put you
in that position by having someone else.
Oh, what is this?
[Dech chuckles]
Pork sarongs. How nice.
What do you mean by what you said?
I will take you
to see Phra Prang Sam Yot today.
[gasps]
I never imagined I would get to see
the real Phra Prang Sam Yot, Rueang.
-Whoa!
-Mm.
[Dech sighs]
Do you want to know what I meant earlier?
Not anymore.
Why is that?
I said I don't want to know.
Mm.
Come.
Let's go.
Whose horse is that?
It's the horse I've arranged.
[horse whinnies]
Walking there will tire us.
Lavo has no canal
for us to travel by boat
like in Ayutthaya.
But I don't know how to ride a horse.
[snickers]
It's not difficult.
-Chuang.
-Yes, my lady?
Come with us.
Oh...
[laughs]
Who would allow Chuang to come?
Only the two of us will go
on a horse riding tour.
Can't you see there is only one horse?
How will her ladyship get there, then?
[playful music]
[Karaked yells, gasps]
Khun Pi.
[yells]
Yes?
Did you see the gifts
the ambassador presented to the King?
I did.
What are they?
[Dech] They are peculiar-looking gifts.
The King is very satisfied.
How are they peculiar?
We've never seen such things,
so they seem peculiar.
What are they?
Many things.
Won't you tell me?
[Dech] Mmm.
Sit comfortably first.
There are plenty of things.
You'll be tired
by the time I'm done telling you.
I will be fine.
You won't. Don't argue with me.
I know for certain
that there is a scope used to observe
the distant stars above.
Khun Pi.
Do you approve of Duke Kosathibodi
being the ambassador?
I most certainly do.
Ambassador de Chaumont
has great respect for his lordship.
He is indeed magnificent.
He is articulate and very knowledgeable.
He is also handsome and charming.
His magnificence has gained him
twenty-two wives.
-[horse neighs]
-What? Twenty-two wives?
[gasps]
I'm going to faint.
Why are you surprised?
It is common.
How is it common to have that many wives?
Wow.
How long will it take for him
to circle back to his first wife?
What did you say?
What circle?
[sighs]
How do his first and second wife feel?
Hmm... I don't know.
I am not his wife.
[laughing]
Do you think it's impossible?
You should try living in Bangkok.
You will have chills down your spine.
[laughing]
Are you cold?
No.
No, I'm not.
How can you not be? I clearly heard you
talking about having chills.
Khun Pi.
Do you see that?
[gasps]
Phra Prang Sam Yot.
It's so beautiful.
This is Khmer architecture.
[Karaked] It was built
nearly four centuries ago
in the reign of Jayavarman VII.
[Karaked] A Buddha in the Nak Prok posture
is enshrined at the center.
The bodhisattva Avalokitesvara
is enshrined on the right,
and a Prajnaparmita
is enshrined on the left.
[Karaked] Its structure
is corn-cob shaped,
ornamented with elaborate stucco work.
It is absolutely terrific.
Lady Karaked?
Oh, how do I know about that?
I had a teacher when I was young.
He told me about it.
Khun Pi, tell me honestly.
Doesn't it bother you
that people call me insane?
[chuckles]
What do you mean?
Well, you are to be wedded
to an insane woman.
Is that right?
That's right. Isn't that shameful?
I suppose I'm as insane as you are.
Khun Pi, you should say I'm not insane.
You told me not to care what others think.
We know ourselves best.
[Dech] I am doing as I am told.
If you are insane,
I'd rather be insane with you.
[romantic music]
[romantic music continues]
[calm music]
[sighs]
Prik.
Yes, my lady.
[Prik sighs]
[Champa] Are you miserable
because you didn't get to go with them?
Yes, my lady.
I told you, that town is nothing
compared to the grandeur of Ayutthaya.
But I want to see
what Lavo is like, my lady.
[sighs]
I will let you come with me next time.
Why can't you take me today?
Look at her attitude.
[sighs]
The palace has three sections.
The building with the mondop spire
is the outer court.
Dusit Sawan Thanya Mahaprasat Hall
is the throne hall.
[Dech] There is a grand window
for the King to receive his guests.
That's the central court.
Chantara Phisan Pavilion is where
the King has a meeting with officials.
Over there
is Suttha Sawan Pavilion,
where the King resides.
Khun Pi, I want to see Phra Chao Hao Hall.
[Dech] Phra Chao Hao Hall is
a western-style building.
It is used to welcome guests
from overseas.
[Karaked] Khun Pi, before we leave,
can I visit Earl Rit Kamhaeng's house?
I want to bid Lady Mali farewell.
Find more people if necessary.
Get women, children, and priests.
Yes, Master.
Your lordship.
[foreboding music]
Viscount Wisarn Wacha.
Lady Karaked.
Are you here to see Tong Guyomar?
Yes, Earl Rit Kamhaeng.
Are you on your way out?
Yes, I'm going to oversee
the construction of the fort.
Yes, sir. Can I go in
to see Lady Tong Guyomar?
Come, Khun Pi.
[Phaulkon] Wait.
Take the men to the fort.
I'll follow you
once I'm done with my business here.
Yes, Master.
His mind changes fast.
I just realized your visit
is more important than my obligation.
If you want to see
Tong Guyomar, follow me.
Come, Khun Pi.
[light music]
Khun Pi, try the desserts.
Thong yip and thong yod are delicious.
I know how to make them.
Lady Mali is an excellent cook.
[foreboding music]
[foreboding music continues]
I should get down to business.
I am here to bid you farewell
before I leave for Ayutthaya.
You're leaving so soon, Lady Karaked.
The French ambassador is leaving soon.
[Karaked] My betrothed and I have
to go back
to get ready for the voyage.
[Mali] Have a safe journey, Lady Karaked.
Don't forget to visit me
next time you come to Lavo.
I won't.
Goodbye.
Farewell, Lady Tong Guyomar.
It is good that you two
got to see each other.
[Karaked] Khun Pi, look at him.
He's glaring at us.
His eyes are blazing,
like he's going to shoot fire at us.
[Dech sighs]
Do not joke around.
Let's leave.
I will see you off.
Goodbye, sir.
-Good luck, my lady.
-Farewell.
[Phaulkon] Tong Guyomar.
Tong Guyomar.
[foreboding music]
Leave them be.
This is between husband and wife.
Don't let it bother you.
[tense music]
Is this common, Khun Pi?
Is what common?
That a husband beats his wife.
It is. Why can't he?
He can't. Wives are human beings too.
You're talking strangely again.
Who says they aren't?
Men and women are equal.
How are they equal?
A woman is under a man's protection.
She is under his patronage.
How can they be equal?
[gasps]
Patronage?
That's right. Patronage.
I can't accept it.
Accept what?
If my husband beats me,
one of us will not live to see
another day for sure.
I mean it.
Can you compose yourself?
Your language disturbs me.
If you are disobedient,
won't you let me lay my hands on you?
You need to be whipped at least,
to be disciplined.
I will lock you in the house
and forbid you to go out.
It seems like a good idea.
[chuckles]
You can forget that idea.
[laughs]
[Phaulkon] After all this time,
are you still longing for him?
What are you talking about?
Viscount Wisarn Wacha has the nerve
to come here on the pretense
of bringing his betrothed.
He probably wanted to see
how his ex-lover was doing.
What will others think
if they hear you speak like that?
[Mali] Won't they think
his lordship commits misconduct
and that I am a whore?
Don't think everyone will be like you.
You have never been so provoked.
Now, you dare argue with me
only because I'm disgracing
Viscount Wisarn Wacha's name.
-Is that so?
-[gasps]
[foreboding music]
[whimpers]
[Phaulkon pants]
[somber music]
[somber music continues]
[light music]
Oh, I think they're here, Muang.
Yes, my lord.
[Champa sighs]
You're home, Lady Champa.
Yes, sir. We went downstream,
so it was quick.
[sighs]
Are you hungry?
I would like to go and change my clothes.
I'm not hungry. Do take your time.
Yes, sir.
[Karaked] Lord Hora.
Yes?
It's a shame you didn't come with us.
It was so much fun.
Is that so, Lady Karaked?
I'm glad that you...
have a happy life here.
[tranquil music]
[tranquil music continues]
Is that right?
Yes, sir.
[sighs]
Dech will be away in a few days.
[Horathibodi] Don't you worry.
Stay with me until your betrothed is back.
I will arrange the wedding.
Why are you crying? What upsets you?
[sobbing]
I'm not upset, sir.
I am happy.
[Horathibodi laughing]
[romantic music]
[romantic music continues]
I love Lord Hora.
He is so kind, Pin, Yaem.
[Pin and Yaem] Yes, my lady.
He was kind even when my lady...
Was a wicked woman?
[both] Yes, my lady.
Are you telling me that
Lord Hora has shown me kindness,
even when I was a bad person?
[both] Yes, my lady.
I know.
People with kind hearts will show mercy
even to the cruelest person.
I am lucky that he takes pity on me.
[Pin and Yaem] My lady.
Let's continue sewing the shirt, Yaem.
Yes, my lady.
Here you go.
[theme music]
[birds chirping]
Measure his arm's length.
The upper arm.
Not too tight, Pin.
Tailor it to the measurements.
Please try on the shirt, Khun Pi.
What shirt is this?
It's called a vest.
What is it for?
It's an undergarment to keep you warm.
[soft chuckle]
Can I wear it over my shirt?
It's better to wear it underneath,
to keep you under my spell.
Under your spell?
Yes, to keep you
from falling for someone else.
Someone else? Who do you mean?
[laughs]
I mean someone close to you overseas.
Someone close to me?
I won't see anyone.
I will only see someone far away.
Let me take this off, then.
[romantic music]
[romantic music continues]
[both laugh]
Pin. Yaem.
[both] My lady.
Let's get sewing.
[both] Yes, my lady.
[birds chirping]
Khun Pi, your clothes are ready.
[Karaked] Come see them.
I made them thick to keep you warm
since it's cold over there.
[quirk music]
Prik, look at this.
[soft chuckle]
Do you know that Master Chi Pa Khao
will be coming with us?
Really?
[gasps]
That's good.
He can protect you from unseen danger.
You are very thoughtful.
Of course.
Master told me
he wants to see you tomorrow.
What?
[tense music]
Why are you staring at me?
You asked to see me, didn't you?
Good grief!
Don't you think about coming to visit me?
Well,
Khun Pi said you wanted
my opinion on something.
What about, sir?
You will know soon.
[Chi Pa Khao] Why so impatient?
What are we waiting for?
People.
[Chi Pa Khao] I have many disciples.
I will be going to France
with Lord Pan and Dech in a few days.
I need to make arrangements
for my long absence.
I must leave them words of advice.
Go sit over there, my lady.
It's improper for a lady
to sit facing a man alone like this.
Improper? Everything I do is improper.
[sighs]
[ominous music]
[ominous music continues]
Earl Phetracha.
Master.
Count Sorasak.
Viscount Wisarn Wacha.
Lord Rueang and the rest of you.
[men] Master.
[Chi Pa Khao] I will be sailing to France
in a matter of days.
I will be away for a long time.
I want all of you over here
to recruit people
and keep training them for combat.
Conduct yourself
according to our moral principles.
Do not stray from them.
Our kingdom is presently at peace,
but we can't predict
what will happen in the future.
So many westerners are in Ayutthaya.
I am being vigilant because we don't know
when they will try to occupy us.
[Sorasak] The worrisome prospects are
Prince Pi, the King's son,
and his brother, Prince Apaiyatot, Master.
[Sorasak] Both of them have their eyes
on the throne.
Thus, they seek support
from the westerner, Earl Rit Kamhaeng.
That will be your task,
and yours too, Lady Karaked.
She is my only female disciple.
[Chi Pa Khao] I accepted her
because I have enough reason to.
While Viscount Wisarn and I are away,
she will provide answers
to your questions.
[foreboding music]
[theme music]
[Dech] Someone else? Who do you mean?
I mean someone close to you overseas.
Someone close to me?
I won't see anyone.
[laughs]
I will only see someone far away.
[theme music]
-Choi.
-My lord.
What are you doing here?
I'm looking, my lord.
Looking at what?
The moon, my lord. It's so big.
Are there people on the moon, my lord?
I don't know. What a silly question.
[lively music]
[lively music continues]
[Prik] Mm-hm!
[Choi gasps]
Oh! You scared me.
-Hey, Choi.
-Hm?
Say whatever you have to say.
-You said you had something to tell me.
[Chuang] Mm-hm.
Well? Look at him acting all smug.
How secretive. You annoy me.
-[Prik scoffs]
-If you're annoyed,
then go back to the masters' quarters.
The nerve. Do you dare chase me away, huh?
Then, I will leave.
[Prik] Stop!
Damn. Come back here.
Hey! Prik, what am I supposed to do?
-[sighs]
-[Chik] That's right.
If you won't go, we will.
-[servant 2] Right.
-Aren't you happy?
Don't you know that Prik
doesn't always mean what she says?
[all laugh]
[Prik] Take that, Boong.
You will have to starve today.
I won't give you food.
Prik, what will I eat
if you don't give me food?
-You can eat my foot.
-[yells]
Boong, since Prik never means
what she says,
I think she will let you eat for sure.
-[Prik] You're such a know-it-all.
-[all laugh]
You're suddenly so chatty, aren't you?
Will you tell me?
You're called a tattletale for a reason.
-Fine.
-[Prik] Good. Tell me.
I let you ridicule me
because what I'm about to tell you
is highly confidential.
[all gasp]
His lordship
used to loathe Lady Karaked, right?
[all] Yes.
But he doesn't loathe her anymore.
[playful music]
[playful music continues]
Don't give me that look.
I'm telling the truth.
[Choi] I will leave now.
[snickers]
[Prik scoffs]
Is that all?
-[Chuang] Prik.
-[Prik] What?
I don't think that's it.
That's right. How did you know
that westerners have such a gesture
when greeting one another?
Doesn't a verbal greeting suffice?
I didn't say it, Lady Champa.
Khun Pi said the Earl told him
that westerners make such a gesture
when they see each other.
His lordship also claimed
that I know how to do it,
-which I actually do.
-[sighs]
That was a long speech you made.
Just teach Dech,
so he won't embarrass himself
in a foreign land.
Don't be alarmed, Lady Champa.
What an odd thing to say.
Why would I be alarmed
by a greeting gesture?
Champa.
If you keep on bickering,
we will have to stay here until evening.
I would like to know very much.
[Champa groans]
Dech.
You don't want to know, do you?
I do, Mother.
[Horathibodi] Hear, hear.
[chuckling]
Khun Pi, move closer to me.
Turn around and face me.
[playful music]
[tranquil music]
[all gasp]
[suspenseful music]
[dramatic music]
Khun Pi, stop grinning.
This is just a greeting gesture.
Good gracious. How obscene. I can't watch.
Me neither.
-[Prik] My lady.
-[Champa sighs]
Lady Champa.
[Champa] Go. You're all dismissed.
-Chuang.
-[Chuang] My lady.
-Prik.
-My lady, this is unbearable.
-I can't stand it. My lady.
-Prik.
Prik can't stand watching them.
Stop calling her, Lady Champa.
[Champa] Prik.
Lady Champa, don't leave.
It's a normal greeting gesture.
Muang, get the chicken.
I'm going to a cockfight.
-Lord Hora.
-[Horathibodi groans]
Westerners are indifferent
to this, Pin. Yaem.
[Pin and Yaem] I'll get to work, my lady.
Oh?
It's just a slight touch on the face.
-Like this.
-Lady Karaked.
You look like you still don't get it.
I do.
[romantic music]
[romantic music continues]
[sighs]
[both chuckle]
[lively music]
Uh?
Use the spoon
and the fork.
[light music]
[utensils clinking]
[Prik whimpers]
-[Prik yells]
-[Horathibodi gasps]
How scary.
What now, Prik?
[Prik] They might pierce your mouth.
I can't bear it.
Western customs are so bizarre.
[sighs]
Will you excuse me?
-[Champa] Come, Prik.
-[Prik] Yes, my lady.
[calm music]
[Prik] Pack them carefully.
Put it down there,
and tie it tightly.
[Prik] Do it properly.
Aren't Pin and Yaem helping you?
Are you asking for Pin and Yaem?
Wait. Or are you really...
[sighs]
This one is okay,
but I want a couple more pieces
of fabric in purple,
black, and light-yellow.
We get purple dye from Jambolan plums,
black dye from ebony.
And light-yellow dye
from jackfruit cores, my lady.
Let's get them from the kitchen,
so we can make dyes.
-[both] Yes.
-Mm-hm. Let's go.
-[Karaked] Hurry up.
-[Pin] Yes, my lady.
Wait for me, my lady.
Wait. What will we use as a container?
-[Pin] Will this do?
-Yes. Let's go.
[quirky music]
Khun Pi.
What are you doing here?
-I've come to read.
-What?
[chuckles]
Why have you come here to read?
Why? Can't I read here?
Uh... Hello? This is my chambers.
[Dech sighs]
Khun Pi, what's the matter?
Why did you ask me so?
Well, you come to my chambers
like you're keeping watch on me.
Did I do something wrong?
[playful music]
Pin and Yaem.
[Pin and Yaem] My lord.
Prepare tea and snacks for me.
Tomorrow, I will be away.
Yes?
What are you saying? I don't understand.
[sighs deeply]
[whispers]
What's with him?
Is he giving me words of farewell?
Lady Karaked.
Yes, sir.
[romantic music]
Tomorrow, I'll be far away from you.
Don't you have something for me
to remind me of you?
[stammers]
Well...
[Dech] What's wrong?
You're shaking. Did you hear what I said?
Should I repeat myself?
No, I heard you.
Do you have it?
What do you desire?
Something you use every day.
Something you keep with you
that will remind me of you
whenever I look at it.
It will reassure me that, when I'm away,
you will be waiting for me
with a faithful heart
and won't betray me.
Wait for me here, Khun Pi.
[Karaked laughs]
[sighs]
[romantic music]
[romantic music continues]
I rest my head on this pillow every night.
You can use it when you sleep.
The western land is cold.
If you should falter
and fall for any western lady,
this should hold you back
when you lay down on it.
If you can wait,
I will also reserve myself
and won't let anyone touch me.
I will wait for you to come back.
[romantic music]
Thank you.
Yes, sir.
[romantic music]
I give you my word.
Yes, sir.
[romantic music]
[romantic music continues]
[rooster crows]
Hey.
Are you awake, my lady?
Yes.
-We were sleeping like a log.
-[both laugh]
[groans]
-Oh.
-Hey.
What's wrong, my lady?
[gasps]
[sucks teeth]
I sprained my neck.
[both] How come?
I didn't have my pillow.
[Pin] Uh...
Where did your pillow go?
It's gone.
And where has your pillow gone?
Well...
[groans]
What?
[Champa] Carry them carefully.
Be careful with them.
[dramatic music]
Pin. Yaem.
[Pin and Yaem] My lady.
Do you see my pillow now?
[Pin and Yaem] Yes, my lady.
Dech, what are you carrying?
Give it to the servant.
I can carry it, Father.
Oh, it will weigh you down.
Let the servant carry it.
-Choi.
-It's fine, Mother.
Be safe, my son.
How strange.
People here don't hug their parents.
Pardon, my lady?
[playful music]
What is this? Are they clothes?
-[Horathibodi] Give it to Choi.
-Well...
It's my treasured object.
What?
-[Dech] Prik.
-My lord.
Take care of my mother for me.
Yes, my lord. Please don't worry.
I will take care of her ladyship.
-You should get going.
-Yes, Father.
I will be away for a long time.
May you be well and happy here.
Do not worry about anything.
Yes, sir.
Do not...
be tempted.
Yes, sir.
[theme music]
[somber music]
[Karaked] I rest my head
on this pillow every night.
You can use it when you sleep.
If you should falter
and fall for any western lady,
this should hold you back
when you lay down on it.
[Karaked] If you can wait,
I will also reserve myself.
[Karaked] I will wait for you
to come back.
My lord.
[Choi] Lord Rueang brought the boat
to send you off.
Lady Chanwad is with him.
Lady Chanwad.
Thank you, sir.
[chuckles]
Did you two come together?
No, sir.
I ran into his lordship at the waterfront.
Mm-hm.
-Boon.
-[Boon] My lady.
Tell the servants
to put things in the kitchen.
[Boon] Go to the kitchen.
Thank you so much
for coming to see me off.
How long will you be away, Dech?
Very long. I suppose a year.
[Lord Rueang] You need to join
the boat procession to the river mouth.
I will take you there.
Thank you so much.
I will say goodbye here.
[Lord Rueang] Dech.
Wait for me at the waterfront.
I will be with you shortly.
Lady Chanwad.
You are in my every thought,
but I do not dare visit you
because her ladyship...
My mother is no different
from any other mothers.
She only wants to be certain,
and it will be your duty
to reassure her.
[uplifting music]
Did you go bid his lordship farewell
at his home, Chanwad?
Yes, Mother.
Did you see anyone else?
I did.
Viscount Rueang Apai Pakdi was also there
to see his lordship off.
Viscount Rueang Apai Pakdi?
I disapprove of him.
I won't accept him as my son-in-law.
[tense music]
Didn't you take my advice?
How could I?
Her mother loathes me.
You want me to pay her a visit constantly,
according to your phrase...
"Constant dripping wears away a stone."
I don't know how.
Don't worry. It's easy.
Go visit her
by choosing the time
when her mother isn't home.
How will I know
when her ladyship is away?
Good grief. Just go see whether her car...
whether her boat is there.
[lively music]
[lively music continues]
Bai.
You've been doing the laundry for ages.
[babbles]
What? Come here at once.
[quirky music]
December 22nd,
B.E. 2228,
the embassy from Ayutthaya
traveled with the French mission
of King Louis XIV,
led by Monsieur Chevalier de Chaumont.
They traveled back to Paris
on big vessels
called La Maligne and L'Oiseau.
There were also 20 students on board
who were to learn European knowledge.
Master Chi Pa Khao also accompanied them.
All is according to history.
Does history predict everything
correctly, my lady?
Every word.
Does history mention
his lordship's overseas voyage, my lady?
Well, well.
You are so insightful lately.
I see you know about history.
You said it hundreds of times.
We can assume
they are past incidents, my lady.
Yes, my lady.
[chuckles]
Okay. This is what history says.
On the voyage, the ship will encounter
whirlpools and storms.
Sky-high waves will rock the ship
up and down,
causing the ship to spin
and fall into a vortex of water.
If it wasn't for
Master Chi Pa Khao's help,
mm-hm, the ship would surely sink.
[Pin gasps]
Does history tell it accurately, my lady?
[Yaem] When his lordship returns,
we will know if history is right.
Does history say how long
his lordship will be away, my lady?
Listen carefully.
It will be a year.
[Pin and Yaem] What?
It's true.
He will be away for over a year.
[Yaem gasps]
Over a year? We are doomed.
Why is that?
If his lordship is gone that long,
someone here will miss him dearly.
[both giggling]
[somber music]
[Pin and Yaem] My poor lady.
[Dech] I will be gone for a long time.
May you be well and happy here.
Do not worry about anything.
[Karaked] Does your husband
have a hand in bringing the French troops
into Ayutthaya?
Why did he bring in troops?
He is up to something.
[Prik] His lordship is back. Come quick.
You look healthier,
not all skin and bones like before.
Did I gain weight?
[Karaked] Kritsana Kali.
[Prik shrieking]
[Prik] Help!
[Horathibodi] If we cast
the Kritsana Kali spell
and Karaked starts behaving
like her old self again,
what will you say?
Please don't go anywhere.
[Dech] Stay here. Don't leave me.
[closing theme music]