Hello?
Why'd it take you so long to answer the phone?
If you answered the phone just a second later then I would've hung up on you.
I need a proxy buyer. The condition is the same as before.
Hello?
CEO Jo, are you listening?
Why aren't you answering me?
CEO Jo, say something.
You think I'm just here to take care of your boredom or something?
I will be your regular customer so take care of my boredom, too. I'm a bit bored these days.
You should go call a friend if you're so bored.
My best friend went somewhere very far.
That's why I'm bored. I'm super bored.
But why is your voice like that, CEO Jo?
Are you not well?
What do we do? I'm also leaving to a place far away as well.
Where to?
Somewhere very, very far.
No, you can't! Then what about my proxy purchase?
Who am I supposed to call?
I don't do proxy buying anymore.
So...
don't ever call me again.
Hello? CEO Jo!
CEO Jo!
♫  It's very weird  ♫
♫ I'm loving you with all that I have. ♫
♫ How and who can do such a thing? ♫
♫  It really doesn't work out well for me even though I try  ♫
♫ Just like you back then... ♫
She should just be a proxy buyer. She's not fun anymore.
Master!
I will be sleeping over here tonight.
You go sleep in my room tonight.
Why would you want to sleep here when you have a nicer bed?
Over there...
I just can't seem to sleep. That's why.
When the late Chairman wasn't able to sleep,
this is what he did.
Pull your chin down and look straight at the lens, please.
I'm going to take the photo now.  One, two, three.
I'm here to get my passport issued.
- Australia?!
- Yup.
It's called a working holiday visa. I will be able to work and also learn English at the same time.
How could you do that without even discussing it with us?
A year will go by quickly. This will help me make some money for a business venture and also gather some ideas.
I'll learn English so well before I return.
Your auntie will be responsible for teaching you your English starting from now on.
I don't have to learn English. Don't leave, Aunt.
- You are so adorable. I'll be back after my part-time job.
- You should get some rest.
You just got discharged from the hospital.
I have to go make some money for my plane ticket. I'm off now.
You scared me. Why'd you come here?
Why do you think I'm here? I came here to fix up your old scooter.
You do know that what you are doing here is pretty random?
Last night, your motorscooter randomly appeared in my dream.
It was saying that it was on its last legs and it needed to borrow the hand of a god to fix it.
So that's why I'm here. And I'm that god's hand.
Forget about it. I can take this to a car shop. So just go.
Wow, Jo Ji Ah, you are so rich. You could just pay me to fix it then.
It will only take me thirty minutes to fix this. So just wait a little while.
Were you able to get some sleep?
Why do you care?
Because you're my creditor.
I have to pay off the debt but if the creditor dies unnaturally, then I'll be in a ridiculous situation.
You didn't understand what I just said, did you?
Seriously, you're such a...
This will be good for at least another month.
- Only a month?
- You should get a new one while you're at it.
What if it stops while you're in the middle of the road?
What's wrong? I didn't focus on the right part of this situation again?
Don't come back here again in the future.
You told me to take responsibility, didn't you?
What I'm doing now is taking responsibility for what I've done.
I'm off now.
There will be an urgent board of directors meeting just as you feared.
The agenda is your dismissal from office.
The weather's nice, too, so smile.
If you save your smiles, they turn into poop, too.
Get lost.
Please come and take a look at these cute hats and gloves.
They are very pretty and will keep you warm so please come on take a look.
Hello there.
They are so cute.
- Can we try them on?
- Of course, you can. Would you like to try this one?
Yes, please. This one is so pretty.
- It really looks good on you, and it's really pretty.
- Oh, really?
- How much is this?
- It is 15,000 won. Would you like one?
Yes, please. Thank you.
Thank you.
You're more adorable.
- Can I take a look at these?
- Yes, of course. Welcome.
This is so adorable. How much is...
Why are you making that facial expression? Is it because nobody is buying these?
I will purchase them all for you. Give me this one and also this one.
Give me this one here and just give me all of them. Come on, give them all to me.
- Do you really want all of these?
- Yes, of course.
Here you go.
Give me all of them.
AG-3, we will soon turn you into a very handsome man.
Thank you, Doctor.
Please make me into a super-duper handsome man.
This is something that Kim Min Kyu used to say pretty often.
Pi, you deleted all of the backup files regarding Kim Min Kyu, right?
Yes, I did.
I wonder if she heard any of us say that?
A part-time job at a parcel service?
Do you know how hard that work is?
No, it's not. I like it. It's the best when it comes to helping me stop thinking about stuff.
- Hello.
- Here you go.
Kim Min Kyu will be dismissed from the company by tomorrow.
The stockholders who are in my favor and the borrowed stocks will easily make us the majority.
Kim Min Kyu's dismissal is already a done deal.
The Santa Maria Team and AG-3
are pretty much in our hands now.
Tomorrow, Hwang Yoo Cheol, you will be the Chairman of KM Financial.
But, Father, you said that you would let me handle this case.
I did leave it up to you, but what happened?
Were you able to hand over that stupid robot to Martin?
No, I'm looking for someone who can take care of this properly again and—
Just forget about it all. If we take down Kim Min Kyu,
then all we have to do is hand over AG-3 to Martin. So why are you trying to do useless things?
I'm setting up the table for you,
and all you have to do is pick up the spoon to eat. So why are you so dissatisfied?
I'm even making Ri El yours, too.
No! Will you just stop it?!
Did you find Jang Do Sam?
I'm sorry, not yet.
That little rat.
Why did he have to come back to Korea anyway?
If he possibly opens his mouth about the death of Chairman Park Seong Jin then we are all dead meat.
Find him. Make sure to find him
and tape his mouth shut.
You can't let him run into Kim Min Kyu, whatever you do!
Hello?
Is this Jang Doo Sam?
You came by yourself, right?
As you can see, I'm by myself right now.
I'll have to think about it again.
Hello?
Don't find me until I contact you.
Mr. Jang Doo Sam!!
Don't look for me!
Jang Doo Sam!!
Crap.
Team Leader Jo?
I think there's something more behind Chairman Park Seong Jin's accident.
All that we can do now is go with Plan B, right?
Ri El: Where are you? You haven't forgotten about our plans later, right?
Your package has arrived.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Hold on. I'll check it right now.
- Okay.
Is the dress from earlier prettier? Or is this one prettier?
Yeah. They're all pretty.
What's that half-hearted response?
No, what are you saying?
Can you sign this quickly?
Yes.
Here you go.
If it were Yoo Cheol...
Hmm, I like the third one
because your neckline's pretty.
Kim Min Kyu,
you've become super-duper handsome.
That's good.
That's good that he's doing well.
The chairman is arriving.
We'll start the meeting now.
As informed, the agenda is regarding Chairman Kim Min Kyu's dismissal from office.
The reasoning is to stabilize the company.
Do you think that's an acceptable reason for his dismissal?
Because of his bad-tempered
and weird actions,
trust towards our company has decreased.
Don't you all know that?
In order to develop a new company's culture that's suitable for the 21st century,
we can no longer accept the old ways
where the largest shareholder treats the company as his own possession.
And that's what most of us believe.
So far, how much profit did he bring to our company?
You only care about money.
You should think about our company's image, too.
Now the Chairman will speak.
Who's the next candidate
for this spot?
It's CEO Hwang Yoo Cheol.
In my opinion, after this Board of Directors meeting,
CEO Hwang Yoo Cheol will be the one being dismissed.
Within Daeyang Shipbuilding, there is a R&amp;D team called Santa Maria.
That team did not make a ship.
They made
a robot.
Everyone,
I introduce to you Doctor Hong Baek Gyun
and the Santa Maria Team, who made the world's best android robot.
Hello, I'm Hong Baek Gyun, the team leader of Santa Maria.
We're going to introduce to you AG-3, the android robot we made.
Three directors who had sided with President Hwang Do Won have now switched sides.
Your dismissal has been canceled and
now they are looking into the dismissal of CEO Hwang.
I will take responsibility for the sale of Daeyang Shipbuilding.
From this moment on,
I resign from my role of CEO.
Do you feel better now
for dismissing me?
You should've done it earlier. It was this easy.
How did you endure
me being the CEO?
Hey, but,
I was trying until the end to not let go of your hand.
No, you'd already let go of my hand, Yoo Cheol.
Fifteen years ago.
That time.
Sign here.
My dad said
that if you sign here, you and I can live together.
I was a kid back then.
You knew what that document meant.
You knew, and until now, you've been pretending like you didn't. Isn't that the case?
Of course, even now,
whatever your dad does, you'll pretend you didn't know.
So, just like what you've been doing until now,
just pretend you don't know and move aside.
The opponent I need to fight isn't you. It's your father.
Oh, so is that why you dismissed me?
Because I'm not even worthy of being in this fight?!
Okay, then.
But would my father's blood disappear from me?
Be careful, too. Don't act all high and mighty, you bastard.
Dad, what did you just say right now?
Who got dismissed?
CEO Hwang ultimately made huge trouble.
Let's go. I made a reservation at the restaurant.
What about Chairman Kim Min Kyu?
He said he'd be getting some air.
Kim Min Kyu, where are you? Let's have a drink.
Let's do that later on.
Here, have a drink. Did everything work out last time?
Yes, everything did.
The Velveteen Rabbit?
There was a rabbit stuffed animal that one boy really cherished.
It's a story where the stuffed animal wants to become a real rabbit.
- So? Does it become a real rabbit?
- Yeah.
But the boy separates from the rabbit
and when they meet again, he can't recognize the rabbit.
Next year's spring,
the boy becomes healthy again and goes to play in the forest.
But one rabbit kept staring at the boy.
The boy mumbled,
"How cool!"
"That rabbit looks exactly like the one I lost."
Chairman Kim Min Kyu, you have to open this.
As promised, I'm giving you the heart ball as a gift.
I'm changing AG-3's face right now.
It's only eighty percent complete. The margin of error is still too big.
You have to wait until it's complete.
It's better for Kim Min Kyu if I change it a day earlier.
AG-3, your face will change soon.
I guess my character's model is changing.
The starting point of all my mistakes was your face.
You have to correct mistakes.
Yes, I do.
Don't worry. No matter what face you have, you're still AG-3.
No matter what face I have, I'm still AG-3.
Then, AG-3? Sleep mode.
No!
Stop it. Don't do it! Just leave her as is.
Kim Min Kyu?
I have to find her again.
Who?
The AG-3 that I trained.
I shouldn't have reset her then.
I shouldn't have sent her away like that. I want to find her.
I have to find her. I have to meet her.
Give up!  You won't be able to find it even if it went through deep learning again with you.
No, I can.
I'll start again. No, I'll do the deep learning just like I did in the beginning.
What is wrong with you! Get back to your senses.
I miss her a lot.
I want to meet her again.
I long for her.
Hi! AG-3.
I love you, Master. What would you like?
AG-3. Friend mode.
Nice to meet you, friend.
You didn't do it like that.
"What?" "Did you call for me?" "You called for me?" You did it like that.
Did you call me?
Right, that's how it is.
Let's do this well and meet again.
You got it, AG-3?
It is a cat.
It is Master.
Ah, it is a cat.
Ah, it's Master.
Ah, it's a cat.
Right, that's it. Good job!
Hold on. The next one was, uh. I use this as perfume, but
you use this as a cleanser.
Using perfume from France as a cleanser is a stupid thing to do.
What do you think?
Is this my room?
Where's the charger?
You're my treasure from now on. But if I were to sell you, how would you react?
Before selling me, you have to reset me.
There's only 10% of battery left.
Will you set me into sleep mode?
It would be so nice
if you could remember all the time we spent together.
What must I do for them to return?
What do I have to do
so that I can meet the version of you from the past?
Master, are you the same as the past version of yourself?
No.
Who I am now
is very different from how I was back then.
Then you cannot meet the old me ever again
because the inputs are different.
Yes, have you arrived?
Yes, I'm currently in Daegu right now. The agreement ceremony is going as we planned.
But, you're not coming in a car?
No, I just thought it would be nice to get some fresh air since it's been a long time.
I wanted to see the people around me as I went, too.
You don't need to pick me up at the station. I'll just meet you at the center.
A meteor shower occurs when dust from comets or asteroids comes in contact with the Earth's atmosphere
and burns.
It's a great site where shooting stars fall down like rain,
which makes it appear to be raining.
This meteor shower that will occur is due to an asteroid that got sucked
into Earth's atmosphere.
♫  I want to tell you  ♫
♫  I want to call you  ♫
♫  Lingering right at the edge of my lips  ♫
♫  Repeating over and over the words of my heart   ♫
♫  No matter how much I yell  ♫
♫  It doesn't seem like you can see my heart  ♫
♫  Behind my happy front  ♫