- Yes, Doctor?
- I will be sleeping here for tonight. I'll come back tomorrow morning.
It's taking longer than I thought.
I got it. Doctor said that he'll come back tomorrow morning.
In that case...
- Hurry and come!
- Hey!
We're here to take AG-3.
Wait, wait! Wait a bit. The thing is...
If you guys didn't have dinner yet...
We already did.
They had it already.
Korean beef!  Steak! Abalone!
Seafood soup!  Lobster, too!
Sunbae, it's food. Let's eat then go since it's prepared.
Hey! Do you have enough food for all of us?
Timing and Subtitles by The Robotic Team @ viki.com
Seafood smell. Wow.
This is... wait.
- This...
- What's that?
That salted sea squirt is for our Masan native... Researcher 1.
And for Researcher 2, the one in front of you. That.
That cheese dish is for Researcher 2, who studied abroad.
And for our Researcher 3, sorry but I couldn't come up with anything. Sorry.
One, two, three? Oops.
Do you not know our names?
Well... do I need to?
Sea squirt? Well, it's the first time I've heard of it.
Even my grandpa wouldn't like this.
Also, although my home town is Masan,
my flavor profile is that of Seoul.
For me as well, this isn't that great.
I ate this in the US every day when I didn't have money.
Then I'll just eat everything.
Why?
This kind of thing...
Amazing. This is amazingly good.
What? What?
I mean, how could you be this terrible at small talk even if you're not good at socializing and get complaints when you're the one who cooked?
Also, how can you just eat?
You said to cook for them!
You need to converse, so you can get closer. Once you're closer, you can ask for a favor.
You should talk to them, naturally.
If they ask you questions, respond honestly.
Okay, I got it.
What do your parents do in America?
Laundromat. They're 1.5 generation immigrants.
What do your parents do?
They are lying in their burial grounds, side by side.
How did that happen?
Half of the car smashed into an oncoming truck.
It was crushed and bent. Only I survived.
Is it true that Hong Baek Gyun is looking for a new investor?
Yes, I am sure. Do you think he clashed with Chairman Kim Min Kyu?
No, that doesn't matter because this is a great chance for us.
You know what to do, right?
Yes. We started.
Yes.
Thank you.
This friend is the smartest one of my students.
His research attitude is excellent, too. I can vouch for that.
I will give you a drink.
They ate all my food. This is a sign that they'll hear me out, right?
It is now time.
Because you all ate well, I am happy.
Well, you know where else would you eat such great food, right?
Yes, I promise you that if you don't leave the house—
I think you made too much food for no reason.
I heard that if you leave food, you have to eat it all when you go to hell.
So I ate forcefully and my stomach is uncomfortable.
- Let's go.
- Wait!  Wait a second.
It's not right to eat it all then pretend like nothing happened.
Did we ask for you to do this?
You guys are too much.
If you ate it all, it is common courtesy to wash the dishes.
Are you going to just leave?
Sunbae Hoktal washes the dishes really well.
Ssanip is good at organizing.
Unnie,
can we not actually leave?
After losing his parents like that, he lived in this huge house by himself.
He's not a weird person. He's just not experienced in everything.
He's sensitive on the inside.
If we stay a bit longer, you'll see that side of him.
It's done already. Doctor is meeting investors right now.
Then Unnie... When we leave later, can you just say that you ate well?
I just wish that today's ending isn't entirely bad for him.
No. If we are planning not to see each other again, it's best to end it badly.
Come to my room, AG-3.
I feel like I am going to throw up.
What do I need to do...
to change their hearts?
It's hard.
It's so hard.
♫  When meeting someone, ♫
♫  It doesn't seem like... ♫
You did well.
♫  One step, ♫
♫  You are there ♫
♫  so lovingly  ♫
♫  The matter of loving with all my heart  ♫
♫  What do I do? To that certain someone, ♫
Should we leave now?
I should at least go and beg them at their feet.
♫  It's not working well ♫
♫  Like you, ♫
♫  I want to love like that kind of person ♫
What are you doing right now?!
Lovely, are you okay? Are you hurt anywhere?
Why are you like this? What the?
Are you okay? Come back to your senses!
I saw it earlier and noticed it was broken.
We'll fix it for you. We can fix this kind of stuff with just one hand.
Just give it.
- Give it to us. Huh? Huh?
- Let go.
Really.
Here.
You're alive.
So happy to see you, Lovely.
Wow, there is a face now.
Since we were fixing it, we upgraded it a little.
If the filter is full of dust, it will cry and when it's clean, it will smile.
It came back.
I'm so relieved.
So he's not a pervert. He actually kisses robots.
I guess he originally was a good person.
I'm thirsty. I'm craving for some beer now.
I haven't used my brain in a while so I'm hungry.
Well...
Chicken. I have it.
A purebred chicken. The one with a huge leg.
The leg is super big, huh?
I want some drumsticks now.
No, you can't. If you eat a drumstick, you'll run away.
So annoying.
Then Sunbae, you eat the leg. It'll disappear.
It might run far far away.
No more. Don't speak about it anymore.
Hey, guys, I'm curious about something.
That money from earlier.
It is so hard for me to understand why you refused to accept it.
Do you know how much money that is?
You can go and  convince Doctor Hong.
It's because Doctor Hong has already made up his mind.
So faithful to him.
A person who can't trust anyone can't be trusted by others.
I don't know why those words popped into my head.
What's she saying?
I really want to eat chicken wings.
No! You'll fly away.
- I'm going to fly away.
- Yes, fly away.
- You crazy fool.
Fly, fly.
Fly far away.
I'm sorry. Yes.
I'm sorry.
Eat some wings and fly far, far away.
Fly so far away that you'll disappear from my eyes.
I'm sorry. To them, someone
has leaked the information about what happened in the US.
I tried my best but I think it will be a bit difficult.
Yes, hello.
This is he.
Investment?
AG-3?
What the heck? Where did everybody go?
Yes, Doctor.
We were on a walk and are about to head in right now.
Yes.
Miss Jo Ji Ah, say that we met up while you came to pick up your stuff, okay?
You absolutely can't tell him that we slept over at Baton's house, all right?
Hurry it up.
Hey!
Why are you coming in at the same time with them?
I'm here to pick up my bag.
- Oh, is that so?
- We met right in front.
That's right.
All right, go get your bag then. Everyone, pay attention here!
We have a new investor.
Under the condition of taking AG-3 to them for a demonstration.
A perfect demo will be hard.
You should meet up with the investor once we stabilize the new part we added.
She just can't walk but the rest is possible to demonstrate.
We can take her in a wheelchair and convince the investor.
Hurry it up. We don't have much time.
All right, let's go!
Doctor Hong will park his full-sized van over here.
Before taking out AG-3,
tell him that you want to have a cup of tea with all of the team members.
- Then take them to the cafe on the first floor.
- And then?
Then I'll drive off with the full sized van that has AG-3.
You'll say that you need to go to the bathroom really badly to the point that your bladder's about to explode, then you just sneak out of there.
Then come to the front and I will pick you up.
What if someone wants to remain in the van?
Ow, that startled me!
I investigated through our US branch and it looks like Doctor Hong has been defamed by one of his colleagues.
And he gave up the lawsuit under the condition that his team members will be protected.
Also, all of the research results have been handed over to that colleague.
All right, thank you for your work.
Before we disable the power cable,
should we take down the MODCC?
Hold on, let me double check.
Hoktal, go and check the NTS.
Okay.
NTS backup confirmation complete.
TPICP back up complete.
I will take care of this cable then.
- It's completed.
- Shut off the power.
Okay, I'm shutting off the power now.
Power off complete.
I'm going to take the power cable out now.
Wait for a moment.
I'll drop you off on our way.
May I come in for a bit?
We have a new investor now.
We will be able to vacate this place pretty soon.
What do you need to say to me?
I have to leave soon.
Doctor, now I understand why you're called the con-artist in the world of science.
KM's Massachusetts branch manager is best friends with Congressman Joo Sang Won.
So I was able to find out all the ins and outs of everything.
I ordered for a recovery of your reputation.
Who do you think you are?
Who the hell do you think you are to talk about recovering my reputation?
Because it was an unfair slander.
Whether it's defaming or whatever, my reputation is
something that I will fix on my own.
If you're here to tell me that kind of crap, then get lost right now.
Just like AG-3 said, I am
not very good with words.
What are you doing? Let go of me!
Help me, Big Brother.
Just how amazing your work is, Doctor Hong,
let me explain it to you this way.
The robot that you created
has saved a person.
Now that we're really leaving, I'm a bit disappointed.
Baton isn't a pervert.
Then don't we not have to leave?
Should I talk to Doctor Hong about this?
You still don't really know Doctor Hong's personality?
Whatever it may be, he's the type of person that sticks to it once he made the decision.
There won't be anything close to a swimming pool in the new research lab.
Not even a gymnasium.
It's almost time, Doctor.
The investor is waiting for you.
Let's go.
I have taken the army medical exam four times already.
Because the medical field does not accept my illness saying it is an illness that doesn't exist in this world.
Of course, there is no treatment.
That is why whenever a new allergy medicine comes out in this world, I have it shipped
and experimented on my body.
I know people call me "Baton."
Nobody would ever think that it is a weapon to keep me alive.
That's how I lived for the past 15 years.
For the rest of my life, I was prepared to live like this.
However, a miracle occurred.
AG-3.
I'm turning the car around.
Doctor?
- You don't have to do it if you don't want to.
- I'll do it.
- If there is anything worrying you, then don't do it.
- I'm doing it.
Answer after thinking carefully first.
Do you know it's the first time?
- What?
- That you asked me first.
When did I not do that?
Anyway, thanks for many things.
I think we misunderstood Chairman Kim Min Kyu.
We cleared the misunderstanding, and he has promised to give 50 billion won.
There is really no reason to leave. I have decided to stay here again.
Pi, come see me for a second.
I am against your decision. Is it because of Jo Ji Ah?
Is it because you want to keep her by your side?
- It's not.
- Then what is it really?
Baton has not caught us yet.
You know this is our last chance to make everything right.
If he finds out, he'll point you out as a con artist again. What will you do then?
The test results greatly exceeded our expectations.
Whatever that is... It was Jo Ji Ah's doing.
No. Chairman Kim Min Kyu believes she's a robot.
AG-3 has done it.
When the new part arrives and we fix it, AG-3 will step in.
Pi. I want to finish this test. We've accomplished a great thing.
That is the reason why we create robots.
Our plan fell apart.
Should I initiate plan B?
Yes, I got it.
What did he say? Do they want us to return the money?
He said to bring it to him no matter what. This robot.
If you sign this agreement, after getting approval from KM's board of directors,
the research fund amount listed on the contract will be administered.
And the new research facility will be prepared after discussion.
Then should your Big Brother sign here?
Did you hear? He just said "your Big Brother."
We're the ones who drank with him. When did  they become so close?
You're the youngest here. Let's get our hierarchy straight.
Three Big Brother and one Big Sister. Wow, you're lucky.
- The thing is—
- Hi, Brother.
Nice to meet you, Little Brother.
So this is the feeling of having a rich little brother?
Mansour has older brothers, too. Right?
Why? Does it make you angry?
Also, there is the most important thing.
If you don't promise this, I won't sign these papers.
Promise me that you won't even lay a tip of your finger on AG-3. Or else, we'll leave.
Okay.
Wait a little bit, heart lamp. I will fix you like you're brand new.
The name of that is heart lamp?
Yes.
I can fix that for you. But in return, give me compensation.
How much?
I will tell you after I fix it?
What are you scheming?
If you don't want to, then never mind.
Fine then. You only need a day, right?
What? "Hi, Brother?"
"Nice to meet you, Little Brother? Mansour has older brothers" and what else?! Gosh these scheming jerks!
Just because I fed them once, they're  clinging on.
Then I will be heading out.
- Wait.
- Yes?
Find a person for me.
His name is Jang Doo San.
I received the message. What's the reason for me to look for him?
It's related to Santa Maria. Make sure to find him.
Yes, I got it.
Hi, AG-3.
What brings you here, Master?
From now on, I will pick you up every day.
We have to lower your battery usage as much as possible.
So don't move around thoughtlessly and don't run around either.
Got it?
Because I'm your precious treasure?
Forget it. Prepare for a scolding when we go inside.
A scolding without a reason is not fair, Master.
There is a reason. Friend mode.
Friend!
What's up with the pick up service all of a sudden?
You abandoned me again yesterday. Do you know how flustered I was when I woke up in the morning?
If that's so easy for you, then keep doing it! I'll just sell you off to a junkyard.
And from now on, whenever I'm meeting someone, stay where I can see you.
Why?
If you don't, it's a violation of the contract.
Shut up and input it. Absolutely and definitely,
stay around where your master can see you. Understand?
Okay.
Also, clean here.
You said not to do physical labor to save battery life.
Just clean.
So moody!
You don't look good in pink.
I'm not giving it to you because you deserve it.
You have to go to places with me from now on.
So your fashion style should be neat and clean.
If not, then I'd be embarrassed so how would I be able to take you anywhere?
Wear anything you like and come outside.
She's still making these.
Timing and Subtitles by The Robotic Team @ viki.com
♫  It seems like I will have time that I didn't have before  ♫
Is it weird?
It's pretty.
Really?
Really pretty.
Oh, wait a second. I can't be like this.
Why not?
I promised Doctor Hong.
Promise me that you won't even lay a tip of your finger on AG-3.
My body is mine, so why is he telling him to not touch me?
♫  I want to know how you feel  ♫
AG-3,
I have something to tell you.
♫  For the moment I meet you  ♫