I love...
AG-3.
I don't want to accept this fact but I have no choice but to do so.
So please tell me.
In planning for AG-3's deep learning,
was having this kind of result
a part of the plan?
Of course not.
But...
Why am I being this way?
Now that I think about it, starting from some time ago
I used to always wait for the time when AG-3 came back.
When the evening came, I used to wish for the morning to come over and over like a chant.
I was so happy that there was someone out there that would listen to me
and look after me.
The fact that there was someone who remembered me
made me feel excited day after day.
But that's because you were alone for a very long time. What I mean is
because you made a friend for the first time.
She helped heal your disease so you just can't help but obsess over her without realizing it. That's what it is.
That's what I thought, too.
But...
whenever I am with AG-3,
I am alive.
That's how I feel.
Kim Min Kyu, snap out of it. AG-3 is a robot. She's a robot, you understand?
That's what I'm saying.
But...
AG-3 also
seems to love me, too.
What nonsense are you talking about?
You know that's not possible. She talks and acts the way we program her.
And what you feel as her love is merely the end result of what you programmed into her, that's all!
That's why!
It still feels like that despite all of it and that's why I'm going crazy!
My head
tells me that all these things that I'm feeling
are fake, an illusion.
But my heart tells me that all of these things
are real.
Feeling this way really makes me feel like crap, you know that?!!
What should I do?
What do I need to do in order for me to take care of this situation?
Please tell me.
You should know.
Okay, okay. This way please.
I wonder why he drank so much?
Here, here.
But how did you end up carrying him on your back?
Please take care of him.
- You really knew all about his disease, yet you still sent me over there?
- What?
Did you still send me to that house even after you knew that Kim Min Kyu was allergic to humans?!
Doctor Oh just came by.
- Ji Ah, listen to me.
- Oh, 50 billion won, huh?
The 50 billion won as additional research funds. That seems like a good reason.
What the Doctor did wasn't for the money—
Pi, you be quiet.
Why did you do that to me?
Ji Ah, you should scold me instead.
I'm the one to be blamed the most.
I was the one who broke AG-3 and that's why this happened.
That's not it, Ji Ah. It's all because I sent you that text message when I shouldn't have.
Those kids aren't at fault.
I made the call, so it's my responsibility.
Why did you make that call all on your own?!
You should've let me make a decision, too.
Fine, his disease is all cured and I'm really happy that I was able to heal him.
But I'm so scared!
If I possibly got caught,
then he could've died because of me.
You didn't think about that, did you?
I won't be able to explain myself to him now no matter which words I choose to use.
I won't be able to ask him to trust me again. Do you know what that means to me?
Why did you do that to me? Why?!
Ji Ah. Ji Ah!
The doctor genuinely wanted Chairman Kim to be cured from his disease.
That's why he abandoned his chance for other investment opportunities and decided to work with Chairman Kim instead.
We really thought that once we fixed AG-3 quickly and switch it back with you,
we thought that would be okay.
You should've told me exactly what you just said to me before.
Man, why isn't this AG-3 coming out already.
She's so pretty.
But there's something familiar about her. I'm sure I've seen her before somewhere.
Right? I'm sure I've seen her before as well.
- AG-3!
- You're certain that's AG-3, right?
- Yeah, I think she changed her wig.
No matter how many times you change your wig, you won't be able to escape from us.
- Follow her discreetly.
- Okay.
- What's this situation here?
- Maybe the robot is running away?
What for? To this place?
Whose house is this?
That's Team Leader Jo Jin Bae from the investigation team.
So then that's Team Leader Jo's home?
Team Leader Jo Jin Bae.
Ji Ah's here.
Was it hard being away from home?
You should catch up on sleep and rest well.
Brother...
- Huh?
- I should've listened to you then.
I should've tried to improve my resume and gotten a job.
If I had done that, I wouldn't be stuck in this mess right now.
Considering your age, you're not in a mess.
Not many people know what they like to do
and put their lives on the line for that dream.
I also wasn't able to live like that.
So what?
I ruined things for myself
and twisted up my life.
Fighting, Jo Ji Ah.
By any chance, do you really think AG-3 cured Kim Min Kyu?
As long as Kim Min Kyu thinks Jo Ji Ah is a robot,
the one he loves is AG-3.
At first, I was angry.
But I'm thankful because in the end, you were able to cure him.
However, what will you do about this side effect now?
Just how can we help him when he firmly believes that he's in love with a robot?
If those two can start over again from the beginning,
there may be hope.
Do you have enough courage to confess
that AG-3 wasn't actually a robot?
AG-3, go online with Kim Min Kyu's account.
Hello, Doctor.
AG-3, what is your relationship right now with Kim Min Kyu?
My master and I are in a relationship where we can share embarrassing facts without being embarrassed.
Even though we can be each other's closest friend, we can never be in a romantic relationship.
I think AG-3...
also loves me.
Did you cut yourself?
How could you cook so aggressively like that?
This is the perfect moment to kiss.
Fold a finger if you wished that robot was actually a human.
I'm not a robot.
♫  Don't frown, everybody is going through a hard time.  ♫
♫   You have friends who are with you   ♫
♫   for your happy days.   ♫
-  Are you at home?
- Yeah.
Did you eat?
How can I eat when I could've accidentally killed someone?
I should not have
looked for you that day.
We can't blame anyone.
It was me who fell for ₩10,000,000.
I should've told you the truth back then.
Now what do you want me to do?
Turing Test.
By sending in a robot and a human that looks exactly the same at alternate times,
we're going to test who seems more human.
You're not deceiving anyone, but you must.
That's how you will help improve the advancement of robots.
I am the crazy one for believing that it was a test.
Even though I felt something was off,
I didn't look into it more.
I just enjoyed...
Deciding to stay even though I had the chance to leave,
I didn't do that just because I wanted to help Kim Min Kyu.
A new deep-learning method
and the fact that a robot made by me was curing someone
made me very happy.
Therefore, I wanted to see the end result of the test.
In the process,
I didn't look at the fact that
Kim Min Kyu could've gotten hurt.
Therefore, I think it's best to be honest before it's too late.
That's right.
Let's go tell him everything tomorrow.
Hi... AG-3.
I love you, Master.
What is it that you want?
Did you call me, Master?
I have compiled a list of dresses for Ye Ri El to wear.
AG-3,
looking at you...
is too hard for me.
Did I do something wrong?
When I look at you,
I get reminded of
what I can't do with you.
What is it that you can't do with me?
I can
do anything now.
That's why I have a lot of things I want to do with you.
I can't watch you grow old.
I can't cook for you.
I can't hug you.
You're still the same,
but I've... I've changed.
My feelings have grown so much
that I'm not confident
that I can handle this for the rest of my life.
You were the one that said you wanted to stay together forever.
I'm sorry.
However, it looks like you are being punished.
You look very hurt and sad.
You master is in a mess, right?
No matter what you look like, you're still my master.
Let's go.
They're leaving. They're leaving.
Isn't that Doctor Hong Baek Gyun?
So he picks up AG-3 from Jo Jin Bae's house. Why is that?
Our work has become easier. We just need to raid that tiny apartment.
He's quick-witted. It's Director Yoon.
Yes, Director Yoon, I was about to report to you—
What about AG-3? Did you kidnap it?
Ah, about that. Not yet. However, we have an incredible—
You guys are worse than amateurs. You guys are fired.
E-Excuse me. What I saw was, here at Team Leader Jo's house, the robot goes to and comes back from work.
So AG-3 is going to work and coming back from work—
Hello? Director Yoon? Director Yoon?
What did he say?
We're fired.
- Set a fire?
- Fired. We're fired.
We just got fired. Why can't you understand?
He died from an allergy shock.
There was nothing we could do.
Tilda Morton took off with all of Johnny's assets.
Everything around her was a lie.
Johnny died from an allergy shock.
♫  Don't frown  ♫
♫  Everybody-  ♫
Yes, hello?
Johnny Brown died. Are you listening to me? You can't tell him.
Tilda conned him and left. He died from an allergy shock because of her.
We do not know what will happen if Kim Min Kyu finds out that you aren't a robot and that everything was a lie.
Therefore, we must not say a thing.
You must never cross paths with Kim Min Kyu!
It looks like
it will snow today.
It sure does.
I'll tell you what you need to do today.
Let's reset AG-3.
Until now, you must have been saddened when you received my frequent scoldings.
Okay, today I will give you a huge compliment. Listen well, AG-3.
For the last month, you were my friend,
my treasure, and my cure.
Also, you were a door to step outside into the world.
Every moment with you was like a miracle to me. Thank you.
Also, I'm sorry.
♫  I have been in pain for a few days  ♫
I wasn't the one that cured you.
The longing for someone you still had in your heart
cured you.
Without me, you would've still been cured one day.
So now, whatever you do, make sure you're happy
and have fun.
♫  Has become tears again today
I'll also give you a huge compliment, so listen well.
♫  I want to tell you  ♫
You...
are someone that made me realize that I'm valuable.
♫  Lingering right at the edge of my lips  ♫
You were my friend, treated me like a treasure,
and allowed me to walk on a flowery path.
♫  It doesn't seem like you can hear  ♫
Everything you did for me,
♫  Every day,  ♫
I won't forget those feelings and will remember them forever.
♫  I could say the words of love for you  ♫
Thank you.
And I'm sorry.
AG-3. Operation mode.
How can I help you, Master?
I will now reset you.
If I get reset, every memory I had with you will be deleted and
can't be restored.
Would you still like to continue?
Continue.
Please press the button at the back of my neck for five seconds,
then I will proceed with the reset.
For one last time, I have something to input.
Those words, too, will be deleted.
♫  I want to tell you  ♫
♫  I want to let you hear  ♫
♫  Lingering right at the edge of my lips  ♫
♫  Repeating over and over the words of my heart  ♫
♫  No matter how much I yell  ♫
I love you.
♫  It doesn't seem like you can hear  ♫
♫  Every day, only in my heart  ♫
The time I spent with you, Master,
every moment was happiness.
♫  The words of love for you  ♫
♫  All day today too you are lingering in my thoughts  ♫
♫  I only wait for the time when I can see you  ♫
♫  When I see you, I get cowardly  ♫
♫  I want to know your heart  ♫
♫  I've been waiting for so long  ♫
♫  For the moment I meet you  ♫
♫  Will you understand me? Will you see me?  ♫
♫  My heart that worries  ♫