Timing and Subtitles by The Robotic Team @ viki.com
I slept. I slept.
Nothing happened as I was sleeping, right? I had a dream.
The dream was quite unsettling.
Sleep more.
I'm sleeping.
For us... from today, is it...
Day one?
So cute.
You are cuter.
Here's your Americano.
Yes, thank you.
You're up? Here.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Should we go around one more time?
We already went around five times. Go home already.
When are you going to come?
I will call after I get some sleep.
That's too bad.
Do you want to start coming to my house for work again?
Hurry and go in.
- Go in.
- I'm going.
I'm going.
Go on.
Bye.
​♫  At this rate, I'd rather have them encompass me as I live  ♫
Go on.
Go in.
You go first.
No, you go in first.
Go first.
Hurry. I will go after seeing you go in.
Okay.
- Go in.
- I'm going. I'm really going.
♫  Not once  ♫
​♫  have I seen a side of you I disliked  ♫
​♫  There's no way I will let you go this easily  ♫
♫  I will take it slow to forget you  ♫
​♫  I will postpone erasing you  ♫
Auntie!
Where did you go yesterday?
Mt. Hwangmae.
Mt. Hwangmae? Why would you go there?
Auntie, wasn't it cold?
Not a bit. It was really warm.
Dong Hyun, hit your aunt.
Come here, come here!
So pretty.
​♫  I have to let them all go now but...  ♫
♫  I don't wanna let you go away  ♫
My president is waiting for you.
Where is my AG-3?
Tomorrow with our contract,
we can send AG-3.
You got lucky. You broke a promise to me.
And your son made me wait. People don't break promises to me.
And they don't make me wait because I don't forgive.
And I never forget.
You know me, Hwang Do Won.
Mister... Mister Martin—
Bring me the AG-3.
We will give it a thorough examination first.
Won't we, Dr. Casey?
Driver Jang.
It's been a long time.
Dr. Hong.
Just like you, I also respected Chairman Park Sung Jin.
He was someone who was passionate about robots to the point of making a secret development team without anyone in Daeyang Shipbuilding knowing about it.
But then, if the contract between Chairman Martin and KM Financial is signed tomorrow,
Chairman Park's dream will end.
Please help us.
Chairman Park Sung Jin's death was not an accident.
Take this money and leave the country.
You worked as Chairman Park's driver for 5 years, right?
You didn't see anything.
Me or Martin or Santa Maria.
Chairman Park died from a hit-and-run accident
and you almost died, too. You just have to remember that.
Chairman Park's accident, did you cause it?
Keep this in mind, you don't know anything.
That way you and your family can live.
Did President Hwang Do Won really say that? Do you have a recording of him saying that?
I might die the moment I give you that recording.
I am being chased right now. Please give me time to think about it.
Have you seen Driver Jang?
Why? Did you think I wouldn't know? Let me ask you directly.
Chairman Park Sung Jin...
Did Father kill him?
No.
Who did?
Chairman Kim Min Kyu will be dismissed after the contracts are signed tomorrow.
No, I'm not asking about that right now.
If Kim Min Kyu finds Driver Jang...
what happens next?
I'm sorry, Chairman.
Would you be able to last long in the company working like that?
I'm really sorry.
Why did you live like that until now, Kim Min Kyu?
Ah, Team Leader Jo Jin Bae?
Yes, Chairman.
Have you eaten?
Pardon?
No. So... Right now, where are you?
I'm on my way to the court to submit the papers for the lawsuit.
Lawsuit?
Yes. For the Santa Maria Team and my sister Jo Ji Ah.
Ah... that, that, that. Cancel that. I am not doing that... The lawsuit.
You should stick with your decision so that you won't regret it later on.
I won't. I won't be suing them.
I understand. Then which side are you not suing?
Is it the Santa Maria Team or my sister?
Well... Firstly... It's a hassle, so both.
I understand. I will keep the files, so if you change your mind, tell me.
I won't change my mind. Also the files, just tear them up.
And come to my house right now.
I mean...
Can you come over, please?
Yes, I understand.
Regardless, I had something to report to you anyway.
Okay.
Wow... what is this?
This is my first time experiencing this weird feeling.
I don't think the term "full recovery" will mean much to you anymore.
I would say, depending on your mood, your symptoms can disappear and reappear again.
I think it will make you feel better if you think of your illness as a friend with whom you will have to live with forever.
Make my illness into a friend?
You're supposed to appease long-term illnesses as you live.
The problem is that medicine won't work that well for you anymore.
You should be careful until a new one is developed.
I'll keep that in mind.
If you made up with Jo Ji Ah, will you also make up with Santa Maria Team?
That... is a different story.
You were the one that spent time with them.
Therefore, what you feel is the truth.
However, the people I saw were sincerely worried for you.
Have a seat, Team Leader Jo.
No. I'm fine.
Ah, you don't have to stand that far from me.
Yes. Just as long as you don't touch me.
No. I'm fine.
I'm comfortable like this.
I see.
I'm not comfortable.
Oh my... That's... not what I meant.
Just... sit down. Please?
Yes. Then I will sit.
Timing and Subtitles by The Robotic Team @ viki.com
You have done nothing wrong to me, Team Leader Jo.
I will not process your resignation letter.
Although you did make a mistake, I am able to understand.
Therefore, don't act guilty in front of me.
That is exactly what makes me feel uncomfortable.
I... believe you, Team Leader Jo.
Don't believe me.
As a civil rights lawyer, I thought I was a person who couldn't even lie about the tiniest thing.
While doing this work, I realized I was wrong.
People are able to change.
Still... I will believe you.
I will deal with the consequences.
However, my younger sister—
I like your younger sister.
A lot. By any chance, will that fact
become a problem in our relationship right now?
Not at the moment.
Then, you can start.
Director Martin flew into Korea today.
What is the current situation of Santa Maria?
Once the deal is signed, they will lose all of their research results regarding AG-3.
Although we were able to locate Jang Doo Sam's whereabouts, we failed to get him to cooperate.
We're going to be there soon.
She is still charging.
Once you arrive, we will pack her up.
If you can, let's end this without trouble.
AG-3.
What type of cow is a cow that can't eat?
I don't know.
(This is a pun. 'Mo-reu-get-so', which means 'I don't know' and 'so' which is the Korean word for cow)
You're going to a good place, AG-3.
When you get there, you will find a new master and be happy.
Don't worry.
I guess you're telling a happy lie for me today.
Once the deal is signed, they will lose all of their research results regarding AG-3.
Ji Ah really didn't know anything, Brother.
It's all our— No, it's my fault.
I was the one that held her back when she said she wasn't going to help anymore.
It's my fault. I'm sorry.
Young Master! I think you have to come out for a moment.
There's chaos in the guest house right now!
Wow. So interesting.
Beautiful girl.
I'll take you apart and all the technology you're made of.
Team Santa Maria, thank you.
Taking apart AG-3 before signing the contract is against our terms.
Calm down.
Today is our first day of testing.
I'll take her apart after arriving in England.
I can take apart her face by myself.
I want to see the motor assembly behind her skin.
Don't even think about touching her before signing the contract.
Ah, sorry. We weren't planning on coming here, but we stopped by for a moment to charge AG-3.
We will start to clear everything out soon.
Where did AG-3 go?
Where did she go?!
They took her away.
I was going to send her away regardless.
How can you just send her away so easily?
Did AG-3 mean that little to Santa Maria?
We didn't send her away easily. It was beyond our control. This is
the only choice we had.
You paid your ex-girlfriend for a part-time job pretending to be robot so you could get ₩500,000,000.
You even conned me saying that this was all a Turing test. Where did all of your guts go?!
You should have found every possible solution that you could try.
I am sorry.
Don't apologize to me. You should be apologizing to your team!
I am sorry, Brother.
We were all on the same page.
I'm... I'm sorry, Brother.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry. Really.
Aren't you mad at all in this situation?
If you want to be mad, then let it all out at me.
You also know why we are sending her away.
Are you trying to show me that you had to send her away because of me?
Just do whatever you want to do! I don't care!!
Hey, Kim Min Kyu.
Do you know what it means for the media to go after you in a negative way?
I... No, we know because we have been through it.
That means you will be labeled for the rest of your life.
No matter how sincere you are, no one will listen to you.
The rest of your life will revolve around how the media negatively portrays you.
We... don't want to see the rest of your life being ruined.
Did I ask you to do that?
How is it?
It's amazing.
It's not only the technology that surprises me.
The learning ability is out of this world.
The client will love this.
Will I be upgraded?
Yeah, you'll be a military robot.
The world's most dangerous weapon.
Am I not supposed to live with humans?
You're just a product owned by a man.
This man.
You do not exist as a living creature.
If you've checked enough, I will keep AG-3 before the contract tomorrow.
To avoid being tracked, let me take out the GPS before you take it.
♫  Please don't frown  ♫
♫  Everyone's going through a hard time  ♫
♫  For the hard times  ♫
Did you sleep a bit?
I just woke up. What about you?
I had a lot of work.
Why are you laughing?
You are really CEO Jo.
You're happy?
Yeah, I'm really happy.
No wonder, I felt so used to talking to you on the phone.
Is that so?
When you switched your phone number, I was really sad.
You changed it because of me, right?
I felt like I would actually run to you if I ever got a call from you again.
Did something happen?
Should I go there now?
No. Later at night. I have things to do now.
The team follows the leader and the leader takes all of the responsibility.
So... all responsibility for this situation lies with you.
I know. I also know what words you want to hear.
So say it. Just the truth.
Jo Ji Ah... was my first love.
But then one day... without telling me a reason, she just left.
I probably made AG-3's face as Ji Ah's face to try to find the answer.
I found that answer, now I can understand Ji Ah,
and more than that, I got to know myself more.
This is why a chapter of my life is done.
On Geoje Island, you two looked very good together.
I'm sincere.
You two looked so good together that I wanted to tell you everything at that moment.
But I lost the chance again.
I'm sorry.
The decisive moment always seems to pass as I hesitate.
I am canceling the lawsuit.
I will not send AG-3, and I will stop that contract tomorrow no matter what.
The reason is not because I have forgiven you.
It's for KM Financial's sake.
Yes.
President, the chairman is here.
You came to see me?
As I live, a day like this comes.
So... what's your purpose for coming?
I'm thinking about resigning from the chairman position.
I'll also stay out of management decisions.
In return, I have a condition.
Condition?
Sell the Santa Maria Team to me.
You decide to give up on KM Financial, yet you want Santa Maria, the team that deceived you?
I don't think it's a bad deal.
It wasn't a bad deal when I didn't know about your illness.
Either way, your body's condition is not good enough for you to carry out your duties.
All this time, I gained profit for KM Financial with this body.
What would happen if the world knew about your illness?
Do you think that you will be able to endure it like right now?
I'm begging you.
Santa Maria will be sold to Bold Group by tomorrow.
Doctor Hong has already agreed to this.
Now what's left is for you is to accept it.
Min Kyu, don't you think a voluntary resignation from the chairman position is better?
Is something wrong with your head?
In return for giving up KM Financial, you want Santa Maria?
Those people who made you a fool behind your back?
Because they're worth that much.
Worth? What worth do they have?
Are they worth it because they are able to scam so flawlessly?
You have been giving me such a hard time because of that one incident that happened when I was younger.
But you're saying those people are worth protecting with all of your assets on the line?
Are you really crazy?
My mind is sound. As you know, my calculations are precise.
Listen closely, Yoo Cheol.
Those people... gave up all that they had for me.
You and your father... will never understand them.
I won't make it long.
Let's pretend that the talk about you and Ri El's engagement never happened.
I-I... was careless.
You were very careless.
Director Martin will be signing the contract tomorrow.
I'm sure you know very well what is going to happen after he signs that contract.
For KM Financial, we have to stop it from happening no matter what.
I'll gather the board members for an emergency meeting.
Please give me support.
Ri El and Yoo Cheol will be getting married soon.
This is my answer.
Once the contract is signed tomorrow with Bold Group,
I'm going to proceed with your marriage with Yoo Cheol.
Dad, I already told you to let me go.
I don't want to continue living like this anymore.
You always acknowledged Min Kyu's ability.
You thought of him as a family member for fifteen years,
so how can you turn on him in a matter of a day?
Family? Who?
Kim Min Kyu?
Dad, were you always supporting Min Kyu with that type of mindset?
Do you not feel bad for Min Kyu?
Yes, this is Reporter Park.
I just received your email.
This is interesting.
Once this goes public, it will be the most searched article.
I'm sure people will be talking about it for a while.
I will be on standby so just give me the sign.
Yes.
What the hell!
Timing and Subtitles by The Robotic Team @ viki.com
Let's go home.
♫  I will take it slow to forget you  ♫
​♫  I will postpone erasing you  ♫
​​♫  Oh your facial expressions  ♫
​​♫  Those feelings, those stories  ♫
​♫  Each one of them is still so clear  ♫
♫  I’m gonna love again, the road to forget you  ♫
​♫  On the road to meet with you again  ♫