[English subtitles are available]
According to data summary,
due to the inspiration of the anime Dooro Bear
the netizens' comments
on Meton Food
are exploding.
I've analyzed and summarized the opinions
on our cooperation.
The first one is the taste is too ordinary...
Lin Yue and Zhen Gaogui are in a relationship.
Do you know that?
But you are her boyfriend.
Did she accept your love and agree to be your girlfriend?
How did you express your love?
You must know a lot
about the Dooro Bear.
Do you have any insight into the future cooperation
of the two companies?
I think the Dooro Bear is very popular online.
Many bloggers use it as a video-making material.
If we can get its long-term authorization,
our sales will definitely increase in the future.
As a consumer,
do you have any peripheral products of Dooro Bear at home?
No.
No?
Doesn't your boyfriend mind?
What are you talking about?
Mr. Zhong,
if we want to work together in the future,
Xinda PR will issue
a detailed plan
for discussion.
Right, Gaogui?
Yes, no problem.
Let's take a break
and have some drinks.
Hello?
Yes.
Okay, I know.
No private calls during working hours.
Mr. Zhong, this is a work call.
It's from one of our media executives.
Okay, Ms. Wang,
I'll send it to you later.
[Amazing Girls]
[Episode 9]
[Meton Food Co., LTD]
[Product R&D Department]
We have cleaners. Why are you cleaning the office?
Mr. Zhong,
our director
asked me to clean this place.
Are you new here?
No, I've been here for two and a half years.
Why haven't I seen you before?
I'm just an assistant product researcher,
so I'm not qualified to attend
the executive meeting.
You're still an assistant after two and a half years.
Have you been slacking off for two years?
No, no, no.
I've been studying
popcorn of new flavors alone.
But Director Shen never approved them.
I'm still trying.
Alright.
You have to work hard.
Our company doesn't provide for idle people.
Mr. Zhong,
could you please
try the new popcorn I made?
Because Director Shen never gives me a chance
to take my work to the executive meeting.
So I really want to know
if I can get your approval.
Sure.
Is there popcorn in the box?
Yes. Yes.
Mr. Zhong, try it.
How is it?
Based on the research I did with Zhen Gaogui,
I plan to launch
popcorn of new flavors.
It will take time to develop and test
to deal with this big matter.
I'm just informing you.
Zhen Gaogui is also here today.
You can arrange the following promotion.
Director Lu, please carry out
the internal adjustment and promotion of the company.
Mr. Zhong.
This is Xu from the Product R&D Department.
Hello, everyone.
Introduce yourselves.
My name is Xu Xiaotian.
Ever since I joined the company...
Put it down.
Since he joined us,
he has created a lot of new flavors.
Zhen Gaogui, try all the new flavors
today.
Think about
our future.
Our
our future?
So please be careful.
How do you go home later?
Take the bus.
I'll drive you.
Don't bother, Mr. Zhong.
I have something to tell you on the way.
I think you should adjust your work status.
If you're in a relationship,
you won't put all your energy
on work.
It will bring some bad influence.
When I'm in a relationship, I will have a better mood.
This will increase my passion for work.
If you don't date,
you can 100% focus on
on me,
no, on work.
I'll take care of it.
When did it happen?
Are you talking about
Yue?
Lin Yue, the man you've mentioned.
How does he call you?
Guigui?
Zhenzhen?
Gaogao?
Mr. Zhong,
if you say that again,
I'll have goose bumps.
How does he call you?
I think it has nothing to do with you.
You'll know it when you're in a relationship.
Do you think I don't want to date someone?
Mr. Zhong,
I suggest you to get a girlfriend.
Yue and I are very happy.
What are you doing?
Can't you see the red light?
Why are you
so indifferent
and cruel-hearted?
I just didn't tell you
the secret between you and Yue.
It has nothing to do with you.
I have a friend
who falls in love with a girl.
But it seems that girl has already had a boyfriend.
Are you making up a story?
No.
According to your girls' experience,
how should I help him?
Make sure
if she really has a boyfriend.
What if it's fake?
Mom,
did you burn something again?
No, no, no.
What a feast for breakfast.
How is it?
Why do I smell something burning?
No.
This...
Mom,
the sandwich you made
is just like my life.
It seems to be good,
but in fact,
it's not.
Mr. Zhong, why are you here?
I have a boyfriend now.
It's not good for you to wait for me like this.
Your notebook.
You left it in my car yesterday.
You can even forget the production materials.
How can you create value?
It's okay that you were not waiting for me.
Now that you know
I have a boyfriend,
let's keep distance from each other.
Otherwise, too many people in the company
will gossip about our relationship.
What relationship?
The relationship between you and me,
and the relationship between you and your Yue.
I don't want to continue this kind of
meaningless conversation anymore.
I have to go to the company to modify your slides.
If you keep asking,
you'll keep me from my work.
[Zhong Yiming, CEO of Meton Food Co., LTD]
Gaogui,
there's just a scandal related to you and Mr. Zhong,
do you really love him?
But what about Lin Yue,
you nominal secret lover?
Take a look.
Gaogui,
I think it's unbelievable
if you're dating Mr. Zhong.
And I feel strange
if you say you're dating Mr. Lin.
Well...
Why do you feel it strange?
Look,
if you have such a great boyfriend,
why are you still working here?
Yes.
Are you here to spy on us?
Come on!
Besides,
what does my boyfriend's work have to do with me?
Can he make slides for me?
See,
I didn't save the slides and they were gone.
We're going to meet him again.
We will meet him more often.
We may have a lot of cooperation
with him on our popcorn of new flavors.
Will you be unhappy if you lose to him?
What do you mean?
Have we ever fought?
He just appeared a few years earlier.
It seems that you and Zhen Gaogui...
What's wrong with us?
We are
just cooperative partners.
Just cooperative partners?
When I saw you two last time,
I didn't think you are just cooperative partners.
Circumstance changed.
Come here, Ke'er.
Mr. Zhong Jr. didn't discuss with anyone
the promotion of new flavors.
Why didn't you stop him?
Why should I stop him from making money?
Has he mentally controlled
your CPU?
He is young and mischievous.
Are you also messing around with him?
Promoting new flavors
means that in the early stage,
we have to input a lot of money on R&D.
It's not easy for the company
to maintain its operation.
If we fail,
the company will be over.
You and I know the current situation.
Even if we stick to the rules,
it can only slow down the company's bankruptcy.
I think we should give it a go.
I'm always optimistic.
But Mr. Sun,
you always target Mr. Zhong but not the business.
Do you really put the company's interests
first?
Look at you,
am I that kind of person?
You...
Mr. Zhong.
your absence
caused the mess of the company.
Calm down. Take your time.
Did he have a conflict
with Xinda PR again?
No.
But I heard
that young lady has climbed up another branch.
The point is
young Mr. Zhong Jr.
told the R&D Department
to promote new flavors.
How can we promote new flavors in such a short time?
I heard that today, there is a bad luck.
Did it affect you two?
I don't know if it's a bad luck.
But I was influenced by a man.
What kind of person
could affect Mr. Zhong?
When did Mr. Lin have a girlfriend?
Why didn't you make it public?
Is there a reason?
Girlfriend?
Who are you talking about?
Do you have several girlfriends?
[Brother]
Hello? What's the matter?
Ming,
do you plan to promote
popcorn of new flavors?
It's a big deal.
Why didn't you discuss it
with others?
Mr. Lin, you really have several?
What?
Girlfriends.
Would you be jealous
if I have several girlfriends?
No.
I just think
we may have a lot of meetings later.
I'm afraid that will delay your date.
You're jealous.
I'm not here to talk about this.
Mr. Zhong
is planning to develop
popcorn of new flavors that are suitable for young people.
I hope we can cooperate with
with your animation IP.
So we may have to
discuss a few times later.
Ming,
I understand that
at your age,
it's inevitable for you to like a pretty girl
when you meet her.
I'm talking about work now.
Let's put it aside.
I'll send you the plan when it's done.
How is it going?
What progress?
Of course, our work.
I know it's about work.
Wait.
Why are you two so weird today?
Did someone expose me?
I didn't see something
on the news.
It looks like we won't have
any substantial results today.
How about this?
Mr. Zhong,
later,
I'll discuss with Mr. Lin alone a few more times later.
I'll report the details to you.
Okay.
Director, what took you so long?
You're going to be late.
The driver took the wrong way.
Wait.
Sorry.
We're 5 minutes and 28 seconds late.
Sorry, Mr. Lin.
Let me correct it.
5 minutes and 32 seconds.
Sorry, Mr. Lin.
Director, I'll get back to work.
Go ahead.
After the shooting,
we should check the agenda together.
Because you're late,
the time we have is less than half an hour.
Speed up.
In this way,
we can finish it in half an hour.
But I can't speak faster.
My speech
is
even
slower.
What do you want?
I'll compensate you for your time.
Haven't you heard of that saying?
Time is precious,
it's impossible to buy time.
Time is very expensive.
I can't compensate you with time.
But I can compensate you with someone. Is it okay?
Deal.
This way.
Sit down.
I'll arrange a job for you.
Just sit here
and watch the sofa.
Don't let anyone steal it.
Who would steal this sofa?
Who knows?
Some people may look like they don't care about it,
but they actually care about it a lot.
Who?
Did I mention you?
Is this sofa useful,
beautiful,
or expensive?
Why do I feel
the air smells sour?
I find you are suitable to be a cook.
You like to add some "flavors" to things.
You know what?
I used to cook a lot when I was abroad.
The food I cooked was quite delicious.
Mr. Lin, the scene is ready.
I'm going to work.
Wait for me here.
Director,
Mr. Lin bought these.
He asked
you to try this flavor.
This,
he asked you to drink it more.
I have one too.
Mr. Lin is so nice.
He is handsome
and takes care of others.
I really want to work with him every day.
Right, Director?
Why don't you go to their company?
Director, I'll get back to work.
Have you been sitting here motionless
and looking at the sofa?
Why don't you eat?
I can't accept a reward without contributions.
I don't like slacking off.
Let's talk about work.
You should eat something.
When I was abroad,
I didn't have meals regularly,
which almost destroyed my health.
Didn't your girlfriend take good care of you?
So sour.
Will you take care of me?
What does it have to do with me?
Nothing to do with it?
Gaogui,
what's going on between you and Mr. Zhong?
And what's going on
between you and Mr. Lin?
Did I really misjudge you?
As an outsider,
I think Mr. Lin is quite nice.
Have you lost your passion
after dating with him for a long time?
That's why
you had a spark with Mr. Zhong?
What spark?
I've been so worried
that my eyebrows are burning.
Mr. Sun took care of me
and let me be the director of the Product Department.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
Besides,
can I let a newbie ride on my head?
Yes.
We've worked hard for so long.
How can we be replaced easily?
What a joke.
I always feel something is wrong
on the relationship of Zhen Gaogui and Mr. Lin.
Is the rumor true?
We'll know it later anyway.
I don't want to wait anymore.
Aren't we going to hold a media appreciation banquet
for Meton in a few days?
I heard from the Media Department that
Lin Yue is on the alternative guest list.
What do you mean?
Invite Lin Yue.
Ju Ran,
I don't think it's a good idea.
OK.
Meton Food's media appreciation banquet
in Shengyi Hotel
is ready.
My colleagues in charge of offline activities
will update the progress at any time.
As for the information about the popcorn of new flavors,
Mr. Zhong, do you have something to say?
I have a lot of things to say.
I'm afraid that after work,
you do not have enough work,
then you will meet someone.
Someone?
You mean Yue, right?
Don't worry.
If I'm that free,
who worked overtime for you every day?
Not now.
But you never know.
People's mind changes fast.
Mr. Zhong, you'd better say it to yourself.
Take this back and discuss
the corresponding relationship between the flavors and the anime characters.
Let's see if they can match.
Mr. Zhong,
do you think
there could be gossips related to you and me
if I don't have a boyfriend?
Of course.
Why not?
How?
You're Party A's CEO.
I'm just an employee of Party B.
It's like I'm taking a shortcut.
Are you kidding?
Do you really think I have a shortcut?
Have you ever had a shortcut?
It doesn't matter if I had one or not.
What matters is
others think I've taken a shortcut.
Didn't Yue
open the back door for you?
Why do you call Yue more intimately
than I do?
We just cooperated for a few days.
It seems that you and Yue will
have a bright future.
Enough.
As for popcorn of new flavors,
does the Product R&D Department
have any new materials?
Let's go. I'll show you.
Xiaotian,
I know
you're an ambitious young man.
Director Shen,
goodbye.
If you go somewhere else,
you will get a higher position.
I'm waiting for your help.
Mr. Zhong.
What's going on?
Here's the thing,
Xiaotian resigned.
He has noble ambition.
He thinks that going to another company
will bring him better development.
Everyone has his own goals.
We can't stop him.
Right, Xiaotian?
Mr. Zhong,
thank you for appreciating me.
I will always remember your help.
Goodbye.
Wait.
Xiaotian, why are you leaving?
I'm sorry.
What a pity.
He's a talent.
I'm speechless.
Such a fool is taking the company's important position.
How can the company get better?
What kind of idiot?
Director Shen of Product R&D Department.
He is afraid that newcomers will cut a smart figure.
I've heard that he fired many people
in the past years with ridiculous reasons.
As long as someone has achievements,
he'll fire him.
I didn't expect Mr. Zhong to care about your employees.
I heard what they said and
I thought you were...
What?
A loser.
You think I haven't heard of it?
Actually, when I first came to the company,
just like you,
everyone thought I know nothing
and couldn't do anything well.
Director Zhang even
didn't want to give me an offer.
Yes.
That's why I'm giving you this chance.
You did a good job.
Actually, I'm grateful to you.
You made me feel that I'm outstanding.
Although I feel like my life is in a mud,
I think
I get to know how to climb up.
Well,
is it so hard?
Lin Yue,
no, Yue,
didn't think of helping you?
Or you two
do not have any relations at all!
Do you
hope it's fake?
I hope it's true,
at least he can sign the authorization contract more easily.
Here.
Thank you, Mr. Zhong.
Mr. Zhong.
Come in.
Xiaotian,
why are you back?
Say goodbye to Mr. Zhong?
Mr. Zhong asked me to come back.
You're just in time.
I have an announcement.
From today on,
I officially appoint Xu Xiaotian
as the director of the Online Product R&D Department.
He is in the same position as Director Shen.
From now on,
he is Director Xu.
He's mainly responsible for the online product development.
Mr. Zhong,
do you mean
the Product R&D Department
will be divided into two parallel parts?
Yes.
As for manpower of the new department,
I will choose some people in the current Product R&D Department.
In the future, Director Shen,
you have to work harder
and do more work.
Xu Xiaotian,
didn't you agree to resign?
Director Shen,
here's the thing,
the troubles you said I would have
if I don't quit
were already
solved by Mr. Zhong.
And he promised they would never happen.
So I decided to stay
to contribute my power to Meton Food.
Mr. Zhong, I think...
Enough.
I'm just informing you.
As for the details.
they will be discussed at the company meeting next time.
[Shengyi International Hotel]
[Appreciation banquet]
Why is Lin Yue
in this guest list?
And his name is handwritten?
I didn't know he would come.
One of my clients couldn't come.
Ju Ran advised me
to invite Lin Yue, who is on the alternate list, instead.
Then, his name was added.
He didn't refuse us?
No.
What's wrong?
Ju Ran.
If everyone hadn't asked you
about the relationship between you and Mr. Lin,
would you keep it a secret?
Yes.
I think there's nothing to say.
Everyone is busy with work.
No way.
Ju Ran,
I think no matter what,
we should let Gaogui and Mr. Lin make their relationship public.
Otherwise, we're afraid that you'll meet a scumbag.
No need. Indeed.
Believe me.
I've seen many gossips like this.
If you don't make it public,
it's very likely that
he will flirt with other girls.
It's bad for both of you.
And I think
this is something to be blessed with.
There's no need to hide, right?
That's right.
Otherwise, we might not be convinced
of your relationship.
What if Zhen Gaogui made up the stories?
This...
How is that possible?
I'm just shy.
Ju Ran,
you mean...
Let me give you an example,
can I make an official announcement?
How long did you stay up
to have such a dream?
You're always dreaming like Zhen Gaogui.
Forget it.
Do you think you're a prince on the run?
Have you seen Mr. Zhong?
No.
I've been looking for him for a long time.
Is he going to be late again?
Director Lu,
I've checked the list of guests.
I have to go out now.
I'll be right back.
The appreciation banquet is about to begin.
Hello, Senior Lin.
I'm Zhen Gaogui.
I'm in Paris.
Welcome, Junior.
Don't just stand there. Come in.
Hello, Senior.
Let me introduce new roommates to you.
Leticia, Bastian.
Nice to meet you.
Your Chinese cuisine smells so good.
I'm a good cook.
Thank you. I'm hungry.
You scared me.
Happy birthday to you.
Thank you.
Blow out the candles.
Senior,
you're back so soon.
I don't know if I can see you again.
I have a chance to start my own business in China.
Call me when you come back, okay?
Good luck.
That's what happened.
That's the thing.
When you go upstairs,
if my colleagues ask you
something that should be asked,
you know how to answer, right?
Help me make up the lie.
I was wondering why Zhong Yiming
was like a Gatling gun,
which would shoot me when we met.
I see.
You used me as your shield.
Did you ask for my permission?
I had no choice.
My life was so hard
but I didn't ask you for help.
Could you please help me this time?
Okay, okay.
How can I not help you?
But it will affect our cooperation
if Zhong Yiming is jealous.
Who cares?
Protecting my job is more important.
You are not the one who will send me an offer.
I've provided a job for you,
but you didn't choose to come to my company.
I did so for our friendship.
How can we be friends if I work for you?
All right, I'm going upstairs,
you go up later.
Okay.
Your Yue
is invited as a special guest, are you happy?
Of course.
Why do you look happier than me?
This is our company's activity,
of course I'm happy.
And you guys are doing well,
so I'm happy.
We didn't see you so happy
after some activities were successfully held.
Not only that.
I thought you would be jealous.
Jealous?
Am I that kind of person
who will be jealous?
Mr. Zhong, you're here.
If you're late again,
I  don't know how to explain it to others.
It's an important event today,
how can I be late?
If I'm late,
I would miss
a wonderful show.
What?
I'd like to see the wonderful show.
Mr. Zhong, you speak first,
and then the guests.
Director Lu, come with me.
Look at them,
they look like an old couple.
They can understand each other with just one glance.
Mr. Lin,
we have makeup artists here.
Do you want some makeup?
Okay.
Do you want to go with me?
I'll go with you to apply some shading powder.