[English subtitles are available]
Gaogui.
Do you really have to pay the material cost yourself this time?
Yes.
That's what I promised Boss.
Don't act tough, newbie.
According to my experience,
Meton won't pay.
Exactly.
The money the company advanced for you
can't be without a price.
If you can't pay it back…
This matter can be solved somehow.
It's not like it's a dead end.
What are you going to do?
If you can't pay it back,
you'll become a credit card slave.
Do you want to work here all your life
until you become an old lady?
I'll find a way to solve it now.
[Amazing Girls]
[Episode 7]
Young lady.
Stop!
What are you doing here?
You can't come in here. Get out.
Come on.
Come out.
Come out! Come out!
Isn't this the processing factory for Meton?
Yes, why?
I just want to ask
if there's something wrong with the circuit
and thus the factory needs to shut down for repair?
What exactly are you doing here?
Does it have anything to do with you?
I'm from the PR company cooperating with Meton.
I'm still waiting for the goods here for promotion.
So I want to ask the person in charge for more information.
Well,
ask the person in charge to pick you up.
Otherwise, you can't get in.
Do you hear me?
Sir, I'm not a fraud.
You can ask your CEO Mr. Zhong if you don't believe me.
What Mr. Zhong?
I've told you.
Our director is the boss here.
Go back now or I'll call the police.
Hurry up.
Duty Room, Gate No. 1 can't open.
Come and take a look.
Okay.
I'm coming.
I'm telling you, don't come in.
Beauty, are you eating?
I want to ask you something.
Do you know the reason
why the factory shut down?
How would I know?
It's all arranged by the leader.
We are also wondering.
Well,
the production was all good.
Why did they suddenly tell us to shut down the factory?
Suddenly?
Wasn't there a breakdown or something before the shutdown?
No. Everything was fine.
The assembly line was fine.
Oh right,
they said we needed to eliminate the potential safety hazard.
Do you also think
this is weird?
Hi.
How dare you sneak in?
I didn't mean it.
I walked in by accident.
-Stop!
-Your factory is too big. I'm lost.
I'm sorry.
Stop!
Come in.
Sit there.
Listen.
I'll call the police later. Explain it yourself then.
Sir, please let me go.
I'm not a bad person.
Let you go?
Listen.
If I let you go today,
100 people like you will come in tomorrow.
So I can't let you off easily.
Duty Room, pick up Mr. Zhong at the gate.
Okay, I'm coming.
Sit tight.
Stay still.
Mr. Zhong, right?
Yes.
The higher-ups told me that you're coming.
Do you want to meet the director now?
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
This way.
Wait. Wait.
What's going on here?
That's the thief we just caught.
Thief?
The factory has shut down. What will a thief steal?
I don't know.
She's sneaky.
She wouldn't say anything.
She even went inside to inquire about things.
I don't know what she was prying into.
She doesn't look like a good person.
Please put in a good word for me, Mr. Zhong.
As a security guard,
you can't tell good from bad.
This is my guest.
And you're locking her like that.
Guest?
Oh my, it's a misunderstanding.
I'm sorry.
It's a misunderstanding.
Hurry up.
Why did you come all the way here?
I'm here to see the director.
Just go back. Don't make trouble for me.
Take me to the director.
Okay.
This way.
I want to go too.
[A Grand Ambition]
Mr. Zhong.
Come on in, please.
Have a seat.
I should have picked you up if I knew you were coming.
I wouldn't bother you with such a trivial matter.
Mr. Zhong.
If you need anything,
just call me.
The factory has been shut down recently. The loss is serious.
I'm here to see
when the factory can re-open.
I might have made a mistake this time.
Well…
Why don't we have a drink tonight and have a good talk then?
No, thanks.
I just want to know
when we can restart working again at the earliest.
We've arranged for an engineer to make an all-round examination and repair.
To count it all,
we can only start working after the Mid-Autumn Festival at the earliest.
I'm very anxious myself.
As you know,
I've been in the factory for so long.
I don't want to be out of stock, do I?
Director, I asked the workers.
They said there was no problem with the production line.
Since you're shutting down the factory to examine it,
you have to give us an explanation
and tell us which part went wrong.
Then we will surely understand and support you.
The safety hazard
is actually a big deal.
You see,
it's about personal safety
and production safety.
But how could we
ensure the safety?
I think
we should make safety
our first priority, right?
This matter
is very important, isn't it?
You
must attach much importance to it, too.
So I think...
Wait a minute.
So,
how did you find out
there were safety problems?
When you find a problem,
you have to solve the problem.
If I don't have a complete overhaul,
how would I know if there's a problem?
Right?
Problems
are all found during an overhaul.
All right, we're leaving then.
You look quite busy.
I won't bother you then.
Don't go. Let's have a drink tonight.
No, no, no.
Let's go.
Are you really leaving?
See you.
Bye.
I didn't know you were such a person.
What's wrong with me?
Can't you see?
The director was obviously hiding something.
As a boss,
why didn't you debunk his lies?
Besides,
as long as you put pressure on him,
he can surely supply the goods.
I just started working in the company.
I don't even know who spread the news.
It's definitely not appropriate to force it.
Why not?
It's fine that you entrap me,
but you still want to harm our company, too?
Do you know
if we can't get money from your company,
I'll have to bear all the cost.
Forget it.
I have nothing to say to you.
No matter how much I do,
it's nothing to you.
I was so wrong about you.
Really?
It's the bonus day again.
After paying off the credit card debt,
I'll be looking forward to getting my next month's salary.
Yes.
Paying off credit card debt
will make disappear the joy of making money, won't it?
That being said,
some things
can indeed
make people forget some of their worries.
Why don't we discuss what to eat for dinner?
The company pays us for one dinner every month.
We have to pick a good day.
For example…
Today!
You guys go. I'm busy. I'm not going.
Let's have a hotpot tonight.
My treat.
Boss, you're so nice!
Thank you, Boss.
Gaogui.
Boss seldom treats us.
Have the hotpot first before anything else.
Yes, go with us.
Okay.
Gao, I'm leaving.
Aren't you leaving?
Hurry up. We're all waiting for you.
Don't wait for me. You guys eat first.
Gaogui works so hard.
It makes us professional eaters
feel ashamed.
Ju Ran, wait for me.
Hurry up!
Coming.
Gaogui.
Hurry up. Let's go have dinner.
I'll be working for a while. You guys eat first.
Hurry up.
Isn't your department having dinner together today?
Why are you still here?
Don't tell me they didn't invite you again.
They did.
But I'm not in the mood to eat.
What are you going to do with this hot potato?
I'll pay off my credit card debt myself.
I'll bear all the costs the company has paid.
What nonsense are you talking about?
You're just working for others, but not starting a business of your own.
It's my last dignity
to keep my promise.
No matter what,
I'll take full responsibility for this.
I'll just find a few more part-time jobs in the worst-case scenario.
I'll make as much money as I can.
I'm off work then.
[Insufficient inventory]
Why is it out of stock even before it goes on sale?
This is hunger marketing.
You think too highly of yourself.
We didn't want to buy it anyway.
I'm turning to an anti-fan from a fan.
Is it a lie?
After all, the shutdown of the factory
[Meiziwei Group]
is not the responsibility of Xinda PR.
You must have seen
the contract we signed clearly.
There are exemption terms in it.
It's written clearly
that the billing will be paid according to the final sales.
The sales are zero now.
We don't need to pay.
This situation
is something neither of us don't want to see.
But based on the spirit of contract,
should your company
bear part of the loss, too?
You shift the problem of the production lines of the factory
to a PR company.
If this gets out,
you'll be laughed at, won't you?
You need to understand this.
If I had a way to solve this problem,
I won't make things so ugly.
But now, we can only follow the contract.
We really can't afford it.
[President's Office]
It's the factory's problem.
Why did you ask Xinda PR to bear the cost?
Mr. Zhong,
You proposed the idea
that the supplier advances the cost.
But I know
your starting point
was to save our company's cost.
But this is the factory's problem.
I didn't say
they have to advance this part too, did I?
This is what we, your subordinates, need to do—sharing your burden.
You didn't expect that,
but I did.
And I wrote it clearly in the contract.
This is my loyalty to the company.
I won't let the company lose a penny.
But business is business, and private affairs are private affairs.
If you feel guilty
and want to pay for it yourself,
I'll have no objection.
Nice bikes.
Are you sure you want to sell them all?
Yes.
Are you selling this racing motorcycle, too?
Sign it.
Please.
Stop asking me what I'll do.
I have Plan B,
but it seems
it's not a good idea after all.
I'm worried about you.
Yuxuan,
It won't help to worry about me now.
Leave me alone.
I'll think of a way.
[Cash from your credit card]
Mr. Sun, here's the thing.
Please pay the unresolved payment
of the bucket-printing factory.
Who will pay?
I myself.
Mr. Zhong,
listen to me.
Where can you get the money?
Don't go astray
just to get money.
It'll ruin your life.
You think too much. I got the money through the proper channels.
All right.
I'll remit the money to you now.
Remit the money…
Where did he go?
He said he wanted to pay the money for Xinda PR.
What money?
The printing cost of the Mid-Autumn Festival promotion project
of Xinda PR.
Weren't we asked them to bear it?
But the goods were not delivered in the end.
So the money...
He wants to pay for it himself.
That is so unprofessional.
In my view,
he just wants to show off
in front of his little girlfriend.
I know him well.
He usually spends a lot and doesn't save money.
I'm afraid there's nothing he can do.
Hello.
Have you made up your mind?
Come on, beauty. Get in.
Wait a second.
Hello?
Really?
Great!
I'm sorry, sir.
I don't need it anymore.
What are you doing? Are you kidding me?
[President's Office]
Mr. Zhong,
the Mid-Autumn Festival promotion plan has completely failed.
Do you have any compensation measures for this season?
Are you listening to me?
We are in a critical condition!
I know.
I thought you would only oppose
any decision of mine.
Don't you have a solution already
and just need the signature from me, the substitute president?
What I opposed
was the part that I thought would disturb
the normal operation of the company.
Mr. Zhong, you need to understand.
I've been working in this company
since I graduated from college.
I have feelings for this place.
If anything happens to the company,
I'll be more anxious and worried than anyone else.
I'm so glad to have a colleague like you.
My brother has good taste.
So, what's your plan?
I don't have any.
You go and discuss with Vice President Sun.
Let me think more about it.
[54, Guangda South Road]
My heart hurts.
Just like you,
I sold all my treasures recently.
Do you feel the pain in your heart?
But I've been doing really well lately.
I'll pass the good luck to you.
Then I have to get some of your good luck.
I heard good things come in pairs.
The money for the factory has been settled.
You haven't encountered any trouble in your company anymore, have you?
Thank you for your support, Mr. Zhong.
I'll continue to do my best.
Mom,
where did you put my socks?
I couldn't find them anywhere.
Did you put them in the chest of drawers again?
Not this pair.
Socks.
This.
[Yangyan Spa]
Mom,
do you think
they will refund us?
Maybe.
Darling, I'm sorry.
Darling, sorry to keep you waiting.
A client insisted that I go.
I just found time to see you, honey.
Darling, why are you here today?
You know what? You came at a good time.
It's time for our anniversary.
We have a promotion—charge 5,000 and get 2,000 for free!
Darling, do you want to consider it?
Well,
we're here to ask
if we can refund
the part of the balance that we haven't spent yet?
My baby, you're here.
Are you going to have your hair permed
or dyed?
Your hair is a bit dry.
If you have hair care in our shop for half a year,
your hair will be smooth and shiny.
Well, we're here today
to refund the balance of the card.
Darling, how about
a full set of skincare?
Did someone treat you badly last time?
Dear,
do you want to go to another place to have a facial?
When are you planning to get your hair permed?
Pore cleansing, exfoliation, and wrinkle removal…
We can do them all very well, honey.
Dye it.
Or at least you can have a scalp care.
You said so much,
but when can I get a refund?
Just tell me the date.
I need to apply to the headquarters.
I'll tell you in at least three months.
If you really want to refund it,
you can introduce some new friends.
If they get a 20,000-yuan value card in one go.
I can refund you 30% of the balance.
What about the rest of the balance?
Introduce some more friends to join us.
What if the headquarters say no?
It's okay. I'll apply again.
Then I'll give you an answer in another three months.
Mom, let's go.
Take care, honey.
You won't refund the card, will you?
It's okay, Mom.
Let's think more about it.
There will be a way.
Director.
We meet again.
Hello, Director.
We brought many relatives here.
Line up.
Order, order.
Line up. Line up.
Sister, what project do you want to do?
This one.
Supreme beauty, regaining your youth.
48 Set A.
Set A, swipe my card.
Honey.
This is
against our rules.
Dear.
How?
You said it yourself
that this card can be used by the cardholder herself and her relatives.
Yes, honey.
But others can't use it, darling.
What do you mean?
They are all my relatives.
Yes, we're all relatives.
All right, don't just stand there.
Hurry up and arrange a service for my third aunt.
Darling.
Bye. Bye.
Mom, we've refunded the card
in an indirect way.
Fenfang.
I'm done too.
Are you?
Your skin is so moist.
You look so good.
Thank you.
It's 438 yuan with 50% off.
-Okay.
-Just give me 400.
It's so worth it.
Okay, I've paid.
Thank you.
Fenfang.
It's such a fancy place. If you don't give me a discount,
I wouldn't have been too stingy to come here.
Will there be another chance like this?
Yes.
I've used up all the balance on this card.
But tomorrow is the special event for the hair salon.
If you want to have a stylish hairdo,
don't miss the chance.
Thank you so much, Fenfang.
I'll bring a few more friends.
Really?
That's great.
Great!
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Bye. Bye.
See you tomorrow.
Thanks.
My goodness.
Here's your steak. Enjoy.
Thank you.
It smells so good.
It's been such a long time.
I feel reluctant as if eating it is a waste of money.
Yeah.
Let me tell you, for a long time I haven't…
I haven't even seen
such delicious food,
not to mention eating it.
Let me tell you.
If I still can't get the money today,
I would have used that credit card.
What are you doing? Eat up.
If you see something nice,
you have to help me pick one.
Sure.
Gaogui.
Hello, Aunt.
You're eating here too?
Yes.
Gaogui, it's been a long time since we last met.
What have you been busy with?
Lately, I've been
busy with work.
By the way, Gaogui,
We are going
-to attend a brand press conference.
-Yes.
There's still one vacancy.
Do you want to join us?
No, thanks.
I have to work overtime later.
Okay. Okay.
We'll leave now.
Bye, Auntie.
See you next time.
See you next time. Bye.
Weren't you friends with them before?
Why didn't you go hang out with them?
Maybe my situation is different.
I feel a little uncomfortable
being with them now.
Eat up.
Are you busy?
Since the company is in a mess,
why don't we pave the way for Mr. Zhong Jr.?
I think he's not far away from getting lost.
If the company is gone,
not only will he get lost,
but we will also go with him.
What's going on?
Why are you being so cynical today?
Don't you think the shutdown this time
is as damaging to ourselves as to the enemy?
If we miss the golden selling season,
we'll lose too much.
Loss is inevitable
if we want Mr. Zhong Jr. to lose his authority.
It is a good opportunity now.
You and I both know the company's situation.
If we keep losing money like this,
the group might give us up completely.
The company belongs to Meiziwei Group.
Just do your job. That's enough.
The company doesn't belong to us.
Don't you always put the company's interests
before everything else?
What's wrong with you today?
Why are you sarcastic to me?
Mr. Sun, let me ask you.
Was there really a safety hazard
so that the factory had to shut down
or was it a fabricated safety hazard?
I know a few people at the factory.
They told me…
You can't accuse people at will.
You need evidence for everything.
Or it'll be slander.
But then again,
the company has suffered a loss,
and Mr. Zhong Jr. has suffered a loss,
but for our future development,
there is no loss, right?
Whether Mr. Zhong Jr. resigns
or gets fired,
we'll go further up the career ladder in the future.
I do want to get promoted,
but it can't be done at the cost of the company's interests.
If it happens again,
I won't keep silent.
Director Lu, go meet someone with me.
Okay.
I hope you can behave yourself.
Do you remember Mr. Lin I told you last time?
The CEO of Dooro Bear?
We have reached a verbal cooperation.
Their IP
is popular among all age groups.
Meton will become
their company's first partner
of trying to co-brand snack products.
Indeed.
Even I, who don't usually watch anime,
know about their anime image.
If we can cooperate with them,
it'll be very good for us Meton.
It's just that…
Mr. Lin.
Hello.
This is Director Lu from our company.
Why don't we play two rounds to relax
and warm up?
You two go ahead, please.
I'm not good at playing it.
Plus, I have some emails
to deal with.
Then… Please.
Alright.
Here.
No, I can't go on anymore.
I really tried my best.
Mr. Lin,
I can't play with you at my level.
How about this?
Let's sign the contract first.
I'll take you to a race next time.
No hurry.
Let's wait for the right time.
Mr. Lin, it seems that you're a bit insincere.
Mr. Zhong is usually very busy.
He specially adjusted his schedule to meet you today.
Mr. Lin must have made time to meet us.
He must be very sincere, right?
How about this?
I'll play a round with Director Lu.
If Director Lu wins,
I'll sign this. How's that?
Okay.
One to zero.
Two to zero.
Ten to zero.
Fine.
Then
I won't waste your time.
Let's continue after signing the contract.
Didn't you just say you can't play?
But why do you play so well?
I've always been the champion of the badminton team in college.
You've been playing it since college? Then...
Sign here.
One more.
How about this? I'm leaving.
I feel I'm not needed here.
Didn't you say…
Why do you leave just after signing the contract?
Didn't we agree to play badminton?
Director Lu is free.
Let Director Lu play with you.
If you're too tired today,
I'll give you a day off tomorrow.
I'm leaving.
Let's play two more rounds.
You play so well.
You can teach me.
Besides,
I'm not that bad, am I?
It's not bad, right?
Indeed.
Your skill of picking up the shuttlecock
is not bad.
As for playing badminton,
let's play together next time.
Why do I feel like I've met two frauds?
Mr. Zhong.
We've got the role authorization
of the new anime IP Dooro Bear.
So, we're now having a meeting to discuss
how to explore a new direction
and increase the overall sales.
We can't leave the buckets
which you put a lot of effort into in the warehouse.
The anime image, Poko,
is inspired by a cactus.
People from little kids to adults
would like to buy it.
Kids…
Director Lu,
why don't we take a break and have a meal?
Okay.
Let's take a 40-minute break.
Isn't it a bit rush?
Mr. Zhong.
It's not the time to eat slowly.
Okay. I'll listen to you.
Mr. Zhong,
I'm going to the convenience store for dinner, too.
I ordered takeout.
I'll get it. Wait for me.
Mr. Zhong.
Did you order all this?
Yes.
Our boss Director Zhang ordered it for me before.
It was exactly the same as this.
You two have great chemistry.
Is it what you ate in the office
that night when you worked overtime?
Yes.
It was I who ordered that.
Eat up.
You ordered it?
Why did you order it for me?
Director Zhang
asked me if I had given you a lot of work tasks.
If he didn't ask,
I wouldn't have known
you had stayed up late every day
for our project.
If anything happens to you,
I'll have to take responsibility, won't I?
Thank you, Mr. Zhong.
Okay.
Here you are.
Hello?
Okay, I'll be right there.
I'll wait for you to come back and eat with me.
I'm an old employee.
This is the best advice for you.
Be good, understand?
Yes.
When you go back,
get the material ready for me.
Okay.
You go back first.
Okay, Mr. Sun.
Well...
Mr. Zhong Jr.
I'll call a taxi for you.
No, it's just two kilometers.
When the taxi you call arrives, I'll be already there.
But you're the president.
It is not decent for you to ride this.
Where is your beloved motorcycle?
I haven't seen it for a long time.
Speaking of which, I now remembered.
Didn't it stop right here before?
I sold it.
Otherwise, where can I get the money to pay Xinda?
No way. It's not that bad.
All right, I'm leaving.
Go back and tell them
that we'll continue the meeting tomorrow.
Okay.
Slow down, Mr. Zhong.
It's not as good as a motorcycle.
Zhen Gaogui, pack up and eat at home.
Mr. Zhong Jr. won't be back soon.
Where did he go?
Do I have to report to you where Mr. Zhong Jr. is going?
Pack them up and go eat them somewhere else.
Okay, I see.
Gaogui.
I just found out that
Mr. Zhong Jr. sold his beloved motorcycle
to pay for you.
That's his life.
You have to work hard
to live up to his efforts.
Did you mean
Mr. Zhong paid the printing cost
by selling his motorcycle?
It's a secret. Don't let anyone know.
Boss.
I heard that Mr. Zhong sold his motorcycle
to pay for us.
He didn't pay with the company's money.
What should we do?
He can do whatever he wants.
I really don't know what to say to you.
You're right to worry.
But you don't have to worry so much
in your position.
Hello?
What?
I'll be right there.
You have to take these away today.
You can't leave them here anymore.
Go back to your work.
Excuse me.
What's going on?
Why are you taking all the goods away?
The warehouse often malfunctions.
We need to empty the warehouse for maintenance.
Your goods
can't be placed here anymore.
How about this?
Can we get them out
the moment the factory ships the goods?
If you don't take them away now,
it will be scrapped.
Don't make trouble.
No.
At least wait for Mr. Zhong's order.
Vice President Sun asked us to move them.
Go away.
Move!