[English subtitles are available]
Is it raining outside?
I remember you didn't bring an umbrella
when you went out.
In my experience,
someone has specifically given it to her.
Don't joke about that.
By the way, has Boss arrived?
He went out.
He asked me to tell you
he'll meet you at the airport tomorrow morning.
The Snacks Expo is a big event.
You gotta work harder.
Leave the company to me.
[Amazing Girls]
[Episode 18]
[Guanghai City]
Give me your ID card.
Hello.
Hello, we booked it in advance.
Please wait a moment.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Here we go. Here we go.
Are we all staying here this time?
You are referring to?
I'm referring to us
and the client.
Yes.
Some of the employees of Meton
will live here.
Zhong Yiming
didn't tell you in advance?
No.
Why did he tell me about this?
Look.
Is that him?
Boss, are you kidding me?
I don't think he'll appear
when we're just talking about him.
Here are your room cards and your ID cards.
Thank you.
Boss, let's go
before he sees us.
What a coincidence!
I came earlier
so I went to meet a distributor.
I just came back.
I'm sorry.
We have a video meeting later.
We need to go up first.
I have an appointment with a client as well.
Okay, we'll go up first.
Let's go.
We'll confirm the things about the exhibition later.
What did they say?
He either didn't reply to my messages
or made perfunctory replies.
Boss, look,
that's how he replied.
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
Let's talk inside.
You scared me.
Why are you sneaking around at my door?
Where are you going?
I need to talk to you.
Director Lu is not here. He asked me to talk to you
about the booth location.
Was it changed to a new place?
No.
They said it's already settled.
They didn't have time to coordinate.
But Boss and I
will go there later to see
if other companies are willing to switch places.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
You're here, Mr. Zhong.
Let's go together.
No, no.
Let's go.
About the location of the exhibition,
we need to double-check.
We need to communicate with them,
okay?
[The Ninth International Snacks Expo]
[Upstairs]
Director Li asked us to come here,
but he didn't answer the phone.
What does he mean?
He deliberately refused to see us.
Isn't it obvious?
What should we do?
Keep calling him.
Excuse me.
Do you know where Director Li is?
I don't know. I'm busy.
That won't work.
I'll work it out.
Brother.
Excuse me.
May I use your speaker?
Sure.
Thank you.
It's okay.
You!
What are you doing?
Director Li!
Someone is here for a security check, Director Li.
Coming. Coming.
Coming.
Coming. Coming. Coming.
Just call me if you need anything.
Don't play such a dirty trick.
I can't get through to you.
I have no choice.
Sorry, Director Li.
Alright. Alright.
What do you want?
It's about the booth of Meton.
I need to
ask other companies.
Some may not come,
so there will be temporary vacancies.
There might be a chance.
I'll let you know later, okay?
What?
That's not much of an answer.
It's not helpful.
Well.
Let's go in and take a look.
Boss.
I think no company will
switch places with us.
It's okay.
There's no better location,
but you still have me.
You can do it?
We PR people are working on
public relations.
Those relationships we have been maintaining
will keep our jobs.
What kind of relationships are those?
Can you teach me?
I'm really sorry.
I've walked around
and asked all the companies.
There are no other booths for you.
What do we do now?
I'll get back to work.
Thank you, Director Li.
You're welcome.
-He's leaving?
-It's fine.
Let's leave.
What should we do?
What do you think of this place?
Of course it's nice.
It's next to the main hallway and the gate.
It's a good spot.
Then if it's for Meton,
what do you think?
Really?
Are you serious?
Will the previous company agree?
Go and tell them.
I'll take care of it.
Will this work?
My client rented this place.
I'll talk to my client.
No way.
You'll get scolded.
Alright, that's it.
When you encountered so many troubles,
you solved them yourself.
I'm a director after all.
At the critical moment,
you should leave these
to me.
Otherwise, what does the company
want me to do?
But...
If that's the case,
your relationship with the client
will be affected.
I'll just tell Director Lu
that there's no other place.
We'll leave it at that.
Don't do that.
Just tell Meton about this.
I’ll deal with the business with the client.
I've done this kind of exhibition for years.
Don't worry.
Director Lu.
This is the place we have now.
Right. It's a really good place.
It's hard to imagine how you did it.
Our company did pay a price for this.
As long as the result is good.
This way.
Your package is here.
Thank you.
[International Snacks Expo Promoting Materials]
This...
No...
Why is it all wet?
Sorry, Miss.
It was all wet when we signed it.
The deliveryman has made a record.
I'm really sorry.
But...
Open it first.
Maybe the thing is...
[International Snacks Expo Promoting Materials]
It...
It can't be used.
Gaogui, Director Lu.
Boss, are you going out?
I have something to do.
What happened?
I don't know.
That's it when I got it.
But I'll take care of it.
Okay.
See you later.
Let's go to the printing shop nearby.
It's not too late.
I'll go now.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
It's not a big deal.
I can handle it myself.
What is it?
I happen to be free.
I'll go with you.
The package of the folded leaflets was soaked.
I need to find a printing shop.
We can have late-night snack together.
Tell me.
Did you specifically send me an umbrella
in the warehouse that day?
It rained that day.
You cared so much about me.
The Snacks Expo is about to begin.
If anything happens to you,
what should I do, right?
Just like that?
Yes.
Get in.
[Industrial and Commercial Bank of China]
Sir. Sir.
We have something to print.
[Focus on the Office
High Quality Printing]
Can you close your shop later?
Okay, come in.
Thank you.
[Find Us for Printing
Professional Quality]
Guys, it's done. Take a look.
It smells good.
This one then.
I'm hungry.
How about fried noodles?
Okay.
Sir.
One fried noodles, one fried vermicelli, and two drinks.
Okay.
Two more sausages.
Have a seat.
Here's your sausages and drinks.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
I didn't tell you last time.
My mom didn't allow me to eat these things
when I was little.
Every time I went to the amusement park with my dad,
it would take me a while
to let him buy it for me.
Now I have money,
nobody will stop me.
But I think it's not
as tasty as it used to be.
When I was little,
if I wanted to eat sausages,
I had to sell a lot of popcorn.
Mr. Zhong.
Stop pretending to be poor.
I've suffered a lot before.
I've never had sausages
or snacks with my dad.
You...
I have no impression of him.
He seemed to be working all the time.
Every time he came home from work,
I have fallen asleep.
I have barely had a meal with him.
Actually,
if you don't mind,
you can always come to my home to eat.
But,
I'm not asking you to make dumplings at my place.
Here.
Your fried noodles and fried vermicelli. Enjoy.
Thank you.
You're so busy.
There are countless emails to check.
Let's eat first.
One sec.
Let's eat.
By the way,
I forgot to bring my laptop charger.
Can I borrow yours?
Okay, I'll get it for you later.
Okay.
Wait for me here.
I'll get the charger for you.
I told you to wait for me.
Why are you here?
I want to see
if it is different from mine.
It looks the same.
Thank you.
I'll go back then.
Bye.
Who?
It's Zhang Feiyang.
Go inside to hide and don't let him know.
Washroom! Washroom!
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Coming. Coming.
Boss.
It's you.
Weren't you in the room earlier?
You went out so late?
Yes, I just went to print leaflets.
Print leaflets?
I saw you wet the leaflets.
I thought you were unfamiliar with the place.
I found a printing shop that I know
to print these for you.
Okay, thank you, Boss.
Well, rest early.
Good night.
Where did he go?
I'm here.
You hid here?
You scared me.
Wait.
We didn't do anything.
Why should I hide?
Right.
Why did you hide?
You asked me to hide.
You were afraid he would misunderstand.
Why did you listen to me?
Besides,
Why would he misunderstand us?
We...
I'm leaving.
Hurry up.
Mr. Zhong.
Am I hallucinating?
Well...
Boss.
Let me explain. He...
No need to explain.
You don't have to explain to me.
No need.
We need to explain.
-He's here to get something.
-I'm here to chat.
-He's here to chat.
-I'm here to get something.
It's okay.
I'll leave you two.
Rest early.
Good night.
[The Ninth International Snacks Expo]
Hello.
[Meton Food]
Please take a look at Meton Food.
There are many new flavors to taste.
Yes, this is our latest flavor.
Hello, we have a lot of new flavors.
You can take a sample.
Hello.
You go first. I need to use the bathroom.
I'll wait for you there.
What are they doing over there?
Why are they all going to the Crispy Popcorn?
How would I know?
I'll go check.
What? What?
Hurry up.
Why isn't he here yet?
Why? Is someone coming? It's so crowded.
I heard it's a famous
French foodie of a Michelin-star restaurant,
called Durand.
He was invited here to taste their popcorn.
I heard that the food consultant of Crispy Popcorn
is this French dessert master.
It should be a very delicious brand.
From French.
I'm looking forward to it.
C-Can I borrow that?
Okay.
Look.
They invited a French dessert master to taste their popcorn.
So they are so popular.
[Crispy Popcorn]
[Special Guest Durand]
[Crispy Popcorn Is Crispy and Delicious]
Their selling point is imported goods.
If that's the case,
the cost is too high.
And it's hard to get.
Let's have a look.
He's coming. He's coming.
I've heard a lot about you.
So this is the master.
-Mr. Durand, this is my booth.
-Okay.
Please take a look.
Excuse me.
Come on.
Let the master have a taste.
Is this the caramel popcorn?
Yes.
The globe shape is beautiful.
Thank you.
It has a nice texture.
Of course.
It tastes sweet on the outside.
It tastes like something
made by a Michelin-star restaurants
in France.
It tastes like something
made by a Michelin-star restaurants
in France.
Do you hear him?
Mr. Durand said
you can only eat it
in Michelin-star restaurants in France.
Time is the key to the popcorn.
Bite it with warmth,
then it reminds you
of the happiness of childhood.
Bite it with warmth,
then it reminds you
of the happiness of childhood.
This taste
can remind you of the happiness of childhood.
Do you want this kind of happiness?
Yes.
Have a taste.
Come in and have a taste.
Come on, have a taste.
Freshly baked popcorn.
Here, you can share it.
Share it with everyone.
It's delicious.
How is it? How does it taste?
Isn't it sweet?
I knew it.
Why are there so many people over there?
A French foodie
came,
and he attracted all of our guests.
Is it Durand?
[Crispy Popcorn]
I heard about him.
He's very popular in France.
All the restaurants he visited
will be crowded.
Is he better than
the influencers?
He's not just an influencer.
He's a predecessor and an expert in the food industry.
We should let him taste
our popcorn.
He's obviously a guest invited by Crispy Popcorn.
If he says our popcorn is not tasty,
then we're shooting ourselves in the foot.
I know something
about these French foodies
They cherish their reputations very much.
They won't say anything against their conscience
because of someone's invitation.
Besides,
they should be invited by
this Snacks Expo.
Most importantly,
I have confidence in our popcorn.
Right.
We should have confidence in our product.
We have confidence! We have confidence!
[Welcome to try]
Are you satisfied?
Hello, Mr. Durand.
Hello.
[Crispy Popcorn]
You remind me of the bakery I visited
in Paris.
Which bakery?
You remind me of the bakery I visited
in Paris.
I heard you recommended it.
It's called Cute Bread.
Yes, I remember that bakery.
Our booth is nearby.
Would you like to try it?
[Crispy Popcorn]
I'm sure it's worth trying.
Sure.
What does this mean?
Mr. Durand wants to taste
other companies' popcorn.
[Welcome to try]
Then get him back.
Mr. Durand has no obligation
[Crispy Popcorn]
to stand for Crispy Popcorn.
He's here for the International Snacks Expo.
No.
This way, please.
It won't let you down.
I knew it.
Mr. Durand
only likes
the popcorn from Crispy Popcorn.
We are
the most popular brand in this Snacks Expo.
I've long heard that Meton Food isn't tasty.
No one bought it long ago.
I also think popcorn from Crispy Popcorn is the best.
Some companies like Meton,
they overestimate themselves.
Right. Am I right?
Yes.
They overestimate themselves.
I want to express my gratitude to you.
You let me taste the flavor I had
many years ago.
I want to express my gratitude to you.
You let me taste the flavor I had
many years ago.
I was very young many years ago.
When I first came to China,
I wanted to find the best local Chinese snacks.
Later, I ate the best popcorn in the world
in an old man's stand.
Although popcorn is not a Chinese specialty,
I can't forget that taste.
I sent someone to look for that old man.
But it failed.
But today I have the same taste.
It's amazing.
I'm glad you like it.
I hope I can see you again in France.
If you come to France, tell him.
He invites you to his house for wine.
I want a box of popcorn too.
Okay.
Give it to him.
It's delicious.
Really? I want a box of it.
Me too.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you very much.
Bye.
This way, please.
What a surprise.
Do you think
the old man he mentioned
is your grandpa?
Maybe two different old men
made the same popcorn.
Maybe grandpa and Durand
met
by fate.
Maybe grandpa and Durand
met by fate.
And Durand
met us by fate.
This world is too big.
It requires many coincidences
for two people to meet.
So now,
we have to cherish the person we meet now.
I don't think you cherish them.
[The Ninth International Snacks Expo]
[Crispy Popcorn Food Co., Ltd]
Come here. Here.
Put it here.
[Crispy Popcorn Food Co., Ltd]
[My Idol Yue][Yue is the Most Handsome Guy on the Internet]
I heard Lin Yue is coming to be a guest today.
I'm looking forward to it.
I've been following him for a long time.
Besides,
what he posted online
makes sense to me.
I really want to see how different he is
from the Internet.
Yes. Yes.
[My Idol Yue][Yue is the Most Handsome Guy on the Internet]
[Why did you stand for my competitor]
[Yue is the Most Handsome Guy on the Internet]
Is she a fan?
I don't know.
Lin Yue didn't post his location
on his homepage.
Is he coming or not?
Yeah.
He didn't announce it before he came?
[Yue Lai Yue Hao]
I really want to see how different he is
from the Internet.
Yes.
Hello, everyone.
I'm very happy to see you
come to the Crispy Popcorn's booth
at this International Snacks Expo.
Our roadshow
is about to begin.
Please stay tuned.
Is he coming or not?
I'm sorry, friends.
Our original guest Lin Yue
can't come here
due to his busy schedule.
Everyone.
Calm down. Calm down.
We prepared a drawing game
to thank you
for your support.
[Drawing]
Those who buy two boxes of our popcorn
have the chance to get
cell phones, Bluetooth earphones and other exquisite prizes.
Come and buy it.
Let's go.
Forget it.
There's more in the back.
It's all delicious popcorn.
Come on.
Buy some.
I've been looking for you for a long time.
I thought you were busy at your booth,
but you came here to see your idol.
Why did you stand for our competitor?
You didn't reply to my messages.
You did such a shameless thing.
D-Do you like shameless people?
No!
Looks like I'm not shameless enough.
This is fake publicity.
I didn't agree to their invitation.
How did it turn out to be a special guest?
Then why are you here?
I-I'm here to see how many people
will come here for me.
It turned out pretty well.
But I've recorded it.
I'll deal with it later.
Okay.
Come with me.
Couple masks.
[Gate 3]
Sit over there.
Do you really think that no one can recognize us
if we wear masks?
Every little bit helps.
I saw your colleague just now.
Where?
What color is she wearing?
Do you have to be like this?
You look like a high school student
meeting the director of the academic affairs office.
Even if I meet
the director of the academic affairs office,
the director will only praise me.
It's working time now. I need to
be meticulous and serious.
Do you want some chips?
No.
Here, try one.
I said I don't want it.
I'll eat it.
[The Ninth International Snacks Expo]
[Meton Food]
Attention, exhibitors.
The exhibition for today is over.
Please leave in an orderly manner before 10 p.m.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Go back and rest early.
Okay, thank you, Mr. Zhong.
Thank you, Mr. Zhong.
Go back.
Please leave in an orderly manner before 10 p.m.
You did a great job today.
I'll treat you to dinner next time.
Why?
It's better not to pick another day.
Do you have work to do later?
I do have work to do today.
Maybe another day.
Go back and rest early.
Attention, exhibitors.
The exhibition for today is over.
Please leave in an orderly manner before 10 p.m.
Boss.
I heard you made another contribution today.
Pack up quickly.
Let's have dinner together.
You've been working for a whole day.
Sure.
I'll go there after I'm done.
I'll wait for you outside.
See you later.
Please enjoy.
Thank you.
[All-media platform promotion data]
Boss, look.
The media department has summarized all the data.
Many influencers
posted news
about our Meton Food spontaneously.
We are here
to take advantage of the foodies.
I didn't expect you to attract all attention.
Good for you.
You taught me well.
It's a new perspective to solve problems.
Yes.
Well,
Today Zhong Yiming and you...
There are so many reposts.
So many people reposted for us spontaneously.
It'll save a lot of marketing expenses.
Boss, what did you just say?
I said
eat now.
This is the real ending pose.
Who is it?
Director Lu, it's me.
Gaogui.
Well,
don't let her see you.
Hide first.
Where can I hide?
It's fine.
This way.
No.
Where can I hide?
In fact, Gaogui can know about this.
Coming.
Director Lu.
Gaogui.
Can I talk to you inside?
Yes.
Okay.
Director,
I've sent the data report to your email.
The exposure this time
is ten times higher than expected
because of the foodie.
Look.
Right?
The data on the Internet is much better.
I remember that Lin Yue also lives here.
I'll ask him if he wants to meet.
No...
need...
to...
I...
You...
Hi, Gaogui.
I heard you wanted to meet me.
You come quite fast.
It's okay. Then...
You guys continue.
I'll leave you alone.
It's okay. You can stay.
Didn't you say we were going to meet?
I saw nothing.
Don't go. Stay here.
Bye-bye.
I heard that today's spread is good.
You are saying this,
then it looks like it's really good.
Thank you for your clever move today.
Are we going
to be so polite now?
Thank you for the last few days.
Good night.
[Three days later]
The Snacks Expo is over.
We're packing up now.
About tomorrow or the day after tomorrow.
Okay.
Got it.
Okay, bye.
Zhen Gaogui.
Come here.
Coming.
Come here. Here.
Slowly.
Be careful. Slowly.
Be careful.
This way.
This way. This way.
Here, here, here.
Watch your steps.
Watch out! Move!
Someone was hit!
[Because it's delicious
That's why it's meton]