[English subtitles are available]
Sir, did you ask for a designated driver?
Yes, I did.
The key is in my pocket. Take it out, please.
Okay, here.
Mister, please wait a moment.
We were drinking, weren't we?
Yes.
We were drinking earlier.
I drank too much.
I don't dare to drink too much usually.
I hate to trouble others.
You're fine. You're not drunk.
How did I get home?
When did I get home?
Yeah, I don't understand, either.
How did we get home in the blink of an eye?
It's amazing.
Let's go. Here.
Let go of me.
I can walk by myself.
♫I like your simple smile♫
Myself…
♫It's as bright as the sunshine after the rain♫
♫I want to ride the wind and waves with you♫
We need to keep it down
♫To see the twilight and auroras♫
My mom must've gone to bed.
♫My heart is pounding♫
Let me take you to your room.
♫The stars are twinkling♫
♫You represent the beauty of the mortal world♫
Zhen Gaogui.
♫I like your hugs♫
♫And your gentle gazes♫
♫I want to lean on your shoulder♫
♫In the spring breeze♫
♫Love is never late♫
♫The smell of popcorn is in the air♫
♫The melody of my heart♫
♫Only plays for you♫
Mr. Zhong, I'll sleep here.
♫Bird songs and the ocean♫
You can go home now. Go.
♫Are only surrounded by each other♫
I'll leave after you fall asleep
♫We're just right for each other♫
That's totally unnecessary.
♫Meeting you is the most wonderful thing in my life♫
♫Ripples and waves♫
♫I block them on for you♫
♫My world is small♫
♫I only let you in♫
♫We're just right for each other♫
♫You're in every part of my story♫
Why are you still here?
I’m leaving.
[Amazing Girls]
[Episode 16]
Gaogui, this is the copy you need.
Thank you.
I heard that your project was carried out early.
Yes.
There are some issues.
That's why we start it beforehand.
Didn't our boss ask Ju Ran to help you?
If you need extra help,
you can just ask Ju Ran.
She has her own project to do.
Besides, I'm still a newbie.
I can't always bother her.
If I know how to do the work,
then I'm going to do it myself.
It doesn't matter if you're new here,
Our boss and the owner
of the company will think you have a good future,
as long as you can make money.
Also, Ju Ran…
She always asked you to do things for her, didn't she?
Well, don't put it like that.
If she didn't
ask me to do things for her often,
I wouldn't grow so much.
Now that I think about it,
I feel grateful to her.
I'll get back to work then.
Just let me know if you need anything.
I would be glad to help. We're friends.
Okay.
The matter of distribution channels are still in discussion.
It may take some time.
And Vice President Sun's issue…
About his issue…
We'll take a pause now.
If we deal with him now,
it will affect the company too much.
And it won't benefit the future tasks.
But isn't this like having a ticking time bomb?
If you get rid of one issue,
there will be a new problem.
We've known how he operates very well.
Just keep an eye on him.
Besides,
he's not going to do anything now.
If something happens again,
it won't be as simple as resigning for him.
He might go to jail for business crime.
Okay, that's it for today.
I have a personal meeting later.
You had a lot of personal meetings before.
Today's event is very important.
You have a date with Zhen Gaogui?
Was it so obvious?
It's just a regular date.
Miss. Zhen.
It's been a while, Sir.
Yes.
Oh, and I'm afraid
I forgot to ask for your contact number last time.
To be honest,
you play better than our
professional pianist.
Really?
Yes.
The next day, some guests asked me
why I changed the piano player.
They wanted to hear you play again.
I'm glad to hear that.
You can come and play
in the future in you would like.
We're happy to have you anytime.
This is my name card.
You can contact me in advance.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I won't keep you any longer.
Please.
Mr. Zhong,
you are in a good mood.
We're not on clock.
You don't have to call me Mr. Zhong.
Why?
Do you shapeshift into something after work?
When we're not working,
you can just call me by my name.
I don’t really want to be the president,
or the general manager.
Okay.
Thank you, Zhong Yiming,
for taking me home the other day
when I was drunk.
Do you remember anything?
When I woke up that morning,
I found myself lying on the couch.
The last thing I remember
is you drinking by my side.
My mom told me you sent me home.
But you told me
you had never got drunk.
I was with you,
so I had nothing to worry about.
Really?
What's so special about me?
You're special.
Because
you're Zhong Yiming.
In my mind,
you are very responsible.
When I didn't believe
I could do all those things,
you believed in me.
So I will believe in you too.
Because trust
should be mutual.
Your compliments
made me feel like I'm really amazing.
Why did you ask me
to eat with you today?
Nothing in particular.
I did some things
that upset you before.
I was worried you wouldn't forgive me.
Do you have something to tell me?
I do have something to tell you.
Actually, I need to ask you something.
But I didn't get the chance before.
And I'm not sure if I'm overthinking it.
No, you're not.
I haven't said it yet. How did you know?
Excuse me.
This is our freshly arrived salmon.
I picked the best part for you.
Please try it.
Thanks. Thank you.
Enjoy.
Shall we eat first?
The fish looks very fresh.
Actually, you did so many awesome things
not because I trusted you.
I always think you're an amazing person.
You say things that I dare not to say,
and do things I dare not to do.
You are the same, aren't you?
I can do those things
only because I've met you.
I never wanted you to know the old me.
The old me was hateful
and self-centered.
I was selfish
and a trouble-maker.
I was bad for others and for myself.
What did you do exactly?
I made a huge mistake.
It was so huge that others wouldn't forgive me,
and neither would I.
Zhong Yiming,
though you wouldn't tell me
what happened,
but I don't think it matters.
It was
in the past.
It's like those junk programs
that you can't delete in your computer.
They will only keep the bad memories.
The moment I met you
was the beginning of many troubles in my life,
but it was also the beginning of many wonderful things.
I lived a dreamy, carefree life,
but now I'm down to earth
and it's more reassuring.
Zhen Gaogui,
I'm glad you're here.
Thank you.
I should thank you.
Thank you for going through
a very difficult time with me,
and encouraging me to keep going.
Zhen Gaogui, I actually…
Hold on.
Hello?
Yes, I am.
Okay, I'll be there soon.
What happened?
My mom is in the hospital.
Let's go. I'll drive you.
[Taning Second People's Hospital]
Excuse me. Could you tell me
which room is Ms. Qin Fenfang in?
Here. In this room.
Thank you. Thanks.
Mom.
Who did this to you?
What happened to you, mom?
Talk to me.
You can't even talk, mom.
What should I do?
Gaogui,
I'm here.
Mom.
Careful.
what happened?
I'm not sure.
Well…
I was teaching a class,
and suddenly I couldn't move my lower back.
The doctor said
it was lumbar strain,
and ordered me to rest for a week.
Other than that, I'm fine.
Mrs. Zhen, call me anytime
if you need anything.
Okay.
Zhong,
were you two
on a date today?
Mom.
Why is that your focus
at this moment?
I can't believe you.
You didn't go home after work,
but went to teach yoga?
A student asked me to give him
an one-on-one aerial yoga class.
This kind of private lesson
charges several hundred yuan per hour.
Why didn't I make the money?
Look at you now.
You didn't earn the money,
but you damaged your health.
Don't do that again, okay?
Be careful.
Okay.
I was scared to death today.
I thought I would never come back
when I was in the ambulance, going to the hospital.
Mom, don't say that.
It's not a big deal, right?
Let me get you some water.
You'll be fine, Mrs. Zhen.
Zhong,
open the drawer of that cabinet for me.
My accident insurance is in there.
There… it's there.
The first or the second drawer?
The first one.
Okay.
I can apply for reimbursement for all the expenses today.
[Personal accident insurance contract]
Zhong.
Zhong Yiming,
Come down.
Are you out of your mind?
Come down now.
I won't.
If you force me to go to that school,
I'll jump.
This is a good place.
This area has great potential.
This area
is not far
from downtown.
It's not far.
I think it looks very promising.
Let's go look at somewhere else.
What's going on over there? Let's go find out.
Mr. Zhen.
I'm not coming down.
Zhong Yiming, come down now!
I'm warning you.
Don't you have any shame?
Look at your brother. And look at you.
Don't irritate him.
I finally understand.
I'm a loser.
I'm useless.
Have a good life with my brother.
I won't trouble you anymore.
Help!
Help! Help!
Mr. Zhen.
What happened?
I saw it just now.
That boy had a fight with his parents,
got too upset and jumped into the river.
And the man in the suit
jumped into the water to save him.
He saved the child,
but unfortunately, he drowned.
What a tragedy.
That man died because of me.
That's too sad.
Did someone in your family pass away too?
It's okay.
You probably don't know whose funeral you're attending.
I went to relatives' funerals a few times before.
I didn't even know them.
But
this time, my dad passed away.
I am very sad.
I remember he was very nervous
every time I was crossing the street.
He was afraid that I would be in danger.
You were in danger earlier.
I don't think I should be alive.
Nonsense.
Did you watch too many martial arts movies?
You can't disobey traffic rules like that.
Everyone will go to that place in the end.
So when we are alive,
we should live a good life.
What do you want to do when you grow up?
I don't know.
But
I want to leave home.
The further, the better.
What about you?
I want to travel around the world.
My dad said
the world outside is wonderful.
I can't stay at home forever.
It's a shame
that in future,
I can only travel with my mom.
This is my chat account.
Do you use chat software too?
Yes.
I suddenly realised
I don't even know your name.
Can you tell me?
Just call me Nana.
I want to be mysterious.
I want to go somewhere far away from home.
A place where no one knows me.
What about you?
Me too.
I'm probably going to study abroad.
But I haven't decided where to go yet.
Go to Paris, then.
I heard it's a romantic city.
We might meet in Paris someday.
I've been in France for a month.
I think life here is interesting.
Thanks to your advice.
I really envy you.
I gave you some advice,
but I didn't make it myself.
I hope I won't fail any exam this time.
Yeah-huh!
I've finished all my courses.
I'm going back home early
and giving my mom a surprise.
I let my mom go to bed.
She cannot join in
those vigorous activities at her age.
Zhong Yiming,
what's the matter? I'm talking to you.
I like him.
Who do you like?
You...
I like you too.
Why are you staring at me?
Is there something on my face?
No.
You...
♫If one day♫
Well, I'm leaving.
♫Life is off track♫
You're just going to leave like that?
♫We'll still be laughing and playing the freest melody♫
You should rest early.
♫We won't fall♫
♫We'll fly higher in the sky♫
♫Gently and firmly♫
♫We're getting closer♫
♫Farewell to the past, turn around and go♫
♫To the next destination♫
♫The starlight along the way falls in our palms♫
♫Look at the sea of stars♫
♫They snuggle up at night♫
[I tickled Zhen Gaogui]
♫I start looking forward♫
♫To growing up and being loved♫
[Zhong Yiming tickled me]
[I tickled Zhong Yiming]
♫Time flies♫
♫Someone's there to share my happiness and sorrow♫
You're still up?
♫That's you♫
♫You're an expected surprise♫
Yes.
You can't sleep either?
I had a good time having dinner with you today.
You just want to tell me this?
Yeah. Good night.
Thank you for sending my mom home.
Good night.
Mr. Zhong.
You're here so early.
I thought it's inconvenient for your mom to move around.
And you stayed up late last night.
So I brought you some breakfast.
Thank you.
My mom is still resting.
Okay, I'll put it here.
Gaogui.
Is Zhong here?
He's here to bring us breakfast.
I'll bring it to you later.
[Professional maintenance]
Mr. Zhong.
You're still here.
I can take care of her by myself.
I'm going to work now.
Why don't you go back first?
It must be inconvenient for your mom to be alone.
I'll stay and accompany her.
You can go ahead. It's okay.
Thank you.
I'm leaving.
Ju Ran.
Here's the white peach flavored oolong you like.
I also want that flavor.
There's none.
I have this.
It's the same. Make it yourself.
I have nothing to say.
You can drink it if you like. Here.
Thank you.
Ju Ran, you can drink mine.
I haven't drunk it.
You two can make tea yourself.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Didn't Ju Ran give you a hard time before?
You two are working well
together now.
We work and make money together.
There's no need to make things difficult for each other.
The less trouble, the better.
If I were as open-minded as you,
I wouldn't have had a hard time with
our team leader for so many years.
But our missions are different.
You're responsible for making money,
I'm responsible for straightening up the workplace.
Harmony brings wealth.
If it weren't for Ju Ran helping me this time,
I really don't know what to do.
Now my mom is sick.
I need to take a leave and go home to take care of her.
Come in.
It's you.
Are you busy with Meton's project these days?
There's feedback from the clients.
We need to go over some details.
Boss, I'm sorry.
I might need to take a leave.
A leave?
Why is it?
My mom sprained her waist.
I have to take care of her.
Then you
should go back now.
You don't have to
come here to ask for leave for things like this.
Just send me a message.
I just want to come to the company
and see if there's any work,
so I can finish it at home.
Parents are more important than anything else.
Okay.
I'll apply for leave in the company system.
Don't apply for it.
You don't have much salary.
It will be all deducted.
You've been working overtime a lot.
You can have a compensatory leave.
Go home and take care of everything,
then come back to work.
Thank you, boss.
And the work you just mentioned
about Meton...
There are so many people in the company.
Go back and take care of your things at home.
Thank you, boss.
Call me if you
need anything.
Use it like this.
Unbelievable.
Yes.
Oh, Mrs. Zhen.
Please try this.
This is the taste.
Before I got married to your uncle,
we used to go to the cinema to date.
The popcorn he bought for me
tasted exactly the same as this.
Really?
Why are you back so early?
I took a leave.
Zhang Feiyang gave you a leave?
He said I worked overtime a lot before.
So he gave me a compensatory leave.
You leader is quite nice.
Anyway, for my work,
I can communicate with you face to face.
But you,
you just decided to work with the Dooro Bear.
Shouldn't you be busy?
No, I'm not busy at all.
Not at all.
Really?
There are more than 90 emails that need your reply.
Replying them one by one, I'll finish it anyway.
Are you going to keep doing this?
Go to her house during the day
and come to the office at night.
I can't leave the two of them
alone at home, right?
You've been working hard lately.
If this is done, I'll give you a promotion and a raise.
[Unread, Administrative Department]
[Unread, R&D Department]
Thank you.
Mr. Zhong, your takeout is here.
Okay, thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
Here.
I haven't worked overtime for a long time.
That's true.
This is a special situation.
You don't have to wait for me tomorrow.
I'll handle these unfinished documents.
No need.
I'm not that old
to sleep on time every day.
Why do I feel
you've changed?
When you first came to the company,
I really
hated you.
I wished you could make a mistake
and then leave.
But after these days,
I realized that maybe only you can save Meton.
I hope I was right about you.
I don't want to take such a big responsibility.
I just thought there was an opportunity
and wanted to give it a try.
You weren't like this before.
Do you remember
that one year when your brother organized
an executive meeting in the suburbs?
You were three hours late.
It seemed like you went to participate in some
motorcycle off-road race.
That meeting had nothing to do with me, okay?
I told him not to wait for me.
He insisted on it.
What could I do?
But all the executives were there,
only you were late.
You embarrassed him a lot.
I thought you were so unreliable at that time.
But now, I admit
I misjudged you.
Thank you for seeing through me.
I haven't even seen through myself.
I'm telling the truth.
Okay.
By the way,
you should discuss it more with Lin Yue
about the Dooro Bear's project.
Just tell me the progress and the result.
No problem.
Our final confirmed plan is this series
and that series.
So please ask your company's designers
to make some changes.
Is Zhong Yiming busy recently?
Or you just wanted to see me
and discuss it with me alone?
Both.
We've worked together in advance.
Can't you be more gentle to me?
Our company paid for our cooperation.
You...
Today's work is done.
Now it's break time.
Let me take you to a serious place to rest.
This is the serious place you mentioned?
It involves health and science.
Definitely serious.
Dear, you're here.
What project are you going to do today?
Today, we have a store celebration event.
There are promotions for recharging.
It's very cost-effective.
Recharge 1000 and get a 10% discount.
Recharge 2000 and get a 20% discount.
Recharge 3000 and get a 30% discount.
Recharge 4000 and get a 40% discount.
If you recharge 5000...
Alright, alright.
We haven't started yet.
You keep promoting that.
We'll talk after we're done, okay?
Okay.
Come with me.
This way, please.
People in this industry are all like this.
It's not easy for them.
How's it?
Does it hurt a lot?
Ouch! It hurts!
You know what?
Last time when you gave me a shoulder massage,
it was much more painful than this.
I didn't
use such force.
How should I put it?
Little help
brings much return.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, it hurts.
Enjoy it.
If I had known it would be like this,
I wouldn't have come with you.
You sit in the office all day long,
not exercising at all,
you'll definitely have backaches and soreness.
What can I do about it?
See?
You're so tense when it comes to work,
and too busy at work.
It will definitely affect your health.
I have OCD.
I have to do everything perfectly.
Otherwise, I'll feel uncomfortable.
No mistake is allowed
for things within my control.
But when your life is very tense,
it will affect your health.
It doesn't want to make mistakes either.
But life itself is prone to mistakes.
I remember I read a saying online.
It said that when people are in their teens,
they don't know what knowledge is,
but they have to choose to study liberal arts or science.
When people are seventeen or eighteen and know nothing about careers,
they have to choose a major.
When people know nothing about society,
they have to find a job.
When people know nothing about human nature,
they have to get married and have children.
All of it is very prone to mistakes.
About what you said,
I don't think I made the right choices.
In high school, I wanted to be an artist
and draw comics for a lifetime.
But my parents thought there was no future in it,
so they sent me to France
to study classical art.
After graduation, I wanted to start a business in China,
but they wanted me
to find a stable job.
My major didn't match,
so I couldn't find one.
In the end, I chose to start my own business.
You see,
my life has no plan.
So in my opinion,
experience is more important than plans.
Whether it's right or wrong,
it will become
right in the end.
Can you do it?
If not,
I'll go to the supermarket and buy some frozen ones.
Mrs. Li said
the handmade dumpling wrappers are more delicious.
Look, Zhong did a pretty good job.
Pretty good?
His sleeves are in the flour.
I think it's not bad.
Mrs. Zhen,
is the fan heater working well?
It's great.
I'm telling you, if it weren't for that fan heater,
I would have been freezing.
Thanks to Zhong always accompanying me
at home these days.
We're like a family.
What family?
Of course...
I'll go.
Mom.