(Episode 114)
Oh my...
Jung Suk Hee.
How dare you steal Ma Eun Hye's necklace?
You knew I was the Chairman's daughter.
Just because you stole my necklace,
do you think that will hide the fact
that I'm Ma Eun Hye?
No.
As if killing my daughter, Seo Rin,
wasn't enough,
you even hid the fact
that I was Ma Eun Hye.
Are you even human?
- You rummaged through my room?
- It's over for you.
My father is Chairman Ma Dae Chang
of Dream Group.
- And I am his daughter.
- No!
Bring my daughter back to life!
Bring her back!
Please, stop. It wasn't me.
Jung Suk Hee, you're mistaken.
It's not true.
I'll make you pay for what you did to me.
Die.
Do you really think your son can live well
after you killed Seo Rin?
Let go!
Fine. You think I'll go down that easily?
In your dreams!
I'll make you pay for everything
all at once.
Go ahead, keep barking.
But you'll still be the one
losing in the end.
You let Seo Rin die, didn't you?
You should die too!
- Die! Just die!
- Stop!
You're asking me what you can do?
Get out of my sight. Just disappear!
Die!
- Stop... Please help me.
- Die!
Help me.
What are you doing?
Are you falling asleep on the stairs?
What?
Jung Suk Hee.
Where's Jung Suk Hee?
An antihistamine?
That's for allergies.
Where's Jung Suk Hee? Where is she?
- Let go of me!
- Why are you so desperate to find my mom?
Let go of me!
Why did you and your mother come here?
Is it a problem that I'm here?
I'm the Chairman's granddaughter.
Come on, just lock.
Chae Hwa Young.
Now that Seo Rin is gone,
shouldn't you be the one
to leave this house?
Where's your mother?
Jung Suk Hee has her memory back, right?
Where's Jung Suk Hee?
- Why are you so desperate to find my mom?
- Jung Suk Hee!
Suk Hee is pooping.
Mom, why use Chae Hwa Young's bathroom?
Seriously...
You could've just used the one downstairs.
I like the thief's bathroom.
- It smells nice in here.
- For crying out loud. You're ridiculous.
Mom, let's get out of here.
- Thief!
- Shut up! Don't you ever say that again!
(Chang)
This thing gave me a heart attack.
What?
You're saying Chae Hwa Young
had Seo Rin's newborn clothes?
Yes. She kept them in a locked drawer.
And there seemed to be something else
under them,
but I couldn't check
because Chae Hwa Young showed up.
Also, I think Chae Hwa Young
might have some kind of allergy.
I saw a bottle of antihistamines
on her vanity.
Chae Hwa Young has allergies?
That bastard doctor who killed our Seo Rin
filed to close his clinic?
- Yes.
- It's not like the closure is immediate.
There are legal procedures,
so it'll probably take a month or two.
Lawyer Kang Baek Ho is often at the clinic
to gather evidence.
Have you confirmed
where Chae Hwa Young was at that time?
I've confirmed she was in Seoul
at that time.
It doesn't seem like CEO Chae
is connected to Director Ma's death.
For now, they might destroy evidence
and run,
- so keep a close eye on them.
- Yes, sir.
I can't let my dear Seo Rin's death
have been in vain.
Something definitely happened
at that clinic.
Yes, I understand.
Okay.
Who was that on the phone?
Things are getting interesting.
What's going on?
That was my source at the Hills Hotel.
Hills Hotel?
They're Dream Hotel's biggest rival.
I heard they've been having
financial trouble lately.
Hills Hotel,
which is the crown jewel of Hills Group,
will be put up for sale soon.
I knew this would happen to Hills Group.
- Their reckless expansion led to this.
- Hills Hotel...
What if we acquire it?
We could acquire it...
and merge Dream and Hills Hotels.
And then we can launch a new brand
called Dream Hills.
As your very own hotel.
It's a tempting offer,
but money's the issue.
The slush fund? Absolutely not.
The source of those funds
isn't transparent.
If we use this cash recklessly...
and the authorities start tracking it,
how would we even handle that?
You don't run a business
with your own money.
You know that.
Bank loans and...
Investors?
Exactly.
We bring in some solid investors.
That's how we create your very own hotel.
So, Jun Ho made that kind of proposal?
Yes. He says I should launch
a new high-end brand.
He said that it's a way...
to escape Chairman Ma's
old-fashioned management style...
and that it would be our winning move,
using a fresh and innovative approach.
Thriving in a crisis.
He really takes after you.
I'll start looking for investors
right away.
Weren't there a few wealthy investors...
on the guest list for the bonsai show?
- Get me that list.
- Yes.
By the way,
what's your plan for Jung Suk Hee?
Why are you bringing her up
and ruining the mood?
If Chairman Ma finds out
Jung Suk Hee is Ma Eun Hye,
it'll be a disaster, won't it?
Find out how far Secretary Kim has gotten,
and prepare our response accordingly.
Got it?
Understood.
Baek Ho.
Is everything okay? You look so down.
I just came back from the police station.
What about the plastic surgeon?
Did you find anything out?
No. It looks like they're wrapping it up
as malpractice by the surgeon.
Before they close the case,
we have to find the nurse
who was in the operating room.
We have to.
It's my mom.
I'll get going then. See you later.
Hey, Mom.
Son.
I just called because
I wanted to hear your voice.
Come on, Mom.
We saw each other this morning.
Why are you calling already?
I'm okay, Mom.
I know...
you must be feeling so unsettled.
But, Baek Ho,
nothing has changed.
We can just keep on living
the way we always have.
The fact...
that you are my son...
would never change,
even if the world turned upside down.
You know that, right?
Of course I do.
I'm your son.
If you are curious...
about how you came to be with us,
you can ask me anytime.
If you want to know about your roots,
I'll do everything I can to help you.
No. I don't really want to find them.
Because if I do,
it would feel like
I'm really not your son.
And I don't want that.
Baek Ho, just remember one thing.
I'm always on your side,
and you know that, right?
I know.
Can you make me
some spicy stir-fried squid?
Okay, you got it.
I'll make the spicy stir-fried squid
my son loves so much.
Mom.
I love you.
I love you too, son.
Talk to you later.
So it turns out, we're not related at all.
What's your point?
You were still my parents' son,
so I always felt this nagging debt to you,
which bothered me.
But now? It's a huge weight
off my shoulders.
It means no matter what I do to you,
I don't have to feel a shred of guilt.
The feeling's mutual.
I'm warning you one last time.
Don't do anything stupid.
I'm done holding back.
Then let me make one thing crystal clear.
The woman you love, Oh Jang Mi, is dead.
- What?
- And the woman who works here...
is Director Ma Seo Rin.
- And she's going to marry me.
- Kang Jun Ho!
Are you still that delusional?
We're married.
We're already husband and wife!
Haven't you seen our parents?
They're married,
but they live like strangers.
You think your love will last forever?
I’m going to show you firsthand
how even a love you can’t live without...
can fall apart in an instant.
Then here's one last piece of advice,
as your former brother.
What you feel isn't love.
It's obsession and greed.
The moment you risk everything
for your greed,
you'll eventually...
be destroyed by the same greed.
Mark my words.
We'll see about that, Kang Baek Ho.
I don't know who your parents are,
but this game is already over.
Just remember whoever gets her first wins.
Manager Lee.
I have a great idea.
- What is it? Did you find an investor?
- No, that can wait.
First, we need to get that eyesore,
Jung Suk Hee, out of the picture.
What? But how?
If Jung Suk Hee so much as mentions
the necklace,
the four-leaf clover,
or the baby clothes to Chairman Ma,
it's only a matter of time
before we're exposed.
How will you get her out of the picture?
If Chairman Ma ends up in a crisis
because of that dim-witted Jung Suk Hee,
he'll never want to see her again.
What exactly do you have in mind?
Yeom San Wol, I need you to run an errand.
Mom, are you holding up okay?
I'm fine. It's what I do.
Look! The thief is here.
Look at the mother-daughter duo,
working hard to avoid getting kicked out.
If you don't like what you see,
you can leave.
After all, you used Seo Rin as an excuse
to come back to this house.
- You've overstayed your welcome. Get out.
- Shut up.
You should be sucking up to me
if you don't want to get thrown out.
In this house, I'm second in command
after the Chairman. Got it?
Who do you think you are
to be second to Grandfather?
You're not his daughter-in-law anymore,
and you're about
to lose your CEO position.
So brace yourself.
Your days here are numbered.
- Get out. Stop bothering my mother.
- You get out.
I came here to speak to her.
Yeom San Wol bought
this organic pomegranate extract...
for the Chairman.
Oh Jang Mi.
Relax, I'm not going to eat her alive.
Are you just going to stand there
and watch?
Why are you trying to get me
away from my mom?
What are you plotting now?
What are you talking about?
What would I be plotting?
Watch what you say.
Seo Rin.
I mean, Jang Mi...
Gosh, it's so confusing.
Come on out.
The Chairman is asking for you.
Okay, I'm coming.
Jung Suk Hee, listen closely.
You know what? Never mind.
Let me just show you.
(Ma)
Look.
This one is only for the Chairman.
See? It's marked here on the bottle.
- Yes.
- Look.
Pour this much into a shot glass.
Okay?
And then add 150 milliliters of water.
You have to add three times
as much water as concentrate.
Okay, three times.
Three times...
Right, three times.
Right. You're getting it.
And here's an unopened one.
You open it like this,
pour it in the glass,
and add ice water just like before.
Okay. I can do this. I'm doing great.
Yes, like this.
Don't mix up the Chairman's bottle
with the ones for the rest of the family.
I won't get them mixed up.
This one is the Chairman's.
Right. The one with "Ma" on it
is for the Chairman, all right?
Gosh, I wonder if you can even read.
- I can't read.
- That's just great.
Look closely. The Chairman's bottle...
See? This one, with this little coaster,
is the Chairman's. Got it?
Don't get them mixed up.
Make sure you serve it to the Chairman
exactly like this, okay?
Okay. I can do a good job.
I can do this.
All right,
let's see you do a good job, okay?
Now, go mix it well and bring it out.
Why are we having juice?
We're about to eat dinner.
For your health, I bought
some cold-pressed pomegranate juice.
The organic kind, no less.
It was a special import and hard to get,
so I had San Wol rush out to buy it.
Juice?
What is Chae Hwa Young up to now?
Suk Hee, bring them over.
Yes.
Here you go.
Why didn't you bring a glass for yourself,
Suk Hee?
I already had some.
- It's so delicious.
- The color is lovely.
- Isn't this good for women's health, too?
- Right, I've heard...
pomegranate is good for the health
of middle-aged women,
but I wonder if it will do any good
for someone like me.
Of course. It's also called
the blood vessel cleanser.
The antioxidants in it...
are said to naturally
lower blood pressure.
When I saw you collapse last time,
I was so terribly shocked and worried.
- That's why I told her to buy it.
- What’s gotten into you,
caring about me like this?
I just took my blood pressure medication
a little while ago.
In that case, Grandfather,
you should drink this after your meal.
Besides, having something sweet
before a meal isn't good for you.
It's actually better to have it now.
Something sweet will actually
stimulate your appetite.
Besides, pomegranate has no ingredients
that affect blood pressure medicine,
so it's fine to have it
even after taking your medicine.
If you're that doubtful,
you can look it up online.
All right. Then let's give it a try.
I've been craving something tart, anyway.
While we're at it,
let's have a toast, honey.
All right, everyone.
To our health. Cheers!
- Okay.
- Here.
Cheers.
Jung Suk Hee.
Soon, you could be charged
for attempted murder.
(Ma)
This one looks a bit cloudy.
Did you mix
the grapefruit concentrate in properly?
Yes. Even a small amount of grapefruit...
is potent enough to block
the enzymes in blood pressure medication.
This should be more than enough
to induce pharmacological shock.
But the Chairman’s bottle
is already unsealed.
Won't Jung Suk Hee get suspicious?
Jung Suk Hee is a dimwit.
She won't notice.
After he drinks the pomegranate juice
with grapefruit...
that Jung Suk Hee prepares,
and Chairman Ma collapses
from a heart issue,
San Wol and I will go to the kitchen,
pretend we found the grapefruit bottle
to expose her. That's the plan.
Jung Suk Hee cooks for a living,
so she knows a lot about ingredients.
- You just have to emphasize that.
- Right.
The story is that Jung Suk Hee knows
grapefruit is bad for high blood pressure.
So she deliberately mixed this
only into the Chairman's bottle...
to try and kill him.
She planned to get revenge
for what happened with Dong Seok.
But can Jung Suk Hee tell the bottles
apart and serve the right one?
I only put the grapefruit concentrate
in Chairman Ma's bottle.
This bottle here
is just pure pomegranate concentrate.
- But what if...
- I'll make it foolproof for her.
Don't worry.
Besides, I had Yeom San Wol buy
the pomegranate concentrate,
so no one will suspect me.
Here you go.
Okay, thanks.
You can go.
Oh my.
This is refreshing. It's quite good.
I feel healthier already.
I should have this more often.
It's really good.
Suk Hee did a good job.
Chairman Ma should be collapsing
from the shock any second now.
So long. This must be what they call
killing two birds with one stone.
Grandfather, are you feeling okay?
You said you took
your blood pressure medication earlier.
I'm fine.
In fact, I feel sharper than ever.
What?
Why is Chairman Ma reacting like this?
He should be feeling dizzy
or getting a headache by now.
That's strange.
I'm certain I prepared his drink myself.
That dimwit.
I told her exactly which one.
Did she grab the other one?
Wait a minute.
My juice tasted a little bitter.
No way...
Hwa Young, what's wrong with you?
What's the matter?
Oh my gosh, that's right.
Hwa Young has allergies.
You...
Jung Suk Hee.
- What?
- Jung Suk Hee!
Suk Hee did nothing wrong.
The thief, Chae Hwa Young, is dying.
She can't breathe.
Oh my, what's wrong with her?
It's agony, isn't it, Chae Hwa Young?
You're allergic to grapefruit.
You tried to kill the Chairman,
but you fell into your own trap,
Chae Hwa Young.
Oh my gosh!
What is wrong with her?
Oh my gosh, what do we do?
Oh, dear. Hey, get it together!
Oh my goodness!
See? This one, with this little coaster,
is the Chairman's. Got it?
Don't get them mixed up.
Make sure you serve it to the Chairman
exactly like this, okay?
Okay. I can do a good job.
I can do this.
All right,
let's see you do a good job, okay?
Now, go mix it well and bring it out.
Chae Hwa Young.
What is this?
Why did she hide it here and leave?
Wait a minute.
They're both pomegranate extract,
but why did she tell me
to open one for the Chairman...
and serve the other one
to the rest of the family?
Why not just open one bottle for everyone?
Why would she bother separating them?
What is it?
She mixed something
into the Chairman's pomegranate juice.
The taste is subtly different.
Wait a minute.
It's like some other fruit extract
was mixed in.
It's grapefruit. It's grapefruit extract.
Chae Hwa Young, that wicked woman.
They say grapefruit is bad for people
with high blood pressure.
She was going to make the Chairman
drink this extract...
to make him collapse.
And then she was going to frame me for it.
The nerve of her.
Mom.
I heard Chae Hwa Young
is allergic to grapefruit.
Apparently, if she eats it,
she gets hives and her face swells up,
and in severe cases,
she even has difficulty breathing.
That's why she carries an antihistamine
just in case.
I had no idea Chae Hwa Young
had an allergy like that.
Chae Hwa Young.
This is going to be very painful.
Let's see how you like
a taste of your own medicine.
Oh my gosh.
Hello, 911? Someone here...
- My goodness.
- What are we going to do?
There's something suspicious
about that hospital.
How could they start shutting down
right after Seo Rin's accident?
I should've investigated the OR
more thoroughly.
What are you doing, son?
Nothing.
What's that?
Go ahead and open it.
What is this?
Back when I first adopted you,
the person who left you
at the orphanage...
left this along with you.
You're saying I wore this tiny thing
when I arrived at the orphanage?
This is a golden spoon.
It's so shiny and bright.
Do you think this is real gold?
I heard the price of gold
has gone up a lot lately.
I bet this would sell for a lot.
But what's this here?
- It looks like some kind of crest.
- I don't know what that is either.
The person who left you at the orphanage
included it with you.
It probably has something to do
with your family roots.
Judging by this, I must have come
from a super rich family.
But if I was from a rich family,
why was I sent to an orphanage?
Even when I first saw you,
you were just a little baby,
but you had this noble air about you
that just lit up the entire room.
Right? Then and now,
I'm the definition of class.
Baek Ho.
You don't have to force yourself
to look cheerful.
I know how you're feeling.
You must be so confused.
For over 30 years, you believed
we were your birth parents,
so it must feel like your whole world
has been uprooted overnight.
If you're confused and hurting,
it's okay to say so, Baek Ho.
I'm your mother. I'll always understand.
I'm okay.
But thank you for saying that, Mom.
If you're curious,
I can introduce you to the director
of the orphanage we adopted you from.
You don't have to do that.
Like I said, I'm happy
with my life as it is.
Aren't you curious at all?
I'm not some angsty teen.
I'm past all that.
What's the point of digging up the past?
You're the only mom I need.
That's my boy.
You're such a blessing.
There's no one like my son, Baek Ho.
Still, if you ever get curious later on,
you can always come and talk to me, okay?
- I will.
- Okay.
Wait. I feel like I've seen
this crest before.
Where could it have been?
(Ma)
Oh my gosh, what do we do?
Oh my goodness.
Chae Hwa Young.
What in the world...
was she trying to pull?
(The First Man)
Don't tell me you're
with Lawyer Han Young Ja.
If you keep this up, I'll have to
take matters into my own hands.
Stop harassing my secretary.
They're acquiring Hills Hotel?
They'd need hundreds of billions for that.
They're probably looking for investors.
It's a ploy to swallow Dream Hotel whole.
I'll put my resignation on the line
to handle Chairman Ali myself.
The CEO of Dream Hotel is so classless.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)