It's an unknown number.
(Episode 132)
Yes, this is Lawyer Kang Baek Ho.
Yes.
Yes, this is he.
I'm sorry?
Are you Ma Dong Seok, the Chairman's son?
Ma Dong Seok?
- That's my biological father's name.
- Yes.
Yes, I understand.
What's going on?
Was that really my father
you were just talking to?
Yes, Jang Mi.
The person on the phone just now
was your father.
But I thought my father was dead.
I was told he went missing
before Seo Rin and I were even born.
Is my father really alive?
Yes, he is. He just arrived in Korea.
You should be able to see him soon.
Apparently, the Chairman has been in
contact with your father for a long time.
The Chairman told him to contact me,
his lawyer, if anything happened.
That's how he got my number.
He rushed to Korea when he heard
that the Chairman had collapsed.
Excuse me.
Are you waiting for me?
Dong Seok?
Is it really...
you, Dong Seok?
It's been a long time, Suk Hee.
Dong Seok.
Is it you, Dong Seok?
How...
Yes, that's right.
It's your husband,
Ma Dong Seok.
Suk Hee.
Dong Seok.
I'm very late, aren't I?
I'm sorry, Suk Hee.
I'm so sorry.
Is it really...
Is it really you, Dong Seok?
Dong Seok, you're really alive?
Yes, Suk Hee.
We used to...
walk along this path holding hands
all the time, remember?
You haven't forgotten me, have you?
Dong Seok.
This isn't a dream, is it?
It's not a dream.
It's me, Ma Dong Seok,
the one who loves you.
To come back to you,
it took 30 years.
I missed you so much
it felt like my heart was tearing apart.
I thought I would die, Suk Hee.
Dong Seok, thank you...
for being alive.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming back to me.
Thank you so much.
Suk Hee.
Father.
Father, your son, Dong Seok, is here.
I guess I came back too late.
I'm sorry, Father.
Even though we share no blood,
you raised me like your own son.
But...
I never got to repay your kindness.
I'm sorry, Father.
Dong Seok,
don't be so heartbroken.
To your father,
who thought his own daughter was dead,
you must have been a great comfort.
And now,
his condition is slowly improving.
I'm relieved to hear he's getting better.
It's such a relief.
Dong Seok.
This is our daughter, Jang Mi.
So you're...
You're Jang Mi.
Yes.
Hello.
I was...
way too late, right?
No, not at all.
I'm just so overwhelmed and grateful
that you're alive.
To only be seeing you
now that you're a grown woman.
I'm sorry, Jang Mi.
Thank you...
for growing up so well.
I'm so sorry.
I couldn't even protect you all,
and we're only meeting
now that you're all grown up.
I'm sorry, Jang Mi.
No, it's okay.
Just being able to meet you like this...
feels like a dream.
Dong Seok.
Right.
We can catch up on everything later.
Lawyer Kang Baek Ho.
My father has told me a lot about you.
It's a true pleasure
to be able to meet you like this.
He's my husband.
I see. You're my son-in-law. Thank you.
Thank you for staying by Jang Mi's side...
while I was gone.
Of course.
I'm so grateful...
that you've returned
to us alive, Father-in-law.
(Dream Hotel, June Cash Flow Statement)
Manager Lee.
What are these outstanding payments?
Why are they all concentrated
in this month?
Weren't the Dream Resort's short-term
loan payments due next month?
Well...
After Chairman Ma collapsed,
our primary bank notified us
that they won't approve an extension.
They said it was for risk management,
but in reality,
it seems like they're planning
to cut off our line of credit.
Those bastards.
We're out of cash right now.
We're short a total
of four million dollars...
for this month's payroll
and vendor payments.
All this commotion
over mere four million dollars?
Selling a few of the collector's stones
in my safe...
would have easily gotten me ten million.
But because of Oh Jang Mi
and Kang Baek Ho,
it all vanished into thin air.
I can't believe them.
I'm so furious I can't think straight.
Get me four million dollars
in cash right now,
I don't care from where.
From loan sharks or third-tier lenders,
I don't care.
Loan sharks are too risky.
Then what do you want me to do?
What if our cash flow stops
when we have no way out?
I haven't even been able to start selling
off the prime assets.
What do we do now?
I'm looking for overseas investors now,
but it will take time.
We have to keep the hotel
running smoothly until then...
if we want to sell it for what it's worth.
Do we have to declare bankruptcy
because of four million dollars?
Oh my gosh.
Come on, Mom.
You've just had a difficult reunion
with your husband.
You're just serving him stew?
You should have made something special.
This is what I used to make
for Dong Seok all the time.
This smells incredible.
It's the kimchi stew I've missed so much.
You know, Suk Hee was the first person
to ever make me kimchi stew.
Really?
You really were born with a silver spoon.
Come on, let's eat.
By any chance,
I'm not making anyone uncomfortable, am I?
Not at all.
We're the ones who are grateful
that you're here.
- We're truly happy you're here.
- Thank you.
If you're Jang Mi's father,
that makes you our father too, right?
Oh Bok Gil was a great benefactor to me.
So I'll think of Tae Pyung and Tae Sook...
as my own son and daughter,
so please feel comfortable around me.
Grandfather, what about Bo Ra?
Will you love me too?
You just called me Grandfather?
Of course. I hope we get along, Bo Ra.
Since the family is all together,
let's make a toast,
even if it's with water.
Hey, Kang Baek Ho.
You're not part of this family yet.
You're not officially family
until the marriage is registered, are you?
- Come on.
- Hey!
You know Baek Ho and I got married
even though it was just the two of us.
Right, honey?
Of course, my dear wife.
This really makes me feel like
I'm back in Korea.
It really feels like I've come home.
Everyone...
- Thank you.
- We're so glad you've come back safe.
- All right. To our family's happiness...
- Cheers.
- Oh my.
Where did you learn that?
- How did it go?
- The situation is serious.
The hotel's accounts...
are completely wiped out.
The employees are threatening
to go on strike...
starting tomorrow morning
over unpaid wages.
I know!
If the employees strike
before the shareholders' meeting,
the board will have my head.
I could even be forced out of my position
as interim Chairman.
The funds are gone. What do we do now?
And you don't have the personal funds
to cover this, not even a slush fund.
There has to be a way. I'm Chae Hwa Young.
Do you have any idea how I clawed my way
into this position?
There's no way I'm stepping down.
So what happened all this time?
For so many years, I thought
you were dead, Dong Seok.
It was when I was on
a business trip to Monaco.
I was on a yacht at night...
when someone hit me hard from behind
and pushed me overboard.
- Oh my.
- I fell into the sea and passed out.
When I woke up to the bright sunlight,
I was on an unfamiliar yacht.
- So someone saved you, Dad?
- Yes.
Luckily, he was a foreign investor.
He was suffering from severe depression...
and was about to end his life
in the middle of the ocean.
And he found me flailing in the water
and pulled me up.
After he saved me,
he laughed and said
he couldn't kill himself just to save me.
The problem was,
probably because of my head injury,
I couldn't even remember my own name.
So all those years, without any memory,
you were struggling in a foreign country?
By the time I remembered my name
was Ma Dong Seok and came back to Korea,
you were with that man, Oh Bok Gil,
and had a new family.
And next to my father was that woman,
Chae Hwa Young,
acting like the lady of the house.
So you just left?
I felt there was no place for me.
I was the Chairman's adopted son.
I had no desire to live
under the same roof as Chae Hwa Young.
Later, the businessman
who saved me passed away.
He left me all his wealth
and a huge investment firm,
so I just focused on work.
As time went by,
I became curious about
who had hit me from behind...
and pushed me into the sea,
so that's when I started to investigate.
But surprisingly, it was Chae Hwa Young.
What? Chae Hwa Young?
That witch went that far?
Chae Hwa Young was after Dream,
so she couldn't have me coming back.
That's why she deliberately sent someone
all the way there to try and kill me.
How could she be so cruel?
So you're saying Chae Hwa Young
went after you, too?
I called my father right away and warned
him to be careful of Chae Hwa Young.
So that's when you started
talking to Grandfather again.
That's right.
My father underestimated Chae Hwa Young.
He said he was going to take all
of her shares and kick her out penniless.
But she got to him
before he had the chance.
From now on, no matter what happens,
I will protect my family.
She took down my father
and killed Seo Rin.
She made my family shed tears of blood.
I will drag her to the depths of despair.
Branch Manager.
What do you mean the extension was denied?
After all the years Dream has done
business with you,
how can you suddenly demand
repayment in full?
I'm sorry, ma'am. The head office's
credit review department...
has issued a clear directive.
An extension is absolutely not possible.
Just a little longer.
Okay, just one month.
No, just give me two weeks.
Once this shareholders' meeting is over...
Hello? Sir? Hello?
(CEO Chae Hwa Young)
Forget our primary bank.
Contact every single tier-one
and tier-two financial institution.
Hit up every single one of them.
You have to bring in cash, no matter what.
Office Manager? It's me.
Really?
Lee Kang Hyuk is at a bar
by himself right now?
Okay, got it.
I see.
But I'm at the place
we were supposed to meet.
That's a shame.
Well, let's meet up next time then.
Okay.
Hey, Young Ja.
No, Lawyer Han.
Oh my gosh, Kang Hyuk.
Kang Hyuk, why are you here
all by yourself?
You've been drinking all alone?
Did something happen?
No.
Anyway, what brings you here?
Thanks.
I was supposed to grab a drink
with a client.
But something came up
and they had to cancel.
Pour me one, too.
Sure.
- Martin Jang?
- Yes. My name is Martin Jang.
So you're living under the name
Martin Jang now, Dad?
That's right.
Your grandfather and I mutually agreed
to file for disownment a while ago...
because I had to live as Martin.
In order to kick out Chae Hwa Young,
your grandfather had to disown me.
Then does that mean you and Mom...
- are officially strangers now?
- We may be separated on paper,
but he'll always be my father.
Thanks to him,
I learned how to run a business
as the successor to Dream,
and based on that,
I was able to make all this money.
Try this.
I made your favorite sweet rice drink.
Jang Mi loves it too.
I guess it runs in the family.
So you like sweet rice drink too.
I used to dream of sitting around
with our kids in a house like this...
eating a meal together.
That's right. I didn't know
how big our family would get,
but I wanted that simple life
of eating and talking together.
You remember that?
We can live like that, Suk Hee.
Let's live like that from now on.
I'll get us a better house.
Jang Mi,
my mom is putting her plan into action,
so come to our house now.
I never thought you'd move...
into the same house as Chae Hwa Young.
I thought you...
at least had some common sense.
How could you take advantage
of the Chairman's collapse?
As you may have heard,
I'm Jun Ho's Dad.
So...
that's why you can't leave
Chae Hwa Young's side.
For once in my life...
Just once...
I wanted to live with my son
and the woman who gave birth to him...
happily under one roof.
And Jun Ho?
Does he accept you as his father?
To my Jun Ho...
His mother is...
Yes.
His mother is a criminal...
and his father is the shadow
that helps her.
Hwa Young and I
are one and the same, really.
Oh my goodness.
- Oh my...
- I'm sorry, it's just...
I think I'm a bit drunk.
Your pants are wet.
Why don't you go to the restroom
and dry them off?
Okay.
(Installing
Smart Real-Time Location Tracker)
(Manager Lee Kang Hyuk)
- I'm back...
- I'm sorry, Kang Hyuk.
No, it's okay.
I think I got a bit worked up
because I'm drunk.
I should get going.
(Lawyer Han)
What is this?
It's a collection of photos of Jun Ho...
from when he was little until now.
It's a cloud link.
The files were too large to send,
so I sent you the link instead.
- Why are you giving this to me?
- I guess...
it’s time I let you take your son back.
When you click the link I sent
and go to the album,
it's like a diary of his life.
All the photos of Jun Ho are in there.
Since you're Jun Ho's biological father,
you should see them.
Young Ja.
Thank you.
This one...
is on me.
(My Jun Ho,
A Folder Shared by Han Young Ja)
(Sanghak Middle School)
Mom, Manager Lee took the bait.
I'm tracking his location
in real time now.
You are? That's a relief.
I'll be home soon.
You did great, Mom.
Baek Ho.
Did your mother really install an app
on Manager Lee's phone?
With his personality,
there's no way he'd just let that slide.
How on earth did she do it?
Well, my mom...
Chae Hwa Young is cornered.
She's so furious,
there's no telling what she'll do.
That's what I'm most worried about.
What if we do this, Baek Ho?
Lee Kang Hyuk is Chae Hwa Young's shadow.
If we just know
where Lee Kang Hyuk is going,
won't we be able to figure out
what Chae Hwa Young is plotting?
That's true,
but Lee Kang Hyuk is so meticulous,
it won't be easy to plant something
on his phone.
We have to exploit his Achilles' heel.
He's Jun Ho's Dad, but he can't
step forward. The sorrow of that.
But deep down,
he believes he is Jun Ho's father.
He must take pride in that.
And he must have a strong desire
to act like a father.
Even for someone like him,
who's unqualified,
if we give him the illusion
that he can play the part of a father,
he'll open the floodgates of misery
with his own hands.
I'm grateful to your mother.
She even told us
about Chae Hwa Young's lackey.
It couldn't have been an easy decision
for her to make right now.
She's very brave.
My mom is pretty cool, right?
Yes.
I can't even begin to imagine
how your mother feels...
letting Jun Ho go like that.
I think my mom has finally
made up her mind.
To let Kang Jun Ho go.
That's why she put a hacking program
in the cloud link...
that had Kang Jun Ho's growth records,
and Lee Kang Hyuk clicked on it
without suspicion...
thinking it was his son's life story.
How many payments
are we going to miss this month?
We can't go bankrupt.
And no one's jumping at a sale.
This is driving me crazy.
- Where are your manners?
- Is now the time to worry about manners?
I just met the head of the linen supplier
in the hotel lobby.
He grabbed me and begged, saying
his company is about to go bankrupt...
because we're so behind on payments.
What is going on
with the hotel's finances?
In business,
cash flow can get tied up temporarily.
- It'll be resolved, so stay out of it.
- Now that Grandfather is bedridden,
are you determined to run the company
into the ground?
Not to mention
your poor management skills.
We'd be lucky
if you weren't embezzling funds.
What? You think you can
just say whatever you want?
I'm the CEO of this company.
Who do you think you are?
As CEO,
you should have crisis management skills.
This whole situation is a crisis
caused by an incompetent CEO.
If you're a CEO, act like one.
You should be working
to get the hotel's finances back on track.
Are you just going to sit back
and do nothing?
Mind your own business, Oh Jang Mi.
You're only here until
the shareholders' meeting anyway.
Just wait until I become chairman.
You'll be the first to go.
Still can't give up on your dream
of being chairman?
If you can't get the company back
to normal by the shareholders' meeting,
you'll be the one who gets fired first.
I'm going to formally propose
your dismissal.
I'll make sure everyone knows that you,
Chae Hwa Young, are poison to this hotel.
Unbelievable.
Fine, go ahead.
You think
you can persuade the shareholders?
How ridiculous. Who does she think she is?
Oh Jang Mi,
none of this would have happened
if you hadn't stolen the bonsai trees.
That wretched woman.
She blocks my path at every single turn.
I'm sorry, but that's not possible.
Dream Hotel's recent revenue
has been cut in half.
On top of that, there's the owner risk
and ugly rumors flying around.
In this situation, there isn't a bank
in all of this country...
- that would approve such a large amount.
- I'm sorry. I don't think we can.
- It's not going to work.
- You don't meet conditions for a loan.
(Daehan Bank, Baekdu Bank, Taeyang Bank)
Mom.
Manager Lee has been going around
to every bank.
It looks like he's trying
to get a loan approved.
The company must be in a really tough spot
right now.
Okay, Mom.
Dad, is the hotel really going
to go bankrupt at this rate?
Don't worry, Jang Mi.
This whole plan is just to get rid of
Chae Hwa Young.
So you're saying this is a trap
to lure in Chae Hwa Young?
That's right.
Right now, Chae Hwa Young can't get money
from anywhere,
but the loan sharks in Myeong-dong.
And if she wants to sell off the hotel's
prime assets and skip the country,
the company
needs to be operating normally.
So she'll do whatever it takes
to avoid bankruptcy.
So, you plan to use loan sharks
to seize Chae Hwa Young's collateral...
and step in when she tries
to sell off the prime assets?
Exactly. I have to let her run herself
into a corner.
That's the only way
she'll take the hand I offer.
My goal is to make Chae Hwa Young
give up all her shares...
and force her to flee the country.
Of course, I'll catch her
and throw her in prison before that.
- Turn on the TV, now. Hurry.
- Tae Pyung, what's going on?
This afternoon, off the coast of Incheon,
the badly decomposed body of a man
was discovered.
The body was heavily damaged
from being underwater for a long time,
but fortunately, his identity
was confirmed through his dental records.
He has been identified
as an auto shop employee...
who went missing.
- His name is Kim Bum Seok.
- What's the matter? Do you know him?
- An autopsy will be ordered...
- That's Kim Bum Seok from the auto shop.
He was on the dashcam footage
when my father was murdered.
He was the one who tried to extort money
from Chae Hwa Young.
Who are you?
I'm the person you need.
- Did you follow me? You got a death wish?
- Calm down. Just listen to me.
I'm not with Chae Hwa Young.
Give me the original.
You've got to be kidding me.
Lee Kang Hyuk was after him,
and in the end...
Anyway, Chae Hwa Young
will be locked up for good for this.
Baek Ho.
Ssangkal's girlfriend.
She's in danger too.
You're right.
Getting the evidence is important,
but we have to prevent...
any more innocent people
from getting hurt.
Let's move now.
From an accidental death
to the possibility of foul play,
the police are investigating
all possibilities.
How could you be so sloppy?
I told you to weigh him down with cement
so the body wouldn't surface.
I apologize.
But I already got rid of
all the direct evidence back then,
- so you don't need to worry.
- Shut up.
Now that he's been identified,
it's only a matter of time...
before the noose tightens around my neck.
I have to stop the cops
from snooping around,
but what do I do? I have no money.
We can get the money.
I just got a discreet call
from the loan sharks in Myeong-dong.
His name is Martin Jang.
He's the head
of a major private equity fund...
that operates in Europe and Asia.
I heard he's been watching Dream Hotel.
Martin Jang?
I've heard that name.
They say his financial power
is beyond imagination.
We can sell him the prime operating rights
and shares of Dream Hotel for dirt cheap,
and in return, we take a kickback.
Let's do that.
There's no way we'd get caught
for a kickback on a dirt-cheap sale.
Shall I arrange a top-secret meeting?
Luck is on my side.
Martin Jang.
My savior has arrived.
(The First Man)
Did you kill Kim Bum Seok?
What does a human life even mean to you?
You wouldn't even blink an eye if I died.
You had me completely fooled.
You were the one who went through my car
to steal that receipt...
and planted a tracker on my phone, right?
I have proof that Chae Hwa Young
murdered Oh Bok Gil.
Jang Mi, it's Shin Ae Ran.
Please, help me quickly.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)