She took the bait. Let's move.
She took the bait?
Yes.
Noon, during lunch, at the spot.
You know the one, right?
"Noon, during lunch, at that spot?"
What are they up to? A secret rendezvous?
If they're meeting secretly
during their lunch break,
they must be dating.
This is just too good.
- Are you two dating?
- Goodness!
I'm the one pestering Baek Ho.
You got a problem with that?
Shit!
Wash these.
That's what you get for scaring me.
Goodness!
Mom, if you need more veggies,
get some more from the self-serve bar.
But why has Tae Pyung been so busy lately?
It's been a while
since he's even eaten at our place.
Tae Pyung is busy. He's going to Thailand.
Thailand? Mom, did you just say Thailand?
Uncle said he was going to Thailand.
Just because he made a little money,
he's going to blow it all?
Does he think all the profits are his
because the restaurant's doing well?
San Wol, have you been waiting long?
- James Park will be here any minute.
- Will he?
He's Korean-American,
so his Korean is poor.
Please bear with him.
- I see.
- So, about the stocks?
Of course. I have them right here.
I just need to sign them over, right?
Exactly.
You brought a big bag for the cash, right?
Please, why would I need a bag?
He can just wire the money to my account,
and I can invest it directly
into that AI crypto.
Right. As you'll see
when you meet him, San Wol,
he wasn't always this rich.
But he bought this crypto,
and suddenly,
he could afford a building in Gangnam.
Oh my gosh.
I'm so jealous.
I think that's him now.
- Hi, Tae Pyung.
- James Park!
- What's up?
- What's up, man?
I'm sorry.
- Nice to meet you.
- Right...
Hello.
I'm...
James Park.
Yes, I'm Yeom San Wol.
This is who I am.
Baek Ho, you set up the virtual account,
right?
I'm sending you the funds now,
so use them to buy Yeom San Wol's shares.
Okay?
Okay. That's okay, yes.
You're so pretty.
Are you single?
What was it again?
- Not married...
- Miss?
- Oh, yes. Miss?
- Oh my, "miss"?
She's not a "miss."
Anyway, this is San Wol,
the woman I told you about.
And you, James Park,
are very handsome.
- A handsome guy!
- Thank you.
James, your business card is pretty slick.
It’s not exactly my perfect dream setup,
but I’ve got two handsome guys
in front of me.
I should take a picture to remember this.
- What?
- No, I mean,
I'm just so happy right now...
that I want to burn it into my memory.
But you look really familiar.
Yes! That's right, baby.
I have a memorable face.
I get that a lot.
A Korean actor? Like Won Bin?
Like Jung Woo Sung?
Like Go Soo? That's it.
San Wol, are you eyeing another guy
when I'm right here?
No, it's not like that.
Look at Tae Pyung getting all jealous.
Let's get down to business.
We don't have a lot of time.
Right. Of course.
Okay.
I am a CEO.
Coin investment company.
So, Dream stock,
balance trading...
The balance, right?
- OTC trading.
- Anyway,
I'm here because you said you'd sell.
Yes. Okay.
Ten times.
Ten.
- Is that right?
- You don't trust me?
I'm really offended. I'm going home.
I'm a very busy man. You know that!
Of course I know. Calm down.
Don't...
You can't just leave.
You can sign here.
Sign here now.
If you don't, I'm going home.
Sign...
(Stock Transfer Agreement)
- The stamp.
- The stamp? Both of them?
Both...
(Yeom San Wol)
Baek Ho. Tae Pyung.
Now, just take Yeom San Wol
to a nearby brokerage firm,
and it's over once we get that
one percent of Dream stock.
We're almost there.
What? Were you hiding here?
Are you here alone, Director Ma?
It sounded like you were talking
to someone.
Are you that obsessed with me?
Do you just follow me around all day?
Following you? As if.
Why are you all up in my face?
Ma Seo Rin.
Since when do you wear glasses?
Shit! My eyes felt a bit dry,
so I put them on.
Do I have to report
every little thing I do to you?
By the way, weren't you supposed
to meet Baek Ho at noon?
What, are you mocking me?
As if Jun Ho rejecting me wasn't enough,
Baek Ho blew me off too. I'm a wreck.
Being pissed off is making me hungry.
Go out and get me some
Dubai chewy cookies.
Why me?
Because you're the one who made me mad.
Our lunch break is almost over.
Hurry up and go get it.
What if they sell out?
(Haneum Stock)
Ms. Yeom.
I did the wire transfer.
- Did you check?
- Oh my.
(Transaction History:
James Park, 17.19 million dollars)
It's here. The money's here.
The deposit's been confirmed.
And I got the Dream Hotel stock.
One percent, thank you.
I should be thanking you.
Tae Pyung.
Now for the most important part.
Of course. We should both be thankful.
Should we just forget
about the crypto investment?
What are you talking about?
After all we went through
to get this money?
You were going to let me experience
the joy of a tenfold return,
and you made time for this.
How can you suggest we quit?
Yes! Money is like a snowball.
You know what I mean, right?
- A snowball.
- Yes, right.
You roll it, and it gets bigger.
- I see.
- It starts off small,
and then it gets bigger and bigger.
Wait.
I need to invest right away
to make ten times my money, right?
- You want to do it right now?
- Yes.
(Buy Order Submitted,
Buy Order Completed Successfully)
Ms. Yeom, you're amazing.
- Wait, are you putting it all in?
- Yes.
I can't be held responsible for this.
Gosh.
It's done, right?
- What?
- It's done.
The order came in.
Okay?
Yes.
I'll make it worth your while later
for setting this up.
Let's take a trip
to Hong Kong later, okay?
Yes, of course, Hong Kong sounds nice.
Maybe we should go to Hawaii too.
Hey, James.
How about going to Hawaii together?
How about the three of us go together?
Of course. Yes!
Tae Pyung, I'm going to head out.
I'll see you later.
Take care.
Bye.
Yes.
Unbelievable.
So with this, one percent
of Yeom San Wol's shares...
is ours now, right?
Jang Mi, we did it.
Where did you get these?
Gosh.
Let go of me.
Let go! That really hurts!
- It's supposed to hurt. That's the point.
- Exactly.
Inmate 6620, you have a visitor.
You monsters.
Just wait till I get out of here.
I'll hunt every single one of you down
and rip you to shreds.
(Visiting Schedule)
Look at the state of your face.
Why are you just letting them hit you?
Just like you did to me,
you should've slapped them.
If you couldn't overpower them,
you should've at least bitten them.
You have to do whatever it takes
to protect yourself.
You've always been a fighter.
So what's with this pathetic state
you're in now?
Jun Ho.
You abandoned me, just to live like this?
So I could see you in this pathetic state?
Jun Ho, don't go! Jun Ho!
Let me see your face, Jun Ho.
Please? My son, Jun Ho.
When I went so long without seeing you,
I just got by.
But now, not being able to see you
is driving me crazy.
It felt like I was
going through withdrawal.
I missed you that much.
- I mean it, Jun Ho.
- Then why'd you do it? Why?
You're mistaken. I'm not the killer.
I've seen the video evidence.
And what about
the late Oh Bok Gil's cell phone?
I heard you were the one who had it.
Isn't that clear evidence?
It was a setup.
I'm telling you, it wasn't me.
So please...
Listen to me,
and just believe me.
You don't really think your own mother...
could be such a monster, do you, Jun Ho?
I'll be getting out of here soon.
As soon as I'm cleared of these charges,
I can get out.
Is that true?
This whole thing was a setup.
You know if someone wants to frame you,
they can make up anything.
You're old enough to have seen
that much of the world, aren't you?
So don't fall for it.
Just trust me and wait.
Okay, Jun Ho?
Who would dare try to frame you?
You wouldn't understand
even if I told you right now.
In business, you make so many enemies.
Is the food...
edible?
When I get out...
Once I get out of here,
I'd like to have a meal with you.
Would you do that for me, Jun Ho?
What makes you think
I'd want to eat with you?
Jun Ho.
Just focus on getting out of here
in one piece.
I will. I'll get out of here, you hear me?
I swear I will.
You know what?
I think we need to get
CEO Chae out of there.
Yes, Chairman.
Love her or hate her,
she's still the mother of my child,
Seo Rin.
And I can't have my daughter living
as the daughter of a murderer.
And we have to marry her off, you know.
For Director Ma's sake, you're right, sir.
Okay, right now,
send one of those boxes...
to Minister Kim...
and tell him to arrange for
CEO Chae's release.
Tell him if he does this for me,
I'll be sure to return the favor.
How's Mom doing?
Yes. She still asks for you, Jang Mi,
but not as much as she used to.
Here.
Use this for household expenses.
And please tell Mom that
I love her very much.
Hey, this is way too much.
I feel guilty leaving you and our sister
to take care of Mom.
What are you talking about?
We know how hard you have it.
Anyway, call me if anything comes up.
I will.
Bye.
- Did Tae Pyung already leave?
- Goodness."
Yes.
Baek Ho, I heard your accent was spot-on.
Too bad I missed it.
- Really? Was I cool?
- You totally pulled it off.
You seem to have a knack for acting.
I'm sure Baek Ho
and Director Ma are together.
What are you talking about?
Why would those two be together?
I heard it with my own two ears.
She was like,
"Yes. Noon, during lunch, at that spot."
"You know the one, right?"
Just like a couple on a secret date.
Can you believe that?
All right, I'll contact Baek Ho.
You can go back to your desk now.
I'm counting on you.
(General Manager Kang Jun Ho)
Hey, Jun Ho, what's up?
Are you with Director Ma?
No. Why?
- Isn't Seo Rin at her desk?
- What do you mean, "Seo Rin?"
She's going to be your sister-in-law.
- Watch your mouth.
- Hey, what's the matter?
What's all this "sister-in-law" talk?
Don't get ahead of yourself.
Listen.
Why would you go around telling people
you're meeting Director Ma at noon?
The staff could hear you
and get the wrong idea.
Why are you being so reckless?
You're being so sensitive.
Are you...
cheating on Jang Mi behind her back?
I'm asking if you're two-timing her.
Why can't you answer me?
Two-timing?
Jang Mi is the only one for me.
Besides, people can meet for work.
Do I have to report every little thing
I do to you?
That's not what I'm talking about.
I told you to stay away from Director Ma,
didn't I?
Just because you tell me not to,
I'm supposed to say, "Yes, sir"?
I do what I want.
It's not your place to tell me what to do.
We shouldn't discuss this over the phone.
Let's talk later.
Kang Baek Ho.
After all that talk about
how much you like that Oh Jang Mi woman,
now you're trying to have your cake
and eat it too?
Baek Ho.
There's no point in provoking
General Manager Kang.
So you want me not to see you
just because he said to?
Is that what you want?
No, that's not what I mean.
But Jun Ho's only acting that way
because he doesn't know I'm Oh Jang Mi.
Still.
I can't say one thing and do another.
Anyway,
I appreciate you standing up for me.
Anyway, I have to come clean
about being Oh Jang Mi.
Deceiving everyone like this
has me on pins and needles.
Right. Now that we've had
Chae Hwa Young arrested,
and we've really stuck it to
Yeom San Wol...
Right.
(Commissary deposit information)
Gosh.
Hey.
Have you ever done laundry in your life?
Why would you hang it up
all wrinkled like that?
As if she's ever done laundry
with her own two hands.
Hey, you witch.
- Can't you do anything right?
- Seriously.
She only learns her lesson
after a good beating.
- We have to teach her another lesson.
- Yes.
Wait, stop!
Wait, just hear me out.
Once I get out of here,
I'll give all of you jobs at my hotel.
I guarantee you'll all have jobs.
- Let's make a deal.
- Listen to her.
You're a murderer.
When do you think you'd get out
and give us jobs at your hotel?
When we're old and gray?
Who does she think she is?
- Get the blanket.
- Okay.
Go get it now.
- She'll never learn.
- Don't! Stop it!
Whatever. Stomp her.
Seriously. Learn your lesson!
She needs a beating every day
just to get it through her head.
- Why won't you just get it?
- Seriously.
- I'm home.
- Hey.
Where's Mom?
She's trying to find out
what's going to happen with CEO Chae.
So you think CEO Chae will be released?
Alright, Manager Kim.
If you hear anything else, please call me.
Mom, what was that all about?
Why would CEO Chae be released?
I thought you said
she was going to stand trial.
The real culprit turned themselves in.
What? The real culprit came forward?
If I tell him everything now,
will Grandfather be too shocked?
Should I wait a little longer?
But I want to go back
to being myself again.
Grandfather.
It's Seo Rin.
Come in.
Secretary Kim, you're here too.
I thought you were alone, Grandfather.
Sit down. We were just talking
about your mother, actually.
My mother?
Don't you worry too much.
Your grandfather will take care
of your mother...
Then there's no need for you
to intervene, Minister.
I'll report that to the Chairman.
Wait, what did he say?
Congratulations.
CEO Chae is being released tomorrow.
Did Minister Kim pull some strings?
No, that's not it.
The real culprit
who murdered Oh Bok Gil turned himself in.
What do you mean?
But my mom is the murderer.
There's video evidence,
and they have Oh Bok Gil's phone.
What do you mean,
the real culprit confessed?
Hang on a second, Grandpa.
Baek Ho, they're saying
the real killer confessed.
You heard too, Jang Mi?
I'm at the police station right now.
I think you should come down here too.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Come on.
I'm telling you, I killed Oh Bok Gil.
I'm here to confess, so what's the holdup?
Excuse me, Detective Kim.
You...
Ssangkal?
- You punk, what are you doing?
- Hold him back.
You're the real killer?
Lawyer Kang, everyone is watching.
Please, calm down.
It's not you. Why are you lying?
- You're not the one who killed my dad.
- Darn it.
You punk...
Detective Kim.
We just got a tip. Take a look at this.
- A tip?
- Yes.
Hold on.
Darn it.
Watch where you're going!
- Are you trying to kill someone?
- I'm sorry.
I killed Oh Bok Gil. Got it?
I killed him.
I'm also the one who bought the alcohol
from that supermarket.
If you're going to commit perjury,
at least make it believable.
How much did Chae Hwa Young pay you
to perjure yourself?
Darn it.
Detective Kim, this man works
for Lee Kang Hyuk.
They're all in it together.
Chae Hwa Young...
is the one who killed my father
and framed Professor Kang Nam Bong!
Give me a break!
I said I'm the killer!
What is with all this nonsense?
Oh Bok Gil stalked and blackmailed me.
It was tough on me too.
When I saw him extorting money
from CEO Chae,
I just snapped and did it.
I was trying to take the money.
- That's a solid motive, isn't it?
- Don't be ridiculous.
Did you cook up this story
with Manager Lee?
Let go of me!
Hey...
Let go!
Unbelievable.
(Yeongseo Detention Center)
You've suffered too much.
Let's get out of here
before the reporters show up.
Right.
What took you so long?
Do you have any idea
how humiliated I was in there?
I was trying to get Ssangkal
to turn himself in,
but it looked like the Chairman
called the Minister.
So I was contemplating,
not sure what to do.
You still don't understand Chairman Ma,
do you?
It's not because he believes
I'm innocent, you know.
It's because he didn't want Seo Rin
to be the daughter of a murderer.
If we had used the Minister's influence,
he would've tied my hands...
and banned me from Dream Hotel for good,
that old geezer.
Yes, I suppose you're right.
When Chae Hwa Young gets out,
she's going to rip us apart.
What am I going to do?
I need to get on her good side
while I can.
Ma'am, did you get the tofu
for when CEO Chae is released?
Manager Lee probably already
took care of it.
Seo Rin, are you not eating
because you're worried about your mom?
Don't worry.
Manager Lee will bring her home.
Okay.
Hey, Manager Lee.
What happened with CEO Chae?
She went straight to the office
the moment she got out.
- What?
- Her priority is to rebuild the company.
Is that right?
Your mother is
always so worried about the company.
Well, there's a reason she's the CEO.
(CEO Chae Hwa Young)
Welcome, Oh Jang Mi. You evil witch.
You knew it was me?
Of course.
Did you think I didn't know
you posed as Seo Rin and betrayed me?
Chae Hwa Young, it takes a lot of nerve
to crawl out here with that face.
As if framing Professor Kang Nam Bong
for your crime wasn't enough,
now you're pinning it on Ssangkal, too?
Do you think you can keep
burying your crimes forever?
(The First Man)
Were you just using me this whole time?
Please, just hear me out.
I sincerely regret ever meeting you.
Hong Ju, I'm ruined.
You invested in crypto?
I lost everything.
I can't take this anymore! Seriously!
Hello, CEO Chae.
You know Mr. Noh Cheol Bong?
Ssangkal?
I was told that if you didn't pay up,
I should go find a woman named Oh Jang Mi.
Ssangkal's girlfriend was here.
Find her, now.
Oh Jang Mi?
He must have given you something
when he told you to find me.
What was it?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)